(upbeat music)
(suspenseful music)
- Come on.
- Relax, he'll be here.
Let's go.
Take a left.
Okay, stop here.
All right, let's go.
(tires screeching)
So how long you been working with Danny?
- Eight or nine months.
- And they put you on this job?
You've come a long way,
eight or nine months.
Must be connected.
- What you looking for?
- He's nervous.
First hit, right?
- So?
- What a way to make your bones.
Whacking off Joey Gallo.
(horn honking)
(camera clicking)
(upbeat asian music)
(people chattering)
(women laughing)
(camera clicking)
- Take a right, then you go straight,
and then you hang a left.
- Looking for me?
- What are you talking about?
- You know what I'm talking about.
You're in half the film I shot today.
You want your picture taken?
Make an appointment with
me, I do this for a living.
- Stevie Collura, how you doing?
- Do I know you?
- I'm a friend of Vinnie's.
- My brother?
- Yeah.
- Who are you?
Oh.
Dominic Cellini, you're
from the neighborhood here.
What's the deal?
- Look, I want to talk
to you about something.
I'll buy you a beer.
- Nah, I got prints drying.
I got to get home.
- What if I walk with you?
It's important.
- Vinnie, he sent you to
check up on me, right?
- Hey, he's a little worried,
you living in Greenwich village.
The hippies, just back from 'Nam.
He thought maybe you brought
back some bad habits.
- Wrong.
If Vinnie thought though that,
he'd come down here
himself and kick my butt.
What do you want?
- I want you.
I know about 'Nam.
We've got guys in narcotics
haven't made as many busts
in their whole careers
as you made in one year in 'Nam.
- You want me to be a narc? Forget it.
- No.
My beat's to find New York mob families.
Gambino, Colombo, Sciacca,
Lucchese and Genovese.
- It's a lot of families.
Must cost you a fortune in birthday cards.
- We don't communicate that much.
That's why I'm talking to you.
- You want me to do it for you?
- Yeah. We need somebody inside.
Someone Italian who
grew up in the streets,
knows how to handle himself.
What do you say?
- You think you got me figured, huh?
- You were me 20 years ago.
- Oh, yeah?
I guess I don't have much
to look forward to, huh?
- Not if you stick with this gig.
Come on, Collura, I know you.
You like to see how close
to the edge you can get
without falling off.
Ain't any edges steeper than this.
We got a deal?
- No.
- Whatever.
When you get tired of
asking babies to smile,
give me a call.
(door opens)
(door closes)
- You call Ma lately?
- Couple a days ago, she seems okay.
- You should visit.
Hey, she misses you.
- I'll see her on Sunday.
Busy, huh?
- Oh yeah.
Lunchtime's been great.
Benny, don't forget, breadsticks.
- Hey, I ran into a friend
of yours a couple days ago,
Dom Cellini.
- Dom? Oh yeah.
- He's a cop, right?
- Oh, big time.
- Kind of big time.
He straight arrows,
he's lining his pockets.
- Hey, hey, what's up?
You in some kind of trouble?
- No, I just couldn't get fix on him,
that's all.
- Huh, that's Cellini.
You never know what that pizon's thinking.
I mean, he has more fun than the bad guys.
You should hear the stories he
tells, the things he's done.
Guy's like a celebrity.
I mean, wherever he goes,
restaurants, clubs, the garden,
they treat them like a VIP
and you don't have to shmear nobody.
- Come on.
A cop with that kind of juice?
He's honest. What's the deal?
- People want to be his friend, you know?
They want to hear his stories,
makes 'em feel like
they're part of things.
I wouldn't want it, but I
guess it's an exciting life
if you don't mind taking chances.
First thing, I think you
got to be a little crazy.
- Yeah. Sounded like it.
(suspenseful music)
- [Inspector] And faithfully
discharge the duties
of a police officer
in the New York City Police Department.
- And faithfully discharge
the duties of a police officer
of the New York City Police Department.
- To the best of my ability.
- Collura, welcome to the force.
- Thank you, sir.
- Detective Cellini.
- Inspector.
Take a good look, kid.
That's the last you're
gonna see of it for a while.
- So that's it, I'm a cop?
- New York's finest, but nobody knows
except Akers, me and you.
Second thoughts? Cold feet?
- No, I'm fine.
What about the rest of
the guys in your unit?
- Even your paycheck comes out
of a photo supply company in Jersey,
deposit it straight into your bank.
Any more questions?
- Yeah. What made you so sure about me?
- Just a feeling.
- Yeah.
I'm you 20 years ago.
(people chattering)
(sirens wailing)
- Beautiful girl lying in the car.
The guy says to the
undertaker, "What she die of?"
"The clap," the undertaker says.
"Get out of here, nobody
dies from the clap."
"Oh yeah," says the undertaker.
"You do when you give it to Fat Tony."
(guys laughing)
Yo, Stevie.
- Hey.
- Long time, how you doing?
- All right.
Old pal from the
neighborhood, Stevie Collura.
We grew up together.
So what's with the camera?
You look like a tourist.
You still live in Brooklyn?
- No, no, I moved out.
My old man died when I was overseas.
- Yeah, I heard. Sorry.
- Thanks. Hey, I got a
place in West Village.
I'm a photographer now.
- Get out of here!
Come, I'll buy you a cup.
So you was in Vietnam, huh?
I would have got in the
army, but I got flat feet.
How was it?
- I made it home, you know? Surprised me.
- You know, I gotta get me one of these.
It's great.
So you making a dollar?
- I am, just made a lot of money
shooting weddings and baby pictures.
- Baby pictures?
You do christenings?
- Yeah, sure.
- I got this idea, it
might do us both some good.
You free Sunday?
- Yeah.
- Okay, man, you're working.
(people chattering)
Remember what I said, careful
where you point that thing.
A lot of people in here
can get real touchy.
- I know, I only take pictures
of the women and the new kid.
- Right, then I want you to
make up a nice picture book
for Scimone and his wife, okay?
And send me the bill.
It's Scimone's first grandchild.
We're gonna make some points here.
It's cool. He's with me.
Mr. Scimone knows all about it.
- Yeah. Okay.
- He's the photographer, okay?
- Hold him up, hold him up.
Hold him up, yeah.
That's good.
Gonna sneak around over here.
(whistles)
(camera clicking)
Okay.
(people chattering)
(camera clicking)
I think we should try
and uh, switch sides.
- He's a good kid, he
just got out of the army.
I like the way he handles himself.
- Yeah? You trust him.
- He's from the neighborhood.
I grew up with him.
I think he could use a few bucks.
He's war hero, Paulie,
he's having a hard time.
- All right. Give him a try.
Go 'head.
- Okay. That's real nice.
Yeah. Thank you.
(soft music)
(camera clicking)
That's a nice smile.
- Steve.
- Huh?
Oh yeah, um.
Excuse me, all right? I'll be right back.
Yeah?
- Stevie, this is my boss, Paul Raggio.
- Stevie, I heard some good things.
See you around?
- He likes you.
- He likes me?
He looks like he wants to whack me.
- When he wants to whack you,
he'll look like he loves you.
So you getting some good pictures?
- Yeah, I think so.
- What's you do?
- I'm just taking out the strobe,
you know, it's gotta recharge.
- Danny.
- Business, okay, get yourself a drink.
I'll be right back.
(camera clicking)
- You know what you got here?
You know who this guy is?
- Yeah. It's Carmine
Persico, Colombo family.
Danny introduced me to him.
- I mean the other guy, huh?
- No.
- Judge Francis X Herbert,
New York Supreme Court, that's who.
This here, Judge Maslow,
Appellates Division.
You know about him.
- Yeah, Danny said there's a
lot of political heavies there,
you know, guys on the tape
paying their respects.
- Oh no, what's his name?
Dunbar.
Guy's a precinct captain in the Bronx.
Damn.
The inspector's gonna blow
his stack when he sees this.
- Oh, sorry about that.
- Hey, it's not your fault.
You did good.
This stuff is gold.
- Piece of cake.
- Stevie, this isn't a piece of cake.
You took a major risk doing this.
Don't do it again.
You get cocky in this business,
you don't get old, understand?
- Oh, oh.
Pretty girl.
Who is she?
- I didn't get a chance to find out.
- Good. You ain't there to socialize.
An undercover cop can't afford to.
- Look, would you relax Cellini?
Come on, I'm in.
In like Flynn, Danny says,
I'm making the rounds with him tomorrow.
- Just take it slow. Okay?
- Careful.
- Take it slow.
- Who is she?
- Her?
It's Maria, forget about her.
She's out of your league.
Nice, you done good, kid.
Lou is gonna like these.
Come on, Ben. Where the hell are you?
- What's his problem?
- He owe us two months.
That mamaluke thinks he's dealing
with First National Bank here.
- So what, we break his legs?
- It's not like the movies, Stevie,
you don't break a guy's leg
because he owes you money.
If he's in the hospital,
how's he gonna work?
How's he gonna pay you?
No, you just lean on him.
Make him think next time
he don't pay his bills,
you break his stupid neck.
Ah, here we go.
You stay here, keep an eye out.
Hey Benny, where the hell's my money?
(Benny grunting)
"You do when you give it to Fat Tony."
- Oh-ho.
- What's going on?
(man speaking faintly)
Don's here.
- Gambino?
- Yeah, just do what I do, okay?
(suspenseful music)
- I feel like I'm in church.
- Shh.
- Hey Paulie, remember Stevie?
- Yeah.
- He went out with me today.
- Yeah, how'd it go?
- Great. He's a natural.
- That's good.
(guys laughing)
- Not bad for the first day, huh?
- It was a piece of cake.
- Yeah, piece of cake, huh?
Come on.
- Come on where?
- Calzone, you're buying.
- Code yellow. Identify.
- Zero two zero, I got
a message for Amber.
Message is code one, need a face-to-face.
Location five, 2300 hours, back please.
- [Operator] Code one, face-to-face,
2300 hours, location five.
Clear?
- Huh? Yeah. Yeah. Clear.
Yeah. Yeah. Her name is Maria.
Yeah. Her name's Maria.
Maria. You know, Maria
like the song, you know?
Yeah. I met her at this christening.
She's incredible.
Maria. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I didn't meet her.
You see, she was holding the baby
and I was taking the pictures.
I didn't want to come on to her
like the rest of them mooks, you know?
But uh...
Hey, hey!
She's here, she's standing right here.
Right in front of me.
Maria, right?
Say hello to my mother.
Say hello!
(Maria laughing)
- It's a dial tone.
- Yeah, she must have passed out.
You see, I never called home
about a girl I met before, you know?
- Very funny.
- Yeah. Yeah.
It's a good way to break the ice,
that and a blow torch.
I'm Steve. Steve Collura, and you are?
- In a hurry.
- Maria in a hurry.
Hey, don't worry, my mom
will love you anyway.
- What is it you want?
- A house in New Rochelle,
three sons, a daughter,
and a cup of coffee.
What do you say?
- Why should I have coffee with you?
Just because you took my picture.
- No, um.
Because I gave it to you.
(soft music)
So how 'bout it?
- I'm paying for myself.
- Fine.
If it makes you feel better
you can pay for me too.
Look, it's easy for people
at home to talk about the war
like it was history or something.
You know what I mean?
Like politically right and morally wrong.
But I was there.
I was in the middle of it.
Guys were dying all around me.
My friends were losing their lives and...
This is a really good conversation
for us to be having on our first meeting.
It's really classy.
- No, it's okay.
I mean, it's certainly more interesting
than the usual things I hear from guys.
- Well anyway, I want to know about you.
- Why?
I mean, I haven't done nearly
the fascinating things you have.
- Maybe.
But I want to know about
the fascinating things
that are going on inside of you.
- What do you mean?
- Eyes.
People say people see a lot
of things with their mouths,
but the eyes tell the truth.
I like what I'm hearing,
I'd like to hear more.
What are you doing?
- I think I've said enough for one day.
- Oh-ho-ho.
You're weird, you know that?
Maria, whatever your last name is.
- Maria Caprefoli.
- Now my mother is gonna be thrilled.
- Oh, come on.
I'm sure you know a lot
of other Italian girls.
- Not like you.
- I have to go.
- That's it?
We don't see each other again?
- Wednesday afternoons I work
at Saint Genesius Church in Brooklyn.
- Wait, hey, wait a second.
Are you gonna be a nun?
- No. I work with the children there.
- Thank you, Lord.
- All right, listen. I want
you to handle this one.
Remember what I told you.
- Guys name is Larner?
- Lerner
- Lerner.
- Right. Watch him.
Thinks he's a tough guy.
- Yeah, it's a piece of cake.
- Didn't figure on this, did ya you punks?
I was waiting for you.
- Look, Lerner.
- Shut your face!
You'll tell that Gambino scum bucket
that Barney Lerner
don't pay no protection.
You understand?
- I don't think that's such
a good idea, Mr. Lerner.
I also don't think you should
be insulting Mr. Gambino.
- What? Heh.
I'm the one holding the gun
and you're telling me what to do?
- You're not gonna shoot me, buddy.
If you do, you're gonna go to jail
or you're gonna end up in a Jersey swamp.
Now what's the percentage in that?
Why don't you just put the gun down?
- I'll put it down.
I'll put it down your throat
and blow your ass off!
- With the safety on?
Now, I've got the cylinder.
It's not gonna fire.
Use your head. Let it go.
And nobody gets hurt.
- No, I let it go, you'll kill me.
- Nobody's gonna kill you.
What's the point of that?
You're a valuable customer.
Let the gun go and I promise you, hey!
I promise you I won't hurt ya.
Okay. Have it your way.
- Ah!
- Danny, hey, I'm handling this, okay?
All right.
I'm gonna take your first
month's installment.
No more, no less.
All right.
- Let me pop him one, Stevie, just once.
- Danny, I promised Mr. Lerner
that nobody was gonna hurt him
and I keep my promise.
- Hurt me?
You broke my finger.
Come on. It's not broken.
It's just dislocated.
Let me see it.
Let me see it!
- Ah!
- Yeah, see?
Try to bend it.
Go ahead.
It's good as new.
Now you have a nice day
and we'll see you in a month, all right?
(engine rumbling)
- So what's the problem?
- I had to hurt somebody today.
- Yeah?
Pain builds character.
- Yeah, well, I still don't like it.
What if they ask me to whack somebody?
- Call me.
- What you gonna do, give me a note?
- If we have to, we'll pull you out.
Don't worry.
We don't leave our people hanging.
- Pain builds character.
It's a good thing you're
not a doctor, Cellini.
- What's that?
- It's $300.
Ma, would you buy yourself a dishwasher?
- I got a dishwasher.
I also got a telephone.
Some people don't know how to use it.
Where'd you get $300?
- Taking pictures.
- Of who? That bum Danny?
- Ma, what is that supposed to mean?
- Oh, I hear what's going, you know?
People talk.
Is that why you risked
your life in Vietnam?
So you could come home and be a punk.
- Ma, I made this money legit.
I'm a successful photographer.
Look, Ma,
I met a girl.
She's Italian.
- So I know the family?
- I don't even know her family yet.
- When do I meet her?
- I'm working on it.
- [Priest] Come on, come
on, come, on all right.
- Excuse me, Father.
(church bells ringing)
- Yes son, can I help you?
- Good day, Father.
Maria Caprefoli, is this where she works?
- Yes, but she's not here.
- Well, she said Wednesday.
- Maria had to leave early, Are you Steve?
- Yeah.
- She left this for you.
She thought you might come.
Her phone number.
Why don't we walk, hmm?
You see, I have known Maria
since she came to this country.
Did you know she was born in Italy?
- No, she didn't mention it.
- Well, there are many
things that is awkward
for her to talk about.
And please don't think that
I'm trying to interfere
but sometimes it helps to know things
for us to make intelligent decisions.
- Yeah, sure. Is there a problem?
- Well that you will have to decide.
Maria came to America after
her own parents were killed.
Since then she has lived
here with her godparents.
- See, I didn't know that either.
I guess there's a lot I
got to learn about her.
- Yeah son, I think perhaps the
most important thing to know
before you call her,
is that her godfather,
who was like a real father to her,
his name is not Caprefoli.
His name is Carlo Gambino.
We cannot choose our families.
I hope in time Maria
will choose her own life.
Yes.
So if you should decide not to call,
she will understand.
(soft music)
- Hey, hey, what are you doing?
- Just checking they ain't wired.
- Hey, those cost me 10 bucks.
- You ain't worried, are you?
Have a nice evening.
- Lovely flowers.
- You should have seen 'em
before they were stripped searched.
- Can you put these in some water for me?
- Yeah, sure.
See yas later.
But not too much later.
(soft Italian music)
- Thank you, gentleman.
- Hey, I'm over here.
- I'm just not used to
double dating with three guys
and one girl.
- Really?
Didn't realize you were so old fashioned.
I know, it's a bit of a drag.
But that's just my family.
- Hey, at least we don't have to worry
about getting mugged, right?
- So you haven't mentioned,
how's the photography going?
- Fine.
I got nothing a couple
of weddings won't fix.
- But you're sticking with it?
- Yeah. Hey, what else
is there for me to do?
- Well, you could always go to
work for the Gambino family.
You didn't think that I would find out?
- I didn't know you were a part of this.
- I'm not.
I'm just the goddaughter,
but when Poppy hears I'm going on a date
he wants to know who with
and people check around.
- Does it bother you?
- What you do for a
living is your business.
That you didn't tell me, yes.
- I didn't know who you were at first,
not until I talked to Father Anselmo.
I didn't want you to thinking
that I was trying to
get ahead through you.
Can you believe me?
- Those two still up front?
- Yeah.
Why?
- I think we should ditch 'em.
- What?
- Give me your car keys.
- You think these guys get a thrill
out of watching us eat spaghetti?
If you want to be tailed,
talk to Don Carlo about that.
Don't take it out on these two chumps.
Okay, I guess you want
me to take you home now.
- No.
I believe you.
- You believe what?
- That you didn't ask me out
just to help your career.
(soft music)
- Thank you.
- Salute.
- Yeah, salute.
(Maria laughing)
- Thanks, for not letting me be a brat.
(both laughing)
I had a really good time.
- Me too.
Maybe we can do it again sometime.
Just the four of us.
(Maria laughing)
- I'd love to.
Goodnight.
(car engine starting)
(man coughing)
- Don Carlo.
Colombo's going ahead with
the Italian American rally
in spite of your wishes.
What shall we do?
- Nothing for now.
- About the Collura kid.
I had a man break into
his apartment yesterday.
- So?
- Nothing, but he's got this book, this
album full of pictures of Maria.
- What else?
- I checked with friends downtown,
he's not on any police payroll.
I think he's legit Don Carlo.
I also think he's in love.
(soft music)
- Are you upset?
- No.
- I'm feeling these feelings
and I don't want to mess up.
- You won't.
- I've never been with
a woman like you before.
- It's never been like this for me either.
- What you saying, that
we're meant for each other?
- I think it's time you
should meet my family.
(soft music)
Poppy wants you to come to dinner Sunday.
- With me? Dinner with Carlo Gambino?
- Well, just think of him as my father.
- Oh, that's supposed
to make me feel relaxed?
What if he doesn't like me?
- Well, I did go out with this one guy
Poppy didn't care for,
but nobody's seen him around
for a long, long time.
(Stevie laughing)
(soft music)
Poppy, Mammy.
This is Steve Collura.
Steve, this is my family,
Carlo and Kathryn Gambino.
- A pleasure to meet you, Steve.
- Pleased to meet you, Mrs. Gambino.
- Collura. That's Italiano, no?
- My dad was from Sicily, Palermo.
- Then you are from Palermo.
- [Paul] Don Carlo.
- Uncle Paul, this is my
friend, Steve Collura.
This is my uncle Paul Castellano.
- I think you're gonna want to see this.
- Today, the Italian
American Civil Rights League
picketed the New York offices of the FBI
and to understand why,
we have with us the founder
of the Civil Rights League,
Joseph Colombo.
Mr. Colombo, how could a
man reputed to be the head
of a mafia family complain
of unfair media treatment-
- Will you look at this guy?
- You know, that's exactly
what I'm talking about.
I mean, mafia, mafia.
Well, where the hell is this mafia?
I mean, books, movies, TV.
There ain't no mafia and I
ain't no head of no family
except my wife and kids.
- What's wrong with him?
- I'm a real estate
salesman is what I am.
- Don Carlo, this is
too much attention here.
This guy is gonna
destroy us with all this.
This is suicide here, Don
Carlo, we gotta do something.
(Carlo speaking in Italian)
- [Joseph] I'm a real estate
salesman is what I am.
And I ain't just concerned about myself-
- This guy is no problem.
Who's gonna watch this cafone anyway?
Put something else on.
- [Joseph] You know, my parents
were great, proud Americans.
(channels changing)
- I'm sorry, Maria.
Steve, come with me, I want
to show you my flowers.
Come on.
Back in Sicily, Maria's mother and father
were my good friends.
I held her in her baptism
when she was a little baby.
She was beautiful.
And then,
her mother and her father
were killed in Veneto.
Maria was left all alone.
So I brought it to this country.
I wanted her to grow up in peace.
I have many godchildren.
They live here.
But Maria,
she lives here.
Hmm.
A lot of young men are after Maria.
And why not?
She's beautiful.
She's intelligent.
She's well-connected.
She's a good catch for
somebody like you, huh?
- If that's what you think
I'll quit working for you
right now and go back to taking pictures.
- No, that's not what I mean.
Maria is gonna have to share you with me
because I got two families
and you've got a place
and a future in both.
- And I pledge my loyalty to both.
- Loyalty.
- My father used to say without loyalty,
we are like the animals.
- You're father was right.
And now you got a family
that's loyal to you.
And that loyalty is more
important than your own life.
(suspenseful music)
- It doesn't make sense.
Two months ago, you're
a part-time soldier.
Now you're chauffeuring the Capo's?
Having heart to hearts with Gambino?
Something's wrong.
- I don't understand you.
You bring me in because
you think I can do a job.
I do the job.
Then you give me a hard time.
- I'm responsible for your safety.
Maybe I should pull you out.
- Out of the family? You can't do that.
- Oh, why not?
There's something you're not telling me?
- Like what?
- I don't know.
It's getting too risky.
- But that's why you brought me in.
I'm the guy that likes
to live on the edge.
Look, you need me and I need this.
- Mm-hmm.
So, I got myself an adrenaline junkie.
- Yeah, you gonna leave me there?
- Joey Gallo gets out
of the joint tomorrow
and some people are gonna get dead.
We need all the help we can get.
That's the only reason
I'm leaving you in there.
- So I run into Joey
Gallo, I should thank him?
- You run into crazy Joey, keep running.
You don't want to know
how he earned that name.
Trust me, Stevie,
there's gonna be blood on the streets.
I just don't want any of it to be yours.
(door opens)
- Don Carlo, Joey Gallo has
come to pay his respects.
- Don Carlo.
Thank you for seeing me.
- Joey Gallo, Joey.
(speaking in Italian)
It's been too long.
- Eight years hard time.
(speaking in Italian)
Deaf and dumb.
I didn't rat nobody out.
- As you have sworn, so you did.
- A lot of people swore a lot of things.
Like Joey Colombo, he swore
that he was gonna protect
my operation until I got
out and what does he do?
Steals from me.
Rapes me.
(Carlo laughing)
- So what do we do, Joey?
Do you want to appeal to him?
- Appeal to him?
Beg him for what's already mine?
The guy's a bug!
He's belong son all fours
in front of me, begging me.
Me beg him?
"I hate victims who respect
their executioners."
Sartre wrote that.
Eight years, Don Carlo.
A lot of time to read.
A lot of time to figure
out who's screwed you.
- So Joey, you're not the only one.
All of us are threatened
by Colombo's speeches.
- Don Carlo,
maybe it's time that Colombo
stops making these speeches.
(projector whirring)
- Now, this is Dino
D'Tosti in from Boston.
He's currently under a federal indictment
for labor racketeering.
Hey Dom, how are you doing?
- These the photos from last night?
- Yeah.
It's supposed to be a
wedding party over in Bayonne
but we got Capo's here from all over.
Okay, Jack.
Chickee Bavonne.
Two weeks out out of Leavenworth.
- [Dom] What happened to his hair?
- Well, word is he lost
his toupee in the joint
in a crap game.
(Dom laughing)
Okay.
Now this is Gambino's
goddaughter, Maria Caprefoli.
Does anybody recognize the guy she's with?
No, new one on me.
- It just slipped your mind
you've been dating the boss's
daughter for three months?
- It's got nothing to do with us.
Strictly personal.
- Personal? You're a cop!
- Yeah and a damn good one too.
I'm getting stuff
nobody's ever got before,
not even you.
- Stevie, what are you thinking?
Gambino's gonna let you
walk away with his princess?
One day, you're gonna be
strolling down the aisle,
wearing a tuxedo?
The only tuxedo you're gonna
be wearing is in a pine box!
- Don't worry about it, all right?
We'll find a way out.
- I remember that song.
That's from West Side Story.
This ain't a musical, Stevie!
When you get a knife in the gut,
you don't come out for curtain call.
- That would make you happy, wouldn't it?
Prove you were right, huh?
- I don't need to prove nothing.
I've been there and I know
you can't keep this stuff separate.
- Maybe you can't, but I can.
I promised you I do you
a job and I'm doing it.
I can promise you my life.
(birds chirping)
- Mm.
Where are we?
Iowa?
- Hmm. Connecticut.
- It's beautiful.
- Yeah, the scenery's not bad either.
(soft music)
- Mm.
(Maria laughing)
(soft music)
(Maria screaming and laughing)
- Come on!
- Let me up!
This is a long way to go for a walk.
Haven't you ever heard of Central Park?
- Well, I wanted you to know there's more
to life than the city.
We could live out here someday.
- In the country?
- Yeah.
Out west.
We can have a ranch.
- A ranch?
What would you do on a ranch?
What would I do on a ranch?
- Hey, what's the matter?
I would find something.
Right?
As long as we're together, right?
- What is it?
It's the job, right?
So be a photographer.
Are you afraid Poppy wouldn't approve?
Don't you know that whatever
makes me happy makes him happy?
- He'll still be there.
We can never get away.
- Why would we want to?
Poppy saved my life, I can't leave.
And there is loyalty and I
know you feel the same way
because he told me what you said.
Maybe you're just getting cold feet
and you want to go west without me.
- Don't even joke.
I don't want any life without you.
(soft music)
- Park the car, then come inside.
Don Carlo wants you in the meeting.
- Me?
Wait, something the
matter, Mr. Castellano?
- Relax kid, it's a big honor.
- Yeah. What am I supposed to do?
- Keep your ears open and your mouth shut.
- So gentlemen, like I was saying,
we told the cops we ain't
having nothing to do
with Joey Colombo's Italian
American civil rights stuff.
And Don Carlo, I put the word out.
No businesses are closed
for Colombo's rally.
(Carlo speaking Italian)
(all speaking Italian)
- Stevie.
Come here.
Sit down.
So, you listen?
Good.
And what do the young
men on the street say?
- Don't Carlo, it's not my place.
- I'm asking you so it is your place.
- Mostly the Joe Colombo thing
and all the noise he's making.
Plus with Joey Gallo back
in town, everybody's tense.
- You know, this Joe Columbo,
Italian American Day.
It's awkward for me.
I disapprove so I can't be there.
So I wanna ask you,
could you go there?
And you'll be my eyes and my ears,
would you do me that favor?
- Don Carlo, absolutely.
- Good.
And then you come back and we talk.
All right?
And how are things with you?
- Great.
I'm learning a lot.
- And with you and Maria?
- It's terrific.
I'd, uh,
with your permission, Don Carlo,
I'd like you to meet my family.
- Sure.
- Thank you, Don Carlo.
- Thanks.
- My wife and I would like to know
what's a beautiful girl like you
doing with a bum like him, huh?
Oh, I know, he promised
to to take your picture,
make you a big movie star, huh?
- I'm not an actress.
I'm starting to be a teacher.
- Yeah, smart guy.
Special education at NYU.
She works with the kids at Saint Genesius.
- That's nice.
And you grew up in Brooklyn?
- Yes, but I was born in Italy.
- You're first generation.
I'm first generation also.
Steven here is second generation.
Aren't you, Steven?
- Steven?
- Your folks still live in Brooklyn?
- Well, actually my parents
died when I was very young
and I was raised by my godparents.
- Oh.
I knew some Caprefolis over in Queens.
Very nice people.
- My godparents are
Kathryn and Carlo Gambino.
(Maria sighing)
- All right, before you say anything-
- Look, Steve, I can make
this real easy for you.
- I don't want easy.
- No, good?
Then the hell with what
your family thinks.
All that matters is us.
- Yeah, that's right.
I'll tell 'em that
- But be sure to tell them
that we'd love to have
them at our wedding.
(soft music)
You do want to marry me, don't you?
(car honking)
(tires screech)
- Yeah. Yeah. The Columbus Circle thing.
He wants me to be his eyes and his ears.
Damn, it's Paul Raggio, he see's me.
I'll call you later.
- Hey Petey, is Maria there?
Ah, just tell her I called.
Hey, Raggio, how you doing?
- Collura, you live
around here, don't you?
- Yeah. Right there.
- Your phone out of order?
- No. Why?
- Oh yeah. I see what you mean.
No, I just didn't want to
take a chance it was bugged.
- Who the hell's gonna bug you?
- I'm just trying to learn from you guys.
You know? Doing the smart thing.
- Yeah?
- So who you calling that you
don't want the FBI to hear?
- Maria Caprefoli.
- You didn't talk long.
- She wasn't home.
I'll call her later.
- Yeah, you do that.
Petey?
- Yo.
- You on the phones tonight?
- Yep.
- Anybody call the last hour?
- [Petey] Steve Collura called for Maria
about half hour ago.
She wasn't here.
Any problem?
- No, no problem.
- [Reporter] Again, this
late breaking story.
Joseph Colombo, reputed head
of the Colombo crime family,
and leader of the Italian
American Civil Rights League
was shot this afternoon
at the Unity Day rally
in Columbus Circle.
First reports indicate that
his assassin was killed-
- It's okay, he's one of ours.
- At the scene
by unknown parties.
Colombo's condition is listed as critical.
- You heard?
- What did you see?
- Everything.
They're just getting ready
to start, Colombo's, uh,
he's talking to people,
he's shaking hands.
This black guy's following him around
taking pictures for about 10 minutes.
All of a sudden he drops his camera
and he pulls out his piece, pop, pop, pop.
Puts three into Colombo's head.
- And the one with the gun?
- Oh, he's dead.
Somebody whacked him out right away.
I couldn't see who.
- It was crazy.
There was people running around screaming.
Why some black guy want
to hit Joe Colombo?
- We heard he was in the
joint with Joey Gallo.
- Well, Colombo ain't dead,
he's gonna be a vegetable.
- And maybe somebody should
plant him in a garden.
- Steve,
you've done very well.
(speaking Italian)
- Thank you, Don Carlo.
(soft music)
- And now we have a special dedication
for Mr and Mrs. Steve Collura.
(soft music)
- You did that?
- It's how we registered.
You should have seen how
badly your hand shook
when you signed us in.
- Oh, like you're not nervous
about spending the night?
- We're engaged and anyway
it's time I knew if you snored.
(laughing)
- Does Don Carlo know where you are?
- Yes.
- He must trust you a lot.
- Me, a little. You, completely.
- He said that?
- Don't you know how
much he cares for you?
Does that bother you?
- No. I just don't ever
want to let him down.
- Why would you?
Hmm?
Mrs. Collura would like to dance.
(door creaks)
(sexy sax music)
- I'm sorry.
I can't.
- It's okay, it's okay.
You want to wait till we're
married? I understand.
- No.
It's not the reason.
- Is it me?
- Do you remember our first date?
And I told you that I knew
you working for the family
but that it was okay
and that I didn't care what you did
as long as you were being honest with me?
- Yeah.
- Well I wasn't being honest with you.
Because now I'm looking
at the rest of my life
and what you do.
It does matter.
It does.
- Look, I have a
confession to make to you.
I haven't been completely honest with you.
- What is it?
- It's a business, a family business.
It's not something I intend to do forever.
- Do you mean that?
- Yeah, I've been
thinking about for awhile.
It's just, I wasn't sure
how you feel about it.
(soft music)
And maybe we should
wait till we're married.
I kind of like the idea
of marrying a virgin.
(Maria laughing)
- Absolutely not, Cellini.
You are not pulling him
out and that is an order.
- Inspector, he's engaged
to Gambino's goddaughter.
He's my undercover
and I got to read about in the damn paper.
- So what? You didn't
get invited to the party?
We have never had anybody
this close to the top.
He has given us gold, Cellini, gold.
- The dumb bastard's
gonna get himself killed.
- He's a cop isn't he?
He knows the risks.
Besides, you told me yourself.
He likes to play it right to the edge.
- Yeah, but this time he's gone over
and I'm the one who's gotta get him out.
- Fine, but not yet.
- They say Gallo's got
a lion in a basement
over on President Street.
- A lion? You're joking.
A lion, lion?
- I'm serious.
Two of Colombo's guys,
Danny Otto and Phil Toria went missing.
The rumor is that they
got a one way ticket
to the Gallo zoo.
- So Joey's not being a nice boy?
(laughing)
Anything else?
- Yeah, not good.
The Lucchese family got
a tip from city hall,
NYPD has slipped a cop
into one of the families.
- Which family?
- We don't know.
Yet.
(dramatic music)
- All right.
New business.
(people chattering)
- Your tight little
ship has sprung a leak,
they know about me.
- Relax. They don't want to squat.
How they gonna?
(door chimes ringing)
What?
- It's Cosentino.
- You know he made a mess.
Did you ever see him eat with chopsticks?
- They never eat here.
- Well, they're eating here now.
Got any ideas?
If they see us, you just tell
them that you're my brother.
- Mm-hmm. Problem.
I'm about to cast my lines.
- I mean, what are we gonna do?
- Here you go.
(Stevie clears throat)
- Okay.
(men chattering)
- Where'd you go?
- Made a phone call.
We've got about 60 seconds.
You gonna eat that shrimp?
Hey, did you hear Joey
Gallo got married yesterday?
I would pay money to hear him
say "Till death do us part."
- Did you check out that lion story?
- Mm-hmm.
The basement on President Street.
- And what are you doing about it?
- What? Call the ASPCA?
From when I hear, it ain't starving.
(door chimes ringing)
- All right, people.
I want you to grab your belongings.
- I called the bomb squad.
First chance you get, out the back.
Keep your head down and
hit the streets running.
(sirens wailing)
- [Officer] Come on, let's go sir, please.
- Hey, Collura!
Wasn't that Steve Collura?
- I don't know. It kind
of looked like him.
Come on, let's go.
Cellini?
What are you doing here?
You working the bomb squad now?
- Nah, I clean up after
the mounted police.
So don't stay too long, eh?
I don't want to sweep yous away.
- What's he doing here?
- That's a good question.
(soft music)
- Maria, hey, it's me.
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
It's after midnight.
- Um, I came by after class to wait.
I guess I fell asleep.
I thought you'd be home earlier.
- Yeah, me too.
Work.
- Oh.
- What's the matter?
- I just remembered a dream I had.
- Yeah, what?
Maria, what is it?
- You haven't change your mind, have you?
About the family business and
all the things we discussed.
- No.
I'll speak to Don Carlo this Sunday
when we go to the house for dinner.
- Good.
- Was your dream?
- It's gone.
- No, not you Marty, him.
- Where to, Mr. Castellano?
- Just move.
(engine starts)
(suspenseful music)
Let's you and me just
take a little ride, okay?
Hester Street.
- Yeah, you got it.
- You live in the village, don't you?
What, you hang out with these hippies,
these flower children?
- I don't hang out with them.
- Who do you hang out with?
(dramatic music)
Take a left.
Pull over and stop.
(dramatic music)
You hang out with Joey Gallo?
He lives in a village too.
- No, I never even met him.
- He's a crazy bastard.
Threatening war with the Colombo's,
whacking out guys without permission.
We don't do that sort of thing anymore.
And after tomorrow,
neither will Joey Gallo.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Still going to the movies?
- Nope. I got to work tonight.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah.
I want to take a picture of the two of us.
- Right now?
- Yeah.
- I'm a mess. I've been in school all day.
Can we do it this weekend?
- No.
- Why not?
- 'Cause, uh,
I need instant gratification.
- Oh yeah?
Good thing all you want is a picture.
- Come here.
- You know, you're
usually not this strange.
Strange? What's strange?
I was looking through all the
pictures that I've got of you
and there wasn't one of us together.
- You were looking
through all my pictures?
- Yeah.
- That's very sweet.
Or did forget what I look like?
- No, I didn't forget what you look like.
Now you won't either.
- Joey Gallo. You sure?
- Yeah. I'm sure.
It's tomorrow night.
- Where?
- Umbertos Clam House.
There's two cars, I'm driving back up.
- Congratulations.
- Hey, my ass is on the line here.
What do I do?
- I'll get back to you.
- It's tomorrow night.
- I said I'll get back to you.
I'll get back. Would you calm down?
All right, five minutes then you leave.
Yo, Stevie, want some fries?
Okay.
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
- Come on.
- Relax, he'll be here.
(sirens wailing)
- Heads up.
- [Man] Let's go.
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
I hope you guys haven't been waiting long.
- Take a left.
(tires screeching)
Next light make another left.
Pull into this alley up here.
Slow down.
Okay. Stop here.
Keep the engine running,
but turn your lights off.
(suspenseful music)
All right, let's go.
(tires screeching)
You're good with garbage.
So how long been working with Danny?
- Eight or nine months.
- And they put you on this job?
You've come a long way,
eight or nine months.
You must be connected.
- What you looking for?
- He's nervous.
First hit, right?
- So?
- What a way to make your bones,
whacking off Joey Gallo.
- When's he suppose to get here?
- Right after the Copa closes.
It's his birthday, he's having a party.
- Happy birthday, Joey.
(dramatic music)
It's the birthday boy.
One bodyguard, you're
getting careless, Joey.
- Hey, relax kid.
We're just back up.
If we have to go in I'll
take Joey and the kid,
you take the bodyguard and the birds.
- What?
- You're gonna hit the kid?
- What's the matter?
She remind you of your sister?
- It's just business, kid.
Nothing personal.
(suspenseful music)
- I gotta take a leak.
- What?
- I got a weak bladder.
- Make it fast.
(coin falls)
- I don't like it.
- Hmm.
- Code yellow, identity.
- Zero two zero, I need Amber.
- [Operator] Not here,
you want the message desk?
- No, no, no, I need Amber.
Where is he? He's supposed to be here.
Where's my backup?
I'm here all by myself.
- Hold on. I'll try and find him.
- I can't hold on, you're
supposed to be here.
Where is everybody?
This thing's going down any minute now.
- Hold on.
- I don't like it, go get him.
- Zero two zero.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I can't locate Amber.
I'll give him your message.
- Come on.
Come on, come on, let's go, eh?
- Next time, piss your pants.
(suspenseful music)
Start the car, kid.
(engine starts)
What you looking for?
You know something we don't?
- Huh?
(gun firing)
Move it kid, move it!
(gun fires)
Come on, kid!
Get going, come on!
(girl screaming)
- Move it, hit it!
(tires screeching)
(gun firing)
(sirens wailing)
It's Joey Gallo.
Bodyguard was also hit and he's
on the way to the hospital.
- Anybody else?
- No, nobody else.
- All right.
Anything?
- Not since the panic call.
You want me to make some fresh?
- Please.
It's gonna be a long night.
- Morning.
- Uncle Paul, is Poppy up yet?
- No, Don's still asleep.
We're waiting for him.
- Uncle Paul, do you know where Steve is?
He was supposed to call me this morning.
- No, no, I don't, I
don't know where he is.
- You know how it is, a guy
gets tied up in the job.
Don't worry, he'll show up.
(dramatic music)
- It's terrible, terrible.
I, for one, am shocked.
- He's dead.
- We don't know that.
- It's been over four hours.
- He'll call, I'm sure he will.
- He's dead.
(dramatic music)
- How 'bout the East River?
(somber music)
- How did this happen?
And how am I gonna tell Maria?
- We're not sure, Don
Carlo, but it looks bad.
- You can't find him.
- He dropped the button
men off in Brooklyn
and took off.
- All right, you find him.
No harm is to come to him until I'm sure.
You understand?
- Si, Don Carlo, I understand.
- Dom, we've been at this for 48 hours.
Nothing, nadda, zilch.
Look, if he's been whacked,
maybe it ain't Gambino.
What if some of Gallo's
boys saw him at the hit?
- Right.
Larry, get your butt over to Gallo's place
on President Street, code three.
Find out if that lions been fed lately.
All right, the rest of
you, gloves are off.
Stop Foley and the wise guys.
Somebody's got to know something.
(suspenseful music)
- Where's Maria, is she coming?
- No.
- I sent Raggio over to Charles Street,
to the kid's apartment.
The place is swarming with cops.
- That's proves nothing.
- Don Carlo, the cops are
turning the town inside out.
They're dragging our guys off the street.
You know, as well as me,
they only look this hard
for one of their own.
- I ain't saying nothing
until I see my lawyer.
(suspenseful music)
- Jack, Larry, will you excuse us?
Mr Raggio and me are
gonna have a little chat.
Paulie. (speaking Italian)
How you doing?
- I ain't doing nothing
and I ain't saying nothing
until I see my lawyer.
- Good idea.
You can have him draw up your will.
He' alive.
- Just a sec.
How do you know?
- Gambino's looking for
him just as hard as we are.
- Well then why doesn't he come in
and let us protect him?
- Is that a serious question, Inspector?
I got a man out there somewhere
who's alone and terrified.
He doesn't know what side he's on anymore.
Why?
Because he's thinking we screwed him.
That's why.
I told them I'd be there.
- [Inspector] Couldn't
be avoided, Cellini.
(Dom sighs)
- Where the hell are you?
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
Hello?
Steve.
I know who you are now.
Who you really are.
Except I don't really know who you are.
Why you did this to me.
You loved me, so I don't understand.
Damn you!
I was ready to spend the
rest of my life with you.
I'm hanging up now.
(somber music)
(engine humming)
(dramatic music)
- We got him.
Location six, 1700 hours, come alone.
- Wouldn't have it any other way.
- Yeah, I'm still alive.
Also accessory to murder one.
- No way, you're on the job.
Nobody's gonna file charges.
- Says who?
- Me.
- You, huh?
Guy who says everything was under control.
We don't leave our people hanging.
No, you just throw their
lives out with the trash.
- Life, Stevie, that's not your life.
They're the bad guys, remember?
You're a cop.
Nobody even figured they'd
use you in the Gallo hit.
Sometimes even we get lucky.
They're calling a grand
jury on Don Gambino.
- So I'm you're start witness?
- What do you think?
- That's it?
That's why you didn't show up?
You wanted Gallo wasted, then
I testify against Gambino
and you get 'em both?
- Don't even think that.
And for God sakes don't ever say it.
They'll chew you up and spit
you out in a million pieces.
Stevie, you go near her
now, you're a dead man.
- Yeah, well maybe I deserve
that, the things I've done.
- After you testify, I'm putting
you in witness protection.
- No, you're not.
I aint gonna spend the rest of my life
in Doorknob, Wisconsin.
- What life?
You go it alone, you think
Gambino won't track you down?
- At least he never lied me.
And he never sold me out.
- You think that's what I did? Huh?
- See you around.
- Hey, you're still a cop.
There's gonna be a grand jury
and you have to appear.
- Fine.
Till then, don't try to find me.
(dramatic music)
(tires screeching)
- That's a good idea.
(indistinct)
There were two cars carrying the hitmen,
I drove the second car.
- But you took no active
part in the shooting?
- No, sir.
- What exactly did you
see, Detective Collura?
- The first shots were
fired inside the restaurant
so I only heard those.
I saw Joey Gallo stumble
out into the street,
the hitman followed him out,
shot him again, killed him.
- And this murder was carried out
by the Gambino crime family, correct?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
- I'd never seen any of the hitmen before
so I don't know if they
were a member of a family.
- Ah.
But the orders came from Carlo Gambino,
isn't that correct?
- I don't know that either.
- Carlo Gambino didn't ask you
to drive the car that night?
- No, sir.
- He never told you that Joey
Gallo was to be murdered?
- No, sir.
- Detective Collura, how
long did you work undercover
in the Gambino crime family?
- Since last October.
- And during that time
you formed a friendship
with Carlo Gambino, a close friendship?
- That was part of my job.
- So close, in fact, you were engaged
to marry his goddaughter, right?
- Yeah.
She had nothing to do with-
- So close, in fact, that
you might be persuaded
to forget certain things he said or did,
isn't that true?
- Carlo Gambino never told me
that Joey Gallo had to be killed.
He never asked me to kill him.
He never asked me to drive any car
that had anything to do with killing him.
That's the truth.
It's also true
that when I knew the hit had been planned,
I informed my superiors at OCCB
and they told me not to worry.
They told me that everything
was under control.
They told me that-
- Thank you, detective.
- That'll be all.
(elevator dings)
- How did it go?
- Oh, beautiful.
Your star witness gave me nothing.
Gambino's gonna walk.
Thanks, Cellini.
Nice doing business with you.
(elevator dings)
(solemn music)
- Can I help you officer?
(soft music)
- Maria!
- [Child] Come on, Maria.
(solemn music)
(soft music)
(upbeat music)