Minister:
I, Tess, take you, Craig,
to have and to hold
from this day forward...
Tess:
I, Tess, take you, Craig,
to have and to hold
from this day forward...
Minister:
For richer, for poorer...
For richer,
for poorer...
Minister:
To love and to Cherish
till death do US part.
To love and to Cherish,
death do US part.
This is my solemn vow.
Minister:
I, Craig, take you, Tess
to have and to hold
from this day forward...
Craig:
I, Craig, take you, Tess
to have and to hold
from this day forward...
Minister:
For richer, for poorer...
For richer,
for poorer...
Minister:
To love and to Cherish
till death do US part.
until death do US part.
This is my solemn vow.
[ Applause]
[ Giggles]
[ Happy chattering]
Congratulations, Craig.
Thank you.
[ Laughing]:
That's my man.
Where you going,
Mr. McCall?
Man:
Where's the champagne?
[ Champagne cork pops]
[ Laughter and cheering]
[ Applause]
Thank you.
I... I would like to, uh
propose a... a toast.
All right.
Oh!
[ Cheering]
Um... 20 years.
[ Laughs nervously]
Wow, boy, if I knew then
what I know now.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
I would do it
all over again,
the way we just did.
I don't know,
sometimes I wonder, uh...
How I ever deserved you or...
Or Sophie...
Or, uh... Josh.
A lot of guys may say this,
but, uh...
I really am the, uh...
The luckiest man in the world.
Cheers.
Hey, mom and dad, you have
the first dance, your song.
Ohh...
[ Clears throat]
Okay, Brett,
come and dance with me.
[ Slow dance song playing]
♪ Like a million miles
away from me ♪
♪ you couldn't see
how I adored you ♪
♪ so close
♪ so close and yet so far.
[ Stops tape]
[ Loud pop song starts]
♪ Everybody party
♪ express yourself
♪ everybody going to party,
express yourself... ♪
Dance faster,
uncle Bobby.
♪ Let the music take you there
♪ higher and higher...
Hold still, Sophie.
Hey, Bobby,
pour me some of that.
Matthew!
[ Laughs]
I'm so glad you're here.
Oh, I wouldn't miss
this for the world.
Renewing vows after 20 years,
thatis something.
Ooh! It is.
No, I'm serious, it is.
It really is wonderful.
You know that Craig and I have
been partners almost that long?
You know something?
I don't really worry
about him out there
'cause I know
he's with you.
You know something?
I don't worry about him
when he's off duty
'cause I know he's
home with you.
♪ Play!
♪ Let the music take you there
shoo, shoo.
Oh, god, look, they even went
for aunt ida's meatballs.
Mom?
It was beautiful.
Oh.
I know everybody writes
their own vows these days
but frankly, I wanted it to be
exactly the way it was.
Hey?
Aw, Denise.
You're my sister,
I know you.
What is up?
I can't explain it.
I just have this hunch.
I think Bobby's
fooling around.
No!
What makes you...
Denise, why would you...
Oh, will you please go
dance with uncle frank
so I don't have to?
Hi, did Denise seem
okay to you?
Yeah.
She was crying
when you and daddy
were saying your vows
but everybodywas crying.
You know, I thought it was
going to be totally weird
seeing your parents
get married.
But I liked it.
What about Bobby?
Bobby, crying?
Yeah, right.
Denise.
Uh, come here.
I'm sorry.
You have to tell me
why you think this.
I shouldn't have said
anything, today of all days.
Are you kidding me?
Of course you should.
Craig:
Hey, Tess,
you got that ice?
Ah, yeah.
We'll get into
this later.
Yeah.
Mom.
Mm-hmm?
Um... Brett and I are talking
about getting married.
Next summer.
Um... honey you still have
two years of school left.
What about the sorbonne?
Oh, I don't know what's
happening with that.
I haven't heard.
But if we do decide
to go ahead
I'm going to take
a leave of absence.
Just for a year
until Brett finishes.
And then he'll support me
and I'll go back and I'll
go on to grad school.
Mom... you do this.
What?
When you sense trouble
you start wiping
down surfaces.
Oh, oh, there's no trouble.
I just...
Honey, I never had the
opportunity for an education.
What does that
have to do with me?
I can have both.
This is not
an either/or situation.
You know,
but Brett and I...
It's supposed to be
a partnership.
You know that.
I'm not going to
give up anything.
Mom?
Mom...
It just turned out
to be such a cool thing
you and daddy did today
and I'm just happy.
And I just wanted
to tell you
what Brett and I
were talking about.
And we're just talking.
Okay?
Okay.
Now go.
This is your wedding day.
Go.
Craig:
I'll be there in 20.
You have to leave?
Yeah, sorry, babe.
This guy we
been watching...
His wife turned up
buried in the basement.
What was up
with your sister today?
Oh, her and Bobby...
Your daughter wants
to get married.
[ Laughing]
I think
she's too young.
Oh, I know, babe.
Hey, we got married
at her age.
We turned out okay,
didn't we?
20 years,
do you believe it?
Tired of me?
Oh, no!
Mmm.
You know, we ought to be
at a romantic hideaway
somewhere.
Just the two of US.
No, I mean it.
I know I've said it before
but... I would
like to do that.
Let's go right now.
[ Party music continuing]
I love you.
I hope you never stop.
'Bye, I'll be back
as soon as I can.
Okay.
♪
Our sun is doomed.
When it's grown
into a red giant
it's going to swallow up
Mercury, Venus
maybe even earth
if we're not careful.
No, not for a long,
long time, now, honey.
Come on, hurry up.
You'll miss the bus.
In five billion years
it'll be a hundred times
brighter than now.
Bummer.
I'm working on my hook shot.
Okay, we'll see
about that.
Mmm, bye bye.
I love you.
And I found a
credit card receipt
in his jacket
for flowers.
I never got
any flowers.
Oh, I can't
believe it.
There must be a
reasonable explanation.
He's just different.
He said he plays basketball
on Tuesday nights.
Yeah?
But I went down there
the other day...
And the guys said
he hadn't been there
in weeks.
Wow.
Oh, neesie, you can't
jump to conclusions.
Tess, our checking account
has been off $100 twice now.
And then...
The sex!
It's changed...
It's gotten really great.
That's bad?
But the main thing
is this feeling.
Why don't men have that?
Well, they do
they just don't know
what to do with it.
[ Sobbing]
Oh, neese.
Oh, honey.
[ Sobbing harder]
Oh, neesie, come on.
It's going to be fine.
It really will.
Come on, sweetie.
Oh, honey.
I don't know what
to do, Tess.
Well, o-okay, all right.
So let's say he sent
someone flowers.
Now, we don't know
what that means.
It could be anything.
I feel so paranoid,
I can't help it.
Look, it's probably not
as bad as you think.
But, but... I don't
know, if, if...
To put your mind at ease,
we need to try and find out.
Oh, what am I supposed
to do, ask him?
[ Laughing, sobbing]
Well, I don't know.
If you think
something's going on
then you need
to check it out.
[ Factory whistle blows]
Denise:
I can't believe you know
how to do this stuff.
Tess:
Hey, I'm a mother.
I may not know how
to turn on a computer
but I know how to be observant.
Remember how we used
to sit out here on our bikes
waiting for daddy
to get off work?
I'm just glad
he's not here to see this.
Never in a million years
did I think...
I know, I know.
Mom and daddy were lucky.
It really was "'till death
do US part" with them.
Man:
Bobby, see you later.
Bobby:
See you tomorrow, Chuck.
Denise:
It's good
we're doing this.
Tess:
It is, you'll see.
You don't...
Tess, there he is.
There, there.
[ Horn honks]
Easy, Bobby.
Later, man.
[ Honks]
God, he never uses his blinker.
Tell me about it.
There he is.
Parked behind that
little convertible.
[ Jukebox playing country tune]
[ General conversation]
I can't...
I have to leave.
What? No, no, we're
seeing this through.
♪ ...stirring up my emotions
♪ as you cross my mind...
Waitress:
Ladies...
What can I
get for you?
Oh, uh, uh...
Ginger ale, please.
One ginger ale.
No, two white wines.
Don't you bail on me now.
Do you have carafes?
Sure. One carafe,
white wine.
They're gone.
What?
♪ Every time our eyes meet
♪ that's how it is with me.
[ Car engines running]
[ Horn honking]
[ Song still audible]
Aw, neese,
oh, come on, honey.
I'm sorry.
Don't.
Don't, sweetie.
I knew it.
[ Sobs]
I knew it, but...
I didn't want to know
it, but I knew it.
I know.
Oh!
I just feel so humiliated.
Oh, sweetie.
Oh, what am I
supposed to do now?
[ Sobbing]
I don't know.
Let me think, okay?
Let me think.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
[ Siren dying down]
[ Horn honking]
[ Crashing]
[ Grunting]
Get off me!
Man:
See you in hell!
I don't want to do this.
No, it'll be fine.
Craig has experience
with these kind of things.
He'll know what to do.
Here, sweetie, sit.
[ Phone ringing]
[ General conversation]
Man:
You want to get
that for me?
[ Intercom buzzing]
Hey.
Everything okay at home?
Oh, yeah. Everything's fine.
Can you just give US a minute?
[ Sighs]
Uh... well, yeah.
It's kind of nutso
around here.
But, uh...
All right.
Go ahead.
He had his stupid arm
around her.
And then the two
of them left-- together.
Oh, come on. Bobby?
Are you sure?
He's my husband.
We both saw him
with our own eyes.
I don't know
how much more you need.
All I'm saying is that unless
you have
some evidence...
Well, sweetheart
that's why
we've come to you.
Because we need
an expert's advice.
Shirley, would you
tell Mrs. Delaney
I'll be right in?
Sure, detective.
Her daughter, Tara
is a runaway.
Oh, how awful.
Yeah, 15 years old.
Honey...
If you could just...
Tell US how
to go about it.
You want me to tell you
how to run
a surveillance.
That's right.
Yeah.
I'll be right back.
Oh, um, no dinner
for me tonight, okay?
Brett and I
are going to the movies.
So, we'll get
something later.
Okay.
Sophie:
Hi, aunt Denise.
Denise:
Hey, hey.
Now?
Yep, this is it.
What?
What's going on?
Uh... just stir the soup.
Well...
And stay with Josh.
I'll be back later,
okay, sweetheart?
Great.
This is what Craig said?
How else are we
going to follow him?
Oh, I just can't.
[ Sighs]
[ Grunting]
[ Plastic shatters]
Oh, god!
Bobby loves this truck.
He's going to kill me.
[ Dog barking in distance]
I know Craig said
to rent an old car.
I just hope this thing starts.
Denise:
It's the same car.
It's her.
Denise.
Get the camera.
Do you...
Wait.
[ Dog barking]
Uh-uh, neesie?
Here, come here.
We have to wait.
All right.
I'm waiting.
Neesie, honey,
please sit down.
Denise.
[ Hushed]:
Neesie.
Neesie, wait.
Oh, geez, don't
forget the camera.
Ow!
Neesie!
Neese!
[ Angry grunt]
[ Moans softly]
Make sure
that thing's running.
N-Neese?
[ Woman screams]You lying,
cheating...!
Get away from my husband!
[ Shrieking]
Get, get!
Easy, neese.
Denise:
You!
Listen to me,
calm...
Nothing in your life
will ever be
easy again!
Neesie, try
and calm down!
Is this a festival...?!
Will you please
stop filming this?
I am going
to kill you!
My client agrees
to a quick settlement...
If,in exchange
Mrs. Hughes doesn't
go into court
with the videotape
as evidence.
And, um, we have
one other point.
Yes.
We would like
Mr. Hughes
to be responsible
for the funds
that he took from
their account for his...
Indiscretion.
It was their
joint account.
We have
the exact amount
Mr. Fisher.
Mm-hmm.
Mrs. McCall.
I don't know what
your availability is
but would you
have any interest
in doing some investigative
work for US here
from time to time?
[ Laughs]
Oh, Mr. Fisher.
That's really nice of you.
It is, but... I was only
helping out my sister.
I mean, I'm not a...
I don't have
a bit of experience
with this kind of thing.
Really?
Well, I like the way you think.
I thought you did a very
good job in there.
I really did.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Why don't you...
Give it some thought
and, uh...
Give me a call?
Sophie:
Here.
Okay, what
about this?
Shall I take that
back to school?
Yeah. Is that mine?
No.
Hey, sophe?
I'm just going
to say this
one last time,
about you and Brett.
Honey, um...
[ Laughs nervously]
You're 18.
I just don't want you
to be in such a rush.
We're not
in a rush.
We just want
to be married.
I don't know.
I look at you
and daddy and...
Don't look at US,
that's different.
We're different.
I mean, when I met daddy
he was just
out of the service
and about to go
on the force, and...
I thought it was a miracle
he even wanted me.
Oh, mom, you always
shortchange yourself.
Oh.
You do.
It's just that
he was this worldly man
this well-traveled,
gorgeous man.
Honey, I guess what
I'm trying to say is...
I never had the chance
to explore.
Mom, I am different than you.
I will continue my education.
I know I will.
I know you say that, but...
Life has a way
of getting in the way.
[ Horn honking
outside]Mom...
Well, I'm sorry you feel
that you got
caught up in US.
Oh, no, sweetie.
I did, but it's what I wanted.
I mean, my life has been...
Very full, very happy.
So are you going
to take that job?
Hmm? Oh, I hadn't
really thought about it.
Oh, mom, why not?
The lawyer
was on the other side.
He must have
really been impressed.
I don't know. We'll see.
[ Honking continues]
Anyway, Brett's waiting.
I know.
Um, sweetie, I just...
Want you to think about
what I said carefully.
[ Laughs gently]
Okay, I will.
And you think about it, too.
Bye!
Bye. Love you.
[ Calling back]:
I love you, too.
[ Sighs softly]
Well, I don't know.
I think you might
lay off her a little.
Hey, you asked my opinion,
so I'm telling you.
What, you want her
to get married?
Well, no, not particularly.
I just don't know
how much
we should get involved.
I was just expressing
my opinion.
Yeah, over and over
and over and over again.
Honey, there's
a fine line between...
Hey, did you call this guy?
Hmm?
Not yet.
What do you...?
You mean, you intend to?
Yeah, I thought
I would, yeah.
[ Chuckles]
Come on.
Babe, yeah, the man paid you
a compliment, but...
But what?
But...
He likes the way I think and...
You know, I think I'm good.
Yeah.
Tess.
I mean,
what's the worst
that can happen
here, I fail?
No, I mean...
Tess.
You don't think
I can do it, do you?
[ Mumbles]
[ Dialing phone]
[ Clears throat]
Mr. Fisher, this is Tess McCall.
Yes.
Yes, I have thought
about it and, um...
Yes, I would.
[ Laughs]
That's wonderful.
I'll see you then.
Woman:
Fisher and torroricci,
good morning.
Tess.
Oh, good morning.
Good morning.
Welcome aboard.
Come on, let's go
into my office.
I cannot tell you how pleased
I am that you're joining US.
Thanks.
I've got some research
I want you to do.
Okay.
I think you'll find
everything you need
at the court records
in the county clerk's
office.
Great.
Oh, by the way,
did you have coffee?
Oh, yeah, thanks,
I'm fine.
Also, you'll find
the county tax files
at the courthouse
as well.
I want you
to check that, too.
Okay.
Tess:
This week's been
about legwork, mainly.
You know, looking
up addresses, records.
Not like what they
make it look like
in the movies, is it?
It's boring
when you get down to it.
There's one that's interesting.
Remember that one
I was telling you about?
The client whose wife was always
going away
on business trips?
Well, I followed her.
[ Phone ringing]
You did?
She went to the airport,
all right--
the airport motel.
Hello.
Oh, yes, just a moment.
Here, sweetie.
Hello.
Oh, hi, yeah, yeah.
Mrs. Delaney.
Yes, about your
daughter, Tara...
So you do what dad does
except you don't work
for the police?
Sort of.
So, you spy on people.
Cool.
Well, not exactly spying
it's more like
gathering information.
Craig:
Good-bye.
Who was on the phone?
Linda Delaney.
She's the mother of that
15-year-old runaway girl.
I was supposed to call her.
Anyway, starting tomorrow
they have me down
at the county center
sorting through piles
of building leases.
Every day?
For the next two weeks, yeah.
Well, looks like we're going to
have to fend for ourselves, huh?
Out.
Thank you.
You got to admit,
it is interesting work.
And you're good at it.
Thank you.
Funny how life really is
an open book.
I mean, whatever you've done
is written down somewhere.
Yeah. Hey, hey, Dennis,
meet Tess McCall.
She's the one that worked
on your case.
Dennis bell.
Nice to meet you.
Excuse me one minute.
So, welcome aboard.
You've been here...
A month, barely.
You were my first case.
Well, you did
an extraordinary job.
And my wife
will think so, too
when she finds out
what I know
about the guy
she's been seeing.
Really, you did
a great job, thank you.
Hey, here's the printout.
Check the d.M.V.
Right.
And the registered voters
listings.
Nice to meet you, thanks.
[ Giggling]
Hey, have they said
when you can cut back on hours?
I didn't think this was
going to be full time.
Well, no, it's not
supposed to be.
Why would I cut back
on hours?
Well, I'm just saying, you know.
I mean, you've got this place,
you've got me, the kids.
[ Giggling]
Honey, hey, are
you feeling neglected?
Oh, not particularly.
Well, what's he going to say?
What are you saying?
You want me
to cut back?
Well, no, I'm just saying
that I think
that maybe it's getting
to be a bit too much.
You know, I'm gone all hours
of the day and night
and now you are, too.
Well...
Okay, I will.
I'll just tell them I have
to rethink my schedule.
[ Rock music playing]
♪ Oh, yeah...
♪ It's high time
that you got my message ♪
[ Phone ringing]
♪ Don't make
promises you can't keep ♪
♪ yeah it's high time
that you got my message ♪
Hello.
Woman:
Is this Tess McCall?
Yeah, this is she.
Tess, this is
Sally Russell calling.
Hello?
Yes, I'm here.
Thesally Russell?
That's me.
A friend gave me your name--
Michelle hess?
I believe you did some work
for her?
Yes, I did.
Well, I was wondering
if I might stop in.
I'm sorry to call you at home,
but I have a matter
I'd like to discuss with you.
You mean here, now?
I'd really appreciate it.
It's very personal, and I've
been told you're very discreet.
Can I tell you, I just love
Sally Russell's table.
I read every issue,
cover to cover.
I get such great hints from it.
I'm sorry,
this isn't your brand.
The commercial you do
is so cute.
Well, thank you.
I do it because, you know
I use their product
in my catering business.
Um, Tess?
Sit down.
Oh!
Sorry.
No, no, no!
I'm the one
that should apologize
for barging in like this.
Um... but it's Jason,
my husband.
That's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
Oh.
I met him in rio.
I was catering a party
and he was there.
In a white dinner jacket.
It was so... m.G.M.
It was just like one of those
old black and white movies.
Sounds romantic.
Oh, he was so handsome
and...
So Brazilian.
I just love that accent.
I could listen to it all night.
But then I discovered that
that wasn't his, the accent...
[ Chuckles]
And that he was
from St. Louis.
No, no, no.
I didn't think a thing of it.
I mean, I do exactly
the same thing.
I pick up on the way people
talk, you know.
Anyway, we fell
desperately in love
and well, we've been married
for a year.
Jason is...
He's my business partner.
Mm-hmm.
And, um, he's younger than me.
Oh, yes, I see.
I mean, he's very handsome.
Yeah.
He's drop-dead gorgeous.
I think he's seeing
another woman.
I think.
I was just wondering if...
You might help me?
Yeah, I saw her magazine
at the checkout counter.
It's... she caters or hosts
parties or something like that?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I just admire her
so much.
I mean, what she's managed
to create for herself.
I thought you told them
you were cutting back?
This doesn't have anything
to do with the firm.
I'd be taking this
on my own.
On your own?
Well, yeah.
I talked to Mr. Fisher
about it
and he said sure.
Because I only work there
part-time...
Slow down,
slow down, slow down.
This is not
what you've been saying, Tess.
Now this is not the kind
of legwork job
that you've been talking about.
I know.
Do you?
Do you know
what you're taking on?
For heaven's sakes, Craig.
I mean, give me
some credit.
I give you plenty of credit.
Then be happy for me.
It's not as if
we can't use the money.
Sophie's in college
and before you know it,
Josh will be there, too.
I know, I know.
I just thought you might
appreciate the fact
that I'm able to contribute
financially.
I appreciate it--
I just want to make sure
you keep some sort
of perspective on all this.
I feel like I'm in
a Calvin klein commercial.
[ Chuckles]
This is my office.
And this is his.
But don't worry,
he's not here today.
Tess, I don't know
if I can go through with this.
It's like I'm already saying
he's guilty.
You told me
you had a hunch.
Mm-hmm.
If you really do,
you owe it to yourself
to follow
your own instincts.
I have to tell you, though,
if you open this door
you have to be prepared
to walk through it.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I just want everything to be
like it was in the beginning.
I really don't know
if I could survive without him.
Then maybe you should think
about this a little more.
Hmm.
Yeah.
[ High-pitched whistling]
[ Gasps]
Oh.
Help you?
Hi.
[ Laughs nervously]
I must have gone past
your shop a hundred times.
I thought...
I'm a private investigator
and I was wondering
what kind of equipment
you might be able to show me
for, you know, surveillance.
What kind of surveillance
would you be talking about?
Oh.
All-purpose?
Cameras, all sizes.
A lineman's telephone
that you hook up
anywhere you have access
to the wires.
Oh, wow.
All kinds of wireless
video and audio monitoring.
Hidden microphones.
Badges, I.D. Cards...
A peephole lens
for your camcorder.
Really?
Drill a hole in the wall
attach this to your camcorder
and you get the big picture
in the next room.
Oh.
Recorder, wall probes--
lets you hear through walls.
An electronic tracking device.
You attach this to the car
you want to follow
and then this piece,
the receiver
lets you hear
a continuous beep, beep, beep
in your own car.
[ Beeping]
Perfect.
Do you have a catalog?
Oh, wow!
Woman:
Ginny got caught.
Man:
Then why aren't you home
with her?
Woman:
Why aren't you?
Who's the mom?
It's your kid too!
Don't push me.
Police officer.
Hey, hey!
Hey!
Woman:
What're you doing, man?
Get the hell off of him,
will you?
Go home.
Listen,
leave him alone!
Stand back!
He's my husband!
Leave my wife alone!
Get off him!
Don't cuff him!
Listen!
Matthew, take him!
It's our runaway.
You guys...
Woman:
I am trying to tell you!
Tara!
[ Classical music playing]
[ Laughing]
Okay.
Bye.
[ No audio]
[ Softly]:
Say that again?
[ No audio]
Yes, that's it.
Okay.
[ Laughs]
It's like an o'keeffe
still life, isn't it?
You know
what Alfred stieglitz said
when he saw Georgia o'keeffe's
art work for the first time?
He said,
"finally, a woman on paper."
I didn't know that.
Yeah, he said that.
Wonderful party.
Tara.
Aw, honey.
Honey, I was so worried
about you.
Nice to see Mrs. Delaney
with a happy ending, huh?
Yeah, for a change.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
Woman:
Shirley, line two.
Usually these...
[ Sniffling]
I want to go home.
It's a nice change.
You are here alone.
Me, too.
Would you like to dance?
Here?
Yeah.
Or anywhere you like.
Um, actually, someone's
coming to pick me up.
Oh, lucky guy.
Well...
It would be my pleasure.
In actuality,
it was like the pinkest sand
I've ever seen in my life.
Oh, excuse me.
We should probably get together
in the morning.
Okay, why?
I think you're right to have
your suspicions.
Did you see him
with someone?
I had a little chat
with him myself, so to speak.
I taped it, it's on tape.
What's on tape?
Did he make a pass at you?
Oh, my god.
Listen, we need more
so don't breathe a word to him
until we can come up
with some kind of a strategy.
All right?
Yeah, all right.
Sally?
Yeah, right.
Craig:
What, babe?
I'm just feeling thankful
that I have you to come home to.
Well, now you know
how I felt all these years.
We're so lucky.
Gone? What do
you mean, gone?
All his things.
Yes. Gone.
He took everything
he could get his hands on.
Wait...
Thank god
I still have my business.
I don't under...
I confronted him.
I had to.
Oh, Sally, I told you not to.
I couldn't help it.
What do you think?
I mean, this has been
horrible for me.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Tess, I'm sorry.
It's okay, it's okay.
[ Sobbing]
Hey, babe, don't beat
yourself up over it.
It's not your fault.
Yeah, it was.
I shouldn't have said
anything to her
till I had the guy
absolutely dead to rights.
Most situations like this
require a professional.
You know, your pipes break,
you call a plumber.
What?
Look, you were fine
before all this
and if you quit
you'll be fine after.
No, I'm not quitting.
I'm not.
Actually, Peter Fisher says
I can rent office space
down at his firm.
Do you think maybe
you're getting
a little bit ahead
of yourself here?
Office space, come on.
Craig, when I see what happens
to these people
my own sister...
I... I want to do something.
Honey, look, it is one thing
to look up records
in a courthouse
but you could get hurt.
I'm not just talking
about your feelings.
I'm very careful.
No, these people, these...
Some wacko you're trailing
finds out
then youbecome the target.
Oh...
You walk into some
domestic altercation
do you know that's how
more cops are killed?
You never know
what you're going
to walk into.
Craig, for the first
time in my life there's...
I found something that matters
that... I can actually do.
And I'm going to do it.
Tess:
Yes, if you could just give US
the correct spelling
of your name?
Right... yes.
That's how we have it
in our directory.
Great.
Thank you very much.
Hello!
How are you?
I'm fine.
Peter Fisher just told me
you opened
your own office here.
Yeah. Come on in.
It's nice to see you again.
You, too.
I wanted you to know
that Maggie and I
are in counseling.
We're trying
to make it work out.
Good.
That's wonderful.
Um, do you want to...
No, I'm not
going to keep you.
I just came by to say thanks
for everything
and I wish you
the best of luck.
You take care.
Okay.
Hey!
Who's that?
Who's that guy?
Oh, a client.
Oh, guess what?
Another firm's put me
on retainer.
Oh, boy, terrific.
Yes, Mr. Turner, Tess McCall.
Yeah, I spoke to him.
I got his particulars
and I think it's a good place
to start.
Yeah.
Why don't...
Well, we'll have a meeting
tomorrow morning, 9:00.
Okay, great, thanks.
Geez, honey...
So who, uh,
who was that guy?
Oh, I told you,
he was a client.
Yeah?
What?
I saw the guy hugging you.
I was just, you know...
A little jealous.
You are, aren't you?
Are you ready
to call it a day?
Let's go.
No, sweetie
I have three hours
of work left.
I can't, sorry.
Don't worry.
Dinner's in the slow cooker.
Okay.
Okay?
Yeah. All right.
I just...
See you later.
Okay.
Man:
Hey, Ruth!
Ruth's out sick,
down with something.
Oh, yeah?
Who are you?
Noreen.
I'm filling in.
Don't waste your time
going in there.
The guy took out a lease
but he wasn't there two weeks.
I'll be up on nine
if you get lonesome
on your break.
I got a thermos.
[ Sighs]
[ Door opens]
[ Knocking]
Hey, you're back.
How was Florida?
Oh, you know how uncle frank
and aunt ida are.
Can't put your feet up
on anything.
Great look.
I leave town
and you blossom.
You doing okay?
So tell me,
how's it going?
Are you having the most
incredible time?
Yeah...
Yeah, I am.
I lose a husband
and you gain a career,
and a wardrobe.
Oh, neesie,
you were lucky.
You just don't know.
I know,
as devastating as it was
it could have been worse.
Some of these
men and women
are left practically
destitute
with no one to show them
how to protect themselves.
Maybe you ought to
teach a class.
[ Chuckles]
Maybe I ought to.
You know what you look like?
One of the lunchroom ladies
from when we were
in junior high.
[ Laughing]
You look good.
I mean, different.
Good different.
A lunchroom lady
with a mission.
Yeah.
Hey, babe.
Hey, listen, uh...
You haven't seen
a gold earring
in here, have you?
Linda Delaney called.
She thinks she may have
lost it in here
when we were looking
for her daughter, Tara.
Great.
She will be very, very happy.
Tess:
We've all seen it
in the movies, right?
Somebody's having an affair.
Romantic dinners
and stolen weekends
at some glamorous-looking
hideaway
presents to die for.
Well, let me tell you.
Infidelity is not cheap.
Even on a real life scale.
So, what we have to do
if we have that uneasy feeling
about our spouses
is not to ignore it, which is
probably our first inclination
but pay attention.
Look for clues,
gather the evidence.
You'll find everything you need
to run a basic surveillance
you probably already have.
From your car to your phone
to baby monitors, even your pet.
[ Laughter]
I'm not kidding.
Saying you're looking
for your dog can come in handy
when you're caught someplace
you're not supposed to be.
[ Laughter]
A very nice speech.
Thank you.
That was very good.
Tess.
Oh, Sally.
Excuse me one second.
Sally.
Yeah.
I wasn't sure
you'd come.
I wasn't either,
but you were great.
You're becoming quite the pro,
Tess McCall.
I want another
chance, Sally.
I'm better at it now.
I think I can help you.
I was going through
building leases
and I found an office lease
in Jason's name.
For Asian-pacific imports?
No.
He'd already
cleared out.
But I found a receipt
that might mean something.
Uh... happy bottom?
That bastard.
Oh, my god.
Sally:
That's what he used to call me.
Sally!
Look what I found!
What?
I.d.s!
Driver's license
from three different states.
Jason ferrell... laszlo sperling
Benjamin Randall.
Who the hell is this man?
Yes!
Hey!
Hey!hi, mom.
Hi, sweetie.
Did you remember those...
Binoculars, yeah.
Where are they?
In the trunk,
I'll get them later.
Okay.
[ Craig and Josh joking]
[ Ball bouncing, scuffling]
[ Dribbling ball]
Craig:
Whoa! Good boy!
"Big bopper"?
Hey, big bopper!
Want to bop on in here a minute?
Placing personal ads
is just part
of your job?
Is that
what you're trying to say?
No, that's
what I amsaying.
It's for an investigation--
a murder investigation.
If you don't believe me,
why don't you call Matthew?
Now, Tess, this is my job.
This is what I do.
This is what
it's always been.
I'm not doing something
different now.
I've never known you
to do this before.
Yes, you have.
You just haven't realized
what it's entailed.
Now, honey, you
have no reason
to be suspicious.
All right?
You're right, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's just...
It's me.
It's my imagination.
The job.
I'm sorry.
"Big bopper."
[ Laughing]
[ Shutter clicking]
Allo?
Sophie?
Hi, sweetie.
I didn't expect you
till dinner tonight.
I know,
we decided to leave early
because I have some news.
Oh, no!
It's nothing bad.
I got into the sorbonne.
Oh, Sophie, that's...
Oh, honey, that is great!
For the whole junior year,
if I want it.
Oh, "if you want it."
Of course you do.
Oh, sweetheart,
I'm so proud of you.
Thanks, mom.
[ Dog barks]
So, if you don't want to go
could someone younger
and smarter than you
take your place?
When do you have
to let them know about it?
By the end
of the month.
Well, if you
don't want to go
don't worry
about disappointing US.
It's your decision.
This is not about US.
Right, mom?
Daddy, it's not
that I don't want to go.
It's just, I'm confused.
I'm sorry,
but the logic here is...
There is no logic here.
Can I be excused from this?
Or am I being punished?
Why don't you help me
clear the table?
[ Whispers]:
Sure thing, mom.
Craig?
[ Panting]
Oh, god.
Oh, god, mom.
Oh, my god.
Oh, dear god.
I'm sorry.
Sophie:
We were...
How dare you.
Mrs. McCall...
Out.
What?
Get out!
Mother!
Get out of my house, now!
You don't have to go.
Sophie!
Just wait.
What is the matter with you?
I can't believe you...
You are out of control.
You are the one
who is out of control.
Sophie, stop it!
Because you are not a child.
Then stop treating me like one!
Sophie!
[ Door slamming]
Hey, babe.
I walked in on your daughter
and Brett in the middle of...
Of what?
They were having sex, Craig,
in our house.
And it's not appropriate
behavior, and she knows that.
Oh, don't patronize me.
You always do that.
I'm sorry.
You don't even know
you're doing it anymore.
Tess, Tess,
I said I'm sorry.
God, it's been a long,
hard night, you know.
She's in the house,
she's safe.
It could be a lot worse.
Let's get into this
in the morning.
In case you haven't noticed,
it is morning.
Why are you trying
to pick a fight with me?
This is what you've
been doing lately.
What is this about?
When you just disappear...
That's what
I'm talking about.
Disappear?
I don't disappear.
You know that.
I get called,
I get paged.
Is some...
Is there something
going on with you...
That I need to know about?
Yeah.
Yeah, there is.
You know what?
I don't like you
in this job.
And I don't think
I ever will.
I don't like
how it makes you.
Now, Tess, honey,
it's like you're obsessed.
You're obsessed.
You are.
I love you.
I know.
I know that.
Let's just...
Try and get some sleep.
Tess:
Hey, how's the job?
Hmm.
You just started,
it's going to take time.
I don't know
that I'll ever be inspired.
I found Jason ferrell,
he's in Seattle.
You did, how?
Through those I.D.S.
He's living there
under the name
of Benjamin Randall.
I'm going there
in a few days.
I wish I could go, too.
Denise?
I think Craig's
seeing somebody.
You don't seem shocked.
Nothing shocks me anymore.
I just have this...
Oh, I know.
That's how it starts.
I need to know, or I just
need it to all go away.
If you think you have
reason to suspect him
then you have to run
a thorough investigation.
Just like you would
anyone else.
This is the receiver
for the r.F. Camera.
Great. Um, what about
that two-way phone recorder?
It starts when any phone
in the house is used
and stops automatically
when it's hung up.
F.c.c.-approved.
I'll take that, too.
TV announcer:
Hamilton dribbling
down the court...
[ Phone rings]
...passes to paterson.
Paterson stops, fakes
passes to Anderson,
Anderson drives
puts it up, over!
And the score is 65-67.
Hello?
Oh, hey, how you doing?
...downcourt to Pierce,
Pierce to earnest
earnest moves around,
passes to kerner.
Kerner puts it up, blocked.
[ Chuckling]
Washington breaks into
the three-two offense.
Hamilton passes to Crosby
Crosby comes back to paterson...
Oh, hey, thanks, babe.
I'm going to Seattle
tomorrow on a job.
I may be gone
for several days.
Oh.
Who was on the phone?
That was, um, Matthew.
...remaining, third quarter.
Turner takes from Washington,
passes to kerner
kerner dribbles around,
passes to Turner... to Pearson
Pearson to pryor,
pryor looks around...
[ TV barely audible]
...scores!
[ Crowd cheering]
[ Rewinds tape]
Matthew:
I want 50 bucks now.
Yeah, I did, I did, I saw it.
I've been playing the same
game as the last...
[ Clicks off]
Announcer:
71-69.
[ Sighs]
[ Whistle blowing]
Boy:
Daddy, daddy!
[ Laughing]
Hi, sweetheart.
Have a nice day?
The dry cleaner called.
They won't have your suit
till tomorrow--
is that okay?
Boy:
Come on, dad.
Wife:
Here we go.
Boy:
Thanks.
I want to push
the button.
Uh, yes... uh
Benjamin Randall, please.
You'll have
to give them a moment.
Mrs. Randall and their kids
just went up.
[ Phone rings]
Door.
Mm-hmm.
Wife and kids?
Statements from two banks
where he opened accounts
with your money.
[ Laughing]
Oh, no.
[ Continues laughing]
A wife?
Do the kids look like him?
I suppose...
Yes.
[ Catching breath]
Sally, we should
go see your attorney.
We should do it right away.
Yeah.
[ Sobs]
Can we do this tomorrow,
please?
[ Crickets chirping]
[ Rewinds tape]
Woman:
Hi, it's Linda.
Craig:
Hey.
So, guess what
I did tonight?
What?
Sold my tenth car.
Really? Cool.
Was he good-looking?
Oh-ho! You're so bad.
You're going to pay
for that, you know.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Is that a problem?
[ Both laughing]
So, uh, we're still on
for tomorrow, right?
Yeah.
7:00?
Room 116.
[ Door opens]
[ Clicks machine off]
Hey, babe, you're back.
I finished early.
Hey...
Did you have a good trip?
Yeah.
I'm running late.
I got to pick up Matty.
Spence is being transferred
to the second precinct.
So we're throwing
a little party for him.
That's why I'm scarfing down
a hot dog.
You don't mind
if I go, do you?
No, of course not.
I'm going to bed early anyway.
So, did you get the bad guys?
Yeah.
Cool.
[ Quietly]:
You don't know it yet,
but, yeah.
[ Faucets squeaking]
[ Shower running]
[ Dog barking in distance]
[ Thunder rumbling]
[ Beeping]
Radio announcer: We're high atop the radio towers overlooking lake erie.
It's music into the night.
And here's one from 1975.
♪ My eyes adored you
♪ though I never
laid a hand on you ♪
♪ my eyes adored you
♪ like a million miles
away from me ♪
♪ you couldn't see
how I adored you ♪
♪ so close
and yet so far ♪
♪ carried your books
from school ♪
♪ playing make-believe
you're married to me ♪
♪ you were fifth grade
♪ I was sixth
♪ when we came to be...
The toilet in the guest room
is broken, did I tell you?
You have to jiggle it
every time you flush.
Want me to call them?
I'm just not quite sure
what to tell them.
Well, just what you told me.
You have to jiggle it.
What, you want me
to call them?
No, I will.
Well, if you want me to,
just say so.
No, I said I would.
Fine. Call.
Oh, whoa-whoa-- lunch.
Keep going.
You're going
to be late.
Bye, mom.
Bye, sweetie.
Bye, dad. See you
after school.
Bye.
Bye, sweetheart.
Have a good day.
I had some files.
Did you see them?
No.
You sure?
Of course.
Why would I see them?
'Cause sometimes
you see them.
Are you saying
I go through your things...?
'Cause I don't.
Yeah, you do.
Why would I...?
If I wanted to see
your stupid files
I could do it without
you even knowing it.
[ Chuckles]
Yeah, sure.
All right. I'll see you.
Tess:
Copies of bank statements...
Marriage certificates,
I.D.S...
And photos.
God, I can't believe
this was going on
and I was completely
blind to it!
Hell of a job, Tess.
You and I need
to get together sometime.
My friend could use an
investigator with your
kind of fortitude.
I'll call
the d.A.'S office.
Sally:
Thanks.
A hell of a job, Tess,
he's right.
Thank you.
[ Patting on back]
Hey, babe.
[ Softly]:
Hey... listen.
I'm sorry about this morning.
I am, I was a real jerk.
I'll call the plumber.
I'll take care
of everything, babe.
I'm so sorry.
Hey...
Remember when we used
to do this, huh?
I'd come home for lunch.
[ Whispers]:
Hey...
Why don't you let me
take this off?
Honey?
I...
I have to meet Denise.
What? Well...
Call her and tell her
you can't make it.
Hey...
[ Sighs]
Everything I tell women
to look for
it's now happening to me.
And I think
it's been going on
for a really
long time, neese.
I just didn't
want to see it.
Tess... I haven't ever
said anything, but...
Craig at Laurel's wedding.
I walked in on him
and Connie carpenter.
Her bridesmaid? So?
What do you mean?
In a bedroom.
You've known about this,
for...
Five years...!
And you've kept it
a secret?
I-I-I... kept it a secret?
I just didn't...
I couldn't tell you.
How dare you tell me now!
How dare you
even talk to me!
Tess!
[ Sighs]
Would you like me to fix you
something to eat before you go?
I'd be happy to.
I know you would,
mother.
I'll probably just
stop for something
on the way.
Anyway,
I'm sure Brett
will be
too mortified
to show his face
in here.
[ Sighs]
Mom...
What?
[ Choked up]:
It's nothing.
I'm sorry.
Oh...
You always do this.
You always say,
"nothing."
No, I don't.
[ Chuckles]
Yes, you do, believe me.
You always deny stuff.
The obvious.
Yeah.
Oh, soph...
You get to be my age and...
And you think you're grown
and you have it all figured out
and I have so much
to figure out.
So is this, uh, a mid-life
thing or something?
Oh, god, I hope not yet.
[ Both laugh]
I am so...
Proud of you.
Yeah...
Guess I'm pretty proud
of you, too...
Mommy.
I trust you, soph.
I hope you know that.
Yeah, I do.
I do, mommy.
Whatever you decide
to do, okay?
I may rant or rave, but...
I'll support you, all right?
Yeah, I know.
Okay.
[ Chuckles]
Tess [with French accent]:
Mrs. Delaney...
Please-- Linda.
It's so luxurious.
Sinfully.
So, are you from here?
No, I'm from back east.
Miss it?
Well, my daughter's
with me and that helps
and there's this guy
I'm seeing.
Ah... that must help, too.
Well, no man's ever treated me
as well as he treats me.
Then you are lucky.
Well, I'm not that lucky--
he's married.
Well...
You never know.
In this case
I'm afraid I do know.
Sorry.
Even if he wasn't married,
this guy...
I get the feeling that
I'm not the first.
Our relationship
is what it is.
As long as we're
in room 116
it's a relationship.
I'm sorry to go on.
You want to take this
for a test drive?
Woman:
Hiya, Tess, he's out
on call right now.
Uh... Tess?
Is he with you?
He's out
with captain popkin--
a robbery over in chaney.
Tess, what is it?
You tell me.
You don't know?
No, I don't.
There are names and dates
and little stars by the names...
As if he rates them.
Women's names.
This doesn't have anything to do
with your personal ads case.
Oh, Tess, you guys
have been my friends
for a long, long time,
both of you have...
And this goes back
a long, long time, doesn't it?
Doesn't it, this, this...
Juggling women, that's what
he's doing, isn't it?
Oh, Matthew, don't worry,
you don't have to say anything.
'Cause you just told me.
Tess, god, I, I...
Matthew, I'd appreciate it
if you didn't get involved
in this.
Parker said
you were here.
Tess...?
I have nothing
to say to you.
Oh, yeah, you do,
don't get defensive.
I haven't done
anything against you.
Yes, you have,
you conspired with him.
Conspired?!
I ought to beat
the crap out of you.
I can still do it,
you know.
I don't know what the
hell else you'd call it.
If I was conspiring,
I was conspiring with you.
You wanted,
needed to believe
that he was a certain way
and I only wanted you to be
happy, so I believed it, too.
I would never hurt you.
You're right,
I did want him...
Decent, I wanted him
to be decent.
And that's
where I went wrong.
Tess...
I made it so easy for him.
I did.
I was so willing to believe,
to accept anything
to make it all right.
Maybe when you
talk to him...
You need
to talk to him.
It's over, Denise.
It's over.
I'm not ever,
ever going back.
I don't want to.
[ Dialing phone]
What are you going to do?
[ Phone ringing]
Hi, sweetheart.
Listen, I, uh,
have to go back to Seattle.
I may be gone
for a couple of days.
I know.
Could you pick up Josh
from school?
No, I already checked with
Denise and she's working.
But she said she can probably
keep him tomorrow afternoon.
All right then.
Great.
Love you, too.
[ Click]
Bastard.
You want to close out
your joint account?
No, no, I want you to leave
just ten dollars in it
and then transfer the rest
to a new account.
Fine, no problem.
[ Horns honking]
[ Beeping]
Man:
Hi. How can I help you?
[ With southern accent]:
Yeah, I'd like
a room, please.
All right-- for one night?
[ Phone rings]
Excuse me.
Newton motel,
good afternoon.
Yeah, we're on highway 101,
just south of the lake.
Just south of the lake,
that's right.
Uh, excuse me,
what happened
to the liquor store
on the corner?
They moved.
They did?
Just one block down.
Okay, thanks.
Hi. All right.
Sorry about that.
No, it's all right.
Is it possible
to get room 117?
117, uh...
Not a problem.
Thank you.
[ Laughter on TV]
[ Laughter on TV,
water running]
[ Whirring]
[ Whirring continues]
[ Traffic roaring]
[ TV playing]
[ Door closes]
Craig:
Hey!
Woman:
Is that a big...
Bad policeman?
[ Craig laughing]
[ Growling playfully]
Listen, listen.
What?
I can't stay long.
Woman:
What do you mean
you can't stay long?
Craig:
I have to run.
I have to
pick up my son.
Your son?
Oh.
Wow, I bet you're a
really terrific father, huh?
[ Kissing, heavy breathing]
[ Traffic roaring]
[ Canned TV laughter]
[ Heavy breathing]
[ Kissing]
[ Truck roaring]
[ Craig, woman panting]
[ Traffic roaring]
[ Both laughing]
Listen, don't worry
about me, okay?
I'll just, um...
Get a cab.
You have no money?
Craig:
No, I don't.
I'm going to have
to stop by an a.T.M.
Here, come on.
Get in the car.
Excuse me.
[ Beeping]
[ Traffic roaring]
[ Sirens wailing]
Oh, damn!
Woman:
What's going on?
I'm going to drive
you home, okay?
The machine must
not be working.
...leave a message
after the beep.
Hey, Denise.
It's Craig, listen...
Ooh!
I was hoping you'd be there
and that Josh'd be with you.
Uh, I got to school
kind of late...
It's all locked up.
Um... I'm going to head home.
So... uh, I'll give you
a call from there.
Is that dad?
No.
Don't think so.
Sounds like dad
on the phone.
Hello?
You there?
Your shot.
Man on TV:
Later or early tomorrow.
Woman on TV:
Well, what is it?
Hey, Josh? Sorry I missed you
at school, buddy.
Man:
...Spoil the surprise.
You'll love it, though.
I've been running late
all day.
Did you catch
the bus, or, uh...
Woman:
Let's go in the bedroom...
Woman 2:
...A big, bad policeman?
[ Canned laughter]
[ Craig growling playfully]
Craig:
...My son.
Man:
One of these days!
Woman:
Wow, I bet you're
a really
terrific father, huh?
Craig:
Yeah.
[ Kissing, heavy breathing]
Woman:
Give me your handcuffs.
[ Craig laughing]
[ Both laughing]
[ Canned laughing on TV]
[ Craig and woman
laughing louder]
We're just getting
to the good part.
Tess, turn it off, come on.
Now!
No.
Not yet.
I'm doing you a favor, Craig.
It's a private showing.
So you know just what
to expect in court.
I don't believe this.
What? That I did this?
Or that I caught you?
Oh, go ahead.
Take it.
I have a copy.
[ Laughs nervously]
All right,
you caught me.
Babe.
I mean, you know
come on...
It, it, it's nothing.
I'm an idiot, I'm an idiot.
Uh, it, I'm a jerk.
I mean, it's over.
You know?
It will never
happen... again.
What?!
[ Crashing]
Say something!
I don't have to say something.
I'm listening to you...
Babe.
I don't even
have to ask you
what her name is
'cause what I don't know
about her I can find out.
I'm outta here.
Oh, no, I'm not
through with you yet.
I have the dates, the times,
the names of the others...
I can trace your infidelity
back as far...
Tess, you made
your point, okay.
No, I took vows, Craig...
I took them seriously.
All right?
And you betrayed me.
Tess, come on.
Tess, you mean
everything to me.
I've provided for you.
I've always been
here for you.
I gave, I gave you
20 years of my life
and you looked me
in the eyes
and you lied to me
and you betrayed me.
And I...
[ Sobs]
I don't deserve this.
To be treated like this,
I don't deserve it.
Get out.
Please, just...
Tess...
Go, please.
[ Sighing]
Did you know that
the porch light was out?
Uh-uh.
I changed it.
Did you?
Thank you, sweetheart.
Hey, you want to do
something special
this weekend?
We can drive up
and visit Sophie at school?
Bet there'd be
a basketball game on.
Just me and you?
Um..., or Denise, maybe,
if you like.
Or not.
[ Knocking]
Hi.
I... do you mind if...
[ Door shuts]
Oh, sorry, I caught you
in the middle of dinner, huh?
Would you care
for something?
Are you hungry?
Uh, no, no, no
I ate.
Please... sit down.
I just...
Stopped by to see
how you guys were doing.
How's school?
Sucks, as usual.
Did you turn in
that science project yet?
When is that due?
It was due
last Friday, except...
I can turn it in this week.
Mr. Evans is cool.
Well, I don't want you
to get points taken off
because you're late.
I won't.
Well, yeah, but...
What do you care!
Josh!
Hey, Josh.
Hey, buddy.
Come here.
I'm sorry, buddy.
I'm so sorry.
[ Sighs]
[ People applauding]
Kenny:
Welcome back to the show.
I'm really excited
to have this next guest.
She's back again.
Please, give a warm welcome
to our very own Tess McCall.
[ Cheering and applause]
Hi, Tess, welcome back.
Kenny:
Tess is an advocate
for those whose spouses
cheat on them
stealing away
the assets of the marriage
not to mention the years
of devotion.
Tess, last time
you told US
how you started
your business
what you learned
and you talked
about fidelity
infidelity...
And our audience
really responded to that.
And I got to tell you,
that surprised me.
Yes, it does seem
to strike a chord,
unfortunately.
Tess, isn't part
of what you do...
Well, some would say,
it's about revenge.
Oh, no!
Oh, no, it's not all.
I mean, I think sometimes
in the beginning it's about...
Fear of abandonment, or it's
about jealousy... but, but...
But I really think, mostly,
this is about love and respect.
Respect for what was.
The life you built together,
all the things you vowed
you'd be for each other,
no matter what.
Finally...
It's about respect
for yourself.
Because what's done
cannot be undone.
And it's how you live with it
that really matters.
I mean, how you get on with your
life... because, believe me
life does go on.
[ Cheering and applause]
[ People talking]
Tess:
Hey! Hi, sweetie.
Where were you?
I know, it took
forever, didn't it?
Come on, quick,
quick, quick.
Hi.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's okay, I'm just
glad you're here.
We saw the show,
you were great.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh, I'm so nervous.
Are you?
It's like
I'm going with you.
Part of me is, actually.
Listen.
Nothing's changed
with Brett and I.
I just wanted you
to know that.
And I also want you
to know
that I realize how
important this trip is.
And that I have to take
care of myself.
Oh, baby, I'm so proud
you're my daughter.
Woman on P.A.:
...Please report to gate 52.
Hey!
Come here.
Give me a hug.
Okay.
This is it.
Yeah?
I love you guys.
Love you, too.
I'm going to miss you.
Take care.
Bye, Denise.
Bye, have a great trip.
You be good, okay?
Okay.
Bye.
Good-bye.
Sorry.
Bye.
Josh?
Brett:
Hey, guys.
Josh!
Promised me popcorn.
Wait up.
Well, she's out of the nest...
I guess.
I guess so.
It's weird.
We've done all the damage
we can do, huh?
Listen, Tess...
I think, no...
Look, what happened
wasn't just you, okay?
It was me, too.
Anyway, I'm okay.
I just want to get on
with my life.
I never realized
you had it in you.
You know?
I know you didn't.
♪