♪ I'll be home for Christmas ♪
♪ You can count on me ♪
♪ Please have snow ♪
♪ And mistletoe ♪
♪ And presents on the tree ♪
♪ Christmas eve will find me ♪
♪ Where the love light gleams ♪
♪ I'll be home for Christmas ♪
♪ If only in my dreams ♪
And why are we having a town council meeting here?
You said if you got elected
you'd get the town hall finished once and for all.
Once and for all, that's what you said.
We hit a snag, Hap, that's all.
Find us a doctor yet?
(indistinct chatter)
I call this meeting of the St. Nicholas
veteran committee to order.
First, on the agenda we have just got word
that St. Nicholas has been named one of the top
100 towns of populations under 1,500 in America.
(group chuckling and clapping)
That's wonderful.
Obviously, we're,
we're hoping that this is going to boost our tourist trade.
It better.
Second on the agenda,
selection of the honoree for this year's
grand electrician of the tree lighting ceremony.
Almost everyone in town's already been honored.
Some of them nine or 10 times.
We need more townspeople.
We need a doctor.
Who wants to live in the town without a doctor?
Now, what have you been doing about finding us a doctor?
Well Hap, I ran ads
all over the country.
And?
This is our latest response.
It's another rejection.
This one's from a doctor in Nome, Alaska.
And he doesn't wanna live here?
Too remote, he says.
I don't get it.
I mean, we got a skating rink.
We got the St. Nicholas Literary Society.
We got the world's largest hay bale.
People don't know paradise when they see it.
Maybe it's because we got a woman mayor.
We got a woman sheriff.
I didn't vote for you.
Well, I didn't vote for you either, you old Scrooge.
(chuckling)
Now everybody, listen up.
Hap's right.
If we don't get a doctor by January first,
we're gonna have to close the hospital.
And then without either one of them,
who's gonna wanna raise their children here?
Who's gonna wanna retire here?
Kinda hard driving three hours to the nearest hospital
when you're having a heart attack.
Doesn't anybody here know a good gall dern doctor?
I do.
Bob, I know it's your son and all, but get real.
Mike will never come back here.
Broke my heart when he left the first time.
Mine too.
Well, just trying to help.
How's Mike been since his wife passed away?
It's been four years and
he's not over it yet.
You don't never get over it.
Yeah.
No, but you gotta get on with your life.
He might be better off here.
He sure would.
It's a moot point.
Let's go on.
Didn't Mike used to be kind of sweet on you?
Oh Hap, we were kids.
He's coming home for Christmas, you know?
Yeah, but that doesn't necessarily mean anything, Bob.
Why don't we make him grand electrician this year?
Hello?
Yeah.
And the mayor can ask him to stay on.
Excuse me!
Now don't go doing too much.
You'll scare him away.
I have to declare right now
that this idea does not have the endorsement
of the mayoral office.
You don't have an office.
I will.
That's a great idea.
(indistinct chatter)
Mark my words.
Mike Greiser will never come back here for good.
Please, listen to me!
Just don't want you to get hurt again.
So what is going on with you Mike?
A year ago you would've never given up a case like this.
Single parent thing.
I promised Jilly I'd take her out Christmas shopping.
And as soon as I was ready to walk out the door
this myocardia infraction walked in.
You can't break a promise to a kid, Fred.
Not at Christmastime.
Don't I know it.
Well, if you're really serious about giving it up
I'll do it.
Thanks.
Thank you.
(indistinct chatter)
Mike, you okay?
To tell you the truth Hal, I'm not sure.
You look stressed out.
Maybe that's it.
Well, you've been more
than a little distracted lately.
Huh?
I said--
Listen, I'm really late
for a very important appointment with my kid.
Maybe we can talk about this later, okay?
Okay.
Merry Christmas, kids.
(bells ringing)
Thank you.
Why do we have to go to Iowa for Christmas?
Why can't we stay here with our friends?
Well grandpa's kind of expecting us.
Why can't he come here?
He used to do that.
Well he's, he's getting kind of old, you know.
Yeah, and scarier every year.
Bob, scary?
You must be thinking of somebody else.
I remember this place.
I remember mom saw and elf in the window
and she wanted it,
only it was for display only.
And the guy in the store,
he wouldn't sell it to her.
But she badgered him for an hour
until he finally gave in.
And then she got it home and she thought
it was really ugly,
and she hid it in the back of the coat closet.
Right.
I'm sorry, dad.
For what?
I know it's hard for you to talk about mom.
Since when did you get so smart?
Good upbringing.
You okay?
I'm okay.
How about you?
I miss her.
Yeah.
But I don't think she'd like it very much
if she knew we were moping around here
because she wasn't here.
I think going home and making some popcorn
and watching a Christmas movie would be good for you.
Okay, sounds like a good idea.
Rudolph the Red Nosed Reindeer.
That's what I think.
Okay, doctor.
And after that, Frosty the Snowman.
Oh, you gotta be careful.
Don't mix your medicines.
Side effects.
(phone ringing)
Oh!
Yeah, it's the hospital.
We'll do it when you get back.
Great.
(gentle music)
You're gonna be okay, dad.
You will.
Dr. Chen, Dr. Chen.
Aneurysm.
What happened to Pearson?
I thought she was on call.
Chicago, airplane, snow storm.
(sighing)
(stretcher rattling)
(indistinct chatter)
Mike?
Fred, can you do an aneurysm?
Yeah, sure Hal.
Get in there.
Mike, my office.
I'm sorry, Hal.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
Ever since Thanksgiving I've felt...
I don't know.
Whenever I walk into the OR
I break out into a sweat,
my heart's starts beating faster.
It's been building up for a long time.
Lately, it's gotten worse.
And today for the first time in my life,
I couldn't do my job.
What are you afraid of?
Failing, I guess.
Can I ask you a personal question?
If it would help.
Do you think this has anything to do
with your wife passing away?
She's been gone for four years.
Well, something's going on inside you.
Denying it will only make it worse.
Well how can you deny something
you're not even aware of?
I have an idea.
You're going home for Christmas, right?
Yeah.
Take some extra time.
Now, go home and deal with this, Mike.
Let it go.
You know you're safe there
and you have people all around you
who love you and can help you through it.
I haven't seen most of those people for over 20 years.
Mike, your patients used to know they were in good hands
the moment you stepped into the room.
That is no longer the case.
You're not fit to practice medicine in this condition.
And if you don't do something about it,
you won't have a career.
I know.
Good.
Now get out of here.
Go on.
(trumpet playing)
Oh come on.
Get those ropes tighter.
You're gonna have to get them tighter.
Get them tight.
Tighten them up.
Oh, I gotta get the show on the road.
(crowd cheering)
Very nice, Dave.
Very nice.
Could I have your attention please?
All right.
Now when I call your section,
I want you to pull on those ropes.
You got that?
Yeah!
Okay!
Here we go.
(indistinct shouting)
(cheerful music)
(crowd cheering)
Sorry I'm late!
Again.
Oh Dr. Sarah, mayor.
Oh honey.
It appears that with word of Mike coming home
everybody's gotten just a little overexcited.
What do you mean overexcited?
Well, maybe enthusiastic would be a better word.
You're making me nervous.
Testing, testing, one two three.
You know, we figure he's gonna be coming through here
anytime between now and dinner time,
and a few people just don't mind waiting around.
(indistinct chatter)
Think we overdid it?
I still don't know why we had to come back here.
We never have before.
It's always kind of hard to get away.
Well, with my job and all.
Are you sure grandpa wants us?
Of course I am.
Why would you say that?
He just sounded so grumpy on the phone.
Well that's 'cause he can't believe
he's being charged money just to talk.
I wish he didn't smoke.
It smells.
Maybe you can get him to quit.
Look, there's Tiny's Luncheonette.
Tiny was 300 pounds.
Possible thyroid problem
now that I think about it.
Down there is the hospital.
I worked down there helping Dr. Jenkins.
I wonder know how he is doing.
Wait til you see the town square.
Every year some old farmer will give them
a great big pine tree for a Christmas tree.
Everybody in the town comes out to help decorate it.
And somebody got the honor of plugging in the lights
for Christmas Eve.
Oh, it's really something.
(chuckling)
What's this?
(indistinct chatter)
There he is!
(Deck the Halls)
Hello!
Come on dear!
You must be Mike's daughter.
(crowd applauding)
What's going on?
Well you'll see.
Mike!
Come on, come on.
That's it, that's it, stop the band.
And of course you know Mayor Sarah.
Sarah?
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is my official duty to inform you
that this year
St. Nicholas's favorite son and most illustrious graduate,
other than our own mayor,
Mike Greiser, has been nominated
the Grand Electrician of the town tree
and we'll plug in that tree this Christmas Eve!
(crowd cheering)
(Deck the Halls)
Mayor Gladstone will now present you
with the golden plug.
Mayor?
Um hum.
And a years supply of Fro Kazinsky's famous
Christmas fruitcake.
(crowd applauding)
(cameras clicking)
Smile.
(gentle music)
Hey Mike.
I'm sorry about all that hoopla.
I guess we, I guess we got a little excited.
I was a little surprised.
Yeah.
Well now you can relax a bit.
Anything in particular you want to do while you're here?
Just take it easy.
I was thinking of going and visiting Doc Jenkins.
Oh.
Doc Jenkins passed away about two months ago.
I didn't tell you, Mike,
because I didn't wanna upset you.
Who's running the hospital?
Oh, that'd be Sarah.
But she's a vet.
Yeah but she's mighty good at stitching people up.
She really is.
And even though she's the best veterinarian around
people are a little leery about letting her work on them.
Being as how her idea of what to do for a broken leg is
euthanasia.
Did we forget somebody?
Jilly?
Hey, aren't you freezing?
Come on up here, girl.
You're gonna catch pneumonia.
Come on!
Now what's the matter with you?
She's going through a shy phase.
We've done everything humanly possible
to get ourselves a doctor.
Nobody wants to come and live here.
You think somebody would see the potential.
I don't get it, that's for sure.
Hey you!
I get a whole box of Christmas decorations waiting for you.
I didn't want to hang them until you got here.
Come on, I'll show them to you.
Come on.
I don't cut myself a personal tree anymore.
That one they put up in the square every year,
I consider that mine.
This year it actually is because I donated it.
Generally, I hang these all over the place.
What's the matter with your dad?
I think something's wrong with him.
You mean because it's Christmas
and your mother's not here?
That's what I thought.
But he says no.
It's a mystery.
He always was a little mysterious.
Even when he was a kid.
Really?
How?
He was always keeping things to himself.
You never really knew if he was sad
or happy or sick or well.
He's still like that.
Excuse me.
Do you think we could designate this a no smoking area?
Sorry.
It's a really bad habit, you know.
But it's the only one I have left.
We have to put all those things up?
Maybe we could just put up a few.
Christmas used to be your favorite holiday.
People change, Bob.
Well let's just do it for Jilly.
What do you say?
Sure.
Would you go and get a pair of scissors
in a drawer in the kitchen, please?
You know, Mike
Lori was a wonderful woman and I miss her too.
But there comes a point
when a person has to get on with his life
for the sake of everybody else around him.
It was just not that easy.
I didn't say it was easy.
Dad liked the same books I do.
I guess the room hasn't changed for 20 odd years.
(gentle music)
Sorry!
Sorry I'm late.
I have tonight's agenda right here.
Let's cut to the chase.
Bob, how's Mike doing?
Oh, you know Mike,
he's kind of hard to read.
No, he's not.
It's plain as day on his face.
He's frightened.
He sure didn't act that scared.
He's a nice man.
He was being polite.
Now, Sarah, your honor,
you know St. Nicholas is paradise if you squint.
All Mike needs is a little encouragement.
I wish you'd all come to your senses.
You know, you're going to have to get up the nerve
and ask him one of these days, honey.
I mean, he's our only hope.
All right, all right, I will.
But I refuse to tell him that he's our only chance
to keep the hospital open.
I intend to keep some semblance of pride.
You're not still stuck on him, are you?
Oh, Margie, come on!
That was a long time ago.
Besides, I'm a professional.
And even if I did still have feelings for him,
I wouldn't let that influence my behavior.
Professionals are allowed to have feelings too, you know.
Feelings interfere with getting things done.
You know that, Margie.
(knocking on door)
You're supposed to be asleep.
So are you.
(gentle music)
You know, Jilly,
Bob is the only grandpa you have.
I know.
Maybe you ought to be a little nicer to him.
We don't exactly have a lot in common.
Well, how do you know?
You gotta try to find something.
You know, you'll regret it someday
if you don't get to know him better.
He's a wonderful man.
Do you know he paid cash for my medical school,
doing extra farming for other people.
Because he doesn't believe in loans.
He's an amazing guy.
Well, you get some sleep.
Now.
First you go to Drysdales
and then you go to Nick's for groceries.
Do you remember where they are?
Sure.
Okay.
You don't mind
having Jilly around, huh?
Are you kidding?
Besides, she's going to help me.
Now you go ahead.
It's gonna be fine, here.
Well, you two have fun then, huh?
Or else.
Hey.
What if we go and see the pigs, huh?
Ooh, you don't know what fun is until you've met a pig.
(cheerful music)
(kids shouting)
(door bell jingling)
(indistinct chatter)
Got your items all bagged up, doc.
Well how'd you know what I wanted?
Oh, Bob called.
Said you were coming by, doc.
We're just so glad to have you back.
You used to shovel the snow on our walk every winter
in order to make money for medical school.
Now you remember that?
I sure do, Mr. Drysdale.
Our walk has never been shoveled again by a doctor.
We knew you'd turn to be a great surgeon.
Everybody did.
Well, thanks, Mr. Drysdale,
Mrs. Drysdale.
(door bell jingling)
Wait til you see her.
She's beautiful.
(pig softly oinking)
Here she is.
Isn't she a beauty?
I just got her a week ago.
Yeah, that is breakfast, honey.
Come on.
Here, come on.
It is she okay?
I don't know.
A pig that doesn't want breakfast isn't right,
that's for sure.
I better call Sarah.
And you, stay here with Janet.
Can't I come with you?
No, no, no, no.
No honey, Janet needs you.
Just stay here, okay.
I'll be right back.
Be right back, honey.
I am so sorry about Doc, Mrs. Jenkins.
I really wanted to talk to him while I was here.
I just hope the next doctor we hire is single.
He works hard all his life to make that hospital go.
It's sad to think of so much hard work coming to an end.
Especially with so many attractive, single women
around town.
Well I'm, I'm sure you'll find someone to run the place.
Somebody single.
Gotta be single.
You know Mike, he always followed your career.
It made him so happy
to see you were doing so well for yourself as a doctor.
Well thank you, Ms. Jenkins.
Yeah, you know,
Mike, I've been getting a twinge of rheumatism lately.
Not, not now, mother.
Well, very nice to see you again, doctor.
Let let go of him, mother.
She won't eat at all, and that that's not like her.
I'll get that gate.
I don't think she feels well.
You're probably right, Jilly.
Jilly, you remember Sarah Gladstone?
She was at the tree raising
when you got here the other day.
Hi.
She's Janet's doctor.
Jilly would you, would you hand me the thermometer there?
It's in bag please.
Sarah and your dad were friends in high school.
Did you know that?
No.
He never told me.
He was always a little bit absent minded.
So what do you mean by friend?
Well...
Used to call it going steady back then.
Yeah, I believe that was the correct term.
You're kidding me!
You and my dad?
Unbelievable, I know.
Wow.
So what was he like back then?
Your father?
Well, he was very popular.
He helped everybody.
He was the star of the debate team.
Championship swimmer.
He used to swim the river upstream just for fun.
My dad?
Um hum.
Told terrible, terrible jokes.
They were horrible.
Everybody loved him.
Everybody thought he'd be coming back after college.
Well, Bob, I know what's wrong with your sweet pig here.
I can take it.
She's pregnant.
What?
We're gonna have babies?
Absolutely.
I never heard of a pig delivering in December.
You have now.
So Mike, what do you think of that daughter of mine?
I'm glad she's been so successful.
Can't never reach her.
Always off someplace doing something,
taking care of everything and everybody but herself.
She's always been like that.
Well, since her mother died.
Sarah was so young, I guess in order to get through things,
she had to mother everybody else.
How much do I owe you?
It's on the house, Mike.
You don't have to do that.
Hey, I fed you more growing up than your own folks did.
You and Sarah are the best thing
this town ever accomplished, Mike,
I feel proud to know
I played a part in you're becoming a doctor.
Thanks Nick.
(whimsical music)
(tapping on window)
So he was all dressed in this suit for the prom,
but there was this poor little calf
stuck in the mud by the road.
So he gets out in the rain,
wades through the mud and pulls this calf to safety.
And then the calf turns around and kicks him.
(chuckling)
Think that's when he decided to become a doctor
because he felt that people were a lot safer
and a lot cleaner, too.
He had to go to the prom was mud all over him.
Everybody was joking with him.
What's going on?
Sarah's telling stories about you.
Oh really?
Yeah, well I better be going.
I gotta stop by Saul Winkler's
and inoculate his llamas.
Thanks for coming out.
Just watch her closely and call me when it's time.
Okay.
Say I, I got an idea.
Why don't you take Mike off tomorrow
and then show him all of the old sites, huh?
I'm sure that you two have got a lot to talk about.
Yeah, well, I'm sure she's probably pretty busy, too.
Well, as a matter of fact, I am.
Yeah, well I totally understand.
If I didn't have a meeting, I would do it.
I really would.
Yeah, then take the day off.
You've been working too hard as it is.
The town council will back you on it, I promise.
Well...
How about two o'clock, huh?
I'll take care of Jilly.
Okay, two o'clock then.
Fine.
He'll be waiting for you.
Now is there anything wrong with
having a little bit of fun?
Well...
Ah, come on!
Is it my imagination or are you decorating
a lot more than you used to?
Oh, that's all part of the town council's
plan to revitalize St. Nicholas.
We want people to think of Christmas Eve here
like they think of Mardi Gras in New Orleans.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
Oh, that's all right.
I understand.
Went to the big city.
Learned the difference between Chardonnay and Merlot
and you forgot all about small town life.
I didn't forget at all.
I'd do anything to be able to come back here and live.
Why don't you?
Hey Mike!
Mike, how you doing?
Long time, no see.
Ethan, is that you?
Yeah, hey look doc!
Straight as an arrow!
You were my first splint.
Well, you're a great doctor.
Good to see you again.
Good to see you, too.
Look, I know you did this for Bob.
So did I.
So why don't you just call it a day
and I'll take you home.
Oh, I don't wanna go back home just yet.
So quiet there.
(upbeat country music)
Oh and Twyla put in a dance floor.
I knew it would go, and I invested.
Well now let me get this straight.
You are a vet.
You're the mayor.
And you own part of a dance hall?
And dad's cafe, we're partners.
That's amazing!
Oh, I wasn't exactly--
No, no, no, it's mine.
Thanks.
I wasn't exactly stuck in traffic all day long.
So I had time to invent my own life, I guess.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Why didn't you come back after med school?
Well, I met Lori.
She never could have survived here.
It's funny.
I always thought that you would be the one to come back,
and I would be the one to stay away.
You did, why?
Because you were the town hero.
Ha!
Well if I was such a hero,
then why'd you break up with me?
What?
You broke up with me.
Never.
I never would've done that.
Don't you remember sitting on the rock in the quarry
and it was a hundred degrees and everybody was swimming.
And you said that you thought that it would be best
if we started to date other people in college
because you didn't know what was going to happen.
Well, I seem to recall you thinking
that was a pretty good idea.
Well, I wasn't gonna let you win.
(chuckling)
Why haven't you gotten married?
Haven't ever fallen in love.
Why not?
I don't know really.
Too busy, maybe.
Afraid you'd have to give up doing all those things
you like to do, huh?
Yeah.
Yes, as a matter of fact, I am afraid.
Seen too many relationships ruin careers.
I think you haven't found the right guy.
Not too many would put up with my schedule.
The right guy could.
Everybody says you haven't gotten over
the death of your wife.
Why am I always the last one to hear about these things?
You don't need to get over it, you know.
I don't?
No.
It's really impractical to expect that of a human being.
I miss my mother every day.
So you wind up giving everybody else
what you missed getting in your own life.
(upbeat country music)
I guess so.
Say, did you ever learn how to dance?
Nope.
No?
Well then now's the time to learn.
Come on, let's go!
(indistinct chatter)
(laughing)
(slow music)
♪ One more lonesome Christmas ♪
♪ The years they've been so long ♪
♪ I'm counting the days ♪
♪ Til I'm there with you ♪
♪ Back where I belong ♪
So did you ask him?
What'd he say?
Actually I didn't ask him.
Why not?
Well, we just never got around to the subject.
What's go into you?
This town is in the state of emergency
and you're out all night dancing.
How did you know?
Oh, I, I heard it from,
from Sadie Fikel,
and she heard it from Jesse Flossmore
and she heard it from Connie Hawkins.
I don't know where she heard it from.
Call him right now.
Ask him out again.
He knows we don't have a doctor.
If he wanted the job
all he has to do is ask.
Well, he hasn't seen the hospital for a while.
So give him a tour.
Show him all the new doctor things that we pay for.
Once he sees all those newfangled toys
Doc Jenkins had put in
he'll jump on it.
Just needs a little inspiration.
One more afternoon with you won't make him suspicious.
All right, all right, all right.
I'll call him.
(phone clicking)
Bob, Bob, this is Sarah.
Uh huh.
Is Mike there?
Well, I'm not gonna be gone long.
Well maybe I will.
I don't know.
She's gonna show me around town some more.
Some of the improvements,
strictly business.
Sure dad.
Yeah, we know.
Haven't seen my cologne around here, have you?
Smell okay to me.
Why?
(car horn honking)
Whoops, there she is.
See you later.
Yeah.
He sure is in a good mood.
Sure is.
Hi.
So where are we going?
Oh, the new bank.
The new skating rink.
The hospital.
Oh Sarah.
Okay, come on!
I've been here plenty of times.
No, not since we made the improvements.
It won't take long.
We have a lot of new equipment.
(gentle music)
Oh, it's still the same.
It hasn't changed a bit.
You know, all this stuff here,
this was all Doc Jenkins's idea.
He figured if he made the place look cheerier, brighter,
people wouldn't feel so bad about being here.
It'd reduce their stress about being sick or hurt.
Oh boy.
You know, he's the reason that I became a doctor.
All he ever wanted to do in life was just
make people better.
You know, later on in life,
Doc became kind of rebellious.
He was sick of all the problems with HMOs
and he refused to become a part of one.
So he let people pay whenever they could,
taking barter.
Wouldn't believe how many chickens he had when he died.
I'm amazed it's still in operation.
Boy, if this was in the city.
Hello?
Anybody home?
You open?
Hi Ruby, hi Cleat.
What's the matter?
Grady got him in the eye at practice.
Well, we wouldn't have come in
except it looks worse than usual.
I panicked.
The eye is so close to the brain.
Okay.
Come on in here.
I'll take a look at it.
I'd rather the doc take a look at it.
If you don't mind, Sarah.
No, I don't mind.
Mike?
How'd you like the dance club, doc?
It was fun.
Did I see you there?
Jerry Hopper told me.
Said he saw you and Sarah there,
and you seemed to be having a good time.
Just like in the old days.
There.
Oh boy.
You're gonna have a very cool scar to show your friends
Really?
Oh yeah.
Do you have any adhesive tape, Sarah?
I'll look.
We're out.
How about a large bandage?
All out.
Duct tape?
Ah.
This will do.
Now, you're gonna have to keep an eye on this all night.
Want you to wake him up every couple hours
and look into his good eye and see if it's dilated.
I'm afraid you're gonna have to
sit out a couple of games there, Grady.
Oh!
I can't tell you how grateful we are.
Thanks doc.
Come on.
You all right?
Why don't you show them out.
I hope dad makes it back.
Yeah, I do too.
His car is blocking my plow.
Grandpa!
Whoa, don't be afraid.
That happens all the time.
We just have to turn on this old lamp here.
There we go.
That's nice.
Oh and we gotta...
I'm gonna build up that fire, too.
It's gonna be a while.
You know, your dad used to love to sit
in front of the fireplace and read.
He did?
Yeah.
What else do you know about him?
Well, he used to...
are you sure your don't wanna play
with that computer of yours?
Nah, that's boring.
He didn't like pigs too much.
I do.
I love Janet.
I know, I know.
I'm happy about that.
You know,
I used to be scared of you.
You were?
I'm sorry.
That's all right, that's not your fault.
I, sometimes I am kind of grizzly.
Do you like popcorn?
Well I've got a little popper
that fits right into the fireplace.
Oh, I think it's in the kitchen.
I'll be right back.
(gentle music)
(wind whooshing)
No road, no phone, no doctors.
Two feet of snow,
but at least we have soup.
Let me see.
Split pea or, or chicken noodle?
Oh, this is fine.
Is it?
Oh!
Mmmm, it's good.
There you go.
Not only is she a vet and a mayor
and an entrepreneur,
but she can cook too.
(chuckling)
I still don't understand why you don't have a family.
Don't have enough time.
You gotta make the time.
Jilly taught me that.
She has made everything about my life more meaningful.
I have to admit, sure is nice being home.
Must mean that it's still a great place.
It is.
Then why don't you stay?
Don't answer that, I don't wanna know.
You pulled Pete Peterson out of the water,
gave him mouth to mouth.
You saved his life!
Well, I remember doing that.
I just can't believe that I did.
And the town declared Mike Greiser day.
If I come back here,
it would be a lot different.
What was your wife like?
She was smart,
and funny.
She was different than anyone else I ever met.
I think you did the right thing.
You do?
Absolutely.
Moving away from here gave you experiences
you never would've had here.
That's right.
And Jilly is the best reason of all.
Oh, I should have known.
You all right?
I just...
I've never talked with anybody about this before.
I better get us some light.
Wait a minute.
Thanks.
You're a much better kisser than you were 22 years ago.
I'll get you your blanket.
I'll see you tomorrow morning.
See you.
Good night.
(sighing)
Well.
I wanna thank you for showing me around.
You're welcome.
So look, there's something that I've been,
I've been wanting to ask you,
but I've been so scared of the answer
that I haven't been able to do it,
but now I have to.
See, the whole reason that everybody's been
so nice to you is because first of all,
they really do love you.
But secondly,
because they want you to take over for Doc Jenkins.
Sarah--
If we don't find a doctor
we're gonna have to close the hospital.
This town will die, Mike.
(slow music)
I'd like to help you out.
Really, I would.
But I can't.
You see I...
I just got a promotion.
Oh well, that's good.
That's true.
As a matter of fact,
I just found out about it yesterday morning,
before you picked me up.
As it turns out
I won't even be a able to stay for Christmas.
They need me right away.
I'll be heading up the otolaryngology unit
in Minneapolis.
It's a chance of a lifetime.
Yeah, of course it is.
I'm sorry.
Well, it'll be hard to tell everybody else.
But it was very nice seeing you again
after all these years.
We don't have to...
Goodbye.
He's back!
I called work this morning from the hospital
when the power came back on.
You know, just to, just to,
you know, see how things were going.
I got some wonderful news.
You did?
What?
Well, I got a promotion.
It's a big jump in pay.
It's very prestigious.
The only problem is
they're gonna need me back there right away.
I guess we'll miss Christmas here, Bob.
(slow music)
He got a promotion at the place
where he were works in Minneapolis.
He's going back there.
What?
I can't believe it.
What did we do wrong?
I don't think it's anything we did.
I'm sorry, Hap.
I tried.
He's a hard case.
She did her best.
We knew you did your best, honey.
Well, I don't know about the rest of you,
but I don't feel much like having a meeting tonight.
Me neither.
See ya.
Now we'll reconvene when everybody's got over it.
Come on Hap, I'll buy you a coffee.
(pig softly oinking)
You sure are easy to get along with.
Not like some people I know.
We come back here and my dad gets happy
for the first time in years.
So what are we doing?
We're going home early.
Now he's gonna be all sad again.
You figure it out.
Morning.
Morning, Mike.
Is there coffee?
Yeah, fresh pot.
Listen, Bob.
I'm sorry about this, but there's nothing I can do.
The hospital needs me.
I sure hope you know what you're doing.
I do.
Look, I...
I'm gonna go into town and gas up.
I'll grab some breakfast there and,
and I'll pack when I get back.
I wanna get on the road as soon as possible.
Suit yourself.
Gosh, Mike.
Edith Drysdale ordered extra socks in your size
for the store.
And Nick got in that yuppie ice cream for you.
Well I'm sorry, Dave.
I didn't know.
We'll be all right with the disappointment,
but it's gonna be hard explaining to all our little kids
when they're coming down with the flu and strep throat,
poison ivy and croup.
Not to mention those new viral diseases.
And of course there's always the measles.
Hello?
Anybody there?
Hey Mike.
Hey, cup of coffee and a donut, please, Nick.
Heard you spent the night with my daughter, Mike.
Well we got snowed in.
I understand.
We slept in separate rooms.
I in no way compromised your honor.
It's too bad, but you'd made a great team.
I understand.
Thanks.
You think we're too nosy?
That's not it.
I understand.
(O Come All Ye Faithful)
Sorry things didn't work out, Mike.
You two cut quite a rug on Central.
Well, I didn't see you there that night, Ms. Jenkins.
Oh, I only go once, twice a week.
Everybody told me.
Well, good luck son.
Oh, don't look so sad, Ms. Drysdale.
I'm not the guy you thought I was.
We're just so proud of you, Mike.
We just wish you loved us as much as we loved you.
That's all.
(slow music)
Boy, you sure are in a hurry.
Well, it's a great opportunity.
I'll be head of the nasopharyngeal unit there.
Well, I can't pass this up, Bob.
No, I guess not.
Grandpa!
Something's wrong with Janet.
I went to the barn to visit her
and she's lying on her side and she can't breathe.
You go and stay with her.
I'll call Sarah and then I'll be right out.
Is she gonna be all right?
I don't know, Jilly.
Daddy, help her!
Jilly, we gotta pack the car.
Please!
Lucky I was just down at your neighbors.
Janet can't breathe!
Looks to me like she's in labor,
but I'm no expert on pigs.
Pig can get very violent about their babies, Mike.
I'm gonna need your help.
I was really planning on getting on the road.
Please, daddy, you have to!
Janet needs you!
Tell me what you want me to do.
(piglets squeaking)
Why don't the other babies let that one eat?
This little guy right here?
Oh, oh there you go.
Because he's the runt.
It's nature's way.
But he'll die.
No, he won't not.
Not if we take care of him.
Yeah.
Will he really be all right?
You'll just have to be his mom.
How?
Well be like your mom.
She was good at it obviously.
You turned out well.
If I'm his mom,
who's gonna be mine?
Hmm, that's an interesting question.
I'm not sure I have the answer.
Too bad you and my dad didn't get back together.
Well, I'm afraid that wasn't in the cards.
It's not easy finding good moms.
Honey,
Why don't you do what I did when I lost mine.
What's that?
Pretend she's there.
Talk to her, ask her questions
in your head.
She's never really gone you know.
She's inside of you.
Then you can have her anytime, any way you want.
I want her to be like my mom,
and you.
Thank you, Jilly.
What's Patrick gonna do when I go?
Can't we just stay for Christmas, please dad, please?
I'm sorry, but we can't.
Jilly, sometimes part of being a good mother,
a really good mother,
is doing the very best for your baby.
What about me?
Well.
She'll get over it.
I'm sure she will.
Good luck, Mike.
I mean it.
Bye.
Okay, this is it, huh?
Hey, wait a minute.
There's one more.
What's this, Bob?
I'm going with you.
Well, you don't have to do that.
I'm not gonna spend Christmas here all alone.
Well, what about the farm?
Oh, I already called a neighbor.
He's gonna cut down and take care of things while I'm gone.
Ah, Sarah's gonna take care of Patrick.
We can drop him off on the way out.
(pig oinking)
(knocking on door)
Come on, honey.
Oh sweetheart!
Look at that, look at that.
I can't believe you won't be here
for the lighting of the tree.
Yeah well, Jilly needs me.
At least you're coming back.
Yeah.
Maybe he'll change his mind.
No he won't.
He's obviously just the wrong person.
It's fate.
Yeah right, sure, maybe.
Though he is making a big mistake.
He'll be bored with otolaryngology in a month.
That's nasopharyngeal he's going into.
No, no he told me otolaryngology.
Well, anyway, it doesn't matter.
There's plenty of fish in the sea.
You know, doc,
you've been running your tail off for 20 years
trying to improve things here.
Everybody thinks you're the best thing since
pivot irrigation.
That's very nice of you to say.
Yeah, but
maybe it's time you did something for yourself.
Get something you need.
I have everything I really want.
No you don't.
(slow music)
Yeah, well it's not that easy.
You know how to get a town hall fixed.
You know how to take care of a little pig,
but you don't know how to go after something
you really want.
Don't be afraid, Sarah.
Bye Patrick.
Merry Christmas, honey.
Merry Christmas.
Bye.
(gentle music)
You know, if everyone carried my things around
like that door man of yours...
I'd be decrepit in a week.
Haven't you got some chores for me to do?
We got maintenance men for that.
Bob, you're on Christmas holiday.
Relax.
Look out the window.
Enjoy yourself.
I did that already.
Well try again.
Okay.
(chuckling)
Oh am I glad Christmas doesn't last long.
(slow music)
Excuse me.
Go ahead.
I'm, I'm looking for Mike Greiser.
A doctor Mike Greiser.
He's not here anymore.
He's not?
Nope.
Told me he had a promotion.
Let me guess.
You're the woman who's been running that hospital
back in Mike's hometown.
How did you know that?
Well, Mike mentioned you.
He works on a different floor now.
I see.
And what department is that?
Administration.
Administration?
Yes, didn't he tell you?
But he's a doctor.
He requested a change.
I wish I knew what was going on with him.
Well, to be honest with you, I wish the same thing.
About a year ago
he started having anxiety attacks at work
that got progressively worse until about a week ago
when he suddenly couldn't do his job anymore,
at all.
I thought going home might help him to work things out.
But he came back early and
asked to be transferred to administration.
He asked?
But he told me that...
I see.
Well, if you'd like to see him, I'm sure he is in.
Yeah, I would.
How's it going back home?
You find a doctor yet?
No, we'll have to close the hospital down for good.
That's too bad.
It is.
Sue, is Mike around?
He's up on the roof getting some air.
If you don't mind, I'd like to surprise him.
Thanks.
I'm sure you will.
(traffic whirring)
You didn't tell me you got a promotion in the North Pole.
I guess when I came home,
I remembered how much I like bad weather.
What are you doing here?
I guess it's hard for you to understand.
Absolutely.
It is hard for me to understand.
You're a doctor, Mike.
What are you doing shuffling papers?
I'm not a doctor.
Not anymore.
I still don't understand.
Look Sarah, when I went home
everybody treated me like a hero.
I panicked.
I'm not a hero, Sarah.
I can't even walk into a operating room anymore.
I'm afraid.
I'm not who you thought I was.
I just couldn't stand the thought of
letting any of you down.
Oh Mike, nobody cares if you're a doctor or not.
They care about the man who listens to them when they talk.
Doesn't judge them for their faults.
A man who knows how valuable love is and can talk about it.
It's not what you are or what became
that makes the whole town want you back again, Mike.
It's who you've always been.
I can't go back.
I just haven't got the courage.
What happened, Mike?
Something must have happened to make you feel this way.
I don't know.
You know, you are always your own harshest critic.
Whatever happened, maybe it's time you forgave yourself.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm...
We got another doctor, you now.
We did?
Um hum.
Congratulations.
She'll be moving in in a few days now.
Great.
Where is she from?
From?
Oh, Nome, Alaska.
She wants culture.
So why did you come all the way down here?
Because I decided you are right.
I need to take care of myself
as well as everybody else.
I need to get something I want.
And I thought that was you.
Boy.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to say.
I have nothing to give.
I feel like such a coward.
Courage is not the absence of fear, Mike.
It's taking action in the face of it.
Merry Christmas.
(gentle music)
Dad?
Sarah.
Some things are just not meant to be.
You did the best you could, Sarah.
Everybody knows that.
Daddy, would you mind hugging the mayor?
The forecast, cloudy and windy today
and cold this morning.
What are you two gonna do today?
I'm taking grandpa to the children's museum
for the Christmas festival.
Well,
you're gonna find that
pretty enlightening, huh?
And then we're gonna do some skating.
You sure you're up for that?
Well if I'm not we'll soon find out.
(chuckling)
Oh I'm late.
I gotta go.
Have a nice day.
See you tonight.
Well, at least he doesn't have to wear a beeper anymore.
Yeah.
I can't send her home.
You know, she's not stable yet.
Anything could go wrong.
I just want to keep her one more night for observation.
There's no justification.
Justification.
I'm having schpillties over this case.
That's not justification enough?
Look, Fred. I understand your line of thought.
But hospital policy dictates that she has to be sent home.
Hospital policy is endangering my patient.
You know, if anything happens and it costs more
to bring her back than to have her stay here one more night.
No.
Mike, please.
I feel very strongly about this.
There's nothing I can do.
You know, you used to be such a good doctor.
How'd you get to be such a good bureaucrat?
I did not become a doctor
so I could risk people's lives
by sending them home from the hospital too early.
I'll get back to you.
What's the problem?
The problem?
Medicine is not supposed to be like this.
I'm sick and tired
of business being more important than making people better.
Uh huh.
I can't believe I have to risk lives
to save a company money
that's supposed to save lives.
I've been wondering how long it would take.
What?
There are very few doctors as talented as you.
Even in your own hometown
they're closing the hospital because they can't find anyone
competent enough to run it.
They're not closing the hospital.
That's what your friend, Sarah, told me.
She told me they just hired somebody.
(slow music)
She took a big risk coming all this way to see you.
That woman has courage.
Daddy!
Daddy, daddy, daddy, daddy!
Grandpa's in the emergency room.
What?
(indistinct chatter)
Hey Fred.
So this is what you do.
He's my father.
Cardiac arrest.
You see anything interesting?
(machine beeping)
(dramatic music)
He's tachycardic.
Let's go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Let's go, let's go, clear the hallway.
I want those blood gasses, stat.
OR seven, I think.
OR seven, let's go!
Let's move!
Okay, let's go!
Tachycardic
I knew this would happen, I knew it!
It's gonna be all right.
No, he's not!
He's old and he smokes and it's his heart.
They're gonna do everything they can for him.
You go, dad!
Jilly.
You can save him.
Please, daddy, you can save him.
You've got to, please!
You sit in the waiting room, okay?
(slow dramatic music)
(machine beeping)
Clamp.
Sponge.
(machine beeping rapidly.)
His blood pressure's bottoming out.
His O2 sats are dropping.
Let's go, let's go!
More clamps.
Bigger clamp.
Come on people, we're losing him.
What's the pressure?
Pressure?
More sponges.
Nurse.
Clamp.
I'm taking over.
You sure?
I'm sure.
Is he gonna be okay?
I don't know, Jilly.
I have to wait and see.
I'm gonna stay up with him all night.
Are you okay here?
Yeah.
And Jilly.
Yeah?
Want you to know
I love you very much.
I know dad.
(slow music)
Can you hear me, dad?
I know we haven't seen each other very much
in the last 20 odd years.
I just didn't realize how fast time was passing.
I'm not ready for this.
And neither are you.
You've got a lot of chores
waiting for you back home.
Fence needs mending.
Barn is a mess.
And Jilly needs you.
So do I.
Don't leave me dad.
Don't make me feel like a failure again.
(machine beeping)
Where you going?
Don't tell me you were worried.
I wasn't.
I knew I was in good hands.
I wish I was as sure as you.
Are you gonna
tell me what's going on now?
I thought I lost it.
You mean Lori?
I suppose so.
But it wasn't your fault.
I was the head of the surgical team.
It was up to me.
I thought we got all of it, but we didn't.
I failed her.
And you stewed on it.
All this time.
I couldn't let go.
Maybe you thought you
you could keep all those around you safe.
And you found out
it just wasn't possible.
All my life
all I've ever wanted to do was make people better.
Why couldn't I do that for her?
It wasn't up to you.
I'm gonna be all right son.
Hey Jilly.
Grandpa.
Yeah, he's gonna be okay.
Can I see him?
Yeah, come on.
Jilly.
Now will you quit smoking?
Oh good, just what I need.
A lecture.
When you get out of the hospital
I'll take care of you.
You will?
I have to practice.
I'm gonna be a doctor when I grow up.
I bet you will.
Just like your old man.
♪ Oh Christmas tree ♪
♪ You share a wondrous message ♪
♪ You must proclaim ♪
♪ The savior's birth ♪
♪ Goodwill to man ♪
♪ And peace on earth ♪
♪ Oh Christmas tree ♪
♪ You share a wondrous message ♪
(indistinct chatter)
Welcome everybody to the 67th annual
St. Nicholas Christmas Eve celebration.
Things have been kind of tough
for St. Nicholas this past year.
We lost Doc Jenkins.
There's no reason that we shouldn't celebrate this holiday
that exemplifies the people of this town.
People who are generous and giving.
And because we have not found a doctor
to replace Doc Jenkins,
the hospital will have to close.
Still,
(crowd moaning)
still it's imperative that we continue
to celebrate this holiday
the way we always have,
with joy and with faith.
The things happen as they do because there's a reason.
And we shouldn't let this setback
make us feel like failures.
And since this year's honoree for grand electrician
was unexpectedly called away,
leaving us with nobody to replace him,
I am--
Wait a minute!
Excuse me.
(indistinct chatter)
Excuse us.
Wait a minute.
Sorry, excuse use.
Uh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry we're late.
My dad had a heart attack in Minneapolis.
(crowd gasping)
He's fine.
He's gonna be just fine.
He's gonna be up and back home as soon
as they can get him here.
Oh Mike, you bring him back here.
We'll let him sty with us
for just as long as it takes for him to recover.
That's right, we will.
(indistinct chatter)
Well I did wanna say um,
you all have always treated me like a hero and
it's you that are really the heroes.
I mean you've stayed here.
You've dedicated your whole lives
to helping other people.
I mean you've made your own lives
but, well you've created the futures of others.
And I think that's great.
I really do.
And I want that example for my own daughter.
So, if it's still okay with all of you
I'd like to accept the position.
(crowd gasping)
As the head of the St. Nicholas hospital.
I wanna come home.
(crowd applauding and cheering)
Here we go children.
Make that connection.
Plug it in!
Get ready!
Watch this now, watch this.
Come on.
(crowd cheering)
(festive music)
Sarah.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
What's wrong?
So all of a sudden you just got rid of all your problems?
No, not all of a sudden.
It's taken a long time
and the help of a lot of people.
What if it all comes back?
That'll make them hurt.
I don't wanna hurt anybody.
I'm in a place that I love.
I'm very happy.
Are you sure?
I'm very sure.
Why did you tell me you'd found a doctor?
I didn't want your pity.
Oh yeah?
Well...
I shouldn't have lied to you.
You deserve more than that.
Yes I do.
You deserve somebody that admires you
and has all of his life.
Absolutely correct.
You deserve someone who respects you
for what you've done with your life.
And wants nothing more than to spend the rest of his life
with you.
Yes!
I told you all along she'd pull it off.
♪ Peace on earth and mercy mild ♪
♪ God and sinners reconcile ♪
♪ Joyful all ye nations rise ♪
♪ Join the triumph ♪
Merry Christmas, Mike.
Merry Christmas, Jilly.
Merry Christmas, Sarah.
Merry Christmas, grandpa.
♪ Christ is born in Bethlehem ♪
♪ Hark the herald angels sing ♪
♪ Glory to the newborn king ♪
(gentle music)
(ACI music)
(Pearson Television International music)