(CATCHY MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, yeah,
my number's winning today.
(YOUNG MEN HOOTING
AND FLIRTING)
Yeah, I'll play.
# Yeah, baby
# I like it like that
# I got soul
I got soul
# I like it like that
# Hey, baby
# I got soul
I got soul #
(MEN FLIRTING AGGRESSIVELY)
You dropped something, baby.
You dropped something.
Word up.
You dropped... My heart, baby.
Can I step on it?
# I like it like that
# Yeah, baby
# I want it like that
# I like it like that
# I got soul
I got soul #
Eighty-nine minutes! Hah!
(CHILDREN'S VOICES)
(THUMPING ON DOOR)
What do you think they're doing?
Come on!
Get off of me!
Go play with your dolls and...
MINNIE: Let me see!
LI'L CHINO: You're getting me!
Relax.
I took care of it.
# I like it
I like it
# I like it like that
Hey, you're knocking down
my ceiling!
MEN: (CHANTING) Go, Chino!
Go, Chino! Go, go!
Go, Chino! Go, Chino!
Go, Chino!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
Go, Chino! Go, Chino!
Go, Chino!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
WOMAN: Stupid!
What are you, fucking stupid?
What's up with you?
What the fuck are you doing?
You got to finish.
You're gonna break
my back, Lisette.
What are you doing?
Come!
You always got to ruin it, right?
It's not me!
It's Mrs. Gonzales
and her fucking broom!
- MINNIE: Come on!
- And them!
- Come on!
- Hey, don't make me
come out there!
Come on, let me look!
LI'L C: No!
- Let me look!
- Look!
Stop looking at the clock!
(MOANING)
Eighty...
(ALARM CLOCK RINGS)
Still going!
Still...
I can go on and on and on.
I can sell this shit to Duracell.
Get off me!
Stay there!
(SCREAMING)
(THUMPING, SCREAMING)
Oh, that's it!
Get off of me!
Oh, look what you did!
Chino!
Look, I'm not
playing with you! Stop!
Hey!
Dad, she started it.
What'd I tell you
about hitting her?
If I hit somebody
smaller than me,
I'm a punk.
- CHINO: That's right!
- (DOORBELL RINGS)
- Li'l C's gonna get beaten!
- Shut up!
Move, move.
Look what you did!
(KIDS ARGUING)
I'm not moving anymore!
- Yes, you are!
- No, I'm not!
Mom!
Surprise.
- Hi.
- Hi, Maggie.
You need something?
Uh, actually, I just came up
to show you the paper.
Look, Chino's number almost hit.
It did?
Cover yourself.
I'm sorry.
Was I interrupting something?
I just wanted to show Chino
how close he came
to being a winner.
Bye.
I can't have nothing in this house!
They break everything!
- I'll buy you a new one.
- Oh, yeah, right.
When you're still paying
for that stupid bike.
I'm a bike messenger.
Where are you going?
Chino, I just...
I'm gonna go off.
I should get out of here.
- What about dinner?
- Chino, I just
want to go down
to Alexis' to hear my tape.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Baby.
Here, look...
Find yourself a stereo, okay?
I'll buy you whatever you want.
Promise.
- Ow, my breast.
- Oh, you found one?
I'm sorry I don't
have big tetas
like Magdalena, all right?
Magdalena...
Do you know what you got
that she don't?
Huh?
My heart.
It doesn't beat for Magdalena.
It doesn't beat for anybody else...
Except you.
Do you know what I want?
No?
Do you know what I really,
really, really want?
What?
I want you to cook.
Oh!
I hate my life.
I hate it.
Hey...
I'm your life.
You hate me?
No.
(KIDS SHOUTING)
Minnie!
That's it.
Lisette...
Come on, Lisette.
- Lisette...
- Mommy!
-Where...
Where're you going?
-Alexis'!
Don't hang out there all night!
LISETTE: Ooh, Alexis, look.
This is the one.
It has a CD
and a cassette recorder.
Why are you even bothering, Nana?
He's gonna have
that stereo on layaway
for the next three years,
just like the VCR
and the furniture
that he promised.
Uh, look, Alexis, not for nothing,
but at least he supports
his family.
That's true.
And he's good-looking.
You got that.
All I'm saying, Nana,
is that, if you want a stereo,
you're gonna have to look into
getting it yourself.
Oh, you gonna lend me the money?
Lisette, why don't you
get back into modeling?
Alexis, when was I into modeling?
Don't you remember?
They gave you $10
to put your picture
in the beauty parlor window?
Remember?
It was at Novia's place.
- Oh, that's right.
- Oh, you're paid.
My wife wants to be a model.
What?
- GUY: Yeah, right.
- Yo, yo, yo, yo,
with them tetas?
Look, it ain't like you got
to have the perfect body
to be a model, okay?
You just got to have the heart.
That's right and she's got corazon.
Hey, hey, hey.
My baby has the heart, okay?
There's only one thing
that you don't have,
and that's tetas.
(ALL LAUGHING)
- True, true, true.
- Hey, yo, Jack!
Papi, let's go play the numbers.
- What's up, my man?
- You know what numbers
I want to play, right?
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait a minute.
You got money to play the numbers,
but you don't got money
to buy me a stereo?
Look, this money's gonna
go to our future, okay?
- Go win the numbers.
- Okay, man.
Not gonna go into this garbage
that you want to go
to modeling and school.
I don't even want
to be a model, okay?
I was just trying
to do you a favor
and get my own stereo,
because I know you ain't even
gonna get me one.
- Yes, he will.
- That's right, I will.
I'll go down to Byron's right now,
and put $5 on any stereo you want.
Yeah, right.
That's you all over.
The Layaway King.
Give me my paper.
(ALL CLAMORING)
What happened?
(GLASS SHATTERING)
MAN: Blackout! Blackout!
(ALARMS BLARING)
Minnie, stop crying.
It's all right.
- MINNIE: (CRYING) I'm scared.
- Here, C, take the baby
with you.
Are you saying I can't
get you a stereo?
Oh, now you're gonna
start stealing, Chino?
You go out there,
I bet you get busted.
Chino don't get
busted.
(SPANISH BALLAD PLAYING)
Just relax, okay?
I'll get you out of here.
Why is he crying?
Is he sick or something?
No, he's not crying, all right?
- Oh, fucking...
- He looks
pretty hysterical to me.
Well, he's not, all right?
He's not crying.
He's laughing, all right?
We laugh like that, okay?
Right, Chino?
Oh, that's so funny!
Funny!
Hey, mama.
Yo, no disrespect,
but that ass is slamming!
Oh, you looking good!
That's my wife.
I'm gonna marry her.
You're a sexist pig.
Get those fake nails
out of my face, Alexis.
Ooh, no disrespect,
but that ass is slamming.
- You nasty.
- Ooh, that's my husband.
- You better stop, stop,
you embarrassing me.
- That's the father of my baby.
You fucking nasty. Stop!
Oh, you're embarrassing me.
(BOTH TALKING)
Wait. He wants me
to play his number.
All you've got is $5,
and he wants you to spend it
on the numbers?
- That's right.
- He's hopeless.
Been playing the number since
Minnie was two.
- So what?
- It's got to come out.
That shit of his
is gonna hit big, man.
Good thing you're
good-looking,
because that's all you got.
So what's his bail?
- $1,500.
- What?
-For a fucking stereo?
That's bullshit.
-$1,500...
- Angel.
- Angelito...
No, no, Lisette.
I got to get my car
out of the shop. No. No.
Fuck him. Did I tell him
to break into Byron's?
No. Thank you.
- Stupid.
- What?
- What are you looking at?
- Come on, Alexis.
- I don't have
that kind of money.
- Yeah, Alexis.
What about the money
you're saving
to cut your dick off?
Yeah. Lisette,
that is so foul.
Oh, shit, man!
- Oh, shut up.
- You're nasty. I'm outta here.
- Go.
- No! No, no, no.
I don't use my operation money
for nobody, okay?
You're nasty.
Look, look, Alexis,
you give me $5, I'll chop
your shit off for you.
- This shit is nasty, stop it!
- Lisette! You could
do the modeling!
- Like, be serious.
- Again with
the modeling, Alexis?
Shut up. Come on.
You could make his bail.
Go down to the modeling school.
Lisette... Shut up,
this isn't funny.
Look, I don't even got train fare.
You got the $5.
That's not enough
to go down there
and play his number.
- Fuck his number.
- (GROANS)
Lisette!
Lisette, you better play his
number, man. That's Chino!
Mami's so beautiful.
Come down.
-He'll see you.
-Papi's not there.
Let's go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go...
Alexis, you're such a coward!
You told me you were
going to go with me.
Let's go.
I don't want to go.
You go and ask her yourself.
- Go. Go on.
- Alexis, let's go!
Look, I don't
want her to see me
all tacky like this, okay?
Look, I rushed
out of the house
without doing my makeup,
and, like, this blouse
doesn't fit me right.
Lisette, I don't want...
Ooh, ooh, ooh...
Let me see if I have a picture.
Oh, which one do you think
I should give her?
Whichever one you don't care
about getting ripped up.
MAMI: This is not my son.
You tell him
that if he keeps on
calling the house,
your father's gonna go
over there and he's
gonna kick his ass.
He just wanted you to see what
he looked like.
All you people think
is about what you want.
Well, I'm sorry.
I don't got what you want.
- $1,500!
- Okay, Mami.
What am I, a fucking bank?
No, all right, then,
just lend me $2.50
so I can take the train...
-I don't have any money!
-...get this job.
$2.50, Mami, that's it.
Give it to me, quick.
Here comes Papi.
PAPI: What does she want?
Ma, please, all right?
Chino got busted.
Mami, he did not
get busted, all right?
What'd that crazy
Puerto Rican do?
Killed somebody?
No, he didn't kill somebody.
It's a mistaken
identity, all right?
So, what's
she gonna do now?
Go on welfare?
I'm gonna get a job, all right?
She wants train fare.
Why you got
to tell him everything, Mami?
What do you mean,
why's she got
to tell me everything?
Because I care about her
and she cares about me.
You don't want to work.
Fine, okay, forget it.
Forget I even asked you.
That's just another excuse
for her to get
money out of you.
PAWNBROKER: I can't take this.
It's dipped.
He gave you
something dipped?
That's too shady.
Give you $35 for
your wedding ring,
$40, if it's not engraved.
- There you go.
- Alexis.
Why?
Forget it.
That way, you could
have train fare,
you could play Chino's number,
and you can have $30 left over.
My wedding ring
stays on my finger, all right?
No. Lisette!
Yeah, so why don't you
sell your botanica
to get your operation?
Aye, don't compare my botanica
to your marriage, okay?
Well, don't compare
my marriage
to your botanica.
Look, if somebody steals
from my store,
I got insurance.
Somebody steals your man,
you got played.
That's a big difference, mama.
Yeah, well, unlike you,
Alex, all right,
I was born with
all the insurance I need.
Oh, hey, don't even be perpetrating
like you got a body,
Miss Thing,
because, not even, okay?
You know something,
you are so superficial, right?
'Cause it's not just
a physical thing, all right?
What Chino and I got is, like,
spiritual and shit.
But, you see, you're on
the materialistic level.
You wouldn't even understand that.
Mira, Oprah, I do for myself.
I don't need nothing from nobody.
(CURSING IN SPANISH)
BOY: Yeah!
Yo, C, where you at, C?
C, you in here?
Come on.
You stealing from Mr. Soto?
Get the fuck out of there.
Don't tell my father.
- Your pop's in jail!
- No! Not true! He's working!
Guess what I heard?
That your father was in jail
sucking my father's dick.
Shut up!
Yo, when you stop stealing toys
and you're ready
to make some money...
Come talk to me.
All right?
Jack!
Oh, here you go,
wasting money on the numbers,
and I'm ignorant?
I need to play Chino's number.
Hey, Lisette!
You owe me $3.50.
- What?
- Li'l Chino stole
another car from the store.
- Alexis, lend me $3.50.
- I don't know why you keep
thinking my last name
is "Lend-me."
"Alexis, lend me."
I don't got no money.
You ain't got no money
and you're playing
the numbers?
I ain't playing, all right?
I'm just talking.
Mm-hmm.
Look, either you give me the money
or he brings the car back, okay?
Where's my father?
You stole another car
from Mr. Soto, right?
Get away from me.
I don't even want to see you.
Where's my father?
You tell him he's at work.
Your abuela says he's working.
Where is my father?
- Where is he?
- MINNIE: Where's my father?
Where's my father?
(PRAYING IN SPANISH)
Where is my father?
Where is my father!
You want to know
where your father is?
He's in jail, all right?
You're father's in jail!
(YELLING)
ROSARIA: Hey, don't you
close the door on me!
- Where's my papi?
- You're trying to make my son
look bad in front of the kids!
You are jealous
because they prefer
my son over you!
(RADIO BEGINS PLAYING)
I am leaving!
You wanted your mommy?
You can have your mommy!
Grandma is leaving.
Come on, where's Papi?
LI'L C: Where's
my father?
TOGETHER: Where's my father?
He's not coming home, all right?
Where's my father?
When is he coming home?
(THUMPING ON FLOOR)
Where's my father?
(MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
When's my father coming home?
(SHOUTING LYRICS)
(POUNDING STOPS)
(SIGHS)
When's my father
coming out of jail?
I don't know.
When is he?
C!
Where are you...
Where are you going?
Out.
Wait a minute.
I want that car
you took from Mr. Soto.
It's mine.
Ooh, Lil C's gonna get a beating!
- She can't hit me.
- Go get your father's belt.
He was wearing it
when he got busted.
Oh.
Come here.
You ain't gonna beat me.
Oh, no?
This will hurt!
Here, Ma.
- That ain't gonna hurt.
- Give me that!
Vinnie Vega's mom
beats him
with a hairbrush!
Vinnie Vega's a punk.
I ain't a punk.
You and Pee Wee go in the room.
- But I don't want to!
- Come on!
Don't fight with me, okay?
Just watch him!
(WHINING)
Think I'm scared?
I ain't scared of Papi,
I ain't scared of you.
If I hit you with this,
will you stop stealing?
I don't know.
Why do I got to treat you
like a baby, C?
Your father's not here.
- That makes you
the man of the house, right?
- Yeah, so?
So, if you act like a man,
I'm gonna treat you
like a man,
but if you mess up,
like stealing and shit,
you're not gonna be a man
in my eyes anymore.
Papi stole that stereo.
You saying he ain't a man?
Huh?
I don't know what I'm saying.
I need your father here.
Just help me out here, C, okay?
I need you to grow up
for a minute and help me out.
Thanks.
Okay, how do I look?
- (SPEAKING SPANISH)
- Why?
Well, you've got back, baby,
your face is beat down,
but you're missing something.
- Alexis, thank you so much.
- I'm gonna lend you my tits,
and you're lucky that
I'm you're sister, okay?
Don't get happy,
and be quick about it, okay?
I'm gonna show you how to walk.
- I know how to walk, Alexis.
- Not how to walk with grace.
Just watch.
Bop. Pose. Move.
Pose and feel it, oh.
Oh. Ooh.
And strut, bom, bom,
work, and pivot, bop!
Yes, that's it.
Work it, girl.
Feel it.
Yes, you better go,
Latin Cindy Crawford,
like that.
- I could be a model.
- No, you are a model.
- Say "Yo soy una modela!"
- Yo soy una modela!
(LATIN MUSIC PLAYING)
(LAUGHS)
You have a great look.
Just great.
However,
you're going to need
some new photographs.
For $75, I can...
Hi. How you doing?
$25 to process your application.
Oh, look, it says right here
that the, um, government
pays for it.
(VIDEO GAME BEEPING)
We don't see you
without an application.
(GAME BEEPING)
Oh, so it's like that, right?
Like what?
I have an appointment.
They're just trying
to get $25 out of you.
- This shit is a rip-off!
- Excuse me. This is my desk.
Do you want to leave?
No, not until you
give me back my $2.50.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
My train fare I spent coming
up to this fucked up place.
I'm not trying to be a model.
- I'm trying to hire one.
- You played me to think
that shit was real.
Oh...
I'm sorry.
You must be
from the record company.
Hi, my name is Jasmine.
Come right in.
We've been expecting you.
So is this a video or print job?
Neither.
My boss has a dinner meeting
with the Mendez brothers.
He wants them to have
something pretty to look at.
I don't think you have what I want.
Hi.
Put me through to Price.
That agency was a nightmare.
I'm through doing this, Price.
(HUMMING)
That's a Mendez song.
They're my favorite group.
Hi. I'm Lisette Linares.
Model extraordinaire.
Want to see my book?
I have to look like a model.
- I want my skin
to be glowing.
- You're gonna look glowing.
Papi's number came up.
What?
Lisette, I told you
to play Chino's number.
You didn't play Papi's number?
Those numbers never
pay anything anyway.
Right?
$6,000, Lisette.
Look, I didn't have enough
money to go to
the record company
and play your number.
I been playing that number
every day for five years
and it finally came up, Lisette.
Finally came up,
and you tell me
you didn't play it?
I'm sorry, Chino.
That gonna get me out of here?
Chino, I'll get you out.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Mira, they're gonna pay me $400
just to go to dinner
with the Mendez brothers.
You are not going anywhere
Do you hear me?
How am I supposed to get money
for your bail?
You don't worry about money, okay?
I worry about money.
All right?
I'll just stay in here
until my trial.
How are you gonna put
food on the table
when you're locked up?
You're gonna have to go on welfare.
- No. No, no. Uh-uh.
- Just for a little bit.
Because my mother didn't raise
no welfare case, all right?
Oh, you think I want my family
on welfare? Huh?
You think I want that?
Look, Lisette...
I'll lose it, okay?
I'll go crazy in here
if I got to think about you
with other guys.
There's nothing going on
with you and Magdalena, right?
No.
Yeah, well,
everybody's saying shit,
Chino, you know?
Oh, oh, everybody's saying shit.
So that's what this is about, huh?
You're gonna go with
those guys to spite me
for something
I didn't even do, right?
That's nice, Lisette.
No, I just want to have
some insurance, Chino.
If somebody steals you
away from me, what do I got?
Nothing, right?
I don't want to be
left with nothing.
Nothing?
How could you say that?
Mami, you see this ring
on your finger?
That's all the insurance
you need from me.
You got to trust me.
And I got to know
I could trust you.
You see, that's what
this is all about. Trust.
Why don't you forget
that job, okay?
And go to welfare.
These are yours?
Yeah, it's a...
It's an emergency thing.
You know, while Chino's in jail.
It's not, like,
really welfare, man.
We didn't even fill out
the application yet.
Lisette, food stamps are for food.
Pa la comida.
You can't buy
diapers and soap with this.
I thought maybe you could
do me a favor and take them.
I don't have any money left
and that's all they gave me
was the stamps.
I really need the diapers.
You trying to make
my father cheat the state?
Because if he says
he can't take 'em,
he can't take them.
Okay, I'll let you have
the diapers and the soap,
but not the cigarettes, okay?
No, no, no, no, Papi.
No, don't let her
pay for nothing
with it, okay?
(MR. SOTO SPEAKS SPANISH)
No.
As a matter of fact,
you should report her ass
to welfare.
Why don't you mind
your fucking business?
Hey, you watch your language
in front of my grandson.
That's right, Lisette,
because nobody told you
to come into this store, okay?
You see the sign outside?
It says "Magdalena's."
That's right, this is my store.
So if I tell you to
step off, you step off.
I'm gonna have to call the police
and have them haul
your ass out of here.
Well, my husband's dick has
my name on it, all right?
And I don't need no cops
to haul your ass off anywhere.
Because I swear to God, Magdalena,
you keep running after my husband,
I will pull that
pharmaceutical blonde shit
out of your head so fucking fast...
Hey, hey.
Take this and go, okay?
I am so scared of you, bitch,
sitting with
that fat old welfare check.
(ALL SHOUTING)
Here, why don't you
take the cigarettes and go?
Yeah, at least my kids know
who their father is!
You belong in a fucking welfare...
(ALL CLAMORING)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
Son of a bitch!
You son of a bitch!
# You'd better
change your ways
# Before you lose me
(RADIO SHUTS OFF)
We don't have to go on welfare.
C, did I tell you to come in here?
I can make us some money.
Not stealing.
- How?
- Looking out for David.
Not dealing or anything.
He's gonna pay me to watch out
for the cops.
No.
I'm the man of the house.
I make the money.
And I'm the mother,
I worry about the money.
I don't want anybody
calling you welfare names.
I can take care of it, C.
You don't got to worry.
Just don't make me worry about you
running around
with David and all them.
Okay?
- Okay, C?
- Okay.
I'm hungry.
# You'd better change
# You'd better
change your ways
# Before you lose me
# A few strikes out
See, the game is in there
# You'd better change
# You'd better
change your ways
# Before you lose me
PRICE: Okay, first of all,
by some fluke of nature,
I was not born a Latino.
However, I do have
a Puerto Rican assistant.
Come on, Price, an assistant?
An assistant, but she's more
than an assistant,
she's like my right hand.
Yeah, so where is she?
She's at the office, working late.
She'll be here any minute.
Hi. I'm Lisette.
I'm sorry I'm late.
This is Lisette.
Lisette, um...
Linares.
My assistant.
This is, uh, Tony Mendez
and Ricky Mendez.
I am your biggest fan.
I just got to say that you are
even more fine in person.
Thank you.
Could I talk to you for one second
about that shoot we had
this afternoon?
-One sec. Excuse us.
One second.
-We'll be right back.
God bless you, boys.
(INAUDIBLE)
So, okay, okay, tell me,
what do you want me to say?
What should I, you know?
I don't mean to hurt your feelings,
but you're not right for this job.
Here's $50 for your trouble.
Wait, wait a minute.
Val said $400.
Don't you get it?
Val is trying to fuck me up.
Excuse me!
Look, Mr. Price.
I can do this, okay.
I mean, I know everything
about those guys.
I know all the words
to their songs...
I want a bottle of Champaign now.
I know why Ricky never smiles,
wanna know why?
- I don't care.
- Because he has crooked teeth.
His cousin said that
in Salsa magazine. See?
You didn't know that
about them, right?
No, I didn't know that.
You didn't know
that about them.
I know that about them.
Come on, man, you need me.
Yeah.
No, you know what I need?
I need her.
That's what I wanted.
That's what I ordered.
Here.
Now you have $100, okay?
Please, just get out of here.
Uh, I can... Thank you,
I can take myself out.
That's terrific.
What can I say, guys, huh?
Dragging you all the way down here.
It seems my assistant...
Lisette.
Lisette...
Is having these painful,
terrible ulcer attacks,
um, so I had to send her home.
- Is she okay?
- Oh, she's gonna be fine.
I'm just sorry
she couldn't have
told you her ideas,
but, now, one of them...
- You're back.
- I'm back.
- But you're so sick.
- I feel much better.
-But you don't look so hot.
You really don't.
-No, I'm fine, really.
I mean, I didn't want
the Mendez brothers to think
I couldn't do my job.
Yeah, uh, Price was
telling us you have
some ideas for our group.
I do. I do have...
We're thinking about marketing...
Price, Price...
Let her talk.
Okay.
Okay, I got, I got a lot of ideas,
but, um, my first idea,
and, I don't want to diss...
But I, uh...
I think you should
get your teeth fixed.
- Huh?
- (LAUGHS)
My teeth? What the fuck
is wrong with my teeth?
There is nothing wrong
with his teeth.
I tell him all the time
about his teeth.
Ricky, look,
let me tell you something.
I think that you're really fine.
But, I mean,
sometimes I see you
in your videos, right?
And you look so sad
and serious, you know, like,
like you don't want to smile.
Yeah, and he sucks on his lip.
Like that.
- Uh-huh, yeah.
- He does that every time.
I can't wear braces.
I got an image.
Nobody wants you to wear braces.
Who said...
That's not gonna happen.
He doesn't need braces.
My sister Alexis
is all about her image.
She wore braces.
She had them
in the back of her teeth.
Nobody could see them.
Yo, Rick, that's a fat idea, man.
You should listen
to this girl, man.
Yeah, I mean, listen,
we're just being straight
with you.
- Yo, thanks for everything,
man.
- I think he's drunk.
Our lawyers'll be
in touch, all right?
- I am very happy.
- Better be all that.
All right, and more...
You can't leave me
with him, please.
- Can I take you home?
- Oh, guys, guys,
I can take her home,
it's right on my way.
You live in the Bronx?
Yeah, well, I mean, I can...
It's not far from me.
It's not far.
I know when I'm not wanted, man.
Listen, baby, maybe
some other time.
- Take care.
- Okay. Take it easy.
- Bye, Ricky.
- Bye, Lissy. Be cool.
- Yo, we'll be in touch.
- All right, you guys.
Later, Price.
Bye!
What a night.
Oh, I can't believe it, man.
Tony and Ricky Mendez.
They were so nice.
They'd better be nice.
I'm doubling their
record sales.
I really like this job.
Job? Who said
anything about a job?
Val said that if it
worked out, you know,
maybe I could be your
assistant for real.
I helped you sign them.
No. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. I signed them.
I. Me.
I signed the Mendez brothers.
Maybe Tony Mendez
thought you were cute.
No, no, no, no.
They liked my ideas.
Look... There's no job.
Whoa. Hey.
Whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
You said... You said
you were gonna drive me home.
To the Bronx?
Are you out of your mind?
No, no.
Cab fare, yes.
I don't think so.
Oh, oh, I think so.
Here. Here's more money.
Look, don't make me go off,
all right?
You don't want to see me go off.
I don't want to
see you "go off"?
What does that mean?
I don't want to
see you go off?
Maybe I do.
But I want to see you get out.
That's what I want. I want.
Now is the time
to get out of my car.
Come on, we've had fun.
Time to go. Taxi!
Out we go. Come on, come on,
come on, let's go.
Let's go!
Look, how about I
tell Tony Mendez you didn't
even drive me home.
Ooh, yeah, let's do that.
Come on.
Or how about I tell him
I'm not your assistant?
- What's that?
- His phone number.
Oh, yeah? Really?
It doesn't matter, I memorized it.
Let's see it.
555-2803. Get in.
Too much air for you?
Yeah, could you just
watch the road, all right?
Keep your eyes forward
and watch the road.
What are you doing?
Look, give me, I'll put it, I'll...
Look, you're gonna make us...
Just relax.
I'll do it, all right?
I'll do it.
Then put it on.
It's a great tape.
Oh, please,
I'm not putting them on.
I heard of them.
You have not heard of them.
They're so new they haven't
even made a record yet.
They played at my cousin's
block party, all right?
- They got booed
off the street.
- Yeah, right.
I've heard them sing.
Listen to the demo.
Yeah, well, maybe
you heard them,
but I saw them.
I'm telling you...
Uh, the...
One of the guys sings,
he does everything.
He does a rap, he harmonizes,
his crew just
lip-synchs to his tape.
Shit.
Oh, why, because now
it's your business?
Chino's my best friend,
okay? Oh, shit.
Look at that car.
You live here?
No, I'm just vacationing.
Listen, um, if you want a job...
I mean, if you really want a job,
I think I can swing it for you.
Why? Because I live here?
No. It's because I'm such
a nice guy.
Yeah. Right, Price. Uh-huh.
Yeah, why are you such a nice guy?
You're a hustler.
I like that.
You want a job or not?
Yeah.
10:00.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Sit down, Ma.
(SCOFFS)
(INAUDIBLE)
What? I can't hear you.
(SIGHS)
I... I spoke to Magdalena.
- Can you hear me now?
- Yes.
Well, good,
because I have news for you.
She told me it's your baby.
- Ritchie?
- Yeah.
That's not my kid.
Darling, it's okay.
Listen, I don't blame you.
Okay, now, I did talk
also to Mr. Soto,
who wants to make a deal.
He says if you give the baby
your name...
Mr. Soto will bail you out
today.
If I give that kid my name,
okay, Lisette's gonna
leave me.
The one son the God left me
and I got to see him in jail.
(SOBS)
You know what?
You know what I wish?
That I would have died
when your brother was murdered
because then I had something
to be proud of.
What do you want me
to say to you, huh?
Do you want me to say
I ruined my life?
I can't do shit about it...
I can't do shit about it now,
okay, Mom?
Okay, listen.
You got two families, right?
One family
will give you nothing
for your whole life.
They just take and take and take...
And your other family,
you got a cute little boy...
And Magdalena, ooh,
she's beautiful. Huh?
And her papi is opening
a new bodega
on the concourse.
You could be the manager.
I'm married to Lisette.
I love Lisette.
(LATIN MUSIC PLAYING)
Take it easy.
Hi, Ma. This is Lisette.
No, I don't want any money.
Ma, listen.
I got a job.
Yeah, I got my own cubicle
and everything.
Yeah, I got a phone
and I got a computer.
Is Papi there?
No, no, no. No, no.
I don't want to talk to him.
Just, um... Tell him
about my cubicle, all right?
Okay. Okay. Bye.
Mami!
What are you doing here?
I came for my tits.
You said I could borrow them.
For one night, Nana.
Not for your whole life.
If I give them back to you
now, my boss is gonna know
that I stuffed myself.
How embarrassing is that?
Look, you wouldn't even
have this job
if it wasn't for me,
and then you turn around
and you steal my tits.
No, Nana, that's too shady, okay?
All right, fine.
Okay, you want them?
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
- Come on!
- Wait a minute.
You're so greedy and selfish
with everything. Here.
I'm so selfish?
They're my tits!
Why is it being selfish
if I wanna put on
my tits, huh?
You want socks?
No, I don't want socks.
I don't want nothing from you.
Thank you very much.
Bitch.
LISETTE: Oh, I'm the bitch,
right?
ALEXIS: No, not a bitch,
you're a thief.
Did you lose this?
Hi.
Ninita, give Pee Wee
his bottle, please.
This is... This is
my sister Alexis.
She just came by to say hi and bye.
Bye, mama.
So you're the guy
with the Lamborghini, huh?
- Uh, yeah.
- Uh, Mr. Price, I, um,
I wanted to talk to you about
the, um, marketing campaign.
The marketing campaign?
- No.
- No. What do you mean, no?
No, I, um...
I don't think that, uh...
It's not a good idea.
What's not a good idea?
You know, uh,
let Val and I come up
with the ideas. Okay?
And you correct Val's Spanish.
Gotcha.
Oh, Mr. Lamborghini...
Do you notice
anything different
about Lisette?
Yeah. I think so... What...
Your hair.
Your hair looks different.
I like it.
You get so stupid sometimes.
How come you didn't
tell me he was fine?
Because I'm married, all right?
- But you think
he's fine, right?
- No, I do not think he's fine.
Ma, you like that white man?
No, I do... Alexis,
do you see what
you're starting?
Look, this is the only man
that I like, okay?
Your father. Chino.
My husband.
I'm sorry.
He like your tetas.
He's got a Lamborghini.
Leave Chino's ass in there,
and go for yours.
Hmm?
Come on, honey.
Have you got
my purse?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What the fuck's going on, man?
Well...
She was in some guy's ride
at 4:00 in the morning, man.
- Word.
- With who?
A white guy in a Lamborghini, B.
I was hurting for you, man.
Bro, that car was shaking
like somebody
was getting fucked.
Man, you didn't see it.
Stop making shit up, man.
But Jose, from 246,
he told me he saw everything
from his window, bro.
- Yeah?
- So everybody knows my shit?
You saying I'm a cabron
or something, bro?
Yo, yo, yo, I... Come on.
I didn't see what
they was doing, so, all right?
You know, so, I can't
actually swear, Chino,
there were actually
fucking and shit.
Yo, but I swear to my moms,
she came out
of that Lamborghini, B.
- I ain't lying.
- Yo, Lamborghini, bro.
He was fucking her, man.
You better not
be bullshitting me, man.
What'd I tell you?
We shouldn't have
said shit, bro.
Because he gets all sensitive, man.
I ain't sensitive.
Yo, bro...
Chino cabron, man.
Chino cabron.
Chino cabron, cabronazo.
That's what they say, man.
I'm getting out of here, man.
You know?
I'm gonna go
up to her and say,
"Hey, what's up, Lisette?
"What's up, baby?
You doing me wrong?"
And if she is, you know,
then I'm gonna
kill her ass!
(ALARM RINGING)
(ALARM CLOCK BUZZING)
Chino, wake up.
You're gonna be late for work.
(ALARM STOPS)
Oh, man, I'm gonna be late.
PHOTOGRAPHER That's it.
Hold it right there.
Hold it.
Excuse me.
Would you do him?
Oh, come on, Lisette.
I'm asking you as a fan, okay?
- As a fan.
- Yeah, that's very nice,
very professional.
Would you jump into bed
with a guy dressed like that?
- Do you want
one sugar or two?
- One.
See, if I can
make him your fantasy,
then I know how
to sell his album,
so help me out here.
What's wrong with that kid's look?
You really want to know?
- Yes.
- He looks corny.
I mean, look at that shirt.
That shirt is scary.
Wrong.
What the hell is wrong with it?
She doesn't like it.
What?
Could you come here a minute?
Fantasize.
(SULTRY R&B MUSIC PLAYING)
# So I gotta do
What I gotta do
# I'm in jail
'Cause I'm a sinner
# I only want to be a winner
But I'm broke
# In a blackout state
And it ain't no joke
# But, see, I'm innocent
The judge won't believe me
# I gotta get out
Because my family says
they need me
# How does it feel
When you got no will?
# I could
take care of my family
# Now my son
Wants to dope deal
# Heaven help him
# Oh, brother
Where's my will?
# 'Cause only with a crew
like that
# He'll end up in jail
# Like his father
And that won't make him
# A better person
# It's like a plot
That only worsens
# Now, my wife claims
I'm cheating on her
all the time
# Oh, man, I ain't perfect
But I swear
that baby ain't mine
# Now she's struggling
And surviving on her own
# But she's got my three kids
And now Daddy's home alone
# Now I gots to get
my life back together
# No doubt
# Here comes the blackout
# And I know it's going
to take some time
to get around
# I want to make up my mind
Hey, you should go to
Pablo's show tonight.
No... I, I can't,
I got to be home by 6:00.
You got to cook dinner
for your husband?
No, to pick up my kids.
You know, you shouldn't
give people the
wrong impression.
How am I giving people
the wrong impression?
Well, you weren't wearing
that ring when I met you.
So? I don't always wear it.
So, you're not always married?
No. I'm always married.
Try to make Pablo's show.
Chino?
Chino!
Oh, shit, here comes the skank.
- How'd you get out?
- Mr. Soto bailed him out.
Come down here.
Where were you last night, Lisette?
Oh, Alexis got a big mouth.
How the fuck
could you do this to me?
Chino, I needed the money.
Oh, no, she didn't.
You did it for the money?
-What do you think?
-That's it. Yo.
Fuck her up, bro.
What's the matter with you?
Oh, man, you going
to go upstairs and cry?
Yeah, man, get out with
that sensitive shit.
You want to see
some sensitive shit, man?
You want to see some
sensitive shit?
Fuck that shit.
Yo, let him go, bro.
What the fuck are you
gonna do to me, G?
Huh? When you can't even
take care of your wife, bro?
No, no, no, no, no. Excuse me.
Your high-paid ho.
Break that shit up!
Break it up, man!
Chino...
- Chino, are you all right?
- Leave me alone!
Now, don't you think
that you did enough?
Get the fuck out of here,
all right? Go!
Do I look all right?
Look what you did to me!
You did this to me, Lisette!
- Chino, just...
- No, no, no, no.
Don't call me Chino, okay?
My name is Cabron...
Chino Cabron since I married you.
You think I played you dirty?
- Everybody saw you!
- Doing what?
Fucking him! Fucking him
in a Lamborghini!
Who said that?
Everybody! The whole block!
Angel. Everybody!
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
You saw me fucking somebody?
No. Yo, yo, Chino, man,
I didn't actually see
what they was doing.
Yo, that was Victor and Chris
that said that shit, man.
Fuck you! That shit
came out your mouth!
All I said was I saw Lisette
coming out of some guy's ride
at 4:00 in the morning.
- So what?
- Oh, so? So?
What were you doing
in some guy's ride
at 4:00 in the morning?
Yes, I want to know.
I want to know
what you was doing
at 4:00 in the morning. Huh?
Wait...
I took a job, all right?
I took that job.
That guy in the car was my boss.
He drove me home, and that was it.
I'm so tired of these
bonchin chozas
that got nothing better to do.
Why don't you go get a job
or something?
Yeah, why don't you go get
some tetas or something?
You swear you didn't touch him?
Chino, I swear.
On your mother's life?
On everybody's life, okay?
Why the fuck do you think
I even took that job?
To bail your ass out of jail.
It's all about you, Papi.
Chino?
Come on, sweetie, we got
to go to the store now.
- Kiss Papi bye-bye.
- Papi?
What the fuck
is that supposed to mean?
He's Ritchie's father.
That's what that means.
You tell me right now
if that's your kid.
No.
- No?
What do you mean, no?
This kid could be anybody's,
Maggie.
You don't know for sure
he's mine, all right?
Including yours?
That's right. Including his.
I got the face
and I got the body
and I got your man.
You got my man nothing!
You see this ring?
You know what that
makes me? His wife.
makes you? His ho!
No, Lisette!
All that piece of shit
14-karat gold nothing
means that Chino paid way
too much money to fuck you!
Fuck you, bitch!
Where you running to?
Fuck you too, Lisette!
You want him?
I'm not fighting you.
He was my boyfriend!
Lisette, what are you doing?
Let's go upstairs
and talk about this.
Chino!
Oh, you want him, Maggie?
Is this what you want?
Come here.
There's your precious
little Maggie.
Here, the two of you
deserve each other.
Pendejo y la sucia.
I hope you're happy.
- Chino, come on! Stay here!
- Let's just talk about it.
Let go of me!
Lisette, he's my son's father!
You don't know that!
I don't care if he's your
son's father, Maggie.
You want him?
You can have him, okay?
All right? You think this
motherfucker's my life?
He's not my life, okay?
I've got a life!
I've got a life! Okay?
Get your fucking hands off me!
You, stay the fuck away from me.
Don't you come near me.
I got a life, okay?
None of you fucking bums
got a life!
I got a job, all right?
I got a job! What the fuck
you people got?
- The color? You're killin' me.
- (AUDIENCE CHEERING DISTANTLY)
Ah, Lisette, tell him how much
you like this shirt.
Take off that shirt.
Give me the shirt.
We don't have time for this,
Lisette.
We don't have time.
The show...
Incredible.
Oh, black, okay.
Come on, Pablo. Come on,
please. Please.
Okay.
Oh, this is much better.
Okay. All right,
all right, I'm hurrying.
Okay, that's better.
Okay? Mira.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
ANNOUNCER
And here he comes.
Ladies and gentlemen...
(CROWD ROARS)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, put that crap down.
Here.
You handled that very well.
Yeah, right.
A water shortage in the Bronx?
So... How is Mr. Linares?
Oh... I'm sorry.
I see we're not married today.
- Boy, you are hard
to keep up with.
- Fuck you!
Aw, shit.
Fuck, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean that.
What's your problem, huh?
What is your fucking
problem, huh?
I didn't mean to throw that at you.
Well, you planned it, didn't you?
I didn't even mean to throw
that at you, all right?
I'm sorry.
It's not about you.
What is it about? Huh?
Your husband?
No.
You have some champagne
in your hair.
I was trying to wipe it off.
It bounced off my face.
All right. Thanks.
(SULTRY R&B MUSIC PLAYING)
Come on.
You all right?
Jesus.
You gotta tell me
when you're having problems.
You know, I never would've
made you come out tonight.
No, forget it.
If it wasn't for this job,
I wouldn't have had
no place to go.
Well...
I'm glad you're here.
Is it still in my hair?
No.
I'm married.
I'm not staying in your
fucking basement, all right?
You and your bullshit
just fucked up my whole life.
Loco. Hey, loco,
take it easy, bro.
I told you,
I'm gonna get you
back upstairs, man.
Fucking touchy, touchy, touchy.
How?
Yeah, how?
I told you how.
This is how, man.
You see this shit?
You see it?
It's like Spanish Fly.
The girly smells that,
it turns her into
a crazy freak
like flies on shit.
They're gonna be
all over your dick.
You can't get 'em off, man.
My last one, but you're my boy.
Freak?
We're talking about Lisette, right?
Oh, yeah, that's a tough one, man.
Yo, got it, bro.
Right here.
It's the good shit.
$29.95, man. Sangria.
A little wine,
a little atmosphere,
a little cactus, bro...
She'll forgive you, man.
(KEYS JINGLE)
Hi.
Where's Alexis?
I don't know.
Pee Wee was crying.
Give him to me.
You could go now.
-No, I got him.
Look, he's calm now.
-What's the matter with him?
Sit down, relax,
take a load off your feet.
Nice feet. Here you go.
I got you some wine...
(TURNS MUSIC ON)
I got you a cactus.
- Chino...
- Here you go. Look.
Sniff that, all right?
Sniff it.
I'll be right back.
You hold it, you hold it.
-Put him to...
Chino, put him to bed.
-What a cutie.
You don't want Papi
to leave, right?
# I often wonder
each and every day
# If I should open up
# Would you run away?
Miss me?
# Or would you stay
here by my side in love?
# In love
# Time will
guide us together #
(STEREO SHUTS OFF)
You got something to say,
Chino, you say it.
(PEE WEE CRIES)
Pee Wee's crying.
Chino, come on, he's fine.
Why don't you just
put him down and go?
All right, if this
is what you want,
then I'm gonna put my jacket on,
and I'm gonna walk
out the door, okay?
I'm leaving.
Papi, Papi
I had a bad dream
you went away
and never came back.
Please don't go.
Oh, Minnie...
I would never leave my little girl.
Look, I'm not going anywhere, okay?
See? I'm sitting down,
taking my jacket off.
Chino.
Could I have a puppy now?
Did Papi promise you
a puppy if you came
out here, mama?
Did he? It's okay.
Chino, why are you making her lie?
Look, Minnie,
this is for real, okay?
I don't know why,
but your mami wants
your papi to leave you
- forever and ever
and ever and...
- Oh!
- Do you want that?
- Look, this is between
you and me, Chino.
Don't bring my kids into this.
No. Your kids?
They're my kids, all right?
Get out before I call the cops.
-I don't want him to leave!
-The cops? For what, huh?
For me?
It's not like I hit you or anything
and what is my bike doing
here in the hall anyway?
You've got Pee Wee crying.
Just get out!
Look, this is my house, okay?
This is where my bike belongs.
This is my coffee table,
my TV, my couch,
my kitchen, my chair!
I'm staying right here.
I'm not going anywhere.
Come on, Chino. Get out!
Get the fuck out before
I call the cops, all right?
-Stop.
-C, stay out of this.
Get the fuck out, Chino!
- I'm tired of your shit, girl.
- Put me down!
Let her go!
Ma!
Open this door!
- What are you doing?
- Chino!
- Helping my mom!
- Your mom?
Okay, then why don't you
go in with your mom?
You all right?
C, just stay back.
- Look...
- Come on, let her go.
Stay in the room with your brother!
Will you calm down a sec?
Then I'll let you out, okay?
Don't talk to me like I'm Li'l C!
Maybe if you'd stop screaming,
he'd let you out.
I don't have to stop
screaming, all right?
I'm an adult!
LI'L C: You ain't
acting like one.
I believed you, Chino.
(SOBBING) I believed you.
Why did you lie to me?
I didn't mean to hurt you, Lisette.
All you care about is yourself.
Everything I did in my life
was for you, and you know it!
Oh, fucking Magdalena
was for me, Chino?
Huh?
Was that for me?
Maybe I had to go to Magdalena
because I wasn't getting
what I needed at home!
What weren't you getting, Chino?
What weren't you getting?
Maybe I got tired of hearing,
"Hurry up and finish!"
Well, maybe
if you did it right,
I wouldn't want you to finish.
I do it right! All right?
I'm sensitive, creative,
spontaneous.
I make crazy, stupid love...
But you don't appreciate that
because you don't know how
to make love to a man!
Maybe if I had a man, I'd know!
Look, it's over between me
and Magdalena, okay?
C!
C, don't you want your mami
and papi to work things out
and be together, huh?
Fuck you, Chino!
You have no right
to bring him into this!
Come on, man.
Help me out!
You see what I put under the door?
It's not about you, C, okay?
All right? It's not about you.
LISETTE: Can I come out
now, Chino?
You gonna...
You gonna be civilized?
You gonna act like a lady?
Yeah, Chino, all right?
All right.
You crazy?
I was going for spontaneous.
Where you going, huh?
To meet
that Lamborghini motherfucker?
Yes, and I wasn't
drinking sangria, either.
I was drinking champagne!
Alexis!
Alexis, open this door up!
I want to talk to my wife.
Let me in!
ALEXIS: Not by the hair
of my chinny-chin-chin.
If I'm so bad in bed,
well, how come
you married me?
How come you married me, Chino?
Mama, you were pregnant.
That had nothing to do with it.
Please, it's not a diss, Lisette.
You're just not
a sexual person, okay?
(POUNDING ON DOOR CONTINUES)
- Lisette!
- What is he doing?
- Alexis, I am
a very sexual person, okay?
- Hey, don't scream.
And I'm sick of you people
telling me what I am
and what I'm not, all right?
You're scaring the baby, stop it.
That's not a baby,
Alexis, it's a cat.
- It's a baby cat.
- Whatever, okay?
And you want to know
something else?
I got fly tetas.
You hear that, Chino?
I got fly tetas. And I make
more money than you do.
LISETTE: You hear that,
Chino?
The stupidest bitch you
ever met makes
more money than you.
If I went on welfare, Chino,
I would still bring home
more money than you did!
I don't need you, Chino!
Okay, nobody needs you, all right?
Come on, Minnie.
So you gonna come with me
or you gonna stay with her?
- Ouch!
- What's your problem, Minnie?
You never cry like this
when Mami combs your hair.
Mami doesn't hurt my head.
- Ma.
- What?
Ma, could you fix her hair?
I don't know how
to comb nappy heads.
- Come on, come on.
- Come on, Ma, please!
Stop it! Get back here!
Listen, the problem
is that you married
a women with bad hair.
In my family, nobody
had nappy heads.
-In my family, we all had
pure Castilian blood.
ALL: "Pure Castilian blood."
- Well, excuse me.
- Stop.
And listen, you can
do me a big favor...
When you find this wild
little animal,
will you put this on him, huh?
C, don't give Abuela
a hard time, okay?
I got to go to work.
Put your clothes on.
I ain't wearing that 'mo shit.
Ooh, ooh...
You got a caca mouth,
you know that?
Get out of here.
- (SPEAKS SPANISH)
- MINNIE: Ooh, you're gonna
get a beating.
Put your clothes on.
I'm wearing my jeans.
No. No, you're not.
No, they are dirty.
Maybe your mother took you
to school with dirty clothes,
but not Grandma.
- No, she doesn't.
- Give it back to me.
Give it back to me!
Li'l C's gonna get a beating.
- Shut up.
- Oh, you know, just take it.
C said he ain't scared of you
no more. And you know what?
He said if you try to
beat him, he's gonna
hit you back.
- Shut up!
- Right, C? You said that?
You got a big mouth,
you stupid idiot.
Hey, watch your mouth, okay?
Don't talk to your sister
like that.
You still scared of Papi,
because you won't even
tell him what you said.
I ain't scared. I'm a man.
I don't care
if he gives me a beating.
Oh, that's wonderful,
you brought him up
real good.
That's just wonderful.
You're a man, huh?
That's right. I'm a man.
Put your clothes on now.
You're gonna be late
for school.
What's this, you don't
listen to me anymore?
Look, I can't.
I gotta go to work, okay?
Here. I can't deal with this.
No, no, no. Wait a minute.
You brought them
into this world... You do it!
Don't make me tell you again, okay?
Put your clothes on.
(ROSARIA GASPS)
Pick it up!
You ain't a man.
What?
You're a punk, because
I'm more little than you.
All you can do
is hit me with that belt.
That's right, Papi.
You said if you hit somebody
more little than you,
you're a punk.
- Did I ask you?
- No.
You are looking
at the work of Lisette.
Listen to me.
Okay, fine, fine,
I don't need to hit you.
Right, C? You're a man.
I should respect you, right?
That's right.
You don't need to live here
with me, right, Mr. Man?
You could go out and get a job,
take care of yourself.
You don't need nothing
from me?
I don't want nothing from you.
See, that's the trouble
with this house...
There is no respect
for grown-up people.
- Where you going, huh?
- You got no control.
It's a jungle,
like animals in here.
No control.
You want to see some control?
I'll show you come control.
These are my clothes.
I paid for them.
Don't take nothing
you didn't pay for.
See those underwear you're wearin'?
Those are mine. Take 'em off.
Come on, come on.
ROSARIA: Wait, wait, wait.
Are you crazy?
You have that boy
out there with no clothing?
CHINO: He's got
to learn respect.
What's he gonna learn?
He's going to learn...
(ARGUING CONTINUES,
INDISTINCT)
Oh, look who it is,
it's Mr. Man.
I got no clothes.
You want a pair of pants?
Some underwears,
maybe some sneakers, too?
Yeah?
C, so then you ain't a man, okay?
Because you living off of me.
Until you can walk out of my house
with your own shirt,
then you're a man.
Until then, you just a naked
little punk in the hall,
and if you wanna come in,
put these pants on
like Abuela asked you to.
Don't you look at me
the wrong way.
You'll find your ass
back out there.
Hurry up! I've got
to get this job!
We've got a lot of work here.
I've worked for you
for eight years.
You're coming up for trial.
How do I know
what's gonna happen?
It's a first offense.
I'm gonna pay for the stereo,
I'm gonna get time served.
Help me out.
Can't do it.
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Oh, fuck you, Chino!
Good morning.
Oh, Mrs. Linares...
I have something of yours.
Coffee, please.
What's wrong, Mrs. Linares?
No... Nothing. I...
(CLEARS THROAT)
(CLOCK TICKING)
Take off your watch.
What?
(SCOFFS)
How long do you think
this is gonna take?
We're never gonna know, are we?
(JAZZY MUSIC PLAYING)
# L is for the way
You look at me
# O is for the only one...
Brujo!
Lisette put a curse on it.
It ain't normal for a guy
to come out of prison
and it looks like that.
I mean, look at it.
# E is even more than anyone
that you adore... #
Price?
# Can love
PRICE: I'm in a meeting.
I just hooked up
the conference call
to Puerto Rico!
Come on, Price.
I've got Tommy, Miguel,
and the director on the line.
Price? Price?
PRICE: I have to get it.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
- Raoul?
- I'm outta here.
No, no. Of course you can have
your girl in the video.
Who told you you can't?
- Yeah, well,
Tommy's a schmuck. No.
- Let go of my leg.
You don't like the chick,
cut her out of the video.
All right? But put her in.
Then shoot around
the mustache, okay? God.
Hang up the phone.
Tommy, Raoul?
I don't believe this.
I can't believe I'm here.
I can't be...
I'm under a desk.
MAGDALENA: You need
a cleansing, baby.
Relax, sweetheart.
Relax, okay?
Maggie...
- This isn't doin'
nothing for me.
- (SQUEAKING)
What is that?
What is that, Maggie?
Don't worry, Papi, it's nothing.
Just relax, okay?
It's a rooster.
No. No, really,
what is that?
It tickles.
I'm gonna rub him
all over your body.
And I'm gonna break
that bitch's spell.
(ROOSTER CROWS)
Uh... Oh! Ah! Oh, shit!
# More than anyone
that you adore
# Can love
# Is all that I can give
Okay, guys, where we at?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
That's it?
That's great.
(WHISPERING) That was great.
- That's fantastic.
- That was great?
(WHISPERING) Fantastic.
Oh, we gonna make
a good video or what?
That's what we're doing here, huh?
I know.
He's not a very good
cameraman, but...
I was just kidding.
He does very good work.
I know. Well, listen...
Uh, wait one sec.
Can you wait one second?
That was great.
I don't know that I can get to
Puerto Rico.
Come on, you sleep
with someone else
other than Chino?
Yeah, right.
- That's right, I did. Alexis!
- What?
Oh, you don't believe I did it?
Babe, it's not that,
it's just that... Like I said,
you're just not
a sexual person, okay?
What's this?
Why you picking up
condom packages
off the street?
What do you...
No! Lisette...
You did!
You did do it!
I told you.
That's right, I did it.
- You did it with somebody?
- I'm a sexual person. Say it!
Dios mio.
I can't believe...
Say it! I'm a sexual person.
I'm a sexual person.
(SHUSHING)
Hello, Migdalia.
What can I get for you today?
You got my order?
Oh, si.
Miggie!
Hurry up!
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
That motherfucker
gave her my cactus!
Yeah, didn't you know?
He's working for her now.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
LISETTE: I got
a present for you.
There's something inside.
Today was the happiest day
of my life, Chino,
and I want to share it with you.
When you were in jail,
I held it together
all by myself.
I know it's fucked up.
I mean, I... You know, I...
I been with you, what, 10 years?
I can't even think of anything
to say to you.
Just open it, all right?
(QUIET HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
What happens after I open it,
then, huh?
Are you just gonna walk away?
Yeah.
I'm not gonna open it, Lisette.
(THUDS)
Come on, Chino,
don't fuck with my head.
You're over here
working for that bitch!
You gave her my plant!
You gave her my wine!
Just open it!
- Look, the only reason...
- Open it!
# Get past that
And live another day
# Walk the wrong way
# Your family
went the other way
# Gots to be down
and stop clownin'
# Until I take my dirt
# Skirt to
the next episode... #
What's this supposed to mean?
We're even.
You ain't even worth it.
# And as a matter of fact
I'm feelin' shady
# I think I'm goin' crazy...
You know, I should
congratulate you, Lisette.
You held it all together,
all by yourself.
And you fucked a guy
all by yourself!
And you fucked up
our family all by yourself!
You should be proud
of yourself, Lisette!
I have something a bit
more constructive for you
than your little tack project.
The Mendez brothers,
they need a tougher image.
They got the girls,
and I want to get the guys,
but I don't want to piss off
the female audience.
You want to take a crack at it?
No.
I might fuck it up.
Well, then we'll go
with Val's strategy
and turn your loverboys
into gangsters with Uzis.
Okay. I'll try it.
Chino? Do me a favor.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
(MIMICS BABY NOISES)
Chino, man, you're crazy
to give that kid your name.
Word, bro, because
you try and leave,
you know she'll get
all vindictive and make
your ass pay...
- ALL: Child support.
- (LAUGHING)
Why you got to act like
a retard and tease him, huh?
I ain't afraid to pay
for my mistakes.
Yo, man, everybody's done
did her, though.
So what?
So why you gotta give him
your last name, man?
That kid's name should be
Ritchie Martinez Cruz
Torres Vasquez Linares.
It shouldn't even be a name, y'all.
It should be a street number...
- "Ritchie 170th."
- (LAUGHTER)
You're all crazy, all right?
Because all you people think
that this is the worst thing
a bitch could give you.
Look, man...
That's the best thing.
The best!
Anything else they give you
is bullshit.
Everything else.
ALL: Busted!
(GUYS TAUNTING CHINO)
Chino, could I talk to you
alone for a second, please?
I'm working.
(GUYS LAUGH)
Chino's not Ritchie's father, Papi.
What?
Maggie?
Why did you make me
bail him out of jail then?
I know, I lied.
I lied because I wanted
Ritchie to have
a good father, like you.
I wanted him to have somebody
he could be proud of.
So, uh, who's the father,
Maggie, huh?
- CHINO: C!
- See you later, C.
Hey, you want some ice cream?
I don't want it
after she put her mouth on it.
Well, you're gonna
have to share, all right,
because I don't got no money.
- I got my own money.
- Where'd you get this?
- I found it.
- Where?
- I didn't steal it, all right?
- Hey, come here.
First of all,
don't you yell at me, okay?
And second...
I didn't say you stole it.
And third...
Where's my hug?
Huh? Where's my hug?
Come on, hug your papi, man.
OLDER BOY: See him
hugging his father?
(ALL MOCKING)
I'm gonna get my ice cream.
- What?
- How come C gets
his own ice cream?
Because C has
his own money, that's why.
But he has new kicks and jeans.
Man, fuck that nigger.
(KIDS SPEAKING INDISCERNIBLY)
Yo, man, tell the guy
what you want.
Let me get a sno-cone.
- Yo, what you doing?
- Watch it, man!
- What is this, huh?
- It's my clothes!
Oh, these are your clothes, huh?
Yo, leave him alone, man!
Yo, he's getting his ass kicked.
- Where'd you get these, huh?
- Come on, I bought them!
You working for him, huh?
You working for him?
Yo, you're fucking
with the wrong man!
He don't need your shit, okay?
BOY: Oh, G, he's taking
off his pants!
You want to be a drug dealer?
Huh?
I do what I want!
I got my own clothes!
That's it.
That's what you want to be,
right? Okay.
Get off of me.
You ain't gonna be a drug dealer.
You ain't gonna be a drug dealer!
- Chino!
- I don't need nothing
from you.
Oh, ho, you want to run from me?
BOY: Put him down, man!
Look at that.
Look at that, C!
Look! Look!
No, Chino, por favor, please.
He didn't know what he was
getting into.
No, fuck that, okay?
That's his uncle
and he fucking knows that!
Look at your uncle! He's dead!
Look at him, look at him!
I know, he knows, but please
don't hit him no more.
Please, Chino. Please.
(LAUGHING MOCKINGLY)
You want to teach my kid
to sell drugs?
Let me go! Let me go!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Harder!
BOY: You're not my father.
You're not my father, man.
You can't hit me.
(SOBBING)
You can't hit me, man.
You're not my father.
(CRYING)
ALEXIS: Oh, yeah.
Yeah, right down there.
Mira, Chinito, talk to Mami, okay?
Mami, I want to stay with you.
See?
Why? Because you know
you can deal drugs
and I won't hit you?
You can get over on Mami, right?
Well, forget that, C,
because I'm through
talking to you.
You want to deal drugs,
answer to your father.
Lisette, what the fuck
is wrong with you, huh?
I'm tired of being played
for a fool.
I'm really, really tired.
Who the fuck's
playing you for a fool?
What...
Lisette, he's just a little boy.
Lisette?
- CHINO: Look, there he is.
- Dude, check out
this little bean head, man.
Yo, word up, Chino,
your kid look like
a crack baby. I ain't lying...
Just shut up, man.
He looks like an angel
when he's sleeping.
You lucky you don't got any, man.
ANGEL: I do.
You do what?
Um...
Chino, man, I'm Ritchie's father.
- You're Ritchie's father?
- Shh!
You're Ritchie's...
Lookit, you're gonna wake the kid.
- Come here, you.
- I can't fucking
believe you, man.
I can't fucking believe...
You're my best friend
and you let her set me up?
Don't even try that,
you like being a father.
To my own kids, Angel!
Oh, this is new.
You're gonna hide yourself
behind a bunch of papers
instead of running into the
bathroom, like you always do.
I'm not hiding myself, Alexis,
all right? I'm proving myself.
They want to disrespect me,
that's all right.
Because tomorrow I got
a chance to prove who I am,
that I got good ideas.
Well, why don't you prove
you're a mother,
and go out there
and talk to your kid?
Excuse me, but who died
and left you a womb?
All the silicone in the world
ain't gonna make you a mother.
So don't even talk about
what you don't know, Alex.
(MUTTERING IN SPANISH)
Okay...
Maybe I don't know
about being a mother,
but I know about being
an eight-year-old little boy.
You don't know shit, Alexis.
My son ain't jumping into dresses.
His father beat his ass
in front of
the whole neighborhood
and told him that he wasn't a man.
Don't tell me that I don't
know how he feels.
He was dealing drugs!
Nana, he's eight years old,
you're gonna push him away
for something that he did?
You're his mother!
You're supposed to love him
more than that.
- Lisette, are you listening
to me?
- No. No. No.
I sat up in that house
like a very good mother.
I never raised my hand to him,
and him and his father
walked all over me, Alexis.
Well, that's over,
because if they can't
act right,
I'm not gonna deal with them
at all.
Oh, you got your life to lead.
Yeah, that's right.
You sound just like Mami.
Well, maybe she's right.
She's got her man.
She's got her cart.
She doesn't let
anybody interfere
with her happiness...
Not you, not me, nobody.
Like pretending we don't exist?
If that's what she needs
to be happy...
Yeah, well, maybe it doesn't
make everybody else
so happy.
Well, then,
that's your problem.
Not Mami's.
(LATIN MUSIC BEGINS PLAYING)
(TURNS RADIO OFF)
Alexis, I was listening to that!
- It's my house.
- Fine, it's your house.
(CLICKS PLAY)
(TRY A LITTLE TENDERNESS
PLAYING)
# Oh, she may be weary
# Them young girls
they do get wearied
# Wearing...
- # That same old shaggy dress
- You going someplace?
- (DOORBELL RINGS)
- # When she gets weary
# Try a little tenderness
Alex?
Alexis.
Why are you doing this to me?
Get out.
Get out of my house!
How dare you come
into my house
looking like a freak?
- Get out.
- I just came to tell you...
I don't want to hear it.
- Two months...
- I don't want to hear it.
- I'm gonna get
the operation, Mami.
- Out.
And I'm gonna be
a real woman, like you.
Do you want to wake up
your father? He'll kill you.
And I'm gonna get married
and make you proud of me.
- Get out of here!
- What you doing here?
Get out of here.
(PRAYING IN SPANISH)
Please bless these notes
and let me kick ass tomorrow.
# You know she's waiting
- # Just anticipating
- (DOOR SLAMS)
Hey, Alexis...
# The thing that she'll
never, never, never possess #
LISETTE: Do you want to hear
my presentation?
(ALEXIS PRAYING QUIETLY
IN SPANISH)
Why are you praying in here?
What's wrong? Are you not
talking to me now?
They saw me.
Papi did this to you?
You know, you're wrong, Lisette.
It's not my problem.
It's their problem.
I still love them
after what they did to me,
and I didn't do anything to them.
But they hate me.
Oh, Alexis.
You are just like Mami.
- I'm not.
- "Fuck everybody else..."
- I'm not like Mami!
- "Go for yours!"
Alexis!
I'm not like her.
I'm not.
(SOBS)
(TOY SQUEAKS)
I'm not gonna run away from you, C.
You can sit in that closet,
you can never talk
to me again,
but I'm not leaving, okay?
I'm sorry.
You forgive me or what?
Yeah, sure.
C... C.
I'm sorry.
I'll pay half of the rent.
Yeah, well, you get the couch.
Oh, fine, I get the couch.
Well, this is my half
of the apartment, right?
Okay, so then, your bike
belongs in your half
of the apartment,
away from my half
okay?
What did I tell you
about that, huh?
Oh, that's nice!
Leave him here,
hanging off of here.
That's beautiful.
Leave him alone, okay?
I got him.
I'm taking care of him.
Stop throwing your cereal
at each other!
No, don't tell them to stop.
They can do whatever
they want in my house.
Oh, they can do what...
Papi says you can do
whatever you want
in the house.
He's cleaning up after everybody!
Come on, let's go, we're late.
If I gotta watch the kids all day,
you're watching them at night.
So you can hang out with Magdalena?
No, I'm getting a night job.
And just because I'm not
gonna be here at night,
don't think you can
bring friends over here.
The kids don't need to see that.
Yeah, well, I'm paying
half the rent, okay?
So I didn't want you bringing
your friends here either.
Let's go! Bye, Papi.
Let's go!
- MINNIE: C messed up my hair.
- Come on.
CHINO: Hey, C,
you got to clean
this mess up, all right,
- when you come back.
- C, come on.
(PEE WEE CRIES)
Have a nice day, Chino.
There's a song
where a guy sings to other
guys about women,
and he doesn't come off
looking soft or nothing.
He's just like, "Look,
here's the deal fellas."
Okay, what song?
Try A Little Tenderness.
You want to do that as a cover?
Yeah, yeah,
and then they could do it
in English and in Spanish.
That way, it could cross over.
-What? What?
What's the matter?
-Shh.
I don't know, I'm just...
I'm looking at the video.
Uh, okay.
So you got
the Mendez brothers, right?
They're on the beach...
- Right.
- Coney Island.
Beautiful women.
(STAMMERING) Wait.
No, I mean, the beach,
I like the beach, right?
- But it's gotta
be one girl. One.
- Okay. One woman.
But one amazing woman.
Yeah, but not some
oiled-down video ho.
No, no, because the song
is about talking.
- It's actually not
about fucking at all.
- Exactly, exactly. That's it.
And then, and then, like,
we could show,
like, Ricky Mendez, right?
And he's walking
behind surf, you know,
and he's like,
"Man, what could I do
to bring her back?"
You know?
He's, like, really...
And then, and then, Tony Mendez,
- he comes along with
his brothers, right?
- Right.
And he comes up to Ricky,
who's all sad,
and he says, "Hey, man,
why don't you just try..."
"Try a little tenderness,"
right! Yeah!
I'm gonna train you for Val's job.
Wait a minute.
I know. Hold on.
Look, Price, why are you fronting?
You don't want to sleep with me.
Oh. Oh, yes, yes, I do.
Come on, Price,
you do this all time.
You got your desk drawer
full of condoms.
You got your pine air freshener.
Yeah, I've made love
with women here before.
Does this bother you?
- No.
- Good.
What bothers me is being
with somebody who doesn't
even know I'm there.
I had to make a phone call, okay?
Look, I don't want to diss...
- Good.
- But you're not
a very sexual person.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
Is this because I had
to make a phone call?
- No. No.
- You know, there was
a crisis in Puerto Rico.
Do you understand that?
What do you want me to have said?
"I was making love to my young
and talented assistant.
I'll call you right back"?
Whatever. Okay, look...
Do you want me
to set up a meeting
- with the Mendez brothers?
- No, I don't. I don't. I'm...
This is weird, you know?
I'm feeling very uncomfortable.
Look, Price, there's no
weirdness here, okay?
I did it with you once,
I'm not gonna do it again,
that's it.
I'm not a sexual person?
I... Yeah... No.
I can't work like this.
So...
What do we do now?
Maybe, uh...
Maybe, uh, you should find a...
Maybe you should work
for a different boss.
- Are you quitting?
- No. No, I'm not quitting.
So what are you saying?
You gonna fire me?
Fine, fire me.
Book some studio time
for the Mendez brothers.
And get outta here, please.
I gotta make a phone call.
I know how much you hate that.
(CLATTERING)
What are you doing?
Can you throw me
that roller, please?
Thank you.
You got the gas on?
I'm talking to you.
Chino, you can't just turn it on.
You gotta light it.
So... How's your new job?
- You like it?
- It's kind of boring.
I just sit in one place.
It's not like riding a bike.
You should get one of those,
you know, portable TVs.
- Maybe next blackout.
- (CHUCKLES)
So how's your boyfriend?
I don't got a boyfriend.
Then what about that thing
you gave me?
Look, it only happened once,
all right, Chino?
It's not even any of your business.
All right, all right, I know.
It's none of my business.
It's over between us.
You do what you want to do.
I wasn't asking because
I was jealous or anything.
I was a little curious.
So how is Magdalena?
I wouldn't know.
I'm not with her anymore.
Angel is Ritchie's father.
Oh.
I'll be honest with you.
Everything I ever felt for you
is dead,
and I would never, ever want
to get back together.
Yeah, well, I feel
the same way, Chino.
I'm just staying for the kids.
I mean, I look at you
and I see you and him
doing the rawest shit.
I mean, things
that we didn't even do.
Well, it's none of your business...
So you shouldn't even
think about it.
Believe me, I don't want
to think about it.
All I'm saying is that
if we talk about it,
then maybe we won't
wonder about it.
But if you're too shy...
I'm not shy...
What do want to know?
Wait a minute.
You write down everything
that you and him did,
and I'll write down everything
me and Magdalena did.
Then we'll pass notes
and we'll never
talk about it again, okay?
Concentrate on your own paper.
- You finished?
- Yeah.
How did you find time
to go to work?
- Is that it?
- Yeah, that's it.
Wait, here, number 11,
you guys didn't do that?
Is it on my fucking paper?
If I didn't write it down,
it didn't happen.
I just wanted to make sure
we both wrote everything down,
okay?
Yeah, well,
I wrote everything down,
all right?
I'm going to bed.
Lisette, Lisette.
Wait, wait, wait. Wait.
Could I just ask you
one more question?
Go ahead, Chino.
Ask me one more question.
Was he better than me?
Um, let me think...
Well?
No.
Ah! Yeah!
I knew it. I knew it.
I knew he...
How could he be better than me?
Yes! Yes! I knew it.
I knew that. I knew that.
You didn't even have to...
I knew it.
I'm telling you
I feel so much better now.
Oh, my God!
Lisette, let me...
Lisette, Lisette...
I feel so much better now.
I don't know about you,
but I feel... I feel great.
I mean, it's getting better now.
I'm looking at you right now,
and I don't see you and him
doing a bunch
of horrible things anymore.
I don't. I mean,
I see you guys doing...
One horrible thing, I'm...
Yeah, and now I just see
you and her
doing 42 horrible things.
Thanks a lot, Chino.
- What's your problem?
- You know
what your problem is?
You never think
about the other person.
# She may be weary
# And them young girls
They do get weary
Good night, other person.
# Wearing that
same old shaggy dress
It's morning, Chino.
# But when she gets weary
Good morning.
# You gotta try
a little tenderness
# You know she is waiting
# Just anticipating
# The things
# That she'll never, never
possess... No, no, no
# Oh, as she's waiting there
# All you've got to do
# Is try a little tenderness
# Baby
# Baby, it's not...
# Sentimental
# She has her grief...
# But these soft words
# Spoken gentle
# Yeah
# It makes it easier to bear
# You won't regret it
# Young girls
they don't forget it
# They don't forget
# Love is their only happiness
# But it's all so easy
# What you've got to do
# Is try, try, try
# Try a little tenderness
# Give her all your love
# Forever
# Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah
# Give her all your tenderness
# 'Cause she needs your love
# Forever
# Forever, yeah
# Try a little tenderness
# Give her all your love
# Forever
# Give her all your
tenderness
# 'Cause she needs your love
# Forever...
# Try a little tenderness
# Give her all your love
# Forever...
# Give her all your tenderness
# 'Cause she needs your love
# Forever...
# Try a little tenderness
# Give her all your love
# Forever...
# Give her all your tenderness
# 'Cause she needs your love
# Forever...
# Love is all
That I can give to you
# Love is more
than just a game for two
# Two in love can make it
# Take my heart
and please don't break it
# Love was made for me and you
# Love was made
for me and you
# So I gotta do
What I gotta do
# Now I'm late for my life
# Had a bad one
Never had none
# So I'm out to get mine
# Had to struggle
in the process
# It's getting deep
# And there ain't no time
For sleep
# Too many things
Running through my mind
# Walking on a thin line
# And there ain't nothin' kind
# I'm feel I'm going
to pass out
Riding that wrong route
# Steady-headed
For the blackout
# Don't want to do wrong
But I gotta live
my life strong
# To be happy
# And you know
it's gonna take some time
# I wanna make up my mind
'Cause I am wasting
precious time #