[Radio Announcer]
It looks like the first
storm of the season
will be hitting us tonight,
and it's forecast
to be a big one.
Someone who doesn't
have to worry
about the weather
is our new President-Elect
William Jefferson Clinton,
or Bill,
as his friends call him,
who is packing up
the Governor's mansion
in Little Rock, Arkansas,
and preparing
for his move
to the White House.
His wife Hillary
has already visited twice,
and is excited about
not only relocating
to Washington,
but also becoming
the new First Lady.
[Woman]
...number 11. So
color that one red.
There you go.
Just the number 11.
How many ones
in number 11?
[whispers] Two.
Two.
There you go.
Okay, just
the red, though.
I can't do it!
It's too small to fill in!
You're right, it is small,
But you can do it,
just go slowly.
I can't. I tried.
You know the word "can't"
isn't in the dictionary?
But I can't do it,
Mommy.
Do you know
what we're gonna do?
We're gonna get rid
of all those "can'ts".
Did you know
you could do that?
Okay.
Okay, take
a deep breath.
Are you ready to blow
all the can'ts away?
Mm-hmm.
Do it.
[Mom blows a raspberry]
Did you see it?
They're going away.
There they go.
Adios.
Okay, now you can
do anything, right?
Right.
[doorbell rings]
It's Daddy!
Remember,
you have to clean up
and tidy everything away
before you can go.
Hey, Kris.
Quinn.
Is the little man coming?
Yeah, he's putting
his paints away.
Where are you
taking him this weekend?
Out on the boat,
like always.
No sailing.
There's a storm coming.
Okay, then we'll just
go down to the harbor.
We won't go out.
You promise me?
I've asked you
not to take him before.
He told me
you went sailing anyway.
You know how much
he loves it.
It isn't safe, Quinn.
Okay, I promise.
I wish you'd have
tried to like the boat
a little bit.
[derisive laugh]
When was I supposed
to find time to do that?
I was raising a child,
going to school.
I didn't have
much time to play.
I'm not
talking about play.
You know, I bought
the boat for business.
That's why, you know,
I've got that dive shop
in the Keys.
For both of us.
Exactly.
You run off
and buy something
on the other side
of the country...
We talked
about that for years.
That was before
I had a child
to think about.
Well, I am thinking
about the child.
It's a great place
to raise a kid.
The Keys are beautiful.
Then I hope
you enjoy yourself,
but you're not
taking my son.
It could've been
so perfect.
I mean, you,
you could've gotten your
law degree in Miami,
open a practice
in the Keys.
Weekends,
we could've just enjoyed
the sand and the sun--
Perfect for you.
That's not the way
you felt when we met.
I was younger then.
It was exciting.
Huh. So then I got
out of the Navy
and it wasn't
exciting anymore?
This is going nowhere.
Take Mark for the weekend,
show him the boat.
Yeah, while I have it.
I don't want
your damn boat.
And what about
the money and the house?
Look, that is not
what this is about.
I wanted to be fair.
Fair?
I put you
through law school,
and now you have
your attorney buddies
gang up on me.
I can't even
go to the mailbox
without getting
some legal mumbo-jumbo
from one of
your lawyers.
Quinn, get yourself
a lawyer.
You can't
do this by yourself.
I don't want one, okay?
I want my family back.
I get my son
one weekend a month.
When it's final,
it'll be different.
Yeah, probably
won't get him at all.
No.
How did we
end up like this?
Maybe it's because
we're so different.
I mean, we always were.
Then why'd you marry me?
Because I loved you.
I have to ask you this.
Please, can we
work this out?
Just the two of us,
without all these lawyers
confusing everything?
Please?
Daddy!
Hey! Yar!
How are ya, my man?
How are ya,
there, sailor?
Feeling good, Captain.
Well, that's good to hear.
Now let's see
if we can find us
some pirates
in that harbor.
What do you say, huh?
So you never did
answer my question.
You know the answer.
Alrighty, then.
Let's me and you
go have us a good time, huh?
Bye, Markie-poo.
Call me
before night-night.
I love you.
Bye, Mommy!
[Radio Announcer]
Thanks, Laura,
Stay safe out there.
This storm front
is really giving
L.A. a bashing.
Winds are strong,
at 60 miles an hour...
[telephone rings]
Quinn?
Who is this?
Grab what's loose
back there.
Right this way.
Let's go.
Come on. Bring it over.
Bring it over.
Kristen Halloran.
Hi, I'm the Harbor Master
Bill Sellers.
I'd like to thank for
driving down all this way
under these conditions.
They said this storm
was gonna slow down
when it crossed Baja,
but it must've picked up
some off-shore moisture--
Have you found the boat?
Uh, not yet.
As I told you
on the phone,
we received a distress call
from theOcean Dreamer
about 8:45.
That is your boat,
right?
My husband's.
We received
a second radio message
about 15 minutes after that.
This one was a mayday.
What did he say?
That they'd lost their mast
and were taking on water--
Where are they now?
That's why
we asked you to come in.
Do you know how many people
might've been aboard the boat
and where they were heading?
This would help us
with our search patterns.
You mean,
you haven't found them?
No, ma'am.
We've had
one of our cutters out
since we got the call.
Dana Point and Catalina
have also got boats
looking for them.
So, once again,
do you know who was onboard
and where they were heading?
My husband
Quinn Halloran
and my son Mark.
And they were going?
I told him
not to take the boat.
He promised me.
Was he an experienced sailor?
6 years, ex-Navy.
As soon as
these winds abate,
we'll have the helicopters
up running search patterns.
That'll help us
in locating--
No, you can't wait.
You have to send
the helicopters up now.
That's impossible.
They can't fly in this.
No! My little boy
is out there!
I'm sorry.
I really am.
We're doing all we can.
[telephone ringing]
Excuse me.
Harbor Master.
Where was it?
Was there anyone aboard?
There was a young child
as well.
How old was your son?
4. He's 4.
A young boy,
4 years old,
plus the captain.
Yeah.
Please. Please, tell me
what they're saying. Please.
Please, Mrs. Halloran,
I know this is difficult.
Give me one minute.
I understand.
No, absolutely not.
Give it another six hours
before changing parameters.
I know that.
So keep it
search and rescue
until we lose the light.
I don't care about that.
I've got the mother
here with me.
They found the boat.
It was capsized
about 7 miles out.
There's no one onboard.
I've ordered them
to continue
the search patterns
for the rest of the day.
And then what?
Then...it becomes
a recovery operation.
What does that mean?
It means we've done
all we can...
and under
these conditions...
I wouldn't be honest if
I offered you much hope.
All we can do is pray,
Mrs. Halloran.
[beep]
[Bill Sellers]
I'm so sorry, Mrs. Halloran.
I really am,
but it's been three days
and we still
haven't found them.
With the conditions
the way they are,
there's no way
they could've survived.
I have to call off
the search.
[sobbing]
I think I look
particularly good there.
Oh, it's...
[laughs]
Oh, you have
to see this.
It's good.
See?
[Man]
I love this.
Running on the beach,
and the horse is
liking the pressure.
[Woman]
Watch out
for that rock! Oh!
Well, that's
the end of tape two.
Wanna see more?
Okay, Steve,
you talked us into it.
The rest of our
Caribbean vacation
coming up.
And I used to think
slide shows were bad.
We've got slides.
Kristen, can we
make more popcorn?
Sure.
Popcorn and movies.
Can't beat it.
How are the kids?
Well, Josh is living
with his mother,
but I get blamed
for any trouble
he gets in.
Rachel's back at college.
We'll see how that goes.
I've got an idea.
How about
if you and Steve
join us next year?
Nothing crazy.
We don't have to go far.
Just drive up the coast.
That sounds lovely,
but it's really difficult
for Steve to take
time off work right now.
Things are rough, huh?
Has the thing
worked out with his son?
No, it's been
really hard on Steve.
Josh has
a preliminary hearing
at the end of the month.
Steve wants
to be there for him,
so he's gonna have
to take some more
time off work.
When it rains...
Have you thought about
taking a home-study course
and taking the bar?
You were so close
to becoming a lawyer.
People told me--
I was a different
person then.
Kristen, that person
is still inside you.
Mwah! Beer run, baby.
Hey, Steve,
I was just saying
how we should
take a weekend away,
just the four of us,
do a little wine tasting.
Will Ronnie video
the whole thing?
Yeah, only the good bits.
But we could
do it really cheap.
I know this hotel in Napa,
it's less than 200 a night.
You know,
I'd love to, but--
Like I said, Marge,
Steve is super-busy
right now.
Yeah, I'm super-busy
getting beer
for everyone.
Okay.
How about we start slowly?
A day out, just you and me?
We'll stay local,
maybe get a facial,
and definitely go shopping.
[microwave timer rings]
Ah, popcorn.
Welcome back toRonnie's
Funniest Home Videos.
We'll be watching
as Marge forgets
to charge
the camera batteries,
and I become the Pirate
of the Caribbean.
[Marge]
He thinks
he's Johnny Depp.
[Ronnie, recorded]
And we're a gazillion miles
from L.A.
We're...where the hell
are we, Marge?
[Marge, recorded]
Santa...
Santa Alicia. Santa Alicia.
A tiny Caribbean island,
and in the spirit
of Christopher Columbus,
Sir Francis Drake,
and our little buddy Gilligan,
we are going
on a four-day cruise
and diving adventure.
I'm king of the world!
Let's see if I can
find our captain.
Father and son
run this boat
and they are
both gorgeous.
[Ronnie]
They're not
that good-looking.
[Marge]
Yes, they are.
No.
Hello, yes they are.
Hey, Ronnie, why
does this green light flash?
And here's our
first mate Matthew.
Marge, point
the camera at Matthew.
Hey.
Say hello to our friends
back home, Matthew.
Hi.
So, uh, you're Canadian,
right?
Yes, sir.
So how many languages
do you speak?
English, German,
Spanish, and French.
And you know
what they call someone who
speaks foreign languages?
Quadralingual.
Poor kid.
And you know what
they call someone that
only speaks one language?
I have no idea, sir.
American. Ha ha. Marge.
She does that
when I crack her up.
When I'm embarrassed.
That's all there is.
Marge forget
to charge the battery.
I didn't forget.
Okay, I forgot.
[Steve]
What is it?
My son.
He's alive.
Unbelievable.
Could this really be him?
Will you just
talk to me about this
for one minute?
There's nothing else
to talk about.
I'm going
to Santa Alicia.
Okay, but you can
just slow down?
There's no flights
to Santa Alicia tonight.
Then I'll take
the first flight out
in the morning.
You know, Marge said
it took them forever
to figure out
how to get there.
It's, like, a world away.
Are you absolutely
sure this is him?
There hasn't been
one minute in 14 years
that I haven't
thought about him--
what he might be like,
what he might've become.
You think I wouldn't
recognize him?
Look, I'm just trying
to be supportive here.
But I don't know
what to do.
How about I--
How about I call
the dive shop?
And say what?
He could run,
and I'll never see him.
Then let's call
the local police.
No. I don't know
what they might do,
what they might
say to him.
Kristen, I'm worried
this might be
too much for you.
What am I supposed to do?
Stay crippled by my grief
for the rest of my life?
Is that what you want?
Is that who I am to you?
Of course not.
I have to do this.
Then let me
come with you--
after Josh's hearing.
I can't risk
losing him again.
I have to go now.
This is my chance.
This is our chance.
I really think
you should get
cancellation insurance
just in case Eduardo
interrupts your trip.
Who's he?
Eduardo is a tropical storm.
Hopefully, it'll stay
out in the Atlantic
and not bother you,
but I would
get the insurance
just in case.
Yeah, we'll take it.
Good. I'll issue
the tickets.
So what's the plan
once you get there?
Bring him back.
He's 18.
Yeah, I was there when
he was born, remember?
I'm not trying to be smart,
I'm just trying to help.
Sorry, it's just--
That's okay.
How about Quinn?
What?
What do you mean?
Well, you might still
be married to him.
I'm married to you.
But your divorce
was never finalized.
If he's alive...
You think
I want him back?
Absolutely not.
Here are your tickets
and your boarding passes.
And, inside, you'll find
your hotel confirmation.
And don't forget
your passport.
I don't
have a passport.
Oh. Well, then you
might not be able
to use these tickets.
Where can I
get a passport?
Go to the post office,
fill out a form,
send it in with
a photograph and a check--
Well, that's too long.
This is an emergency.
Isn't there something else
my wife can use?
You have
a driver's license, right?
Yes.
Well, you can
get on the plane with that,
and if you bring along
your birth certificate,
that may get you
into Santa Alicia.
If not, will they
send her back?
Hopefully.
Hopefully?
It's possible
they may hold her
for awhile in custody.
That's ridiculous.
Please, just
give me the tickets.
Taxi's on its way.
You can do this, Kris.
I believe in you.
What if he doesn't...
want to know me
when I meet him?
Your mother and you're--
you're a great mother.
I haven't
been a great mother
to your children,
Steve.
They've always
gone to their mom
when they've
needed anything.
It's not your fault.
Don't second-guess
yourself.
Sometimes things just--
they don't turn out
the way you hope.
Will this turn out
the way I hope?
[car horn honks]
Taxi's here.
You ready to do this?
Yeah. Yes, I am.
Then no matter
what happens,
you have a family here
waiting for you to come home.
Thank you.
[Announcer]
Attention all passengers,
this is
the final boarding call
for inter-island
flight 101 to Santa Alicia.
Would all
transit passengers
for Santa Alicia
proceed immediately
to gate three?
[buzzer rings]
The final boarding call
for inter-island
flight 101 to Santa Alicia.
All passengers should
be onboard at this time.
[Quinn]
It could've
been so perfect.
Kristen, how did we
end up like this?
Can we work this out,
just the two of us
without, you know,
all these lawyers
confusing everything?
So you never did
answer my question.
Go ahead, take a peek.
Such beautiful
scenery out there.
It's a shame
to fly over it
and not see it
as the angels do.
Just go ahead.
It's breathtaking.
You're right.
But I'll feel happier
when we land.
You and me both,
sister.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Next in line.
Do you have a passport?
No, I...I lost it.
We need some assistance
at desk two.
Possible illegal entry.
We called your husband
and he vouched for you.
Can I go now?
Not that quickly.
We don't have anyone
to vouch for him.
He's just a phone number
you gave us.
He's my husband.
So you say.
I also called the airline
and they don't
have a record
of a passport
being left on the plane.
Maybe they haven't
found it yet.
Maybe.
Listen...Mrs. Collins?
We have rules and laws
that have to be followed,
just like in America.
What do you think
would happen to me
if I tried to enter
your country with this?
I don't know.
I do.
It's my job to know.
I would be
refused admission
and deported
at my own expense.
Well, it was
an accident
that I lost it
and you have
my driver's license.
Do I look like
Budget Rent-A-Car to you?
I need a passport.
Your license
and this can be bought
on any street corner
or printed up on any
home computer these days.
And it's not even
a certified copy.
Please, you have to
let me in.
I think my son is here,
and I haven't seen him
in so long.
Don't you have children?
Yes, I do. And my eldest
is away working.
I haven't seen him
in two years.
Well, I haven't
seen my son in 14.
Okay.
We're a small island,
and we can bend the rules
from time to time,
so this is what
I'm prepared to do.
You fill out
the lost passport form
and I'll submit it
to your local consulate.
Once filed, I'll admit you
into Santa Alicia for 48 hours,
during which time
you must report
to the local police officer
and have him
extend your visa.
Miss that deadline,
and I will come
and get you myself--
and I know
where you're staying.
Thank you.
I'll take care of it.
Good. And say hello
to your son for me.
Yes, ma'am?
Which hotel?
No, do you know
where Caribbean
Dive Adventures is?
Yes, I do.
Okay, good.
[sigh]
G'day!
You're Kristen Collins,
right?
The American lady
who got in last night?
Yeah.
Welcome to the islands
and to my hotel.
I'm Patrick.
Let's get you
a nice table, shall we?
I don't think
I'm going to
have breakfast.
I just wanted
to find someone
who might know something
about Caribbean
Dive Adventures.
Captain John's outfit?
His boat, thePhoenix,
is the busiest on the island.
They have a dive shop
not too far away from here.
I went there last night.
There was a sign saying
they were closed
until Wednesday.
They're probably out
on a charter, then.
Lucky for you
they weren't closed up
for the season.
A lot of folks already are.
You're not gonna hook up
with them today so...
let's get you that table
and start the morning off right.
Come on.
Well, I haven't
eaten in awhile.
You'll like this--
a lovely view of the beach.
It's right up here.
See?
This suit your fancy?
You're
not from around here.
Me, no.
I'm from all over,
but originally from Oz.
Australia?
That's a long way
from the Caribbean.
Yeah, it makes for
a hell of a commute
in the morning.
Nah, I'm just
joshing with you.
I've been here
for six years now.
Let me get you
an orange juice.
Where are you from?
California.
I know it well.
Used to work
on a cruise line
that sailed out
at San Pedro
and down to Mazatlan.
But my favorite place
in all of California,
it's Malibu.
You ever go there?
Yeah, I've been there.
That surf is almost
as good as back home,
and the birds
are amazing.
There's something
about an Aussie accent
that works wonders
with an American girl.
Huh.
[Man]
Stack them all over there!
What are they doing?
They're getting ready
to board up
in case we get any
weather coming through.
After what happened
last year,
the folks around here
don't want to take
any chances.
You had a bad storm?
No, we were fortunate.
Ivan just grazed us.
But other places
weren't so lucky.
It's gonna
be days at least
until we get any
weather coming in,
if we do at all.
Until then,
it's going to be
just like this--
clear, sunny.
Tell me some more
about Captain John
and his son.
They're good people,
and that boy Matthew,
he is shaping up
to be a real heartbreaker
with the holiday girls
that come here
during the season.
He's giving me
some stiff competition.
Now, see if there's something
that catches your eye.
My tip is the eggs Benedict.
They are the most wicked
thing on this island,
apart from me, of course.
[telephone rings]
Hello?
[operator]
Miss Collins?
Yes, it is.
Your call.
Thank you.
[Steve on telephone]
Hey, honey.
Thanks for calling
me back, Steve.
These hotel phone calls
cost a fortune.
That's okay.
I was so worried when I heard
from immigration yesterday.
I have to report
to the local police
if I'm gonna stay.
And are you?
I have to.
I found their shop.
But they're
off the island.
They'll
be back in two days.
Thanks for watching my back.
It's worth watching.
So now Rachael's in trouble.
She was called down
to the Dean's office.
Why?
Same as before--
drinking, boys.
How about Josh?
He's doing his best.
He's scared about
what might happen
when he goes to court.
Tell him not to worry.
Just make sure he
dresses appropriately,
and have him listen
to the judge,
and the most he'll get
is a few hours
of community service.
I'll tell him. Thanks.
How are you doing?
Good.
Really?
Yeah.
Good.
You call me
if you need anything.
I will.
I love you, Steve.
I love you, too.
Always have,
always will.
You be careful.
Okay.
[lock clatters]
Hello!
Anyone on board?
Hey, American lady!
Kristen!
It's me, Patrick,
from the hotel, remember?
Where you going?
The boat's back.
Have you seen them?
Well, I'll tell you what.
Instead of us
yelling at each other,
why don't you come up
for a drink
and I'll see
if I can figure out
which boat
you're talking about.
Seems like I'm always
showing you to a table.
Now you're gonna
have to tell me
what boat
you're talking about.
Captain John's,
thePhoenix.
Yeah.
It was parked on the, uh...
The dock.
Yeah.
Yeah?
But it wasn't due back
until tomorrow.
He probably came back
for Junkanoo.
What's that?
Junkanoo.
That's a carnival.
It starts at sundown.
Everyone on the island's
going to be there.
Everyone?
Everyone.
If they're back,
they'll be there.
Where is it?
It's a street festival,
so it's everywhere.
It's up and down.
I'll tell you what,
I'll take you,
but first
you have to tell me,
what's your poison?
What?
Your poison.
What are you drinking?
Oh, no, thanks.
If you want me to
take you to Junkanoo,
you have to let me
buy you a drink.
It's the local custom.
Come on.
We got an hour to kill.
Maybe I can tempt you
with the finest brew
known to man.
I don't drink beer.
Wine it is.
Melvin, can you bring me
a glass of red wine
for the lady?
You know,
you're kind of different
from the regular tourists
that we get here.
For start,
you're an American,
and we get mostly
Europeans.
Plus, I noticed on your hand
you got a wedding ring,
but you're traveling
alone.
So what's that about?
My husband couldn't make it.
I see.
Your husband
couldn't make it.
So you're here alone,
slap in the middle
of hurricane season...
you sure you're not here
for something else?
Like what?
Like finding a man,
looking to get
your groove back?
No, I'm not looking
to get my groove back.
[scoffs]
[Man]
Red wine for the lady.
Cheers.
Are you always this...
persistent?
Business on the island
is quiet this time of year,
and there's a bunch
of bloody storms
out there already.
What do you do
when there are no tourists?
Some people work
on their shops
and some people
fix their boats.
And some, like me,
just hang out
and talk the days
and nights away.
Now, your guy,
Captain John,
he set up
a lifesaving program
in the local schools,
and his teaching
has probably saved,
like, 20 kids over
the last couple of years,
so everyone
on the island loves him.
He's better in the water
than I am,
and that's saying something.
[cheers, fireworks]
What is that?
Junkanoo's starting.
It's Fourth of July,
Caribbean style.
Everyone is here?
On one of these
streets, yeah.
I'm gonna look around.
For Captain John?
Quinn?
What?
Oh, I'm sorry.
All right.
It's full of sweets
and candies for the kids
so they can break it open
like a piñata.
Here.
What is that?
It's a lucky charm.
Put it on
and make a wish.
[no audible dialogue]
[lock clatters]
Thanks for the lift.
I'll see you
when you get back.
[telephones ringing]
[sighs]
[Man]
Make sure you
check that out.
Can I help you?
Um...
Are you all right?
You look like you've
just seen a ghost.
Are those for me?
Yeah, I have to get
my visa extended.
I didn't have
the right papers.
Ah, you're the lady
with the lost passport.
I've been expecting you.
Sit down, please.
Immigration sent over
your papers.
So you filed
a lost passport form
at the U.S. consulate,
and your birth certificate
isn't a certified copy?
I think we can
let it slide this once.
You don't look
like a spy to me.
But if you're gonna be
doing much traveling--
No, I'm not. Just here.
Fine, then I'll sign
an extension for you.
Is two weeks long enough?
Yeah, it should be.
Okay.
Make a copy of this
for my files.
I'll let you know
what the consulate says
when I hear back from them.
I'd like
to stamp it for you,
but we're out of ink.
My friend's picking some up
while he's off-island.
Is that the person
who dropped you off?
Captain John?
Maybe I was wrong.
Perhaps you are a spy.
No, I'm just kidding.
Yes, Captain John's
on the Cay seas
picking me up
some printing supplies
while he's in Puerto Rico.
When will he be back?
About a week.
Did his son go with him?
No, Matthew
just dropped him off
at the airport.
Why?
Do you know them?
No, I don't.
Thank you, um...
Officer Bodden.
Officer Bodden,
thank you.
Miss Collins,
if you don't know
Captain John,
how did you know
his name?
And how did you know
the other person
in the car
was his son?
Some friends of mine
were here in the summer...
diving, and they told me
about him.
I see.
Well, have a good day.
Hello.
How are you?
Good.
I was just looking
at your boat.
Oh. It's no problem.
Would you like
to come on board?
No, no.
I can see fine
from here, thank you.
So where you from?
The hotel--
the Grand Vista.
I know that.
I mean what country?
Oh, the U.S.
California.
Oh, that's awesome.
We don't get many
Americans around here.
I'm actually Canadian myself.
Haven't been back there
since I was 4.
My name's Matthew--
or Matt.
I even respond to "Hey, you!"
Sorry about that.
What should
I call you, ma'am?
Kristen.
We just got in last night
for the Junkanoo.
You were there.
I think everybody
on the island was.
Did you go?
Yeah.
Can I charter the boat?
Is that possible?
Oh, of course, yeah.
Just not today.
I need to wash her down.
But how about tomorrow?
Tomorrow's fine.
Great.
Where would you want to go?
Anywhere.
I don't mind.
That's good.
We kind of need
to stay close to shore.
We had some problems
with the radio
on the last trip,
and I wouldn't want
to go too far
without a radio,
at least not
this time of year.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
There's nothing wrong
with thePhoenix,though.
She's the best boat
in the Caribbean.
We'll just have to stay close
on these inshore reefs here,
but there is
excellent diving--
I don't want to dive.
Then why would you
want to go out?
Just to see everything
that there is to see.
That makes it real easy.
We'll just give
thePhoenixa rest
and take theZodiac.
So how many?
How many what?
Passengers.
You, your husband--
Just me.
Okay.
Isn't there something
you want to ask me?
What?
Something important?
I don't know. What?
[laughs]
How much it'll cost.
Oh.
How much will it cost?
$400 U.S., please.
That's fine.
Can you leave a deposit?
You take credit cards?
Sure do.
Actually, could I see
your passport, please?
The bank insists
that we write--
I don't have a passport,
but I do have
a birth certificate
with my maiden name,
Shepard,
and a driver's license
with my current
photograph,
and I have
a visa extension
which I just got
from the local police.
Is that going to
work for you?
That's more than enough,
thank you.
Thank you.
Can you sign this,
please?
Sure.
We're gonna have
a great day tomorrow.
Any special requests?
Fishing rods, wine,
or anything?
No, I'll leave that
up to you, Captain.
Great.
Well, in that case,
I'll get her ready.
Just be here around 8:00
and don't forget
your sunscreen
and your swimsuit.
Swimsuit?
Yeah.
Right.
Woosh!
You find the view
interesting?
Do you have a problem
with the truth,
Mrs. Collins?
I saw you down at the dock
earlier with young Matthew,
and you've been sitting here
watching him for hours.
I don't mean to pry,
but do you mind
telling me why?
Isn't that prying?
We just heard back
from the U.S. consulate.
They couldn't understand
why you had us file
a lost passport form.
They say you've never
been issued a passport.
So unless
you can explain to me
how you can lose something
that never existed,
you're gonna be spending
the night in a cell,
and you're gonna be
out of here on the first
flight in the morning.
Well, I...
Allow me to escort you
to the station.
You're telling me that this
man that everybody loves
faked his own death,
stole your son,
and moved to a tiny island
in the Caribbean?
Yes.
It would help
if you had something
to back up your claim,
like a marriage license,
anything.
All I have is this.
How old is this photograph?
15 years.
Mrs. Collins,
that child could be anyone.
I couldn't tell you
what he looked like now
any more than
you could tell me
what my children will
look like in 15 years.
It would help
if you had a photograph
of your ex-husband.
I don't.
I got rid of everything
when...
Why would I make this up?
You have my word.
You gave me your word
that you lost your passport.
We both know
that that was a lie.
I keep copies
of everyone's files
who comes through here,
including yours.
Here,
take a look at these.
This is your supposedly
dead husband's passport
and Matthews.
But the name isn't
Quinn Halloran.
It's John Williams,
and he's from Canada,
not Los Angeles.
That's a forgery.
Which is more likely,
that he created
an entire life
for himself and his son,
or that this is just a case
of mistaken identity?
After all,
he has the documents
to prove who he is.
You don't.
I know that this
is how it seems.
I know you're upset,
so I'm not gonna
force you to leave
the island right now.
Thank you.
We'll
check on his passport,
the same
as we did with yours,
but I don't want you
telling young Matthew
any of this,
because if what you're
telling me is true,
Quinn may be dangerous,
and he could run again.
If I find out you've done
anything to jeopardize
this investigation
by telling Matthew,
I'll have you off
of Santa Alicia
within the hour,
and this will be all over.
Understood?
Do you have
all the details you need?
Names, numbers--
I'm on it.
Remember,
not one word to Matthew.
[ringing]
[Man on answering machine]
Hello, you've reached
Caribbean Dive Adventures.
We're under water
right now
and obviously can't
get to the phone,
so leave a message
after the beep.
[beep]
[Bodden on speaker]
Hey, John, call me
as soon as you get back.
I had this woman
Kristen Collins in here
telling me this crazy
story about you.
I'll tell you all about it
over that beer you owe me.
Ahoy, there, Matthew.
Ahoy, yourself.
Come on board.
You know,
I haven't been on a boat
in nearly 20 years.
Really?
Yeah.
You have life jackets,
right?
Oh, yeah, definitely.
Here you are.
Thanks.
When you're getting
on theZodiac,
just sit in the back
next to the outboard.
You got to be real careful.
Keep all your weight
inside the boat.
Otherwise,
if we hit a big wave,
I might have to come
and fish you out.
Don't worry, though.
Just relax.
I'll do all the work.
Good.
Ooh!
All right,
your turn to drive.
Yeah.
Come on, it's easy.
Look, twist it this way
to go faster,
and back to slow down.
Piece of cake.
Just put this on first.
What is it?
It's called a kill switch.
It's just a cord
connected to the engine.
That way, you fall overboard,
it pulls out and cuts off,
and your boat won't
sail off into oblivion.
Huh.
You can swim back.
How's that sound?
You want me to let go
of these ropes?
You're gonna have to
to drive this boat.
Here, you promised.
I never did.
There you go.
Okay.
Remember, twist it
towards me to go faster
and back to slow down.
Head out that way.
See? You're doing great!
You're a natural.
[Matthew]
Good.
Good, good!
Keep it up!
Check it out.
Did you build this?
Yeah, me and my dad.
No one knows it's here.
Now I do.
Oh, no.
Remember, I said
I didn't want to dive.
Come on,
you have to try it--
just on the surface
for now.
I'll put air in your jacket,
and you won't sink.
Here's your wetsuit.
I'll put air in your jacket,
and you won't sink.
Here's your wetsuit.
It's just like snorkeling,
only water doesn't
get into your mouth.
It's just like snorkeling,
only water doesn't
get into your mouth.
It's perfect, right?
I can't.
You can,
I promise you.
Trust me.
You'll just be
suspended, floating,
looking down
on the fish
and the coral.
Really, Matthew,
I'm sorry. I can't do it.
There's no such word
as "can't"
in the dictionary.
Just relax,
take a deep breath,
hold it for
a couple seconds,
and blow all
the "can'ts" away.
[exhales]
My mother
taught me that once.
You know what? She's right.
It always works.
I do it to all
the nervous divers.
You just got to try it.
[inhales]
Good.
It's beautiful.
It was awesome.
Oh, man.
Woo!
Got it.
[no audible dialogue]
This is wonderful.
I know.
Isn't it?
How did you end up here?
My dad bought the shop
three years ago.
Before that,
we had a charter yacht
in Honduras.
We've been all over.
Are you in school?
Yeah.
Everywhere we went,
Dad made sure
I was in school.
He helped me out
with classes at night
and always insisted
that I finish my semester
before we changed ports.
Why did you keep
moving around?
Dad's sort of a genius.
He'd buy a small business
in an out of the way place,
and pretty soon
he'd build it up until
it was a huge success.
Then he'd just sell it.
Then we'd start
all over again.
That's
how I ended up here.
Why not keep the business
if it's doing so well?
I don't know.
It's not really
what Dad's all about.
Your childhood,
do you remember
where you grew up?
Oh, yeah, sure do.
I remember my mother.
She was so beautiful,
in every way, too.
She just...
[sigh]
I can remember her
pushing me on the swing
in the backyard
when I was small.
She was always so kind,
reading me stories and books.
She called me "Little Markie."
Mark's my middle name.
[sigh]
Do you have
a picture of her?
I wish I did.
My mom died
in a terrible fire
when I was little.
I can remember it
like it was yesterday.
My father took me out.
It was so stormy
on the boat.
It was raining and cold.
When we got back,
we heard that the house
had burned down
to the ground
with everything in it--
pictures, our furniture,
toys. We lost everything.
My dad was...so upset.
We just never went back.
He used to talk about her
all the time, though.
What did he say?
That she was an angel
and we should never
forget her.
We still go to church
the first Sunday of the month
and light three candles--
one for her
and two for me and Dad.
They represent our family.
If she were still
alive today,
we'd all be together.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to make you cry.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Can we do this
again tomorrow?
Really?
Tomorrow's on me,
no charge.
You already paid double.
I did?
Yeah.
When you asked me for 400,
you should have
bargained me down
to the real price,
which is 200,
but you said yes
too quickly.
It was worth every cent.
The last American couple
we took out
argued about
every single penny.
Marge and Ron Satrum.
You know them?
That's how I found out
about you and your boat.
I hope I lived up
to my reputation.
Matthew, there's something
that I have to tell you.
I'm not here as a tourist.
I came here for a reason.
Don't say it.
I got it.
You figure that if I
can get Marge to dive,
then I can get you
to become a pro, right?
Well, hey,
we'll go deeper tomorrow.
How's that sound, okay?
Okay.
All right.
8:00 A.M. sharp.
[Kristen]
Oh, my God, Steve.
He's incredible.
He's everything
I could have
ever dreamed of.
I had the most
amazing day.
[indistinct phone chatter]
I know.
No, Quinn isn't here.
It was just Mark and me.
It was perfect.
[telephone ringing]
Hello.
[Quinn on telephone]
Hey, son.
Hey, Dad.
How's Puerto Rico?
Hey, hey!
Everything's good here.
Jose and Maria
send their best.
How's things going?
Great.
Just rented a day charter
in theZodiac
up to Gibbs Key
for a dive and a picnic.
Hey, that's cool.
What else is going on?
Officer Bodden left you
a pretty strange message.
It was actually about
the American woman
I took out today.
Said that she had
some crazy story about you
and you should probably
call him back.
What was her name?
Kristen.
Kristen what?
Collins.
But she had another name
on her birth certificate.
I wrote it down
when I called her charge in.
Hold on.
Her other name was Shepard.
Well...
how old was she?
Uh, a little bit
younger than you.
[Quinn]
Did she say anything else?
About what?
About anything.
Think.
She said some friends
recommended our boat.
[Matthew]
It was that crazy
American couple
we took out
about six weeks ago.
The ones from L.A.?
Yeah, yeah.
It was a bit weird.
She was acting
really nervous,
and she said that she
had hated boats
even though
she had been married
to a sailor before.
I don't know.
Did I do something
wrong, Dad?
No, no, no.
It's not you, it's her.
Listen, Matthew,
you have to do
exactly as I say.
I want you
to wake Mavis up,
tell her to get all of our
savings out of the bank,
and then I want you
to go over to the boat
and head out to Salt Cay.
I will meet you there.
Dad, wait,
I don't understand.
She already paid
to go sailing
again tomorrow, Dad.
Don't worry about that.
We will refund her money.
Just do what I say.
Why? What's wrong?
I will tell you
when I get there.
But, Dad,
what if I want to stay?
You don't want to stay
if that woman is around.
But she was nice!
I don't care
how nice she is.
Please, just leave now.
I will explain it
to you later.
Are you still there?
Matthew, are you there?
Yeah, I'm still here.
Please, son, just do
this one thing for me.
Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey, Kristen, I have something
for you at the desk.
Is there a storm?
More than a storm.
Eduardo out in the Atlantic
took a right-hand turn
last night.
It's not a category 3
hurricane and building,
and it's making a beeline
right for us.
But the weather's
so beautiful.
You heard about
the calm before the storm?
Eduardo's pushing
all the good weather before it,
but when it hits,
all hell is going to
break loose.
But you don't have to worry.
The old Grand Vista,
she's a hurricane shelter.
In fact, we're gonna
open the doors to the locals
in just a few minutes,
and they can ride
the storm out here.
Is this a refund
because of the hurricane?
No, it's
from young Matthew.
He came by last night.
It's the leftover money
from your charter.
Did he cancel
because of the storm?
I shouldn't think so
because he came over
before 10:00,
and the hurricane hunters
didn't get the word out
about Eduardo's new track
till after midnight.
He said something about
he was leaving the island.
He had to join his dad
at Salt Cay.
Did he say anything else?
Yeah, he said good-bye.
Right there,
come on.
[chattering]
[Announcer on TV]
You are advised to evacuate
to your nearest
hurricane shelter
immediately.
The storm is expected...
He's gone.
Who's gone?
Matthew!
He's left the island.
When did he leave?
Last night.
His father must have
found out that I'm here
and told him to go.
You have a very active
imagination.
I am not imagining
that the boat is gone
and the shop is closed up.
If you haven't noticed,
we have a hundred-year
storm coming our way.
By this time tomorrow,
it's going to be
pounding this island.
Maybe Matthew just took
the boat someplace safer
to ride it out.
Safer than the harbor?
Where else around here
could be safer than that?
There could be any number
of reasons why.
Or maybe his father
told him to run.
Oh, please.
You never even called
about his passport, did you?
I have a thousand
residents on this island
to worry about right now,
not just one tourist.
Maybe tomorrow, when
this hurricane is gone,
we can deal with this.
No, it will be
too late by then!
He will have gone again.
What kind of
police officer are you?
I'll find him myself.
[Kristen on telephone]
I found him, Steve,
and now he's gone.
Let him go for now, honey.
It's all over the news
about a hurricane heading
straight for the islands.
I can't. Not now.
What about the police?
No. The police?
They don't even believe me,
and I have no proof.
Maybe I can dig something up.
Did you get
the police officer's fax
or email or something?
No, just the hotel's,
but I don't know how much
longer I'll be here.
I'm going to find Mark.
Kristen, please,
stay where you are.
If this hurricane's
as bad as they say,
it's gonna
be a monster.
Okay. I love you.
Hold all my calls.
I'm going home.
It's in the back,
but it should be sheltered
from the hurricane.
Is that all right
for you girls?
I've got two beds
in there, okay?
Excuse me.
Patrick,
I need your help.
Kristen, you're
gonna have to wait.
I need to find Matthew.
Matthew?
Not Captain John?
Matthew is my son,
and I need to find him now.
Your son?
He told you Salt Cay?
Yeah, Salt Cay.
Where is it?
It's due south of here.
Where's south?
South is straight
out the harbor.
You keep the land
to your back.
You can't go there now.
It's 20 miles of open ocean.
I realize that.
I have to find him.
You can't survive
a hurricane there!
It's a flat salt marsh!
What the--
Check the moorings
in South Harbor.
Make sure that
they're all secure,
all right?
Officer Bodden?
What can I do for you?
I just received this.
She was telling the truth.
I guess she was.
Where is she now?
She said she was
going to Salt Cay.
With a hurricane
coming in?
[panting]
Kristen?
You bastard!
Damn!
You stole my son!
Calm down!
I didn't have a choice,
okay?
You were taking him
away from me!
Ehrrr!
Kris--
Where is he?
He's out
getting fresh water.
He's gonna be back
any minute now. Calm down!
[sobbing]
Get off me,
you son of a bitch!
They told me he was dead!
Look, I'm sorry.
Your attorneys were gonna
take him away from me.
So instead of trusting me,
you took him and ran!
Look, I gave you
everything you need, okay?
I gave you the house,
the money, the car,
everything you needed
to continue with your life.
My life?
My life was over
when you took Mark.
I'm sorry. I wanted
to give him a chance.
I didn't want him
to grow up in the city
with the crime
and the drugs.
That is crap!
You just didn't want him
to be with me!
That's not true.
I wanted him to have
a chance at a good life.
Without a mother?
Would he have had a father
if he'd stayed with you?
He's a good kid.
He's a great kid.
Kristen, I did not do this
to hurt you, okay?
I just could not take
a chance on losing my son.
So what do we do now?
I want Mark.
What about me?
You can go to hell
for all I care.
[Matthew]
Dad?
Matthew.
That's the woman.
She's the one.
I told him
you're from the IRS.
Huh?
Come on board, Matthew.
We need to talk.
Matthew, son...
I know I told you
that, uh...
that this woman
was from the IRS,
but that wasn't true.
Why would you--
She...
She's your mother.
She came here
to bring you home.
My mother?
You're my mother?
I thought you were dead.
Dad?
I'm sorry. I, uh...
When you were a little boy
your mother and I were--
were getting divorced.
I was scared
I was gonna lose you,
so I--I
just took you away.
I made a mistake,
a big mistake.
I did it for all
the right reasons.
I'm gonna fix the radio,
so why don't you two, um...
go down to the beach,
take a little walk on shore?
Everything
she said was true.
Matthew even closed
their bank account
before he left.
So what are you gonna do?
I have a helicopter
coming over from Provo.
It's picking me up,
and then I'm going
to Salt Cay.
And then what?
You tell me.
Kidnapping,
immigration fraud,
false passports.
It's a laundry list
of charges.
Our Captain John
could be going to jail
for a very long time.
Is that really necessary?
I hope not.
Why didn't you
tell me yesterday?
I wanted to. I tried.
All these years, I tried
to remember your face,
what you looked like,
the things you taught me.
Now you're here.
It must have been
really hard for you.
I would wake up...
to your scent
every day.
And then I would bury
myself in the pillow
and try to...
breathe you in.
But it only lasted
for a second,
and then it was gone.
I couldn't stand
to open my eyes.
I can't believe
you're here.
"Can't" is not
in the dictionary, remember?
[both chuckle]
Matt! Kris!
Let's go.
We got to get back
to the boat.
Dad, what is it?
The hurricane,
it's coming.
Eduardo?
It's way
north of us.
Well, not anymore.
It turned last night
and it's speeding up.
It's already
a category 4.
I didn't hear
anything about it.
The radio was broken,
but I, uh--
I fixed it.
It's on every frequency.
Maritime posted a warning.
It's stretched out
500 miles.
It's true.
They were boarding up
in Santa Alicia.
There's no shelter
on this island.
Maybe we can make a run
for Ambergris Cay.
They got a harbor.
Santa Alicia's
way closer.
I know, but I can't
go back there.
They'll be looking for me.
You're just gonna
keep running?
I got no choice, son.
Now come on.
[Man on radio]
Dive boatPhoenix,
this is Provo air rescue.
We're approaching Salt Cay.
Come in if you are
receiving us.
Come in, please.
There's a helicopter
coming to take us out.
We can beat the storm.
Phoenix,this is
Officer Bodden onboard
Provo air rescue.
[Bodden on radio]
What is your exact
location on Salt Cay?
Are you on the north end
or the south end?
Dad, they've got
the police with them.
If you tell them
how to find us,
you'll go to jail.
Matthew, if I don't,
we could all die out here.
But you'll die in prison.
You can't live locked up.
Look, I couldn't--
I couldn't live
the rest of my life
if anything happened
to the two of you.
I've already caused
enough pain.
Provo air rescue,
this is thePhoenix.
I repeat,
We're on the southwest
end of Salt Cay
awaiting your
instructions, over.
[Man on radio]
Stay where you are,
Phoenix.
We should be with you
in six minutes.
Is that you, John?
No, Officer Bodden.
It's Quinn Halloran
with my son Mark
and his mother.
We're, uh...
we're awaiting
your arrival.
Well, son,
we had a good ride.
Dad, please,
just take the boat.
Go, please.
I can't.
Bodden will have alerted
every port in the Caribbean,
and I'd rather
serve my time here
than rot in some
jail cell in Haiti.
We had a good ride, son.
Then take the key
to theZodiac.
They'll never
find you on it.
It's too small.
You sure?
Don't ask me. Just take it.
Take care of our boy.
Be seeing you around,
sailor.
Dad, wait.
Please, you don't
have to do this, Dad.
Don't go, please.
I'm sorry, son.
There's just no other way.
Your mother needs you
now, okay?
And you need her, too.
I love you.
I love you, Dad.
I know.
I love you, too.
I've got to go.
[Matthew sighs]
I'll be seeing you.
All right, man.
All right.
Keep in touch.
I hope you don't mind.
I left your Los Angeles
number with some locals
just in case anything,
you know--
You didn't give it
to Patrick, did you?
No, no.
Good.
[both laugh]
It's gonna be
so different.
America, you know?
It's your home.
Yeah.
But your husband--
Steve.
Yeah, you think
he's going to--
Like a beach bum
like you?
He has been wanting
to learn how to surf
ever since we met.
Did I tell you
how we met?
Well, once upon a time...
you're in for
a long ride home.
[Matthew chuckles]
Closed-Captioned By
J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA