("I've Got My Love to Keep Me Warm"
by Dean Martin playing)
♪ The snow is snowing ♪
♪ And the wind, it is blowing ♪
♪ But I can weather the storm ♪
♪ What do I care how much it may storm? ♪
♪ I've got my love to keep me warm ♪
♪ I cannot remember ♪
♪ A worse December ♪
♪ Just watch those icicles form ♪
♪ What do I care if icicles form? ♪
♪ I've got my love... ♪
Okay, so this one's called a cushion cut,
and the other one is called a...
SALESWOMAN:
Princess cut.
Yeah. Uh, these-these things
don't really feel like her.
Do you have a presidential cut?
How about...
something a little more classic?
That is the one.
You have good taste, Daisy.
Yes, I do.
You heard the boss.
Very good. Right this way.
♪ So I will weather the storm ♪
♪ What do I care how much it may storm? ♪
♪ I've got my love... ♪
Hi. Can I help you?
Sorry, yeah. Um, I'm looking
to get a present for my girlfriend.
I was hoping that one of those blue boxes
would do the trick.
Okay. Anything specific you had in mind?
Not really.
Uh, just hopefully something
that's reasonable.
- All right, let me show you what we have.
- Great.
(entry bell jingles)
♪ I thought you ought to know
my heart's... ♪
- Sure you're okay with this?
- Yes, Dad. I'm fine, okay?
I mean, everything is good.
Like... (grunts)
(Daisy scoffs)
People are crazy here, huh?
- No crazier than L.A.
- (horn blares, tires screech, thump)
- (people gasping)
- (gasps) Oh, my God, Dad, is he okay?
- Do not leave my sight.
- I-I won't.
- ETHAN: You okay, man?
- Yeah.
- ETHAN: You call 911?
- No, but there's an ambulance right there.
- (siren wails) -MAN: Right here, man.
- ETHAN: Hey, you okay, man?
- Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, chill.
- EMT: Hi. I'm a paramedic.
- I got this.
- GARY: Yeah, no, I'm totally fine.
- EMT: Sir, what's your name?
- What?
- No, no, I'm fine.
- Yep, you're okay.
(slurps)
Do you need harissa?
Hmm.
Mmm!
You needed harissa. Perfect.
- Let's boil.
- (stove igniter clicking)
- Great. Actually...
- Are you talking to your fish again?
- No.
- Uh-huh.
I'm talking to my soup.
Oh, okay. Well, I come bearing Eureka.
Oh, my God, thank you.
Yeah. That's just the type of friend I am.
You just asked for lemons,
but I know you like...
BOTH:
Eureka!
Yeah, 'cause you like doing that.
Had to.
Okay, wow!
Casual at-home anniversary, huh?
Ha ha.
Rach, I love that you finally framed this.
I will always love our firstborn.
Even if that one critic did say the
ambiance reminded him of a gas station.
I personally like gas stations.
They have really good snacks.
God, you have such a good attitude.
- It's terrifying.
- (laughs)
Um, I need to change.
Can you simmer the soup
in like two minutes, please?
Okay. You got, uh, food
in your hair, by the way.
- Yeah, right there.
- Hmm? Oh. Oh.
Yo, it's amazing what a mess
you're capable of making.
It looks like you taught a cooking class
to a bunch of toddlers.
Yeah, that's the vibe I was going for.
Um, you should get going 'cause
Gary's gonna be here around 7:00.
Okay, so I guess I'll leave
in, what, like two, three hours, then?
That's hilarious.
What are you, a stand-up comedian?
I been working on a tight five.
(chuckles)
By the way, I saw his write-up
in New York Magazine.
- You did?
- New York's freshest tattoo artist.
I assume you helped with that?
- Hmm.
- Okay, I did.
What? So I sent him
a bunch of our cannoli.
I was like, "Maybe you can put in
a good word with the culture editor,"
- and they did.
- Hmm. Aren't you generous.
You can bribe people with cannoli.
Good to know.
Terri, you haven't said anything
about my outfit.
What do you think?
- You look incredible.
- It's a lot.
It's a lot, but I'm thinking
it's sort of giving off
a J.Lo picking up her kids from school
on the way to the Grammys vibe.
He definitely won't notice
this messy-ass kitchen.
No, he won't.
- (phone vibrating)
- (laughs) Oh, your phone's ringing.
- Oh.
- It's Gary.
(singsongy):
Looks like I'm having fish tonight.
- Terri.
- What?
Hi, honey. You on your way?
I'm sorry, who's this?
What?
(tablet ringing)
I can't find it anywhere.
If I help you find your phone,
will you give me one as a thank-you?
Don't start. And don't tell her,
because you know she hates it.
Hey, hey!
- VANESSA (over tablet): Aloha.
- Mahalo.
- Girl.
- Oh, please.
Like you've never seen Moana.
- How is it going over there?
- It's the best.
All the trees are lit,
we went ice-skating,
and we saw a guy get hit by a car.
- Oh, my God.
- No. It was a good... really good day,
minus the guy and the car,
but he's fine, I-I think.
You know, we could do it all again
once you get here.
No need.
Yeah, I remember very well,
you know, the crowds, the smells.
I actually like all those things.
- When's your flight get in?
- Uh, tomorrow night at 5:00.
What are you guys gonna do until then?
Well, Daisy's gonna hang out with Nina,
who she hasn't seen since the first grade.
Oh, fun. Okay.
Yeah, while Dad has his meeting.
- What meeting?
- WOMAN: Vanessa, margarita time!
I'm coming.
Okay, I have to go, but I will see you
guys so soon with lots of presents, okay?
DAISY: Have fun on the last day
of your girls' trip.
(sighs) So, here's the thing about
not telling Vanessa about the meeting.
What's wrong?
You said you "think" that man's okay.
Look, sweetie... (stammers)
the ambulance got there really quickly.
But sometimes people aren't okay.
What if he's not?
You're right.
I think he's fine, but in the morning,
we can go to the hospital
and-and check up on him.
Okay.
- (monitor beeping steadily)
- RACHEL: The doctor on call last night
told me that he had a concussion.
How bad is it?
- How do you feel?
- I've felt worse.
Concussion's mild.
You know, no broken bones.
Maybe a bruise here and there.
- That's it?
- That's it.
(sighs) Damn it.
- My phone.
- Your what?
It's cracked.
- (chuckles)
- Yeah, you're right.
It seems like he's gonna be just fine.
All right, well, Rita's got it from here.
- Okay.
- All right.
Okay, so we're holding him for an MRI
because he has some memory loss.
Memory loss? She didn't say anything...
You don't remember
what happened last night?
Not really.
I mean, that can't be good.
That sounds bad.
Is that... is that serious?
He's gonna be fine.
So I should be getting seen
any minute now, right?
Uh, looks like not until tonight,
um, worst-case tomorrow.
- You should go.
- No.
I'm not leaving you here.
Come on. Really.
You should be more worried
about my phone right now.
Stop it.
It's broken.
I'm totally fine.
You should be at the restaurant.
Seriously.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Bye.
- I'm gonna take your stuff.
This is it.
Take good care of him.
- I love you.
- Love you.
(man speaking indistinctly over P.A.)
Hey, what's the snack situation here?
Hmm?
No, no, we're not family.
We just... we wanted to check up on him.
All we know is that he was hit by a cab.
I'm sorry, I can't release information
on patients,
especially if you don't even
know his name.
Please. We just want to know if he's okay.
All right? He came in last night.
He was hit by a cab in SoHo.
My dad brought him back to life.
No. (stammers)
Um, no, that's-that's not...
DAISY:
But you did. It was because of you.
Excuse me?
- That's not exactly what happened.
- Hi.
Hi.
Sorry to interrupt. I just overheard you...
Were you guys there last night
with the guy that got hit by the taxi?
You know you don't
have to disclose anything.
Oh, no, I know. His name's Gary.
He has a concussion.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, but it's so small.
- He's gonna be totally fine. Yeah.
- ETHAN (sighs): Oh, good.
We're glad to hear that. You hear that, D?
What happened?
Uh, I'm sorry, you guys can't linger here.
If you want to finish this conversation,
you're gonna have to take it elsewhere.
- Are you and Gary married?
- Uh, no, no. We're...
We are... we're...
- Best friends.
- Well...
Are you a stripper?
- What? (chuckles)
- ETHAN: Wow.
Do you live in New York?
Yeah, I live in, uh, Queens.
- What about you?
- DAISY: L.A.
But we used to live here,
uh, and we might come back.
Well, that's cool.
You can work from either city.
Bicoastal. Fancy.
Uh, kinda.
You know, I-I'm a creative writing
professor at UCLA.
- Cool.
- DAISY: But he's also an author,
and he wants to write another book.
All right. So, yeah.
We probably should bounce
before Rachel here leaves
with our Social Security numbers.
At least I didn't ruin the proposal.
I heard nothing.
I heard absolutely nothing.
I'm losing it. I should go get some sleep,
put on human... human people clothes.
I'm wearing heels in a hospital.
That is what I'm... doing. I got to go.
Sleep sounds most important right there.
- I think you're right.
- Yeah, I think so, too.
So, if you guys find yourselves
in Bryant Park at all,
my restaurant has, uh, a little spot
in the Christmas market,
and I would really love to
properly thank you with a meal or...
- Oh, for real? Yeah.
- Yeah.
What's it called?
It's called Gillini. It's a bakery.
- Bakery?
- Uh-huh. And a restaurant in Little Italy.
Hold on, now. Like, you just met
the biggest consumer of bread in America.
- Ah, no way.
- Yeah.
That's you?
I've been dying to meet you for years.
(sighs)
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
(breathes deeply)
♪ ♪
- (phone ringing)
- Oh, shit.
Corner office. Well done.
I guess print's not so dead after all.
Oh, well, I'm hanging on for dear life.
Have a seat.
Let's see if we can get you back into
the Simon & Schuster family.
Okay, well, that's what I want to hear.
Hold on. So you're not gonna open the box?
No, no, no, I can't.
I mean, I can, but...
No, I can't. That's-that's not okay.
That's worse than, like,
going through someone's phone.
But he's in the hospital.
He won't even know.
Terri, Terri, even if I opened it,
I couldn't get it back
to the way that it was.
You know that tying bows gives me anxiety.
My fingers... my... they're tiny fingers.
- They don't work like that.
- That's true.
You did wear Velcro shoes
until the seventh grade.
But Sophia has a very artful hand.
- Right, baby?
- Damn right I do.
TERRI:
Come on. I got to know what's inside.
Inside what? Inside what?
You act like I'm not gonna hang up
and tell you everything.
What if it is... (chuckles)
what we think it is?
I don't know if I'm ready for this.
What do I do?
TERRI: I mean, hey,
that would be more surprising than
him having a secret love child
or something, right?
He has a secret love child?
- (mouthing)
- RACHEL: Terri.
Okay. All right. So what's the plan?
I don't know what the plan is.
I guess the plan is that I'm gonna work
until they schedule him for an MRI,
and then I'm gonna run and pick him up.
That's the plan.
And the box?
- Are we just glazing over that now?
- No, no, no. It's just...
The thing is, right, we don't know
for sure, like, that it's a ring, right?
(chuckles)
They sell lots of things at Tiffany's.
- (whispers): What box?
- Pens. They sell pens.
RACHEL:
And you know what?
Actually, one time,
I saw a yo-yo from there.
It could be a yo-yo, Terri.
Hell, if he got you a pen or a yo-yo,
girl, you got bigger problems.
RACHEL:
I don't know.
A Tiffany's yo-yo
sounds pretty cool to me.
Okay, I just got in the stall.
I got to go.
And I need 17 coffees.
Okay, bye.
Girl, it's a mess.
Just be glad we ain't them.
(phone dings)
(phone chirps)
("Warm December" by Julie London playing)
♪ I'll keep you warm in December ♪
♪ Warm when the cold breezes blow ♪
♪ My arms so lovin'... ♪
You're welcome. Uh, what do I recommend?
The za'atar focaccia, the garlic
sun-dried tomato or cornetti, my favorite.
(chuckles) It's a funny story.
I'll give you the short one.
Uh, I admittedly dressed up as a cornetti
for Halloween when I was 11.
It was like a... I made it.
It was a papier-mâché marvel of sorts.
- MAN: I'm sorry, I'm in a rush.
- I digress. Yes.
No, no, no, no, no, keep going.
Hi.
I wasn't sure you'd be here,
but I was nearby and remembered.
- Um...
- WOMAN: How much is this?
That's 4.99.
- What is this?
- That's a...
- cutting board.
- Can I buy it?
For sure. Yeah.
I'm just gonna finish up with her.
That's good. That's perfect.
Enjoy. Thank you so much.
I want a coffee, hot.
Okay. I'm just gonna get him.
I'll get you.
You good?
(laughs):
Yeah, I'm good.
I mean, I ain't cheap,
but I could at least help with coffee.
Oh, no, no, no. Thank you,
but, um, um, everything is just...
- (woman gasps)
- (clattering)
Oh, God.
...going swimmingly, clearly.
I've been here 15 minutes.
Can I buy all the cornetti
and five coffees?
- Do you have a manager?
- (timer beeps)
Whatever your rate is, I'll pay it.
- Who wants coffee?
- WOMAN: I do. -MAN: Right here.
And, uh, yeah, thank you for getting that.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you. Have a great one.
- Is it coming out or... Oh, man.
- ("Lady Luck" by Richard Swift playing)
What would you like?
- Uh, would you...
- Oh, sure.
- All right, all right.
- (busy chatter)
- Two waters or just one water?
- (stammers)
- WOMAN: I'll take one of those.
- Got it.
4.75.
- Okay, great.
- Thank you very much.
- You guys good?
- (chuckles) Okay.
- You okay?
- (both laugh)
Thank you very much.
♪ Lady luck, she is lovely... ♪
- (mouth full): This is good. (mumbles)
- That's really good, right?
- Cheers.
- Okay.
- ♪ Lady luck, she is free... ♪
- (song fades)
I didn't realize there was such a market
for cutting boards.
- Any word from Gary?
- Yeah, actually.
It sounds like he can finally get a scan
in the next hour, thank God. (chuckles)
(phone chirps)
Where's Daisy and your...?
Daisy's at a friend's house,
and Vanessa's flight got delayed, so...
RACHEL:
Oh, no.
I have a little hot chocolate left.
Would you like a cup?
Sure.
Do you want regular old hot chocolate,
or do you want hot chocolate a la Gillini?
(Ethan chuckles)
(laughs) Whatever the chef recommends.
This is what the chef recommends.
- Ah, oh.
- (laughs)
Okay.
Yeah, oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You are my friend.
You're delicious, and you make me happy.
We're gonna pour a little bit of you.
- (laughs)
- And a little more of you.
- Okay.
- I have a small tendency
of talking to my culinary creations.
I talk to myself all the time
when I write.
Well, mostly yell at myself,
but same same.
- Cheers.
- Mm.
- (chuckles)
- Cheers.
- Shit.
- Good, right?
What?
Well, as a thank-you...
...for you.
What?
Uh, my late wife and Daisy,
they used to bake bread together.
Right around Christmas.
Was she a baker?
- No, it was... the bread was awful.
- (laughs)
The bread was awful.
- Bread is hard.
- Really hard.
(sighs) I hadn't thought about it
in a while.
What was she... like,
if you don't mind me asking?
No. She was like, uh, like a song.
Like a song that you wanted to play
over and over again.
The risk of love is loss, right?
That's something my mom used to say.
When did you lose your mom?
Uh...
I had just turned nine, so...
(sighs)
Well, that's all the time
that we have here, so...
(both laugh)
I'll invoice you.
(laughs)
How'd you decide that this is
what you wanted to do, though?
Like, to bake.
It was never really, like,
a firm decision.
I just kept falling
more and more in love with it.
It's like a meditation,
it's a love language all in one.
It's messy, but I just...
I love that something beautiful
always comes out of the mess.
I like that. It's cool.
I don't mean to pry.
What was... what were you...
Daisy was saying you're writing a book?
- Another book, yeah.
- Oh, so there was a first?
Yeah, it was a disaster,
the Titanic of books, yeah.
(laughs) I'm sure it wasn't that bad.
Well, nobody died from it.
You know, Gillini was not
my first go-around.
My first go-around,
my first restaurant was a big flop.
Huge. Embarrassing.
Disastrous. Bankrupting.
- You get the point.
- (laughs): Yeah.
If yours was the Titanic of books,
mine was the 127 Hours of restaurants.
- Wow. (laughs)
- But Gillini...
Gillini was always my dream, you know?
Toss this out.
Okay.
Do you know what this is?
A croissant.
First of all, this is a cornetto.
(laughs):
Okay. All right.
Little-known Italian cousin
of the renowned croissant.
Thank you very much.
You know why it tastes so good?
Because it was baked with love,
not strategy.
- And probably a shit-ton of butter.
- Oh, yeah.
Maybe you need to start
doing things with your heart.
Not your head.
(chuckles)
Well, I do have this one idea
that I... I really love.
Tell me. What is it?
I kind of got to show you to explain it.
If you, if you have time, we could...
I don't know, um... Yeah.
I mean, I guess I have a little time.
We could drop these off at the shelter
and then check it out quickly.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, that-that'd be great.
Okay.
My secret spot.
What do you think?
- Well...
- Yeah, it's like, can you believe
no one is ever here?
That's, um...
I mean, that's-that's crazy.
Have you been here?
- Me?
- Yeah, you.
Um... yeah, maybe a few times, but...
- Wow. Dang.
- (laughing)
Well, great minds think alike.
No, I love it here.
This is what inspired my idea.
Go on.
Tell me.
It's a novel about light and dark
based in New York City.
It's this little girl.
She finds her imaginary friends
in the shadows of the city buildings.
So it's all about how
she creates this world where
people overlook the shadows, but
that's where she finds beauty and life.
This...
This is your cornetto.
Yeah, maybe it is.
I think it is.
(phone vibrating)
Oh, it's Gary. Um, one sec.
Hi, honey. How you feeling?
(phone dings)
Oh, my God, that's great.
That's great. Okay.
Well, I'm close, so I-I'll be right there.
All right, I love you. Bye.
Gary just got out of his MRI.
Yeah, Vanessa just, uh, text me.
Her flight just got here,
so I should probably go.
Okay.
Thanks for everything tonight. (chuckles)
Yeah. I'm glad Gary's okay.
Uh, M-Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
I'm Jewish, by the way.
(Rachel laughs)
ETHAN:
Happy Hanukkah.
Bye.
(siren wailing in distance)
("Underneath the Tree" playing)
♪ We are young and haven't got a cent... ♪
- Hi.
- Hi. Merry Christmas.
(Rachel chuckles)
I like semi-concussed Gary.
- Girl could get used to this.
- (chuckles)
Ooh. What is this?
Oh. (chuckles) Crumbs.
- I'm making a pie for tonight.
- Oh.
What are you making now?
This is a chervil frittata
with preserved lemon salsa verde
and roasted tomatoes on the vine.
- Huh?
- Eggs, herbs, tomatoes.
Mm.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Just kind of a mess in here.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- We have hot sauce, right?
- Yeah, right there.
Oh, good. Thank God. Okay.
Hey, babe, um, why don't you pause
on those eggs for a minute.
We have Chrismukkah presents to open.
Come on.
Oh. Ok... You want to do that right now?
Well, okay, Vanessa, you first.
- Come on.
- No, Daisy, you go first. Here.
DAISY:
Oh, okay.
Are you sure you don't want to eat first?
Because when eggs sit on the stove,
bacteria festers,
and that bacteria gets much worse,
like, more deadly
- as the food is cooling.
- This is for you.
(sighs)
RACHEL:
You first.
- Okay.
(gasps) This is nice.
One for every day.
DAISY:
I've always wanted an affirmation journal.
Thank you.
This is the most expensive hint
I've ever seen.
(laughs) I did not mean it like that.
Oh, no. I-I love it.
- You do?
- Yeah.
- Maybe it will help.
- It might.
- It very well might.
- (laughs)
Okay, now Vanessa's turn.
Uh, let's let your dad open one.
Here.
(Vanessa sighs)
- Now we can eat.
- GARY: No.
- It's your turn.
- Wow.
Gary.
ETHAN:
Okay. Now it's your turn.
(Vanessa chuckles)
Wow. (chuckles)
(sighs):
Okay.
(clears throat)
(chuckles)
♪ ♪
Ethan.
Oh, my God.
They're beautiful.
They're so cute.
What do you think?
Uh...
What? You-you didn't think I'd like them?
No. I-I, um...
- They're-they're so you.
- So cute.
I don't know what to say.
Me neither.
- Are you...
- (sighs heavily)
Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
No, I-I'm just... (exhales)
- Me, too. I'm...
- (chuckles) I mean, this is...
this is a really big moment, you know?
- Very big moment.
- Very big.
I mean, I-I thought that I had
something prepared to say.
I'm sure I did. I'm pretty good at that.
- I-I like talking.
- You do.
You know, so... But-but I don't.
I don't remember what I was thinking or...
- or what I was gonna say. (chuckles)
- It's okay. You don't have to.
- No, I...
- You don't have to say anything.
It doesn't matter.
I mean, who cares
if I don't remember a day or two?
Right?
What I do remember
is the last three years, Rach.
You made me into a better artist.
Into a better person.
And I have you to thank for that.
'Cause you encourage me,
and you tell me that
I can do more and be more.
And you believe in me.
I do.
So...
- (softly): Oh, my gosh.
- (exhales sharply)
Will you?
Yes.
I'm sweating. (laughs)
- Uh, champagne.
- Okay.
Okay. (laughs)
(whispers):
Holy shit.
All right, time to eat.
Where can we order in on Christmas?
'Cause I did not cook. (laughs)
(chuckles) Thank you.
What happened?
Holy shit.
(camera clicking)
(sighs)
♪ ♪
- (birds chirping)
- (horns honking)
- TERRI: Oh, my God.
- (chuckles)
- Did he rob a bank?
- (laughs)
He must have sold an organ or something.
Did... did he kill somebody?
You know, a lot of people
been doing life insurance fraud.
I'm-I'm not saying that's what he did,
but damn, that's a big-ass ring.
- It is beautiful, Rach.
- Thank you.
- It's huge.
- Yeah.
Kind of wildly huge.
But he did a great job.
I guess he's been saving up
for a studio, but...
- MAN and WOMAN: Thank you.
- Bye. Thank you guys so much.
...clearly, also for this.
Maybe instead of saving up
for that ridiculous cappuccino maker
we just had to have,
you could buy your wife something nice.
You love my latte art.
I made your face last week,
and you loved it, remember?
- That was supposed to be me?
- Yeah.
Oh, hell no.
Anyways, are you guys gonna have,
like, a big party or something?
I don't think so.
I'm not really into big parties
and all that.
Yeah, nah, she loves the romance
but not the fanfare.
- Well, I am so excited for you.
- Thank you.
You deserve everything, sweetie.
Hey, I'm excited, too.
But if I'm too genuine,
my heart will explode and I'll die, so...
- I can't with you.
- (inhales sharply) Can't do it.
I have to go to work. Can you behave?
Yeah, I'll try.
- SOPHIA: Later, Rach.
- Bye.
Can you take this? Thank you so much.
- I'll take those.
- TERRI: Hey, um...
what was that weird text
you sent me last night?
- Hmm?
- "The East River is so serene at night"?
Oh, my God, I forgot about that. Yeah.
Yeah. Who gave you mushrooms,
and can you give me their number?
No, I was at this beautiful park
with Ethan when Gary called...
Wait, wait.
- Run that back. Who's Ethan?
- Ethan.
I told you about Ethan.
No, you never told me about an Ethan.
Ethan's the one who helped Gary
when he got hit.
I met him at the hospital.
And then he came by the stall.
And then you two just
went on a romantic stroll
- down the East River alone?
- Oh, my God, Terri.
I'm not doing this with you.
We were just killing time.
(stammers) He lives in L.A.
I'm never gonna see him again,
so whatever. Okay?
- Okay.
- Look how shiny.
(sighs):
Yeah.
Gary... How do I say this?
It feels like he's really trying.
And I'm not saying that
it changed everything overnight,
but it feels like there's so much
possibility for the future.
Like, he's so excited,
and I'm excited, and...
Hey. I'm excited, too.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Bling-bling.
♪ ♪
ETHAN:
Oh, I'm so glad you're here.
I-I have something
kind of weird to tell you.
Excuse me?
Uh, sorry, I-I thought
you were someone else.
Where's Rachel?
Uh, well, she's not here right now,
but I am. (chuckles)
- Hi.
Uh, she'll be back at the Little Italy
location tomorrow afternoon.
Is there something
I can help you with now?
No, no, no. Um, no.
I-I'll figure it out. Thank you.
Surprise.
Alvin Ailey. Who's that?
Oh, that's a dance company.
That's gonna be so fun.
Wait, there's only two tickets.
Dais, you can handle yourself, right?
I figured a girls' day might be in order.
Wow. And what are you gonna do?
That three-story Olive Garden
in Times Square looks fun.
(laughs):
Nah, nah.
I-I think I'm gonna try to write.
Yeah, I haven't done it in a while, and
the city is really inspiring me right now.
Wait, you're gonna (chuckles)
write on our vacation?
I-If that's cool.
You know, uh, I asked for
a girls' day out anyway.
So I feel like I could use one.
- Thanks, Dad.
- (sighs)
Yeah. I-I feel very honored.
Um, I will get dressed,
and we will head out.
- Okay? Okay.
- Okay.
- Thank you. Wish me luck.
(door opens, closes)
Please don't tell me
you forgot your phone again.
You got to go get the ring back.
Just remember not to say anything.
I won't say anything.
I won't. Promise.
(door opens, closes)
- TERRI: Hey, Rach.
- Hey.
What did you need again?
It was, uh, black truffles and...
Porcini mushrooms.
Oh, and I talked to the wheelman.
He said he's gonna get the entrées
out of the window much faster tonight.
Perfect. I'm gonna get some more focaccia.
Okay.
TERRI:
Porcini.
- Hi. Uh, sorry, yeah.
- Hi.
Um, I'm-I'm looking for Rachel Meyer.
And who might you be?
- (laughs) Sorry, I'm Ethan.
- Ethan.
Hello again. (chuckles)
Hi.
Mr. East River. Ooh.
Yeah, this is... th-th...
this is Terri, my business partner.
I also identify as her best friend.
Business partner, best friend.
She does it all.
I was actually looking for Gary.
Oh.
Uh... okay.
What do you need Gary for?
Yeah, no, sorry.
I-I thought maybe I could meet him here
or you could connect us,
just to check up on him.
How is he, actually?
- Um...
- You're quite the detective, aren't you?
And fine as hell, too.
- What are those, hazel?
- Terri. Oh, my God. Terri.
- Huh? What?
- (laughs)
I need you... we need... can...
We need more focaccia.
Can you go inside
and get some more focaccia?
I know for a fact that
we don't need more focaccia.
But you know what?
I'll go get some ciabatta.
Thank you so much.
- Good day, fine sir.
- Thank you.
- (chuckles): Good day.
- Sorry about that. (laughs)
Um, I'm actually about to go grab a bite
with Gary around the corner.
You want me to give him your number?
Well, I-I was actually hoping
I could meet him.
Oh. Want to eat with me and Gary?
Yeah, that could be cool.
Or I could walk with you.
- Whatever. (chuckles)
- Okay. Sure. Sure.
Absolutely.
I'm gonna put these in the back.
- Okay. (chuckles)
- We'll head out.
Awesome.
- RECEPTIONIST: Gary.
- Oh.
Got time for one more?
(sighs) I should really get going.
Are you sure? This guy requested you, man.
- Ah. Yeah.
- Yeah? Okay.
I'm sure Gary will be here any minute.
(sighs) You know, all good.
I could just wait until he gets here.
Hmm?
(chuckles)
Uh... wow.
Oh! Yes.
I forget that it's... yes.
Wow.
Christmas morning.
That's... it...
That looks beautiful on you.
Thank you. Just such a big gesture.
It was very unlike Gary, but what a ring.
It's the most beautiful ring
I've ever seen in my life.
Uh-huh.
(chuckles):
Yeah.
No, what about you?
How'd your proposal go?
(clicks tongue)
(exhales heavily)
It didn't.
Oh.
But it will.
(phone dings)
Gary.
Seems like he got caught up at work,
so I don't think he's gonna be able
to make it, actually.
But we could stay if you want.
Sure, yeah.
Sorry about that.
Um, how did you and Gary meet?
Actually, this.
I wanted to get a tattoo of my mom's name,
and a few friends recommended this
one shop, and he was the artist available.
Which is so funny.
I mean, I know it sounds kind of cheesy,
but now sometimes I wonder if it was fate.
Yeah. It's fun...
- Weird.
- Mm-hmm.
(stammers) Let me ask, uh...
Here's a good question.
- Mm-hmm?
- Gary's a good guy, right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah?
Like... (stammers) like, would he, say,
return fi... a five-dollar bill
if someone dropped it?
What?
Yeah, no. That's... Yeah. That is...
Um, I was just trying to, you know,
g-get to know him a little.
- (chuckles)
- How do I describe Gary?
Gary is an artist.
He's super talented.
On the surface,
he can come across a little self-absorbed,
but there's so much more to him.
Nobody stood by me quite like him
when my first restaurant fell apart.
He was amazing.
I'm trying to think of what else.
I mean, there's a lot to say. Uh...
Oh! Another example.
This bracelet was my mom's.
I wear it everywhere.
I do not know
what I would do if I lost it.
It's very precious to me.
You get the point.
I took the bracelet off when
I was in the chair getting my tattoo,
and when I got home,
I realized I didn't have the bracelet.
I panicked, I ran to the station,
and there was Gary.
He rode all the way out to Astoria.
And I remember looking at him, being like,
"Wow, this is the kind of guy that he is."
So if I ever... well, when I get frustrated
that he's late or misses dinner
or (laughs) is wrapped up in his own stuff
or always on his phone,
I remember that he's the guy that went
eight subway stops out of his way for me
when he didn't even know me.
So, sorry. In the longest answer ever,
yes, he is the kind of guy
who would return five dollars.
(clicks tongue) Wow.
You really do have a thing for bread.
(laughs):
I do. Yeah. I'm sor... Yeah.
- Uh, number one fan.
- Numero uno.
- Number one fan.
- That's you.
DAISY: I can't believe
how they just move all together like that.
I mean, the kids in my grade have a hard
time just getting into alphabetical order.
Yeah, well, you know,
I was jealous that they were so flexible.
I do Bar Method three times a week,
and I can barely touch my toes.
- Brian?
- Vanessa.
Hey, how are you?
- Good. How are you?
- I'm good, good.
Uh, I'm sorry.
- This is my colleague David.
- Hey.
David, this is Vanessa Randall.
She was in-house PR for
the YA division before she abandoned us
for the dark side... L.A.
- Ah.
- Well, you know,
three years of slush and street garbage
was plenty for me.
No argument there.
- Uh, this is Daisy, Ethan's daughter.
- Hi.
Brian actually introduced me to your dad.
It's true. You know, he showed me
a picture of you the other day.
Listen, I'm so excited Ethan came in.
You know, I've been telling him for ages
to give it another shot.
I bet it was your encouragement.
Uh, I-I always encourage him,
but, you know, you know Ethan.
He just needs to forge ahead.
You know, none of us have
a crystal ball, right?
- Yeah.
- We just got to do our best.
Uh, good to see you.
- You, too. Bye.
- Nice to meet you.
- Bye.
(sighs):
Okay.
(groans) God.
- And these are new.
- (laughing)
Taxi?
GARY:
Hey, T.
Well, lookee lookee who it is.
She's mad, huh?
- Well, I came to surprise her.
- Mm.
Got her these flowers.
- Pretty nice, huh?
Yeah, they're from the bodega.
Uh, is she here?
No.
I actually haven't seen her
since she left to meet you.
Mm.
Mm-hmm.
You know what I was thinking about
earlier today?
- What?
- The book you're gonna write.
Ah, well, I hope I write it.
What do you mean, you hope?
It's a lot of (sighs) procrastination
mixed in with self-loathing.
I've got a great therapist.
You just got to go for it.
I can't wait to be walking by a bookstore
one day and see it in the window.
- (laughs) I like that.
- (men singing "I Only Have Eyes for You")
♪ I can't see anyone but you... ♪
(scatting and harmonizing)
- (sighs) I love this song.
- I love this song.
Okay.
(both laughing)
♪ For you ♪
(Rachel laughing)
- Okay.
- Wow.
- (laughing)
- This is ridiculous.
It is nice, though. (laughing)
♪ Maybe millions of people walk by ♪
♪ But they all disappear... ♪
Ethan, I'm sorry that
Gary didn't show up, but I...
Can I just ask you a question?
Did you really come
to see him tonight, or...?
Um...
(sighs):
Uh, are you okay to get home from here?
What? I...
I-I hope everything works out for you.
No matter what happens,
I want you to know that
I mean that sincerely.
♪ ♪
(Ethan sighs)
VANESSA:
Ethan?
I'll be in in a second.
I-I called you. Where'd you go?
(sighs) Sorry. I...
My phone is MIA again.
I-I need to put a damn tracker
on that thing.
Is there something you need to tell me?
Nothing that you need to worry about.
Okay.
I mean, you pushed hard for this trip.
I changed my plans.
I got on a flight for ten hours to be here
with you and Daisy 'cause you asked me to,
and, you know, now I'm here
and you're not.
I know.
Okay, well...
whatever it is, I'm here.
Okay.
(sighs)
Uh, Gary Wilson?
What can I do for you?
I'm Ethan Greene.
I... We haven't formally met.
Oh, yeah.
Um, you're the guy from the accident.
- Yeah, I-I read the report.
- Yeah.
Um, thank you so much
for what you did, man.
It was nothing, man.
Um... happy to help.
How can I... help you? (chuckles)
Um...
So, I-I, you know, I think...
I think we have something of each other's.
Look, I have about a week's worth
to catch up on in here, so...
...thank you again so much
for what you did...
Okay. I want my ring back.
(smacks lips)
What ring?
The ring that was supposed to be
on my girlfriend's hand right now,
but I saw Rachel wearing it last night.
You saw Rachel last night?
Okay. You...
Give me my ring back,
I'll give you your earrings back.
No harm, no foul.
Um...
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yes, you do.
You can't be serious
about letting her keep it.
Not telling her?
Stay away from my fiancée.
You lost something, it's not my problem.
- ♪ Trust in me ♪
- ("Trust in Me" by Etta James playing)
♪ In all you do ♪
♪ Have the faith I have in you ♪
♪ Love will see us through ♪
♪ If only you trust in me ♪
♪ While there's a moon ♪
♪ A moon up high ♪
♪ While there are birds ♪
♪ Birds to fly ♪
♪ While there is you ♪
♪ A you and I ♪
♪ I can be sure ♪
♪ That I love you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Stand beside me, stand beside me... ♪
- (song fades)
- (quiet chatter)
- Hi.
- How can I help you?
I recently got... engaged.
- Mazel.
- Thank you very much.
And I-I just...
I-I wanted to ask you, like,
ab-about cleaning it, keeping it clean.
I've never had anything quite this fancy,
so I don't want to mess it up.
Very common question we get.
I have a jewelry care kit that we sell.
Would you be interested in one of these?
Yes, that'd be perfect.
I bake a lot, and I just...
You know, I don't want,
I don't want to ruin it. (chuckles)
- I knew you'd say yes.
- What do you mean?
- I never forget a ring I sell.
- You sold the ring?
He made the right choice.
And it was a tough one.
It was?
People around here
say I have a sixth sense.
(laughs)
- About couples.
- Oh, okay.
Anyway, seeing him,
I knew right then, that was the one.
- You did?
- Congratulations again.
To all three of you.
To all three of us?
Well, your fiancé's daughter.
She's quite a spitfire.
- Oh, no, he doesn't have a...
- What was her name?
I can almost think
it's like a flower... Daisy.
Daisy.
Yeah, Daisy's the one
who picked that ring.
We looked at the cushion cut,
the princess cut,
- but that was the one for you.
- Um...
Whoa. What about your care kit?
- TERRI: Gary.
- T.
What did you do?
Uh, wh-what do you mean?
Uh, I mean she's on
her third batch of rye.
Well, it is a bread store.
We don't need that much rye.
That's her thinking bread.
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
- Today.
- Oh.
Yeah.
Gary, get your ass in that kitchen
and fix this, okay?
GARY:
Hey, Rach.
(Rachel sighs heavily)
You got a little, uh... schmutz...
Sorry.
Look, I'm really sorry
about the other night.
A client came in late.
And, I mean, you know how it is.
I don't like to say no to the walk-ins.
Part of that is because of you.
'Cause of the New York Magazine article.
Because you're the best.
(sighs)
How did you get the ring, Gary?
What?
It's...
so extravagant, it's so beautiful,
you know, I can't help but wonder,
how did you manage that?
I mean, you did buy it, right?
Gary?
You know.
Yeah, I know.
How?
That doesn't matter, Gary.
Look, Rachel, I messed up.
Yes, you messed up.
But also... (sighs)
Also, what?
It's like when I wake up
in the middle of the night
with some crazy idea for a tattoo.
Once I sketch it, it becomes obvious.
When I saw you open that ring box,
it was the most obvious thing
I'd ever seen.
What was your plan, though?
What, were you gonna wait until we were
in a nursing home to tell me this story?
What were you thinking?
You gave me
somebody else's engagement ring.
- That's crazy.
- I know. I know.
It's crazy. I don't know what happened.
I don't know what happened, Rachel.
I didn't have a plan.
And then I saw that ring on your finger,
and I realized this is the thing
I want the most in the entire world.
(sighs) How could I give that back?
What if there was no ring?
What do you mean?
I'm giving it back.
So I'm asking you right now,
not half-concussed,
no ring you have to hide behind, like...
do you still want to marry me?
Yes.
Of course I want to marry you.
I see a future with us.
If you just give me one more chance,
I will be so much better.
I promise you.
As a matter of fact, I think we should
celebrate the shit out of it. (chuckles)
Let's have an engagement party.
I mean, really. We should have
this huge New Year's party here.
My cousin Finn will be in town,
and we can invite everybody that loves us.
- (laughs)
- (sighs) Because I love you, Rachel.
Remember to let me do all the talking.
Why can't you just ask for the ring back?
It's complicated, honey.
Sometimes, when there's a mix-up, you
got to be careful of people's feelings.
What about your feelings?
East River.
I feel like I should be
more surprised to see you.
Hi, Terri.
This is my daughter Daisy.
Hi. Uh, my dad's gonna do all the talking.
Don't worry, kid.
I don't know social cues yet either.
You here to see Rachel? Again?
Yeah, she-she texted me
and told me to come by.
Oh, yeah, she's in the back.
Dad, can I go say hi?
Yeah, go ahead.
She's right around the corner.
So, um...
do you have something you want to tell me?
Or...?
You know?
I know that something feels off,
and I have a feeling that
you have something to do with it, so...
I want to know what's going on.
For Rachel.
- Hi, Rachel.
- RACHEL: Hi, Daisy.
- Hi.
- Is your dad out front?
- Yep.
- Your dad's here?
Are you making bread?
Can I help?
Of course you... abs...
I need help. That'd be great.
Um, do you want to grab an apron?
- Yeah.
- Right there.
- Can I talk to you for one sec over here?
- Yeah.
What do you want me to do?
Want me to talk to him?
- I'll handle it.
- Really?
Oh, my God, thank you so much.
- You're the best.
- Right.
Well, I'll meet you
at the apartment later tonight.
Maybe we can go over ideas
for New Year's Eve.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. (laughs)
- I love you so much.
- Okay.
I promise I won't mess this up.
Okay. Bye.
I'm gonna sneak out back.
(clicks tongue) All right.
What?
He got my ring, I got his present.
Wow. That is way worse than I thought.
And I-I tried to tell her the other night,
but I couldn't.
I just...
I didn't want to break her heart.
RACHEL:
All right. Perfect.
You can get your hands in there.
Make a little mess.
(both laugh)
Yours is way better than mine, PS.
DAISY:
So, how long does this take?
Takes a while.
Oh. What do you do
while waiting for it to be done?
I don't know. That's a good question.
What do I do while I wait...
I do a lot of thinking
while I wait for my bread to bake.
Well, I also spend a lot of time thinking.
You know, when I was about your age,
I lost my mom, too.
Do you like thinking about your mom,
or does it make you...
make you kind of sad?
- A little of both.
- Me, too.
Can I teach you a little trick
that's helped me?
- Okay.
- Okay, so you find one thing
that you did with your mom
that was really special,
and you make sure
to do that thing once every year.
And at least for me,
it feels like she's right there with me.
Mm. Do you have anything like that?
Well, every year, on Christmas Eve,
the three of us would pick out
these really ugly sweaters for each other.
I mean, they were always so funny.
But...
we... haven't done it
since she's been gone.
Uh, yeah.
You can't stop doing it
'cause she's not here, though.
You got to keep the tradition alive
because of her.
- Right?
- Right.
Your mom sounds like she was pretty cool.
(softly):
She was.
Hey.
RACHEL:
Thank you so much for coming.
Oh, yeah.
What, uh, what are y'all up to here?
My God, it looks like I'm in heaven.
(chuckles) Well, I'm helping make it.
Yeah? You ask for a paycheck?
Oops. I forgot. Sorry.
Can I talk to Rachel for a little bit?
Yeah. I'll invoice you, Rachel.
(Rachel laughs)
(Daisy chuckling)
I will just cut right to the chase.
I know about everything.
And I know it's insane.
All of it is insane.
(sighs)
I just wanted to say I am so sorry.
No, I am.
I-I wanted to tell you, but I couldn't.
I just didn't think
it was my place to say anything.
Thank you for being
exactly who you are through all of this.
You're a really, really good person.
I appreciate that.
I just wanted to apologize myself.
Gary's gonna reach out to you, obviously,
give the ring back, and, um...
...then we can all just move on.
I, uh... I made this one special
for you all to share together.
Thank you for this.
Yeah.
Okay. Well...
I guess this is it.
♪ ♪
Bye.
(busy chatter)
Hey. Hey, Rach.
Can you have a seat for me real quick?
- Uh, yeah.
- Um...
I, uh, I got to talk to you about
a situation with you and Gary.
But before I do, just know that
I am getting my ducks in a row
to absolutely kick his ass...
- I know, Terri.
- You know?
- What do you know?
- I know all of it.
It's done, and I...
I just, I don't really...
I don't want to talk about it right now.
But wait. Rachel, uh-uh. Hold up.
We gonna talk about it.
Are you and Gary still...?
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
- Yes.
- Yes?
- Yeah.
Yes. Okay. Wow. Okay.
Computer is processing.
Terri, not every relationship
is that simple.
Okay? Right?
Like, what about you and Sophia?
When you met her,
she was seeing somebody else.
- That's not exactly a perf...
- That... No one's perfect.
Hell, I used to have an eyebrow ring.
Nobody's talking about that.
Always bringing up old stuff.
What about Ethan?
Look, I know something when I see
something, and that wasn't nothing.
He just wanted his ring back.
That's it.
- I deleted his number.
- (sighs)
It was nothing.
Look. Hey.
Gary's not perfect either.
I know that, but you don't turn your back
on somebody because they don't know
how to tell you that a ring they could
never afford just ended up in their lap.
He has some work to do. Who doesn't?
I think you got to hold on to the good.
And I think you got to love people
when you can,
because there is no guarantee
that they'll be here tomorrow.
You know?
Well...
does that mean that
I have to start being nice to him or...?
(sighs) Terri, I think people would be
very confused if you did.
I would be very confused if I did.
(both laugh)
Oh, hold up. Wait.
What did you do with the ring?
So, there I was, stranded in Brooklyn,
on a Zoom, trying to get a Lyft,
but it was impossible
because it was rush hour.
It was just horrible.
Well, lucky for you, all the subways
will have Wi-Fi by the end of the year.
There was a sign.
I was bored on the subway.
Where'd you go again?
Uh, j... um...
Dad? Where did we go?
ETHAN:
Hmm?
Uh... we-we had... we went to the bakery.
- Remember?
- Yeah.
Uh, and I got to help make the bread.
Well, n-not this one,
but still, can we try it?
Sure.
- Yeah. Oh. Sorry.
- (phone vibrating)
Oh, there's a warm piece.
- That smells amazing. Okay.
- Make sure it's not poisoned.
- My turn. Whoa.
- Wait, I wasn't done.
- You got your piece. Come on.
- I was... I wasn't, I wasn't done. I...
Vanessa...
...will you marry me?
Yes. Yes!
- Oh, my gosh.
- (kisses)
This is why you've been acting so weird.
(gasps)
We'll have to get it sized
when we go back to L.A.
This will never fit, but...
What a unique way to propose.
- Uh...
- It-It's so original.
Okay, now we're gonna have so many things
to do when we go back to L.A.
You know, we'll have to look at venues.
I'll make a list. Okay.
I-I'm-I'm gonna call a couple people.
Okay? (laughs)
- I love you.
(door opens, closes)
What about moving back?
Did you even talk about that yet?
We...
Let's just focus on
everybody being happy right now.
But the night we went to Alvin Ailey,
though, I mean...
Sweetie, that everything is back on track.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Okay.
("Something on Your Mind"
by Karen Dalton playing)
♪ ♪
♪ Yesterday ♪
♪ Any way you made it was just fine ♪
♪ Saw you turn your days into nighttimes ♪
♪ Didn't you know ♪
♪ You can't make it ♪
♪ Without ever even trying? ♪
♪ And something's on your mind,
isn't it? ♪
♪ Let these times ♪
♪ Show you that
you're breaking up your mind ♪
♪ Leaving all your dreams too far behind ♪
♪ Didn't you see ♪
♪ You can't make it ♪
♪ Without ever even trying? ♪
- ♪ And something's on your mind... ♪
- (song fades)
(line ringing)
- TERRI: Gillini.
- Hi.
I, uh, was wondering if you had anything
still available on New Year's Eve.
Party of three for Greene.
No, I'm sorry.
We have a private event that night.
(sighs) You're kidding.
That's too bad.
I just... I recently got engaged,
and your restaurant played
kind of a big role in it,
so I was hoping we could all come by
before we leave for L.A.
Wait, y-you said you got engaged?
And it's a party of three for Greene?
Uh, yes, for me, my fiancé
and his daughter.
A small table is fine.
You know what? Um...
I think we can squeeze you in.
Uh, 8:00 work?
That's perfect, yeah.
Okay. See you then.
(line clicks, phone beeps)
- MAN: Hi.
- Hey.
What can I get for you?
♪ Every day ♪
("Every Day Will Be Like a Holiday"
by William Bell playing)
♪ Will be like a holiday ♪
(busy chatter)
(camera clicks)
♪ When my baby ♪
♪ When my baby comes home ♪
T, it is 7:50, and I'd like
to officially announce I am early.
I see you, Gary.
'Bout time.
- GARY: Babe.
- Oh, my gosh.
- This is Finn.
- How are ya?
Hello.
- I have heard so much about you.
- Oh, thank you.
So how was your flight in?
Oh, it was not so bad, not so bad.
God, I'm so stoked to finally be
meeting the famous Rachel.
- (laughs)
- (Finn sighs)
You are as hot as your picture.
Oh.
- Hey, can I get you a drink?
- Yeah, yeah, sure.
- Cool. I'll be right back.
- RACHEL: Wow.
God, it's so crazy that
we haven't been introduced,
considering I was with Gary
the same day you two met.
Oh, I don't think I knew that.
That's so funny.
Yeah, I was visiting that weekend.
We were, uh, hanging out
at that underground hot dog joint
- before his mad dash to Astoria.
- (laughs)
- Oh, thanks, brother. Yeah.
- Here, buddy. Cheers.
Right up until that text from Amber.
(Finn sighs)
You know, she and I are hooking up,
by the way.
- Oh, are you?
- Yeah, she is a, she is a riot.
Still though,
best late-night text ever, right?
Went to Queens for a hookup,
left knowing your future wife.
Call that a win.
Are you guys doing pasta apps or anything,
or is it just the crudités?
I'm a little, a little peckish.
This is fine. This will do.
That's why you c...
(quietly):
you came out to Astoria that night?
Not to give me my bracelet back?
Rachel, that isn't fair.
We weren't even dating yet.
That's so absolutely beside the point.
You let me think
that it was because of me.
D-Do you get that?
Do you get why that is hurtful?
- That was three years ago.
- Exactly.
It was three years ago. It was last week.
It was yesterday. It was today.
- We're good.
- We're not.
If we're not good, then we can work on it.
Gary, this is not working.
It's just too hard.
I'm-I'm not saying that it should be easy,
but it shouldn't be this hard.
You keep digging these holes,
and I keep throwing you rope,
and I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't.
Rachel.
I'm definitely eating
all this dessert tonight.
Well, as long as you're paying.
- Daisy got it.
- (scoffs) In your dreams.
Wait, what are we doing here?
You'll see.
- GARY: Please, Rachel, talk...
- What?
GARY:
What the hell is he doing here?
Hi.
Hey, what...
I made a reservation.
I saw this going way differently
in my head.
What'd you do?
Do you know these people?
Uh, yeah, that's Rachel
and Gary, the guy Daddy helped.
Oh, hi. I'm Vanessa, Ethan's fiancée.
There. See?
He proposed to her, she got the ring, and
everything can go back to the way it was.
No, Gary, no.
Just... What are you talking about?
Sorry, the ring...
Are you talking about mine?
Oh, my God.
Uh, they're getting married.
We actually discussed it.
We're not getting married anymore.
Wait, you're not?
No, we just broke...
Does it matter?
Why do you care
if I marry her or not, hmm?
I mean, what is it to you?
Well, I didn't say that,
but you did steal the ring.
- He didn't steal the ring.
- You cannot prove that.
- Wait, actually, did you steal the ring?
- No.
- What is happening?
- I don't...
Okay, Ethan, what is going on?
Oh, hey, that night that
Gary got himself hit by a cab...
- I get hit by a car, and it's my fault?
- Probably, but...
- Terri.
- Okay.
I bought you that ring.
He bought Rachel those earrings.
Th-The earrings that I opened
on Christmas?
That's where you went?
Trying to get the ring back?
Is there spinach in this?
'Cause, um, I'm allergic.
Dude, read the room.
All right. That's my bad.
So, did you know about this
the whole time?
No. I mean, yes.
Not until recently. Yes, I knew.
And I assume you're the one
who put it in the bread.
Um, did you even mean
to propose that day or...
- Babe, I... Not that day, but I...
- Okay.
Babe, listen...
GARY:
Rachel.
I think maybe we should go home and talk.
We ready to get absolutely ripped?
Now?
Yeah, all right.
♪ New Year's Eve... ♪
CROWD:
Five. Four. Three.
(over headphones):
Two. One.
Happy New Year!
(song fades)
ETHAN:
I don't know. I-I don't know.
I felt like an idiot, Ethan.
I didn't know you were
gonna make a reservation there.
Wait.
Just so we're on the same page,
that's what you think the problem is here?
Not the revelation that
you didn't even mean to propose?
Okay. I d... I did mean to propose,
on Christmas Day.
I fully expected the ring
to be in that bag.
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't know. I... (sighs)
And what about that meeting the other day
with Brian Harrison?
I ran into him with Daisy the other night,
and he talked to me about
your... your new book?
Y-You didn't mention any of that to me.
Nothing.
I mean, why? Like...
I'm really, really trying
to figure out a good reason,
and I can't come up with it.
I don't know.
Okay, but, Ethan,
if on any level you do...
...then just say it.
Fine. Okay, fine. I...
You're not always supportive.
Uh, you-you change the subject
every time I talk about my writing.
I thought that maybe you'd think
it was gonna be another failure,
and you'd just be embarrassed of me.
Well, that's... I mean...
That sucks.
Look, just forget all of this
for a second, okay?
E-Everything you haven't told me.
The shit show of
an engagement New Year's dinner.
What is it that you really want?
I want to write another book.
Yeah, I-I want to take another shot.
I feel like I have to.
And...
...I want to move to New York.
Ethan, I...
I hate it here.
I-I don't even like it
when it's 70 and sunny.
Hey, it's... it's too much for me.
I know.
And even if it were with you and Daisy...
...I can't move back.
And I think we both know what that means.
(Rachel sighs heavily)
So you just had that ready to go?
Yep.
(chuckles softly)
Look, you did the right thing tonight.
I don't understand.
Why did you do that?
Why did you take their reservation
on the night of my engagement party?
(sighs, smacks lips)
I don't know.
It was dumb.
I just always had
this bad feeling about Gary, and...
I don't know what I was thinking.
I just made a mistake.
Look, I'm so sorry, okay?
For what it's worth,
Ethan just didn't want to crush you.
That's why he didn't tell you.
I was gonna be crushed
no matter what, so...
RACHEL:
Mm.
Yeah, go ahead.
Tasty.
I'm gonna go home, eat the shit
out of this cornetto and pass out.
Hey, you do you.
(both chuckle)
I love you, Rach.
I love you, too.
- (sighs)
- (door opens)
(door closes)
SOPHIA:
You okay?
- Yeah, I'll be fine.
- Mm.
And the fact that you thought you could
pull this off without me is baffling.
Why you got to throw salt on my wounds?
Salt bae.
♪ ♪
ETHAN:
Don't eat all of this.
(sighs) Can't promise you I won't.
Mmm.
Now, this is good.
I'm definitely gonna eat all of this.
Vanessa went home this morning?
It was the right thing.
Did you guys break up for good?
Yeah.
Were you going to marry Vanessa
for me, Dad?
What?
Listen.
You said that she was gonna be
a good mom and role model for me.
Which, yeah, awesome.
But you should be with someone
because it's right for you.
You definitely need your own podcast.
Well, then I definitely need
a phone for that.
Okay. D... listen.
You got to trust that I'm-a be all right.
You can't go around worrying about me.
That's not your job.
What? Daisy?
(Daisy sighing softly)
Dad, Rachel might be white,
but the girl can cook.
Uh, what? (laughs)
(sighs) Okay.
Hello? What are you still doing here?
Where do you want me to go?
Want me to stand outside the restaurant
with a boombox over my head?
Get your ass up, and let's go.
("Oh Yes Baby I Love You So"
by Ervin Litkei and Lenny Curtis playing)
- You're grounded. Get your...
- (stammers)
(both laugh)
(lively chatter)
(phone ringing)
♪ Oh, yeah, baby... ♪
Gillini. How may I help you?
- You the owner?
- Wait, what?
These are for you. Signature?
- Enjoy.
- Hold up.
Tell me more about your cannoli emergency.
♪ Oh, yeah, baby... ♪
You got my phone?
You didn't.
How are we supposed to know
if they were delivered?
Guess we just wait and see if she comes.
TERRI:
Hey, Rach.
The case is almost empty of bomboloni,
and this woman who I swear
is the real-life Carmela Soprano
just cleaned us out of cannolis.
I heard. Here, table five.
♪ Baby, you stay out all night long ♪
♪ Baby... ♪
I know you're gonna say
this isn't the right time,
but maybe if I had a phone,
we could use mine in times like this
when you forget yours.
What? I-I'm being serious.
- Hey, baby.
- SOPHIA: Hey.
How's she doing?
Well, I asked her to make
a date night menu for the long weekend,
and she gave me blood sausage and oxtail.
In other news, point taken.
Thank you.
I don't know what you're thanking me for,
but I like it.
- The flowers.
- What flowers?
- These.
- I didn't send you these.
- You didn't?
- Why would I send you flowers?
You should be sending me flowers.
Oh, my God, did you read this?
No, it's been crazy busy in here all day.
- Oh, my God.
- I know.
- When did you get this?
- Don't ask questions you don't want the answers to.
What do I do?
- You got to go.
- Shit.
Okay, it's after 4:00.
When does afternoon end?
- Girl, get out of here. -Shit.
- Go, go, go, go, go, go.
You know, I'd run across town
for you, too, baby.
(sucks teeth) Don't suck up.
I would.
I'm lying. I'd probably take a Uber.
You right.
("Oh Baby" by LCD Soundsystem playing)
You know what? I'm just gonna...
Taxi!
(groans)
Thank you! Hi.
In a rush.
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go.
Okay, maybe a little longer.
Don't give up, please.
Come on.
Hey, just right here.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm just gonna run.
Sweetie...
...I don't think she's coming.
It was a good idea, though.
♪ Oh, sugar... ♪
Five more minutes, please?
Please, Dad?
RACHEL:
Hi!
Hey.
(gasps)
(Rachel panting)
- Hi.
- (breathlessly): Hi.
I got it. I got your note.
I got it a little late.
Yeah, I was starting to think,
"Could I trust that bike messenger?"
You said that you thought that
there was something between us,
and that if I thought so, too,
that I should come here.
Yeah, um, look, I-I know
we barely know each other, and...
(sighs) You were probably just talking
about a croissant... or-or corn-cornetto.
- Cornetto.
- (laughs)
But you were right.
I need to start making decisions
with my heart and not my head.
This, you know, feels...
Like maybe one of those things?
Yeah. It does.
♪ ♪
♪ And you're already gone ♪
♪ Yeah, you're already gone... ♪
(laughs)
- This was your idea, wasn't it?
- (laughs)
He wanted to hold
a cardboard box over his head.
- Cardboard box?
- Uh, a boombox.
- A boombox.
- Boombox.
- I don't know what that is.
- (Rachel laughs)
- What?
- You got to... (laughs)
- You don't be listening to me.
- You don't know what a boombox is?
- That's concerning. (laughs)
- You knew what a boombox was.
- DAISY: Why?
- I told you what it was.
- You're embarrassing me.
- DAISY: I'm embarrassing?
- ♪ Hard ♪
- ("Just One Look" by Doris Troy playing)
♪ In love ♪
♪ With you ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
- (lively chatter)
- ♪ I found out ♪
♪ How good it feels... ♪
- Here you go. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
All right. (chuckles)
Oh.
♪ Your love... ♪
Here you go. Thank you so much.
Happy holidays.
- Daisy, give me one sec, okay?
- Oh, yeah, I got you.
Hi. Merry Christmas.
- Hey, you.
- Hey. What is this?
It's a surprise.
This better not be a milk frother.
Ooh.
(gasps) It's our initials!
- This is the corniest thing I've ever seen, and I love it.
- (laughs)
Thank you.
- Um, are we all set?
- Uh, yeah. Daisy's covering the door.
Ready for your cue.
- All right. Let's do this.
- Let's do it.
Uh, can I get
everyone's attention, please?
- (chatter quiets)
- (song fades)
Uh, I'd like to wish everyone
a Merry Christmas Eve,
and I'd love to give
a special shout-out to your head chef,
- Rachel Meyer.
- (chuckles)
- Okay.
- (crowd murmuring)
Let's raise a glass to this beautiful,
talented, kind person,
who could probably achieve world peace
with one loaf of that bread,
and who's also a surprisingly harsh editor
I found out over the past year.
- She knows a lot about semicolons, folks.
- Baby, what are you doing right now?
She's my cornetto.
(men scatting "I Only Have Eyes for You")
♪ My love must be ♪
♪ A kind of blind love... ♪
(scatting and singing continues)
And I don't know
what I would do without her.
And I don't plan on finding out
anytime soon.
Listen, I-I know all this
came together really messy,
as some of us know in here.
But someone I love dearly once told me,
"Don't think so much about the mess.
Focus on the outcome."
And I can't imagine a better outcome
than forever with you.
Obviously, this ring agrees.
(softly):
Oh, my God.
Rachel, will you marry me?
Yes.
Of course. Yes. (laughs)
(cheering, applause)
("Get Ready" by The Temptations playing)
We're getting married!
(cheering and applause continue)
(Ethan chuckles)
♪ I never met a girl who makes me feel
the way that you do ♪
♪ You're all right ♪
♪ Whenever I'm asked who makes
my dreams real, I say that you do ♪
♪ You're outta sight ♪
♪ So, fee-fi, fo-fum ♪
♪ Look out, baby, 'cause here I come ♪
♪ And I'm bringing you
a love that's true ♪
♪ So get ready, so get ready ♪
♪ I'm gonna try to make you love me, too ♪
♪ So get ready, so get ready
'cause here I come ♪
♪ Get ready 'cause here I come ♪
♪ I'm on my way ♪
♪ If you wanna play hide-and-seek
with love, let me remind you ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ But the lovin' you're gonna miss
in the time it takes to find you ♪
♪ It's outta sight ♪
♪ So, fiddley-dee, fiddley-dum ♪
♪ Look out, baby, 'cause here I come ♪
♪ And I'm bringing you
a love that's true ♪
♪ So get ready, so get ready ♪
♪ I'm gonna try to make you love me, too ♪
♪ So get ready, so get ready
'cause here I come ♪
♪ Get ready 'cause here I come ♪
♪ I'm on my way ♪
♪ Get ready ♪
♪ ♪
♪ If all my friends should want you, too,
I'll understand it ♪
♪ Be all right ♪
♪ I hope I get to you before they do,
the way I planned it ♪
♪ Be outta sight ♪
♪ So tweedley-dee, tweedley-dum ♪
♪ Look out, baby, 'cause here I come ♪
♪ And I'm bringing you
a love that's true ♪
♪ So get ready, so get ready ♪
♪ I'm gonna try to make you love me, too ♪
♪ So get ready, so get ready
'cause here I come ♪
♪ Get ready 'cause here I come ♪
♪ I'm on my way ♪
♪ Baby, I'll stay ♪
- ♪ Get ready 'cause here I come. ♪
- (song ends)
♪ ♪
(music fades)