(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
- [Man] It's just a few more
miles, don't be so squeamish.
It's gonna be a breeze.
(suspenseful music)
It doesn't feel right.
After all, we are the law.
(woman speaking indistinctly over radio)
(dramatic music)
But the world does not need these dudes.
Don't quit on me now.
Remember this money's ours.
We're the ones with our asses on the line.
If we score now, they're
gonna lose us in a panic.
(suspenseful music)
Payoff is one thing,
but collecting it by deadly force...
(suspenseful music)
(woman speaking indistinctly over radio)
- I'm not laying down for this.
Let's get the money and
we're finished with this guy.
- Let's call for some back up first.
- Back up?
How are we gonna explain this?
(suspenseful music)
(wind blows)
(man groans)
(dramatic music)
- Fuck.
(man grunts)
- Want it?
We're good to you, you piece of shit.
(man groans)
(dramatic music)
I've had enough of your shit.
- Boss.
- What?
- They're cops.
(dramatic music)
(guns firing)
- God, no, no.
(dramatic music)
God, no, no.
(gun fires)
(guns firing)
(man groans)
(dramatic music)
(guns firing)
(suspenseful music)
(gun fires)
(groans)
(suspenseful music)
- Can't wait for your fucking money?
- Don't do it, man.
- Shut the fuck up.
Fuckers should know better by now
not to fuck with me.
You're the last one here.
You're all by yourself, motherfucker.
Huh?
You and I are gonna party, boy.
I'll be back for you.
(suspenseful music)
Get the goods.
I'll take care of this son of a bitch.
(suspenseful music)
(man groans)
How 'bout you and I go for a ride?
I bet you ain't never had
a ride like this one, boy.
(suspenseful music)
(engine revs)
(man screams)
I'll give you a fucking ride.
(man groans)
(suspenseful music)
(gun fires)
(dramatic music)
(man groans)
- Come on, silver boy.
We don't wanna be late for
our little fishing trip
with Mr. Jacoby.
Now get your ass up off
the ground right now.
(dramatic music)
- Hey, what the hell's going on here, huh?
You guys are making a
big mistake, you know.
Once the boss man finds out
what you're doing to me,
he's gonna be pissed and mad, really mad,
so I suggest you--
- Shut up and walk.
(dramatic music)
- [Man] Tell me, I gotta carry him.
- Oh, yeah.
- Lighten up, homie.
- Drag him up.
- Oh, yeah.
(dramatic music)
(groans)
- [Man] Hey, kid.
Go tell Mr. Jacoby we
got Silver Boy, here.
You hear the man or what, dude?
- You have something so fucking important
to tell Mr. Jacoby, tell him yourself.
He's in the back cabin.
- [Man] Kid, go get him.
(knocks)
- Who the fuck is it?
- Mr. Jacoby, we got
Silver here to see you.
- Give me my robe.
Simon.
What an honor.
First, I was upset, now I'm happy.
Laying odds against
seeing you on this boat.
Unbelievable.
- Why do you say these things to me, huh?
And why you treat me like this?
Somebody's been telling you lies.
I thought I was your boy, huh?
How far we go back?
And now I'm hearing a
rumor about your short
on your collections,
and you think I'm on the take.
It wasn't me, boss.
I wouldn't do that to you.
Somebody's trying to set me up here.
I'm serious--
- Shut up.
- It wasn't me.
Shut the fuck up.
(dramatic music)
Too many women for you,
and they make men greedy.
Too powerful.
Delilah to Samson,
Cleopatra to Marc Anthony,
you are a fallen victim now.
- It wasn't me, boss.
I swear it wasn't me.
- Aww, shh.
Don't piss me off more than I already am.
You need a drink.
Honey, champagne.
- Is there a problem, sweetheart?
- Nothing that doesn't concern you.
- [Silver] I'm telling you, I was set up,
and I did not do his.
I wouldn't do that to you.
- I'm telling you you're thirsty.
Drink, drink it.
Good boy.
- You gotta believe me.
Things have been really slow, I'm serious.
(dramatic music)
Sit down.
- No, boss.
Please, please.
(groans)
Oh, fuck.
- You owe me.
- My face, man.
Why'd you have to scar
me up like this, huh?
Jeez, I told you, I didn't do it.
God.
- Go check the kid outside.
Get out of here.
- You fucked me up so good, man.
Thought I was your boy.
- [Jacoby] You ain't shit
you're weakling little baby.
Does it hurt?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Here, here, relax.
Here's how's this?
- Ow.
- You take that shipment up to Billy,
and you tell him, if it doesn't happen,
he's gonna look like him.
You got it?
Nobody wants to look like him.
(phone rings)
- Hello?
It's Billy.
- Jacoby, what's going on?
You said we'd be finished
here in two months.
Here it is, six months later,
we're still jerking off in this shit hole.
(laughing)
- Listen to me, you little fuck.
I've been taking care of you
since you were a punk kid,
and that's all you are.
Your family doesn't even
give a shit about you.
- Yeah, right.
- So you listen to me.
One more fuck up like that in
the desert and you're history.
- If it doesn't happen in
two weeks, we're out of here.
- You little fuck.
I swear, if he doesn't does this,
they won't be able to wipe
down a file in forensics.
- Yeah, tell me.
Take it easy.
(dramatic music)
(groaning)
- [Crowd] Get him!
Yeah, get up, come on, get up.
Yeah, get him, oh!
Get up, get up, come on.
Yeah, hit him, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Go, go, go.
Come on, yeah.
Hit him, hit him, hit him, yeah.
Go, go, go.
Come on, yeah.
(dog growls)
(cars honking)
- [Man] Here, I'll give you a hand.
- Thanks.
I wish you'd reconsider my invitation.
Are you sure I can't change your mind?
- No, I need the bucks.
- Well, I gotta get going.
- All right, you take care of yourself.
- [Woman] Okay, you too.
(cheerful music)
- Hiya, ma'am, can I fill her up for you?
- Yeah, please.
Could you tell me how to
get up state route 56?
I couldn't find it on my map.
- Route 56?
- Uh huh.
- [Attendant] How far you going?
- To the base of the volcano.
- That's not a good idea.
There's some bad old
boys that live up there.
- Well, I have a government grant
to research the area, so those boys
are just gonna have to
learn to live with it.
(upbeat music)
- Hi, Jake.
- Howdy.
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheers)
- Boy, you really think
you're a stud, don't you?
- Hey, man, it was easy money.
- Good to see you.
You got that gear ready for
that hunting trip tomorrow?
- You bet, I can't wait.
- Sounds like we just better
head up there in the morning.
- [Friend] Yeah.
- Hey, babe.
(laughing)
- Hey, what the hell's going on here, huh?
- What's going on here?
(grunting)
(punches landing)
(upbeat music)
- Hey, man, I think it's
time for that hunting trip.
(crowd shouting)
(upbeat music)
(engine revs)
(laughing)
- Hey, that was close that time.
You boys are getting better.
- Man, you made me dent my bumper.
You're gonna kill us one of these days.
- When the hell you gonna grow up?
You could have killed me, you dumb shit.
- What are you sniveling about?
You wreck your bike every other race.
Come on, guys.
Let's head on up to the
hill and set up camp
fore it gets too dark,
you want a cold beer?
- Now you're talking, toss me one.
- It's the least you can do
for making me crash my bike.
(laughing)
(engine revs)
(birds chirping)
- Home sweet home.
(gentle music)
You know, Johnny, humans
aren't loners by nature.
Here I am in botanist
heaven and it's so quiet.
You would think I would
be used to the outdoors.
You know, every time I
come to a place like this,
it feels like the first time.
Do you ever feel that way?
I remember when Dad showed
you how to use the gun.
You were shaking like a leaf.
Seemed like it took an
hour to pull the trigger,
and you were squinting your eyes so tight,
I bet you couldn't even see.
Did it ever get easier
to pull the trigger?
You've already used up enough lives
to make any cat jealous.
I think you should visit
as soon as possible.
Besides, it would do your ego some good
to be your little sister's lab assistant.
It's too quiet up here, Johnny.
(engine revs)
(birds chirping)
- [Man] Woah.
(engine revs)
(birds chirping)
(horses trotting)
(engine stalls)
(engine revs)
(horses trotting)
- Hey, Billy.
How things holding out up here?
You ain't looking so well.
- Cut the shit, I'm fine.
You're four months overdue on our deal.
- Takis, Mr. Jacoby sends his best,
and he apologizes for the inconvenience.
- I don't give a damn
about the inconvenience.
Get the goods.
(birds chirping)
Not as good as last time.
Getting real tired of this shit.
Put that away.
(branch snaps)
- Expecting company?
- I'll take care of it.
- No, probably just some kid from town.
I'll be right back.
(horse whinnies, gallops)
- Mr. Jacoby is concerned.
Don't let things get out of control here.
(dramatic music)
(groaning)
- Well, what do we have here?
- But I didn't see anything.
- Shut your fucking mouth.
- No.
(groaning)
No.
(dramatic music)
(screams)
(fire crackles)
(insects chirping)
- Hey, you guys wanna head up
the Devil's Ridge in the morning?
Some pretty big game up there.
- If we're gonna go all the way up there,
we'd better plan on staying the night.
It's a long hike.
- Shit, I'll just ride my bike.
You guys can walk.
- Listen to you, guys.
You sound like a couple damn pansies.
(insects chirping)
What the hell?
- Help me.
He might still be after me.
- [Man] What's going on, who's after you?
- There's a man, a man on a horse.
He tried to kill me.
- Oh, come on, sit over here and sit down.
Sit down.
(dramatic music)
- We oughta get her to town.
She don't have no business being
up here in the first place.
- What do you mean I have
no business being up here?
Are you telling me men are the only
ones allowed in the mountains?
- He's not saying that.
Just some bad boys live in these hills.
It's just not a safe place.
- Yeah, it looked like they
were dropping drugs from a boat,
and a man on a horse
noticed me watching him,
and he started chasing me,
and then he tried to rape me.
(dramatic music)
- All right, here's a song
I wrote for my ex-wife.
She's out there somewhere.
(country music)
- Hello, Joy, how 'bout a
little company at my place?
- I'm not blind, Dave.
♫ Come here at night
Hey, Elmo, why don't you cut Dave off?
(engine revs)
- My mom owns this place.
♫ But the winds of old December
♫ Cold as they can be
Hey, Mom, I need your help.
This is Saundra.
I didn't catch your last name.
- It's Ryker, Saundra Ryker.
- What happened to you?
- She ran into Billy and
there's some bad shit
going on up there.
- Hi, hon, who's your new friend?
- This is Saundra Ryker.
She ran into Billy up on the hill.
It isn't all, she stabbed him.
- Is he dead?
- He was moving when I ran away.
Could I use your phone?
I really need to call my brother.
- Let's get her out of here.
Myrna, will you take her back to my place
and get her cleaned up?
♫ And her memory remains
(dramatic music)
- Oh, Jesus.
- Man, Billy, you gotta get to a doctor.
- Bullshit, fucking doctors.
What are you stupid?
- Jesus Christ, you don't
have to jump down my throat.
- You'd better watch your shit,
always out fucking guys.
(sultry music)
You don't want it.
Leave me alone.
- Yeah, just a little.
- Take it.
(sultry music)
Come on, here.
Come on.
- Come on.
(moaning)
(sultry music)
- You're a freak, so not yet.
- Takis, bring me that stuff
from the shipment today.
(insects chirping)
Here, have some, we have work tonight.
That bitch is gonna pay.
- No, boss.
- All right, I guess it's just as well.
Need you on your toes.
Go round up some of the
boys, going to town.
Do it.
(insects chirping)
(suspenseful music)
(phone dials)
- [Woman] Hello, you've
reach 805-648-7611.
(beep)
- Johnny, are you there, Johnny?
Pick up the phone.
- Will you be okay?
I need to go close the restaurant.
- Johnny, are you there?
♫ Three years old beneath
the stars, oh dear
(applause, cheering)
(horn honks)
- Hey, Jake.
Where's the bitch?
Her and I have some unsettled
business there, Jake.
- I have to deal with this.
He won't just go away.
- Come on, Jake.
Don't make me wait any longer.
You know how I am when I get mad.
- Don't go out there.
- Don't worry, I'll be back.
- Billy, ain't seen
you in town in a while.
Must be pretty important business.
- Always a joker, Jake.
Yeah, Jake, it's pretty
important business.
Bring the bitch out.
She's gotta pay for what she done.
- She left, Billy.
Why don't you and the boys
just head on up to the hill.
- You know, Jake, you always
did have a knack for bullshit.
Bring her out or I'll level
this whole fucking town.
- Your shit don't scare me, Billy.
You gotta problem with me,
just jump down off of the hood there
and we'll settle this man to man.
- Gotta be a big man, Jake.
We can give you a fight if you want one.
(dramatic music)
Surprise, surprise, Jake.
(cheering)
- Yeah.
(blows thudding)
(grunting)
- Let's go, come on.
(dramatic music)
(blows thudding)
(grunting)
- Get back.
- Oh, shit.
(blows thudding)
(grunting)
(phone dials)
- Could you connect me
with the local police?
Thanks.
(phone rings)
There's never a cop
around when you need one.
(phone rings)
(dramatic music)
(gasps)
- Hi, honey, I'm home.
(suspenseful music)
I know.
I've had a rough day myself.
(dramatic music)
Keep ahold of her.
You are really starting to piss me off.
(groaning)
(dramatic music)
Get in here, get her, get her.
Well, look at you, Jake.
You got your fight.
Hope you feel better.
Any of you good folks get any ideas
about being witness or
anything stupid like that,
you better think again.
Let's get the hell out of here.
This place is boring me.
(horn honks)
- Myrna, give me a hand, we
gotta call Doc Henderson.
(tires squeal)
(wolf howls)
(country music)
♫ Roll out every morning, I
drink my coffee on the road
- Hey, partner.
Do you ever get enough of this stuff?
♫ Just the way my daddy done
♫ But honey, I'm making me
- I could do this all day.
- Well, I bet you 10 that
you can't give me five more.
- You're on.
♫ Telephone keeps ringing
♫ And it gets under my skin
♫ They all call to ask me
when I'll send money in
♫ ATT does a favor for me
- You ready for that month
of special assignment
the agency has planned for us?
- You know how I feel about that?
I'm gonna retire and blow this place.
How 'bout lunch?
I'm buying.
- That's a switch but I
gotta take a rain check,
but get your stuff together
and I'll give you a lift.
Let me ask you a question,
you're at home on night and you hear
your next door neighbor screaming
because some sick bastard is in her house,
what are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna call 911 like everybody else.
- Bullshit, you're gonna
go into your closet,
you're gonna grab your Beretta,
and you're going over there,
and you're gonna handle the situation
the only way you know how.
(phone beeps)
- [Man] This call is for Mr. John Ryker.
Please call Harold Henson at the office
regarding your interview.
The number is 855-1439.
(phone beeps)
- [Woman] Johnny, are you there, Johnny?
Pick up the phone.
- [Waitress] Will you be okay?
I need to go close the restaurant.
- [Woman] Johnny, are you there?
I need your help.
(dramatic music)
- Oh shit.
(wind blows)
- Hey, baby.
Sleep good?
Oh, the silent treatment.
Gosh, honey, don't be mad.
I promise I'll be good.
(grunts)
(dramatic music)
Give me a kiss.
Just a little one, come on.
Just a little one.
(groans)
You know you like it.
You really need to trust me, you know?
Yeah.
Come on.
Oh, how 'bout this?
You like this?
Yeah.
How 'bout another kiss, huh?
(grunts)
Come on.
(laughs)
Looks like it's gonna
take a little more time
for you to come around.
When really, you should trust me.
Before you know it, you
and I will be good friends.
(grunts)
(water splashes)
(insects chirping)
- Here, take this.
You need to eat.
- Hey.
How am I supposed to eat this?
Could you at least untie me
so I can eat like a human?
- Yeah, I guess I could untie one arm.
You try anything, I swear to God,
I'll break your fucking neck.
Nothing personal.
- I won't.
(insects chirping)
Why do you put up with
his animalistic behavior?
- Billy's good to me.
- Yeah, sure.
I see the way he treats you.
No woman wants to be treated like that.
- Okay, so he's a little different.
He's not that bad all the time.
- Just most of the time.
- Look, why don't you
just finish your grub,
all right and stay out of my business?
- You know, we could get
out of here, if you wanted.
- What are you, crazy?
Don't even talk like that.
If Billy thought that I'd try to help you
out of here, he'd kill me.
- After dark, all these guys
are just a bunch of drunks.
We could start a new life.
- Forget it, all right,
and why should I help you anyway?
- The way I see it, Billy has his sights
set on someone else.
- All right, so he's going
through a little shit right now.
Okay, don't get your hopes up, huh?
- You know I stabbed him
because he tried to rape me.
- All right, that's
enough, I've heard enough.
Come on, now give me your arm.
Give me your arm.
Come on, put your arm back here.
You're pushing it.
- If you keep letting
him treat you like that,
later, you'll wish you had listened to me.
- Look, if I were you, I'd just worry
about your own situation.
- Thanks for not tying the ropes as tight.
(insects chirping)
- Hey, baby.
Come to Papa.
Mr. Happy is starting to get restless.
- Come on, Billy, would you be serious?
I want something more between us.
- What, stability?
A relationship?
Sounds to me like you've been watching
too many damn daytime talk shows.
Why don't you go sleep
with the damn dogs tonight?
- Fuck you.
- Excuse me?
I don't think I got that.
- Well, what word didn't you get?
Fuck or you?
(dramatic music)
(groans)
You son of a bitch.
(dramatic music)
(grunts)
Son of a bitch.
(dramatic music)
(coughs, gasps)
(birds chirping)
(engine revs)
- Howdy, looking for my sister.
She came up here a few days
ago to study the volcano.
Have you seen her?
- There was a girl up
looking for directions.
- Where is she at right now?
- Well, if it's the same girl,
she had a run in with
the boys up on the hill.
- Up on the hill, what hill?
- Up at the base of the
volcano, up route 56.
- Thanks a lot.
- You betcha.
(suspenseful music)
(engine revs)
- Shh.
(birds chirping)
Don't say a thing.
I am so sick of this shit.
Only way out of here is
an old truck up the road.
(birds chirping)
(engine revs)
(lively music)
- They're gone.
- Find them.
(lively music)
(engine revs)
- Are they behind us?
(lively music)
- He's right behind us.
(engine revs)
(lively music)
Faster.
Shit.
(car crashes)
Come on, faster.
(lively music)
- Where are they?
(tires squeal)
- Watch it, watch it, he's gonna hit us.
(lively music)
(engine revs)
(grunts)
- Well, well, ladies.
You really screwed up.
Starting to piss me off.
Get them in there.
Get them back to the pit.
Now we're gonna have some fun.
- Fuck you.
(engine revs)
- [Billy] Let's go.
(birds chirping)
(engine revs)
- Throw 'em in the pit.
Come on, get 'em in there.
Lock it up.
(birds chirping)
You watch 'em.
(wind blows)
(fire crackles)
- Better take her easy,
we're on guard tonight.
(insects chirping)
(farts)
(burps)
(insects chirping)
(snores)
(burps)
(insects chirping)
(dramatic music)
(groans)
(blows thudding)
(dramatic music)
(groans)
(blows thudding)
- Oh my God, it's Johnny.
- Who the hell's Johnny?
- He's my brother.
(groans)
(blows thudding)
- I didn't know you had
a commando for a brother.
(groans)
(blows thudding)
(wind blows)
(gasps)
- What is this?
Throw him in the pit.
(grunts)
(dramatic music)
- Nice to see you, sis.
Seems like the only time you call me
is when you're in trouble.
- I'm so sorry, Johnny.
- Look, I hate to break
up this little reunion,
but we gotta get the hell out of here.
- She's right.
We have time to waste.
Look, I left some weapons
dashed around the camp.
Give me a minute.
Here's what I want you guys to do.
- Do what?
Look, you don't know him like I know him.
Billy's psycho.
We could be dead by morning.
- That's right, that's why
gotta get out of here tonight.
- Shh, that guy is listening.
(dramatic music)
- Psst, Harold.
I gotta do a bump, man.
- What do you want, Cindy?
- You got enough for a line?
Ooh.
You like it when I touch myself?
I know you've been watching me.
It's been a long, long
time, hasn't it, Harold?
Come on, baby, you wanna touch these?
(suspenseful music)
Come on.
Woah.
(groans)
(suspenseful music)
(chain rattles)
(wind blows)
(insects chirping)
- Take this.
Okay, Saundra, you see that
big stump up on the hill?
I put some weapons right behind it.
You get those.
Okay, you see if you can
get some kerosene lanterns
and bottles and rags.
I got some more weapons
stuck over this way, okay.
(insects chirping)
- Psst.
Here, you know how to use this?
- Yeah, yeah.
- That son of a bitch is gonna pay.
- Light that and blow
this place up, come on.
(groans)
(suspenseful music)
- Fucking bitch.
Takis, Takis, Takis.
- What's happening, boss?
- Find them.
(suspenseful music)
- [Men] What's going on?
Yeah, fuck.
- I don't know man.
- Fuck's going on?
(suspenseful music)
(grunts)
(explosion)
- What's that, smoke, Jesus Christ.
(gun fires)
(screams)
(guns firing)
(dramatic music)
(groans)
(blows thudding)
(guns firing)
(groans)
(blows thudding)
- [Man] Oh, God.
Jesus Christ.
(screaming)
(explosion)
(groans)
(blows thudding)
(explosion)
(groans)
(blows thudding)
(guns firing)
(groans)
(blows thudding)
(guns firing)
(engine revs)
(explosion)
(groans)
(blows thudding)
(dramatic music)
(screaming)
(groans)
(blows thudding)
(screaming)
(suspenseful music)
- How's it feel?
How's it feel?
- Cindy, stop.
Don't do it.
He's not worth it.
Come on, Cindy.
- You know what?
She's right.
You ain't worth shit.
Burn in hell, Billy.
(upbeat music)
♫ I'm naturally bad
♫ Bad as sin
♫ Something's gonna happen tonight
♫ I'm naturally bad
♫ You can win
♫ Doing wrong just makes me feel right
♫ From the time I was 10,
I held a gun with my right
♫ Kept fear at my back and evil in sight
♫ Walked in the shadow, I ran from the law
♫ The fire in my eyes
would even scare my own ma
♫ Yes, I'm naturally bad
♫ I'm bad as sin
♫ Something's gonna happen tonight
♫ I'm naturally bad
♫ And you can't win
♫ Doing wrong just makes me feel right
♫ When I smell trouble
♫ Wicked voice in my mind says
♫ Go get it, boy
♫ You found your own kind
♫ They call me a rebel, a sinister snake
♫ I'm so depraved, I make
them eat what they say
♫ I'm naturally bad
♫ Bad as sin
♫ Something's gonna happen tonight
♫ I'm naturally bad
♫ I won't give in
♫ I do whatever makes me feel right
♫ I said to myself
♫ This reputation is fun
♫ Renegade bad boy is second to none
♫ I ravage, I steal, I
take all that is mine
♫ I make a career of
crossing over the line
♫ Dirty dancing with danger
♫ I howl at the moon