- Oh, oh, oh, oh. [laughs]
- [grunting]
[grunts, sighs]
[theme song whistling]
[Greg narrating] What's great
about having an older brother
is that they can
teach you stuff,
because they've gone through
all of it before you.
[students cheer]
At least that's the way
it's supposed to be.
[snoring]
But my brother Rodrick's too busy to
teach his little brother anything.
I guess I'm just not
a big priority for him
because all his free time
just goes to his band.
The thing is, if Rodrick would
just take me under his wing,
I could totally surprise him.
And that would really
change things for us.
[crowd cheers]
But I guess that's
just not gonna happen.
And before long,
Rodrick will move out,
and I'll have to figure
things out for myself.
[coughs]
[both snoring]
But as long as the two of us
are living under the same roof,
I'm gonna soak up every bit of
big brother knowledge I can get.
[theme song ends]
[video game beeping
on television]
[announcer on TV] Player has
received Hammer of Ultimate Smashing!
Smash, smash…
Ooh. Ready, aim, fire!
Manny!
Aw.
Boys, the stuff in the
dishwasher is clean.
You just need to put the
dishes away before we get back.
Okay, yeah. I got your
hair dryer and my belt.
Um, was that... Was... [stammers]
Am I forgetting something?
Your pants?
Right. My pants.
Wait. Where are you
guys going again?
Your father and I are going into
the city for our anniversary.
You're going away?
Like, overnight?
Two nights, Greg.
Come on, Greg. We've been
over this a hundred times.
But... But how are we gonna
take care of ourselves?
What about Manny?
- [mom] Manny's staying with Gramma.
- [grunts] Hey!
And you boys will be just fine.
I stocked up on groceries.
- Groceries?
- [both gasp]
Did you get snacks?
- [grunting]
- I refuse to buy junk food for you guys.
I've told you before, if you want
snacks, you can buy them for yourselves.
Mommy, gimme!
Ugh, fine.
[paper rustling]
- [both groan]
- [Rodrick] I'm cashing these in.
250 Mom Bucks for 25 real ones.
"Mom Bucks"?
Oh. [chuckles] Yes, Frank.
The boys earn them by doing
chores and getting good grades.
Wait. Then how did
Rodrick get so many?
Mind your own business.
- [groans] Yuck.
- Rodrick should be earning real money,
not play money with, you
know, like, a real job.
When Löded Diper makes it
big, money won't be an issue.
Okay. And what if, just saying,
just putting it out there,
what if your band doesn't make
it big? What's your plan then?
I'll sell my hair for wigs
and fake mustaches and stuff.
Well, that sounds foolproof.
[grunting]
Okay, time to go! We've
got dinner reservations.
- See you boys Sunday!
- Whoo! [laughs]
Mom!
Now, we are trusting you to
be responsible this weekend.
I don't want you doing
anything I wouldn't do. Got it?
Frank, we talked about this.
I-I just wanted to make sure
we're all on the same page.
We good here?
Okay? Okay, we're good.
You can't leave me and Rodrick
alone together for a whole weekend.
Mom, we literally don't even know
how to take care of ourselves!
- Oh, come on, Greg. You two will have fun.
- [giggling, grunting]
Play some video games together.
Throw a ball in the backyard.
[snoring]
Do you even know Rodrick?
Listen, I know that you and your
brother don't always get along,
but a weekend like this
can help change that.
- [grunts] Yeah!
- [Greg] Ow!
[horn honks]
Who knows? You two might
surprise yourselves.
[car door closes]
Don't forget to
unload the dishwasher!
[groans]
- Whoa!
- All right, Greg.
We've got one hour to
get this place ready.
Ready for what?
The party.
What? No way! Mom and Dad would
never let you have a party!
They'll never even know, and
it's not my party anyway.
It's our party.
Whoa. What do you
mean "our party"?
The Heffley brothers are
throwing this party together.
The Heffley brothers?
That's right. You
and me, together.
People will be talking
about this night for years.
It's gonna be epic.
Epic.
So, what do you say? Are you in?
Okay, I'm in.
But who's coming to this thing?
I invite my friends.
You invite yours.
W-Wait. Y-You do
have friends, right?
Yeah, I have lots of friends!
There's Rowley, and there's Rowley.
Well, then, why don't
you call this "Rowley"
and have him come
over to help set up?
I don't know. I'm not sure Rowley could
really handle a high school party.
Plus, his parents would
never let him come.
So, you have him tell
them it's a sleepover.
Come on, we need all
the help we can get.
Oh. That's pretty good.
And when he gets here, you guys can start
by bringing up one of those plastic tables
from the basement.
Wait. Why can't you do that?
Because…
I can't do this
without your help.
And besides, I'm
going to get snacks.
Whoa! How do you
have so many friends?
It's called popularity.
You should try it.
All right. The
clock starts… now.
Now.
["Neighbourhood Brats" playing]
♪ The mutant offspring Of
council house schemes ♪
♪ The dreaded nightmare
Of town planners' dreams ♪
- [phone dings]
- Whoa! Party at Rodrick's, dude!
- Yeah!
- [laughs] Yeah!
- …totally got their nose rings locked.
- [phone dings, buzzes]
Whoa! Rager at Rodrick's!
- [laughs] Yes!
- It's gonna be awesome!
- [phone dings]
- Whoa!
[groans, grunts]
Party!
♪ The mutant offspring Of
council house schemes ♪
[doorbell rings]
- [music stops]
- [record scratches]
Hey, Greg! It's party time!
[Greg] No, no, no!
[blows party horn]
Whoa! Rowley, what
are you wearing?
You said this was a party.
Not that kind of party.
A cool party with, like, high
schoolers, and loud music and stuff.
You mean a boy-girl party?
Rowley, don't call
it a boy-girl party.
Why? Is it gonna be guys only?
'Cause that could be fun too.
No, just call it a party, okay?
And seriously, don't
embarrass me tonight.
It's just that me and Rodrick
never team up like this,
and I really don't want
anything to mess it up.
- Okay?
- Okay.
[door opens]
All right. You boys got
your work cut out for ya.
Get to it.
["Neighbourhood Brats" resumes]
♪ You blame the teachers
The troubles at home ♪
♪ You blame the parents
Where did we go wrong? ♪
[shouts]
[laughs]
♪ The dreaded nightmare
Of town planners' dreams ♪
♪ Neighborhood brats ♪
Ugh.
♪ The mutant offspring Of
council house schemes ♪
♪ The dreaded nightmare
Of town planners' dreams ♪
♪ Neighborhood brats ♪
- [screams]
- [laughs]
Go! Go, go, go, go!
♪ Folks step aside
When they pass ♪
- [groans]
- Ow!
Hmm. Good job, guys.
Huh. You know what, though? We
could use one more of those tables.
We're on it.
Do we have to do this?
The first table was heavy.
Everything's gotta be perfect!
Rodrick's, like, an expert at this stuff.
But it seems like he's just getting
us to do all the hard stuff.
You don't get it, Rowley.
Rodrick's depending on me.
Our party's gonna be… epic.
[whistles]
Um. [gulps]
[gasps]
Whoa.
- [cackles]
- [screams]
[mike feedback]
I don't think we should
be in Rodrick's bedroom.
Relax, we're just in
here for the table.
[Rowley] Do you think
there will be party games,
like charades or pin
the tail on the donkey?
- [amplifier sounds]
- [cymbals clatter]
It's not that kind
of thing, Rowley.
High-school parties are totally
different than little-kid parties.
How do you know?
I just know stuff.
Listen, we're gonna be the only
middle schoolers at this thing.
We've gotta blend in. Just
try and be cool, okay?
But pin the tail on
the donkey is cool.
Wait, what?
"See you after the party."
Oh, no.
What's going on? Is it stuck?
It's not stuck! I think
Rodrick locked the door.
But why would he do that?
What about the party? What
about the Heffley brothers?
It was, uh, probably
just a joke.
[grunting] Rodrick? Rodrick!
- [loud music playing]
- [knocking]
Rodrick!
- [pounding]
- [glass breaking]
Rodrick!
[increases music volume]
[teenagers cheering]
[grunts]
Rodrick!
Is he coming?
Just wait here, okay?
But I have tap-dancing
lessons in the morning.
I was sick last week,
and if I miss two in a row,
Miss Tilly's gonna be mad.
Relax, Rowley. I've got
everything under control.
Hmm.
I'm scared. What if
we starve down here?
- My celery sticks are in my overnight bag.
- [screams]
Can you please stop talking for
five seconds? I need to concentrate.
What's going on out
there? Are they… partying?
[Greg] I think I can
reach the lock. [grunting]
[Rowley grunts] Ow!
[sighs]
Can you reach it?
No.
But I've got an idea. Wait here.
[rock music playing]
Let's get this party started!
[cheering, laughing]
- Whoo!
- [teenager] Nice brain bucket.
And I was like, "Underwear
goes under your pants, bro."
Ew!
Whoa.
- Whoa.
- [blows]
Move.
[gasps]
[shutter clicks]
[Rowley] What's that for?
[Greg] Evidence.
Whoa.
- [camera shutter clicking]
- [teenagers] Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it!
[teenager] He actually did it!
Yeah! [laughs]
Whoa!
Huh? What...
[birds chirping]
[both snoring]
[sniffs]
[grunts]
[snoring]
[both] Whoa!
- [grunts]
- Ow!
What?
- [all snoring]
- Ew!
[gasps]
[stammers] I think
I'd better go home.
Yeah, that might be a good idea.
[door closes]
[groans]
[sighs]
♪ Never gonna give you up ♪
- [gasps]
♪ Never gonna run
around And desert you ♪
[groans] Dude.
Not cool, dude.
♪ Never gonna say goodbye
Never gonna tell a lie ♪
- Not cool.
- [thud]
♪ And hurt you ♪
- [music playing muffled]
- [teenager 1] My head.
- [teenager 2] This sucks.
- [Bill] Not cool.
[Rodrick groans]
[music stops]
[groans] What's
your problem, man?
It's not even,
like, afternoon yet.
You locked me in the basement!
Yeah, like, as a joke.
[laughs] Well, the joke's on you, because
when Mom and Dad get home tomorrow,
I'm gonna tell them all
about your little party.
You wouldn't have the guts.
[phone rings, buzzes]
Hey, Mom. How is the trip going?
Well... Well, it was going great
until Manny got a stomach bug.
We're headed to
Gramma's to pick him up.
Wait. You're coming home today?
- Yes, Rodrick.
- [Frank] Got it.
We should be home in an hour.
Did you boys empty the
dishwasher like I asked?
[Frank] You gotta be kidding me.
Not yet.
[Mom] Well, it had better be
done by the time we're back.
No problem. See you soon.
[phone beeps]
Okay, you heard her. We've got one
hour to clean up this whole mess.
Not my problem.
I'll be in my room.
Dude!
Mom and Dad are gonna go ballistic
if they find out I had a party!
Please, you've gotta help me.
And why would I do that?
[clock ticking]
Because we're brothers.
Yeah, well, brothers don't lock
each other in the basement.
Okay, okay. I slipped up.
Won't happen again, I swear.
Please!
If I help you clean up this mess, things
are gonna be different between us.
Different? Like how?
For starters, you're gonna start
treating me better, like an equal.
Okay, okay. Done.
Equals. Got it.
And you're gonna owe me.
Owe you what?
I'm... I'm... I'm thinking.
Dude, we've got no time!
Okay. Yeah, I owe you. Can we
just work out the details later?
[sighs] Fine.
All right, my man!
Let's do this.
And go!
[grunts]
[toilet bubbling]
[Greg grunts]
- What?
- Hmm.
- [Rodrick yells]
Gonna blow chunks!
Don't worry, Manny.
We'll be home in a jiffy.
[dry retches]
Honey, better step on it.
- [engine revs]
- [Manny] Whoa!
[yells]
- [groans, gags]
- [stomach rumbles]
I am taking the shortcut!
[Manny] Whoa! [shouting]
Manny!
Huh? What?
[screams] Whoa!
Ouch!
[gags]
- [Rodrick tuts]
- [Greg screams]
[yelps]
- [Frank] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- [mom screaming]
[both scream]
Mission accomplished,
little bro.
[door closing]
[car approaches]
[both screaming]
It's permanent ink! This
is never coming off!
Um... [gasps]
We need another door!
Another door? Where are
we gonna get another door?
[gasps] The basement! Go,
go, go, go, go, go, go!
[groans]
Oh, let's hurry up
and get you inside.
[grunts] Quit pushing!
Quit pulling! Push!
I said pull!
Ow!
[groans]
Come on, Frank.
Boys?
We're home!
Oh. Hey, Mom!
So, did you guys do some brotherly
bonding while we were gone?
Uh, kinda, I guess.
Rodrick, y-you're sweating!
Oh, I hope you don't
have what Manny has.
[Frank] I knew it, Susan!
I knew they couldn't be trusted!
They didn't empty
the dishwasher.
[Manny gags, vomits]
- [Frank] Oh, that's gross.
- [Manny] Manny all better!
[sighs]
[chuckling]
[phone beeping]
[laughing] Oh.
Oh, man!
Hmm.
[sniffs] There's gotta be
evidence. They're not that smart.
Aha!
[groans]
[laughs]
[screams]
[chuckles]
You think he knows?
I... I think he knows!
Shh! Keep your
voice down, dummy.
If he doesn't know, he's
gonna figure it out.
I mean, he's been sniffing around
the house ever since he got back.
He's gonna find something.
You need to calm down. We covered
our tracks. We cleaned up the place.
Yeah, and you owe me for that.
And you can start paying me back
by finishing with these leaves!
Wait, wait, wait. What...
What is this about owing you?
I don't remember saying
anything like that.
Are you kidding me? I cleaned up your
stupid party, and that wasn't easy!
Don't you mean our party? We
were partners in this thing.
That mess was our mess,
and if Mom and Dad ever find out
about it, we're both in hot water.
No way! This was your party!
You're the one who's
getting in trouble, not me!
I'm gonna tell Mom and
Dad what really happened.
Fine, fine. I'll pay up.
Yeah? And how are
you gonna do that?
By giving you my most
valuable possession.
What? Mom Bucks?
No, thanks. I've seen
where you keep them.
Something even better
than that. Knowledge.
[scoffs] I've seen
your report card.
Not school knowledge. Real knowledge.
Stuff you can actually use.
I'm listening.
I'll give you a little taste.
Let's start with the
way you bag your leaves.
When you do it, you fill your bag
to the top and then tie it shut.
But that's not smart.
Mom's paying three
Mom Bucks a bag.
So, if you wanna maximize your
income, you've gotta do it like this.
But isn't that cheating?
It's not cheating. It's
just gaming the system.
So, what? You're just gonna give
me a bunch of yard work tips?
I can teach you lots of
things, little brother.
Stuff that'll make
your whole life easier.
Your problem is that
you work too hard.
I want that underwear
off the table
by the time I get back
from the grocery store.
- [door closes]
- [Rodrick] What you do is set the bar low,
so Mom and Dad don't
expect too much out of you.
Because then…
Wha...
[Rodrick] …they're happy when you
do practically nothing at all.
Here's another tip.
Pretend you don't
know how to do stuff,
because that'll get you out
of a lot of unnecessary work.
[sighs] H…
H… Hmm.
I'll just do it, okay?
[typing]
[Rodrick] And if you really
don't feel like doing something,
a well-timed trip to the bathroom
is always your ticket out.
I'm ready to start!
I just finished.
My body is on a schedule.
[groans]
Okay, I'll admit it.
That's... That's pretty good.
What else can you teach me?
Oh, I've got loads of stuff like
that. I call it my Rodrick Rules.
Don't you mean
"Rodrick's Rules"?
No, Rodrick Rules. There's
only one Rodrick, me.
[sighs] Yeah.
I meant, like, apostrophe S.
Rodrick Rule number one. No
apostrophes or any other nerd stuff.
That kinda stuff will get
you beat up at school.
So, what's rule number two?
Uh, I've already
given away too much.
If you want more, we're gonna
have to make this deal official.
You keep your mouth shut about the party,
and I'll tell you everything I know.
Deal.
Greg, Rowley's here! Time to go!
Hello, Rowley. Don't
you look handsome?
[gulps]
Um, this weekend I had tap-dancing
lessons with Miss Tilly. [chuckles]
Uh, nothing out of
the ordinary happened.
[chuckling]
- [parents gasp]
- Whoa. Hey, Rowley!
It's been a while.
Friday afternoon, right?
Yeah, we...
- Whoa! So clean.
- Uh… [chuckles]
Yeah, yeah. Time to go, Rowley!
Time... Time to go. Get out.
Come on, Rowley. Two
more seconds in there,
and you were gonna spill your
guts about the whole party.
Sorry, I'm not
good at this stuff.
You don't think my dad
heard you back there, right?
'Cause he's been acting
really suspicious.
How did you get the
house so clean, though?
Um, me and Rodrick
actually did it together.
I told you, me and
him are a team.
[shouts] You and Rodrick? But
he locked us in the basement!
Uh, yeah. Brothers just
joke like that. [chuckles]
It's actually pretty hilarious
if you really think about it.
Don't look at me like that.
Anyway, yeah, Rodrick's been, uh...
He's been taking me under his wing.
He's been teaching
me a bunch of stuff.
Really? What kind of stuff?
Uh, like, how you need
to set the bar low,
so your parents don't
expect too much from you.
Oh, and how you can trick them into
helping you with your homework.
That kind of thing.
That seems like bad stuff.
This information is
like gold, Rowley!
It's what makes having an
older brother worth it.
But why is Rodrick being so
nice to you all of a sudden?
I don't know. Maybe 'cause he
just likes having me around.
You know what? You wouldn't
understand. You're an only child.
No offense.
Well, I'm glad I'm an only child. 'Cause
this brother stuff is complicated.
["Requiem in D Minor
Lacrimosa" playing]
[song stops]
[continues playing drums]
Rodrick!
What?
You need to teach me something new.
You never got past rule number one.
You only get one rule a week.
That's Rodrick Rule number two.
[rim shot]
What? That's not fair.
Life's not fair.
Rule number three. And now you
made me break rule number two.
[sighs] Fine.
Ow! What the...
I've been looking for that.
What is this?
It's an echo pedal. We need it…
[echoes, singing]
…for the talent show.
Oh, yeah, the talent
show. I'm trying out too.
You? You don't have any talent.
Yeah, I'm in Rowley's magic act.
I'm his…
assistant.
[scoffs]
[laughs] Man, they're... They're
gonna laugh you off the stage.
Yeah, I know. Mom's making me.
Hey, do you think you
can get me out of this?
[laughs] Sorry, you c... You
can't leave your friends hanging.
Rodrick Rule number four.
All right, enough with the rules. How
about you teach me something for real?
Like what?
I don't know.
Maybe you could teach me how
to play the drums or something.
[snickers] Are you sure you could
handle that, little brother?
- Yeah!
- All right.
It's simple.
You just gotta grip the sticks,
feel the flow, and let it rip.
Okay, now loosen up that wrist a bit.
Keep it flowing. Feel the rhythm.
That... Th-That's it! [laughs]
You've got potential, little bro.
- [door opens]
- [gasps]
Are you ready to rock?
[Greg narrating] Bill Walter is
the lead singer of Löded Diper,
even though he's something
like 35 years old.
I'm pretty sure Rodrick
asked him to join
because he got named "Most
Likely to Be a Rock Star"
when he was in high school.
[laughs]
Beat it, kid. Grown-ups
are talking here.
Nah, that... That's all
right. He can stay. He's cool.
Whatever you say, dude.
You ready to burn
this place down?
We are Löded Diper!
One, two, three, four!
[rock music playing]
[Bill] ♪ All right ♪
[screams]
- [music continues]
- [groans]
- ♪ So, he sent us underground ♪
- Huh?
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ You never listened ♪
[vocalizes]
[babbling]
Isn't setting the
table Greg's job?
He's hanging out with his
brother in the basement.
I didn't want to interrupt
their "together time."
Listen, I... [stammers]
Do you think it's a good idea that those
guys are spending so much time together?
Why wouldn't it be a good idea?
It's just that...
[stammers] Well, I mean...
Look, who knows what kind of
stuff Rodrick is teaching Greg?
- [music stops]
- [Rodrick] Somebody farted!
- [all coughing]
- [Greg groans]
Ew, gross.
[all laughing]
- [echoes] Somebody farted!
- [all laughing]
I rest my case.
The boys are bonding, Frank.
Isn't that what
we want to happen?
Look, sometimes my older brother,
Joe, would string me along,
and then I'd get burned.
Greg needs to protect himself.
Because if Rodrick pulls the rug out
from under him, he's gonna get hurt.
We can't police every interaction
between these boys, Frank.
They need to work
things out on their own.
[sighs] Maybe you're
right. But I just... I...
Now why don't you just take off that
tie, and try and relax a little?
[clears throat] I'll, uh,
go get washed up for dinner.
[music resumes]
[handle jiggles]
Hey! Didn't this
door used to lock?
So, you guys are telling us
that you have no idea why the
bathroom door suddenly doesn't lock?
Wait. We have a
bathroom on this floor?
[sighs] I feel like there's
something the boys aren't telling us.
Greg, would you like
to say something?
Um…
Actually, something did
happen on Friday night.
Something I should've
told you about.
[groans]
I went in the bathroom, and
I tried to lock the door.
But I couldn't.
I think I must have broken it by
shutting it too hard or something.
Sorry.
[sighs]
Okay. Mystery solved.
Let's move on.
[whispers] Nice save.
Boys, your father and I are taking another
shot at celebrating our anniversary
since our first
attempt got cut short.
You're going away this weekend?
Yes, but don't worry.
You see, we're not gonna leave
you two on your own again.
Why? Who's coming over?
You two boys are gonna
visit your grandpa.
Wait. At Leisure Towers? But
there's nothing to do there.
Oh, there's plenty to
do at Grandpa's complex.
Shuffleboard, bingo, the pool.
[singsongy] And you know how
much my dad loves board games!
Board games?
Come on, guys.
You know Grandpa appreciates it
when you spend time with him.
- But... [sighs]
- Mom's right, Greg.
It's been way too long since
we paid Grandpa a visit.
This... This is gonna be great.
Okay, guys. Better get packed.
Greg, I'll help you.
- Rodrick?
- Yeah?
Good role modeling.
Well, I try.
Ready, set, go!
Whoo-hoo! Whee!
- [crashes]
- Aha!
- [snores]
- [groans]
- [elevator bell dings]
- Ooh. Hey!
[squeaking]
[elevator bell dings]
Dagnabbit!
Okay, boys! This is Gutbusters!
One player reads a card, and the
other players try not to laugh.
Them's the rules!
- That sounds so fun!
- [sighs]
- Roll the dice, Grandpa!
- [dice rattling]
[Grandpa] Ha! Snake eyes!
It's your turn to read, Greg.
[groans] "A man who would pun,
would just as easily pick a pocket."
[both snickering]
Huh? I don't get it.
- [Rodrick laughs]
- [Grandpa laughs]
Come on, Rodrick!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[laughing] I'm sorry, I...
I... I-I-I couldn't help it.
[laughing] That one
gets me every time.
[exhales] All right, boys.
Now, why don't you clean up this
mess while I take a potty break?
Okay, Grandpa. But don't
take too long in there.
I can't believe you
agreed to coming here.
Why didn't you at least
try to get us out of it?
Can't talk. Concentrating.
Rodrick, what are you doing?
Isn't one game enough?
You think I'm here
to play games?
Are those Mom Bucks?
Millions of dollars worth.
[sniffs]
That's amazing. Wow!
So, this is why you wanted
to come to Leisure Towers.
Bingo. Now you're
starting to get it.
Come on. Let's split it up.
- Ah! Da, da, da, da! Not so fast.
- [grunts]
Go find your own supply.
Come on, Rodrick. You owe me.
[groans] Fine, here's a hundred.
Don't spend it all in one place.
Now, why don't you go change?
You look like you wet yourself.
I can't. Grandpa's
in the bathroom.
Then use the one in the lobby.
[Greg narrating] I've gotta hand it
to Rodrick on this Mom Bucks thing.
Every time I think I've
figured him all out,
he surprises me
with something new.
It's pea soup again
tonight, I hear.
That sounds pretty good to me.
[shoes squeaking]
Huh?
[both gasp]
[elderly person] Oh, my.
[groans]
[chuckles]
[grunting]
[elderly person] Hi, Merle!
Going to bingo tonight?
[Merle] I wouldn't
miss it for the world.
[elderly person] Well, you can
kiss your winning streak goodbye.
I'm bringing a good
luck charm with me.
- [squeaks]
- Oh! Isn't he cute?
Merle, Irene, bingo tonight?
Ha! We'll see.
Can you believe my luck last
week? Two games in a row.
It was all thanks
to my lucky charm.
[squeaks]
[whimpers]
[flushes]
[shouts]
Say…
"Boys size small?"
[gasps] A Peeping Tom!
[shouts]
We see you in there,
Boy Size Small!
[Irene] We're gonna hand
you over to the authorities!
[Merle] They'll put
you in the slammer!
- [Irene] Where did he go?
- [elderly person] I don't see him.
[Irene] Did he give us the slip?
[squeaks]
[shouts]
- [screams]
- There he is!
He's on the move, ladies!
[laughing]
[grunts]
[shouting]
After him!
[alarm sounds]
- Huh? Huh?
- [grunts]
- We're coming through!
- Hey! Watch it!
- Don't let him get away!
- [panting]
[ladies muttering]
[sighs]
- [yelps]
- You get out of here!
- [shouts]
- [chattering]
[elderly person]
Killing my bingo buzz!
[Irene] There he is!
There's Boy Size Small.
- Come back here! We're gonna get you!
- Yeah! Yeah!
There he is! Come on!
- [shouts]
- [guard] Hey, kid!
- Come back here!
- Come on. Wait!
- Out of my way!
- Hey! Get off!
Where do you think you're going?
[panting]
[gasps]
Hmm, what do we have here?
- Oh!
- Uh…
That's nasty.
- [gasps]
- All right!
- Hey!
- There he goes! This way!
D'oh!
Come here!
[groans]
I could've sworn
he went this way.
Where is he?
He gave us the slip.
[sighs]
[Greg narrating] Somehow, I managed
to get back to Grandpa's room.
But Rodrick can never find out about
this. 'Cause if he does, I'm a dead man.
You're in big
trouble, young man.
[whimpers]
Rodrick just rolled a 12!
[chuckling]
That means you've gotta
fork over half your cards.
Come on, snake eyes!
Put some pants on,
for the love of Pete.
[chuckles]
Is there something you want
to tell me, little brother?
[gulps]
[snoring]
[sighs]
Open up!
[snores]
[grunting]
[gasps] Grandpa, can we... Can
we please change the channel?
There's nothing but a
bunch of garbage on TV.
I like to watch
people come and go.
Ooh! Hot in there.
[Grandpa] Barry Grossman!
You've got time to sit in
the sauna for two hours,
but you can't bother yourself
to return my vacuum cleaner!
[laughs]
Bah, fine! You can
have the clicker.
And in some disturbing
news, earlier this evening,
a Peeping Tom was spotted in the
women's bathroom at Leisure...
[button clicking]
[snores]
[door opens]
[shouts]
You're jumpy tonight. Mind you
don't wake up your brother.
Oh, yeah. You're right, Grandpa.
There's... There's nothing good on TV.
Ha! Told you so.
[sighs] You know, Greg, I
might be old, but I'm no fool.
I know what's really going on.
You do?
You and your brother aren't here
because you want to be here.
Your parents made you come.
That's not true. Grandpa,
we wanted to come here.
[laughs]
No boys your age would choose to spend
the weekend with an old codger like me.
Ha! Yeah, well,
I'll tell you this.
I've enjoyed every second
of it. You're good boys.
I guess.
I know you boys love each other,
because you spend time together.
It wasn't always that
way with my boys.
And now they've grown apart.
They don't even spend
the holidays together.
I just wish they'd worked
things out when they were young.
Like you and Rodrick have.
Maybe things would
be different now.
[Greg] Yeah.
[doorbell rings]
Hey, Greg.
Rowley, I told you
not to wear stripes.
But I thought we could be twins.
Eh, eh? See? Twins.
Great. Now I gotta change.
What did you do your
Life Sciences project on?
- My what?
- Your Life Sciences project.
It's due today.
That's due today?
Yeah. And it's, like,
25% of our grade.
Oh, man! I forgot all
about that project.
What are you gonna do? 'Cause
this project is 25% of our grade.
I know, Rowley! Let me think.
Rodrick.
Rodrick?
Rodrick! I need your help!
Calm down, Gregory. What's
got your underwear in a bunch?
I've got a Life Science
project due today!
Yeah? And what's that
got to do with me?
Well, I figured you might know
some trick. Some way out of this.
Well, you could pretend
you're sick. Skip school.
Mom would know I'm
faking. She always knows.
You could tell your
teacher Manny ate it.
Really, Rodrick? That's the
best you can come up with?
You know I still have dirt on you,
right? I can come clean to Mom right now.
Hmm. Did you say Life Sciences?
That does ring a bell.
Let's see.
No. No.
- [grunts] Ah!
- What are you doing?
My life Sciences project.
And in mint condition too.
Let me see that.
Uh-uh-uh-uh!
This is some of my best
work. It's why I saved it.
Awesome. Here, give it.
No, sir. This is gonna cost you.
Come on, Rodrick. Me and you
have a partnership. A deal.
Yeah. Well, our deal doesn't cover
this kind of thing. This is extra.
Okay, what do you want for it?
I want cash.
[groans] I don't have any cash.
I'm talking Mom Bucks.
Large bills only.
Come on, Rodrick.
Don't you have enough?
No, you can never have enough Mom
Bucks. That's Rodrick Rule number five.
Fine. I'll give you
20. That's fair.
Mmm, actually, you seem
a little too eager.
Make it a hundred.
[groans]
Fine. But you can't
tell anyone about this.
I may be a lot of things, but
one thing I am not is a snitch.
Great doing business
with you, brother.
[bell rings]
You got one of Rodrick's old
projects? But isn't that cheating?
It's not cheating.
It's gaming the system.
I told you not to
look at me like that.
But what if he got a bad grade?
My parents always help Rodrick
with his homework. So, I'm all set.
Can I see?
Um, Greg? I don't think your
parents helped with this one.
Give me that!
[Rodrick] Do plants sneeze?
Hypothesis. Plants
probably sneeze.
Experiment. Hmm.
Conclusion. Plants don't sneeze.
[chuckles, whimpers]
Hmm.
Rodrick!
[rock music playing]
[Bill] ♪ All right ♪
[grunts]
[screams]
♪ Oh, yeah! Yeah! ♪
[mike feedback]
[drums beating]
You lied to me!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Not true, bro.
You said this was
your best work!
It was. You should've seen
my other school projects.
Yeah.
Well, I want my money back.
No refunds. A deal's a deal.
Yeah, about that. Let's see
if these change your mind.
Yo! That's me.
Wha... Oh. [chuckles] My bad.
Please, uh... Please
continue, bros.
You wouldn't show these to
Mom or Dad. You're no snitch.
You have no idea what
I'm willing to do.
All... All right. Here, I'll
give you your $100 back.
Hmm. You seem a little eager.
It's gonna cost you
approximately 200 Mom Bucks.
Uh, "Mom Bucks"?
[sighs] Nice doing
business with you, brother.
So, do plants sneeze?
[Greg narrating] I'm not gonna say
I'm proud of myself for what I did.
But I learned how to
negotiate from the master.
[rock music playing]
[humming]
♪ Uh-huh, that's right
That's where you're shaking ♪
- [screams]
- [grunts]
Greg, you need to watch
where you're going.
[groans] Just look at this mess.
[gasps]
[scoffs] I don't believe this.
I... A party? Guys? Seriously?
Counterfeit money? Where
did you boys get all this?
I knew that bathroom locked!
Aha! I am not going crazy.
You boys had a party in our home.
Somebody could've gotten hurt or worse.
See? See?
Didn't I tell you it wasn't a good
idea for these two to be hanging out?
Greg, it might not have been your
party, but you helped cover it up.
You lied to us.
And because of that,
you are grounded.
No video games or
electronics for three weeks.
And Rodrick, you're
the older brother.
What kind of example are
you setting for Greg?
A bad example?
You're grounded for a month.
Hand over your van keys.
Plus, you boys are doing
the dishes every night.
And don't give me any of this "my
body's on a schedule" nonsense.
Mom?
What, Rodrick?
So, I get that I can't
use my van. Totally fair.
But I can still go to the talent
show if I get a ride, right?
No, Rodrick. Grounded means
grounded. No extracurricular stuff.
But... But... But... But we... But
we've been practicing for months.
If I can't play, the other guys
won't be able to be in the show...
Actions have consequences.
What kind of parents would we be if
we let you go to the talent show?
Good parents?
- Mom?
- Yes, Greg?
Since Rodrick can't be in the
talent show, I can't either, right?
Because that wouldn't be fair.
You are not using this as an excuse
to get out of that talent show, Greg!
You can't let Rowley down.
He's done so much for you.
Now go. Go help your
brother with the dishes.
So, that was pretty
crazy back there, huh?
I mean, three weeks of no
electronics, I expected.
But your punishment was a
little harsh if you ask me.
It wouldn't have happened
if you didn't snitch.
Hey, whoa! I didn't
say anything!
You marched right upstairs and
went straight to Mommy and Daddy.
You ratted me out!
No snitching. That's
Rodrick Rule number one!
I thought rule number
one was no apostrophes.
And besides, that's
not what happened!
I took you under my
wing! I trusted you!
Yeah, it's been great.
You've taught me a lot.
Yeah, and the only reason that I
did was because you had dirt on me.
And now you don't.
So, watch your back.
But...
I thought you were
cool. Guess I was wrong.
Introducing the Amazing
Rowley Jefferson!
Whoo, yeah!
And with a wave of my magic
wand, the egg has disappeared!
[egg breaks]
Greg, you were supposed to turn the cup
upside down before you gave it back to me.
Huh? Oh, yeah. Next time.
If we don't get this right by
Friday night, we're never gonna win!
We're not gonna win, Rowley. We're
competing against high schoolers.
Well, at least we don't have to
go against your brother's band.
[sighs] Yes, we do. They
got a replacement drummer.
Oh.
Hey, I've got an idea.
I was thinking maybe I
could be the magician
and you could be the assistant.
It's way more
believable that way.
But it's my magic set! I
got it for my birthday!
Okay, okay.
- Gee whiz.
- [door opens]
Hey, guys!
Hi, Rodrick. Wanna
see some magic?
Nah, wouldn't want you to spoil it
for me. Save it for the big night.
Oh. Okay!
Wait. What are
you doing up here?
I found something on the kitchen
table. Thought it might belong to you.
Hey! Give it back!
Easy there, little brother. I
was just returning your property.
Wait. You didn't
read it, did you?
Read it? [scoffs] Way
too many words for me.
[sighs]
I did look at the
pictures though.
And boy, I learned a lot.
Like what really happened
at Leisure Towers.
That's private.
Well, it's about to be public.
See, I know people.
And those people have little brothers
and sisters that go to your school.
And I'll bet they're gonna love
reading about your little adventure
in the women's bathroom.
You wouldn't!
You ratted me out. These
are the consequences.
- [shouts, grunts]
- [grunts]
Give me that!
Oh! [chuckles]
- [Greg grunts]
- [Rodrick] Ow!
No!
Ooh!
Nice catch.
[chuckles]
- Oops!
- [phone beeps]
[phone chiming]
No!
My bad.
[Greg narrating] Believe me, I did
not want to go to school the next day.
After Rodrick's little text was sent
out, my reputation was gonna be ruined.
But I knew I couldn't
hide forever.
So, I just decided to bite the
bullet and get it over with.
[students chattering]
All right, Rowley.
Let's do this.
Rowley?
You got this, Greg! [chuckles]
[sighs]
- This week's flying by, like, so fast.
- I know!
- Wait. Wait. Is that Greg Heffley?
- Look!
[both] Whoa!
[cheering]
What?
[chanting] Greg! Greg! Greg! Greg!
Greg! Greg! Greg! Greg! Greg! Greg!
[Greg narrating] It took me a few
minutes to figure out what was going on.
Rodrick's message went
out to all of his friends.
[phone beeps]
His friends told their brothers
and sisters what happened to me,
and they told their friends.
Just like Rodrick planned it.
But I guess people
mixed up the facts
because by the time I got to school,
the story was totally scrambled.
Somehow the story went
from me being caught in the
ladies' room at Leisure Towers,
to me sneaking into a bingo game and
walking off with the grand prize.
Bingo! [chuckles]
- [grunts]
And the only thing people got right was
me getting chased by the security guards.
But even that stuff
got exaggerated.
- [growls]
- Hey!
- Whoa!
[blows raspberry]
[Greg narrating] Even the
thing with the vending machines
made it into the story,
but the facts got
mixed up there too.
I wasn't exactly in a hurry to
set the record straight, though.
Because the new version of the
story made me look pretty sick.
[crowd cheering]
So Rodrick's plan backfired,
and I got a taste of what it's
like to be popular for once.
Wow! This is so cool!
I got his autograph!
[Greg narrating] But I
knew it wouldn't last.
Because the second I took the stage as
Rowley's assistant at the talent show,
my reputation was
gonna take a nosedive.
[sighs] I don't get why I
have to go to this thing.
You're here to cheer on your
brother, Rodrick, and your bandmates.
Ex-bandmates.
[grunts] D-Does the rec
center have a bathroom?
[engine revs]
[chattering]
[Frank] Okay. Everyone, hop
out. I'll go look for a spot.
Yo! What's shaking, little man?
Uh, nothing much.
So, we heard about your little
dustup over at Leisure Towers.
The what?
Oh, yeah. That.
Dude, you're a legend!
An absolute lege, dude!
Yeah, I guess.
So, we were thinking,
if we join forces tonight,
we could win this thing.
Huh? I-I don't get it.
You've got the middle school vote.
And we've got the high school vote.
And I've got the Mom
vote. Not to brag.
What do you mean "join forces"?
How'd you like to be
Löded Diper's new drummer?
What? I don't know
how to play the drums.
We know your brother's
been teaching you.
Time for the student
to become the master.
Sorry, guys. I'm in my friend's
magic act. I can't get out of it.
That's where Larry comes in. We'll
do a clean swap. You for him.
Magic is my real passion.
Ta-da!
I just can't do that to
Rodrick. He's my brother.
Why don't you just
think it over?
Maybe this is your
turn to shine, my dude.
I'll think about it.
That's all we're
asking, little man.
[audience chattering]
[mike feedback]
- Yo! It's Greg!
- That's Greg Heffley!
- You're a legend, dude.
- [chuckles] Yeah, thanks.
Oh!
Is that Boy Size Small?
Where were you?
I just got held up.
[orchestral music playing]
Oh, this is so exciting.
[announcer] Ladies and
gentlemen, boys and girls!
- Welcome to the Talent Show!
- [cheering]
[playing off-key]
[crowd murmuring]
[groans]
Then the man in the orthopedic
shoes said, "I stand corrected!"
- [laughs]
- [grunts]
[house music playing]
[beatboxing]
Oh.
♪ Amor fatal ♪
♪ Tremendo ♪
[whispering] I've
got to get ready.
- Break a leg, Greg.
- Okay.
Do your best for Rowley. Try
and look like you're having fun.
Hey, Greg.
Can't wait to see you do your
magic. [scoffs] So uncool.
Are you ready for
some magic, Manny?
- Yay!
- Yes, you are. Yes, you are.
[Bill] Ladies and
gentlemen, boys and girls.
We have just one
question for you.
- [snores, gasps]
- Wake up!
Are you ready to rock?
[mike feedback]
Yeah!
Now, before we explode your eardrums
with a blast of pure rock and roll,
it's time to introduce the
newest member of Löded Diper.
Please join me in welcoming
Greg Heffley to the stage!
- [gasps]
- Greg?
[cheering]
Come on, little dude.
Give 'em a taste.
Oh. Oof.
- [audience chattering]
- [laughs]
[cheering]
Yeah, right on.
We love you, Greg!
[chanting] Greg! Greg! Greg! Greg!
Greg! Greg! Greg! Greg! Greg! Greg!
Yo, you ready to blow
the roof off this place?
Hey. You're missing the show.
What are you doing out here?
Aren't you supposed to be on stage?
I don't know. It
didn't feel right.
Well, maybe that's
because it's not right.
You stole my spot just to get
back at me for the diary thing.
Pretty much. But it
wasn't just about payback.
[scoffs] Yeah, right.
I, uh, wanted you
to be proud of me.
Proud of you? For what?
I-I know. I-It was dumb.
I've got something that I've got
to get off my chest too, I guess.
I... I shouldn't have
taken your diary.
That wasn't… cool.
I don't understand why we can't
just get along like normal brothers.
This is normal. Brothers fight.
We just… took it too far.
But do you think we're gonna be
all right, like, in the long run?
What? What do you mean?
Well, Dad and his brothers don't even
see each other on holidays anymore.
Is that gonna happen to us?
Heck, yeah, we're gonna see each
other on the holidays. We're family.
But I am not hosting.
Too much work.
Okay. Deal.
Listen, me and you are
gonna have our battles.
But I really hope you know
that when the chips are down,
and I mean really down,
I'm gonna have your back.
And you better have mine.
Because it's the Heffley
brothers against the world.
The Heffley brothers.
[crowd cheering]
Greg! Greg! Greg!
So? Are you gonna keep sitting out
here, or are you gonna go make me proud?
Yeah, about that. These
don't belong to me.
Like you said, there's only
one Rodrick. And that's you.
[shouts, grunts]
[laughing]
[Rodrick] Wait a second.
I'm still grounded.
[Greg] Oh, yeah. I
forgot about that.
[Rodrick] Oh, well. Rodrick Rule number
ten. Always go out in a blaze of glory.
[both laugh]
- [crowd jeering]
- [crowd member] Come on, entertain us!
Stand by. Uh, we're just having
some, uh, technical difficulties.
[drums beating]
All right!
Please welcome Löded
Diper's original drummer,
Rodrick Heffley!
- Whoo!
- [crowd cheering]
- What?
- Rodrick?
Rodrick rules!
We love you, Rodrick!
Unbelievable.
Greg, you do understand
that you're both grounded?
Yeah, I know.
Rodrick isn't supposed
to be up there.
So, we have no choice but
to extend your punishment.
It's worth it.
He's my brother.
I've got his back.
You're raising some
good boys there, Son.
Yeah.
[drumsticks hitting]
♪ All right! ♪
- ♪ Oh, yeah! ♪
- [chuckles] Yippee!
- Whoo!
- Whoo-hoo!
[grunts]
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ You never liked us So
you sent us underground ♪
[grunts]
Come on!
♪ You never listened So
we turned up the sound ♪
Huh?
♪ And now you're quaking
As I'm standing on stage ♪
- Yeah! Löded Diper!
- [Bill] Uh-huh! Yeah!
♪ That's why you're shaking
'Cause you're feeling your age ♪
Whoo! That's my jam!
♪ Your arms are waving
As you get on your feet ♪
♪ Your booty swaying Like
you ate some bad meat ♪
♪ So we say Can
you smell us now? ♪
♪ Filling up your nostrils
And you're mopping your brow ♪
♪ Come on Can you smell us… ♪
What? Susan!
Yeah!
[screams] Whoo-hoo!
[both] ♪ Can you smell us now? ♪
Susan, your bunions!
Whoo!
- Oh, man! [laughs]
- Look at her!
♪ In stadiums, gymnasiums
So let's hear you shout! ♪
- Oh! See, I can't unsee that!
- [both laugh]
That's right.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Oh. [chuckles] Whoo!
[theme song playing]
[Greg narrating] Even after all that,
Löded Diper didn't win the talent show.
First place went to the
Amazing Rowley Jefferson
and his assistant
Larry the Wonderful.
[cheering]
But it wasn't all bad news
for Rodrick and his band.
Thanks to Mom, their music
reached a whole new audience.
I'm really not too worried about
me and Rodrick growing apart.
Sure, we'll have our ups
and downs, but for now…
[shutter clicks]
…we're cool.
[theme song ends]
[rock music playing]
♪ All right! ♪
♪ Oh, yeah! ♪
[grunts]
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Can you smell us now? ♪
♪ Filling up your nostrils
And you're mopping your brow ♪
♪ Come on Can you
smell us now? ♪
♪ We're leaking through your
speakers Like a chocolate cow ♪
♪ Can you smell us now? ♪
♪ The pressure's building up
Now we're about to bust out ♪
♪ Can you smell us now? ♪
♪ In stadiums, gymnasiums
So let's hear you shout! ♪
♪ That's right ♪
♪ Whoo-hoo! ♪