(Multicom Jingle)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(strong wind blows)
- Papa.
(melancholic orchestral music)
♪ Someone's falling asleep tonight ♪
♪ Sandman, I'm talking to you ♪
♪ This little girl has
just turned off her light ♪
♪ Make sure her dreams
are a colorful sight ♪
♪ Chase all the fear from
her bedside tonight ♪
♪ Tomorrow is not far away ♪
- Cut!
Cut, playback.
(bell rings)
Hello, Mr. Snow Man?
I have a blizzard going here.
Mr. Snow Man, I have
a blizzard going here.
I need a lot more snow, say
50% more snow, you got that?
- Jane!
- [Jane] Your turn.
- When do I get to play a
real part instead of just
being your stand-in or hangin'
around in the background?
- Maybe when I think you're ready.
- [Director] Come on, Blanche.
- Maybe you'd better go with her.
- [Director] Alright, going one more time.
I need some help, people,
we gotta make this thing.
Let's go, let's go!
- Honey, the parts will get bigger.
- Not in her pictures.
I really, really don't understand her.
Sometimes she's nice and
then she gets really mean.
I think she's crazy.
The way she treats everybody,
even you and Daddy.
- Please, we need you on your
sister's marks, thank you.
- We promised your
sister a real part, Jane.
- We did, Jane.
- Blanche is clumsy.
- [Director] Okay, Blanche.
Take your sister's position
on the bed, please.
- Whoa, whoa, sky bombers, sky bombers!
- I'd like to live at the beach always.
- Maybe we could!
- Daddy?
- No, Blanche, it's just
too far from the studios.
- It might be nice for the girls.
- Yeah, but when Blanche
begins her acting lessons,
it'll be just too inconvenient.
- Now me, and let's do it like Betty Boop.
- Okay.
Get your nose.
(girls giggle)
Okay.
Put your lips together.
(laughs)
(father laughs)
- Good job, Blanche, good job!
(Blanche yelps and giggles)
Good job. (laughs)
(bell rings)
- Ice cream!
- Ice cream?
Oh, oh, oh, ice cream, ice cream.
We scream, we all scream, oh!
(somber orchestral music)
- I know, but I didn't know what to do.
You'd gone and I didn't think
you were ever coming back.
You won't leave, now that you're here?
- No.
- You promise you'll stay?
- Always.
- Oh, Bill.
Bill.
Ah, I didn't hear you come in.
- How could you, with
that damn thing blaring?
- Bill.
Bill.
- That one of your turkeys?
- I can see so many things
Tony could've improved upon,
that would've, might've helped the movie.
- Like not releasing it, you mean.
- Oh, it wasn't that bad.
Host of the series says
they're making some videos
out of my movies.
- Really?
- Jane, Jane, would you
please get a video recorder?
I've asked you so many
times, it would be fun.
I wanna see some old movies.
- Oh, great.
We could have a film festival
of your films, Blanche.
- No need to be sarcastic.
Anyway, you seem to have
forgotten that you had parts
in most of my movies.
- They weren't parts, Blanche,
they were scraps, leftovers.
- Some of them were big.
- And then cut to nothing,
you took care of that.
You, the editor, the director,
you were in it together.
- That's not true.
- Yeah, that is true, Blanche.
Yeah, you shot my scenes,
so I could be cut out of the film later.
Yeah, I know that trick.
You seem to forget I was a star
when your billing was still
"pioneer child killed by stampede."
Just really glad that Daddy never lived
to see what you did to my career.
(man whistles jauntily)
(collar rattles)
(dog barks)
- Tweak!
Come here, boy, come here, come on.
That's my baby boy.
- Frank, Frank.
Come over here, quick, quick, quick!
Do you know who that is?
- I wanted to die, I
couldn't face it alone.
- No.
- That's Blanche Hudson.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Don't be so smug, you love
living nextdoor to a movie star.
- Sweetheart, I wouldn't
know her if I fell over her.
I've hardly ever seen her.
- I saw her, I did, I saw her once.
Frank, Frank, I'm watchin' the TV.
- You know, the only one
I've ever seen is that sister
draggin' herself around like
a ratty old flower child.
- Now, be nice.
- She looks like she got
trampled at Woodstock.
- Shh!
(Frank laughs)
- [Frank] I heard she was a lush.
- Do you know that I got one
of those trashy newspapers
from the supermarket.
They did a whole week
on Where Are They Now?
It said that Jane Hudson
deliberately tried to kill
her sister Blanche in
that so-called accident
and only succeeded in paralyzing her.
- Now, please!
Oh, please, can I have the TV?
- Nope.
Watch upstairs, I got work to do.
(Blanche moans)
- Bye bye.
Jane, did you take your pills?
- You'll miss your big scene.
(moody string music)
Ow.
- Miss Hudson, I'm Connie
Trotter from right next door.
I don't mean to bother you,
but I was just making some
cookies and after seeing
your sister's film on TV,
I couldn't resist sharing
what I do real well
to thank your sister for
what she does real well.
(chuckles) I kinda rehearsed that.
Did you know that there's a retrospective
of your sister's films on?
- Yeah, I know.
- Um, you know, I have a video
cassette of Dark Sunrise,
the movie that your sister
did with William Carol.
I was pretty young when all
your sister's films came out,
but I have become a real fan
through TV and I was wondering
if maybe she was--
- She doesn't give autographs.
If that's what you're after.
- Oh, would you and your
sister like to come over
to our house for dinner some night?
My husband and I would really like that.
- I don't go out much and she
doesn't go out at all anymore.
Thanks for the cookies.
- You have to hold the
bottom of the bag, because,
because it's greasy.
- "Dear Miss Blanche Hudson.
"My mother told me to
watch your old films.
"And I did.
"And I was..."
(laughs)
(dog whines)
- Frank, Frank.
I just went over there,
right, and I brought her...
- Jane!
(phone rings)
Jane?
Jane, would you come up here, please?
- What is it now?
- Come here.
Jane, was that our
nextdoor neighbor I heard?
- [Jane] You didn't
wanna see her, did you?
- I could've said hello.
- When they moved in, you
said they were gawking at you
in the backyard, you
didn't wanna see anybody.
- That was six months ago, I looked awful.
- You don't look any better now. (laughs)
- Could you wash my hair?
Oh, do something different.
Do you remember when we were
kids we used to go to the ocean
we'd get sandy and we'd come
back and we'd get showered
and I'd do your hair
and then you'd do mine.
- Yes.
- Why do you always try to hurt me?
- I didn't say anything.
- It's unfair.
It was just an accident,
I've never blamed you.
- I don't wanna talk about the accident.
- I've never blamed you for anything.
(hairdryer blows)
(both laugh)
- [Jane] Do you remember,
at the beach, we would get
on Daddy's shoulders and
one of us on one shoulder--
- And he would walk out into
the water as far as he could,
and the waves would hit us!
(both laugh)
- And then he'd fall and we'd laugh!
Oh, god, how we laughed.
- Can I look?
Can I look?
- Okay.
(melancholic orchestral music)
What have you done?
- What do you mean?
- [Blanche] It's way too short.
- No, it's not, I think it looks great.
- It's awful, it's way too short!
What have you done?
- You never think I do anything right!
- Jane!
I'm sorry.
I'll even it out somehow, I'm sorry!
- How'd you get in?
- Miss Hudson told me where
you keep the extra key.
Don't worry, I put it back.
- Yeah?
Well, she was gettin'
herself all pretty for ya.
Now you ruined it.
- Yeah, well my schedule
got all screwed up
on account I got a call
back for that series.
- Yeah, well, I've been there.
I wouldn't quit my day job just yet.
- How're you doin' today, Blanche?
What happened to your hair?
- I cut it.
Did you get your series?
- Well, I got a call back.
- Oh, that's wonderful.
- Yeah, well, your sister didn't seem
to think it was any bid deal.
- Oh, Dominick, you'll get
that series, I know you will.
- Thanks.
Alright.
Ready?
Up and over.
Blanche.
Did you talk to Dr.
Shelby about your sister?
- Not yet.
- She's gettin' worse, you know.
Saw an open bottle of vodka downstairs.
You know, the doctor said
she might do somethin' crazy
if she started drinkin' again.
- I thought she was getting better.
- Yeah.
Well, she's not.
I found this on the floor downstairs.
- What ever made her do this?
- Sick mind, that's the
kind of stuff you see
scratched on public toilets.
- She's perverted a lovely fan letter.
- Mm-hm, reads like hate mail.
- But why?
- Like I said, nuts-oh.
Maybe she knows about
you sellin' the house.
(Blanche gasps)
- She couldn't.
- Your health drink!
Right on time.
(dog barks)
I'm gonna put a contract out on that mutt.
- (chuckles) Doesn't bother me.
- Hey, Bruno, you wanna strangle it?
I'll give you $10.
- [Dominick] Dominick, and
I don't mistreat animals.
- [Jane] Oh, I forgot,
you have principles.
I'll give you 20.
(door closes)
- [Dominick] She's not kiddin', you know.
- You won't change your mind?
There are two rooms for
you in the new house.
- You keep your word, I'll keep mine.
Gotta find a place that'll take care
of your sister properly.
- I will, today, I'll call Dr. Shelby.
- What?
My sister said what?
Now you listen to me, our
credit is good all over town.
So when I hang up from you,
I am gonna call another
liquor store and order a
case of vodka or maybe two,
because you are really bugging me,
and I do not like your attitude.
You've got five seconds to decide.
Oh, good, thank you.
Usual order, thank you.
That feely-touchy stuff you do up there,
is it doing her any good?
- Without the therapy, she'd waste away.
- Maybe I'd better ship
her off to Lourdes.
- That'd be a waste of time.
- Oh, yeah, that's right.
A lot of charlatans around
who say they're doing good,
when really they're just
stealing from nice people,
when they are supposed to be helping them.
- Miss Hudson wants to know
when the cleaning people are comin' back.
- A couple weeks, when
are you comin' back?
- I don't know, hard for me to set a time,
what with my call backs.
- Oh, I see, so you're
just gonna pop in whenever
you want to, even if it's
not convenient to me, huh?
Oh, sure, hell, you do what you want!
You just come by whenever you want.
As long as we're still here!
(door closes)
(dark string music)
- Thank you, darling.
Thank you.
- Room service.
(music swells and intensifies)
(Blanche screams)
- Jane!
Jane!
(somber piano music)
♪ Someone is falling asleep tonight ♪
♪ Sandman, I'm talkin' to you ♪
♪ This little girl ♪
♪ Has just turned out her light ♪
♪ Make sure her dreams ♪
♪ Are a colorful sight ♪
(suspenseful string music)
♪ Take all the fears ♪
♪ From her bedside tonight ♪
♪ Tomorrow ♪
♪ Is not far away ♪
♪ Sandman will help you to sleep tonight ♪
♪ But there's one thing
I want you to know ♪
♪ My little girl ♪
♪ I love you so much ♪
♪ I'll always be there ♪
♪ When you need me to touch ♪
♪ My ♪
♪ Little ♪
♪ Will go with you ♪
♪ Protect you and such ♪
♪ See you in the morning's day ♪
- I'm not so dumb, you
know, when I've had a few,
I may not drive straight, have accidents--
- I never said that you did--
- I may not drive straight,
but I can still think straight.
- What're you getting at?
- You thought I didn't know
about you selling the house,
but I did, I know everything you do.
First you get rid of the house
and then you get rid of me.
- Jane, I didn't want to upset you.
This house is so expensive.
Some of my investments haven't worked out.
I just thought that--
- Yeah I bet you just thought.
- I got a letter from my business
manager and he said that--
- No, you didn't, I get the mail first.
- Oh, well, maybe it was a
telephone call, I don't remember.
- Liar.
You're just a liar, you
always were a liar, Blanche.
I'll telephone your
business manager downstairs.
I wouldn't want you to tire
yourself with so much talking.
When I was a little
girl, I was a big star.
A bigger star than you ever were,
and I didn't have to kiss a lot
of wet sloppy mouths either.
My money bought this
house and always remember
that my money got you started.
Miss Big Fat Rotten-Movie Star.
(dog barks)
Hey, what you gonna do
about that damn dog?
- The barking bother you?
- Yeah, it bothers me and
bothers my sister, too.
- Well, we were thinking
about obedience school.
- You better do more than think about it.
- We're looking at several.
- Well, look harder.
Make it a quest.
(dog snarls)
(funky electronic music)
Hm, Blanche Hudson movie, I wouldn't.
Do you have machines here?
- Video machines?
- Yeah!
- No.
- Well, where can I get one?
- Beats me, try the Yellow Pages.
- You try the Yellow Pages,
make a list for the customer.
Go on, go on, go on!
- [Jane] Um, excuse me, I was wondering.
Do you have any Baby
Jane Hudson films here?
- Blanche Hudson, I'm
sorry, I wish we did.
- You remember them?
- Sure I do.
Northern Outpost, there was a
whole series of Outpost films.
Trail Through the Pine, no,
Trail Through the Trees.
Now, what was that song she
sang in Northern Outpost?
I always identified her with that song.
It was sort of a lullaby.
♪ Tomorrow's not far away ♪
- You're Baby Jane Hudson.
- Yeah.
- I'm honored.
I'm Billy Korn, with a K.
- Hello, Billy.
(Billy laughs)
See, I was planning, um,
one day soon I'm gonna
get my career goin' again,
and I thought that if I could
look at some of my old films--
- I thought big movie
stars had screening rooms
right in their homes.
- Oh, I do!
Daddy built me an underground
movie theater, but the prints'
all scratchy and since they
put my sister's films on tape,
I figured that they'd put mine on, too.
Seems they didn't!
- Oh, Miss Hudson, if I can
get Braindead over there
to look after things, can
I buy you a cup of coffee?
- Gotta go home.
- Well, uh, there's some right over there.
I'll pour us two cups
and walk you to your car.
I've been out here for a long time now.
It's just starting to pay off.
I've gave up on agents,
I'm a personal manager now,
for myself and a couple other clients.
I figure I can sell myself
better than anybody else.
Got some good contacts, too.
So, just, uh,
what did you mean about getting
your career going again?
- Well, I haven't really thought about it.
Maybe a one-woman show?
Could do a couple of songs
from the early films,
and there was a song that
I recorded with my sister.
That was real popular.
- There Should Be Love.
(laughs) I've got the
score on an old album.
Music was second nature to me.
Hell, I've done everything,
I've booked acts,
written acts, choreographed, accompanied.
- You've done all that?
- Sure!
You know the business, boom or bust.
I had a bad year, got
overextended, so here I am.
(chuckles) You gotta pay the
rent, but I'll get it together.
- Thanks, Billy.
- You know, maybe we oughta talk.
I know your work, I know what you can do.
I bet I could create something
we'd both be proud of.
- Really?
- Can I call you?
- Yeah.
Yeah, you can call me.
Here.
- (laughs) Why not?
(chuckles)
(dark string music)
(Blanche groans)
- Hello.
It's Blanche, Blanche Hudson,
can I speak to Dr. Shelby?
You've gotta help me,
I've got to speak to him.
Well, interrupt him!
I'm sorry, I don't mean to
be rude, it's an emergency.
Come on, come on.
Dr. Shelby?
Yes, it's about Jane,
she's drinking again.
She's hostile, she's...
Well, I don't know if
she's taking her pills.
Not yet, she isn't violent
yet, but she's unbalanced.
I'm frightened.
Could you come over, please,
could you come over here?
Oh, thank you.
Bye.
(yelps)
- You are trying to get
them to take me away!
- No, I'm not.
No, Jane, I had to make,
my legs, they're so bad.
The circulation's so bad, I
had to get a prescription.
- Yes, a prescription for me, you mean,
'cause you wanna keep me doped up!
- Oh, Jane, you know those pills help you.
- I know what you and
Dr. Shelby have planned!
- No, we weren't planning anything.
- Stop lying, will you
stop lying, Blanche!
Stop lying!
- I'm not!
I'm just trying to remind you,
Jane, that when you do take
those pills, you know, you're
not so neurotic or paranoid,
and you're not imagining that
everyone's trying to lock you
up or put you away, you know?
A chemical imbalance, it's very common.
Oh, god, you are so lucky
there is something you can take
that will help you.
Oh, god, you're so lucky there's something
you can take to help you.
(yelps)
- Yeah, that was very good,
Blanche, that was a very sly
reworking of the shrink
you played in Other Faces.
I'm gonna give you seven
out of a possible 10
for performance and zip for originality.
You always were a
personality actress, Blanche.
Same performance.
Different outfit.
I know that performance backwards.
Oh, hello, this is Blanche
Hudson again, I'm sorry.
Is Dr. Shelby still there?
And you thought I couldn't act.
Oh, hello, Dr. Shelby.
Thank god I caught you in time.
I was feeling a little
hysterical, that's all.
Being alone and all that, but
Jane's here now and I'm fine.
- Dr. Shelby!
- Yes, Jane, I have Dr.
Shelby on the phone.
I was feeling a little
deserted, I'm alright now.
Thank you.
- Help!
(dramatic music)
Help me!
Somebody help me, please!
Oh, help me, help me, help me, help!
Help, help, help!
(screams)
- When we were kids
and I was still a star,
you had to depend on me.
The house, food, clothes on your back.
It all came from me and
you hated me for that.
You never thanked me for anything.
I paid for your acting classes,
for Mother and Daddy's funeral.
I paid for everything.
And now you have to depend
on me for everything again.
One thing I'm happy about, though.
Daddy died while I was still a star.
And you were still my stand-in.
See how funny life is, Blanche?
We're right back where we started.
(peaceful electronic music)
(knocks)
- [Billy] Oh.
Hi. (chuckles)
- Billy.
You got any cigarettes?
- Well, sure.
Sure.
Here you go.
- Thanks.
We're still waiting for our money.
- Well, I haven't gotten paid yet.
- Well, somebody got paid.
Me and Tom are on your
local news stands nude.
- You got paid for the session.
- We want 250 more for each
publication, we count four here.
- I'm onto something, it'll be ready cash.
- You got a week, Billy,
then things get ugly.
(chuckles) We're underage.
(Billy chuckles)
You can meet the new kid
tonight, he's got some film,
but you gotta be a better
broker than you've been.
- Okay, okay.
Yeah.
(phone rings)
- Hello?
- Miss Hudson, it's Billy Korn.
- Oh, hello, Mr. Korn.
- Please, call me Billy, Miss Hudson.
- Oh, (chuckles) sorry, Billy.
If I call you Billy, you'll
have to call me Jane.
- Alright. (chuckles)
Jane. (chuckles)
I thought we should get
together as soon as possible.
You know the business, time is money.
- Yeah, well, how about right now?
No, tell you what, give
me an hour, make it two?
- Alright.
- Yeah, you have my
address, 168 North Plymouth.
Uh-huh, bye.
- Jane.
(dark string music)
- It's good.
- Is the scarf new?
- No.
But the belt is new.
- Mrs. Trotter!
(upbeat electronic music)
Mrs. Trotter!
- Billy!
Billy, we want you to meet someone.
- I can't, I've got an appointment.
- But this is the boy I
was telling you about!
- Good morning.
- [Billy] Hm.
(doorbell rings)
- Hi.
Remember this outfit?
Northern Outpost?
All the Outpost films, I wore this outfit.
Had it made years ago.
Put it on for you.
- That was nice. (chuckles)
I just love these fine old homes.
This is what Hollywood used to be.
- It was a wonderful time.
- I could've been Ray
Moland or Robert Taylor
taking my constitutional up your street.
I really felt like I was back in the 40s.
- You didn't drive?
- No, my car's with my mechanic.
- Well, come into the living room.
- Oh.
Oh, this is wonderful.
(Jane giggles)
Now, this was your parents' house?
- Oh, yeah, yeah, but I
paid for it, you know,
with all the money that I
earned, we all lived here,
but of course, it wasn't
smart enough for my sister
when she became Miss High
and Mighty, so she moved out.
- Oh, she doesn't--
- Oh, yeah, yeah!
But when I had my episode,
she moved back in to take care
of me but now I'm taking care
of her, isn't that somethin'?
(chuckles) Here, look here, it's Daddy.
- Oh.
- Isn't that great?
Oh, I have all kinds, I've
got cream cake and caramel.
I just love petit four, I
usually buy half a dozen,
but I just limit myself to one a day.
Got these today.
(buzzing)
Here.
- Oh.
I'll try the, uh, the caramel. (laughs)
- Oh, this is Daddy's favorite chair.
I bought it for him.
(buzzing)
Here, why don't you go
ahead and help yourself.
I'll be right back, then you just join me
in the rehearsal room over there?
I'll be there.
- Who's downstairs?
- It's none of your business.
Is it so hard to believe
somebody would come to visit me?
- What are you trying to do to me?
- You mean what are you doing to me?
Listen to this damn buzzer for
20 years and I am sick of it.
Oh, you didn't want your dinner?
I made it just the way you like it.
Mm!
Onions and seasoning, this is good.
I'll save it for Tweak when he gets back
from obedience school.
- What?
- Yeah, ran into our nextdoor
neighbor this afternoon,
and he says they found a
dog school that takes rats.
- I'm hungry!
- Well, of course you're hungry,
you don't eat what I put out for you!
- You're trying to kill me.
- (chuckles) No.
- Yes, you are, you're
trying to starve me to death!
You're frightened to eat!
- I'm not trying to starve you to death.
That would be a silly thing to do.
- Oh, yes, yes, it would,
because if something happened
to me, something bad, there
wouldn't be any money.
- Yeah, there'd be money.
- Oh, but not for you!
Because they'd have to
put you away somewhere,
and I wouldn't be there
to sign the checks!
What do you think of that?
- Yep.
- Good.
Then you bring me some dinner.
- I'm gonna have my career
again, what do you think of that?
♪ My love will go with you ♪
♪ Protect you and such ♪
♪ I'll see you in the morning's day ♪
♪ Tomorrow is not far away ♪
- You remembered.
- And not a dry eye in
the house, I'll bet.
- They'll expect me to sing that.
- It's a little dated. (chuckles)
- Oh, what about a new arrangement?
- Well, it's a lullaby, you
can't really update that.
You know, we oughta get the
business part out of the way
before we go on.
- What business part?
- You know, the ugly
money part. (chuckles)
- (giggles) What'll it cost?
- Well, I wanna try it out.
Test it at a club, a cabaret,
a showcase kind of thing.
That's when the agents come.
- Really?
- Do a couple of songs,
'cause that's all the time
they'll give us, you
know, see what happens.
- Is that expensive?
- It could run...
$1,000.
But that's for the spot,
you know, advertising,
paying the lighting man,
the costumes, arrangements,
choreography, everything.
If you want a little time, think it over?
- When could we do it?
- When they got room.
The owner's a friend of mine,
you want me to make a call?
- Oh.
- You know, this is the kind
of break that could put us
both right over the top.
- Really?
- Really.
- Yeah, go ahead, you make
that call, phone's in the hall!
There.
- Okay.
- Mrs. Trotter, this is your
neighbor, Blanche Hudson.
I need your help, I'm
unable to use the phone.
Could you please call Dr. Shelby for me?
His number is 555-6314.
And ask him to come over at once.
(gasps) Please, don't tell
my sister about this message.
For me, his number is 555-6314.
And ask him to come over at once.
- [Billy] Okay, I'll find
out and I'll call you
later tonight, (laughs) alright.
- Look at this, Sword of Excellence award.
I won it when I was a little
girl for the Outpost films.
- Real nice.
Listen, Jane, I've got
good news and bad news.
They want both you and your sister.
- No, my sister's in a
wheelchair, it's my act, not hers.
- I'll talk to him.
I told you, Luther the
owner's a friend of mine.
- Well, when do we do it?
- Wednesday.
- What? So soon?
- I know almost all the songs
already and the choreography.
Everything.
You could do Orphan of Love
and, uh, There Should Be Love.
- The music's on the piano,
There Should Be Love.
- Alright! (laughs)
Okay.
Medium bounce.
(upbeat piano music)
(laughs) Okay.
- Again.
(upbeat piano music)
♪ There should be love ♪
♪ Love should be there ♪
♪ Not being scared ♪
♪ Should be love ♪
♪ There should be you ♪
♪ You should be there ♪
I did sing beautifully
when I was very young.
- I know.
(chuckles) I know.
It's okay.
Jane, you could lip-sync to the record.
- Who'd sing Blanche's part?
- Oh.
- We were on the record together!
- Alright, oh!
Alright, we'll black out
one side of the stage.
You'll be in a spotlight
and Blanche's voice just
comes out of the darkness.
- Will that work?
- Jane, you're a star.
Your sister's a star,
they're after an event.
Now, let's give 'em one.
You leave it to Billy.
- You're so nice.
(Billy chuckles)
- Um... (chuckles)
Well, I hate to bring this up
but I'm gonna need some money.
- When?
- [Billy] Tomorrow?
- Tomorrow?
Um...
Tomorrow I give you half?
- That'll be fine.
Oh, I should be going.
- I'll drive you, where do you live?
- Oh, you just drop me in Hollywood.
- Yeah?
Where do you want me to stop?
Just here?
Here?
- Okay, so I'll come
by tomorrow around 10,
and we could go to the bank together.
- What do they want?
- No they don't want anything.
Go away, go on.
- They scare me.
- Jane, you go on home,
alright, there's no reason
why you should ever have
to see any of this, okay?
Go on, hey, get away from there.
Go on, Jane.
Jane, just drive off, just go home, go on.
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
- You alright, lady?
- I wanna go home!
- Where's home?
- Plymouth Street!
- That's easy.
That's highland over there.
Take a right, you go straight down.
- Right, thanks.
- Hey, lady!
Do you want me to go with you?
(Jane sighs)
(door unlocks)
- I've gotta go out, important business.
Get you breakfast later.
Sorry, I'm in a rush.
(melancholic string music)
My sister wants it all in
cash today, she endorsed it.
- Well, usually she deposits
her monthly allowance.
If she doesn't, she normally calls us.
- She endorsed it, there
isn't a problem, is there?
- No.
Wait just a moment.
Fine, how would you like that?
- Big bills.
- Okay.
Thank you.
(dark string music)
(music swells and intensifies)
(Blanche screams)
- [Billy] You can just
drop me right over here.
Yeah, just right around
here, just right here.
Yeah, this is good, alright.
Okay.
- I'll see ya.
- I'll be over in just a little while,
and we'll have a rehearsal, alright?
Now, you know, Jane, they
still want your sister
to be part of the act.
- What do you mean, Billy?
We talked about it, you said--
- Relax, no, relax, relax.
I told them, I told them.
- You told me before that--
- I told them Blanche was disabled.
- You said before that they wanted her,
and I don't want her in it.
- Jane, it's all fixed.
- She's in a wheelchair, Billy.
Billy, she's in a wheelchair
and I don't want her in there.
- Jane, I fixed it,
everything's okay, it's okay.
- It better be.
- Yes.
Jane, Jane!
(horn honks)
Jane?
Jane!
She's crazy.
Crazy.
- Everything grows so
fast here in California.
Especially all the weeds.
- I wonder where I dropped this.
- The winds that you have
here in California are really
something, what are they
called, they're something,
they happen in October,
it's Spanish, it's...
- [Jane] Blanche?
(dark atmospheric music)
- Hello!
Jane?
Jane, Dominick.
- (yelps) What are you doing here?
- [Dominick] Told me I
could come whenever I want,
'cause of my crazy schedule.
- I don't remember.
- Well, you did.
- She doesn't wanna see you.
- What are you talking about?
- Well...
She's got another therapist.
- Well, nobody called me.
- Oh, I know, I'm sorry, I should have.
- [Dominick] What's the matter?
- Well, nothing's the
matter, you gotta go now.
- [Dominick] You haven't been
takin' your pills, have you?
- None of your business!
- Why are you so anxious to get rid of me?
- I got things to do, I gotta rehearse!
- So, rehearse.
- I told you, she does not wanna see you.
- [Dominick] Yeah I think I'll
let her tell me that herself.
- This is my house!
- It's half your house.
I'm gonna go talk to the
other half, you calm down.
Jane.
Jane, come on, move.
- Hey, don't--
- Move.
(knocks)
Blanche, Blanche?
Why'd you lock this door?
- I don't have to tell you anything.
- Where's the key?
- I don't have the key.
- Jane, give me that key.
- I don't have it.
Hey, that's my purse, that's
my personal things in there!
There's nothin' in there, I...
(suspenseful music)
(Blanche mumbles)
- Blanche.
I'm so sorry.
(Blanche mumbles)
I'm gonna get you up.
You stay right there, you understand me?
I warned you, Blanche.
I warned you something
like this might happen.
It's okay, you're safe now.
I'm gonna take care of
you just like I promised.
(Blanche screams)
(dramatic music)
(screams)
(groans)
(Blanche grunts)
(Billy whistles jauntily)
(doorbell rings)
(suspenseful music)
- Hello?
(Jane yelps)
- What are you doing here?
- I was looking for you.
We had a rehearsal, you know,
the side door's not locked.
And you weren't around,
I thought something might
have happened to you.
What's the matter?
- What about posters?
You said there'd be posters.
- There's not enough time.
Posters are for the real
gig, Wednesday night is about
reacquainting you with the public again.
It's for agents and casting people.
- What about my dressing room?
- [Billy] The dressing
rooms are already taken.
This is just a showcase.
- You mean there's somebody
else on the same bill?
I didn't know there'd be
anybody on the same bill.
- It's better having more
than one on the same bill.
There's less pressure this way.
Jane, I know you're scared.
It's been a long time, but
you're gonna be wonderful.
Jane, now do you believe me, hm?
You know, we don't have a
lot of time, so do you think
you can pull yourself
together enough to rehearse?
Jane?
(chain rattles)
"Hudson sisters had a song
together in the film and that
"was There Should Be Love,"
then the spot on the curtain,
then the music and now.
(upbeat pop music)
Jane, Jane.
On the music, the intro is
when you come down the stairs.
Right, come down now, yeah.
♪ There should be love ♪
- Change hands.
♪ Love should be there ♪
- [Billy] Change, both
hands, right, right, okay.
♪ Not feeling scared ♪
- Billy!
- Okay, keep going, keep going.
- She's not wearing that outfit.
- No.
No, she's wearing the actual
dress she wore in the film.
- [Luther] I've been
hearing some things about
your Jane Hudson, did
you get your money yet?
- Had. (chuckles)
My back rent ate that up.
- How many times have you done this?
When are you gonna learn?
- Why?
What're you talking about?
- She's crazy.
Tried to run down her sister
after one of those Hollywood
parties, then she drove off,
didn't see her for three days.
I bet she doesn't even remember doing it.
- That's old news, cheap gossip.
That story's been around
longer than you have.
- Did you know that they
found her shacked up
with an actor she was makin' a movie with?
- So, what's so special about that?
- [Luther] She was drunk
and crazy, a raving lunatic.
They had to lock up the
silly broad in an asylum.
Her sister had her released.
Imagine that, after all she'd done to her.
- Must be love, like the song says.
♪ There would be love,
there would be love ♪
♪ There should be love,
- That's not true, Jane.
Luther loved you and he loved your act.
You still owe me $500, you know, Jane?
So, you will bring it tonight, won't you?
Good.
Alright, now, we're on
between 9:30 and 10,
so be there by nine, alright?
Okay.
Bye, Jane.
- Oh, Billy?
See you tonight?
- Yeah.
- Oh, have our money, or
we'll a couple of phone calls.
- We wouldn't want you
be in jail on crutches.
- Okay.
Okay.
You'll get your money.
- Blanche, what do you think?
Blanche?
Blanche.
What do you think?
(Blanche mumbles)
- Want some water, please,
give me some water.
- Oh, you always make trouble.
(water splashes)
Here.
It's gonna be my second debut.
(giggles)
Wish me luck!
(hums melodically)
- Hey!
That's not the entrance, lady!
That's for the talent!
- I know that.
(muffled jazz music)
Billy?
Oh, excuse me, I'm looking for Billy Korn.
- Shh.
- I'm looking for my manager.
- Shh, shh, shh.
- Oh, have you seen my manager?
(knocks)
- Occupied.
- Billy?
- Oh, Jane, thank god.
You're late, you're on next.
- What?
- Got your props?
- No!
- [Billy] Go get it, wait
in the wings for your cue!
- Okay.
- One minute to go.
- Here's your dummy mic.
- I got it.
- Uh, you hold this, right?
- Oh.
- Are you okay?
- Of course I'm okay.
(audience applauds)
- [Host] Along the Way was
made during the sixties.
It starred Blanche and Jane Hudson,
stars of different eras
and sisters in real life.
They had a song together in the film,
and that song was There Should Be Love.
(upbeat pop music)
♪ There should be love ♪
♪ Love should be there ♪
♪ Not being scared ♪
♪ Love ♪
♪ There should be you ♪
♪ You should be there ♪
♪ With me to care ♪
♪ Through your fears ♪
♪ Where have you gone ♪
♪ What have I done ♪
♪ To make you run away from me ♪
♪ One night with you ♪
♪ Can make me see ♪
♪ The one I want, the one I need ♪
♪ There would be love ♪
- Jane, Jane.
- Keep going, Jane.
- Love.
There should be love.
♪ There should be love ♪
♪ Someone's falling asleep tonight ♪
- Jane, Jane.
♪ Sandman, I'm talking to you ♪
♪ This little girl has
just turned off her light ♪
♪ Make sure her dreams
are a colorful sight ♪
♪ Chase all the fears
from her bedside tonight ♪
- Get down from there, you're ridiculous.
Get out of here, scram, honey!
(dark atmospheric music)
- Papa.
(melancholic orchestral music)
When I see this, I feel like I'm there.
Like no time has passed.
I remember the woodsy
sawdust smell of the set.
And also lamps that had been on too long.
And they smelled to me like wax melting.
And I can feel the hugs and I
can hear the congratulations
everywhere I went 'cause
I was so important then.
All of my pictures made money.
That's why they gave me this award.
Sword of Excellence,
Best Child Actress, 1949.
(suspenseful music)
- Jane!
Jane?
Blanche Hudson.
What has she done to you?
(music swells)
(gasps)
(clatter)
(ominous tones)
- [Jane] Blanche?
- I came back for the
money you owe me, Jane.
- What money?
- It's not a lot of money, Jane.
Not to you, it isn't.
But it is to me.
- Always about money, Blanche.
- I need it badly, Jane.
If you don't have it, maybe
we could work something out.
I wanna be your friend, Jane.
I consider myself a very
good friend, am I right?
(flesh squelches)
(gasps)
(groans)
(music swells)
- Billy.
(birds tweet)
Blanche?
Blanche, we can go away now.
Just like you wanted.
Everyone's gone.
They've all gone.
Do you hear me, Blanche?
Do you hear what I said?
We can go to the beach.
You like the beach, remember?
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Say yes.
- Yeah.
- Gotta go now.
Gotta leave now.
The dark here.
It's always cold and dark.
Wanna see the sun.
Don't wanna be cold anymore.
- Yeah.
- [Jane] Look what I got for you.
There.
- Jane.
I'm thirsty, please.
- [Jane] Find someplace to get it.
- Stop someone, please.
I need a doctor.
- [Jane] No, 'cause then
they'll make me go away,
and I wanna stay with you.
- I'm dying.
- And I'll be alone.
(bell rings)
- Listen.
That night I was driving
in the car and you weren't.
You were full of drink,
full of dope and I hated you
because you had so much
love when we were young
and you tried to keep
me from having anything.
- [Jane] Do you remember we
used to find bottles that were
all worn, smooth from the ocean?
They were like samphires and emeralds,
and that kind of stuff?
I liked that, those were the best times.
- I lied to you, I cheated you.
I wanted you dead, I
wanted to run you down.
- [Jane] No I was driving that
car, Blanche, and I hurt you.
- No, I was behind the wheel,
and you were too drunk.
- No, that's not the way it was, Blanche.
- I was...
Thrown out of the car
and you were too drunk
and you were frightened and you ran away,
and when they found me, I let them believe
you did it and they found
and you were frightened
and confused and I was lying by the car,
and they assumed you did it.
- No.
- What you thought...
You did...
I did.
To myself.
Because I wanted to hurt you.
- You mean, all these years,
we could've been friends?
(melancholic string music)
(Blanche sobs)
(Jane sobs)
- Here you are, okay.
- Thanks!
(Blanche groans)
There, I got us strawberry.
You like strawberry.
Here.
- Jane.
I'm sorry.
I'm so very sorry.
- Nose will get red in the sun.
(chuckles)
Maybe we could live at the beach.
(dark orchestral music)
- Miss?
Miss?
Is that your white Cadillac over there?
- Yeah.
- Are you Miss Hudson?
- (chuckles) Yeah.
I'm Baby Jane Hudson and this
is my sister, Blanche Hudson.
She's a movie star, too.
- See if she can talk.
- Miss, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
Miss.
- Call for an ambulance.
- Right.
This is 14-23 requesting
an ambulance, Venice Beach.
100 feet north of the pier.
It's a code three, we have a woman down.
Pulse is low, breathing shallow.
- [Dispatch] Yeah, we copy
14-23, what have you got?
- [Officer] That's code three,
just north of Venice Pier.
- [Dispatch] We copy, 14-23.
- You're gonna be alright, miss.
Miss Hudson!
Jane Hudson!
- Papa!
Let's live at the beach.
Can we?
(dark orchestral music)