Arkham Asylum July  3rd then made known
only as  the Joker has escaped proving
once again  that the system is broken
I've had to put my ongoing investigation
of a serial killer Victor Zsasz on hold
the Joker is always top priority
his footprints into the West End sewer
caverns this is why I'm here
his path of destruction has already
begun putting Arkham nurse
twenty-three-year-old or Rebecca white
in the hospital she had only been
working at the asylum for two weeks
the news coverage of this has spread
like  a raging fire today  the people of
Gotham  are waking up to the Joker's
words the zebra has escaped  from the zoo
to feast on the  blood of the life
ever since my parents deaths  I rarely
appeared the city in daylight
but this alley  I know too well I come
here when I can no  longer silence the
demons in  my head
as with all children
I look to my parents for help for an
answer
I'm not that insane
the Gotham skyline  towers home to
councilman  Johnson his wife and
ten-year-old son earlier this evening
the councilman and his son were
kidnapped while his wife was  brutally
murdered  by the Joker
hearing this news tears have the only
humanity that I have left another child
stripped of its innocence by Gotham's
underworld  - kidnapped one dead
can you confirm that  joker was here well
the preliminary evidence matches his
profile
are there any recognizable prints none
this was very clean and precise there
has to be something in here we  can use
all the evidence left here was
intentional as always
the city was the  Joker bad there's a
crowd  already gathering outside of the
hospital  for that poor Arkham nurse  I
hate to say it  could I blame Batman why
look I know our city is dirty we know
the only way to come clean is to put our
faith in a force that's greater than  the
law  a force that can take liberties
where the law can't and we've given that
force the power to stop this madness and
it hasn't Gotham sick of Batman's
conscience so am I
to skill
shift  gears
your Harley it seems that that the lack
of conscience is what has created  these
freaks of Gotham
this city will  never know how lucky they
are that I've never crossed that line
because  if I did step into that abyss  I
take all of Gotham with me
he's here open his cell
partly where is he I'm not supposed to
talk to you
two people are already dead their child
is missing  I thought he'd be with you by
now you're always at the  top of  this
dance card he doesn't care about you
Harvey he's just using you that's why he
needed your help to  escape from Arkham
me he'll come back
he can't help himself he's going through
something terrible  you know this you
know him better than anyone  I don't know
anything about  a missing kid but I do
know something about a little man owing
him a favor and that he plans to  cash a
parlays reference to the little man
was obvious he runs one of the dirtiest
clubs in Gotham
we go
that's your friend
my money
yeah
oops
I could have taken the silent approach
slipped in unnoticed but I'm looking to
be noticed  I need to make it clear that
criminals will no longer be tolerated  in
Gotham
that's night it ends
I don't have time for your games Wesker
you got something to say say it to me
dummy where is he no idea
you come in here  off the track into  my
honest business and think you can put
the screws in me Wesker why was the
Joker here what did you want you  read
one word I'll put you  in a wooden box No
Wesker  a child's life's in danger
don't say a word she'll kill me act like
a man you dummy
no go to hell more time why was the
Joker here I don't know something about
Carnival did you like Carnival
god
councilman Johnson
hey we got  time for shriek real boy bomb
pops
are you sure you don't want any no well
then how  about a story once upon a time
there was  this fear slide who ruled over
the land unfairly  he would bully and
scare all of the  zebras sometimes in  the
devour them  one day one delivers the
challenges  alive
the councilman's body was  bound two
miles from here the missing child is now
lost both of his parents deaths for
safety  first
it's gonna be a great show
your best
oh boy tell me
yeah
where do you think you're going
I placed a tracking device in the Joker
before I let him go  I knew he would lead
me straight to the child
oh it's you
I see about my toy cow it's all fun and
games here see  give a little chain
why didn't you save my parents
the Joker was anything but anticlimactic
which is  exactly what this death is
with all of his mischievious almost
whimsical schemes the Joker was nothing
to roll your eyes at every performance
as he called him  at a point
even if a horrific death toll landed him
back in Markham it was always part of
his plan but this doesn't seem to  follow
any plan
is it possible that this child was  able
to do what should have been  done years
ago
is it really that  black-and-white is
this a victory is this a sign that the
store is passing or getting worse
I failed I failed my parents and most of
all I failed him
the batmanning says to make sure  that
what  happened to Bruce Wayne never
happens to anyone else
how many more broken families  exist
because of  the Joker's reign of terror
a terror that I couldn't seem to  end
even in death  the Joker is still getting
the last laugh
even without the Joker Gotham has a
share of scars
but for those that have amassed  too many
scholars
it has pushed them  over the edge
have I been wrong all these  years
as I just too afraid  to pull the trigger
I can't believe that to be true
but as my city and I grow older  I began
to doubt  the choices that I've made I
often ask myself if I were faced with
the same  situation
but I've taken the life of my parents
killer
that is the question  that has haunted me
my entire life
the only answer  that I have is the life
that I now live the answer to that
question is  that
where there once was the sound of
laughter  ours
a cold  where they won't sing a thousand
voices lies a graveyard
we
pray to heat
where there one screw a beautiful garden
now sow the seeds of  kill where there
once stood  a proud soldier lies though
the country his forefathers fail
take a good look  watch
down to the city of scars
you