[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[ALARM CLOCK RINGING]
SINGER: ♪ If I could take you
up in paradise up above♪
♪ If you would tell me
I'm the only one♪
♪ That you love♪
♪ Life could be a dream
sweetheart♪
♪ Hello, hello again♪
♪ Sh-boom I'm hoping
we meet again♪
CHARLIE:
♪ Oh, life could be a dream♪
SINGER: ♪ If only
all my precious plans♪
♪ Would come true♪
♪ If you would let me spend...♪
CHARLIE:
♪ My whole life loving you♪
♪ Life could be a dream,
sweet...♪
-SINGER: ♪ Now...♪
-CHARLIE: ♪ Every time I look♪
♪ At you♪
♪ Something is on my mind♪
♪ If you do
what I want you to♪
♪ Baby, we'd be so fine♪
SINGER: ♪ Oh,
life could be a dream...♪
CHARLIE: Hey, Willy,
I'm taking another alarm clock.
Put it on my tab.
Another one? What'd you do?
-Send them to your friends?
-[CHUCKLES]
MITCH:
He doesn't have any friends.
Where the hell
is the craftsmanship these days?
You know, these are not
very durable clocks, Willy.
Give me a beer.
Starting early, Charlie.
Put a shot in it.
How's the surf, Polo?
Like a bathtub.
WILLY: There hasn't been
any surf on this beach
since typhoon of '52.
Oh, yeah. '52, man.
Gentlemen, here's to the typhoon
of '52.
Don't sit here.
You fascinate me, Mitch.
Move, cop.
He's not a cop anymore.
He smells like a cop.
You know, when you get mad,
your neck gets real big
and your nostrils swell?
You're lucky I got to go
to work.
Really lucky.
[GROWLS]
[CHUCKLES]
He's gonna hit you one day.
He and his bad breath.
Give me another shot.
WILLY: [LAUGHS] It's too early.
Leave him alone, Willy.
He's drinking to forget,
right, Charlie?
Yeah. Is it a woman?
Nine of them.
Nine women.
I don't wanna listen
to this again.
How can one guy love nine women?
I didn't love them,
except for one.
I loved one.
But I got all their faces
right here.
Pretty faces, huh?
Yeah. Pretty faces.
I'll never forget them.
So you said?
How many times have I told you
guys this story?
Once a month for four months.
CHARLIE: Well...
WILLY: So tell us
something different, Charlie.
Tell us about the snow
in New York.
Tell us about ice skating
at the Rockefeller Center.
That I forgot, Willy.
I forgot.
[WAVES SPLASHING]
[LAUGHS]
CHARLIE: Oh, I got one.
I got one.
Come here, fish. Come on, fish.
Come into--whoa, whoa, whoa.
Look out. World's biggest wave.
No. No. Oh, my--
[LAUGHS]
Oh, my God, man. It's a fish.
Come on, fish.
Woo.
[LAUGHS]
Yeah. All right.
Oh.
-PATTY: Nice catch.
-Oh.
Hi.
-I've seen you.
-PATTY: Uh, last night
at the bar.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Cathy.
-Patty.
-Oh. Right. Patty.
Patty. Patty.
At the bar.
-Did we have a good time?
-[CHUCKLES] Well,
you asked me to come by
and visit you
-at your beach house some time.
-And you did.
Great. Great.
Great. Oh.
Why?
Oh,
I thought
you might have some money.
No.
No money.
-Whisky.
-PATTY: [CHUCKLES]
Mmm.
-Sorry.
-PATTY: [CHUCKLES]
You a working girl, Patty?
No. No.
Just broke
at this particular time.
-Oh.
-It wasn't just the money.
I came because I liked you too.
You sang.
[CHUCKLES] Yeah. Yeah.
I always sing.
Hey, come on inside.
I wanna show you something.
Come on. Come on. [CHUCKLES]
Sure.
CHARLIE: That's Bobby,
and Dean,
and Danny Greco.
Professional, huh?
No. Just four New York cops.
But we sung at functions,
you know.
Four-part harmony.
-Barbershop quartet?
-No,
no, no.
Popular doo-wopp stuff.
You know The Platters?
Never mind.
Hey, why don't we cook up
that fish you caught?
Hey, good idea. Good idea.
Make a nice lunch.
How about dinner?
Wanna stay for dinner?
Sure.
Um, breakfast?
Uh, let's wait and see
how dinner goes, Charlie.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
CHARLIE: What?
Charles Raski?
Right. So what?
I'm Jim Ishita.
This is Richard Aga.
Oahu police. Can we come in?
Why?
It's about a homicide,
Mr. Raski. Very important.
What the hell does it have
to do with me?
Are you the Charles Raski
who was a homicide detective
-from New York?
-Of course, I am.
How many Raskis you got
on this island?
You know, I doubt
there's a large Polish-American
population here.
You know what I mean?
We tend to burn, not to tan.
Now, I'm out of patience here.
In New York,
you worked on a particular case
we're interested in.
Look, I'll tell you what.
Why don't you two guys
go over to that bar over there,
and I'll meet you over there
in about an hour?
'Cause you see right now,
I'm playing Trivial Pursuit,
-and I'm sort of winning, and--
-Mr. Raski,
perhaps you wanna take a look
at this.
What the hell is this?
You tell us.
CHARLIE: When?
RICHARD: Two nights ago.
Her name's Ansella Suarez.
-Do you know her?
-No.
Charlie, are we busted
for something?
-What's your name?
-None of your business.
Doesn't the photo remind you
of the mask murder case
-in New York?
-Of course, it does.
-Murder weapon?
-Nylon stocking.
What's the name
of the serial killer
-in New York?
-Albert Revin.
Maybe you guys
got the wrong man.
CHARLIE: No way. Not a chance.
We tied him to every murder.
Every one.
It was Revin.
No questions asked.
We had fingerprints,
the whole works.
ISHITA: And you're sure
he's dead?
Dead and buried.
You kill him?
I was there.
So I guess what we've got here
is a copy cat
of some kind.
But why, here in Hawaii,
just 10 miles
from where you live,
the only cop tied
to the Revin case?
I don't know.
Will you come downtown
and talk to us?
Can't help you.
You've got Albert Revin.
Maybe with your help,
we can find--
I can't.
Keep it, for your files.
I don't have files anymore.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
PATTY: What's in there, Charlie?
You stay for a while.
Will you stay?
-Sure.
-Thanks.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
CHARLIE: No,
no, no.
No,
No.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
REVIN: Charlie.
Charlie Raski.
It's me, Charlie.
-Remember?
-MAN: Come back, Charlie.
Kill him. Get him.
-MAN: Shoot him, Charlie.
-MAN: Do it. Do it now.
REVIN: Remember, Charlie?
[PANTING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
-WILLY: Aloha.
-Hi. Uh, coffee please.
Hey, can I buy you a shot
with that?
Maybe lubricate your engine.
Hey, Willy.
Now, just keep it in your pants.
Ooh.
"Coffee,
which makes
the politician wise."
Alexander Pope.
[CHUCKLES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Charles Raski?
I've got my drink.
Hawaiian coffee is the best
in the world.
Oh, not the way Willy makes it.
Goodbye, officer.
It's Mahona. Dr. Mahona.
I'm a psychologist
from private practice.
I'm not in the market.
And I also do some work
for the police department.
Bingo.
A patient of mine
was killed a few days ago,
Ansella Suarez?
You have her photograph.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, every now
and then you connect
with a patient.
You really affect one.
And this girl
was making excellent progress
and really changing
and reaching out to me,
and now she's dead.
Yeah, well, a lot of people
are dead.
Not that way.
Nobody should die that way.
Revenge? You want revenge, Doc?
What do you want?
I don't know.
My memory's fading.
You're trying too hard.
You're trying to be
some tropical beach bum
from some bad movie
you saw somewhere.
A lot of you Haloes
from the mainland, they come
over here, you try to play
that role,
and it's embarrassing, Charlie.
Can I call you Charlie?
You can call me long distance.
DIANE:
That's two within ten days.
Police department
has formed a special task force.
We just want you to come in
and talk to us. That's all.
Just talk to us.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[CHATTER]
This is the boss,
Capt. John Kilalo.
-Sgt. Charles Raski, NYPD.
-On leave.
-Permanent.
-KILALO: Yeah. I heard about it.
Thanks for coming in.
Everybody--Raski,
that's Jimmy Ishita,
Det. Aga and Craft.
We're just getting started here.
We appreciate any bit of help
you can give us.
We read the reports
on your case, but you lived it.
[CHATTER]
Ansella Suarez, twenty-four,
worked as a maid in one
of the expensive homes
-in Diamond Head.
-And it turns out
she was making it
with her employer,
a nightly in the pool house.
Uh, it's a real soap opera.
It wasn't as trashy
as he likes to make it sound.
True love.
Caused a scandal
for a few minutes
but it didn't lead anywhere.
We checked the boss' story.
It's tight.
And he had no connection
with victim number two.
Yeah, nobody does.
Just a guy
of a Japanese fishing boat,
out for a good time
on Hotel Street.
Nobody in the island knows him.
-Same MO?
-Yup.
Nylon stocking
with a rope inside.
A rope?
Uh-uh.
Revin was different.
Like most serial killers,
he had a target type.
Female, usually tall.
All his victims were dresses
or skirts.
Your killer doesn't seem
to have a target profile.
Also Revin never used a rope,
just a nylon stocking,
same one every time.
He would sexually
abuse his victims after.
And his masks were more crude,
less elaborate than your man.
What was Revin's connection
to you?
He liked teasing us,
playing cat-and-mouse
-with the police.
-CRAFT: Yeah?
Why pick you?
I gave some interviews
to the press
for the task force.
He attached himself to me.
Started calling me up
on the phone and...
Saying?
Just my name at first,
and then he found out
something personal, something...
-You don't have to, Charlie.
-I think we should know.
The report didn't go into it.
Raski, this killer might copy
that part of Revin's pattern.
He might attach himself
to one of us.
We should be prepared.
-Now, Capt. Kilalo, I don't--
-It's all right.
It's all right.
Revin knew that my wife and I
couldn't have children.
We were trying to adopt a child.
He, um, used to talk about that.
He knew the names
of the two men I killed
in the line of duty.
Not secrets but personal things.
He would describe my house.
Even the inside.
He was crawling inside me,
working me like an expert.
And every few weeks
I was looking at the face
of another one of his victims.
He was dragging me right down
into the horror.
He connected it all to me.
With messages for me.
Then he called up
and he described my wife,
Claire. He said
he was gonna kill her.
That's when I should have quit,
left the case,
grabbed my wife, left town
for a while.
But I didn't.
We put guards on the house,
on Claire,
day and night.
But he got by my people
and he--
she was victim number seven.
I see you didn't put her
photo up. Thanks.
He killed two more people
after Claire before we got him.
By that time,
I was so emptied out,
I almost let him kill me.
How did you get him?
You scouted the murder scenes
for witnesses?
Yeah. It turned up nothing.
You have to go back and do it
again and again,
and never stop. Never!
Somebody saw something.
In New York, we finally
connected a van, a dark van,
to two of the murders.
It took us months
and months and even more months,
checking every dark van
in the city, every one,
looking for a strong
left-handed male
with brown hair,
'cause that's all we had.
But we got him.
We got him.
'Cause somebody
always sees something.
Why don't you work with us,
Charlie?
CRAFT: Uh, Captain,
-uh, I don't think--
-DIANE: Well, maybe
-Mr. Raski could excuse us for--
-CHARLIE: For what? Go ahead.
What are you gonna say?
Captain, we picked up
Raski twice
in the four months he's been
on the island.
He's involved in a fray,
I know, in the Pair A' Dice bar,
charges dropped.
Criminal property damage,
that was the same place,
and that was overnight
in the tank.
Uh, there's a $200 fine.
And, um, Captain.
I never had a problem
on the job.
I stood up for 12 years
without a problem.
DIANE: The Revin case
was too traumatic for Mr. Raski.
-He could be at risk.
-At risk?
-Emotionally.
-[SCOFFS]
Now, this is the Honolulu
Gazette, April 4th.
"He crawled inside of me.
Revin was driving me.
I almost offered myself.
"This is your quote, Charlie.
A reporter suckered me
as soon as I got here.
"Off the record," she said.
I told her every damn thing.
And that's another thing,
another thing.
In New York,
we had too much press coverage.
Too much. Revin was able
to stay ahead of us.
He knew our next moves.
You got to limit
your press coverage.
[WAVES SPLASHING]
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
CHARLIE: [MUMBLING]
PATTY: It's all too heavy,
Charlie.
I got to go.
Bye, Charlie.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
Patty Gresher.
I don't know how to spell it.
She said she was from San Diego.
Another drifter.
We used to get a better class
of mainlanders.
Now, for 99 bucks,
anybody can come over here.
They end up sleeping
on the beach,
trying to deal weed, hooking.
Uh, David...
I want in.
I want on your task force.
Call New York.
I'm still officially
on the force.
We don't know if we can use you,
Charlie.
Look. Look, you knew the girl.
That makes you a suspect.
What the hell
are you talking about?
A girl gets out
of some guy's bed,
takes a walk on the beach,
gets herself killed.
The guy's got no alibi.
Now, you're a cop.
Who do you suspect?
You know it's the mask killer.
You know that.
I don't know anything,
except you're coming apart.
Now, maybe you
and your girlfriend
had a fight and you knew
just how to cover up her murder,
or maybe you're just whacked out
enough to be the mask killer.
-You son of a...
-DIANE: You're out of line!
CRAFT: Oh, the hell I am!
If there's a serial killer
out there,
why hit so close to you?
It's too much of a coincidence.
It's no damn coincidence.
Don't you see that?
He's copying that part
about it too.
The part about me.
Playing cat-and-mouse with me,
with Charlie Raski.
He's brought this case to me
now, and I'm in it!
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
I want in. I want a badge, NYPD,
attached to your task force.
Charlie. No more crap.
We know everything.
For instance, we know you were
a lieutenant once.
So what?
So I quit. I didn't want
the responsibility.
So it's all bull.
You're an alcoholic.
You've been sliding downhill
with a bottle in your hand
for five years now.
You are coming apart
and it showed.
That's why Revin went after you,
isn't it?
He saw the weakness
and he went for it,
right?
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Before coming to Hawaii,
Charlie, where were you?
Connecticut?
The Wallen Clinic?
A mental hospital.
I checked myself in,
I checked myself out.
It was a rest.
I'm all right now,
and I can work.
Use me out there.
[CLATTERING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
CHARLIE:
What's my bar bill, Willy?
WILLY: Um, 70 bucks.
Plus, uh...
32 for the clocks.
Are you leaving?
No, Willy.
I just got here.
WILLY: Hey, Charlie!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Charlie, I came to tell you,
you're on the task force.
Good. You spoke for me?
No.
No. I think it's a bad idea.
[CHUCKLES]
So you're my watchdog, huh?
So let's get started.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHATTER]
[WHISTLES] Hey, buddy.
Oh. Oh, sorry. Sorry.
Little mess here.
Sorry about that.
Sorry.
Hey, you ever seen any of these
people before?
Never seen them.
You police?
Yeah, me police.
Could you look
at the photos please?
Never saw them.
You hear me that time?
You didn't even look at 'em!
He didn't even look
at the photos!
I'm very upset.
Come on, Charlie.
Let's go, all right?
There are other bars around.
Let's go check them out.
No. No, this is gonna be fun.
Trust me.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Honolulu Police! Get up!
Get up now! Get up! Form a line!
Get up, get up, punk!
Come on, get up, get up,
stand up, get up,
come on, come on, baby.
Stop drinking, get up, stand up.
Get up, toots.
Yeah, Navy, get over there,
get your girlfriend up too,
get up, get up now.
Hey, what are you saying
something about me?
Get over there, I read lips.
Stop drinking get over there.
What, what, what?
Your mother know you're in here?
Get over there, get over there.
Now.
Oh, what are you
laughing and smiling?
You're making a face at me.
I could arrest you
with that face, get over there.
Okay, boys and girls,
Charlie Raski's here.
This is the game.
Everybody looks
at these photos, okay?
Take a picture, pass them down.
Take this picture,
pass them down.
If you've seen any
of these people,
I want you to--you don't get
a picture.
I want you to talk to me.
All right?
Take these photos.
Look at them, look at the photo.
Okay?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
You got weapons here?
You got whores here?
You got people making very ugly
faces here
and I'm gonna close you down
unless I get some cooperation.
You post these,
you talk to people
and you call me.
You hear me that time?
Good.
Thank you very much.
This has been
the Charlie Raski Show.
We'll see you later, bye-bye,
have a drink for me
on the house.
Bye.
MAN: Hey.
DIANE: What do you mean?
CHARLIE: I don't know
it just doesn't feel right.
It's clean, it's quick,
there's no passion,
none of Riven's sexual violence.
It's, like, Kilalo says,
there's a piece missing,
we're just not seeing it.
Maybe you're the missing piece.
Now he pulled you into the case,
he got your girlfriend,
so maybe he's watching you.
I mean maybe we should
be watching you.
You are, aren't you?
Now victim number two.
The sailor's got me
going in circle,
it doesn't fit
and there is one other wrinkle
in the book that doesn't fit
with anything else either.
Sammy Yung was in town
-just for that day.
-CHARLIE: Who's he?
CRAFT: He's one of the big
Kahunas from Hong Kong,
he's the Mafia there
and he calls them the Triads.
Yeah. But they're a lot older
than Mafias,
I mean--and he's really
high up in Triads.
But why does he come into town
for one day and then gone?
CHARLIE: Triads, we tail him?
Yeah. He shopped,
he had a meeting
with his lawyers.
Real estate it's 7197
Corporation,
you know, they're based out
of New York.
Never heard of them.
Oh, I have. They bought up a lot
of Nahele Lani,
they were in the papers.
CHARLIE: There's that Nahehe,
whatever again,
what's so special?
It's Nahele Lani,
it's one of the most beautiful
and wild places
on the island, Charlie.
It means heavenly wilderness
in our legends.
It's Lewa.
What the hell is Lewa?
Paradise.
CRAFT: I just think
that we should put a team
on Charlie's house.
What the hell for,
you keep circling me Craft?
I got my theories
about this guy,
do you wanna hear them?
Sure--no, sure I do,
sorry Craft.
I wanna hear
everything about this case
and Hawaiian Police work
in general that you know.
I got 30 seconds, I'm not doing
anything, so shoot.
Let's get out of here Jimmy.
This man gets real mean
when he's on a wagon.
Forget the coffee, let's get out
of here, hit the streets.
I'm going home Charlie.
What? What are you--what are you
on Hawaiian time or what?
Yeah, what do you know about it?
About what?
About Hawaii?
You've been here, what,
four months.
You don't try to fit in,
you don't try
to understand the people,
you don't try to learn the ways,
you don't even try
to pronounce the words.
You could be anywhere.
But you are nowhere.
I guess maybe you're right.
Hey.
Charlie, I'm sorry.
Now listen,
it's been a long night
and we're all very tired.
I'm sorry.
I feel better, thanks Doc.
I'm gonna go to work now.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
CRAFT: Take a look.
I see.
Take a close look.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
ISHITA: Names Wineha.
He's a Paniolo,
a cowboy in a big ranch
in Nahele Lani.
DIANE: Nahele Lani again.
CRAFT: His wallet's not missing,
same M.O., stocking around
his neck as you can see?
CHARLIE: Why Nahele Lani,
like the first killing.
Ansella Suarez,
her boss was a trustee up
in one of the biggest
states up there.
Nahele Lani.
-So?
-So he loses his job,
the land gets sold
and now this guy,
he's got a connection
in Nahele Lani, coincidence?
DIANE: What else Charlie?
I don't know.
I'm just telling you
it doesn't feel right to me.
I mean what if this is about
something,
what if this is not about
a serial killer?
And what if that's the missing
piece?
What do you mean, Charlie?
What missing piece?
I don't know, Nahele Lani, the
land, I don't know.
Man, you want it to be about
something look at his face.
It's got your name on it Raski.
Your name.
-What are you saying?
-CRAFT: I'm saying the man died
about 4:00 this morning,
-where were you?
-You get off of it, Craft.
Get off of it.
He's losing it.
Tell him.
Look Charlie,
the Japanese fisherman
has nothing to do with the land.
Or Patty either.
Tell him Mahona or I will.
Tell me what?
It could be a lot of things
Charlie.
Some people are even saying
it could be you.
You're on the suspect list buddy
and not the one
we released to the press.
Not yet.
But we're watching you Raski,
now you stay in the light
and walk real straight.
You understand?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh.
No.
-RIVEN: Charlie.
-No. No.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUNSHOTS]
Riven!
[HORN BEEPING]
-[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
-Charlie?
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
ISHITA: Come on Charlie,
we're gonna be late.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
ISHITA: Hey Charlie.
Charlie?
The shower's on.
[SHOWER GUSHING]
ISHITA: Hey Charlie.
Charlie, come on wake up.
DIANE: Charlie no.
[PANTING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
He's inside me again.
Oh, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
You people are putting up with a
lot.
I don't know what to say.
Why don't you try a thank you.
Mahalo.
Komo Mai.
Murder number one,
your friend the maid is killed.
The love affair comes out
in the open
and the guy loses
his trusteeship
over the land at Nahele Lani.
Now, we know
that that very same land
was sold to the 7197
Corporation.
It's like dominoes.
That's a stretch, Charlie.
CHARLIE: Keep listening.
Murders two and three.
They had nothing to do
with Nahele Lani.
Right. They were decoys.
Decoys. Think about it.
Two random killings
to make us think
we're chasing a serial killer.
Murder number four,
back on track.
The cowboy, he managed
the ranch at Nahele Lani.
Now, we know the ranch
wasn't doing very well,
but I found out this morning
that he was being paid in shares
and he was approached to sell
those shares.
Yeah. But a lot of people
are buying land here,
it's like gold now.
Listen.
He wouldn't sell the shares,
right?
But now his family
is thinking of selling
and guess who the high
bidder is?
I checked.
It's 7197 Corporation.
Dominoes.
All right. Dominoes.
Who's playing dominoes?
It's a rich man's game.
It's the land, Mahona.
There's only so much land
on this island.
So, where are we going?
To Nahele Lani,
to see the land barons.
[PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hey, how you doing?
I'll have eggs Benedict.
Talk to her.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Wagner Thorne?
I'm Charles Raski
this is Diane Mahona,
And your business
just couldn't wait.
I know.
You're collecting for the,
uh, police charities, right?
And whoever collects
the most money
wins a trip to Detroit
or somewhere.
Oh, I'd be in a hurry too.
We're investigating
the mask murders.
-And?
-And I think this case
may have something to do
with this area,
this land, the Nahele Lani
Peninsula.
These murders? Here?
Does your chief
know you're visiting today?
Have you been approached
by the 7197 Corporation
to buy your land?
By them and others.
Is that any business of yours?
And are you considering selling?
Oh, I'm considering
throwing you out.
Mr. Thorne, we're just trying
to follow every possible lead.
Murders on Hotel Street,
skid row.
And you're dragging them
onto my lawn.
I hope you wiped your feet.
WOMAN:
Just look who's being killed.
What could those people
have to do with Nahele Lani?
It's ridiculous.
Some of those killings
could be decoys.
I don't believe you were invited
to our little party.
Did anyone invite them?
Well, they certainly
aren't dressed for it, are they?
Well then I think the best idea
is to throw them out.
Agreed?
Listen, Slick.
You could ask me to leave,
but you couldn't throw me out
in a million years.
And if I could get some
cooperation here
maybe some people
wouldn't have to die.
Oh, and you could lose
some weight.
DIANE: I learned something
about you Charlie.
I learned that you are not
the prejudiced cop
I thought you were.
No, you're just as stupid
when it comes to pushing around
rich Caucasians.
Do you have any idea
what the chief is going to say
to Kilalo or what Kilalo
is gonna say to us?
CHARLIE:
I'll worry about that later.
DIANE: So sure you're right,
everyone else is wrong.
You have a typical haole
attitude.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
-Mrs. Danton?
-Wait. It's beautiful.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Police.
EMMA: So, how can I be of help,
Officer Raski?
CHARLIE: Sergeant Raski.
Well, we're with the task force
-that's looking into--
-I know.
You're the police officer
who likes to throw
his weight around.
Who likes to treat everyone
like a pusher,
or a pimp,
or even a hooker.
DIANE: We have a few question
Mrs. Danton.
Am I a suspect?
You could be a victim.
Of a killer who roams
downtown alleys?
How is that possible?
I think it has to do
with this land.
Thank you, Jackie.
From teacher to house boy,
he's very serviceable.
Teacher?
Oh no, Mr. Raski,
I'm the teacher.
Now, what were you telling me
about my land?
CHARLIE:
Have you had any offers?
We've all had offers
in this peninsula
but I'm not selling.
This land...
Belongs to my late husband's
family.
I keep it for his memory
also because it's beautiful.
I happen to have the most
exquisite spot on this earth.
CHARLIE:
I hear it isn't even on earth,
I hear it's paradise.
Thank you.
I'd be happy to show it
to you sometime.
Uh, why don't you ask
Ms. Mahona,
I'm sure she's heard of it.
Oh, I've heard of it, yeah.
But, uh, in my lifetime,
the best of Nahele Lani
has been owned and fenced,
and, uh, closed off
to the people.
In the last hundred years,
the only Hawaiians
to have seen it have been
employees of the Danton Estate.
Hmm, well, I'd be glad to show
it to you, too.
And you can take a picture.
CHARLIE: Have you had any offers
from the 7197 Corporation?
We've all had offers Mr. Raski.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I must take a shower.
Oh, why don't you do the rest
of your business by telephone?
You act like I just did
my business on your rug,
Mrs. Danton.
You know, Wagner Thorne
said that you have this sort
of attitude that makes one want
to punch you in the nose.
Wagner didn't have the guts.
Now, I'm sorry
our dirty little business
has ruined your playtime
here with Jackie,
but I need a few answers.
She's a tough lady.
Why didn't you bring it
to the team?
Why didn't you bring
it to me?
All you did was start a fire
and it cost me valuable time
to put it out.
We have ways to approach people
like the Thornes
-and the Dantons--
-Excuse me, captain.
Charlie, there's nothing
on the lawyers who operated here
for the 7197 Corporation.
Their orders come out
of New York.
What's the name means,
7197?
That's their phone number
in New York,
212-555-7197.
Anything more
on the Hong Kong Triads?
-Zip.
-Thanks.
-Where are you going?
-Emma Danton.
It's all right. She called.
Well, is this business
or what?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
EMMA: Do you feel the magic
here, Charlie?
-CHARLIE: Yeah, I do.
-EMMA: It's very old magic.
Very old. You know, I've tried
but we're strangers here,
Charlie.
CHARLIE: Even you? You own it.
Nobody can really own it...
nobody, Charlie.
Even a rich spoiled woman
like me knows that.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
EMMA: Now, this...
was sacred long
before they built this church.
You know, it was built
in a foundation
of a very ancient temple.
It was over a thousand
years old.
Some people say that
about my house on the beach.
You're very funny.
I'm sorry, I hit you Charlie.
Well, I thought
that if I bought you up here
you might forgive me.
"If you forgive people enough,
you belong to them."
-James Hilton.
-Hmm...
very good, Charlie,
you've read English novelists.
No, my bartender does.
Oh, that's very funny.
Well, believe it or not
I can be funny sometimes.
Tell me something, Charlie.
Is it wrong that only a few
people can see all of this?
And doesn't make it more
of a treasure?
Well, everybody wants
to see paradise.
EMMA: It's more than paradise,
Charlie.
Eternity, Charlie.
That's what they call it.
The land of Po.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
The regions of the spirits.
The good ones as well
as the evil ones.
You could join them.
All you have to do is jump.
Hey.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Emma.
[LAUGHS]
Whoa.
-Hey. Hey, Emma.
-[LAUGHS]
Oh, look what you've done
to my blouse, Charlie.
That will be $250 you owe me.
Bill me.
[LAUGHS]
That's another $250.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
EMMA: Are you leaving, Charlie?
Aren't you? It's gonna be dark
pretty soon.
Are you afraid of the dark?
Sometimes.
Stay.
I can't, Emma.
Hey, look what you've done here.
Look at this.
You owe me a fortune, Charlie.
I got to go.
Charlie.
You are not leaving me here.
How am I supposed to get home?
-You are home.
-[LAUGHS]
Hey, Charlie Raski.
You're not leaving me here.
And after I've showed you
where the world ends?
[LAUGHS]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
CHARLIE: Hello.
-Hello?
-MAN [OVER PHONE]: Charlie.
It's me.
It's me, Charlie.
Remember?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[WAVES CRASHING]
Detective Medina, please.
Oh.
Who's this? Oliver?
Yeah, yeah, it's Raski.
[LAUGHS]
Hell no, I'm not to back yet.
Are you kidding?
I got flowers around my neck
and no tan lines,
you know what I mean?
Yeah.
Yeah, what do you mean?
Of course I still talk the same.
All right. All right, okay.
I--I'm sounding a little bit
like I'm less from New York.
I know. Some people
have been teasing me about that.
Uh, well, listen, um,
is, uh, Danny Greco there?
I mean,
who's keeping New York safe,
you know what I mean?
Yeah.
Danny.
Oh. [LAUGHS]
Ah, same to you, you gutter bag.
How's Emily?
Good.
Give her a hug for me,
will you?
Oh, I'm doing so-so, Danny.
Hanging in there, you know.
You heard?
Yeah, yeah.
Four murders so far.
And listen,
I got a question...
the tapes
on the Albert Revin case,
you know, the ones
of his phone conversations,
you know where they are?
Yeah--no, wait, I--yeah,
I know, I--but are you sure
they're all there?
Would you?
Would you, buddy? Thanks.
Would you check?
Thanks man, thanks.
Yeah.
[SIGHS] Yeah.
Listen, um...
listen, Danny...
we nailed Revin, didn't we?
I mean, you put three in him
and Hank blew his whole clip,
and the man was dead
on the scene, am I right?
I mean, we buried him,
he's gone.
Sure. Uh, no, I know.
Sure.
I know.
The phone calls
have started again.
No, no, no. I can't,
I can't back down now.
Home?
I don't know where home
is anymore, Danny.
I can't, I got to stay with it.
I...
Listen, uh, Danny, I got to hang
up the telephone now, all right?
I'll be talking to you. Thanks.
Thanks, Danny. Bye.
DIANE:
Charlie, where have you been?
I have been calling you
all day.
You can't just disappear
like that.
You want some pineapple juice,
Mahona?
I was right.
You shouldn't be on this case.
-I am this case.
-Meaning what?
The killer
is calling me now.
-The police can tap the line.
-Wait a minute.
Wait.
You know, maybe I just imagined
it. I don't know--
Imagined what, Charlie?
What?
Maybe I don't want some.
Maybe I don't want anybody
hearing some psycho
open me up on the telephone.
What do you see out there,
Charlie?
Devils, Mahona...
and ghosts.
Your wife?
I don't think about that.
DIANE: Maybe you should.
They say you found her body.
CHARLIE: I can't remember.
Some things are blank.
They're supposed to be.
DIANE: Charlie,
let the police tap your line.
It's for your sake.
Word keeps filtering
through the department
that you're the number one
suspect.
You're the only pattern
in this case, Charlie.
It's like you said,
you are this case.
What do you think?
DIANE: I think you need a shave.
[LAUGHS]
DIANE: Eight hours sleep
and a home-cooked meal.
[SCOFFS]
Are you inviting me?
DIANE:
You wanna meet my parents?
-[LAUGHS]
-DIANE: I live with them.
Yeah. My brother and his wife
and kids and the dogs.
There's always room
for one more.
You'd be more than welcome.
Why would you do this?
It's our way. [CHUCKLES]
You know.
You're my friend
and they're my family...
you know.
We're all on the same island.
And maybe you need a new place
to hide out and act tough.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, I'm not ready for your kind
of life yet, Mahona.
But it's nice that you asked.
It's nice.
DIANE: It's Hawaiian.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
-CHARLIE: Tell me something.
-[GASPS]
Oh, my God! Charlie!
Tell me about
the 7197 Corporation.
You scared me to death.
-Tell me.
-Tell you what?
About the 7197 Corporation.
They're a company
that's been buying land.
-Why?
-Who are they?
How should I know?
Ever hear of a man
by the name of Sammy Yung?
No.
CHARLIE: Ever hear
about the Hong Kong Triads?
No.
CHARLIE: Your houseboy,
Jackie Lo, he's from Hong Kong.
I checked.
Did you know that?
Do you trust him?
Are you staying the whole night,
Charlie?
Tell me something else.
Are you wearing stockings
or pantyhose?
Would you like to check
for yourself, Charlie?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I hate stockings.
I do, too.
And I hate pantyhose.
Sometimes nothing is best,
don't you think?
I can't think.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Mahona!
What are you doing?
Checking up on me?
I got a message
you wanted to see.
Not from me.
I'll jump in the shower,
we'll grab some breakfast.
Too late, Charlie.
Look on the bed.
-Don't touch it.
-Diane, I...
There was no murder weapon
found on the last victim.
-Do you remember, Charlie?
-Diane, it's a plant!
The whole thing is a setup!
I wasn't even here last night!
-I'm calling it in.
-Diane, not now! I'm close now.
They--they'll hold me
if you call it in.
Twenty-four hours,
then I'll come in.
Diane, do you really think
that I could have
strangled all those people?
I don't wanna believe it,
Charlie,
-but I have to look at it!
-At what?
The possibility!
[PANTING]
Do you really think I killed
your friend, Ansella?
You want your revenge, Doc?
No.
I just want it to be over,
Charlie.
It's not personal anymore.
Good.
Good for you, Doc.
It's healthier that way.
But for me, it is.
It's personal.
Thirty minutes,
then you call the police.
-Fifteen.
-DIANE: Charlie.
Charlie!
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Be patient.
Two more minutes.
Are you going to be rushing
me all night, Wagner?
THORNE: Probably.
Emma, I've been knocking
on your door for years
ever since you've been a widow.
Let's face it, Wagner.
You've been knocking
on my door long
before I was a window.
[SCOFFS] You noticed.
EMMA: Where are you taking me
tonight?
The club.
-All right?
-EMMA: Oh, yes.
-Then I'll take you.
-Oh? Where?
To the beach.
To your beach.
I love the beach at night.
Sounds like fun.
[EMMA HUMMING]
-Ready?
-Are you?
[CHUCKLES]
Thank you for waiting.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
CHARLIE: Hand.
Eye.
Spear.
Flame.
Damn.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Task force. Ishita.
CHARLIE [OVER PHONE]:
Listen to me, Jimmy.
-It's Charlie.
-CHARLIE [OVER PHONE]: I'm not
gonna give you time
to trace me,
but I know you're gonna try.
-That's okay, Jimmy--
-We need a trace! Now!
CHARLIE [OVER PHONE]:
--as long as you listen.
Come on, come on,
get sick, guys.
I don't have all night here.
Shoot, Charlie.
You told me about the Hong Kong
Triads and Sammy Yung.
They use symbols, don't they?
-Symbols?
-CHARLIE [OVER PHONE]: Damn it,
Jimmy, don't try and stall me.
The group
that Sammy Yung leads.
ISHITA: Society of the Hand.
CHARLIE [OVER PHONE]:
The hand, yeah. What others?
ISHITA: Of the Eye.
-CHARLIE [OVER PHONE]: Flame?
-ISHITA: Yes.
-CHARLIE [OVER PHONE]: Spear?
-Arrow, yes.
-What have you got, Charlie?
-CHARLIE: Now, tell me the date
that lease is up in Hong Kong
and it reverts back
-to Communist China.
-It's 1997, July the 1st,
-I think.
-In--tell me in numbers,
month, day, year.
719...
7.
The Triads are getting out
before then.
They're getting out of Hong Kong
and they're coming here.
They're coming to Hawaii.
Did you hear that, Kilalo,
or whoever else is on the line?
Are you hearing me?
The Triads are planning
on building an empire
in Nahele Lani,
and somebody's getting the whole
damn peninsula for them.
You're gonna have the world's
worst criminals
-right in your lap.
-Keep him on.
Will you come in
with what you've got?
Raski, get your haole
in here!
Listen to me!
There are still two land owners
who are alive and in place
and they're in danger.
Do you understand?
Wagner Thorne, Emma Danton.
Ten more seconds
and we got him.
Damn.
Woo-hoo!
[LAUGHS]
-Emma!
-EMMA: Woo!
Oh, oh...
your stocking.
What is it, Wagner?
WAGNER: You lost your stocking!
[LAUGHS]
Listen, Wagner,
tell me something.
-Hmm...
-Tell me something, darling.
What would you do
if you had to choose
the last words
in your life?
What would they be?
Tell me.
What would they be, darling?
I don't understand.
That's perfect.
That's perfect. Wagner.
Oh.
[GASPING]
I'm sorry, Wagner,
but I promised them paradise,
all of it.
It'll be all right, Wagner.
We'll all mourn your death.
And we'll all bid
on your property, Wagner.
[CHUCKLES]
But I'm gonna win.
I'm gonna win, Wagner.
[CHUCKLES]
Wagner...
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm going to make you
beautiful now, Wagner.
[WAVES CRASHING]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
Mister Thorne's not at home.
-Where the hell is he?
-Not here.
He went to the club.
-His car is here.
-He--
[WAVES CRASHING]
CRAFT: Drop it, Raski!
Drop the gun!
I said, drop it!
Take it easy, Craft,
take it easy!
[GUNSHOTS]
DIANE: No!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Charlie!
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Are you Dr. Diane Mahona?
I got a message for you.
I gotta see some ID.
Don't look as good
as you, huh.
You some one, Doc.
Kidding, huh?
Yeah. Wait.
Hey, sister, I'd like to stay
and talk story with you,
but I gotta bag now.
No, wait...
Who gave this to you?
Hey, some haole guy.
Describe him.
Uh, some kind beat-up-looking
Caucasian bro,
you know, with the no shave,
'bout this high, huh?
Did he say anything?
Yeah, he say,
"Kenny, no say nothin'."
-Well, where is he?
-He say if she say where is he,
you say he's in paradise, huh?
Mahalo.
Hey, who are you?
How'd you get in here?
CHARLIE: Willy?
They're out there.
They're watching your house.
I know they are.
Hey, you got some food?
Yeah, you must be hungry.
Give me a drink, too.
A drink?
You sure?
You sleep at all?
Man, you look rotten.
Stay in the back,
catch a few hours.
Huh?
Maybe by then,
they catch that guy.
Those guys couldn't catch
a dog on a leash.
I gotta go find Emma Danton
before the killer does.
I'm going back
to paradise, Willy.
Paradise is where I am.
Yeah, Voltaire, huh?
[CHUCKLES]
Something was stuffed
in the mailbox here.
It's for you.
I have a feeling
about the doctor.
She's a good woman.
She is.
But she's up there
in the dark near a cliff
where people used to leap off.
The land of "Po",
heaven or hell.
You ever hear about it, Willy?
Yeah.
This is a trap, Willy.
Don't go there, Charlie.
I gotta go.
Hey, listen,
can I borrow your car?
Thanks, man.
Drink, Charlie.
-No, I'm [INDISTINCT]
-It's on the house.
Hey, for me.
[SPITS]
Jasmine tea.
Against the evil spirit.
Luck, Charlie.
Here, Charlie.
Thanks, big man.
Thanks for the keys.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
CHARLIE: Emma.
DIANE: Charlie?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Ugh!
[GRUNTING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN [OVER CASSETTE]: Suspect
Albert Revin voice tape four.
REVIN [OVER CASSETTE]: Charlie,
I'm calling about Claire.
Your wife looks great
in that green and black dress.
Nice legs. Nice neck.
I'd like a date with her.
I'd like an hour with her,
Charlie.
I think I'll arrange that.
Do you mind?
CHARLIE: Claire!
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
CHARLIE: Diane.
DIANE: [MOANS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
CHARLIE: You'll be okay.
EMMA: Charlie.
It's me, Charlie.
It's me.
Remember?
It's me, Charlie.
EMMA: Remember, Charlie?
It's me.
It's me, Charlie.
Remember, Charlie?
REVIN: It's me, Charlie.
-It's me, Charlie.
[GUNSHOT]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
I'm coming back for you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[WIND HOWLING]
Isn't that beautiful, Charlie?
Step back, Emma.
Charlie, please, Charlie.
Give me your hand, Emma.
-Oh.
-CHARLIE: Give me your hand.
Come on.
Come with me, Charlie.
Come with me.
[SCREAMS] Come with me!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[WAVES CRASHING]
DIANE: No fish?
Plenty of fish. No bait.
Sorry to disturb you.
It's okay. No problem.
"Some are lost
and some are saved."
Willy the bartender.
You saved my life too,
you know.
New York, huh?
Yeah. I'm getting to miss
the noise a little bit.
Is that a good sign, Doc?
What, you don't wanna hide out
and act tough some more?
CHARLIE: [LAUGHS] Nah.
Aloha,Charlie.
A hui hou kakou, Mahona.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Charlie.
What?
What do you see out there?
Water!
Sunlight on water, Doc.
SINGER: ♪ If you would let me
spend my whole life...♪
CHARLIE:
♪ Whole life loving you♪
♪ Then life could be a dream,
Sweetheart♪
SINGER:
♪ Now every time I look at you♪
♪ Something is on my...♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
DIANE:
It's Hawaiian, Charlie.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]