(theme music playing )
♪ I don't know nothin'
'bout chemistry ♪
♪ Except the kind
between you and me ♪
♪ Oh, I do know
that I love you, girl ♪
♪ So take a trip
and rock around the world. ♪
Okay, now here's
the real creepy thing.
They only eat this beef,
and it has to be bloody.
- Yuck.
- I know.
And if it isn't
dripping in blood,
then Professor Fuller's all,
"There's not enough blood,"
and then I'm all,
"Sorry."
Gotcha.
But I figure, if we're making
seven bucks an hour,
they can have dinner
and a movie for all I care.
Tell me about it.
Does Professor Fuller get mad a lot?
Only when the bats
don't get fed.
And when he gets mad,
he gets mad
in that weird-professor-in-
his-sweater-genius kind of way.
- That is so sexy.
- Isn't it?
( electronic beeping )
Wow, it's creepy in here.
What's with the lighting?
Bats like to sleep
in caves during the day,
so this makes them feel
right at home.
Okay.
They can't get out,
can they?
Nah, they're locked up
nice and tight.
I wouldn't want these
freaky boys going anywhere.
- You see this?
- Uh-huh.
It means they're hearing
this sound
that makes them
all calm and blissful,
Iike they're listening
to an 'N Sync album,
but only they can hear it.
Now watch.
When it's time
for them to be fed,
you push this.
( bats squealing )
Oh, wow.
Now they're hearing another
sound only they can hear.
It tells them
they're about to be fed.
If you don't turn it on,
the professor's all,
"Why didn't you turn it on? "
And then I'm all,
"Sorry."
Got it.
Watch.
Come on.
Want it?
They're so gross.
( screams )
Ahh! Get it off of me!
Get it off!
( screaming )
I've never seen
such a nervous cat, Dr. Winslow.
It just breaks my heart
to think of Dinah's suffering.
Well, she doesn't look
that nervous to me right now.
No, no, she is.
Just look
at the tension.
Why don't we bring her over here
and I'll have a look at her?
You know,
I was holding her close
and I could feel
her little heart racing.
Do you feel it?
I'm trying.
Can you help her,
Doctor?
Have you tried
massage?
No.
Not too rough-- just enough
to relieve the tension.
- Ohh.
- ( cat purring )
Ohh.
( laughs )
You see, she's starting
to relax already.
You have to touch
with females, John.
( laughs )
Thanks.
The Apple Blossom Dance
is this weekend.
Oh, I know.
There'll be a lot
of single women there.
I'll be there,
gettin' down...
and gettin' funky.
I'm not sure I'm quite ready
for funky just yet.
How long has it been?
Almost three years
since the funeral.
Well, you can't live
in Heartbreak Hotel forever, John.
I'll try
to remember that.
It just jumped into my hair
and attacked me.
I was there,
Professor Fuller--
I literally
saw it happen.
It bit me in the back of my head
and it wouldn't stop bleeding.
I used like,
a half a box of Band-Aids.
A completely
natural reaction.
The saliva of blood-feeding bats
contains an anti-coagulant.
- Anti-what?
- Anti-coagulant.
It prevents blood from clotting
and closing up the wound.
Yuck.
They're very efficient
little eating machines,
when you stop
and think about it.
I don't want to think about it.
Someone should do something.
Perhaps if you kept your hair
out of the cages in the future?
No, I mean something
more than that,
Iike tell my parents
or the Dean or something.
Diane, have a seat.
You're in my Biology 1 01 class,
aren't you?
Yeah.
If we were to keep this
among ourselves,
without involving
people on the outside,
people who might not share
our love of science,
I would express
my gratitude
by making sure
your final grade is an A.
What about Heather?
Her too.
Deal!
( wings flutter )
( chimes ringing )
( ringing )
What was Scottsville like
before the invasion?
What invasion?
The invasion of the young,
upwardly-mobile urban professional
seeking a slice
of the small town life!
- That invasion.
- You're not helping, Dad.
Come on, I need something
for my documentary.
Genny, I'm your father,
I'm not a sound-byte.
Please, just tell me something
about how Scottsville used to be,
before I was born,
back in the olden days.
Let's see if I can remember
back that far.
Okay, the town moved slower.
People took their time
and everybody knew each other.
Did the town have
a mega-mart back then?
No mega-marts,
just regular sized ones.
And when you went to the movies,
they didn't have 21 screens,
- just one.
- One!?
That's totally vintage.
Did you have a TV back then?
No, on Saturday nights,
we used to sit around in loincloths,
and beat big rocks
with sticks.
( scoffs )
Man:
Hey, Professor!
- Oh, hello, Al.
- Working late?
It seems I get my best work
done late at night.
Just like your bats.
Excuse me?
You get your best work done
at night just like your bats.
Oh.
( chuckles )
( squeaking )
- ( electronic beeping )
- ( lock clicks )
( bats squeaking )
( whistling )
( distant yell )
So nice of you
to stop by, Logan.
( muffled )
Thank you, Mr. W.
But maybe your parents would enjoy
your company this evening.
No way.
They hate having me around.
- How would you know?
- They said.
"Logan, we hate
having you around."
Oh, I'm sure they didn't mean that
in a negative way.
- Genny: All set.
- Tell him what you're gonna call it.
You're gonna love this.
"Scottsville,
Town without Pity."
I love it! Channel 1 2
is going to run it, definitely.
"Look up the words, 'perfect
small town' in the dictionary,
and you'll probably find
a picture of Scottsville there.
For years, this small,
uncomplicated town
was the perfect place to live,
work, and raise your family.
Then suddenly,
catastrophe struck.
Serenity was replaced
with urban blight--
superstores, strip malls,
junk housing.
All thanks to a man
named Carl Hart."
- Honey, we could get sued.
- Shhh.
"Hart gets property by foreclosing
on small family-owned farms,
and it's all handled
through his finance company.
Is it legal?
- Maybe it is on paper--"
- We're definitely gonna get sued.
Daddy, I verified
all of my facts.
"Unsuspecting buyers
from the city
plunk down
their hard-earned cash,
and wind up with yuck
for their buck."
I wrote that!
"Modern suburban blight
at its max.
And it's all been
brought to you by--
Carl Hart,
the Duke of Doom."
The Duke of Doom?!
I only wrote
the first half of that.
Genny: "And whenever things get
too messy for Hart to handle,
he calls on his one-man,
personal police force..."
Get that camera
out of my face!
Gimme it! Gimme it!
I'm gonna break it!
Get back here!
( giggling )
"... a low rent, rent-a-cop,
Louis the enforcer."
- Now wait just a minute!
- Shhh!
Genny:
"What have we lost?
Oh, not much.
Just our way of life.
Before Hart..."
People took their time
and everybody knew each other.
I ended it with you, Daddy.
Oh, great! I'm on camera.
Why don't we call
your grandma and ask her
if she's got something to say.
Then we can all
be named in the lawsuit.
Heather:
He must have asked me
to the Apple Blossom Dance
a dozen times.
And I was all, "Which part of no
don't you understand? "
Diane:
What'd he do?
He started dancing around,
showing me his cool moves,
so I'd be all,
"I've got to go to the dance
with Mr. Smooth."
Gross.
He was wearing sandals
with socks.
- Eww.
- Sad.
( screaming )
- ( police radio chatter )
- Howard, you're a professional.
You're supposed to be used
to this kind of thing.
But, Ally,
it's just that--
I've never seen
a dead person before.
Not even at a funeral.
When my grandmother died, I was 1 2.
I didn't go to the wake.
I stayed home. My mother
was furious, but I told her,
"I don't care.
You can punish me all you want to.
I'm not going to Nana's funeral."
That's what we called her.
Howard, why don't you wait
in the patrol car,
and see if Chief Taylor
radios in?
Really? Can I?
Whew! Yeah.
That'd be, um...
Yeah, yeah, I'll do that.
And if anything
comes in, I'll...
I'll find someone
to tell you.
Whoo. Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Hello, I'm Detective Parks.
Are you the two lab assistants
who discovered the body?
Yes, we were going
to feed the bats, and--
I'm in training.
And we found Professor Fuller
just like this.
When's the last time
you saw the professor?
Yesterday,
when he yelled at me.
I need you to stick around.
I want to talk to each of you
separately. Okay?
- Okay.
I need a list of everybody
who was here last night.
- I'd like to take a look.
- Heather: Don't!
What happened to him,
it's gross.
- It's horrible!
- Thanks, ladies,
but I worked homicide
in Los Angeles for nine years.
Trust me,
I've seen everything.
Whoa!
Do you think
we still get our A's?
- Hi!
- Oooh!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
- Are you Detective Parks?
- Yes.
I'm John Winslow. I'm the town's
animal control officer.
Well, actually
I'm a veterinarian,
but the animal control thing
is just part-time.
You know, until they can
find someone else
who's willing to do the job.
Henry-- Henry Banks
used to do the job before me,
and he answered a complaint
about a boa constrictor
in some woman's basement--
Well, I guess he and the woman
hit it off together.
They ran off to Mexico.
No one knows what happened
to the boa constrictor.
Is there any particular reason
why you're here?
Uh, bats. Professor Fuller
had hundreds of them.
And if they had rabies
or any other disease,
then it's a case
for animal control.
- Is this where they were kept?
- ( sputtering )
Can you not touch that?
This is a crime scene.
Oh. And you think
maybe the victim
was killed by that door?
There could be fingerprints.
Can you really get a fingerprint
off a bar that small?
We'll never know, will we,
now that you've touched it?
Did you come down here
to see about missing bats,
or to get your greasy fingerprints
all over potential evidence?
I think you might
have your dates mixed up.
Mean and Angry Day
is tomorrow.
Today is Be Nice To
The Animal Control Guy Day.
Everyone knows that Fuller
was doing bat research.
He had over 500 of them,
and now they're gone.
And I've got to look into it.
It's my job.
I'm also here to do my job,
which is slightly more relevant
than being the town dogcatcher.
- Dogcatcher?!
- Look, Fuller is dead,
and someone let
all his bats out.
What this case needs
is a criminologist,
someone who is trained in homicide
and accident investigation,
someone who is not going to
contaminate the evidence,
- with-- whatever.
- Fine. I'll just go then.
- That would be better.
- I'll come back and do my job
- after you've finished your job.
- Good, yes, thanks. Goodbye.
I'll try not to touch
anything on the way out.
Certainly wouldn't want to
contaminate the crime scene.
Not any more
than you already have.
Are you sure you don't
need any help?
I can manage.
( rustling )
( wings flapping )
Oh! Ohh.
- Howard, you scared me to death.
- Sorry.
How was it?
Was it gory?
You know what? Don't tell me.
I don't want to know.
Good, because after spending
all day in there,
I don't really
want to tell you.
How'd he die?
It was an accident, wasn't it?
I don't think so.
The body was so badly mutilated
you couldn't see his face.
Accident victims
don't look like that.
I-- Fuller was murdered.
Weird.
I wonder where
those bats went.
( squeaking )
Oh, it looks like Mr. Hart.
( dog barking )
- Stop him!
- I'm trying, sir.
Omar, shut up.
Shut up!
What's wrong with this dog?
I don't get it.
He only acts this way with you.
Tell him to bark at the vandals
who damage my homes,
not the guy who signs
your paycheck.
Maybe he's seen what you pay me.
( laughs )
Sorry.
Bad dog, Omar.
- ( dog whines )
- Stupid mutt.
Look, Louis,
I got a truck coming with a couple
thousand sheets of drywall,
6:00 a.m., tomorrow morning.
If they're late,
- I need you to be here.
- Will do.
Whoever signs for them,
I want to count each and every sheet.
2,000 sheets of drywall?!
You better believe
I will.
( laughs )
I never built this many homes
in one development.
And they're beauties.
Real beauties-- especially that
three-bedroom Key Largo model.
Now, that's a real honey.
Enjoy it now, because you're never
going to live in one.
Listen, Willy Kramer's
supposed to
vacate his farm
sometime soon.
He may need a little bit of,
uh... persuasion.
- Louis: That's my specialty.
- ( cell phone rings )
Hold on.
Hello?
What?!
"Police Seek Clues
in Professor's Murder"
They can't print that!
It's the Apple Festival this week.
I got 1 00 home buyers
coming to town, for--
If that thing hits the stands,
I-- Just don't move!
Don't move,
I'll be there.
- ( phone beeps )
- I gotta go.
Is there anything
I could do for you, Mr. Hart?
Yeah, try buying every copy
of tomorrow's "Scottsville Journal."
It'll take a lot of quarters,
but--
- ( dog whines )
- I know.
He's a jerk.
( thud )
You hear that?
Me too.
( wood creaking )
( thuds )
( squeaking )
Who's in there?!
( squealing )
Hart: I can't believe that thing
almost hit the stands.
If I had gotten there
five minutes later,
I would have been
a dead man.
How'd you get the newspaper
to stop the presses?
I threatened to pull
my advertising.
I'll bet that got their
attention.
( chuckling )
It's not funny!
It's Apple Festival week,
the Apple Blossom Dance is Friday.
My daughter is going to be
crowned Miss Apple Blossom.
How do you know
she's going to win?
Because I'm making you
the judge.
You listen to me, Sam,
if people thought there was some
sort of killer loose in this town,
I couldn't give
my homes away.
And I can't go running down
to the newspaper every time
they're thinking about running
a headline that can ruin me!
Yeah, I know. I know.
I don't want to know what
happened to this clown Fuller,
I don't care! I just want
this investigation stopped!
Or would you rather
not get paid your cut?
I'll take care
of the problem.
I promise.
I'm gonna take a nap.
( whimpers )
No, you don't get to nap.
You stay awake and watch these houses.
( squealing )
( whines )
( snoring )
( chattering )
( dog yowls )
( growling )
( whimpering )
I got one more problem that
needs to be taken care of.
I want you to evict Willy Kramer
from his farm tomorrow night.
Kramer? No,
he's still got 30 days.
I got his contract
here somewhere.
He doesn't become delinquent
until the 23rd of next month.
Forget that-- I've got
an amendment to the contract
with an eviction date
as of... tomorrow.
You got a judge
to change the date?
No. I got an inkjet printer
to change the date.
- ( laughs )
- You what?
- You can't--
- Don't tell me what I can't do!
I got more than 30
home sales pending,
and every contract's
got a clause promising
a golf course. Kramer's farm
is that golf course.
The entire new development goes
bust unless I can deliver on this.
Louis: You're not going to
charge me for this, are ya, Doc?
- No.
- Good, 'cause I'm not some doctor
that makes a gazillion bucks
a week, like you.
I'm just an honest
working man.
That's why I'm not
charging you for it.
See, I really didn't
know what to do,
and someone at work said this
was something for animal control.
No, you did the right thing.
So you say Omar
was killed by bats?
Hundreds of 'em.
Maybe even thousands.
How is it that
you weren't attacked?
I was asleep in my truck.
So how'd you see the bats?
I woke up!
Listen, Doc, are you gonna
give me the third degree
or are you gonna
look at the dog?
I-- uh-- I'm gonna
look at the dog.
Definitely look at the dog.
Let's just see here.
I got to warn you, Doc,
these bats,
they really went
to town on Omar.
What they left,
it ain't pretty.
- Wow!
- Told ya!
Okay, look,
I'm gonna have to do
a few tests.
Can you leave him here
for a couple of days?
You can keep him forever.
He won't do me no good dead!
No, I guess not.
Must be kind of upset
about losing Omar.
Yeah, I'm upset. Now I gotta
go buy me another dog.
- Right.
- ( door shuts )
- ( knocking )
- Come in.
You wanted
to see me, Chief?
Yeah.
I was going through
my paperwork and I can't seem
to find your report
on the Fuller case.
That's because it's not
finished--
- not yet anyway.
- Problem?
No, I'm just waiting
for the coroner's report.
The coroner's report?
( chuckles )
And... what's it gonna say?
No, no, I'll tell you
what it's gonna say.
Fuller was a kook. One night,
his bats decided to take a hike,
He got upset,
had a heart attack and died.
Death by natural causes.
Case closed.
Actually, no. The "natural causes"
thing isn't going to fly.
I see.
So in addition to being
a big time homicide detective
from big time Los Angeles,
now you're a mind-reader too?
This isn't just a hunch, sir,
the body was badly mutilated.
This was a murder.
Did you recover
a murder weapon?
- No, but I'm--
- How about a witness?
Sometimes it helps to have
a witness, you have one?
- Not yet--
- A suspect, that'd be nice.
You have a suspect?
It could have been
animal rights' activists,
it could have been the two girls
who discovered the body,
One of the two girls
who discovered the body?
What were their names?
Muffin and Bambi--
- Heather and Diane.
Now there's the names of two
lifelong violent felons.
The deadly duo
of Heather and Diane.
I suppose you discovered
the girls' motives?
Motive, as in,
a reason
they felt it was necessary
to kill somebody.
What did Fuller do?
Break their hairdryer?
Steal their
bellybutton rings?
- Sir, if you just let me--
- You know, Parks,
Scottsville isn't
anything like Los Angeles.
Scottsville is different.
Way different.
Our local businesses
are run by families.
Those families count on the money
the Apple Festival brings in.
So the last thing this town
needs right now
is a murder!
So I want your report on how
Fuller died a peaceful,
and natural death on my desk
tomorrow morning!
- Sir, that would--
- Tomorrow!
Yes, sir.
How long does it take to get
an autopsy in this county?
- Man: Seven days.
- I'm aware of that.
But I need
this information stat.
- What?
- That's what doctors say
when they need something fast.
Don't you watch TV?!
- Nope.
- Uh-huh.
Okay, what about
the blood work, then?
- State capitol.
- You sent it where?
- Sacramento.
- By mail?
- Nah, pony express.
- Do you know--
- Can you hold?
- Okay, I'll hold.
( phone rings )
- Parks.
- Hi, this is John Winslow.
- I'm sorry, who?
- Winslow, Dr. John Winslow.
The veterinarian--
we met yesterday.
- Oh, the dogcatcher.
- Yeah, the dogcatcher.
I also entertain
at children's birthday parties.
Listen, a client of mine
just brought in his dog--
You know what, I don't have
time for a dog story right now.
I'm in the middle of a very important
homicide investigation.
Okay, you had
the roast beef
with mayo and a diet Coke,
right, Ally?
This dog is dead.
He was attacked
by bats.
This could have something
to do with your investigation.
Did you tamper
with the evidence?
Did I run my hands all over
a chewed up doberman? No.
Don't touch anything.
I'll be right there.
( chuckles )
Howard?
I'm gonna go see
Dr. Winslow.
I've got the coroner
on line one.
Tell him I need
those blood results yesterday.
Gotcha.
Hey, what about
your lunch?
I'm not hungry.
Can I have it?
Sure.
I've been looking through
some of my books,
and most bats attack in areas where
it's easiest to draw blood.
They go for the ankles
and the neck.
Yeah?
But these bats didn't just
take blood. They took flesh.
I can see that.
They ate this dog
like he was dinner.
This is just like
Professor Fuller--
Exactly.
Here's something else that's
really weird. Listen to this.
When a bat bites
it's host--
yeah,
like you invited them--
their saliva contains
small amounts
of procaine hydrochloride.
- What's that?
- Well, it numbs the pain.
The host puts up
less of a fight.
But these bats,
the ones who killed Omar--
I took some tissue samples
and ran some tests.
Their saliva
contained 20 times
the regular amount
of procaine hydrochloride.
What does that mean?
It means the more they attack,
the less you feel.
So what causes a bat
to turn killer like that?
I don't know.
A disease, or some kind
of genetic engineering.
Okay, wait.
You want me to go
into my boss' office
and tell him
that these deaths
were caused
by mutant killer bats?
Yep.
I don't think so.
I need proof.
I need a bat.
I need to connect
the fangs with the bite marks.
Ah, so now you want
the dogcatcher's help.
I mean, I figured
you'd like to help
and thought I'd just
give you a break here.
Gee, thanks.
So?
Come on,
what do we do?
Well, bats love caves.
There's only one
in the area.
Great.
When do we go?
It's probably safest during
the day when they're asleep.
Right, we don't want
to wake any of them up.
No, we don't.
And I have some
cave exploring equipment.
This is your
cave exploring equipment?
What?
You can do better?
I guess not.
Why do we have
to wear this stuff, anyway?
Protection.
Okay.
How'd you find
this place?
Teenagers come up here
and make out at night.
And you know
this because?
Because I caught my daughter up here
with her boyfriend one night.
- What about you?
- What about me?
You done any parking
at the bat cave lately?
Not since
I left LA.
Left your boyfriend behind?
Ex-boyfriend.
He moved in with another woman.
Ooh, boy.
When they move in with someone
else that's a pretty good sign
that your relationship
might be in trouble.
Oh, man, I cannot believe
I have to wear all this stuff.
I must look ridiculous.
It's not a fashion show.
You're out here
in the middle of nowhere.
No one's gonna see you.
Are you afraid that
someone's gonna laugh at you?
All right,
you're right.
( laughs )
What?
You look ridiculous.
- John?
- Yeah?
- Maybe I should tell you.
- What?
I have this thing
about bats.
I'm not afraid
of felons with guns...
but bats just
give me the creeps.
Well, news flash. Duh.
Bats give
everyone the creeps.
No, I take that back.
I saw this guy
on the Discovery Channel once,
who put this bat right here--
John.
Okay.
All right.
Watch your head.
Oww!
What are we looking for?
Bat droppings.
( screaming )
- ( laughs maniacally )
- ( screams )
It's okay. It's okay.
It's just there was
this big spider
in this icky web,
and I--
Settle down.
You're all right.
Let's just keep going.
Come on.
You're all right.
What do bat droppings
look like?
You know what cow droppings
look like, right?
Yes.
Bat droppings are the same,
only smaller.
Cute.
That's real cute.
( bats squealing )
Sounds like
they're overhead.
They could be.
This is as far
as you can go.
We don't find them here,
we won't find them anywhere.
Oh, darn.
What's wrong
with the light?
I don't know.
Can you fix it?
Probably just needs
a good whack.
The only thing that scares me
more than bats is the dark.
- I wish you hadn't done that.
- Why?
( bats squealing )
( screaming )
Why did they do that?
The flare.
They were trying
to get away from the light.
I think they were fruit bats,
just normal everyday fruit bats.
Not the kind
we're looking for.
How can you be sure?
Because we're
not dead and bloody.
Oh, good, that makes me feel
so much better.
Genny: One professor,
one ferocious guard dog--
both dead.
A coincidence?
I think not.
The number one suspect?
Bats.
Violent,
aggressive,
flesh-eating,
blood-sucking bats!
I'm sorry, miss,
you can't tape this.
Is it an official
crime scene?
No.
I look ridiculous.
We're here
with John Winslow,
former small town
vet-turned-bat-hunter.
What's going on here, sir?
- Am I in focus?
- Yep.
- The light's good?
- I think so.
Framed up
nice and tight?
Uh-huh.
If you don't turn
that camera off right now,
you're grounded
until you're 40.
( beeps off )
( car alarm beeps )
- Does Kramer know you're here?
- Not a clue, boss.
Okay. Are we ready?
As ready as we're
ever gonna be.
We were waiting
for you, Mr. Hart.
All right.
Let's go.
This property is in
the middle of my golf course.
I promised my home buyers
a golf course,
and this house is in the middle
of the seventh fairway.
Shut up!
Sam, how are we doing on this
so-called murder investigation?
- It's all under control.
- It better be.
I expect to close most of my deals
at the dance on Friday night.
Yeah I hear you daughter's
gonna be Miss Apple Queen.
Miss Apple Blossom.
And yes, that is
the icing on the cake.
Your job, besides, mmm...
is to make sure that nobody
touches my icing.
Is that clear?
No touching of the icing.
It's taken care of.
All right.
Let's go.
You let me
talk to Willy.
He's owned
this farm forever.
All right, all right,
I'm coming.
Hello, Chief.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, Willy.
There's no easy way to say this.
It's after midnight and you should be
off the property by now.
- This is my land.
- So beat it, ol' man!
What are you talking about?
My contract says I got 30 days.
That's enough time for me
to bring in my apple crop,
and make the payment.
That contract was subject
to the terms and conditions
of the amendment.
- What amendment?
- This one.
You see this here?
We both initialed it.
- Those aren't my initials.
- Yes, they are.
What, are you trying
to cheat Mr. Hart?
This says that you had until
midnight tonight to vacate.
You're not gonna make me
pack up my stuff
and leave in the middle
of the night, are ya?
( grunts )
You didn't have to come out here
in the middle of the night.
That's okay. Julia Roberts
canceled our date, anyway.
That's funny.
I have to solve this by tomorrow
so I do appreciate it.
Well, at least it beats
vaccinating a pit bull.
- Well, I'm glad of one thing.
- What's that?
- Those bats haven't come back.
- Yeah.
Over here--
Fuller's desk.
Okay, boss,
all their junk's in the back.
See that tree
over there?
I can remember the day
my father planted it.
I was five.
When it got big enough
he put a tire swing on it
for me and my sister.
He took care of that tree
until the day he died.
That's a really sweet story.
Don't hit the mailbox
on the way out.
( bats squealing )
Yuck.
No kidding.
Disgusting.
This guy sure was
into bats.
It's almost
like an obsession.
I know. He was them
all labeled too.
Red bat,
Southern yellow,
Mexican free tail,
vampire bat.
What's this?
( Ally groans )
If Kramer comes back,
I want you to handcuff him
to a fencepost
and call Chief Taylor.
With pleasure.
You know, I've been driving past
this farm since I was a kid.
Yeah? Take a good look.
Two days from now
it won't be here.
Get off my car.
( squealing )
( screaming )
This is just weird.
He has notes
not only on bats,
but on sea snakes
and leeches and--
Things that suck blood
for 500, Alex.
I wonder
what's in here.
Yuck.
- Ahh.
- Oh, boy.
Both: Ahh!
Could we please
not open any more drawers?
Wait a second.
Bingo!
Morning, Howard.
They don't pay me nearly enough,
- not for this.
- Will you be okay?
I don't know. Two dead bodies
in one week. It's ridiculous.
Scottsville hasn't seen
a crime spree this bad
since those kids siphoned
the Big Gulp machine at 7-1 1.
- Is Ally here?
- Over there,
Iooking at Louis,
or what's left of him.
You take it easy.
We'll have to stop
meeting like this.
- Louis.
- Yeah, I heard.
- Just like the first?
- Worse.
Nah, come on.
Nothing could be worse--
okay, it's worse.
What was Louis doing here?
This is Willy Kramer's farm.
Not since midnight last night.
It now belongs to the king of:
"no money down and easy
monthly payments."
My guess is Louis was attacked
after Hart and Taylor left.
Any luck with
that computer you found?
Not exactly.
I know it's Professor Fuller's,
but I need his password.
- Did you try his birthday?
- First thing I tried.
- What about his social security number?
- Second thing.
- What else do you have?
- Not much...
except the victim managed
to take a couple of them with him.
Courtesy of Professor Fuller.
- John: How do you know?
- Bands on their legs.
I want a bat.
Can I have a bat?
Please?
Please, can I have a bat?
- John: Hmm.
- What's the matter?
Guess how big an average
bat's fangs are,
in millimeters.
- A hundred millimeters.
- Come on.
A bat would look like a walrus
if they were that large.
You guessed too high.
You ruined
what I was going to say.
You should guess small, and then
when I tell you, you're surprised.
Ah-ha, I see.
Let me guess again.
Fangs on a bat.
One millimeter.
Wrong. Three.
That's so much bigger
than I would have guessed.
Now guess how big the fangs
are on the bats Fuller bred.
- Two millimeters.
- No. Six. They're twice as long.
Somehow, Fuller managed
to genetically engineer these bats
to be more aggressive
and to have longer fangs.
There are 500 killers
on the loose
and the Apple Blossom Dance
is tonight.
- John: Where are you going?
- Go see Chief Taylor.
We need a dusk till dawn curfew.
Nobody in this town is safe.
I've got to go
shut down the dance.
( John screams )
Murray!
Come on.
Yeah!
Yeah.
Taylor: Cancel the dance,
shut down the Apple Festival,
impose a curfew.
Are you insane?
You haven't seen the bodies.
Look at these pictures.
Those people died horrible,
violent deaths.
Have you personally
seen an attack?
No.
Then stop,
until you have proof.
I have proof. I examined
a bat that killed Louis.
If somebody dies tonight at the dance,
the blood is on your hands.
Because of some little micies
- with wings flying around?
- Yes!
Because of that,
you want me to tell people,
"Lock yourselves up
at home and stay there"?
Now you listen to me.
I told you there are too many
little people in this town
that depend
on this time of year.
So if I catch you at the dance,
saying anything to anybody,
or trying to cause trouble,
you can just hand me your badge.
As of right now,
this investigation is over.
Pack up everything
and send it to storage.
- But Chief--
- Do it!
This town has
too many little people.
- You heard.
- Everybody heard.
- He's so full of it.
- What do you mean?
The chief doesn't care about
the little people in this town.
But Hart sells most of his homes
to out-of-towners.
And most of them get their first taste
of Scottsville at the Apple Festival.
- The Chief's in for a cut.
- He's what?
He's on Hart's payroll.
He won't shut down the festival.
He'd lose too much money.
You'd have a better chance to ask
the Pope to cancel Christmas.
And by the way,
you didn't hear it from me.
Maybe the bats
won't attack tonight.
John: I doubt that.
They've attacked every night so far.
Then, we'd better get
to the dance before dark.
Yeah, uh...
this doesn't mean I'll actually
have to dance, does it?
You'll have to dance
with somebody,
or you'll look out of place.
It's been a long time since
I've been on a dance-floor.
Let me refresh your memory.
- Come here.
- What, right here?
Stand right there.
This hand goes here.
- That hand goes up in the air--
- Yeah, I know.
I know.
I'm not a cactus.
You can get closer.
- You're not a cactus.
- Not a cactus.
So, you just sort
of move your feet...
and follow me,
and you're dancing.
I'm dancing.
Whoa, Mr. W.
- You move fast.
- We were actually...
comparing arm lengths.
- Logan almost got a speeding ticket.
- John: What?
I would have, but I had
too many soda cans on my dash.
- You're lucky you only got a warning.
- I don't understand. Soda cans?
The aluminum messed up
the police radar.
How many aluminum cans
do we have in the recycling bin?
Bunches. Why?
I know.
I could fill my van with them,
- so we don't get a ticket tonight.
- John: That's not what I mean.
What I'm saying is if we cut
the cans up in little pieces,
we might be able to interfere
with the bats' radar.
- I can't wait to catch that on tape.
- You'll be waiting a long time,
- 'cause you're not going to the dance.
- But, Daddy--
John:
Honey, three people have died.
- You won't be the fourth.
- But this is the biggest story ever.
That's it.
You are staying here.
And I can't believe
I'm saying this.
I want Logan to stay with you.
- Dad.
- Oh.
Woman: I haven't been
to anything like this in years.
Man: Can't do much dancing
in these shoes.
Woman #2:
You'll love this place.
I got apple butter
and apple jelly.
What an incredible town.
I bought a hand-made quilt,
only $800.
You should see
the new house we just picked.
Parks.
Did I not make myself
clear earlier?
No, sir, you did.
- I just thought--
- You thought what?
That you'd warn people
they can be eaten alive,
maybe shut down the dance?
I told you what I'd do
- if I you tried to make trouble.
- John: Honey, I'm sorry I'm late.
I was wondering
where you were.
Hit some traffic.
Couldn't be helped.
What?
- You look terrific.
- Really?
Yeah.
You don't look like a cop.
Where did
you hide your gun?
Wouldn't you like to know?
Yeah.
Is there something
I can help you with, Chief?
Well, I--
I didn't know that you--
Councilman Woods! Excuse me.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
He would have fired me.
Yeah, I know.
It was quick thinking.
Well...
anything to save your job.
Anything?
I didn't want you
to get fired.
So you...
forced yourself to kiss me?
Umm...
- somebody had to.
- Somebody had--
well, thanks for being so brave.
What are you getting
all bent out of shape for?
Nothing.
Oh boy.
( rock music playing )
Hart: Ladies and gentlemen,
a Hart home is a home for keeps.
We use only the highest quality
construction material.
I promise you, I defy you
to find a more beautiful house
at this price, anywhere.
- And it's on a golf course.
- Not just a golf course.
It's got a 6,800-yard
championship golf course.
And this town
is safe to live in?
Safe?
As long as Chief Taylor
isn't hitting from the 1 6th tee,
- you'll be just fine.
- ( all laugh )
Please, everybody, come around.
- Who would have thought?
- Howard Spiegel, king of swing.
Should we dance?
No.
From the dance-floor,
we could keep our eyes
on the windows and doors
at the same time.
Okay.
Remember to keep
an eye out for my dad.
Logan: Right.
Let's go up here.
- Genny: Great view.
- Logan: Excellent.
- Where's my camera?
- Here.
All the windows are secured.
Doors are all shut.
What am I missing?
Did you see anything outside
that looked dangerous?
- I looked for bats.
- And?
- I didn't see any.
- Maybe we worried for nothing.
John: Maybe.
You know, if I could get
a bat attack on tape,
I bet I could sell it to Nova...
or National Geographic.
Or America's Funniest Pets.
- Are you sure we're safe up here?
- Couldn't be any safer.
And this is a family town?
Are you kidding?
It's country living that brought me
so close to my daughter here.
Daddy, you're wrinkling
my charmeuse.
Apple of my eye.
Look...
I'm sorry about that remark
I made outside,
about kissing you
just to save your job.
I kind of liked it.
Kind of?
Umm...
actually, I really liked it.
it's just been a long time since
I put my lips on someone else's.
How long?
Not since I gave
a collie mouth-to-mouth.
Well, if it's not
Mr. I'm-Not-Ready-To-Date-Yet.
Hmm?
- Who was that?
- I massaged her cat once.
Look at them.
Logan:
They're acting like
they're having a good time
or something.
Genny: Don't they know
how ridiculous they look?
My grandfather
does this sometimes.
He goes out and acts
like a regular person.
How come?
Usually, it's because
he forgot his medication.
( drum roll )
As you all know,
it's time to crown
this year's Miss Apple Blossom.
You know, I'm a lucky man.
I have a beautiful daughter
and a lovely family,
good health, and it's all because
I live in a town like Scottsville,
where there's no stress,
and oodles of clean air and water.
I invite each
and everyone of you
to visit me
at the Hart Homes booth.
Remember my motto,
"Hart is where the home is."
Even if you have bad credit,
I want--
okay, all right,
Miss Apple Blossom.
It's time to crown
this year's winner,
and I am proud to tell you...
it's my daughter, Alexis.
- ( crowd sighs )
- The judges have good taste.
( laughter )
Alexis Hart,
I hereby crown you...
Scottsville's own...
Miss Apple Blossom.
( crowd claps )
Ain't she pretty?
Wow, me?
I can't believe it. This is
the happiest moment of my life.
Alexis:
I want to thank my daddy,
and Chief Taylor, my dermatologist,
and my cosmetic surgeon--
( screeching )
This is Genny Winslow,
reporting from Scottsville.
This is a bat attack
we're witnessing!
John: The lights!
- They're not working.
- Maybe it's the wrong switch.
- We have to act fast.
- Plan B.
Everything is under control.
Calm down.
- Shoo! Get out of here!
- Oh my God!
Let me get you to the car.
I want--
Slow it down, people.
Don't panic.
Slow it down. Just relax.
- ( screeching )
- Genny: The light.
- Logan: What?
- The spotlight.
Oh yeah.
- Let's do it.
- You think it'll work?
I hope so.
- Logan, this is so awesome.
- Come on, get some. Want some light?
Don't mess with the man.
It's working.
Yes!
I like Plan B.
- Man: Come on! Run!
- ( screaming )
Miss Smith, you wanted
a place near the school.
Aren't you the schoolteacher?
You two.
- Come here. Come on.
- Hart, tear up my check.
But you signed a contract.
Buyer's Remorse. We've got
72 hours to change our minds.
- It's state law.
- I'll sue.
- Woman: Just try.
- We're both lawyers.
- Sam.
- I've never seen anything like this.
Everybody wants
their money back. I'm ruined!
I'll think of something.
- Like what?
- I don't know...
This bat thing happens
once every 1 000 years...
- the position of the moon.
- The moon?
You'd better do
better than that.
Every cent I own's tied
up in this new development.
If it goes bust, so do I!
And so do you.
The moon?
Sir! The place--
I'll give you the pool for free. Oh.
That aluminum can thing
was brilliant.
Yes, I know.
Screwed up the bats' radar.
They couldn't see
where they were going.
- It was great!
- Ow!
Sit still.
Why didn't the bats attack you?
Because I'm wearing
aluminum underwear.
- I'd like to see that.
- I bet you would.
Ow!
Doctors make
the worst patients.
I'm saying ow so you'll think
I'm weak and helpless.
I already think that.
What about handsome and sexy?
Um... I'm still stuck
on weak and helpless.
But you're missing
handsome and sexy.
What exactly am I missing?
This.
Genny:
How was the dance?
It was like Pearl Harbor
with music.
- Logan: Huh?
- The bats showed up,
but the aluminum can thing
worked great.
I'm just glad you listened
to me and stayed home.
I'm glad we did too.
- Sounds scary.
- What's really scary
is if these bats are allowed to mix
with the local bat population,
it'll make the problem
1 00 times worse.
I am not living
in an aluminum foil house.
I was looking
through some of the footage
I didn't use in my documentary,
- and I found these street signs.
- Street signs?
Apparently, whenever
Hart bulldozes another farm,
he names the street
after the former owner. Look.
Miller Lane.
John:
I remember the Millers.
Demarco Terrace.
Genny: Fuller Place.
George Fuller.
I remember him. He was
a sweet old guy. What?
Didn't all this start
when Arthur Fuller died?
Did George Fuller
have any family?
- Genny?
- I don't know.
We have to crack
Arthur Fuller's laptop
and get to his files.
Logan, John says
you're a computer whiz.
- So, it's time to prove it.
- Can we download some MP3s first?
Logan, no.
Aw...
all right.
( screeching )
Morning, Logan.
- Logan.
- I finished painting the driveway, Dad.
It's me, John.
Oh, hi, Mr. C.
- It's Mr. W.
- Oh yeah, right.
Any luck breaking
into Fuller's files?
No, sorry.
I tried every password,
decryption schemes, websites...
Thanks for trying.
- There's good news, though.
- What's that?
I found out I'm related
to one of the Three Stooges.
Well,
you must be very proud.
Yeah.
Taylor?
I saw an ambulance outside.
Is he still alive?
Not quite.
- Then why the ambulance?
- That's for Howard.
He discovered the body.
Don't go in there.
I've never seen anything like it.
Can I get a pillow?
He'll live.
- What's that?
- I don't know.
- We found it near the body.
- Some kind of police equipment?
Nothing I've ever seen before.
Have you noticed something?
With the exception
of Professor Fuller,
all of these attacks seem
to be connected to Karl Hart.
You're right.
Hey.
I hear that Sam Taylor
was killed last night.
- Is this true?
- I'm afraid so.
Good grief.
Right here,
in police headquarters.
Hart: What is going on
with this town?
It'd be easier to sell
real estate that was on fire.
I've got a mob standing
outside my office.
They're demanding
their money back.
Plus your best friend
was killed last night.
Oh yeah.
Yes, there is that.
- Are you the chief of police now?
- Yes, I am,
till the City Council
appoints someone else.
I want an end to this.
Do you understand?
Whatever's going on,
I want it to stop.
Pronto! Today!
I want you to get
to the bottom of it,
and I want it to just stop!
Hart:
This is ridiculous.
I think he's taking it
pretty well.
Genny:
Right. Got it.
( computer beeps )
Computer voice:
Welcome back, Professor Fuller.
Yes! I'm in!
- That's great!
- Not really.
I have no idea
what I'm looking at.
Genny:
Ah-ha. Right. Okay.
Thank you very much. Bye.
- Logan cracked the code.
- What have you got?
We don't know.
Looks like Fuller had
a special file on audio research.
- But that wasn't his field.
- Yeah, but it makes sense.
The lab assistants said
they had to activate
some high-frequency audio device
when they fed the bats.
Well, I'm no expert,
but my guess is
that most of the time,
this little baby plays
the bats' favorite tune.
But when it plays
their dinnertime tune,
you're history.
Which means
that it wasn't an accident,
or some freak of nature.
Taylor was targeted.
And Louis.
But what about Fuller?
Genny:
I just spoke to the County Clerk
at the Hall of Records.
One of the first farms
that Carl Hart foreclosed on
was owned by George Fuller...
father of Arthur Fuller.
It would make sense he'd be
the one to start all this.
- But he's dead.
- And Hart is next.
No, Monday's too late.
Woman on speaker:
But we're not open weekends.
I don't care.
Get them to open it on Sunday!
- This is a medical emergency.
- Miss, I'm sorry--
Hold on, let me get
rid of this other call.
- Hart Homes.
- Ally: Is Mr. Hart there?
He's not here right now.
Bye-bye.
- Ally: Wait. Is this Alexis?
- Yes.
Ally:
This is Detective Parks.
- Can you tell me where he is?
- I don't know where he is.
Even if I did, he told me
not to tell anyone.
Ally: Listen to me.
These bat attacks--
I have reason to believe
your father might be next.
He's in extreme danger.
Do you know where he might be?
No, but he got a call
20 minutes ago.
Someone offered to buy him out
at twice what he paid.
- Ally: Did you happen--
- Thank you for calling Hart Homes.
- Okay, I'm back.
- Receptionist: As I was saying,
the doctor does not perform
cosmetic surgery on Sundays.
You're not getting it.
I have a supermarket opening on Monday.
Alexis said that someone offered
to buy out her father
- at twice what he paid.
- Genny: Sounds like a setup to me.
Yeah, could be.
But if this person wants
the bats to attack Hart,
they'll need
another homing device.
- Yeah?
- So, if we can build a device
that detects
high-frequency sound waves...
Then we could triangulate the location
and find out who's behind this.
- Is that possible?
- I don't know.
Logan, can you build
a device like that?
A device that detects
ultra-high-frequency audio?
No way.
They sell them at Radio Hut
for 30 bucks, though.
Ally: I'll try scanning
north-northwest.
Anything?
Nothing.
But then again, I don't know
what I'm looking for.
Any signal over 20 kilohertz,
outside the range
of human hearing.
And it'll be a steady tone.
- ( steady buzz )
- Hold on.
What do you think?
Yeah, could be.
Give the frequency to Logan.
Logan, we're getting
a tone at 23-950.
Copy that,
two-three-niner-fiver.
Genny: Hold on.
Yes, there it is.
Heading at...
5-6-4.
We got it at fiver-sixer...
four-er?
- Where is it coming from?
- Ally: I don't know yet.
On this map, Route 6,
looks like.
That's the Kramer farm.
Logan, on speaker:
Did you find the location?
- Yeah--
- Wait a minute.
Yeah, but you kids have
to promise not to go there.
We won't.
John, on speaker: The audio tone
is coming from Hickory Lake,
the south shore.
Okay. We won't go there.
- Over and out.
- John: Over and out.
That's not the location.
I know. But tell them
not to go there,
and that's where
they'll go for sure.
You're a genius.
That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
The lake isn't in line
with our coordinates.
It's nowhere near them.
Well, what else is?
A Dairy Queen...
a mountain...
and the Kramer farm.
Both:
The Kramer farm!
( screeching )
Fuller: Don't worry.
They won't hurt you.
Not yet.
My babies won't do a thing...
till they're told.
And they never let me down.
Ally: So you have
the coroner's report?
What does it say?
The dental records of Arthur Fuller
don't match the body.
The victim was someone
named Sheldon Broydo?
Okay, Howard, listen.
Get into evidence lockup.
But it's locked. That's why
they call it an evidence lockup.
- You're the only one with a key.
- Ally: Break the lock.
- And who will pay for that?
- I will. All right?
Do you remember last year
we seized explosives
- from that truck on the interstate?
- Uh-huh.
I need you to get a few pounds
of C-4 and a timer,
and meet us at the Kramer farm.
This doesn't involve seeing
dead people, does it?
Let me talk to him.
Howard, it's John.
We might have
these bats cornered.
And if we do, we need
something to make sure
they will never
attack again, okay?
Okay, all right,
I'll be there.
Ally: That's it, up ahead.
Cut the engine.
Kill the lights too.
This isn't the first time
we've met in a barn.
After you ruined my father,
he went in his barn and killed himself.
If I'd known
that was going to happen,
I'd never, never, have applied
the pressure I did.
Pressure?!
It was a trick.
He thought he had more time
on his loan.
You gave him 24 hours
to vacate the only home
he ever knew.
Hart:
Arthur--
may I call you Arthur?
When I foreclosed on your father's
farm, many years ago,
my partners and I may have...
falsified certain documents.
But I'm now willing
to give you a complete refund.
With interest...
and no questions asked.
Stop!
Stop it!
The time for deceit is over.
Hold it right there,
Fuller.
Put the gun down
or I'll push the button,
the one that'll end
all our lives.
You're bluffing.
Fuller:
You want to call my bluff?
It's a horrible way to die.
Yeah, we've seen.
It's a nice trick...
faking your own death
to avoid suspicion.
Thank you.
And thanks to Mr. Hart...
Scottsville's
become more urban.
We have more and more
homeless drifters than ever.
The body outside your lab.
One of our drifters
was kind enough to volunteer.
Volunteer. Yeah, right.
John: Is that what these attacks
are all about? Vengeance?
Yes.
Righting a wrong.
Carl here cheated
my father out of his land
and built a mini mall
where his farm used to be.
My father
was left with nothing!
Now it's time...
to bend our plows
back into swords
and destroy the urban slime
that sucks the lifeblood
from our sweet, simple town!
There you are.
I thought you'd be--
Hurry!
The timer's going.
- Well, turn it off.
- There's no stop button.
- There are no buttons at all.
- Somebody untie me!
John: Let's get out
of here! Come on!
John:
Come on, let's go! Go!
- What's happening?
- It's over.
- We're blowing up the barn.
- Little sooner than we thought.
- What about my babies?
- Give it up, Fuller.
What about the years
of scientific research
and the loving, the caring
that went into them?
You can't just--
- Ally: Hey!
- Ally!
- It's too late!
- Fuller: My babies!
My babies!
Thank goodness.
We're free of that nut.
Now I can get back to business.
The only place
you're going is to jail.
To jail for what?
Because of what you told Fuller
about his father's farm.
- I heard it all.
- John: So did I.
She heard, he heard.
So what?
So I swindled the old man
out of his land.
Big deal.
You haven't got any proof.
- It's your word against mine.
- Logan: I wouldn't say that.
We heard it too.
And I got it all on tape.
John: Good going, honey.
Thanks, Daddy.
Howard, place Mr. Hart
under arrest.
- Howard: Up against the car.
- Are you serious?
Up against the car, dogmeat.
You have the right
to remain silent.
If you refuse
the right to remain silent,
anything you say can and will be
used against you
- in a court of law.
- Hart: Ow!
Howard: You have the right
to an attorney...
This will get me in good
with the City Council.
Think they'll let me
keep my job?
I don't think you'll have
a problem, Chief.
Some honeymoon,
exploring caves for bats.
- Are you having fun?
- Most of the time.
You'll love this cave.
The guidebook says that over
a quarter of a million bats nest here.
Man, that's a lot of bats!
I hope I brought
enough videotape.
- John: What the--
- Ally: Oh, not again.
John: We're okay,
as long as no one lights...
a flare.
♪ I don't nothing
'bout chemistry ♪
♪ Except the kind
between you and me ♪
♪ Oh, I do know
that I love you, girl ♪
♪ Just take a trip
to rock around the world ♪
♪ Just like the Earth
needs the sun ♪
♪ I know that
you're the only one ♪
you're the girl for me ♪
♪ We got a bond,
we got an attraction ♪
♪ We got a chemical
nuclear reaction ♪
♪ I hold you close
and we start to kiss ♪
♪ It just doesn't get
any better than this ♪
♪ Sometimes I don't know
what to say ♪
♪ I guess it must be
in my DNA ♪
♪ You got my molecules
scrambled up ♪
♪ Then have another
peanut buttercup ♪
♪ Just like the Earth
needs the sun ♪
♪ I know that
you're the only one ♪
you're the girl for me ♪
♪ We got a bond,
we got an attraction ♪
♪ We got a chemical
nuclear reaction ♪
♪ I hold you close
and we start to kiss ♪
♪ It just doesn't get
any better than this ♪
♪ We got a bond,
we got an attraction ♪
♪ We got a chemical
nuclear reaction ♪
♪ I hold you close
and we start to kiss ♪
♪ It just doesn't get
any better than this ♪
♪ We got a bond,
we got an attraction ♪
♪ We got a chemical
nuclear reaction ♪
♪ I hold you close
and we start to kiss ♪
♪ It just doesn't get
any better than this ♪
♪ Better than this ♪
♪ It just doesn't get
any better than this. ♪