These'll be great.
Thank you.
[clears throat]
Ta-da!
What's this for?
Because I love you.
[alarm ringing]
[shouting]
[car screeches]
[screaming]
[gunshots]
[music playing]
MAN: Call 911!
No, stay back!
Nick?
Oh, no!
No, Nick!
Somebody, quickly!
Nick!
No, Nick!
No.
[music playing]
Nick?
What's that?
Nothing.
[buzzes]
You sure about this, ma'am?
It's not too late to go rightback to the station, you know.
Listen, any time you wantto leave, night or day,
you call me.
Good luck.
You're going to need it.
[buzzes]
SECURITY GUARD: Yes?
What do you want?
Hi.
I'm Elizabeth Guinness.
I believe I'm expected.
[beeping]
RICHARD KEATON:
You're too young.
Dr. Keaton?
You can stay until morning.
You'll find a room prepared.
Mrs. Pram will
attend to your needs.
Wait.
[music playing]
Dr. Keaton?
Dr. Keaton.
Dr. Keaton, please.
I'm not too young.
I'm very experienced, and Ihave excellent references.
My son has driven
off three other
professional and
highly-qualified nannies
in the last four months.
What makes you think that youcan succeed where they failed?
Well, I happen to specializein working with children
that are challenged.
I grew up with four brothers.
I don't know.
Please just give me the
month's trial period,
and then we'll see.
Please.
All right.
But you won't get very
far as long as you
see Andrew as a challenge.
He studies on his own,and he is best left to be
by himself as much as possible.
I am not to be disturbed
except in emergencies.
Mrs. Pram.
Dr. Keaton, one other thing.
What are the custody
arrangements?
Does Andrew spend
time with his mother?
MRS PRAM: Yes, sir?
Please come up here.
Andrew's mother is
dead, Ms. Guinness.
[gunshot]
Please do not
speak of her again.
Mrs. Pram will take care of you.
Please wait for
her on the landing.
[music playing]
Yes.
Good night.
Ms. Guinness?
[humming]
[shrieks]
You must be the new nanny.
Haven't you been told to knockbefore you enter a lady's room?
You're not a lady.
You're an employee.
I most certainly
am a lady, and I
expect to be treated like one.
You stay here.
My name is Elizabeth Guinness.
My friends call me Liz.
You must be Andy.
Andrew Philip Albert Keaton.
The Albert is for Einstein.
You may call me Master
Andrew if you wish,
but Andy is out of the question.- There.
I'm decent, but I'd like
to get dressed properly.
Then I'll make you
your favorite breakfast
and we can get to
know each other, OK?
Can I watch?
I've only learned female
anatomy from books
and internet searches.
I've never seen an adult
female naked before.
Really?
Well you're not
going to see one how.
Skedaddle.
I think I'm going tocall you nanny number four.
Why?
Because you're going to goaway like the other three.
I thought that was a closet.
It's kind of
like a big closet.
It's where I'm stored.
Breakfast in five minutes, OK?
Mrs. Pram goes
to the supermarkets
on Wednesday mornings.
I don't think she'll
be very pleased
with you using her kitchenwithout her permission.
I think she'll get used to it.
Here.
Napkin?
Napkin, where?
Right-hand drawer over there.
Thank you.
You look different
with clothes on.
Don't you have any
jeans and sneakers?
Of course, but
I don't like them.
Why?
Here.
I thought you could
show me around.
Perhaps we could go riding.
Now those clothes
might get dirty.
I hate horses.
Besides, I'm much too busy.
Father left for
Geneva this morning,
and I want to finish readingthe almanac before he returns.
You're going to finish thealmanac before he returns?
Yes.
Father read the phone
book when he was three.
Well, he didn't sayanything to me about a trip.
He didn't tell me either.
I downloaded his
computer scheduler.
He didn't say goodbye to you?
No.
Father has no time for
that kind of stuff.
What kind of stuff?
Unscientific stuff.
You should be wearing
your uniform, you know.
Nannies wear uniforms.
Well, this nanny doesn't.
So I guess it's just
you and me, huh?
We're not alone.
She's here.
Who, Mrs. Pram?
Well, who else lives here?
Mother.
Andy, your father toldme your mother passed away.
She's still here.
There are 36 deaths
by snakebite recorded
every year in thecontinental United States.
Yeah, how do you know that?
Just download the insurancecompany's mortality tables.
I thought you said you
knew about computers.
Well I do, but I'm
not as morbid as you.
[music playing]
[squeals]
Stop, stop!
Don't you know what water willdo to a scientific calculator?
This is a very
delicate instrument.
Shake then you
grasp like that.
And then you slide
it and you grip it.
And then you get your
thumb here in that,
and then you do like this.
You [inaudible] a couple, shh.
And then you pull out,
you got to go boom.
And then you blow the
smoke from the gun.
Whoosh.
Stick it in your holster.
It's really cool.
What do you think?
I think it's silly,
and I also think
you'd do much better if youread one or two of these.
Read this one first,
and then this one.
And I'd advise you to geta pen and a piece of paper,
because they have a numberof equations in them.
She's dribbling
down the court,
And she's coming
at a high speed.
And it looks like
the [inaudible] team
is going to win thechampionship of the world.
And she passes it to
Andrew Keaton, who's
putting it up for three points.
Come on, Andy.
Shoot!
Shoot.
Go on!
[window creaks]
Who's that?
ANDREW KEATON: Did it scare you?
Did what scared me?
When the window crashed open.
Well it woke me, but it
was just a gust of wind.
How did you know about that?
It was her.
Who?
The ghost.
What ghost, Andy?
My mother.
You're nowhere near as
beautiful as she is.
Of course I'm not.
Do you talk with her?
No.
Is she scary to you?
Look, don't do the
shrink stuff on me, OK?
It doesn't work.
She's a ghost, OK?
She doesn't want you here.
[music playing]
Andy.
My mother was murdered.
Ask father.
Do you think Dr.Keaton will be back soon?
He doesn't tell me his
schedule, Ms. Guinness.
Have you been here
long, Mrs. Pram?
Ever since Dr.
Keaton was a boy
and went away to
school in England.
I took care mostly of Blain.
So you knew Mrs. Keaton.
Everybody knew Alycia Keaton.
How did she die?
She fell from the east tower.
Oh, my god.
Was there an inquest?
Dr. Keaton is a very wealthyman, a famous scientist.
People like to gossip about him.
So what was the verdict?
They called it a suicide.
How old was Andy?
What happened to him?
Andy was three.
He went away to live
with Alycia's parents.
They died in a boating
accident six months ago,
and he came back here againto live with his father.
Poor little boy.
Mrs. Pram, how havethings been between them?
I'm sorry.
Good night, Mrs. Pram.
[music playing]
[clock chiming]
RICHARD KEATON: I seeyou've found the library.
Yeah.
Hi.
It's a beautiful room.
I'm afraid I can't
take credit for it.
Generations of Keaton
women have conspired
to make this room what it is.
Would you like
something to drink?
No.
No, thank you.
So how was Geneva?
Geneva was a hotel room, auniversity conference center,
and an airport like anyother scientific meeting,
only this time withchocolates and cuckoo clocks.
Is it OK me being here?
Well I'm generally not inhere until after midnight.
I doubt if we'll be
in each other's way.
No.
So how was your
trial by Andrew?
Was it a test?
Well, my schedule
has nothing to do
with your responsibilities.
It was good.
Andrew seems to think thathis mother was murdered.
I thought I told younot to mention his mother.
You did.
I'm sorry.
I suppose his
grandparents told him.
They despised me.
Why?
Because they
believe that I did it.
Why did Andy go to live
with his grandparents?
Because they wanted
him, and I didn't.
It was as simple as that.
Until they capsized
their sailboat, and then
I had to have him.
How do you feel about him now?
If you'll excuse me,
I'd like some privacy.
I have a lot of reading to do.
Of course.
Good night.
[music playing]
[knocking on door]
I'm sorry.
Ms. Guinness.
Don't worry.
I don't kill nannies.
[slams door]
Andy, would you take
this up to your father?
- No.
- Well, please.
You're going that way.
I don't want to disturb him.
Well Andy, he has to eat.
Please.
Oh, all right.
Thank you.
Can you manage?
Yes.
Why did Alycia's parents tellAndy his mother was murdered?
They never accepted that Mrs.Keaton could take her own life.
Didn't they understandwhat it could do to Andy?
[music playing]
[knocking on door]
Yes, Andrew.
What is it?
Welcome home.
I brought you breakfast.
Thank you.
Look, I'm real busy right now.
We'll talk later, OK?
I'll come down for dinner.
Yes, father.
Uh-oh.
They don't sound
like very happy feet.
Andy, what happened?
What happened?
It's all your fault.
You made me go up there.
I knew I shouldn't have.
I was right about you.
[slams door]
What on earth happened?
Andy is crying his
eyes out downstairs.
Now you've been
gone for two weeks.
Can't you give him a
moment of your time?
Does this constitute
an emergency?
Is there some kind of problem?
Well yes, I think
there is a problem.
Your son Andrew thinks
his mother is a ghost.
Now I can't bring him backfrom that without your help.
If you can't accept theterms of your engagement,
you are free to leave.
I don't understand you.
Ms. Guinness, do you know whatI do if I reach a conclusion
that doesn't make any sense?
I re-examine my premises.
He's not a problem in physics.He's a little boy.
What has made you so-called?
A ghost, Ms. Guinness.
[slams door]
A ghost.
[music playing]
[neighs]
But I thought
you hated horses.
Hello.
Oh, he's beautiful.
What's his name?
Her name is Amber.
She was my mother's favorite.
Have you ever ridden her?
No.
Well you know, I love to ride.
So maybe we could
go out some time.
120 Americans were renderedquadriplegic last year.
There were 18 fatalities.
Is that a yes or no?
You ride her.
[honking]
There's uncle Blain!
Blain, Jilly!
US genuine army surplus.
Picked them up in a
junk shop in Barbados.
They work.
I think they'll
need some fiddling,
but I thought you'd like them.
Your father and I had thesame pair when we were kids.
Of course, Richard
took them apart
and we never could get
them to work again.
They're great.
Thanks, uncle Blain.
They're terrific.
Hi.
Well hello.
Blain Keaton, official
family black sheep.
This is Jillian Zale, my friend.
Hi.
Care for a drink
while I'm pouring?
Oh, no thank you.
I'm Liz Guinness.
I'm Andy's--
She's my new nanny.
Well, my brother's
taste in nannies
has definitely improved.
What are they, Andy?
Walkie-talkies.
If I replace the inductioncoils in the modulator circuits,
they should be effective
anywhere in the house.
So where is the famous man?
He's up in his office working.
Should I send word
that you're here?
My dear girl, he knew wewere here before you did.
Hi.
What a nice surprise, Jillian.
I thought you were going tospend the summer at the Cape.
Oh, Richard.
How could I stay away from you?
Blain.
Richard.
Oh, it's great to be
back in the country.
I'm so sick of the city.
I have a hankering toride your horses, Richard.
Well please do, Jillian.
They could use it.
I've not had time
to ride lately.
Why don't we go
tomorrow morning?
I can't.
My publisher will
kill me if I don't
finish my manuscript on time.
Oh, you're a writer.
And I am his muse.
Isn't that right, Blain?
I must say I was surprised tosee how happy Andrew was today.
Big change from the
last time I saw him.
Well, we have Ms.Guinness to thank for that.
She's working wonders with him.
Well she certainly is a stepup in the nanny department.
Makes me wish I
were eight again.
Still, better late than never.
If you'll excuse me,it's been a very long day.
Andy gets up very early.
Good night.
Liz?
Liz.
Are you really going to bed,or were you just choking
on the tension in there?
They don't like eachother very much, do they?
That's theunderstatement of the year.
How about you and
I having a drink?
OK.
Come on.
How long are you
staying for this time?
Long enough to
finish my manuscript.
Fine.
Then just keep out of my way.
Richard, I want
to sell the estate.
I've told you just give metime, and I will buy you out.
I'm not prepared
to wait that long.
I want to sell it now.
Oh, don't be so absurd.
This house was built by ourgreat-great-grandfather,
if you hadn't forgotten.
No, I haven't forgotten,as much as I would like to.
Do you really think this
is an appropriate place
for Andy to grow up in?
- Oh no, Blain.
Don't question what
I do for Andrew.
Your rules, your house.
Everything's got to be your way.
You're damn right.
No wonder Alycia
was so unhappy.
How dare you.
You know, I'd have
thought you to be
ashamed to show your face.
I have nothing
to be ashamed of.
Don't mind Blain.
No one else does.
He's not very subtle, is he?
He just can't imagine
a man and a woman
being alone in a place
like this and not
actually sleeping together.
So are you sleeping
with Richard?
No.
I'm sorry.
Blain must be rubbing off on me.
Cheers.
So you like to ride?
Oh, yes.
Especially these horses.
They're so good.
Do you ride?
Mhmm.
I grew up with horses.
Really?
Well we'll have to
ride together sometime.
I'd like that.
I don't understand why
Dr. Keaton keeps them.
I mean, he never goes near them.
Alycia loved them, andthey're part of the museum.
It must have been very
difficult for Dr. Keaton
after she died.
Depends on what you mean.
Luckily, she was my bestfriend, but she was no saint.
She liked two things in life,and used one to get the other--
money and men, and in
no particular order.
Really?
But she always
came back to Blain
before and after her marriage.
Why did he marry her?
Because he loved her.
She really was quite beautiful.
[rumbling]
That didn't take long.
[music playing]
[glass shattering]
[shouting]
Stop!
Stop it!
Stop it.
[crying]
I'm going to call it a night.
Andy?
[door creaking]
Andy, is that you?
[crying]
Andy.
Oh, Andy.
Mommy.
Oh, it's OK.
It's OK, darling.
It's OK.
[music playing]
Did my father kill my mother?
I don't think he could
do a thing like that.
So you're not leaving then?
No.
I told you I'm going to stay.
Besides, I quite like it here.
You're not scared of her?
Andy, there's no ghost.
Now sleep tight.
Don't that the bed bugs bite.
If they do, hit
them with your shoe.
I'm sorry.
For what?
For scaring you.
I made your window crash open.
You did that?
Yeah.
How did you do that?
I can't tell
you because you'll
tell all the other nannies,and then it won't work anymore
because they won't be scared.
Oh, you can't
tell me, can you?
Well, I think I'm just goingto tickle you until you
tell me exactly how you did it.
[laughter]
Do you give up?
- Yes, yes, yes.
- OK, tell me how.
Don't tickle me.
I've put magnets in
the window frames,
and I used a massive
electromagnetic pulse
to open and close the windows.
Not an electromagnetic pulse.
No, no, no.
Oh, my God, you're so clever.
Go to sleep.
[laughter]
Night night.
See you in the morning.
Good night, Liz.
Good night, Andy.
[music playing]
[gunshot]
[clock chiming]
[rustling]
Who's that?
Sorry.
I fell asleep.
I'm going.
Is Andrew all right?
Well, he was very upset.
He's asleep now.
Look, I'm very sorryabout that scene in there.
My brother and I have
some unresolved issues.
It must all seem
pretty pathetic.
Dr. Keaton, may I?
I think you should know
tonight, Andy asked
me if you murdered his mother.
Did he?
Well, I said I
didn't think so, but--
I appreciate the
vote of confidence.
I keep trying to
find the liar in you,
but I just don't see it.
Really?
You're one of the
few that doesn't.
I was lucky
enough to be married
to a man who didn't lie.
So I think I know
what to look for.
I didn't know that
you were married.
You never asked.
Are you still married?
No.
He died.
I'm sorry.
I'm becoming a little clumsy.
That's OK.
I don't understand you.
Now he's such a
wonderful little boy.
He's bright.
He's sensitive.
Why do you keep
pushing him away?
I provide him witheverything that he needs,
the best that money can buy.
Yeah, but he needs
love and affection.
That's what I hired you for.
Doesn't it bother you?
He's your son.
I provide for him,
but he is not my son.
[music playing]
Andy, are you ready?
[knocking on door]
Come on.
Let's go.
You can't go on a picnic
dressed like that.
I can dress any way I want.
You do.
I dress appropriately,
and so should you.
Put on your jeans and sneakers.
All right, on conditionthat you wear your uniform,
and don't forget the tie.
ELIZABETH GUINNESS: You'll
have to help me, OK?
One, two, three.
Get some stuff out of here.
[horses neighing]
Well, well.
And I thought you were going tobe working on your manuscript
this afternoon.
Well, Jillian
convinced me that it'd
be more fun to go riding.
Yeah, fun.
The story of your life, Blain.
You could lighten up a
little bit, big brother.
RICHARD KEATON: Go to hell.
[horses neighing]
Just, just further
than the real--
Andy, it's your father.
Hi.
Hello there.
ANDREW KEATON: Hi.
I see we're playing
truant this afternoon.
And you, Ms. Guinness,are looking very official.
Well, I lost a
negotiated settlement.
It's a one-time-only event.
This is good.
May I join you?
Oh, sure.
Andrew, I'm very sorry forwhat happened last night.
How come you and uncle
Blain always fight?
Andy, why don't
you tell your father
what you were just telling me?
Well go on, Andy.
Well, what I was
saying was at the moment
that the black hole
is formed, time
freezes on the event horizon.
And the last photons
of light that
escape after the
black hole is formed
are frozen in that moment.
It's not on the
event horizon, Andy.
It's an infinitesimal
distance above it.
You wouldn't detect
time-frozen photons
if they were at the horizon.
Well, why don't--
why don't you explain thedifference to us so we know.
Well you have to understandthere are no margins
for imprecision in science.
Andy.
Don't call me that.
Only Liz can call me Andy.
Only Liz!
Why did you bother
to come out here?
I was curious.
I couldn't imagine Andy--
Andrew, enjoying all this.
You were curious.
Well he is a child, and heneeds to learn how to play,
how to enjoy
sentiment and emotion.
Ms. Guinness, it seems thatyou are a bit of a romantic.
What is that supposed to mean?
It means that logic and reasonplay no part in your makeup.
Well, that's ridiculous.
I'm the most logical
person that I know.
I'm sorry if I
ruined your picnic.
He has to learn.
[music playing]
Dr. Keaton, you
go to him, please.
Just make it up to him.
Invite him to your lab tomorrow.
It doesn't have to be for long.
I know he'd love
to see you working.
Please.
I don't know how you can
say he's not your son.
You're exactly like him.
Pretty picture,
don't you think?
[thunder]
Damn.
[screaming]
Liz!
Liz?
Liz, wake up.
Come on.
She's at my window and
she wants to come in.
The lights won't go on.
What time is it?
It's 17 minutes after 3:00.
[screams]
ELIZABETH GUINNESS: It's OK.
Let me get a flashlight.
It's OK.
Come on.
[thunder]
ANDREW KEATON: That's her!
Stay here.
[screams]
It's just a tree.
It's OK.
There really aren't
any ghosts, Andy.
Andy, are you all right?
There was a tree
tapping at the window.
Yeah, power's off
in the whole house.
Oh.
Well, why don't we go
down to the library?
At least we know
there's a fire there.
Yeah, why not?
Can't work like this anyway.
Good.
I'll go and put on a robe.
I'll see you down there.
OK.
[whimpers]
Can we go now?
Are you still scared?
No.
Good.
Let's go.
Have you been
awake all this time?
You snore.
I do not.
It's very relaxing.
Power's back on.
Do you think you couldcarry him up to his room?
Every father should
try it at least once.
Richard.
Thanks.
For what?
For coming to see
why he screamed,
for carrying him upstairs.He won't forget.
He was asleep.
No, he wasn't.
Good night.
[music playing]
No, I can't.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
I'm sorry I--
I have to be sure.
Of what?
Whether or not I killed my wife?
I wasn't even
thinking about that.
What then?
What you have to understand isI've known real love, Richard,
and I won't settle
for anything less.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
[music playing]
[horses neighing]
Thank you.
Maybe I'd better
saddle up Augustine.
Amber doesn't like
strangers much.
ELIZABETH GUINNESS: Oh,
she'll be all right.
I'll just change
into my riding gear.
Thank you.
You're very brave
taking Amber for a ride.
Alycia was scared stiff of her.
Thanks.
Poor Andy.
Can't say I'm surprised.
He has scared off
three other nannies.
So you think he did it?
Of course he did.
Why would you think otherwise?
I don't know.
It just seems really odd.
I thought we were
really getting along.
Have you told
Richard about it?
No.
No, not yet.
I want to work it
through with Andy.
[horse neighing]
Be careful.
She's a sly one.
Alycia's the only one
she ever let ride her.
I think I'll be OK.
So where's Andy?
He's with his
father in the lab.
Oh, really?
Mhmm.
They're making progress.
You're quite the
nanny, aren't you?
Are you off somewhere?
Off to plead for
another deadline
extension on my manuscript.
Or if not, to sell my car.
You'd sell your car?
Actually, no.
I think I'd rather be the onlyhomeless person in America
sleeping in a 1924 Darracq.
I don't understand
how you can be broke.
I mean, you seem to be
doing pretty well to me.
Yes, well appearances
can be deceiving.
Blain, I am--
I don't know what you
make of this, but I--
I found it in my room.
You don't belong here,
so you'd better leave.
Alycia.
Do you think Andy wrote it?
Well, I think
that we can be quite
certain that Alycia didn't.
That's for sure.
Did he do this sort of thingwith the previous nannies?
Yes, but he didn't like them.
He likes you.
Have you shown that
to Jillian yet?
Yeah.
She thinks it's Andy.
Does she?
My guess is that she
probably wrote it.
What?
Jillian has been in lovewith Richard for years.
She sees the way that
Richard looks at you,
and I don't think she
likes it very much.
I thought you and
Jillian were an item.
No.
We're just convenient,
like an old habit.
She tends to hang outwith me in between affairs
with rich married men.
And all things
being equal, I don't
like coming up here by myself.
Jillian says you were
in love with Alycia.
She speaks the
truth, in the instance.
So you both were,
you and your brother.
He never loved her.
He only married
her to get at me.
How can you be sure?
I base my theory on the
fact that he killed her.
[music playing]
ANDREW KEATON [ON RADIO]:Testing, testing, one.
Two, three.
1,618 Americans every yearundergo plastic surgery
for purely aesthetic reasons.
Testing, testing,
one, two, three.
Testing, one, two, three.
49 Americans were murderedtoday, many of them by people
they know.
Testing, one, two, three.
Andrew, can I
leave you in charge
of the lab for the afternoon?
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
Because I think I'm goingto take one of the horses
out for a ride.
You, father?
Don't sound so
incredulous, young man.
I used to be a reasonably goodrider before you were born.
Maybe I have not forgotten how.
[music playing]
Come on.
[screams]
[horse whinnying]
How are you feeling?
I remember falling.
You've had a concussion.
You were very lucky it
wasn't that serious.
You could have
been killed if you
hadn't been wearing a helmet.
Where's Richard?
Richard?
He asked me to sit with you.
Thank you.
Ow.
[horse whinnying]
Jillian, would you mindleaving us alone for a moment?
No, of course not.
Thank you.
Liz.
Hi.
How are you feeling?
Better.
It's a good thing
you were there.
Thank you.
I would appreciate it
if you could leave just
as soon as you've recovered.
Are you firing me?
Well, shall we saythat I won't be requiring
your services anymore.
What about Andy?
I'm making arrangements forAndrew to go away to school.
I am considering an excellentestablishment in New Hampshire.
Why are you doing this?
Because it is my
prerogative, and I
am not prepared to discuss it.
[crying]
You promised you
wouldn't leave.
I'm afraid there's
nothing I can do.
Is it because
you fell off Amber?
No.
No, it has nothing
to do with that.
Your father has decided
it would be best
for you to go away to school.
Why did he decide that?
I don't know.
You'll have to ask him yourself.
I don't want to go
away to any school.
I don't want to go either.
But you're going.
I'll email you.
[music playing]
Amber's saddle girth was cut.
How do you know that?
I know who did it.
Who?
- She'll hear you.
- Andy, who?
Mother.
Where's the saddle?
Father took it in the
car this morning, early.
So you're still here.
Where's the saddle?
What saddle?
The one you took to town.
The saddle I was riding on.
The saddle that got cut.
- How did you know that?
- Andy told me.
I just took it
over to the sheriff.
Get in.
Look.
If you don't believe
me, here is the receipt.
Received one riding saddle,brown English for Dr. R Keaton
for evidentiary purposes.
You see, it's signed
Sam Getting, [inaudible]
River County Sheriff.
Why didn't you just tell me?
Because if I had, I knewyou would never leave.
Liz, I was scared for you.
I was afraid something likethis might happen again.
So please do get in.
Sending you away like thatwas one of the hardest things
I've ever done.
I'm very sorry.
You must never lie to
me like that again, OK?
I am a grown-up.
I don't need to beprotected from the truth,
and I'm not leaving.
- There.
You see?
I can't leave now.
Liz, somebody
tried to kill you,
somebody who knew youwere going to ride Amber.
Richard, everyone
knew I was riding Amber.
Well, that narrows it down.
How did Andy know
the girth had been cut?
I thought you told him.
Me?
No.
I think I'm going to
have a word with him.
Oh no, let's not frighten himany more than he already is.
I don't know.
Maybe I could take him camping.
Camping?
Yeah.
I used to go with my brothersall the time when I was a kid.
Pretty easy to talk whenyou're lying in your sleeping
bag staring at the stars.
I think he needs to talk.
Mrs. Pram says
you're not leaving!
- That's right.
- Really?
Really.
Does that mean I don't haveto go away to any school?
I think so.
Yes.
I'm so happy.
I got all this stuff out.
And I thought to celebrate,we could go camping.
What do you say?
- Camping?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Mhmm.
Go and get ready.
Well you look like
you're feeling better.
- I am.
- Go and get ready.
Long pants and long sleeves.
Well you know myhooded ski suit and boots
would afford me very
good protection.
Andy, it's the
middle of August.
See you later.
We're going camping, Jilly!
Yes!
Oh, camping.
How quaint.
What brought all this on?
I think you should know myfall, it wasn't an accident.
Somebody cut the saddle girth.
What?
How could anyone do that?
I don't know.
Richard's looking into it.
But we're playing
safe and getting out
of the house for the evening.
I don't blame you.
Why don't you come
to the city with me?
We'll have fun.
You'll probably be
safer there, anyway.
I can't.
I promised Andy I'd
take him camping,
anyway, we'll be
OK with Richard.
Will you?
Last chance.
I'll be fine.
Are you ready, Liz?
Oh, hi, Jillian.
Are you off?
Safe trip.
Where's Andy?
He's looking for
a sleeping bag.
Oh, good.
Bye.
A little bit more.
My brothers and I used totake turns telling ghost
stories around the camp fire.
Do you want to go first, Andy?
No.
Oh, come on.
You told me a kind
of ghost story
today when you said the
ghost of your mother
cut my saddle girth.
You shouldn't
have said anything.
I had to.
Liz could have been killed.
I know.
Who cut it, Andy?
We have to know.
I already told you, my mother.
Come on now.
Don't be silly.
Your mother has been
dead for five years.
Who else then?
RICHARD KEATON: You don't know?
No.
Then how did you
know it had been cut?
I locked the saddle
in the tackle room.
I diverted your email.
You what?
I hacked into
your email account.
I read the letter you sent tothe sheriff about the saddle.
Andy, my email
has an encryption
algorithm I wrote myself.
It wasn't that hard to hack.
How long has this
being going on?
I started right
after I came here.
RICHARD KEATON: Why?
I wanted to know
what you were thinking.
You didn't talk to me very much.
Sorry, father.
Hey, come here.
You're not half
as sorry as I am.
Is he asleep?
Well, at least one goodthing has come out of all this.
I feel so very much
closer to Andy.
[chuckling]
Diverting my email.
A chip off the old block.
I'm not sure what I
feel about that anymore.
A year ago-- oh hell--
three weeks ago, I couldn'thave imagined doing any of this.
I have you to thank for that.
Thank you.
[gunshot]
[music playing]
Oh my god.
What was that?
[gunshot]
[screams]
Get down!
Get down.
[gunshot]
[screams]
Father?
Andy, come here.
Come here.
It's OK.
ELIZABETH GUINNESS: Nick?
[gunshot]
All right.
Now look, you two stay here.
Keep your heads down.
I'm going for the car.
ELIZABETH GUINNESS: No, no.
No, it's all right.
Don't worry.
Whoever it is seems
to be a lousy shot.
That wasn't her, was it?
That was somebody real.
You're OK.
Don't worry.
Will you be able to sleep?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Mother's really dead.
Yes.
So she can't come
back and scare anybody
or even watch anybody, right?- No she can't.
Good night, Liz.
Good night, darling.
Where'd you say
they came from?
The north ridge.
But I can show you theexact spot in the morning
when it gets light.
Well, it's most
likely a head lamp
or some damn fool
who couldn't hit
a barn door if it was moving.
That's not hunting.
That's plain murder,
taking a deer like that.
No sheriff, I don't
think it was a hunter.
I think it was my brother.
Why?
Hello?
There he is now.
Blain.
Is everybody all right?
Why?
Shouldn't we be?
What's going on?
What are you doing
here, sheriff.
Where were you
at 10:30 tonight?
I was on my way
home from the city.
Oh, come on, Blain.
Who are you trying to fool?
Would someone mind explainingto me what this is all about?
I know you were up
at the north ridge
and you fired three shots at us.
No, I wasn't.
Did anyone see you?
Well, I can't tell you whereI was at 10:30, but I can--
Hey!
But if you let me
get into my wallet,
I can prove where
I was at 10:15.
I got a speeding ticketgoing through Briggenville.
It's 60 miles from here.
Take it very easy.
10:15 PM, doing 65 in a
40 in beautiful downtown
Briggenville.
Well, you have to
watch for Leonard.
He's a terror on peoplespeeding through his town.
Well, you won't be needing
my services any further.
I think I'll just
go home and see
what's left of the ball game.
[music playing]
It was a head lamper.
Conscience bothering you?
How the hell do you think Icould do something like that?
Well if it wasn't
you, who was it?
Who's there?
It's OK, Andy.
It's just me.
I wanted to see that
you were all right.
Did they find out it who was?
No, but we will.
Come on.
Let's tuck you back in.
OK?
Are you going to
marry Liz, father?
How do you feel about
calling me "dad?"
Are you going to marry Liz?
Do you want me to?
Yes.
Well then, you're
going to have
to put in a good word for me.
Sleep well.
Good night, dad.
Good night, son.
[music playing]
[clock chiming]
I couldn't sleep.
Neither could
I. What happened?
Blain has an alibi.
So it wasn't Blain.
I didn't say that.
Why do you hate
each other so much?
Well more than anyone, Blainthinks that I killed Alycia.
He thinks you marriedAlycia to get back at him.
No.
No, I loved her very much.
I always loved her.
Why do you think
she killed herself?
I don't know.
She wasn't that kind of woman.
She intended to live forever.
Maybe she did just
fall out of the window.
What happened
the night she died?
She'd been to a
party in the city.
She came home drunk.
I hated being around her
when she was like that.
She started in on
me about how she'd
married the wrong
brother, how it was
Blain that she really loved.
She must've been
very confused.
Yeah, I think she
was, and I obviously
didn't know how to help her.
She could be very
cruel, particularly when
she was drunk.
And that night, she told methat Andrew was not my son,
that he was Blain's.
Maybe she was just
trying to hurt you.
Yeah, maybe.
Or maybe she was
telling the truth.
Anyway, I stormed out, andthose were the last words
that passed between us.
I couldn't deal with it.
I shut myself down emotionally.
Then you showed up.
Suddenly, I had feelings again.
You opened my eyes.
I love you, Liz.
Oh, I know I could never beanything like your husband,
but don't you feel anythingfor me, anything at all?
This is very
hard for me to say.
Then don't.
I don't think I ever lovedNick the way that I love you,
and I found that hard to face.
Andy wasn't the only one
carrying around a ghost.
And if he can let go, so can I.
Thank you, Mrs. Pram.
Morning, everyone.
Hi.
Oh, could I have some
eggs please, Mrs. Pram?
ANDREW KEATON: Hey.
I'm hungry.
Liz, if my father
were to marry you,
you'd be my mother, right?
Well, that would
depend on you.
But you'd be willing to be?
Well you do
realize that mothers
don't take orders like nannies.
I know.
They give them, but it'sbecause they love you.
Mine didn't.
My mother never loved me.
I'm sure she did.
Hey, you know what?
I love you very much.
Where are you going?
I give up, Richard.
You win.
It's all yours.
Last night was the last straw.
Look, I need the money.
So if you can raise
it, buy me out.
No, no, you're not leaving.
You're not going anywhereuntil you tell me
what you know about last night.
You know it wasn't me.
No Blain, I know
no such thing.
Richard, you're my brother.
I may not like you, but
I wouldn't shoot you.
Why not?
You'd have the house.
You'd have your son.
Seems reason enough to me.
Richard, you've
got to believe me.
I never slept with Alyciaafter she married you.
Andrew is your son.
Oh my god.
She really had us
both, didn't she?
Good evening, Mrs. Pram.
Where are you off to?
Dr. Keaton left me a note.
He needs some things from town.
Hello, Liz.
[music playing]
Liz.
[knocking on door]
Liz, are you in there?
Can you come and play with me?
Liz, are you sleeping?
Liz!
[pulling on door]
ANDREW KEATON [ON RADIO]:Dad, are you there?
Are you there?
Yes, Andy.
What is it?
It's Liz.
She's in big trouble.
What's wrong?
It's Jillian.
She took her to the east tower.
Jillian.
Andy, are you sure?
Hurry, dad.
She's got a gun!
A gun?
Andy, I'm locked in.
Get up here fast and let me out.- I can't!
I'm locked in, too.
Dad, are you there.
Yeah Andy, I'm here.
Now listen, listen
to me very carefully.
The rope fire ladder isunderneath your computer table.
Get it out.
Dad, I'm scared.
RICHARD KEATON [ONRADIO]: That's all right.
Brave boys get
scared, too, but they
still do what they have to.
Do you understand?
Yes.
RICHARD KEATON [ON
RADIO]: Good boy.
Then do it.
Do it, Andy.
Do it for Liz.
OK, dad.
Oh my god.
Jillian.
Andy, are you all right?
Talk to me.
Why are you doing this to me?
I lost him once.
I'm not going to let
that happen again.
Please Jillian, let's
just talk about this.
Oh, there's nothing
to talk about.
Why don't you just move
towards the window?
Don't be crazy.
You'll never get away with it.
I did before, and
no one found out.
I followed her back
here from the party.
She was drunk, and
she was mocking me.
She had Richard, and
she knew I loved him.
It didn't take much to push her.
Good boy.
Please Jillian, why
are you doing this?
Why?
Because you spoiled it all.
All these years
I waited for him.
And in three weeks,
you have destroyed
everything I worked for.
But Richard will
know that you did it.
Well, maybe I
don't care anymore.
Jillian, stop this.
Come on now.
Put down the gun.
Put it down.
You never loved me, did you?
No Jillian, I didn't.
And I'm truly sorry
if I ever gave
you the impression that I did.
All these years I never
wanted anyone but you.
Oh, god.
[inaudible]
RICHARD KEATON: No!
[crying]
I've got an idea, Richard.
All we have to do is selloff 10 acres at the far end
of the property, pay off allour debts, fix up the old pile,
and we live happily ever after.
Do it.
Well, that's it?
You're not going
to argue about it?
I have no time
to argue, Blain.
I am off on my honeymoon.
Dad, I want to come
on your honeymoon.
Oh, no, no.
Children are not allowed.
Well, that's not fair.
I put in a good word foryou just like you asked.
Didn't I, Liz?
It's true.
Ha, this is a conspiracy.
It's outrageous.
Well, you are
going to need someone
to go fishing with while Ifinished reading "Jane Eyre."
Mhmm.
Of course you can.
Come on.
Hop in.
Yay.
Are the bags in the car?
Yeah.
Good.
Blain, thanks for the car.
What are brothers for?
Bye, Blain.
Bye bye, guys.
- Goodbye, uncle Blain.
- Bye, Andy.
Bye Mrs. Pram.
Bye bye.
ANDREW KEATON: Bye, uncle Blain.
Goodbye.
Bye uncle Blain.
See you soon.
ANDREW KEATON: Good bye.
ELIZABETH GUINNESS: Good bye.
[music playing]