(MultiCom Jingle)
(soft piano music)
(soft jazz music)
- How are you holding up?
- Better than I thought.
- It's not the end
of the world, is it?
- No, it's not the
end of the world.
(cell phone buzzing)
Hello?
(crackling voice)
- Sam.
- Hello, Mom?
- [Cecilia] Sam,
can you hear me?
Sam, where are you?
I need you.
- Something's wrong.
I can feel it.
- Sam, Sam!
Where are you going?
Wait, wait, wait
where are you going?
Tell me what's happening?
I thought we were
past all this shit.
- Something's
wrong, I have to go.
- What about the press,
what about all your friends?
- Tell them I'll be back.
- Hey, hey!
After all the shit
I've been through
to help you get
to where you are.
You walk out on me?
You're walking out on us.
- I'm sorry, I have to go.
- [Alex] I told you I'm not
dealing with this shit anymore!
- Ma, just call him, please!
- [Alex] What's up,
baby, it's okay.
- What's going on?
- Dude, I'm over this shit, man.
- [Sam] What'd he do?
- I told her I'm not gonna
deal with this shit anymore.
He's never gonna
fucking change, okay?
You don't know the shit that
he's fuckin'
rollin' in, alright?
He's gonna end up fucking
somebody else over
and we're gonna end
up paying for it.
Fuck that!
It's okay, baby.
It's okay, we're going home.
- [Sam] I'll see
you later, okay?
Alright, I'll call you later.
- Do not call me
about this shit!
I'm done.
- Ah, shit!
(grunting)
Damn it!
Sam, Sammy!
That you?
Come help me out here.
(speaking foreign language)
- Dad, what's going on in there?
- I don't know, I don't care.
Come on, papa.
- I got you.
- Hurry up, I'm
late for my shift.
- [Sam] Here.
- Good, thank you.
- [Sam] Sure.
- [Bill] Alright.
- Can I get you anything?
- No, no, no, no, no.
Just, (laughs)
have fun with that.
Alright, I'm leaving.
- [Cameron] Leave me alone.
- [Cecilia] We are
not calling him.
- Ma, just call him,
it's the only way
to get these people
out of my life!
- What the hell happened to you?
- Hey Sam, I fell skateboarding.
- Oh yeah, you skateboard now?
- Tell him.
- Nothing!
Look, are you gonna
take the car or not?
- What car?
- Forget about the fucking car!
Tell him!
- Oh my God!
You people make me
sick, literally sick!
- Chill out!
- Baby, baby we need their help.
- He's doing heroin.
- I'm not doing heroin!
- Oh no, then why
do you keep taking
little pieces of
aluminum foil, huh?
Those fevers you get,
you think I'm an idiot?
And you better bring me
back my wedding ring!
- What are you
talking about, ma?
I didn't take your ring!
- Oh yeah, because I was the one
who broke the lock
to my door, right?
- Cameron, I really hope
you're not doing heroin.
Do you know how that shit
changes your physiology,
like literally changes you?
- Relax, geez man, I know.
Okay?
I know.
This nigger thinks
he's the only one
that can look shit up on Google.
Besides, I haven't been
doing it for that long.
- So you have been doing it!
- Mom, mom, mom, stop!
Hold on, mom, mom, mom, mom!
Mom, mom, mom, stop!
Mom, calm down!
- I swear to God!
- Calm down, calm down.
Alright, everyone calm down.
- Michelle, are you gonna
take the car or not?
- Oh, my God.
- I already told you,
I'm not going anywhere!
- What car?
- Don't worry about
it babe, okay?
They always do what
I want them to do.
My friend's car, bro!
- Alright, well
go take it to him!
- I would, but it stalled on me
and something that was
in the car went missing!
- What went missing?
- Okay?
I don't know!
- [Sam] You don't know?
Then how do you know
it went missing?
- Because it was
in the car and then
(clapping) then it wasn't!
- That is what he's asking you.
What was in the car?
- It was a white box, Mom, but
I don't know what was in it!
- Cam, do you have this box?
- No, look!
Mike and I were
using the car, okay?
- Who's Mike, is he
the owner of this car?
- No, he's Bosco's brother.
- Bosco?
Is Bosco the owner of this car?
- Yes!
I dropped Mike off
but on my way to Bosco
the car stalled,
it wouldn't run!
- Alright, then tell him that.
- Did you forget
about the part where
something went missing
from his car, Sam?
You're supposed to
be the smart one!
- Hey!
- It's fucking Bosco.
- Shut up!
- Why, who is he?
- He's my friend.
- You're friend?
He is not your fucking friend!
This dude owns a Maserati!
Okay?
Not a fucking Prius,
a $200,000 dollar car!
Baby, you are fucked!
- Okay, okay alright.
Cameron, you understand that
this isn't normal, right?
Do you get it?
This is not normal!
Cameron, look at me!
Look at me, hey!
What the fuck are you on?
- I'm not on anything!
- Oh really, really?
- Oh my God, stop lying to
them, we need their help!
- Will you shut the fuck up?
- I will not shut the
fuck up, it's the truth!
- Stop it!
- I don't care!
I don't care anymore!
- Alright, Michelle.
What was in the car,
what'd you lose?
- Oh, my God.
Will you please just help me out
and go take this guy his car?
Come on, Sam, this is
my only way out, man.
I'm trying to get away
from these people.
They're the reason
I'm like this.
Please just tell him you're
bringing him his car,
that I'm in jail and that you
don't know when I'll be out.
Please!
- Okay, so say, what,
we bring him the keys,
we bring him the car, we
tell him you got arrested.
And how did we get the keys,
how, what about the box?
- Just.
- Look, tell him
you came and picked
them up from me in jail.
And the box, tell him the cops
took it when they arrested me.
He'll never bother me again.
- Okay, but you gotta
do your part, okay?
You have to stop.
- I will, okay?
I will.
- What's his number?
- I'll call him.
- [Sam] What's his name again?
- Bosco.
- [Sam] Bosco.
(phone ringing)
- [Bosco] Who is this?
- Hi, is this Bosco?
- I'm Cameron's brother.
- [Bosco] I don't give a fuck!
What do you want?
- I'm trying to get
your car back to you.
- [Bosco] Why do you
have my fucking car?
- I don't actually
have your car,
but I'm trying to arrange
a way for you to get it.
Where does he live?
- I don't know.
- [Bosco] Where's Cam?
- He's locked up.
- [Bosco] Put Cam on
the phone, please!
- Look, I'm just telling you
what my mom told me, alright?
She told me that Cam and
Mike were driving someplace,
he dropped Mike off,
he was going to return
the car to you, it
stalled on the highway.
And then somewhere along
those lines he got arrested.
That's it, that's
what she told me.
(Bosco laughing)
She told me this in Spanish.
- You're lying to me.
I might have misunderstood
something, but...
- [Bosco] I don't believe you.
- Cam isn't here!
- [Bosco] Stop
fucking around with me
and put Cam on the phone!
- Hello, hello?
- [Bosco] Cameron?
- Hello?
Who the fuck is this?
- I told you!
You think everybody doesn't
know you're a fucking liar?
- Relax, relax, okay?
Ma, ma you know who it is.
You remember when you picked
me up from Brooklyn last week?
It was the guy
with the Maserati.
- So this is the same?
Oh, my fucking God!
Are you sending mom and Michelle
to return this guy's car?
- Thank you, thank you!
- Get the fuck off me!
Why are you even here, man?
Did ma call you?
You calling in the troops?
Oh, you love this, don't you?
Yeah, you and Alex.
You both need people
like me so you can point
your fingers and say,
ooh, that's the bad guy!
- Yeah well, right
now you're not
really acting like a good guy!
Are you?
- I'm whatever I need to be.
- You're a fucking liar!
- Stop calling me a liar!
- But it's true,
though, you are lying!
(all screaming)
- Stop it!
Stop it, stop it!
I'm just gonna go take this
Bosco guy his car, okay?
I don't want any more
of your problems.
- Mom, wait!
Does he know where you live?
- Everyone knows
where Cam lives.
Fuck.
- Lock the doors and
text me his number.
- Really, lock the doors?
Man dramatic, bro!
- Not letting you go alone!
I'll meet you in the car.
- Fucking asshole!
- Wait, you need a jacket!
(tape rewinding)
Cam?
Papa?
- [Sam] Cameron!
- Sam?
- [Sam] Cam?
- What's wrong?
- Where's Cameron?
- I just got here.
- Oh, my God!
- What are you doing in there?
It's freezing!
(laughs)
- Jesus Christ, this is crazy.
Mom, he called me.
Said he was tired of not
feeling loved, of feeling alone.
- Why didn't you--
- He said he was
gonna kill himself.
- Why didn't you call me?
- Mom, he needs
psychiatric help.
- I know, I took
him to the doctor.
You know what they told me?
They told me I was
the one who was crazy.
- What?
What are we gonna do?
- I don't know.
What can I do?
It's not like before
when he was 14 or 15.
He's gonna be 19 in a few months
and there's nothing
I can do for him.
Legally, if he
doesn't want the help.
He went away to that
school and I thought
he'd come back better,
but he won't get a job.
He won't go to church.
He won't take his medication
and he won't stop doing drugs.
I don't know how much
longer I can take this.
- We'll figure something out.
We gotta get him outta there.
(ominous music)
- Why are you here?
- I'm trying to help
you keep your job.
I don't know what's
going on, Cecilia.
But remember you have an
obligation to your students
that supercedes your own needs.
Think that through.
This may not be
where you should be.
Have a good day.
- Okay, sorry about that.
Let's begin.
(door slamming)
(melancholy music)
He said the two would
be here in 30 minutes.
- It's been 45.
(opera music on radio)
- I wanted to do that.
Be an opera singer
like my Tia Ana.
- I didn't know that.
Why didn't you?
- I think it was just
too big a dream for me.
Then I had you guys.
- I think I'm gonna
write about all this.
- Like a book?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Mmhmm.
- That's good.
- Just tell me if you
don't want me to do it.
- No, do it, do it.
Maybe it will do
someone some good.
How did it get so bad?
- I don't know.
How much longer
can we keep it up?
Till he's 30, 40?
- Sam, believe me,
if I could jump
inside his body and
change him I would,
but for now, we just
have to help him.
Cameron's not like you or Alex.
He's always needed us.
He said he's gonna
go back to rehab,
so that'll give me 30 days
to focus, to really focus.
- If he stays the 30 days.
- He said he was this time.
And Michelle's going with him.
- Can I see the keys?
(alarm beeping)
(engine revving)
I thought he said
it wouldn't start.
- He said the battery stalled.
I don't know, maybe
it needed to rest.
What are you looking for?
- I don't know.
Something doesn't feel right.
Mom, what is it,
what's going on?
- Something's wrong.
- What is it?
- It's Cameron.
- What?
- It's Cameron, it's Cameron.
- What are you talking about?
Mom, it's alright.
- Oh, my God!
- Mom, Mom, Mom!
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- What is happening?
- No, no! (crying)
Please, please, no!
(moaning)
(speaking foreign language)
- Mom, it's alright.
(crying)
(police radio chattering)
- The detective
tells me how he died.
Dozens of pictures before me,
still he tells me how he died.
How Cameron drowned
in our backyard pool
after he was shot
in the back twice.
He warns me then
flips the folder open,
Michelle's head open, the
left side more intact.
I could almost tell it was her.
It's honest, it's,
it's dark.
I'm just concerned
that the overall tone
is on a par to Blackout.
(muffled talking)
- Anybody wanna tell me
how good my turkey is?
- [Sam] It's really good, Mom.
- It's good, right?
I wish Deanna and
Emily were here.
- Yeah, I know, me too.
They're still down in
Florida with her parents.
- You know what, we
should do a family trip.
You want that papa,
you go down to Florida?
- No!
(laughs)
Hey, hey check these out.
You tell me how
much you think's--
- Bill, don't start.
I thought you getting
a desk job meant that
the basement was gonna
start looking the way it did
before you started
filling it up with junk.
- Antiques.
- [Cecilia] Antiques?
- Dad, I don't think
these are worth very much.
- These are the first
memory cards ever made.
- These are USB drives.
It's a USB drive, Pop.
(laughs)
- And technology doesn't
really gain value with time.
- How much do you think
the iPhone costs now
compared to what it was
when it first came out?
- Yeah, but these aren't
the first iPhones.
This is not the first that's
anything (laughs) sorry.
- Dream killers.
- [Sam] Sorry, Pop.
- Give it back.
- [Sam] No, I want it.
- Forget about it, give it back.
- You wanna eat?
Let me get you some
juice, okay papa?
- [Alex] Dad, you
want some gravy?
- Thank you.
(men chattering)
Thank you.
- [Alex] Sorry, Dad.
- [Bill] That's the last
advice I ever ask you.
- [Sam] Aw, come on.
- [Cecilia] Hey.
- Thank you.
- Okay here, drink that.
Why don't you tell Sam
about your new job?
- You got a job?
- I got him the job.
- Wow, what is it?
- [Cecilia] Come on, tell
him what you're doing.
- Just loading shit
into a warehouse.
- You're welcome.
- Well, that's good.
You never know where
there's room to grow.
- That's right.
I keep telling him
that, you never know.
You just gotta be positive.
Every job is an opportunity
to discover something new,
to discover something different.
You know?
Are you tired of being home?
- Did you put something in this?
- What?
No.
- What's that
bitter taste, then?
- I don't, you
want me to try it?
- No, we're supposed to
trust each other, Ma!
The counselor told us we're
supposed to trust each other.
But how the fuck am I
supposed to do that--
- Oh!
- When you keep
doing shit like this?
- Alright, okay I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- Whoa, dude!
- You ungrateful little fuck!
- Wait don't, stop,
Bill, stop, stop!
There's no fighting
this Thanksgiving!
- You can't let him
get away with that!
(speaking foreign language)
- I'm done.
I'm sorry.
(speaking foreign language)
- Dad.
- [Sam] I thought you and
I could use a little rum.
- Thanks.
That was the worst
Thanksgiving dinner ever.
- At least it's over.
(glasses clinking)
You excited?
- About what?
- Spring semester.
- I think I'm gonna
take some time off.
- Won't that affect your
candidacy for tenure?
- Sam, they're never
gonna give me tenure.
- But, you were looking forward
to teaching that
Shakespeare class.
- I don't know, I just,
I'm ready for a change.
I'm thinking about
doing real estate.
I can work from home,
make my own hours.
- I don't know, Mom, you were,
you waited three years
to teach that class.
- Shakespeare isn't
going anywhere.
- They can't come in here,
Mom can't come in here.
Fuck, man!
This isn't fucking normal, Sam!
People aren't supposed to
go through this shit, man!
I keep fucking waking up in
this goddamn fucking nightmare!
Nothing seems to fucking
make sense anymore!
This isn't who we are!
Right?
Look at this shit.
Thinking about moving to
Miami, we're selling the house.
Taking Mom and Dad with me.
And get a fresh start.
No one should be
dealing with this shit.
Sam, are you scared, man?
- [Cameron] You want
something to drink?
- No, I'm alright.
- [Cameron] Good, 'cause
I didn't get you anything.
(laughs)
- [Sam] Really, you're
gonna smoke right here?
- Relax, bro, it's not
gonna go in the house.
- [Sam] How are you?
- [Cameron] I'm good.
- Nah.
I mean, like, how's
everything been at home?
- (laughs) I'm as
good as I'm gonna get.
I'm selling heroin, coke too.
If any of your friends need
it, let me know, I got 'em.
- Damn.
That's heavy.
Cameron?
- Yeah?
- Just be careful.
- I know man, I'm not stupid.
- Alright.
- Besides, it's not like any
of this shit even matters.
Look at the sun.
It's gonna die.
The stars, the universe, it
all ends for everything, man.
None of it matters.
- You sound like you've
already given up.
- Nah, I just understand
how shit works now.
All the little things
inside the big things
start to become the same thing.
It invalidates everything.
Just think about it,
man, this explosion.
(laughs)
Scary, right?
- Yeah.
You know what's really scary?
- What?
- Thinking about
your 13 year old
self's opinion of yourself.
(laughs)
- What?
- I picture my 13 year old
self walking into my room,
checking out my shit,
looking at my room,
my apartment, the
diploma on the wall.
Seeing how much I aged.
It can really mess with you.
What about yours?
What would your 13 year old
self feel if he saw you?
- If he saw me?
- [Sam] Yeah.
- He would feel nothing
because he wouldn't know me.
- I think I'm gonna
write about all this.
- What do you mean?
- About, you know,
all this, you.
- What are you gonna call it?
- I don't know.
It can't be a word, it
has to be like a feeling.
- Maybe you'll write
me a happy ending.
- [Sam] Yeah, hopefully.
(melancholy music)
Hey.
- I'm really sorry.
- I could have done something.
- It's not your fault,
it's not your fault.
You cannot blame yourself.
He was too far gone.
- I'm not sure, I'm not.
- Look, you told his story.
That's gonna keep him alive.
(cell phone buzzing)
- Yeah, Dad, what's up?
- It was fast.
Bosco had a very strong alibi,
confirmed by over
a dozen people.
They couldn't find his
prints in the house.
They're letting him go.
- What?
- They can't charge
him with anything.
They're letting him go.
I'm on my way over there.
- Hey, do you know if
Mom's still sleeping?
- They're letting him go.
- What?
- Yeah, Dad called,
they're letting him go.
What are we going to do?
What are we gonna tell Mom?
- Whatever we fucking,
whatever we have to.
Alright, whatever we have to.
(Alex sighing)
- I wish we could just like,
oh, move the whole family here.
Like, be safe, you know?
Out of the city, safe.
- You like that house?
- Yeah, I like
that, that's pretty.
- Good.
- That's my lucky number, too.
- How about that?
Me, too.
- [Cecilia] What?
- You really like that house?
- [Cecilia] Yeah.
- Good.
I'm glad you like it
because you own it.
- What do you mean I own it?
- We own it.
- What?
- Happy anniversary.
(laughs)
- Oh, my God!
For real?
(speaking foreign language)
(laughs)
- It's got a big
pool in the back.
- Let's go see!
- Let's go swimming!
- [Cecilia] Let's go! (laughing)
(speaking foreign language)
- Cece, please just come.
Okay, breathe with me, okay,
'cause you're very nervous.
Breathe, okay.
(speaking foreign language)
One day at a time, okay?
- Okay.
- Okay, breathe.
- I wanna go home.
- Why, I'm taking
care of you here.
- Because everything is there.
Everything of his is
there, I wanna go home.
- No, come on let's, breathe
with me a little bit.
- [Cecilia] I wanna go
home, I wanna go home.
- [Wilma] Cece, please
you have to breathe.
- [Cecilia] I wanna go home!
- [Wilma] Cece!
- [Cecilia] Where'd
you get that?
- [Cameron] Relax,
I didn't steal it.
Where are your records?
- Beneath the TV.
(laughs)
- [Cameron] Here,
check these out.
- Oh man, I haven't
seen these in so long.
Oh, you have to play this.
It's my favorite.
- I had a weird
dream last night.
- Oh yeah, what was it about?
- Just a weird dream.
- Dreams are very powerful
things, like a web.
You're at the center
of it and dreams
are everything that
extends outward.
Everything you are,
are meant to be, were.
But, you know, you can't
be all those things
in real life, so
dreams are a nice way--
- It was a bad dream.
Just me driving on
some dark highway.
It works. (laughs)
- Ooh, I love this.
(both laughing)
Tell me more about
your dream, papa.
- Don't worry about
it, it's nothing.
I got you these seeds.
- What?
What are these?
(laughs)
- Relax, Ma, they're
just flowers, okay?
I was helping Miss Russo,
the old lady next door,
clean out her garage.
She gave me the record
player and 40 bucks.
So that was pretty awesome.
She um, she told me
she hears us yelling
and screaming all the
time, so she gave me these.
Said to plant 'em in
the front of the house,
that they'd being happiness.
- I love you, papa.
- I um, I know I've
been kind of bad lately.
But um, (laughs)
I'm gonna go clean.
Okay?
I promise.
(speaking foreign language)
- You're a good boy.
I know you are.
(speaking foreign language)
- There was a fight
a few weeks ago,
some classroom disturbances.
Truancy is the real
issue here, however.
Out of 62 school days so far,
he has only attended 19 of them.
Our psychologist
evaluated him yesterday
and there was nothing
troubling or remarkable.
- Nothing?
- Nothing that he
could see, anyway.
We can consider after
school programs, mentoring,
but if he's not
willing to attend them,
then there really is no point.
Whatever he's going through,
that change has to
come from within him.
- You're telling me I
have to just be patient?
- You know what they say.
Patience is bitter,
the fruit is sweet.
He is a good kid, Cecilia.
He will realize what he
has to do soon enough.
- What if he doesn't?
- If he doesn't then we'll cross
that bridge when we come to it.
Okay?
- Okay.
(school bell ringing)
- [Sam] Hey, there's
the birthday girl!
- No!
- [Sam] What is it?
- Where's Cameron?
- He left with Alex, why?
- My purse is missing.
- Shit.
- Yeah, I need to report this.
- What?
- I need to report that
my stuff is missing, Sam.
He has my credit cards, my
identification, my work phone.
- Alright, well maybe
it's here someplace.
- No, because it was
right fucking here!
God, fuck that
fucking drug addict!
Why did you invite him?
- Because I want
to feel like I have
a normal fucking
family sometimes.
- I should have said no,
but then I would have
been the asshole.
But I told you, I
fucking told you!
You know what an enabler is?
Open your eyes, Sam!
Or are they only
open for your book?
You need to fix this.
(knocking)
- Cam?
- [Cameron] I'm not going!
- What the hell do you
mean, you're not going?
Cameron, open this damn door.
Don't play with me, Cameron!
Okay, do what you want.
You wanna stay and do
eight years in prison?
Stay and throw away all the
money I spent on that lawyer!
But you better think
about your future, boy,
because you're still only 17.
This is your last
chance to start over.
(banging)
Cameron?
You choose because I'm done!
I've done enough!
(thudding)
- Cameron?
- Cameron!
Cameron!
Stop the car, get
out of the car!
Get out of the car!
(panting)
(ominous music)
- It's too late.
- [Cecilia] What?
- [Man] They waited for
over an hour, Cecilia.
- Did you tell them
I had an emergency?
- I did, I did but you can't
keep these people waiting.
It's over.
- I'll appeal it.
- You'll appeal it?
- Yes.
- And then what?
You win and you're allowed back.
How many more classes
are you gonna miss?
How you gonna get your
evaluations out of the toilet?
I've been patient,
Cecilia, believe me.
I've been really patient.
We're gonna offer
you paid suspension.
Take it, take it.
Take it and just
walk away, okay?
I'm sorry.
- As far as the wine we'll
go with the Pinot Noir.
- [Cecilia] Can I
get a Long Island?
- Oh, my God, what
are you doing here?
- I missed my baby sister,
I thought I'd stop by.
Are you busy, is
now a good time?
- Oh yeah, yeah, it's fine.
I wish you would have
told me you were coming.
I would have opened
the kitchen for you.
- No, no it's fine.
It's just one of those spur of
the moment things, you know.
- Cece, you hate the city.
You live 50 miles away.
What's going on?
- I got fired.
- What?
I thought you were
getting tenure.
(laughs)
- That's a joke.
How about that drink?
(laughs)
- Merlot?
Two merlots, please.
- You know I thought
I could do it, Wilma.
I thought I could do both,
have a family and have
a successful career.
- You did, you are doing it.
- Cameron's doing something.
He's up to something, I
don't know what it is.
(speaking foreign language)
No, no it's not all
his fault, you know?
He has issues.
We moved out to Long
Island because we thought
that's what you do,
you buy the house,
you put the flag
out in the front.
That was the dream, right,
when Mami came here?
That's what she told us.
But, we're not doing it right.
I don't know,
somehow I'm failing.
I feel like I'm failing him--
- Listen to yourself.
- I'm failing my family.
I'm just, I'm failing everybody.
- You have to stop!
You have to stop
blaming yourself
for whatever Cameron
chooses to do.
He's not a child anymore.
He knows that his actions
have consequences,
yet he continues to
behave the same way.
You have to focus on
the rest of your family.
Why do you think Sam moved out?
- Why he got that
job in the city?
- He could have waited
tables anywhere,
but he chooses the city.
Why do you think that is?
This thing with Cameron, it
doesn't only affect you, Cece.
It hurts me, it hurts
your boys, it hurts Bill.
- Okay, you know what?
Enough, Wilma. (speaking
foreign language)
- Nobody can say anything
because you don't wanna hear it.
- No, you have said enough.
- What's wrong?
Missing pills again?
- I don't know,
I don't, maybe...
- Every time those pills
mysteriously disappear,
where do you think they go?
Hmm?
- Hey Kevin, have
you seen Cameron?
- Yo Kev, come over!
Want a hit?
- Oh shit, let's go upstairs.
I'm sure he's fine.
- It's been three days.
We haven't heard back from him.
- When he runs out of
money, he'll come back.
- So you don't know where he is?
- I know he's been spending
a lot of time in Brooklyn,
but we haven't spoken to
each other in a while.
Do you know who he's
been hanging around with?
- No, we don't know anything.
We just wanna make
sure he's okay.
- What would you do if you were,
I don't know, a five year old?
And someone comes up to you and
gives you a free piece of candy.
The next day they
give you two pieces.
What do you do on the third day
when that person
doesn't show up?
You go looking for them, right?
- Right.
- That's who he's been
hanging around with.
(tea kettle whistling)
- How is she?
- It's been difficult.
Alex brought Emily
over yesterday
and that cheered
her up a bit, but...
She wants to go home.
I think it's too soon.
But you know how she is.
So, they let him go.
- Does she know that?
- No, of course not.
- Okay.
- Cece?
You awake?
Look who's here.
- Mom?
Mom, you awake?
Tia was telling me
that Emily spent
the day with you here yesterday.
Have you been taking
your medication?
You know you have to take them.
They'll make you feel better.
Look what I brought you.
Remember when you
gave me these books?
Samuel, happy first
day of school.
I hope you understand our
decision in moving out here
and see that Long
Island is not so bad.
I'm sure you'll make
lots of new friends
and in a year you can
have your own car.
No more trains.
I'll be here to talk
when you're ready.
Love, Mom.
- Today has, it's
been a bad day.
- How would you like to come
stay with me for a few days?
Would you like that?
What do you think?
(festive Latin music)
- [Cecilia] Hey, what
are you doing out here?
- Just waiting for Alex and Cam.
- You okay, papa?
- I just don't want
things to go back
to the way they
were before he left.
- They won't, they won't.
- Mom, I can't see next year,
I can't see the next five years.
Waiting tables was
not part of the plan.
- Well, maybe you need to
shift your focus, you know?
Go back to writing your book.
- I don't know.
- Look, it's a cliche, but
they say it because it's true.
Write about what you know.
Write about what you love,
what makes you happy,
what makes you tick,
what scares you.
- A lot of things scare
me these days, Mom.
- Alright, come on,
you can (laughs).
It's all about, it's
just all about focusing.
You know?
Allowing yourself to go there.
It's gonna be
different, he's changed.
- I wouldn't get your hopes up.
- You can be so cynical.
(horn honking)
Ooh, there's my baby!
(laughs)
- So, I pick him up
at the train station.
I leave him in the
car for five minutes
to go get groceries and
this little piece of shit--
- [Cecilia] Wait a minute.
- Fucking takes off in my car!
Get out of the fucking car!
- What are you doing?
- Get out of the car!
- Alex!
- He's fucking stoned.
He's been gone for two years.
The first time we
see you and you're
already fucking
stoned, aren't you?
- Jesus Christ.
Stop yelling, you're here, okay?
Are you alright?
- Welcome fucking home!
Little shit.
- [Cecilia] You okay, papa?
- Cecilia, just leave him there.
- Can you make it?
Oh, my little baby, I miss you.
- Ma, you need help?
- [Cecilia] Yeah.
Thank you, papa.
- You're welcome.
I gotta head out of here.
- What?
But it's still early!
- Yeah, I know, but
the party's over
and I gotta be up at
three in the morning.
- You still working on
that housing development?
- Yeah, yeah, I am.
Uh, listen, I gave Cam the list
of interviews he's
got for tomorrow.
They're not the classiest
jobs, but it's a start.
Can you just make sure
that he makes it there?
- Yeah, don't worry, I will.
I will, don't worry, okay?
- [Alex] Alright,
no, I'm not worried.
Okay.
- I'll drive him myself.
Okay?
- Cool, and make sure he brings
his resume with him, please.
- Okay.
- Good, I know. (laughs)
Alright, I gotta go, Mom.
- Okay.
- Alright.
(speaking foreign language)
- I love you.
- I love you too, papa.
- I'm sorry I didn't get
to go up there that much.
- [Cameron] It's cool.
It's a bitch of a drive, I
wouldn't have gone up either.
- Yeah.
Alex tells me about
all the interviews
he has lined up for you.
- Yeah, a bunch
of weak-ass jobs.
- [Sam] It's better than
sitting here, though, right?
- Yeah.
What about you, you still
doing that writing thing?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm still
doing the writing thing.
- [Cameron] That's cool.
Gotta do what you love, right?
- Yeah.
What about you?
What do you love?
(laughs)
- What do you love?
You sound like my
counselor, man.
- [Sam] Alright.
- [Cameron] You wanna smoke?
- Nah, you know I
don't do that no more.
- [Cameron] Yeah, yeah.
I'm selling heroin, coke too.
(voices echoing)
- Thank you, Annie.
Anyone else?
- I uh, lost my daughter Paige,
six months and 10 days ago.
Overdose.
It's completely ripping
us apart, me and my wife.
The sense of pain
and the desperation,
the guilt that comes
along with it is like,
it's unlike anything I've...
I mean, still, six months...
(stammering)
I haven't had a moment
of silence up here
and I'm afraid that
when that moment comes,
when I finally stop
thinking about it,
that's when I'm afraid that
it's going to be too much.
To be alone in the silence.
Without her laugh or without me
being able to tell her
how much I love her.
(man sobbing)
She was only 17.
I just miss her so much!
- I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Sam I wanna go home.
- Okay.
- So, what do you think?
Should I just take the
sign off right now?
(laughs)
Ms. Dern, Miss Newman,
I am so sorry I'm late.
- It's alright, gave us a chance
to check out the backyard.
- Big, isn't it?
Let's go, come on I'll show
you the rest of the house.
If I can find the keys, okay.
So what's great about
this layout is that you
can convert the media
room into a third bedroom.
That's room to grow.
- How many square feet is it?
- About 1600 square feet.
(cell phone buzzing)
Oh, excuse me for a second.
Hello.
Oh, you're kidding.
Jesus Christ, I'll
be right there.
I am so sorry, but...
Unbelievable.
What the hell happened?
- [Cameron] It's nothing,
she just ran out of money,
so they kicked her out.
- I'm sorry, I
rushed my clients out
of the house so I
could give her a ride?
Who are you?
- Hi, I'm Michelle.
- Hi, Michelle.
Who's Michelle?
- Oh, my God, Ma, you're
gonna drive me fucking crazy.
- I'm gonna drive
you fucking crazy?
- Yeah.
- This is the third
time this week you have
called me with this
bullshit, Cameron, come on!
I'm trying to keep this job.
- I know, but she has
nowhere else to go!
So she's gonna be staying
with us for a few days, okay?
- Oh, great.
- Come on, you know I love you.
(speaking foreign language)
- You're gonna make me crazy.
You're gonna kill me.
- Thank you so much.
- Come on, let's go,
bring your pink bag.
Get her bag, be a
gentlemen at least.
- No.
I'm not raising
someone else's kid.
- It's only a few days.
- A few days.
A few days turn into a few
weeks, turns into a few months.
No!
- I already told
her she could stay.
- Untell her.
She isn't staying.
And Cameron needs to think about
getting his own place, too.
- What does that mean?
So you're gonna kick him out
now, is that what's happening?
So that's your answer now
for everything, right?
You just wanna kick him out.
- Cecilia, what are you doing?
You're losing
sight of everything
because you can't cut the
fucking umbilical cord!
You already gave birth to him.
You're waiting around
for him to kill you?
He almost killed me!
He has you in the palm of his
hand and you can't see it!
You need to make the choice.
Yeah, I'm telling you right now.
Make a choice!
- Oh yeah, go, walk away Bill!
That's what you always
do, anyway, you disappear!
- Bullshit!
I've been right
here the whole time!
Paying my dues!
But you don't see me anymore!
No!
Look at me!
Look what he's done to me!
What you've done to me!
(sobbing)
(laughs)
You remember when
you had to play
the pumpkin in that
Thanksgiving play?
You had to get your
hair cut but that guy
in the barber shop didn't
know how to cut your hair?
So you gave yourself a buzz cut.
(laughs)
I remember when we went
to that amusement park
and you wanted to get
on that roller coaster.
You made me get in
the front with you.
You made me get on that
five times in the front.
I was so scared.
And you kept saying, you
just gotta let go, Ma.
You just gotta let go.
Was this my fault?
- Alex and I cleaned everything.
Washed everything ourselves.
We didn't want them
to touch his things
any more than they already have.
I've been doing some
reading about well,
how to pass the time, I guess.
- What's this?
- [Sam] Singing classes.
- Singing classes?
- Yeah, to help take
your mind off things.
- Why does everyone
keep saying that?
Why does everybody
I don't wanna take
my mind off it.
My son just died.
I don't wanna take
my mind off that.
This just isn't the same.
None of this is the same.
- I'll wait for you downstairs.
Let me know if you
need anything, okay?
(somber opera music)
- They didn't.
It's empty!
Why is this empty?
(sighing)
(sniffing)
I can't smell him.
No!
(sobbing)
No, no, no, no!
No, no, no!
(screaming)
- [Cameron] Ta-da!
- No, no, no Cam, no.
- Come on.
- Babe, once you
start doing that shit.
Come on, just smoke it.
Or chip it, I'll do it with you.
- No, you're not.
- Yeah, I am, come on.
I'll do it with you.
- Let me just, let me
just do it this one time.
I'll do it here, with you, safe.
Besides, I gotta
test the merchandise.
Quality control.
This is work.
- I'm still pretty toasted.
You're not high?
- Yeah, but this is different.
Get me a spoon?
(rap music)
* Can't take it
* What life you wanna live
* What path you tryin' to go
* Reflection on my city
* All I see is blow
* Nobody ever gave
me shit, though *
* Why you watchin' me go
* Wanna a piece of this life
* That's history
* Middle finger's up
I'm chasing three *
* Father told me
don't grab game *
* Don't game, the same thing
* B-I-G, I'm screamin' it
* Street life, I'm meanin' it
* Feet forward,
I gotta get out *
* Bright lights
and gold chains *
* Long nights, I'm not free
* Fuck that, I know me
* Greater self, I owe me
* Almost took my life at 19
* Honestly, you don't know me
* Make a toast for
these young kings *
* Only thing got fast me
* All our rappers they're ADT
* I'm so high my nose bleed
* These second people
they don't know me *
* Take it all
* I can't take it
* I can't, I can't take it
(fast rap music)
- Get out, get out!
I will kill you
before you kill me!
- Bill, what the
hell are you doing?
- Cecilia, I've had it!
I'm not gonna take
his shit anymore!
No more!
- He sold the car.
- Dad's car?
- Yeah.
He said he heard a number
on the radio, called,
they came, they took the car,
they gave him $200 dollars.
I'm afraid of him.
For him, for all of us.
You know, we've had
to start sleeping
with the doors locked at night.
The other night I woke up
and he was hovering over me.
He said he's been hearing voices
in his head and they
tell him what to do.
- Oh yeah, right, so
now he's schizophrenic?
- Oh, Sam.
You know, when you were little
I was scared of this moment.
The moment when
children stop being
children and they become adults.
But it never comes.
No matter what you do
or how bad it gets,
you'll always be
my little babies.
- How much is in there?
- [Cecilia] 10 grand.
- [Alex] What did Dad say?
- He doesn't know.
- He lied to us.
- Have you thought about what
you're gonna do with the money?
- What do you mean?
- It's a lot of money.
- I'm not taking that money.
- You can cover the
funeral expenses with it.
- I already said, I'm
not touching that money.
- [Sam] Why not?
- Why not?
What's the matter with you?
Think for a second!
- It's true though, you've
already lost so much.
- That money got
your brother killed!
- Yeah, we understand that, Mom,
but right now you
and Dad need it.
- How much did you loan
me for the funeral?
- Oh, that doesn't matter.
- Alex, how much did
you lend me, two grand?
- Mom, please.
- Here, here you
go, take the money.
Take the money.
Alright, you happy?
Now get the hell out!
Get out, get the hell out!
Go!
(melancholy violin music)
- Whoa.
- Jesus.
- Watch where
you're going, bitch.
- [Michelle Voiceover]
This dude owns a Maserati!
- [Cameron Voiceover]
Ma, you know who he is.
The guy with the Maserati.
(dramatic music)
(knocking)
- Oh, shit.
(speaking foreign language)
What are you doing here?
- Why haven't you
returned my calls?
- I've been busy.
- Yeah, Dad spoke to me.
He said you didn't
come home last night.
- Sam, please.
- You're losing the house?
What happened to
you getting a job?
It's always gonna be
like this, isn't it?
- Like what, huh?
Like what?
Am I supposed to just forget
that my son died six months ago?
Or that the man who killed him
is out there
walking around free?
- How do you know that?
- You lied to me, Sam!
You lied to me!
I saw him!
I smelled him!
I looked into his eyes
and you know what?
He had no idea who I was
or what he did to me.
So, I'm sorry if this is all
a little bit too emotional
for you, but right now
my world has changed!
- Yeah, well you're not alone!
I loved Cameron, too!
But do you think he cared about
the pain that he brought us?
The danger he put us in?
No!
I think about how lucky
we were to have left
before everything
happened in that house!
That's what I think
about and I think
about it every single day!
And I'm thankful.
You know, I was thankful for
the fact that I
was alive after it.
I was thankful for the
fact that you were safe.
And a part of me was
thankful for the peace
that I thought that his
death would bring our family!
- You son of a bitch!
- Mom, Mom!
Mom, Mom, you stop!
He's gone, alright?
He's gone!
He's fucking gone
and oh my, God,
the way that he still haunts our
family is just
fucking unbelievable!
So I don't know
what your plans are,
I don't know if you're gonna let
this destroy you, but
I'm done and I'm gone.
- Sam.
Sam!
(dramatic music)
Don't move.
I think about everything
you've taken from me.
Everything I've
loved and I think
there must be a
reason for all this.
There must be a balance.
Maybe this will
help tip the scales.
(gun firing)
(Bosco gasping)
- I can't move, I can't move!
Help me!
No, no, no, no, fuck!
- Rot in hell, you
son of a bitch.
(muffled yelling)
(gasping)
(haunting laughter)
Cameron?
(gasping)
(dramatic music)
(speaking foreign language)
- What the hell did
you bring in with you?
I felt you coming.
Come on.
Why did you come here?
- I need help.
- Yes, you do.
- I need to get rid of someone.
(speaking foreign language)
- A curse?
I think I have a better
solution for you.
- I don't understand.
- [Sorida] You will.
- Why are you so
fucking nervous?
We haven't done anything yet.
Sweetheart, lose the shades.
Put your hands up against
the fucking fence.
- What?
- Come on, let's
go, I'm in a hurry.
- [Cecilia] What are you doing?
- I wanna make sure
you're not a goddamn cop.
- I, I'm not a cop.
- Stop moving.
- So, what do we do now?
- You got a picture,
a name, an address?
What do you got?
- [Cecilia] Yes, all of it.
- Give it to me.
What did he do?
No, actually, I don't really
give a fuck, I had a long week.
My fee is $6,000 dollars,
cash, upfront, not negotiable.
Do you understand that?
- Okay.
Anything else?
- I'll call you and I'll
see you in a few days.
You are fucking late.
- I'm sorry.
- We're on, 5 p.m.
- [Sam] How is she?
- I don't know.
Remember I told you about Miami?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Me and Deanna
are gonna head down
there this weekend and
check out this house.
- Oh.
- Her parents said we could stay
with them until
we find something.
- That's great,
that's great, wow.
I hear the housing market is
looking really great down there.
- Yeah, it's picking up.
Alright, man.
I gotta get back to work.
Call you later.
- Alex, hey.
- It's a book.
- Yeah, it's a book.
- Thanks, Mom.
(tense music)
- It's 5:15, where are you?
You told me to be
here at 5 o'clock.
Call me back!
Shit!
Where is he?
- [Sorida] What?
- The man you sent me to.
Where is he?
- I don't know where he is.
- You gave me his number,
don't tell me you
don't know where he is.
(speaking foreign language)
- Stop!
- What are you gonna
do with that? (laughs)
You're not gonna kill me.
- Just tell me where he is.
- You've known from
the moment you walked
in here what you
had to do yourself!
- Give me back the
money I gave you.
- Or what?
You gonna call the police?
Tell them you wanted me
to hire you a hit man?
(laughing)
- [Cecilia Voiceover]
You're to blame.
Maybe you are.
(kissing)
- [Cameron] Okay, okay.
- [Sorida Voiceover] You've
known from the moment you walked
in here what you
had to do yourself!
- [Cecilia Voiceover]
I love you, papa.
- [Cameron Voiceover]
I love you too, Mom.
I'm gonna go clean.
I promise.
(speaking foreign language)
(tires screeching)
(knocking)
(gun firing)
- [Cecilia Voiceover]
Sam, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
(melancholy music)