Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
(vocalizing)
(bubbling)
(muttering)
(clanking)
(vocalizing)
(♪♪♪)
Okay, roll up like a ball.
- Yeah.
- This feels super comfortable.
♪ To the land of the Big Apple,
the land of the harvest ♪
♪ Where the sun never sets ♪
♪ And all of my dreams
are gonna come true ♪
Make space for the baby.
♪ I just wanna live ♪
♪ The American lifestyle ♪
Oh, it's heavy.
(indistinct remarks)
♪ I'll make friends
with celebrities ♪
♪ And their nose jobs
will be on me ♪
♪ I just wanna live ♪
♪ The American lifestyle ♪
♪ And I just wanna live ♪
You wanna really remember
that the baby
is coming out of your vagina
and not your face.
Like, imagine you're
sitting on the toilet
and you're taking a big poop.
You're face is usually like...
You might be
making some tension,
but you're really focusing in
down on your bottom.
- Mhm, yeah.
- Right?
Next time you pee,
just notice what you're doing
with your face.
(♪♪♪)
♪ I just wanna live ♪
♪ The American lifestyle ♪
♪ That American lifestyle ♪
♪ And I just wanna live ♪
♪ The American lifestyle ♪
(glass shattering)
Is this my pee face?
So, clue me in.
Tell me a little bit
about how you're feeling.
Like, how's everything going?
How's it all?
I think pretty good.
Um.
I'm hormonal.
- Mhm.
- I do feel like...
(clearing throat)
(chuckling)
Do you have something to say?
We... we had kind of
a Defcon 3 meltdown
in Target the other day.
- It was about car seats.
- Yeah.
We read all this stuff online,
all the safety things,
all the recommendations,
and...
and I had a friend say,
"You know, this one's great
'cause it's the lightest one."
The Chicco that goes...
- Yeah.
- That's, yeah, interchangeable.
- But, once we get there,
I saw it was also
the cheapest one,
and then that made me
so uncomfortable,
'cause then I didn't trust it,
and then I, like...
I felt like a shitty mom
for going to buy
the cheapest car seat
'cause it was the lightest one,
and it was the one
that was recommended to me,
but it wasn't
the highest rated one.
Hm.
(sighing)
I, like, totally lost it.
We didn't wind up
with that car seat.
- Okay.
- Um.
And... and we've never
done this before,
so we don't know what...
what the right thing to do is.
We don't know
what the right way to go is.
But, I mean,
I know that my tendency
is to... you know,
I get anxious about this stuff,
- and...
- Yeah.
And then, I try
to mitigate my anxiousness
- with control, and...
- And when he gets,
like, high tense
and controlling about stuff,
then I start
to just take care of him,
and I totally throw myself
out the window...
Right, she's trying
to take care of me,
and controlling the situation,
which... which pisses me off,
because we just keep
triggering each other, and...
Like, we've always,
you know, kinda sometimes
we just get into
a cycle of, like,
- Caretaking, controlling...
- Caretaking, controlling.
But, I would say it's like
- mm, mm, mm, because of that.
- It's on steroids.
So, why don't you just
take a deep breath?
Okay.
(breathing deeply)
Now, close your eyes
for a second,
both of you,
and I want you
to think about is,
what do you need most
from each other
to get through the rest
of this pregnancy?
And how can you
best show up for each other
and make sure that
those needs get met?
(birds chirping)
(♪♪♪)
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Bye.
Okay.
(♪♪♪)
Oh, don't forget, oxytocin.
At least one orgasm a day, okay?
One orgasm every day.
- Just one.
- For both of us?
- More her, you...
- It's my oxytocin.
- It's hers.
- It's my oxytocin, too.
- One.
- Bye.
Bye.
(♪♪♪)
(overlapping conversations)
- These kinda go together.
- I like this one.
His and her?
These are for us to wear, right?
Yeah.
(indistinct chattering)
(♪♪♪)
You don't have to watch us open,
especially if you got us
a shitty gift,
but if you want to,
we're gonna be determining
which ones of you
are our close friends,
and which ones of you
are expendable, so.
- Ohh.
(♪♪♪)
- Oh, my God, it's the Chicco!
- Oh, man.
- That's cool.
- Oh, my God, it's a car seat.
It's a good one, it's light,
it's not too heavy,
so you can pop it out,
and I'll teach you
a little trick for how to,
like, loop your arm under,
- and it makes it easier to...
- It's a huge gift.
- Kids do well with it, and...
- So, yeah, and the breastfeed,
it, like, really hurts
for a long time.
Oh, my gosh, she talked about
the latch-on like it was so hard
for new Rudi be able
to latch on,
and she just, like,
"Near, near near,"
like a little gremlin,
just biting and trying to,
like, suck you dry
of every little ounce of life
- in your soul.
- The only part of it
that is cute is, like,
your friend who, like,
posts a beautiful photo of her
breastfeeding on social media.
(overlapping remarks)
It's like, "Uh-huh, okay."
- Nature at its best.
- I've got, like, the cracked,
bleeding nipples,
and you're just like,
"Fuck you."
It's cute, it's cute.
Well, that's the thing,
and I feel like women,
and correct me if I'm...
if I'm speaking out of turn,
but I feel like women
do other women a real disservice
when they talk about
their birth experience,
like, "Oh, my God,
it was so wonderful."
I think that that's
a really messed up thing to do
to somebody who's about to
go into childbirth,
'cause you should prepared
that it's gonna be
the worst thing ever.
It is, sometimes it just tears
all the way down.
But, that's just the beginning,
and that's gonna be, like,
one to two days tops of...
of your life,
and then it really... begins
- to like...
- Do you guys have a method
- that, like, you're in?
- Your, um, parenting method.
So, we've been doing, um...
been doing these RIE classes.
- Uh-oh.
- Which are pretty cool.
- Yeah.
- Read the Janet Lansbury books,
- which are fantastic.
- And Babywise.
- Babywise.
- To get around
our sleep schedules,
so like, we know when
her cry phase will be, and...
I think picking and choosing
different pieces
from different books
is totally fine, that's great.
But, you have to decide, like,
"Are we gonna have
a family bed?"
Like, is she gonna
sleep with you guys.
- That's what we did.
- We did not do that.
We had her sleeping with us
until she was, like, 5?
- Yeah, about 5 years old.
- Were you guys just
afraid of, like, crib death,
is that why you...?
- Yeah, that was...
- Well, that was one of
the big things, of course,
it's crib death.
We wanted to
keep her close to us.
But, I mean, she is a girl,
so I mean,
it's not that high crib deaths
for... for girls baby...
You keep saying "crib death"
like that's a thing to...
- It's... it's a thing.
- Well, yeah, it is.
(overlapping remarks)
It's... for a while it's hell,
so just be prepared
- that it's gonna be...
- You don't get a lot of sleep
- at all.
- As soon as they're born,
you will no longer do anything
that you enjoy, because...
Your baby dictates
who you will become.
You don't get to
be yourselves anymore,
'cause you're so tired,
and so focused
on making sure that you're not
ruining this kid's life,
and you're trying to make sure
that you're doing it
in a healthy way,
in a productive way,
in a happy way.
You're not gonna repeat
your parents' mistakes,
you're not gonna
do the wrong things,
- and you do.
- Yep.
- You just do.
- Watching my parents
deteriorate in front
of my eyes as a child,
and not really understand
what it was,
I feel like you can
see them shrinking from
- who they wanted to be.
- You're basically
- getting thrown into war.
- You don't have time
for yourself, you just don't,
like...
My mother didn't wanna
become her mother.
Her mother didn't wanna
- My sister didn't wanna become...
- And you see it, you know it,
you hate it,
- but you can't stop...
- My dad had his money in order,
had, you know,
a record collection,
all this cool stuff.
He had a car
that he really liked,
he cared about his fucking car,
and then at a certain point,
everything was annihilated.
I saw that happen, I saw a man
deteriorate in front of my eyes
as a teenager.
I... it was a nightmare.
I can't... I couldn't do it.
(♪♪♪)
But, you guys
are gonna kill it, I...
(chuckling)
Yeah.
Babe, babe, can you...
can you please tell me what's...?
Jackie.
Can you... can you just stop
for a second?
(whirring)
Babe,
can you look at me
and talk to me, please?
(whirring)
Babe.
What the fuck is this?
Hummus.
Did you not see this one?
- I...
- I got this one two days ago.
- I didn't... I didn't see that.
- It's huge.
Okay, I didn't see that,
but I don't think
- it's a big deal, can we not...?
- Now, we're just never gonna
get through both of these
before they go bad.
- Oh, okay, but...
- This one's huge.
I... I didn't see it,
I didn't look.
I was also... you gave me
the list with the bok choy
- and the tamarind.
- Yeah, I gave you a list.
I was just trying
to do a nice thing.
I'm just asking you
to do an aware thing.
Look, we've...
we've already eaten some.
Look, there's already
that much out...
You're making that up,
you're, like, making that up
- to make your argument stronger.
- Okay.
The seal is still on it.
Okay, okay,
so the seal's still on it,
- but... but the way they pack...
- Why would you lie to me
and be like,
"We already ate some"?
I mean, look,
it's not that full.
- It's like a potato chip...
- You actually think we're gonna
eat all of this
before this one...
- Yes!
- ...goes bad?
- We eat a lot of hummus.
- We would never eat this much.
- We've definitely eaten...
- When?
- When? When?
- two things of hummus in a week.
Okay, this is not... do you hear
yourself talking right now?
Do you hear yourself talking?
You're, like, making shit up
- about the stuff we do!
- Would you fucking stop?
I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to yell.
Would you just stop?
Because you're getting
really stressed out,
and the OB said
you can't get stressed out.
Babe, please don't cry.
I'm... I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Look, this was all my fault.
I should've absolutely seen
that you bought hummus
two days ago.
I was trying to do a nice thing,
but you're right, it was stupid.
It wasn't a nice thing.
It was a stupid
and oblivious thing,
and, hey, stop, stop,
please, please, please?
Babe,
I'm really sorry.
Hey.
(tearing)
Ew.
Why did you just
put your hand in it?
If having too much hummus
is an issue,
then I'm gonna
take care of the issue.
Whether it makes sense
to me or not.
It looks...
you're not enjoying it.
This is the best hummus
I've ever had.
(laughing)
I love this hummus so much.
Oh, my gosh, I mean...
- Ugh, the smell.
- This is fun.
The smell, please stop.
Please stop putting it
in your mouth,
- stop putting it in your mouth.
- And I'm gonna eat that one
- after I'm done with this.
- No.
- And we're not gonna
have enough, are we?
And we're gonna have to
go shopping for more hummus
later on this afternoon.
- Don't you fucking dare.
- 'Cause I'm gonna be
a hummus-eating machine.
Don't put it in your mouth,
it's so...
Ugh!
Oh, God, sorry, that's so gross.
- I just wanna establish that...
- Oh, God.
In this case, your concern
about our... our hummus overage,
um,
might've just been rectified,
'cause look, look,
that one's half gone.
- It's half gone.
- And here's a vow
that I make to you:
I will never, ever, ever
buy too much hummus again.
- Never.
I really appreciate that.
(♪♪♪)
(sniffling)
There are gonna be times when
I probably want more hummus.
If you ask me to buy you hummus,
I'll go out and buy you hummus
that minute.
(sniffling)
Hm?
(♪♪♪)
(chuckling)
- Oh, God.
- Mm.
- It's smelling.
(chuckling)
What are you doing?
Maya said, "Once a day."
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
- What?
- Do you still have
hummus in your mouth?
- No, I swallowed the hummus.
- I think there's probably
- still some there.
- No, I think I...
- Yeah, but...
- I think I swallowed it.
I can smell it still, so.
What if you...?
No, it's so...
I'm super turned on,
but if you, like,
maybe just
brush your teeth, or...?
- 'Cause of bacteria.
- Okay.
I could go for it, but it...
it's the bacteria
- and the baby.
- Okay, yeah.
I'll go brush my teeth.
And then, I'm gonna be...
I'll meet you upstairs.
Thank you.
(♪♪♪)
You're right,
it was the whole day.
It was the whole day.
- I know.
- Our friends...
- suck.
- I know, our friends suck.
They were so discouraging.
It's still a little...
I still smell it.
- You're such a dick.
- I'm a super smeller.
(streaming)
Who brings up crib death
at our baby shower?
Mhm, I know.
- Who does that?
- I know.
They said my vagina
is gonna rip down.
To your asshole.
I don't mean to laugh,
because I know
- that would really suck.
- Apparently it happens
- all the time.
- I am just laughing
at the severe insensitivity
of our asshole friends
that they would bring it up
at our fucking baby shower.
I truly don't think
they want us to be parents.
What, you think they want us
to have an abortion?
Third-term abortion.
I do.
- Oh, that's so dark.
- I do, I think they were trying
- to convince us...
- That's so dark
to go into the OB, be like,
"Um, here's the thing:
we know we were
- really excited...
- "We were, we were excited."
...about having this kid, but..."
"But, we had a...
we had a baby shower."
"And our friends
really fucked us up,
and now we're wondering
if you could
take her out, and just, like,
- get rid of her."
- You need to kiss her
after this joke,
this joke is too bad.
- Baby, it's really dark and...
- Baby.
Dark, bad jokes
for a dark, bad baby shower.
(kissing)
But, they were so serious
about... turning out
like their parents.
I know, but you know what?
And it's true.
- But, you know what?
- They have.
But, in fairness, B's always
been a living nightmare, and...
But now,
she's exactly like her mom.
Hey, babe, it's okay.
- You know why?
- Why?
'Cause we're cooler
than they are.
(♪♪♪)
Come on, take your pants off,
come to bed.
(♪♪♪)
Fuck.
Honey,
I have to tell you something
before I take my pants off.
No, take your pants off,
then you can tell me something.
- That's so bad.
- No, can you just
take your pants off first,
and then you can
tell me something
if you have to?
(♪♪♪)
Take your pants off.
I got a text from my dad
at the baby shower.
(sighing)
I'm so sorry.
Ugh.
- No.
- He said he was gonna
be evicted.
No.
Um, I know.
- I know, honey, I know...
- How much did you send him?
2,000.
I'm... I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
(breathing deeply)
(grunting)
Woo.
Babe, your dad is always
about to be evicted,
because your dad
is a fucking drug addict
who spends
all his money on oxys.
You swore.
- You swore to God...
- I know, I did.
...the last four times,
not just, like,
the last time it happened.
The last four times it happened
you swore to me
- that you'd never do it again.
- I did.
- You swore to your sponsor.
You swore to our therapist.
- I did.
- We sat down
and we had this discussion,
and you said,
- "I'm never gonna do it again."
- I know.
That's the fucking kid's money
that you just gave him.
You are so, so right,
and I know you're so, so right.
Can you... can you not
turn this into, like,
"You're so right,"
self-flagellation stuff?
Can you just let me be
really pissed for a second?
Yes.
Thank you.
Okay, that's all I needed.
(sighing)
- Oh, man.
- It's not fair.
- That's a bummer.
- It's such a bummer.
It was just habit,
but I know I...
I can't, I gotta change.
Well, we both have...
look, I just...
I just... my first reaction
when I was upset
- was to, like, do that.
- It's very scary.
And... and I don't...
I mean, how many
fucking hundreds of hours
in therapy have I spent
trying to work through
my rage issues.
- There's still...
- A hole.
The hole in the sheetrock
from... from, like,
a month and a half ago,
and that's insane.
It's like,
if we don't
pull our shit together,
- she's gonna...
- We're gonna fuck up our kid.
Mm.
Like, we signed up
for each other's madness.
- I know.
- She didn't sign up for it.
I know, it makes me
really sad actually.
The therapy has made us aware.
- Mhm.
- But, clearly...
Hasn't actually changed
our behavior enough.
It's like we need to,
like, shake ourselves,
'cause we gotta pull it together
before we're parents.
And I'm scared, too,
because we've got
- a month.
- What if we shake it up?
What if we challenge each other?
What if we challenge
each other to, like,
activities and tasks?
Like, we have a month...
- I like this.
- ...before this baby is coming.
- That is time.
- We got...
- We got four weeks...
- It's a short amount.
to become fully realized humans.
(vocalizing)
To be parents.
- Okay, so we got four weeks.
- Let's do something.
- Let's do it, let's do it.
- Let's do it, let's change.
Let's do it.
- What are we gonna do?
- More... let's, like...
Let's jump out of an airplane.
- Dine and dash.
- Dine and dash, I'm in.
- I'm in, let's do it.
- I mean, just to get ourselves,
- like, uncomfortable...
- Okay.
...and, like...
and see what we're made of.
We could, uh...
we could buy a classic car
and drive it up the coast.
Like, we go to Antarctica.
Great, we dive under an icecap,
and swim around,
and we come up, and woo!
- Yeah, yeah!
We could jump off a cliff
into the ocean.
- Um, we could swim with sharks.
- We could graffiti something.
Uh, we could get tattoos.
- Let's, um...
- Go to a punk-rock show.
- Mosh pit.
- We buy a falcon.
- I would love a falcon.
- Oh, yeah.
- Sitting on the porch.
- Um.
We could...
let's get chased by the cops.
We could do anything honestly.
We could... but we could both take
- pole dancing classes.
- I could fuck you in the ass.
(chuckling)
That's funny.
(laughing)
- Yeah, no.
- Okay, what else could we do?
- No, but, honey.
- What?
- Actually that one...
- Oh, we're not playing a game,
- you're serious now.
- All the other ones
it's super fun to think of,
but we actually
can't travel right now,
'cause of the baby,
and we can't put her
in dangerous situations.
Like... like, it's fun to think
about jumping out of a plane,
but I'm never gonna
do that with a baby,
but... but what about
pegging?
- Because that's...
- I... I... I...
- ...intimate.
- I just got...
It is intimate,
I don't see how it really
prepares us
to become better parents
- in a month.
- No, but it... it makes us
- deal with stuff.
- Ugh.
It's an act... it's so actionable.
Yeah, no,
it's definitely actionable.
I read this article
and it's like it's supposed
- to be so empowering.
- Mhm.
And it... and honestly,
it really deals with our issues
in a way where...
'cause I'm always being
a caretaker,
and I'm always, like...
Like, when we have sex,
I receive you and I hold you,
and I'm always going
- with your rhythm.
- I wait until you come
- until I come every single time.
- Which is... which is awesome.
No, you are
a very generous lover,
you're very good, but it is
like a waiting for you...
it is... there is, like, um...
you're in control,
and what if
you weren't in control?
Hm?
I mean, it would be so...
remember what Maya said?
Yeah, when... when we were
humming the song back then,
I didn't think it was leading
to fucking me in the ass.
(sighing)
- Honey.
- Uh-huh?
I feel like I need this.
(♪♪♪)
(beeping)
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hi.
So, this is our sweet spot.
First time, it's so exciting.
I remember my first time
like it was,
uh, 10 years ago.
(chuckling)
Uh, I guess it kinda depends
on who this is for.
I mean, obviously it's
for both of you, right?
Yeah, more for her
in this case than for me,
- but yeah.
- I think for you...
- Mhm.
- ...you might like something
- with vibration because...
- Nah.
...you'll also have a bit
of clitoral stimulation during.
- Ooh.
- So, that could be really nice.
I think... I think we don't
need to do vibration.
Let's just...
let's skip the vibration.
Let's skip
any bells and whistles,
and really
what we're looking for
is just kinda the VW Bug
of strap-ons.
We do have
a beginner strap-on actually.
Oh, that is, that says,
"Beginner strap-on" right there,
- "For him."
- It's 4-and-a-half inches.
- Okay.
- So, I think plus belly...
I was gonna say, if...
do we need, like...
I think you're gonna
want more length, personally.
Personally, I would say
you're gonna want more length
given belly and.
Okay, I would suggest
going modular.
We've got
a couple harness options.
This is our most popular,
this is my favorite.
- I have this one actually.
- Oh, you have this one?
Yeah, this one's
really, really great.
Super well priced,
really easy to use.
Um, not super intimidating.
Can you just tell me, what...
what are these?
This is, um, if you want
a dick on your dick.
Uh, oh, that's just if...
- Length.
- ...you have a small dick
- and you want a bigger dick?
- You don't necessarily
have to have a small dick,
it's for any size dick,
but if you want more length.
So, I... I would go here.
It's a really good color.
- If it's your favorite.
- Yeah, I would go here.
- And then...
- Can I just ask,
um, is something that you use
with your current partner?
It is something I have used
with past partners, yes.
Um, and without
getting too personal...
I guess as a general question,
'cause I think
what he's getting at is,
a lot of straight couples
- use this, right?
- Definitely.
- That's what I was asking.
- Definitely, plenty of
- straight couples use these.
- But, is your partner a...?
So, I would say
this would be
a great place to go
if you wanna
go for something modular,
where you can purchase
a harness and also a dildo.
And are these the only
two options for dildos?
No, we have a plethora
of options.
Uh, would you like to see them?
- Okay, there we go.
- Good.
- And that'll be all?
- And some of this.
- Plus lube, okay.
- I got this one.
- Thanks, babe.
- Yeah.
(♪♪♪)
All right, come here,
I love you.
I just want you to know
your mama's dick
is bigger than mine is,
and, um, I'm okay with that,
because I am
a modern, evolved man
- in a modern, evolved world.
- Mhm.
And, um, that doesn't make me
feel insecure at all.
- Okay, okay.
- Mhm.
Okay, okay.
- I like this angle.
- Thanks.
I'm gonna need your butt
a little higher.
- Okay.
- Like, put a little arch
in your back, a little cat cow.
- Uh-huh.
- Okay.
Just... I know
what you're feeling.
- Uh-huh, uh-huh.
- I've been there.
Just put the weight
on the elbows.
- Okay.
- And let yourself
rock forward.
It's better, right?
You're gonna feel
- a little something...
- Okay!
Um, stop, stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop.
- I didn't even put it in.
- I know.
If I say, "Stop,"
you stop immediately.
- Immediately.
- Safe word:
"Immediately."
"Immediately" is our safe word?
No, "stop" is our safe word,
I'm just... I was just trying
to reiterate
that if I say, "Stop,"
that you immediately stop.
Yes, and maybe,
just throwing out there,
we pause,
as opposed to, like,
pull everything apart.
Okay, except if I tell you
to pull it out, you pull it out.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Okay, I just, you know,
- I would do the same for you.
- You would?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Just breathe.
- Okay, huh!
- Huh!
- It's a familiar.
- It's me.
- Ah, ah, ah, ah!
Breathe.
It's okay, are you okay?
- Mhm.
- Okay, I want you to...
I want you to enjoy it,
and if you don't, it's...
we're just gonna pause.
Just let me breathe, just stop
right there and let me breathe.
Uh-huh.
(breathing laboriously)
You're doing so good.
- You're doing so good, baby.
- Okay.
I'm just gonna...
your back is all sweaty.
- Okay, um...
- Like it, do you like it?
- Yeah, I'm just...
- You do?
- I'm gonna move for a second.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Yeah, lean in.
- Uh-huh.
That's what it looks like.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Get it.
- Okay.
- Oh, sweetie!
- Ah, ah!
- Oh, sweetie.
- Uh-huh, uh-huh.
- Ah, ah!
- Oh, sweetie, sweetie!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
- Ah, ah!
Yeah!
Yeah.
(♪♪♪)
I'm... I'm the woman.
I'm the woman.
(♪♪♪)
(grunting)
Honey?
Are you okay?
Yes, and I'm sorry.
(♪♪♪)
Where'd you fucking go?
Fuck!
(♪♪♪)
(whirring)
(birds chirping)
(yawning)
(squealing)
You're awake?
Mhm.
- Good mornin'.
- Good morning, baby.
I feel great!
- Great.
- Honey,
I just slept through
the whole night.
I know, you didn't
get up and pee, or anything.
I can't believe it.
Uh, you deserve it.
It's like a miracle.
I haven't slept a whole night
the entire third trimester.
I know.
Ahh.
I'm glad.
I wore myself out yesterday.
- Yeah, you sure did.
- Yep.
Yeah.
Oh, how do you feel?
Mm, I'm okay.
I feel a little funny,
I didn't sleep much,
- but I'm all right.
- No?
Uh-uh, it was a bit
of a fraught night.
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- I felt so profoundly...
...completed.
I really appreciate it,
I'm sorry you had
such a bad night.
- Mm.
- I mean, don't you feel
like we...
we broke the mold?
I feel like I... I broke the...
the mold in some way.
I, like, feel funky and weird.
- Hm.
- Like,
we can do anything.
There's no rules,
Hm.
No.
I think...
I mean,
okay, if I'm being
totally honest.
Mhm, which I want you to be.
Okay.
Um.
Do you know how many times
my dad used the word "faggot"
when I was a kid?
That's so bad.
Like, "Faggot this,
and faggot that."
And that didn't even
really mean "gay."
It just meant
"weak."
And so, here I am,
an adult man,
who's in
a loving relationship...
- Mhm.
- ...with a strong
and beautiful woman, who has,
at least biologically speaking,
- proved my manliness.
- Totally.
And all of a sudden
we're doing this thing
where we're... we're conducting
this experiment.
- Yeah?
- And then, the second
it felt good,
my head came back in,
and it was like, "What,
'cause you're a faggot?"
- Okay.
- And... and... and that's terrible,
and I'm sorry
I keep using that word.
It's just,
it's obviously not me talking.
- Yeah.
- It's... it's all the baggage
from my hometown,
and from growing up
- with an alpha father...
- Yeah.
...and... and so,
when I was downstairs,
I really started trying
to pick this apart
and go like, "What...
what's at the core of this?"
Because there's two things
that are competing inside of me.
One is that, um,
I wanna be your partner,
and I wanna be...
I wanna be truly open
to new experiences
in the universe.
Um, and the other side is,
my dad was a homophobe,
and I just let my wife
fuck me in the ass,
and so all of a sudden
I felt like,
"You're not a man."
And then... and then,
I started thinking about
all of the therapy
that I've had,
and... and going like,
"Why is this... you know,
why is this such an issue?"
This shouldn't be such an issue,
and maybe I would like it
if we did it again.
If I could get past the shame.
If I could get past
all the stuff that's built up
in my head, and so I think
in the same way
that you had to
go on your journey
to feel more in control,
and... and to feel powerful,
I think I got
some work to do, too.
- Totally.
- You know?
Yeah, what do...
what do you wanna do?
I think I need to punch
somebody in the face.
That...
And also, I think
another important component
of this is that I need
to know what it feels like
to actually take
a full face punch.
You want somebody
to punch you...?
Punch me in the face.
I hate this.
(♪♪♪)
(indistinct remarks)
Okay, jab.
(♪♪♪)
- Hello!
- One, two, one, two.
Uh, hello, back here.
Okay, give me a jab.
- Hey, man.
- Give me a jab.
One, duck, two.
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey, what's up, man?
Ah, it's good to see you.
Hey, what's going on?
I'm Elliot.
- Hi.
- What's your name?
- I'm Josh.
- Josh, nice to meet you.
Elliot, Jackie,
these are my friends.
You guys look like
you're hanging tough in here.
Yeah, hooking it up...
what's up, man?
Uh, can I... can I steal you
for, like, 3 minutes?
- Uh, you cool with it?
- Yeah.
- Are we cool with that?
- Is that cool?
- 4 minutes, it'll be real quick.
- Okay, a couple.
- I got a little favor to ask.
- It's fine.
All right, Josh,
100 jumping jacks.
Count 'em out.
When you're done,
I'll be back, okay?
- All right.
- Okay.
- I'll bring him right back.
- All right.
One, two, three, four, five...
Um, so here's the thing.
Yeah?
I would like you
to hit me in the face
as hard as you can.
Fight Club.
Hm?
You're Fight Clubbing me?
Hey, did you do
a Fight Club to me?
(chuckling)
Oh, shit, that is from
Fight Club, isn't it?
No, I kinda...
in the back of my head,
I had some recognition,
but I didn't realize
- it was something...
- It was it exactly.
- That's exactly what it's from.
- Yeah.
Okay, so I know you have to
get back in there.
This is real quick,
if you could just punch me,
and, um, if it's okay...
if it's okay, I'd love to
be able to punch you back.
- That would be super helpful.
- I can't tell
if you guys are fucking with me.
- Is this real?
- It...
Yeah.
(laughing)
- No, no way.
- Okay, um.
You're out of your fucking mind.
I'm not gonna punch you.
- Here, here's the thing.
- In the face?
I swear to God
I won't be upset.
I won't either.
She won't either.
Okay, here's the thing.
Do you remember
at our baby shower
when you came
up to me at the end,
and you hugged me,
and you were just like,
"Brother, anything you need...
- Yeah.
- ...anything at all?"
- Yeah, I...
- This is it.
Not gonna do it, I'm sorry.
- I lied to you.
- This is it.
I can't.
- I've...
- Okay, so I'll tell,
I'll tell, I'll tell you why,
I'll tell you why
'cause I do think
it'll make a difference.
It's this thing that
- Jackie and I are doing...
- Okay.
...because, uh, because
we're about to have a baby...
- Yeah, yeah.
- ...and we're trying to become
fully realized humans.
I mean, you know,
I've talked to you about
my dad stuff, my rape stuff.
You know, I've been in therapy
since I was
fuckin' 18 years old.
And, obviously,
you know, they're like,
"You shouldn't punch people."
So, I punch walls,
I, like, kick things,
but what I've never done
in my entire life
is I've never been
punched in the face.
And my dad used to do
- this to me all the time.
- Yeah.
So, I am so afraid of this,
and I just, I, I just need,
- I need the full thing.
- Not happening.
I appreciate everything
you just told me.
I'm sorry you had a mean dad.
And whatever you guys
are going through
feels weird.
Uh, I can't help you with this.
I'm facing
my biggest fear.
This wall of fear.
And her and I together,
are gonna get over
that fuckin' wall.
Cool, man.
So we can be...
I'm not goin' over
the wall with you.
I don't need you to,
I just need you to punch me.
There's a kid
in the other room waiting.
You punch guys in the face
- every day!
- Yeah,
'cause I don't care
about them, and also...
Okay, can I punch
you in the face?
- No.
- Please?
Absolutely not.
I just need to
punch you in the face.
- Well, okay.
- Dude, no.
One of the two
is gonna happen.
Neither of the two are gonna
- happen actually.
- Okay, punch me in the face.
- I am not gonna...
- Punch me in the face.
- Elliot, I'm not gonna...
- I'm not punching...
- I'm gonna punch you in the face
if you don't punch
me in the face.
I'm gonna
punch you in the face.
You're not gonna
punch me in the face.
I'm gonna... Punch me in the face!
- No one's getting punched.
- Punch me in the face!
How 'bout this,
no one's fucking
- getting punched.
- I'm gonna punch you!
Ah!
(groaning)
Ho!
Ooh.
That was...
Are you bleeding?
- Ah, shit.
- You're fuckin' bleeding.
- Oh, brother!
- Fuckin' damn it, man.
I'm sorry, but that was amazing!
- What are you doing?
- Come on, that was amazing.
That wasn't amazing,
that was ridiculous.
Get the fuck outta here.
Josh, go in the other room.
- Oh!
- Okay, okay, so you're mad.
- Jackie...
- So, punch me in the face!
- I'm gonna...
- Come on, come on, come on,
- come on, come on.
- I need you to go.
Dude, dude, dude, dude, come...
(thudding)
Oh!
- Oh!
- Dude, I'm sorry.
Oh!
- Hey!
- Honey, honey.
- Elliot, I'm sorry.
- Oh, it's okay.
Flip over.
Oh, my God.
Dude, I'm so sorry.
Elliot, I'm so sorry.
(deliriously laughing)
You're okay?
Yeah.
- He's okay!
- Oh, I went out.
- I went out!
- Yeah.
Oh, that really...
- Fuck you!
- That was crazy!
Can I help you,
let me help you both up,
then you can get
the fuck out, okay?
- Sorry. You did it!
- Do I have a black eye?
- You do a little bit!
- Yeah, you have a black eye
'cause you're a fuckin' idiot.
Now, can you please leave?
Dude, I know
you're upset, but...
- You have no idea.
- ...it's the best thing
- in my entire life.
- I don't wanna
- hear it right now.
- Can I?
No, don't touch me.
Okay, some day
you're gonna understand.
No, I won't!
You'll be lucky if
we talk some day soon.
- Get the fuck out, Elliot.
- I love you.
- No, Jackie.
- Let's get out.
- Okay, I feel you.
- Let's go. Thank you.
No, don't thank me,
just fuckin' go.
♪ Been around a while
learned a thing or two ♪
(thunder rumbling)
♪ Been around a while
doin' what I do ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ When I tell ya
you know I'm tellin' the truth ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ When I tell ya ♪
♪ I'm better than you ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ Better than you ♪
♪ Been around a while
would I lie to you? ♪
♪ Would I lie to you? ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ Been around a while
I got a high IQ ♪
♪ I got a high IQ ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ When I tell ya
you know I'm tellin' the truth ♪
♪ I'm tellin' the truth ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ When I tell ya ♪
♪ I'm better than you ♪
♪ Better than you ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ Best solo ever ♪
♪ Better than you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
(♪♪♪)
First of all, we have to
- thank you.
- Oh, my God.
The things you said to us
- resonated.
- Something broke open.
- You asked the question...
- You were like,
- "What do you need?
- ..."What do you need?"
I've never been this
confident in my entire life!
That's, that's, that's great!
Also, when you were saying
you gotta trust each other,
- and, like, fuck everybody else.
- And fuck everybody else!
Everything in us went, "Whoa!
- Break the cycle."
- Like, stop.
What do we need?
- What would do that?
- Yeah, 'cause all that...
- And the oxytocin...
- Everything you,
everything you said
made sense in our brains,
- but we've never put it...
- But we had to do it.
- ..into effect.
- Got it.
And more stuff
with my dad, obviously.
- But, like, the thing...
- Her dad's money,
- drugs.
- I realized
I needed, sexually,
to give it.
- I needed to fuck him.
- She wanted to fuck me.
It just seemed like
the only answer..
So we went to a shop,
and we got a strap-on,
- and then we went home...
- And then...
...and we did it,
and it hurt,
um, for me.
For you...
Great, but emotionally,
- I felt like a rock star.
- Mm-hm.
- And then...
- And then, I cried.
I mean, I didn't cry
around you because I didn't,
I didn't want that to tamp down,
- you know, your moment because...
- And how nice is that?
And then it, the chain reaction.
Somehow, the Pavlovian
connection between
masculinity, and sexuality,
and violence,
the smallness I felt,
I was six years old again.
And I was sitting
at my kitchen table
in my childhood house,
and I just spilled
a glass of orange juice.
And my father turned, and he,
and he cocked a fist
like he was gonna punch me
because I spilled a fucking
glass of orange juice, okay?
And that fear has dictated
so many of the choices
that I've made
- my entire life.
- Like, the cycle of backing away
from that energy had to break.
Because I'm a grown-ass man,
and I'm about to be a father.
And so, I can't be scared.
I can't be scared of a fist,
or, like, a plastic dick
the way that I have
been my entire life.
So, I went to visit my friend.
- It was amazing!
- And I punched him in the face!
And he didn't...
I asked him at first,
I was like, "Can I, can I..."
Well, I asked him
if he'd punch me,
and he was like, "No,
I'm not gonna punch you."
And I was like, "Come on,
please, punch me."
- And he was like, "No!"
- Like, don't be a pussy!
(indistinct speaking)
- I punched him!
- Got it.
And then he still
wouldn't punch me!
So then...
(laughing)
- I was amazed.
- And then,
and then I saw it happen on his
face when he was just like...
And then, he was like
black out.
(indistinct speaking)
Just punched me in the face.
It was the best.
And then, and then...
(laughing)
...and then I'm
seeing stars for a second.
But, I could tell, like...
But then I came up,
- and I was clear as day.
- Yeah.
You know what,
give me a second.
I'll be right back,
I'm just gonna grab something.
She's the bomb.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
I could take a nap.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll take a nap.
Can we go take a nap?
- Wanna go take a nap?
- Just a midday nap?
And then go to a rave?
How 'bout the zoo?
You wanna go to the zoo?
I think they have
pandas there now.
Did they get pandas at the zoo?
So, this is for you.
What's this?
It's a full refund.
- Um.
- You deserve it!
You deserve so much
more than this.
It's really okay.
I don't think there's
any amount of money that
either of you could give me
that would make it okay
for us to work together.
Wha...
This whole thing, the eye,
the battery, the pegging,
- just there's a lot of...
- I don't think it's battery.
There's a lot of
liability issues here that
just make me feel
super uncomfortable.
So, I think it's probably gonna
be best if both of you just
- get up...
- Wait a minute.
- ...and leave.
- Babe?
- Wait a minute.
So, wait.
- You want us to go?
- Yeah.
Are you still
gonna be our doula?
No, no doula.
All done.
Finito.
Need you both
to get up, and leave.
(♪♪♪)
The thing that's just, like,
nuts is that it's not evident,
and it's not so apparent
- that this is amazing.
- Other people don't get it.
No, it's incredible.
How do other people not get it?
I mean, and that's hard.
If I didn't have you,
I'd be so lonely.
- Honey!
- To have these revelations,
- to really...
- I see them,
I see what you're going through.
...have my brain
break open in these ways.
And have other people
look at it and go like,
"Eh, not into it."
It's so weird 'cause I see you.
- You see me.
- And look, I get it with Zach.
Like, I punched my
dear friend in the face,
- and that might have been...
- Zach? Yeah.
...a little fucked up...
- But Maya.
- ...but still!
- Maya.
- She, like, talks the talk,
- but doesn't walk the walk.
- Walk the walk.
No, she's a fake truth teller.
Yeah, she's living
in her own lies.
Well, I think you,
I think we live in a culture
that's not prepared
for the truth.
I think we live in a culture
- that can't handle the truth.
- I think we do.
'Cause it's just easier
to lie to each other.
It is, like, how many times
has your mom been like,
"Do you like the casserole?"
and I'm like, "I love it!"
Oh, exactly, and how many times
has my mom been like,
"Was I a good mother?"
And I'm like, "Of course, Mom."
We do it, why?
Just because it's easier.
It's just like a path
of least resistance.
I know, and that's why
we're so fucked!
We're fucked as a country
because of this
- epidemic of lying.
- We're fucked as a world.
Maybe we have been afraid
of that with each other.
That's why we had a...
And now, for the first time,
we're like,
"I can totally show you me,
and you can
totally show me you."
- We can just, like, be like...
- And we love it!
...like, "This is me.
- This is me.
- And I love you!
You are everything!
- You are everything to me, babe.
- Oh.
I trust you more than anyone.
And you're gonna have my baby.
- And...
- I've been thinkin'.
What are you thinkin'?
- Since this whole Maya thing.
- Uh-huh.
Like, "Ah, where we
gonna find a Doula now?"
- I know what you're thinkin'.
- I don't, I don't think we need
some other stranger
coming into this.
We don't need
anybody else comin' in
and coaching us
on what the truth
of our experience is,
bringing our
baby into the world.
I think you can be my doula.
I've never seen
a better doula...
- That makes me...
- ...than the one right in
- front of me.
- ...makes me wanna cry.
- But, you're right.
- You can take the pain.
(♪♪♪)
♪ You sheltered me from harm ♪
♪ Kept me warm ♪
♪ You gave my life to me ♪
♪ Set me free ♪
♪ The finest years I ever knew ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ Were all the years
I had with you ♪
♪ And I would give
anything I own ♪
(♪♪♪)
We should probably get back
before it gets dark.
(♪♪♪)
Okay.
Let's go.
(♪♪♪)
(animal howling)
No! There's not
a path over here!
There's not a path over here!
It can't be that far.
We were just
on the fucking path!
No, we weren't
just on the path.
We were just on the path.
- We were coming down it.
- By "just," do you mean
20 minutes ago?
Now we're way off!
- Okay.
- Would you stop going up there?
I really know
the path is not up there.
I think we might
have to go back up
to go back down.
But down is
clearly the direction
we need to generally be going.
(animal howling)
Um.
Let's go, let's go this way.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, I think down
is a good idea.
- Ow! Ow.
- Ow.
- Ah! Ah! Fuck!
- Oh, my gosh.
- Okay, okay.
- We're... We've gone.
No, we're totally
off the fucking path.
- I understand that.
- Will you keep your
- voice down?
- Can you not be condescending
- right now?
- I'm asking you
to keep your voice down
for a very practical reason
- because I feel like...
- Yeah, what's the practical
- reason?
- ...we're like,
like shouting, like,
"Help, we're lost."
Like, "Help, ow! Ow!"
- Okay, can, can you...
- If there are gangs out here,
- they're just gonna like...
- Jackie.
- Jackie, Jackie, Jackie!
- What?
Can I just talk for ten seconds
without you getting
all fucking vicious on me?
I'd like to make a suggestion.
Mm-hm?
Okay, do you
remember that podcast
that we were listening to
where the two guys
went hiking in Muir Beach
up by San Francisco?
And they got up to the top,
and it was dark,
and one guy was like,
"Let's just stop here
for the night."
And the other guy was like,
"I'm gonna keep going.
- I'm just gonna push through."
- You're not suggesting
that we are stopping.
But the second guy,
the guy who kept going,
he fell off the fucking cliff.
And the guy who stayed there,
he found that other guy's
body the next morning
- with his head bashed in!
- We're not just gonna
sit like ducks
- out in the middle of the woods!
- I'm trying to do
the safest thing.
I'm trying to do
the safest thing
for me, and you, and our baby.
- And you can sleep...
- Honey, just 'cause you hit
one guy!
- You hit one guy...
- I'll put my coat on you.
- ...and now you think...
- I'll make a fire.
...if we get attacked
by multiple people,
or animals, or whatever,
that you're gonna
be able to, like,
get us through the night?
Honestly!
That was really mean.
- I'm just...
- I mean, that was,
that was, like...
Hitting that guy,
you know that was my thing.
- And...
- You know that that,
- you know what a huge...
- I know internally
- that that was...
- ...demarcation
that was to make me feel
like I could be a protector
of you, and our child,
- and our family, and now I do...
- Like...
...and now, and now I do.
And you said you trusted me,
you said you wanted me
- to be your doula!
- I didn't say that I wanted
- to sleep in the woods.
- It's not fucking fair!
I'm not a baby,
I'm not a fucking child!
- I'm not drawing a line.
- I'm not a goddamn junkie
like your father!
Why would you say that?
What? Is that an unfair thing?
Is that an untrue thing?
How...
I have nothing to say to you.
I hope that we can
do the rest of this
silently, or just
part our ways out here.
Okay, but what if
the thing happens
that happened in the podcast?
Well, it was meant to be.
(dog barking)
(footsteps)
(insects chirping)
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
That shouldn't
have been aimed at you.
No?
Who should it have
been aimed at, Elliot?
(car dinging)
(car door slamming)
(car starting)
(♪♪♪)
Do you like it?
Yeah!
Sort of picks up this...
Does anybody need anything else?
More coffee, or... No.
When is the baby actually due?
Uh, one more month.
Four weeks.
No more drinks?
Good, we good?
Everybody cool?
For a little while.
I'm so worried
about your eye, honey.
- My eye's okay.
- Don't you think we need to put
- ice on it?
- No, it actually doesn't hurt
at all anymore.
It really hurt at first,
but it hurt...
I'll tell ya about it later.
- Bob?
- Hey, Dad?
Bob?
Yeah?
Will you come over here?
Sure, sure.
(clearing throat)
Here we go!
Here I am.
- Hey!
- Hey, thanks!
So.
(clearing throat)
I know it's weird, it's like
we've called this meeting.
- Here! Here!
- We've called you here...
- Today.
- ...today to, uh,
- well, I'm joking around.
- Well, we have, we have
because we, um...
We've been going through this
intense transformation.
We've been on kind of a quest.
- Mm.
- Hm.
And, um, we've had
some revelations
- that we'd...
- Oh!
And we wanted to share
those with you guys.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Great hummus.
Thank you.
You have anymore?
No.
- No, there's...
- That's it.
...there's no more hummus, Dad.
So when, when
is the baby coming?
It's in, it's in four weeks,
three and a half.
Ah, right, right.
Final countdown,
as they said.
- Yeah.
So, we, we have realized that
the thing
that set all this off
was about being parents
and how we feel
we've been parented.
- And, and, some of the...
- And...
...issues we might hold onto,
which have something
to do with, um...
- You.
- ...stuff, stuff... You.
I can't take
my eyes off your eye.
It's okay, it's okay.
- I'm okay.
- Don't you want an ice pack
- or something?
- I'm okay.
- I'm just so concerned.
- Okay, guys.
There are lots of good things.
It can hemorrhage,
you can get a hemorrhage
- in your eye and a blood clot.
- He's not gonna get,
he's not gonna
get a hemorrhage.
- My eye is fine.
- We do need to, you know,
I just... What did you wanna say?
We just need to be
- honest.
- Okay, honest, go.
So you have your
hand on your cheek?
Yeah.
- Um, do you wanna? Or, should I?
- I can take it off.
Should I?
- Should I? Okay.
- Okay.
Okay, Dad, I'm afraid of you.
(chuckling)
Right now?
Um, always.
Always, I always have been.
Your, um, anger, um,
well, it scared me
when I was a kid
'cause I was much
smaller than you.
And, um, and it scares me now
because I don't wanna be
that way with our daughter
when she's born.
Well, get rid of that so
you don't pass it on to
your whippersnapper there.
Well, yeah, that's,
that's what I'm trying to do.
- Um...
- But, honey,
we've dealt with all that stuff.
Okay, but actually,
we haven't dealt with it at all.
Do you, do you remember
what he's talking about?
Mm, not specifically, but...
Do you remember all
the times when you would
pinch me, or you'd spank me,
or you'd cock a fist back
like you were gonna hit me?
- Do you remember that? No?
- Mm-mm.
- No.
- He never punched you
- with his fist.
- You seriously don't remember?
I don't remember
a lot of things.
- Really?
- Really.
- Really!
It's gotta be
in there somewhere.
- Well, I don't remember...
- You're choosing
to not remember.
- You almost drowned him.
- Huh?
- Nothing.
- What do you wanna say?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, in the pool,
when you got pissed off at me
because you thought
I should be able to swim,
and I couldn't swim,
and I was scared of the water,
and you told me
to figure it out,
and you turned around
and you went back inside?
And you swam.
- Well...
- Could you not laugh?
Please don't laugh
about it, Richard.
Mom came out,
and she had to jump in the pool
with all her clothes on
and pull me out.
- Exactly!
- I didn't actually
magically learn to swim.
She's a better
swimmer than I am.
Okay, Dad, do you remember,
do you remember
the time in church
where I was six,
and you kept telling me
to tuck my shirt in,
and my shirt wouldn't stay in
because it was
a little too short?
And you pulled me
over to the side,
and in front of everybody,
you pulled my pants down,
and pulled my shirt down,
and then you pulled my pants,
like, almost up to my chest?
Do you remember that?
Yeah, did we get
your shirt tucked in?
(clearing throat)
- I'm just gonna run and get...
- Mom?
Mom, Mom, Mom, stop, please?
Please put that down.
You're just tryin' to clean up
because you're
conflict avoidant,
and that's always
been your issue,
and it's crippled you
as a human being.
Conflict avoidant?
Well, I don't know about that.
Please stop, please stop!
I think you need to calm down,
buster.
- We're calm!
- We're,
we are in a safe space.
- This is a safe space.
- This is a safe space
- for us to just...
- This is not a safe place.
This is a safe space
- to talk about what's really...
- This is the most unsafe place
I've ever been in my whole life.
There is nothing
safe about this!
This is a safe space!
What does that mean,
a safe space?
It's not a safe place.
There's no such thing
as a safe place!
- What is a safe place?
- This is a family safe place
to just say everything
you gotta say!
Dad, I think you're petrified.
I think you're
fucking petrified,
and I just wanna
create a safe space
to talk about why you're scared.
I'm just frightened to death,
so how we gonna help me?
- What happened to you?
- When?
When you were a kid?
I got the shit beat outta me.
(sighing)
I got hit with a fist,
I got hit with a belt,
I got hit with a stick.
I got hit with
whatever was available.
You don't know real fear
until you met my dad
when he was younger.
He'd come home from a trip,
and I don't know where
the rage was coming from,
but this guy came
like a fucking lion
out of nowhere!
And he would beat
the shit out of me,
and then he'd leave again
for three days.
All I knew about
being a parent is
how he parented me.
What else is there?
(deeply breathing)
Well, I, I, I gotta go.
Dad, no you don't.
Well, I gotta go soon.
Real soon.
I know we haven't,
I haven't talked to you yet,
but I do, I do need you to stay
because...
I don't wanna talk
about that other thing.
Well, we are going
to talk about it
because this is an open forum.
It's open forum day.
And the whole
reason that I got
sent up on this quest
was because of your text.
What text?
Where you asked us
to pay your rent?
Mm.
That's why we're here?
I'm, I'm sorry I,
I got backed up.
I got behind.
I got behind,
and that's what family's for.
Family's there
to help each other.
I helped you when
you were a little baby.
Dad, the...
Can we talk about the pills?
And the relapse?
And the fact that
this is the fourth time
in the last two years
that you've hit us up for money?
I'm not a drug addict.
I have a pain problem
with my back.
Had an accident many years ago,
and sometimes it's
hard to maintain
the right, you know, balance.
But, Dad...
I needed the money
'cause I needed the money!
And I don't appreciate
you bringing it up.
- How many pills are you taking?
- I take it as prescribed.
What is prescribed?
I don't know.
I'm sorry, just kill me, okay?
Just fucking kill me?
Why don't I just
fucking kill myself?
Then it'd be over, then you
wouldn't have to... You could
- raise your kid by yourself.
- Whoa!
- Okay, Bob...
- I don't give a fuck!
- Dad!
- Do you understand how
narcissistic you're being
- right now?
- Narcissistic.
- Fuck you!
- Yeah!
Yeah, I mean,
we drive down here
five hours to come here,
and take you out,
and have a great
time to celebrate
the birth of our grandkid,
and you, you wanna have
an inquisition with us
about the parents that we were
years and years ago,
when we didn't know any better?
We didn't have these
parenting classes,
this RIE, RIE parenting classes,
whatever the heck
it was you went to...
You don't understand
- how different it was.
- I was out on the streets
when I was a kid.
I was sellin' papers
on a paper corner,
on a corner when
I was nine years old.
- It's different!
- It's real different.
I had to walk to school,
miles, when I was
seven years old!
They would just put me out.
I mean, anything
could have happened,
and bad things did happen!
Yeah, you can't teach
somebody to climb a tree.
I fell out of a tree!
That's right, you gotta
learn to climb the tree.
Cut my ear, I still have a scar.
Oh, I'll tell you
another thing that happened.
They would give me a dog,
my mother would give me a dog.
I'd fall in love with the dog,
I'd have the dog for six months,
then Daddy would come home,
and give the dog away!
On Christmas Eve, once,
I had a dog named Stray.
They gave the dog away
on Christmas Eve,
and my mother said, "Oh,
it's a good time to
give the dog to the pound
because on Christmas,
people will be goin' to get
dogs for their children."
You wonder why I didn't want
you to have a dog growin' up?
- I couldn't bear it!
- It's a different world
that you're living in
from the world we
lived in and grew up in.
And you really don't know
what it was like.
And feelings, I mean,
it's a luxury,
it's a privilege
to have feelings,
to be able to discuss feelings.
If I would have stopped to
talk to my dad about feelings,
he woulda knocked me for a loop!
I didn't even know
I had feelings.
- What are feelings, man?
- Feelings.
Good luck!
Is that what you want,
is you want, you want,
you guys want,
you want an apology?
I'll apologize to you.
I'll look right into
your eyes right now,
and I am so sorry
for all the times
that I ever hurt you,
and all the times that I ever
made you upset,
and all the times...
I'll apologize for him too.
I hated it when he
- threatened you.
- Is that what you want?
For us to tell you we're sorry?
- Tell him! Apologize to him.
- I mean, okay, I'm sorry
if I hurt you.
I'm sorry.
But say it,
say it like you mean it.
I am sorry if I hurt you.
See?
He is sorry.
This is a good man,
and he loves you.
You doin' okay, Dad?
I'm sorry.
Dad, Dad, look at me.
How many pills are you at?
How many?
I don't know!
I don't know.
Dad.
I don't know!
I take 'em, I take 'em,
I just, it doesn't...
I take 'em as needed!
And I need a lot.
I need a lot.
Will you go to rehab?
Okay.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I'll go to the meetings,
I'll do whatever I can.
I'll do anything!
I'm gonna throw these
freakin' pills away.
Here! Take 'em,
and flush 'em away.
This is it, this is
day one... day zero.
Tomorrow's day one.
Dad.
If you mean it,
it would really
mean a lot to me.
(♪♪♪)
I mean it!
But I don't know.
(♪♪♪)
But I wanna see your baby.
I'm excited for you
to be a grandpa.
(♪♪♪)
I don't wanna miss that!
I don't want you to miss that.
We don't want
you guys to miss it.
That's why we wanted to
talk to you because
it's important to us
that you're in our kid's life.
♪ Hands on the radio ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ We left too soon ♪
♪ We left you in the afternoon ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ I hurt somebody ♪
Oh, that's weird.
Ooh!
(♪♪♪)
Oh, my God, I have
to go to the bathroom.
You okay?
Ooh, I gotta go.
Uh, okay.
(laughing)
I'll be right back.
(♪♪♪)
♪ And I promise I'll come back ♪
♪ Girls, I promise you ♪
♪ And boys I promise you too ♪
(inaudible)
(♪♪♪)
♪ Da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Da-da-da ♪
Uh, honey?
Can you come up here?
I'll be right back.
Wow.
What the fuck was that?
I don't know.
- Hey.
You okay?
It's starting.
It's star...
Oh, like, it's
starting right now?
Yeah, right now.
Okay.
Awesome!
Awesome.
(laughing)
Oh!
(♪♪♪)
♪ I'll be your future fucker ♪
♪ I'm your mother ♪
♪ Your whirling dervish ♪
♪ Your body double ♪
♪ I'm gonna wreck your life ♪
♪ Get used to it
and feel all right ♪
♪ I'll be your future fucker ♪
♪ I'm your mother ♪
♪ Your daddy, your sister,
your fucked up brother ♪
Are you okay?
- No.
- Are you okay?
I'm really stressed,
and I'm really tired.
Oh, okay.
My white blood cell count
- is not doing well.
- No, I know.
You need to not stress out.
- I can't be stressed out!
- You need to not stress out.
I know I need to not stress out!
- Just, so just calm down!
- So I know, so you...
(laughing)
(♪♪♪)
Okay, let's try it again.
♪ I'll be your future fucker ♪
♪ I'm your mother ♪
♪ Your daddy, your sister,
your fucked up brother ♪
♪ I oh I ♪
♪ I'm gonna love you
'till I die ♪
Wait a second, 'cause we can
figure this out mathematically.
- Let's go that way.
- The city lights are there.
The moon is there.
Do you remember
where our car was
in relation to the moon?
(♪♪♪)
(laughing)
Do you remember
where our car was...
I peed my pants.
(♪♪♪)
Hey, stop.
♪ Future fucker ♪
♪ I'm your mother ♪
♪ Bad kids come
and bad kids go ♪
(♪♪♪)
Eighty-eight,
eighty-nine,
ninety, ninety-one,
ninety-two,
ninety-three,
ninety-four, ninety-five,
ninety-six, ninety-seven,
ninety-eight, ninety-nine.
(♪♪♪)
♪ Bad boys come
and bad boys go ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ I'll be your future fucker ♪
♪ I'm your mother ♪
♪ Your daddy, your sister,
your fucked up brother ♪
♪ I oh I ♪
That's good, hold up.
Hold on, just like that.
- Hold on just like...
- Don't take a picture!
We don't need a picture,
- this is for us!
- Let me take a picture!
No, that goes to the cloud.
I'm about to let you fuck me.
- Let me take a picture.
- Yeah, this is different.
It's not on the cloud.
- You swear your phone?
- I swear to God
it's not on the cloud.
'Cause this is not
for social media.
(♪♪♪)
♪ I'm your mother ♪
♪ Future fucker ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ I'm your mother ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
(♪♪♪)