[ Baby Crying ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Crying Continues ]
[ Cleaver Thudding ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Bird Twittering ]
[ Twittering Continues ]
WILD OUT THERE TONIGHT.
[ Laughing, Chattering ]
[ Sighs ]
YOU'RE BACK THEN ?
WHAT'S FOR DINNER ?
OH !  WHAT IS THIS ?
HER LADYSHIP
CAUGHT HER BITCH, DIANA,
WITH THE GATEKEEPER'S DOG.
NOW SHE WANTS TO ABORT
TO AVOID ANY BASTARD PUPS.
CHRISTINE, YOU REALLY SHOULD
LEARN TO EXPRESS YOURSELF
WITH MORE DIGNITY.
AND YOU
SHOULD CARRY YOURSELF
WITH MORE DIGNITY, JEAN !
I TOOK THE COUNT
TO THE STATION.
I DROPPED IN THE PARTY.
HER LADYSHIP INSISTED
I DANCE WITH HER.
I COULDN'T REFUSE, COULD I ?
WELL, COULD I ?
[ Door Creaks ]
SHE'S COMPLETELY
MAD TONIGHT.
COMPLETELY MAD.
THAT SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN.
[ Chattering ]
[ Christine Sighs ]
BUT NEVER LIKE
THE LAST TWO WEEKS.
IT'S SINCE HER ENGAGEMENT
WAS BROKEN.  I'D BE
EMBARRASSED IF I WAS HER.
NO MAN WILL WANT HER NOW.
CARRYIN' ON LIKE THAT
WITH THE SERVANTS.
WHY DIDN'T SHE GO AWAY
WITH HER FATHER ?
SPEND MIDSUMMER'S NIGHT
WITH HER OWN KIND.
[ Woman Laughs ]
AH, WINE GLASS,
PLEASE, CHRISTINE.
WHERE DID THAT COME FROM ?
WE GOT IT LAST YEAR
IN DIJON.
"WE" ?
THE COUNT.
MYSELF AND THE COUNT.
[ Pops ]
MMM !
[ Sighs ]
[ Bird Twitters ]
YOU SHOULD WARM
THE PLATE, CHRISTINE.
YOU SHOULD HAVE BEEN HERE
15 MINUTES EARLIER.
[ Chattering, Laughing
Continue ]
[ Utensil Tapping ]
IT'S GOOD, VERY GOOD.
KIDNEY.  CUT OUT OF THEIR VEAL
FOR TOMORROW'S ROAST.
WELL DONE.
YOU KNOW,
SHE'S A STRANGE ONE.
SO STUCK UP IN SOME WAYS
AND IN OTHER WAYS--
YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN THE WAY
SHE WAS DANCING OUT THERE.
SHE'S JUST LIKE HER MOTHER WAS,
JUST LIKE HER.
GOD REST HER SOUL.
AT HOME IN THE COWSHED,
BUT A ONE-HORSE CARRIAGE
WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH FOR HER.
FILTHY CUFFS.
HAD TO HAVE A COAT OF ARMS
ON EVERY BUTTON.
YOU'RE RIGHT, CHRISTINE.
SHE SOMEHOW LACKS...
FINESSE.
BUT THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS...
WHEN THE GENTRY START
TO MIX WITH THE RABBLE.
WE WOULD NEVER DO THAT.
WOULD WE ?
ONE MONTH'S WAGES.
[ Scoffs ]
YOU ARE MORE PARTICULAR
THAN THE COUNT HIMSELF.
[ Chattering Continues,
Applause ]
[ Tapping Continues ]
[ Scoffs ]
WELL, DO YOU WANT TO DANCE
WITH
ME
WHEN I'M READY ?
I SAID I WOULD, DIDN'T I ?
PROMISE ?
IF I SAY I'LL DO IT,
THEN I'LL DO IT.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Footsteps
Approaching Rapidly ]
VERY GRACIOUS,
RUNNING AWAY FROM
YOUR PARTNER LIKE THAT.
ON THE CONTRARY, MA'AM.
I WAS RUNNING BACK TO
THE PARTNER I'D LEFT BEHIND.
OH, CHRISTINE.
HAVE YOU DONE IT ?
YES, MISS JULIE.
[ Christine ]
I HAVE TO BOTTLE IT.
IT WILL BE READY FOR MORNING.
WELL, THEN, JEAN, YOU CAN COME
AND DANCE WITH ME AGAIN.
FORGIVE ME.
I PROMISED I'D DANCE
WITH CHRISTINE.
SHE CAN DANCE WITH
SOMEONE ELSE, CAN'T SHE ?
CAN'T YOU, CHRISTINE ?
WON'T YOU LEND ME
JEAN FOR ONE DANCE ?
IT'S NOT UP TO ME, MISS.
IF HER LADYSHIP ASKS YOU
TO DANCE, JEAN, YOU SHOULD
BE GRATEFUL FOR THE HONOR.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S WISE TO DANCE WITH
THE SAME PARTNER TWICE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT ?
THE SERVANTS ALL EXPECT TO
BE TREATED THE SAME, MA'AM.
GO ON.
PERHAPS IT MIGHT NOT
LOOK GOOD...
TO SELECT ONE SERVANT
AND FAVOR HIM ABOVE THE OTHERS.
FAVOR !  FAVOR ?
HOW CAN YOU EVEN THINK OF IT ?
I AM THE MISTRESS OF THE HOUSE.
I'M HONORING THE SERVANTS
BY ATTENDING THEIR PARTY.
AREN'T I, SWEETHEART ?
[ Twittering ]
WHEN I WISH TO DANCE,
I WISH TO DANCE WITH
SOMEONE WHO CAN LEAD...
BECAUSE I DO NOT WISH
TO LOOK RIDICULOUS.
SWEETHEART.
[ Twittering ]
THEN I'M AT
YOUR COMMAND, MA'AM.
OH, NO, DON'T
TAKE IT AS A COMMAND.
TONIGHT WE'RE ALL CELEBRATING,
ALL OF US TOGETHER.
NOW, GIVE ME YOUR ARM.
DON'T WORRY, CHRISTINE.
I WON'T TAKE YOUR FIANCE
AWAY FROM YOU.
GOOD NIGHT, SERINE.
♪ [ Continues ]
[ Chattering, Laughing ]
AH, JULIE !
[ Laughs ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Jean Whispering ]
CHRISTINE.
I'M SORRY.
SHE'S REALLY CRAZY TONIGHT.
SHE'S ALWAYS THAT WAY
WHEN SHE'S GOT HER PERIOD.
POOR THING.
LIKE A BITCH ON HEAT.
[ Christine Chuckles ]
YOU GONNA DANCE
WITH
ME
NOW ?
YOU'RE ANGRY WITH ME
FOR DESERTING YOU THEN ?
NO.
HMM ?
I KNOW MY PLACE.
YEAH ?
YOU'RE A SENSIBLE GIRL,
CHRISTINE.
YOU'LL MAKE SOMEONE
A GOOD WIFE.
WE SHOULD START LOOKING
AROUND FOR SOMETHING
FOR WHEN WE GET MARRIED.
MM-HMM.
A PORTER.
A CARETAKER.
OR A CIVIL SERVANT.
YEAH, WELL, THE PAY IS MEAGER,
BUT THE JOB IS SECURE.
JEAN ?
HE DANCES LIKE NO ONE ELSE.
DID YOU KNOW THAT ?
BUT WHY DOES HE WEAR LIVERY
ON MIDSUMMER'S NIGHT ?
TAKE IT OFF AT ONCE.
WEAR THAT.
THAT'S THE
COUNT'S JACKET, MA'AM.
I KNOW WHAT IT IS, AND
I'M ASKING YOU TO WEAR IT.
I CAN'T DO THAT, MA'AM.
WHAT IF I WERE
TO COMMAND YOU ?
THEN I WOULD HAVE
TO OBEY, MA'AM.
THEN I COMMAND YOU.
ARE YOU EMBARRASSED
JUST TO CHANGE YOUR COAT
IN FRONT OF ME ?
I'LL WALK AWAY
FROM YOU THEN.
[ Footsteps ]
HE'S VERY FAMILIAR
WITH YOU.  ARE YOU
ACTUALLY ENGAGED TO JEAN ?
ENGAGED ?  YES.
THAT'S WHAT WE CALL IT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"CALL IT" ?
WELL, YOUR LADYSHIP
WAS ENGAGED ONCE AND--
YES, YES, BUT WE WERE
OFFICIALLY ENGAGED.
♪ [ Continues ]
AH !
TRES GENTIL,
MONSIEUR JEAN.
NOTHING CAME OF IT THOUGH.
TRES GENTIL.
VOULEZ-VOUS PLAISANTER,
MADEMOISELLE ?
ET VOUS PARLEZ FRANCAIS ?
WHERE DID YOU LEARN
TO SPEAK FRENCH ?
SWITZERLAND.
I WAS A WINE WAITER IN
THE GRAND HOTEL, LUCERNE.
REALLY ?
CHARMANT.
YOU DON'T LOOK
LIKE A WINE WAITER.
YOU LOOK...
LIKE A GENTLEMAN.
DON'T YOU THINK SO,
CHRISTINE ?
FORGIVE ME, BUT THAT
SOUNDS PATRONIZING.
PATRONIZING ?
OH, YOU MAY SIT.
MY NATURAL MODESTY
FORBIDS ME TO BELIEVE...
THAT SOMEONE OF YOUR CLASS
WOULD PAY A GENUINE COMPLIMENT
TO SOMEONE IN MY POSITION.
I, THEREFORE, ASSUME
THAT YOU ARE FLATTERING ME,
OR TO BE MORE PRECISE,
PATRONIZING ME.
[ Laughs ]
WHERE DID YOU LEARN
TO SPEAK LIKE THAT ?
YOU MUST HAVE
BEEN TO THE THEATER.
I'VE BEEN TO MANY THEATERS,
BOTH AT HOME AND ABROAD.
BUT YOU COME FROM
THIS AREA, DON'T YOU ?
MY FATHER WAS A LABORER
ON THE PEDERSSEN ESTATE.
REALLY?  I DON'T REMEMBER YOU.
I REMEMBER YOU.
GO ON.
NO.  ANOTHER TIME PERHAPS.
♪ [ Continues ]
ANOTHER TIME MAY NEVER COME.
I DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
SOUNDS DANGEROUS.
NO, NOT DANGEROUS.
I JUST DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
WON'T YOU SIT DOWN ?
NO, WAIT.
GIVE ME SOMETHING
TO DRINK FIRST.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WE HAVE.
ONLY BEER, I THINK.
ONLY BEER ?
MY TASTE IS SIMPLE.
I PREFER BEER TO WINE.
WON'T YOU JOIN ME ?
[ Bottle Top Clatters ]
[ Whispers ]
SHE'LL MAKE
A VERY GOOD WIFE.
DOES SHE SNORE ?
NO, BUT SHE TALKS
IN HER SLEEP.
HOW DO YOU KNOW ?
DRINK TO MY HEALTH THEN.
ON BEHALF OF ALL
THE SERVANTS, MA'AM,
MAY YOU LIVE A LONG
AND FRUITFUL LIFE.
AND NOW KISS MY SHOE.
STOP THIS, MISS JULIE.WHY ?
- SOMEONE COULD
COME IN AND SEE US.
- DOES IT MATTER ?
PEOPLE WILL TALK.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
- OH, REALLY ?
- IF ONLY YOU KNEW HOW THEIR
TONGUES WOULD BE WAGGING.
- WHAT WILL THEY SAY ?  TELL ME.
- CAN'T YOU GUESS ?
NO, I CANNOT GUESS.
IF SOMEONE COMES IN,
THEY SAW YOUR LADYSHIP
ALONE AT NIGHT WITH A MAN--
WITH A SERVANT--
THEN--  THEN WHAT ?
ANYWAY, WE'RE NOT ALONE.
♪ [ Continues ]
- CHRISTINE IS ASLEEP.
- THEN I'LL WAKE HER UP.
[ Whispering ]
CHRISTINE.
LET HER SLEEP.
[ Whispering ]
CHRISTINE.
LET HER SLEEP.
[ Whispering ]
CHRISTINE.
SHH.  SHH.  SHH.
SHH.
♪ [ Continues ]
SOME PEOPLE SLAVE OVER
A HOT STOVE ALL DAY.
SOME PEOPLE ARE EXHAUSTED
AT THE END OF THE DAY.
SLEEP SHOULD BE RESPECTED !
[ Clock Ticking ]
YOU'RE RIGHT.
HOW NOBLE.
[ Water Splashing ]
I WISH I COULD
SLEEP LIKE THAT.
WILL YOU COME AND PICK
SOME LILAC WITH ME ?
NO.  IMPOSSIBLE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
- SURELY YOU DON'T IMAGINE--
- NO.  NO, NOT ME.
THEM.
WHAT, THAT I HAVE FALLEN
FOR THE FOOTMAN ?
YOU FEEL QUITE
ABOVE THEM, DON'T YOU ?
I AM QUITE ABOVE THEM.
AND I... CAN COME DOWN.
[ Squeaking ]
I HAVE A RECURRING DREAM
THAT I'M ON TOP OF A PILLAR,
AND I CAN'T GET DOWN.
I KNOW THAT I MUST,
BUT I HAVEN'T GOT
THE COURAGE TO THROW MYSELF.
I FEEL DIZZY
WHEN I LOOK DOWN.
I CAN'T HOLD ON.
I LONG JUST TO FALL,
BUT I DON'T.
I KNOW I WON'T HAVE
ANY PEACE UNTIL I'M DOWN,
BUT I ALSO KNOW
THAT ONCE I'M THERE,
THE GROUND WILL OPEN
AND I SHALL SINK INTO IT.
HERE I AM
TELLING YOU MY DREAMS.
HAVE YOU EVER FELT
ANYTHING LIKE THAT ?
COME WITH ME.
COME ON.
[ Groans ]
WHAT IS IT ?
NOTHING.  IT'S--
LET ME SEE.
NO, LET ME SEE.
SIT--  SIT DOWN.
LET ME SEE.
MISS JULIE.
SHH !
[ Water Splashing ]
I HAVE A DREAM.
I DREAM I'M LYING
AT THE BOTTOM OF A TREE.
IT'S A TALL TREE.
AT THE TOP OF THAT TREE,
THERE'S A NEST,
AND IN THE NEST,
THE EGGS ARE GOLDEN.
I DREAM...
THAT I WANT TO GET
TO THE TOP OF THAT TREE.
THE FIRST BRANCH
IS TOO HIGH,
AND THE TREE IS SLIPPERY.
BUT I KNOW IF I CAN
JUST GET TO THE TOP,
AND I'LL GET THERE...
IN MY DREAM.
YOU CAN KISS MY HAND
AND THANK ME.
YOU'LL ONLY HAVE
YOURSELF TO BLAME.
FOR WHAT ?
YOU'RE NOT A CHILD ANYMORE.
IT'S DANGEROUS
TO PLAY WITH FIRE.
NOT FOR ME.  I'M INSURED.
NO.
NO, YOU'RE NOT INSURED.
AND BESIDES,
THERE ARE OTHER PEOPLE.
YOU MEAN YOU ?
MM-HMM.
YOU ARE SO CONCEITED.
I SUPPOSE YOU THINK
YOU'RE IRRESISTIBLE,
DON'T YOU ?
I THINK YOU'RE ALL TALK.
I THINK YOU HAVEN'T
GOT IT IN YOU.
YOU THINK SO ?
I SUSPECT SO.
ARE YOU SERIOUS,
OR ARE YOU JOKING ?
SERIOUS.
[ Gasps ]
YOU PLAY TOO
SERIOUSLY FOR ME.
I'M TIRED OF PLAYING.
AND NOW,
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I'LL GET BACK TO MY WORK.
EVERYTHING'S A SCUM DRIFTING
IN THE WATER UNTIL IT SINKS.
WILL YOU PUT THOSE AWAY ?
THIS IS MY JOB.
THIS IS WHAT
I'M PAID TO DO.
I'M NOT
PAID
TO BE YOUR PLAYMATE.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN IN LOVE ?
WE DON'T USE THAT EXPRESSION,
BUT, YES, I HAVE LOVED.
AND WHO WAS SHE ?
IS THIS A COMMAND ?
NO, NO, I'M ASKING YOU
AS AN EQUAL,
AS A FRIEND.
WHO WAS SHE ?
[ Sighs ]
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THE WORLD
LOOKS LIKE FROM DOWN HERE ?
NO, YOU DON'T.
[ Spits ]
YOU SEE THE WORLD FROM UP THERE,
HOVERING WITH THE GREAT HAWKS
HIGH ABOVE US.
WHAT'S IT LIKE ?
I'VE NEVER FLOWN
WITH THE HAWKS.
I WAS BROUGHT UP WITH
SEVEN BROTHERS AND SISTERS...
AND A PIG IN A HOVEL.
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN AWFUL.
FROM ONE OF OUR GRUBBY LITTLE
WINDOWS, WE COULD SEE THE WALLS
OF YOUR FATHER'S ESTATE.
THE APPLE TREES
RISING HIGH ABOVE IT.
TO US IT WAS PARADISE.
BUT EVIL ANGELS WITH
FLAMING SWORDS WERE GUARDING IT
FROM THE LIKES OF US,
BECAUSE YOU DESPISE US,
DON'T YA ?
WE DON'T.
YES, YOU DO.
YOU SAY YOU DON'T,
BUT I KNOW YOU DO.
FIRST TIME I WAS
EVER IN YOUR ESTATE...
WAS WHEN I WENT WITH MY MOTHER
TO WEED THE ONION BEDS.
DO YOU REMEMBER
THE TURKISH PAVILION
JUST BY THE KITCHEN GARDEN ?
ALL SHADED WITH JASMINE TREES
AND OVERGROWN WITH HONEYSUCKLE.
YES.
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL BUILDING
I'D EVER SEEN.
I NEVER UNDERSTOOD WHY PEOPLE
WENT IN AND VERY SHORTLY
AFTERWARDS CAME OUT AGAIN.
I WENT IN.
IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
ALL THOSE PICTURES
OF EMPERORS AND KINGS.
THE CURTAINS WITH THE TASSELS
DRAWN ACROSS THE WINDOWS.
I'D NEVER BEEN IN A BIG HOUSE.
I'D NEVER BEEN ANYWHERE
EXCEPT INSIDE THE CHURCH.
YES, YOU CAN SMILE,
BUT YOUR TOILET
WAS MORE BEAUTIFUL
THAN ANYWHERE I'D EVER BEEN.
FROM THAT MOMENT ON,
WHEREVER I WAS,
WHATEVER I WAS DOING,
MY THOUGHTS
ALWAYS RETURNED THERE.
I HAD THIS
OVERWHELMING DESIRE...
TO RELIEVE MYSELF
IN ALL THAT SPLENDOR.
ONE DAY I SLIPPED INSIDE.
I STOOD THERE IN SILENCE...
AND MARVELED.
THEN I HEARD SOMEONE COMING.
COULDN'T LEAVE BY THE WINDOW.
COULDN'T LEAVE BY THE DOOR.
THERE WAS ONLY ONE WAY OUT...
AND I TOOK IT.
DOWN THE SEWER...
THROUGH THE DARKNESS...
AND YOUR SHIT.
WHEN I GOT OUT,
I STARTED RUNNING...
ACROSS A RASPBERRY HEDGE,
A STRAWBERRY FIELD,
TILL AT LAST I CAME
TO THE ROSE TERRACE.
IT WAS THERE I SAW...
A PAIR OF WHITE SILK STOCKINGS
AND A PINK DRESS.
AND I HID--
FILTHY AND STINKING--
UNDERNEATH THE THISTLES
AND THE ROTTING EARTH.
AND I WATCHED THE GIRL...
WALK AMONG THE ROSES...
AND I THOUGHT TO MYSELF,
"IF A THIEF CAN SIT WITH
THE ANGELS IN GOD'S PARADISE,
"THEN WHY CAN'T A LABORER'S SON
ON GOD'S EARTH...
PLAY WITH THE DAUGHTER
OF A COUNT ?"
WHAT DO YOU SAY ?
IT MUST BE TERRIBLE
TO BE POOR.
"IT MUST BE TERRIBLE
TO BE POOR."
A DOG CAN SIT
ON A COUNTESS' SOFA.
A HORSE CAN BE CARESSED
BY A YOUNG LADY'S HAND.
BUT A SERVANT ?
[ Clock Ticking ]
ANYWAY, THE FOLLOWING SUNDAY,
I WENT TO CHURCH
JUST TO SEE YOU.
CLEANED MYSELF UP.
WORE MY BEST CLOTHES.
AND THEN I SAW YOU.
I WENT HOME...
DETERMINED TO DIE.
BUT I WANTED TO DIE PLEASANTLY,
WITHOUT PAIN.
SO I STRIPPED AN ELDER BUSH
OF ALL ITS FLOWERS,
AND I MADE A BED
IN THE OAT BIN.
YOU EVER NOTICE
HOW SMOOTH OATS ARE ?
LIKE HUMAN SKIN.
VERY SOFT TO TOUCH.
I SHUT THE LID,
AND I FELL ASLEEP
WITH THE POISONOUS FLOWERS
IN MY ARMS.
AND WHEN I WOKE UP,
I WAS VERY ILL,
BUT NOT, AS YOU CAN SEE,
DEAD.
SEEING YOU IN CHURCH
THAT SUNDAY MADE ME REALIZE...
HOW UTTERLY HOPELESS
IT ALL WAS,
THAT I WOULD NEVER BE ABLE
TO RISE ABOVE THE CLASS
THAT I WAS BORN IN.
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL--
THE WAY YOU TELL YOUR STORY.
WHERE DID YOU LEARN THAT ?
DID YOU GO TO SCHOOL ?
[ Chuckles ]
NO.  NO.
NO, I LEARNED MOST FROM
LISTENING TO THE GENTRY.
YOU MEAN YOU STAND AROUND
LISTENING TO US ?
MM-HMM.
HOW COULD YOU NOT ?
WHO--  WHO DO
YOU LISTEN TO ?
[ Sighs ]
THE COUNT.
YOU.  YOUR FIANCE.
WHAT ?
WHAT DID YOU HEAR ?
I WOULDN'T LIKE TO SAY.
ALTHOUGH I MUST CONFESS
I WAS RATHER SHOCKED...
AT SOME OF THE WORDS.
WHAT WORDS ?
[ Clock Ticking ]
YOU KNOW, MAYBE THERE'S
NOT AS BIG A DIFFERENCE
AS WE THINK BETWEEN US.
AT LEAST WE DON'T
BEHAVE THE WAY YOU DO
BEFORE WE'RE MARRIED.
ARE YOU SURE ?
YES, I AM SURE.
[ Whispering ]
I SAW WHAT HAPPENED
IN THE STABLE YARD.
[ Footsteps Departing ]
[ Latch Clicks ]
THE MAN I GAVE MY LOVE TO
WAS A BASTARD.
YEP, WELL, THEY ALL
SAY THAT AFTERWARDS.
NO, NO, TH-THAT'S NOT TRUE.
WELL, I'VE HEARD IT
OFTEN ENOUGH.  LAST TIME--
ALL RIGHT !
SHUT UP !
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ANY MORE.
IT'S REMARKABLE.
THAT'S WHAT SHE SAID.
AND NOW...
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I'M GOING TO BED.
TO BED ?
ON MIDSUMMER'S NIGHT ?
YES, WELL, THE IDEA OF DANCING
WITH THAT LOT OUT THERE...
DOESN'T APPEAL
TO ME JUST NOW.
NO, DON'T GO.
WE COULD GET THE KEY TO
THE BOATHOUSE AND ROW OUT ON
THE LAKE AND SEE THE SUNRISE.
OH, PLEASE, MISS JULIE.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU
WORRIED ABOUT ?
I-IS IT YOUR REPUTATION ?
YES, YES, I CAN'T
AFFORD TO LOSE MY JOB
WITHOUT A REFERENCE,
AND I HAVE CHRISTINE
TO THINK ABOUT.
OH, I SEE.
IT'S CHRISTINE.
NO, IT'S NOT JUST CHRISTINE.
IF ANYONE COMES AND
SEES US ALONE TOGETHER--
LET THEM.
I KNOW THESE PEOPLE,
AND I LOVE THEM
JUST AS THEY LOVE ME.
OH !  MISS JULIE,
THEY EAT YOUR--
[ Shouting ]
GO TO BED.
GO UPSTAIRS TO BED.
WHAT ?
PLEASE.  I'M BEGGING YOU.
DO AS I SAY.
NOW, GO UPSTAIRS TO BED !
WHY SHOULD I OBEY YOU ?
FOR ONCE.  FOR ONCE.
PLEASE.
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Thudding ]
THIS WAY.
PLEASE.  PLEASE.
JUST DO IT !
[ Gasps ]
MISS JULIE.
HURRY !
[ Gasps ]
WHERE'S THAT FUCKIN' JULIE ?
[ Mutters ]
I FEEL TOO BEASTLY !
[ Giggles ]
YES, YOUR GRACE.
AT ONCE, YOUR GRACE.  YES !
[ Man ]
THREE BAGS FUCKING FULL,
YOUR GRACE !
AH, STICK IT UP YOUR
FUCKING ARSE, YOUR GRACE !
[ Giggling ]
♪ [ Drumming Continues ]
♪ OH, A CARROT
UP YOUR SHITTER ♪
♪ A CARROT UP YOUR ARSE
♪ [ Drumming Continues ]
[ Thuds ]
FUCK.
[ Mutters ]
WHERE'S YOUR FUCKIN' STASH ?
EH, JEAN ?
WHERE IS YOUR WINE ?
I KNOW IT'S HERE...
SOMEWHERE.
[ Laughing ]
♪ [ Fiddle Joins In ]
♪ THE COUNTESS OF THE MANOR
SO FINE AND SO WELL-BRED ♪
♪ HAD BALLS
INSTEAD OF PISS FLAPS
THE COUNT FOUND OUT IN BED ♪
♪ ONE EVENING IN THE EAST WING
WHEN THEY WERE ON THE JOB ♪
♪ THE COUNT FOUND OUT
THE AWFUL TRUTH
THE COUNTESS HAD A KNOB ♪
♪ SHE WHIPPED HIM WITH HER
CHOPPER, SHE WHIPPED HIM
WITH HER DICK ♪
♪ THE COUNT WENT WEAK
BETWEEN THE KNEES
'CAUSE HE'S A USELESS PRICK ♪
[ Glass Breaking ]
♪ OH, A CARROT UP YOUR SHITTER
A CARROT UP YOUR ARSE ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE TOO PISSED
TO GET THE GIST
JUST LISTEN TO THIS FARCE ♪
♪ A CARROT UP YOUR SHITTER
A CARROT UP YOUR ARSE ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE TOO PISSED
TO GET THE GIST
JUST LISTEN TO THIS FARCE ♪
[ Glass Breaking ]
♪ COUNTESS JULIE IS THE DAUGHTER
THE KID THEY DID NOT WANT ♪
♪ SHE IS THE NOBLE OFFSPRING
OF THE COUNTESS AND THE CUNT ♪
♪ HER LADYSHIP IS DAINTY
A LOVELY PIECE OF FLUFF ♪
DON'T LISTEN.  DON'T LISTEN.
♪ CHASING LIKE A BITCH ON HEAT
AFTER EVERY BIT OF ROUGH ♪
♪ SHE'S HORNY FOR THE FOOTMAN
AND THE BLACKSMITH
AT THE BALL ♪
♪ SHE'S HORNY
FOR CHRISTINE AS WELL
GOOD GOD, SHE'LL FUCK US ALL ♪
[ Laughing ]
DON'T LISTEN.
♪ IF YOU'RE TOO PISSED
TO GET THE GIST
JUST LISTEN TO THIS FARCE ♪
♪ A CARROT UP YOUR SHITTER
A CARROT UP YOUR ARSE ♪
WHAT CAN WE DO ?
♪ IF YOU'RE TOO PISSED TO GET
THE GIST, JUST LISTEN TO THIS
FARCE ♪
WE CAN ESCAPE.
♪ A CARROT UP YOUR SHITTER
A CARROT UP YOUR ARSE ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE TOO PISSED
TO GET THE GIST ♪
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN
TO SWITZERLAND ?
THE ITALIAN LAKES ?
NO.  IS IT BEAUTIFUL ?
OH, SO BEAUTIFUL,
SO BEAUTIFUL.
ETERNAL SUMMERS,
LAURELS AT CHRISTMAS,
ORANGE TREES.
♪ AND THERE IS JEAN, THE FOOTMAN
SUPERIOR AND BOLD ♪
♪ HE LICKS THE ARSE OF THE
RULING CLASS WITH HIS TONGUE
RIGHT UP THEIR HOLE ♪
♪ HE'S SURELY QUITE ABOVE US
REFINED BEYOND BELIEF ♪
♪ BUT UNDERNEATH THAT SLIMY
GIT'S A LIAR AND A THIEF ♪
[ Laughing ]
♪ SO TALENTED AND GIFTED
HE PREFERS POSH WINE TO BEER ♪
♪ BUT WE ALL KNOW HIS SECRET
THE SHIRT LIFTER IS QUEER ♪
[ Laughing ]
♪ IF YOU'RE TOO PISSED
TO GET THE GIST
JUST LISTEN TO THIS FARCE ♪
♪ A CARROT UP YOUR SHITTER
A CARROT UP YOUR ARSE ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE TOO PISSED
TO GET THE GIST
JUST LISTEN TO THIS FARCE ♪
♪ A CARROT UP YOUR SHITTER
A CARROT UP YOUR ARSE ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE TOO PISSED
TO GET THE GIST
JUST LISTEN TO THIS FARCE ♪
SHH !
I'LL SET UP A HOTEL.
THAT'S LIVING.
BELIEVE ME.  BELIEVE ME.
NEW FACES,
NEW LANGUAGES.
NO TIME TO WORRY.
TOO BUSY TO BE BORED.
TRAINS COMING, GOING,
ALL THE TIME.
MONEY JUST KEEPS ROLLING IN.
AND YOU'LL BE
THE JEWEL IN THE CROWN.
THE MISTRESS OF THE HOUSE.
YOU'LL SIT BEHIND YOUR DESK
AND PRESS YOUR ELECTRIC BELL.
YOU'LL BE MY QUEEN.
THE GUESTS WILL
FILE PAST YOUR THRONE.
AND THEN THEY WILL
HUMBLY SETTLE THEIR DEBTS.
BECAUSE YOU HAVE NO IDEA...
HOW EMBARRASSED PEOPLE ARE
WHEN IT COMES TO PAYING.
[ Water Running ]
SAY MY NAME.
SAY JULIE.
THERE ARE NO BARRIERS
BETWEEN US NOW.
[ Panting ]
NOT HERE.
NOT IN THIS HOUSE.
THAT WAS THE PAST.  THIS--
[ Panting Continues ]
THERE'S THE COUNT.
[ Mutters ]
HE CHOSE ME.
THE COUNT CHOSE ME.
I-I RESPECT THIS MAN.
I RESPECT THIS MAN
MORE THAN--
MORE THAN ANY OTHER MAN
IN THE WORLD.
[ Grunting ]
[ Panting ]
SUPERSTITIONS, PREJUDICES...
CRAMMED INTO MY BRAIN
FROM THE DAY I WAS BORN.
LET'S--
LET'S GET RID OF THEM.
LET'S GO ABROAD.
ANOTHER COUNTRY.
A REPUBLIC WHERE
THEY'LL GROVEL FOR ME.
MALMO, 6:30.
FRANKFURT, 8:30.
YOU LET ME GET TO
THIS FIRST BRANCH--
AND YOU WATCH ME CLIMB,
STEP BY STEP.
[ Pages Flipping ]
FRANKFURT.  BASLE.
LAKE COMO.
WE GO-- WE GO--
WE GO BY THE GOTHARD LINE.
GO BY THE GOTHARD LINE.
TODAY-- TODAY, MISS JULIE,
I AM A FOOTMAN.
ONE YEAR FROM NOW,
AND I WILL BE A HOTEL OWNER !
TEN YEARS FROM NOW
I WILL BE A MEMBER
OF THE LANDED GENTRY.
I'LL GO TO THE EAST,
I'LL GET MYSELF DECORATED,
AND I MIGHT-- I JUST MIGHT--
END UP A COUNT !
YOU CAN BUY ANYTHING
IN THE EAST.
WE'LL BUY A TITLE.
SO YOU WILL BE
MY COUNTESS AFTER ALL.
MY
COUNTESS !
SAY YOU LOVE ME.
WE'VE MADE FOOLS
OF OURSELVES ONCE.
LET'S NOT DO IT AGAIN.
YEAH.
THE COUNT WILL BE HERE
ANY MINUTE.
SO YOU AND I--
WE MUST MAKE DECISIONS.
LET ME SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
MY HOTEL.
THEY'RE JUST
DRAWINGS, BUT--
WHAT DO YOU THINK ?
THEY SEEM FINE.
ONLY SUCH PLANS
NEED A LOT OF RESOURCES.
UM, DO YOU HAVE THEM ?
ME ?  OF COURSE I--
MY PROFESSIONAL SKILLS,
IMMENSE EXPERIENCE,
KNOWLEDGE OF LANGUAGES.
THAT'S RESOURCES ENOUGH,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY ?
BUT, UM, THAT DOESN'T BUY YOU
A TRAIN TICKET.
EXACTLY.  EXACTLY.
AND THAT IS WHY
I AM LOOKING FOR A PARTNER
WHO CAN ADVANCE ME THE MONEY.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING TO FIND
ONE ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE ?
WHO WOULD THAT PARTNER BE ?
THE PARTNER WOULD BE YOU.
[ Chuckles ]
I HAVE NO MONEY...
OF MY OWN.
[ Pages Flipping ]
THEN THE WHOLE THING IS OFF.
[ Book Thuds ]
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
AND ?
AND WE'RE BACK
TO SQUARE ONE.
YOU MEAN--
DO YOU REALLY THINK
THAT I CAN STAY UNDER
THIS ROOF AS YOUR WHORE...
WITH THOSE PEOPLE POINTING
THEIR GREASY FINGERS AT ME ?
DO YOU THINK THAT I CAN
FACE MY FATHER AFTER THIS ?
MY GOD,
WHAT HAVE I DONE ?
THE SAME AS PLENTY
OF OTHERS BEFORE YOU.
AND NOW YOU DESPISE ME.
WHAT ON EARTH
DREW ME TO YOU ?
'CAUSE I'M WEAK
AND YOU'RE STRONG ?
BECAUSE I'M FALLING
AND YOU'RE RISING ?
WAS THAT IT ?
OR WAS IT LOVE ?
IS THIS LOVE ?
DO YOU EVEN KNOW
WHAT LOVE IS ?
I SHOULD HOPE SO.
YOU THINK I'VE NEVER
HAD A FUCK BEFORE ?
MY GOODNESS.
THE LANGUAGE YOU USE.
THE THOUGHTS YOU THINK.
THAT'S WHAT WE LEARN
WHERE I COME FROM.
THAT'S WHAT I AM.
AND DON'T PLAY
THE LADY WITH ME.
WE'RE AS BAD AS
EACH OTHER, REMEMBER ?
WHERE DID THAT WINE
COME FROM ?
THE CELLAR.
MY FATHER'S BURGUNDY.
NOT GOOD ENOUGH
FOR THE FUTURE SON-IN-LAW ?
AND I DRINK BEER.
THAT JUST GOES
TO SHOW YOUR TASTE
IS INFERIOR TO MINE.
THIEF.
ARE YOU GOING
TO TELL ON ME ?
NO, I AM AN ACCOMPLICE
TO A THIEF.
AH, WHAT'S WRONG ?
YOU GOT WHAT YOU WANTED.
WHAT ABOUT CHRISTINE ?
OH, SORRY, YOUR LADYSHIP.
HASN'T SHE GOT FEELINGS ?
I WOULD'VE THOUGHT SO BEFORE,
BUT NOT NOW.
- SERVANTS ARE SERVANTS.
- AND WHORES ARE WHORES.
I DON'T MIND TELLING YOU
THAT WHEN I SAW YOU
IN THE ROSES,
I HAD THE SAME DIRTY THOUGHTS
AS ANY OTHER BOY MY AGE.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED
TO DIE FOR ME.
IN THE OAT BIN ?
THAT WAS JUST TALK.
YOU WERE LYING ?
NO.
YES.
IT WAS A STORY.
A STORY FOR WOMEN.
YOU BASTARD.
PUTAIN.
SO NOW YOU'VE FLOWN
WITH THE HAWKS.
I WOULDN'T SAY EXACTLY FLOWN.
- I WAS TO BE THE FIRST BRANCH.
- AND THE BRANCH WAS ROTTEN.
I WAS TO BE YOUR HOTEL SIGN.
I WAS TO SIT
BEHIND YOUR COUNTER,
ATTRACT YOUR CUSTOMERS
AND FIDDLE YOUR BILLS.
NO.  NO, I WAS GONNA
DO THAT MYSELF.
YOU WERE GOING TO COVER FOR ME
WITH YOUR SWEETEST SMILE.
YOUR VERY SOUL STINKS.
WASH IT, THEN.
HOW DARE YOU ?
SERVANT.
FOOTMAN.
STAND UP WHEN I SPEAK TO YOU.
SERVANT'S SLUT.
FOOTMAN'S WHORE.
WHY DON'T YOU SHUT YOUR MOUTH
AND FUCKING GET OUT OF HERE !
HOW DARE YOU ?
I STINK ?
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN ANYONE...
BEHAVE THE WAY
YOU HAVE TONIGHT ?
HMM ?
DO YOU THINK,
JULIE,
THAT A HOUSEMAID
WOULD BEHAVE TOWARDS A MAN
THE WAY YOU HAVE ?
HAVE YOU EVER,
JULIE,
SEEN ANY WOMAN OF MY CLASS
BEHAVE THE WAY
YOU HAVE TONIGHT ?
I'VE ONLY EVER SEEN IT
IN ANIMALS AND PROSTITUTES.
[ Whispers ]
HIT ME.
TRAMPLE ON ME.
I'M WORTHLESS.
I MUST SAY I'M QUITE PLEASED
WITH MY PART IN THE SEDUCTION.
ALTHOUGH IT WAS
A LITTLE TOO, UM, EASY
TO BE REALLY EXCITING.
WHY DON'T YOU HIT ME, THEN ?
[ Whispers ]
HIT ME.
NO.
FORGIVE ME.
I WOULDN'T KICK A DOG
WHEN THEY WERE DOWN,
LET ALONE A WOMAN.
THOUGH I MUST SAY I WAS...
GLAD TO REALIZE
IT WAS ONLY TINSEL
THAT DAZZLED MY HUMBLE EYES.
BUT IT HURTS TO REALIZE
THAT WHAT I WAS STRIVING FOR...
WASN'T SOMETHING
MORE SUBSTANTIAL,
MORE NOBLE.
IT HURTS TO SEE YOU
SUNK SO LOW,
FAR LOWER THAN A KITCHEN SLUT.
AND HOW YOU TALK AS IF
YOU'D ALREADY RISEN ABOVE ME.
I HAVE.
I CAN MAKE YOU A COUNTESS.
YOU CAN NEVER MAKE ME A COUNT.
I AM A CHILD OF NOBLE BIRTH.
THAT'S MORE THAN YOU
COULD EVER BE.
TRUE.  TRUE,
BUT MY CHILDREN COULD.
YOU'RE A THIEF,
AND I'M NOT.
THERE ARE MUCH WORSE THINGS
IN THIS WORLD THAN A THIEF,
BELIEVE ME.
YOU'RE A FINE WOMAN.
FAR TOO GOOD
FOR THE LIKES OF ME.
YOU MADE A MISTAKE,
AND NOW YOU'RE TRYING
TO JUSTIFY IT...
BY FOOLING YOURSELF
INTO BELIEVING YOU LOVE ME.
YOU DON'T LOVE ME.
YOU CRAVE FOR ME.
THAT MAKES YOUR LOVE
NO BETTER THAN MINE.
AND I COULDN'T BEAR
TO JUST BE YOUR ANIMAL.
AND I COULD NEVER
MAKE YOU LOVE ME.
HOW CAN YOU
BE SURE OF THAT ?
BUT I COULD LOVE YOU.
YOU'RE SO FINE...
AND EDUCATED...
AND LOVABLE
WHEN YOU WANT TO BE.
AND THE PASSIONS
YOU'VE AROUSED IN ME
WILL PROBABLY NEVER DIE.
ONE KISS FROM YOU--
YOU WON'T WIN ME LIKE THAT.
HOW THEN ?  HOW THEN ?
TELL ME HOW.
I CAN'T DO IT WITH SPEECHES.
I CAN'T DO IT WITH KISSES.
HOW THEN ?
[ Whispering ]
HOW ?  HOW ?
YOU ARE LOWER
THAN A SEWER RAT.
I LOATHE YOU, I LOATHE YOU,
I LOATHE YOU,
BUT I CANNOT...
ESCAPE FROM YOU.
THEN ESCAPE WITH ME.
[ Crying ]
HOW ?
HOW ?  TELL ME HOW.
GO UPSTAIRS...
TO YOUR FATHER'S STUDY.
THERE'S A KEY IN THE TOP
RIGHT-HAND DRAWER.
TAKE IT AND OPEN
THE BOTTOM LEFT-HAND DRAWER.
THERE IS MONEY IN THERE.
TAKE THE MONEY...
AND BRING IT DOWN HERE.
GIVE ME A GLASS OF WINE.
[ Footsteps Departing ]
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
HOW IRONIC.
I SWORE TO MY MOTHER
THAT I'D NEVER BE A SLAVE
TO ANY MAN.
SHE TAUGHT ME TO HATE MEN.
SHE HAD AN AVERSION
TO MARRIAGE.
SO WHEN MY FATHER PROPOSED
TO HER, SHE TOLD HIM NO,
SHE COULDN'T BE HIS WIFE
BUT THAT HE COULD BE HER LOVER.
[ Gulping ]
DON'T DRINK LIKE THAT.
WHY ?
IT'S COMMON.
HMPH.  I AM COMMON.
MY MOTHER WAS A COMMONER,
AND SHE BELIEVED
IN EQUALITY FOR WOMEN.
AND I WAS TO BE
THE LIVING PROOF
THAT A WOMAN...
IS EVERY BIT
AS GOOD AS A MAN.
I WAS TAUGHT EVERYTHING
BOYS ARE TAUGHT.
I WAS TAUGHT TO GROOM,
TO HARNESS, TO RIDE, TO SHOOT.
I WAS EVEN TAKEN TO AN ABATTOIR
TO LEARN HOW TO SLAUGHTER.
I COULDN'T DO THAT.
BUT MY FATHER ADORED HER.
HE ALLOWED HER TO CHANGE
EVERYTHING HERE.
THE MEN WERE GIVEN
THE WOMEN'S TASKS
AND THE WOMEN THE MEN'S,
AND THE WHOLE PLACE
FELL APART...
UNTIL MY FATHER CAME TO HIS
SENSES AND PUT  EVERYTHING BACK
TOGETHER AGAIN.
THAT'S WHEN SHE BECAME ILL.
I LOVED MY FATHER,
BUT I SIDED WITH MY MOTHER.
SHE TRIED TO SET
THE HOUSE ALIGHT, YOU KNOW ?
ALMOST DROVE HIM
TO SUICIDE.
DID YOU KNOW HE TRIED
TO SHOOT HIMSELF ?
[ Gulping ]
[ Chuckling ]
BUT HE MISSED.
YOU HATE MEN,
DON'T YOU ?
YES, MOST OF THE TIME.
BUT SOMETIMES WHEN I'M WEAK--
OH, MY GOD.
YOU HATE ME, DON'T YOU ?
UTTERLY.  I'D LIKE
TO HAVE YOU SLAUGHTERED.
SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW ?
WE ESCAPE TO LAKE COMO
WHERE THE SUN ALWAYS SHINES,
AND THE LAURELS ARE GREEN
AT CHRISTMASTIME,
AND THE ORANGES GLOW.
AND THERE...
WE ENJOY EACH OTHER...
FOR TEN DAYS, EIGHT DAYS,
HOWEVER LONG IT LASTS,
AND THEN WE DIE.
I'D RATHER OPEN A HOTEL.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO DIE WITH ME ?
I DON'T WANNA DIE.
I LIKE LIVING.
AND BESIDES,
SUICIDE'S A MORTAL SIN.
DO YOU BELIEVE IN GOD ?
[ Scoffs ]
I'M TIRED OF THIS.
I THINK THAT
A MAN OWES SOMETHING
TO THE WOMAN HE HAS DISGRACED.
ENOUGH ?
YOU BASTARD.
ME ?  A BASTARD ?
[ Gulping ]
WELL, AT LEAST I DON'T HAVE
ANY PIMPS IN MY FAMILY.
WHAT DID YOU SAY ?
YOUR FIRST RECORDED FOREFATHER
WAS A MILLER...
WHO GOT HIS TITLE, "COUNT,"
BY LETTING THE KING
FUCK HIS WIFE
DURING THE DANISH WAR.
I DON'T HAVE
NOBLE FOREFATHERS AT ALL.
NO, BUT YOU COULD HAVE
TRULY NOBLE OFFSPRING, JEAN.
BE KIND TO ME, JEAN.
TREAT ME LIKE A HUMAN BEING.
THEN BEHAVE LIKE ONE.
YOU SPIT ON ME,
BUT YOU WON'T LET ME
WIPE IT OFF ON YOU.
[ Bottle Thuds ]
IS THERE NO OTHER WAY OUT ?
YES.
YOU PACK YOUR BAGS
AND YOU LEAVE.
ALONE.
CAN'T DO THAT.
I NEED ORDERS
TO GET ME GOING.
I NEED... ORDERS.
I CAN'T GO.  I CAN'T STAY.
I NEED TO BE TOLD.
GO UPSTAIRS.
GO INTO YOUR FATHER'S STUDY,
GET THE MONEY
AND BRING IT DOWN HERE.
NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
[ Gulping ]
COME UP WITH ME.
NO.
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
WHAT'S BEEN GOIN' ON ?
MISS JULIE DRAGGED
EVERYBODY IN HERE.
MUST HAVE HEARD SOMETHING.
NO, I--
I SLEPT LIKE A LOG.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO TAKE ME
TO COMMUNION THIS MORNIN'.
MMM.
WHAT'S THE SERMON TODAY ?
[ Dishes Clattering ]
JOHN THE BAPTIST
HAVIN' HIS HEAD CUT OFF,
I SUSPECT.
IT SHOULD BE SUITABLY BRIEF.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING
ALL NIGHT ?
YOU NEVER CAME TO BED.
I WAS TALKING.
TALKING TO--
MISS JULIE.
[ Scoffs ]
THAT ONE DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT'S PROPER.
WERE YOU DRINKING
WITH HER AS WELL ?
LOOK AT ME.
WERE YOU DRINKING
WITH HER ?
YES.
OH, THAT POOR GIRL.
YOU DIDN'T--
[ Whispering ]
WELL, SHAME ON YOU.
WHAT AN EVIL THING TO DO !
I DON'T WANT TO STAY
IN THIS HOUSE ANY LONGER IF
YOU CAN'T RESPECT YOUR BETTERS.
WHY SHOULD YOU
RESPECT THEM ?
YOU WOULDN'T WANT TO WORK
FOR PEOPLE WHO AREN'T
RESPECTABLE, WOULD YOU ?
TAKE COMFORT IN THE FACT
THAT THEY'RE NO BETTER
THAN WE ARE.
IF THEY AREN'T
ANY BETTER THAN US,
THEN WHAT IS THE POINT
IN US STRIVING
TO BETTER OURSELVES ?
DID YOU THINK OF THE COUNT ?
DID YOU ?
OF THE SORROW
THAT MAN'S HAD ?
I DON'T WANT TO STAY HERE
ANY LONGER.
[ Bottles Rattling ]
IF IT HAD BEEN CLARA
OR ONE OF THE KITCHEN GIRLS,
THEN I'D BE JEALOUS.
BUT... NOT OF HER.
TO GIVE HERSELF TO YOU ?
THE FOOTMAN ?
IF IT HAD BEEN THAT LAWYER
OR SOMEONE BETTER--
I WON'T STAY.
I WON'T STAY HERE
ANY LONGER.
WHERE WOULD YOU GO ?
WHERE WOULD
WE GO ?
I CAN'T GET
A POSITION LIKE THIS
ONCE I'M MARRIED.
BUT YOU CAN GET A JOB
AS A PORTER OR A CARETAKER--
OR A CIVIL SERVANT.
THE CIVIL SERVICE PAY IS BAD,
BUT AT LEAST THERE'S A PENSION
FOR THEIR WIFE AND CHILDREN.
I'VE NO INTENTION OF DYING
FOR MY WIFE AND CHILDREN.
NOT YET !
I'VE GOT MORE AMBITIONS
THAN THAT.
I KNOW ABOUT
YOUR AMBITIONS.
OH, YES.  WHAT ABOUT
YOUR RESPONSIBILITIES ?
DON'T TALK TO ME
ABOUT RESPONSIBILITIES !
[ Footsteps Overhead ]
WHO'S THAT WALKING AROUND
UP THERE ?
[ Footsteps Continue ]
IT'S CLARA.
IT COULDN'T BE THE COUNT,
COULD IT ?
NO, THE COUNT
WOULD HAVE RUNG.
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Footsteps Departing ]
YOU GO AND GET READY
FOR CHURCH.  COME ON.
GO ON, GO ON.
OFF YOU GO.
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Whispering ]
SHH.  CHRISTINE'S AWAKE.
DOES SHE
SUSPECT ANYTHING ?
NO.  DID YOU
GET THE MONEY ?
YES.
ENOUGH ?
[ Suitcase Thuds ]
MISS JULIE ?
ENOUGH TO BEGIN WITH.
DO YOU WANT TO COUNT IT ?
ARE YOU STILL
COMING WITH ME ?
YES.  YES !
[ Panting ]
NOW WE--  WE'LL LEAVE
BY THE FRONT DOOR.
[ Bird Chirping ]
ALL RIGHT ?
GOOD MORNING,
SWEETHEART.
GOOD MORNING.
THE SUN IS RISING.
[ Chirping Continues ]
CHASING THE DEMONS AWAY.
YES, THE DEMONS WERE
CERTAINLY OUT LAST NIGHT.
COME HERE, SWEETHEART.
NOW, I'VE BEEN THINKING.
WE CAN'T GO BY THE BACK DOORS,
SO WE'LL GO THROUGH THE FRONT.
THAT WAY NO ONE
WILL SUSPECT ANYTHING.
I'LL PLAY THE FOOTMAN.
PRETEND TO BE A FOOTMAN.
LAST TIME.
[ Whispering ]
MISS JULIE,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
MISS JULIE !
MISS JULIE,
WE CAN'T TAKE THE BIRD.
IF WE TAKE THE BIRD,  WE DRAW
ATTENTION TO OURSELVES.
IF WE DRAW ATTENTION
TO OURSELVES, WE GET CAUGHT.
[ Bird Screeching ]
LEAVE THE BIRD !
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE
WITHOUT HER.
MISS JULIE,
WE HAVE TO LEAVE NOW.
SHE'S MY ONE MEMORY
FROM THIS HOUSE !
SHH !
[ Wings Fluttering ]
COME AND HELP ME WITH HER.
[ Sighs ]
ALL RIGHT.  ALL RIGHT.
LET ME IN.  LET ME--
[ Chirping ]
[ Chirping Continues ]
[ Gasps, Screams ]
[ Cleaver Thuds ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Crying Softly ]
YOU SHOULD HAVE LEARNED
HOW TO SLAUGHTER PROPERLY.
[ Crying Continues ]
SLAUGHTER ME TOO.
I CURSE THE MOMENT
I SET EYES ON YOU.
I WAS CONCEIVED
IN MY MOTHER'S WOMB.
I DESPISE YOU.
I HATE YOU.
YOU THINK I CAN'T STAND
THE SIGHT OF BLOOD ?
[ Sobbing ]
YOU THINK I'M WEAK ?
I'D LOVE TO SEE
YOUR BLOOD AND BRAINS
ON THIS CHOPPING BLOCK !
I'D LOVE TO SEE
THE WHOLE OF YOUR SEX
SWIMMING IN A LAKE OF BLOOD !
I'D DRINK FROM YOUR SKULL,
WASH MY FEET IN YOUR RIB CAGE,
DEVOUR YOUR HEART
IN ONE MOUTHFUL !
YOU THINK I'M WEAK ?
YOU THINK I LOVE YOU BECAUSE
MY WOMB DESIRED YOUR SEED ?
YOU THINK I WANT TO
CARRY YOUR OFFSPRING
UNDER MY HEART...
AND NOURISH IT
WITH MY BLOOD ?
BEAR YOUR CHILD
AND TAKE YOUR NAME ?
I'VE NEVER EVEN HEARD
YOUR SURNAME !  I SUPPOSE
YOU HAVEN'T GOT ONE.
I'D BECOME "LADY FOOTMAN"
OR "MADAM SHITHOUSE" !
YOU DOG WHO WEARS MY COLLAR !
YOU LABORER'S SON
WHO WEARS MY COAT OF ARMS
ON YOUR BUTTONS !
AM I TO SHARE YOU
WITH MY COOK ?
AM I TO BE THE RIVAL
OF THE KITCHEN SLUT ?
YOU-- YOU THINK I'M A COWARD
AND WANT TO ESCAPE ?
I'M STAYING !
[ Clattering ]
LET THE CLOUDS BURST !
MY FATHER WILL COME HOME.
HE'LL FIND HIS DESK
BROKEN INTO, THE MONEY GONE.
HE'LL SEND FOR THE POLICE.
I'LL TELL HIM EVERYTHING.
EVERYTHING.
AND IT WILL KILL MY FATHER,
AND THAT WILL BE THE END
FOR ALL OF US.
AND THE COUNT'S LONG LINE
WILL HAVE COME TO AN END.
BUT THE FOOTMAN'S LINE
WILL CONTINUE
IN AN ORPHANAGE...
AND WITH LAURELS IN THE GUTTER
AND END UP IN PRISON !
[ Gasping ]
[ Panting ]
YOU BASTARD.
[ Sobbing ]
[ Sobbing Continues ]
AND WHERE WOULD YOU BOTH
BE GOING DRESSED LIKE THAT ?
OH, HELP ME,
CHRISTINE.
SAVE ME.
SAVE ME FROM THIS MAN.
YOU-- YOU DON'T
TRUST THIS BASTARD.
LISTEN.  LISTEN.
YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
NO, I WON'T.
NO, I DON'T.
THE KITCHEN SLUT
WOULD LIKE TO KNOW
WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
TO CHURCH, I HOPE.
YOU BETTER SHAVE.
PLEASE.
[ Sobbing Continues ]
CHRISTINE.
TRY-- TRY TO UNDERSTAND.
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
BUT IF YOU'RE THINKING OF
TRICKING HIM INTO RUNNING AWAY,
I'LL SOON PUT A STOP TO IT.
[ Breathing Heavily ]
WHAT IF ALL THREE OF US
WERE TO GO ABROAD TOGETHER...
TO SWITZERLAND ?
I'VE GOT MONEY,
YOU SEE.
PLEASE SAY YES,
CHRISTINE.
PLEASE SAY YES.
WE'LL SET UP A HOTEL TOGETHER,
AND YOU COULD BE IN CHARGE
OF THE KITCHENS.
WOULDN'T THAT BE GOOD ?
PLEASE SAY YES.
[ Crying Softly ]
YOU'VE NEVER TRAVELED,
CHRISTINE.
YOU SHOULD GET OUT
AND SEE THE WORLD.
YOU CAN'T IMAGINE
WHAT FUN IT IS
TO TRAVEL BY TRAIN.
THERE'S NEW PEOPLE
ALL THE TIME
AND NEW COUNTRIES.
AND WHEN WE GET TO HAMBURG,
WE'LL VISIT THE ZOO--
YOU'LL LIKE THAT--
AND THE THEATER
AND THE OPERA.
WHEN WE GET TO MUNICH,
WE'LL VISIT ALL THE MUSEUMS.
THE GREAT PAINTERS ARE THERE.
RUBENS, RAPHAEL.
YOU'VE HEARD OF MUNICH,
HAVEN'T YOU ?
WHERE KING LUDVIG LIVED.
THE KING WHO WENT MAD.
HIS CASTLES ARE STILL THERE,
JUST LIKE IN THE FAIRY TALES.
[ Crying Continues ]
AND FROM THERE
IT'S NOT FAR TO THE ALPS.
IMAGINE THE ALPS
WITH SUN ON THEM...
AND SNOW IN THE MIDDLE
OF SUMMER.
WHERE THE SUN ALWAYS SHINES
AND THE LAURELS ARE GREEN
AND THE ORANGES GLOW.
WE'LL SET UP A HOTEL THERE,
AND WE'LL HAVE SUCH
A BUSY LIFE, YOU'LL SEE.
TRAINS WHISTLING,
COACHES COMING AND GOING,
BELLS RINGING IN THE APARTMENT
AND IN THE RESTAURANT.
AND YOU WILL BE
THE HEAD WAITRESS.
I WILL SIT BEHIND THE COUNTER
AND FIDDLE THE BILLS.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW EMBARRASSED PEOPLE ARE
WHEN IT COMES TO PAYING.
BUT YOU, YOU WILL BE
THE HEAD WAITRESS.
YOU WON'T HAVE TO SLAVE
OVER A HOT STOVE.
OH, NO.
YOU'LL BE NICELY DRESSED,
TALKING TO THE GUESTS.
AND YOU WITH YOUR LOOKS--
I'M NOT FLATTERING YOU--
YOU'LL MAKE YOURSELF
A GOOD CATCH ONE DAY.
A RICH ENGLISHMAN.
'CAUSE ENGLISHMEN
ARE SUCH AN EASY CATCH.
AND THEN WE'LL BE RICH,
AND WE'LL BUILD OURSELVES
A VILLA ON LAKE COMO.
AND IT-- IT DOES SOMETIMES
RAIN THERE A LITTLE,
BUT IT MUST SURELY BE SUNNY
SOMETIMES AS WELL.
ALTHOUGH IT LOOKS DARK.
AND THEN WE--
[ Crying Continues ]
OR ELSE WE--
WE CAN RETURN...
HERE OR GO HOME.
OR WE CAN GO SOMEWHERE ELSE.
[ Sniffling ]
[ Softly ]
DOES MISS JULIE
BELIEVE ANY OF THIS ?
[ Sobbing ]
[ Sniffling ]
SO YOU WERE PLANNING
TO ESCAPE ?
YOU LYING BASTARD !
WATCH YOUR LANGUAGE.
WATCH YOUR LANGUAGE
IN FRONT OF THE MISTRESS.
[ Scoffs ]
"MISTRESS" ?
SHE'S STILL YOUR SUPERIOR.
ARE YOU COMIN'
TO CHURCH WITH ME OR NOT ?
NO.  NO.
YOU GO AND YOU CONFESS
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN UP TO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YOU STEAL FROM THE GROCERIES.
ALL RIGHT, I WILL GO.
AND I'LL COME BACK
WITH ENOUGH FORGIVENESS
FOR BOTH OF US.
THE SAVIOR SUFFERED AND DIED
ON THE CROSS FOR OUR SINS,
AND IF WE GO TO HIM
WITH FAITH AND REPENTANCE,
HE'LL TAKE OUR SINS
UPON HIMSELF.
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT ?
I BELIEVE IT...
AS TRULY AS I STAND HERE.
IT'S BEEN MY BELIEF
SINCE I WAS A CHILD,
AND I'VE KEPT IT EVER SINCE.
WHERE SIN OVERFLOWETH,
THERE OVERFLOWETH GRACE.
[ Gasps ]
IF ONLY I HAD YOUR FAITH.
[ Water Splashing ]
WELL, GOD'S GRACE ISN'T GIVEN
FOR EVERYONE TO RECEIVE.
WHO DOES
RECEIVE IT, THEN ?
WELL, THE LORD
DOES NOT FAVOR ANYONE,
BUT THE LAST
SHALL BE THE FIRST.
[ Splashing Continues ]
BUT THEN HE DOES FAVOR.
HE FAVORS THE LAST.
"AND IT'S EASIER FOR A CAMEL
TO PASS THROUGH THE EYE
OF A NEEDLE...
THAN FOR A RICH MAN
TO ENTER THE KINGDOM OF GOD."
SEE, THAT'S HOW IT IS.
ON MY WAY OUT, I'LL STOP
AT THE STABLES AND TELL THEM
NOT TO RELEASE ANY HORSES,
JUST IN CASE ANYONE
SHOULD WANT TO LEAVE
BEFORE THE COUNT RETURNS.
GOOD-BYE, MISS JULIE.
[ Blade Scraping ]
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN A HYPNOTIST
IN THE THEATER ?
WHEN THE MAN
SAYS TO THE SUBJECT,
"TAKE THE BROOM,"
AND HE TAKES IT.
THEN HE SAYS, "NOW SWEEP,"
AND HE SWEEPS.
DO THAT.
YOU CAN.  YOU WERE SO GOOD
IN MY FATHER'S COAT.
YOU WERE A REAL ARISTOCRAT.
YOU CAN DO IT.
IT'S LIGHT AND PEACEFUL,
AND THE ROOM IS...
FULL OF SMOKE.
AND YOUR EYES ARE LIKE
TWO GLOWING COALS...
IN A DYING FIRE.
I CAN FEEL
THE HEAT FROM YOU.
TELL ME TO TAKE THE BROOM.
TAKE THE BROOM.
THANK YOU.
NOW TELL ME THAT THE FIRST
MAY ALSO RECEIVE
THE GIFT OF GRACE.
SAY IT, EVEN IF
YOU DON'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU'RE NOT ONE OF
THE FIRST ANYMORE.
YOU BELONG TO THE LAST.
THAT'S TRUE.
[ Telephone Ringing ]
[ Ringing Continues ]
YES, YOUR GRACE.
MM-HMM.
OF COURSE, SIR.
YES, SIR.
CERTAINLY, SIR.
MM-HMM.
NICE TO HAVE
YOU BACK, SIR.
[ Giggling ]
[ Giggling Continues ]