Christopher Titus 2017 Born with A Defect
Hello Everyone! Yes! Hello!
Way too much! Alright! Good!
Very nice! Thank you!
Ok, alright. That’s enough.
I have a show to do.
I’ve never talked about this
before, I’m gonna talk about it now…
I was born with a defect, um,
I was actually born a
child, and,
I don’t understand how
human beings run anything.
We’re the only species born
without ability or instinct.
Every other animal has it.
Dolphin,
swims for its first breath.
Deer, walks in an hour.
Human child needs two
adults around it for 5 years
so it doesn’t
choke on a Cheerio.
If babies didn’t smile
cute they would be food.
Babies are worthless,
there’s nothing there.
Having a baby is
like buying a laptop
that won’t turn on
and shits itself.
We can’t even survive
the first couple years
unless someone’s ramming a nipple
in our face every two hours.
I still feel like that to this
day, anyone else?
Yeah. Yes, thank you.
But,
if it’s a boy child,
the nipple’s rammed in too often,
he has a problem with
women later in life.
And if it’s a girl child,
the nipple’s rammed
in too often,
she “experiments in college”
You know what you did.
Every other animal on the
planet has fear programmed.
We invented the X-games.
Every other animal hears a combine
going through the corn field,
hears that motor
– hides in a hole.
A human toddler hears a combine
going through a corn field,
runs in front of it and goes
“Daddy! Truck!”
Thhrrtthrrrt, “Ahhh, dammit.
Gotta clean out the shoot again.”
That’s right. Joke number five
we chopped up a
child in a combine.
Are you guys ready? Good.
Good. Yeah, yay! Wooo!
Every other animal on the planet
is instinctively afraid of fire.
Human beings learn about fire…
By touching fire.
That’s defective.
How did we get the keys to this planet?
Now, my brother learned
about fire when he was 10,
because 10-year-old boys are just
pyromaniac puppies with opposable thumbs.
And we had a real
cool uncle growing up.
Remember that cool uncle we all had
– he was so cool when you were a kid!
And then you became
an adult and realized
someone should have
called child services.
“Hey, here’s a magazine.
Put that under your bed
– don’t tell your dad, huh?
Hey, you ever tried
120 proof Whiskey?
Don’t tell your dad, huh?
Don’t sign anything from
the God Damn government.
I signed your dad’s name,
don’t tell your dad, huh?”
That uncle.
When we were little,
he would do like, the thumb trick.
I mean the, the thumb… not…
that’s the other uncle.
That’s, no.
He would do – the magic trick.
But as we got
older in my family,
uncle started giving us
criminal knowledge at barbeques.
And we were always hanging out with
him and the adults weren’t there,
I guess in case
they had to testify,
I don’t know why.
And one day my uncle just
comes out on Fourth of July
with this giant can
of bug spray and goes
“Kids,
you know bug spray’s flammable?
Don’t tell your dad!”
Pulls a lighter and just goes
PHHFFFFFHHHHHH
and we were little
kids, we were just like
“THAT’S THE COOLEST
THING WE’VE EVER SEEN!”
And now as an adult I realize
IT’S ALSO HOW THEY TRAIN ISIS!!
But you can’t show
little kids this…
so this knowledge beats around in
my brothers head for three months
and then one day
in the backyard,
it pops like a stupidity zit
And we had these giant concrete
planters in our backyard
that my dad had…
stolen from work.
Or as dad said “It aint stealin’
if they aint usin’ ‘em!”
“Then why are we picking
them up at midnight, dad?”
“Cuz they aint usin’
‘em, dumb-ass!”
Some of these jokes dad
wrote when he was alive, so…
So my brother gets this
big giant can of bug napalm
and starts just filling
up this planter with mist
and he’s throwing matches into
it, and it was working,
it was “PHHHFHHHH”
it was like a KISS
concert in the backyard.
Without the 55-year-old women
flashing their boobs – oh my God.
Yeah, there’s a day for all
of us to keep our shirts down.
And if you don’t know that day –
ask a friend, they’ll be honest.
I have to do a little side-bar.
I actually did a show a while back,
four years ago up in Northern California
for uh, Michael Anthony and Sammy Hagar, then
we opened this big thing for a radio station.
It’s 15,000 seats, I go up.
I’m doing jokes.
In the middle of me doing jokes,
some 450 lb.,
like 60-year-old woman just goes
“RAAAAAAAAAAH.”
You MAY be able to play guitar…
but it’s hard to tell jokes
with puke in your mouth.
So, my brother’s setting
these planters afire.
He does that for like an
hour, then he gets bored,
and he’s a 10-year-old boy so he
wants some more pyrotechnic knowledge,
cuz he knows one day
he may be a warlock.
He snaps a branch off a tree,
makes a fuse out of it,
strips it all down,
puts it in the bottom of the planter,
coats it in this horrible,
toxic, cancer-causing bug juice,
fills it with mist again,
and he’s gonna light it.
But before he lights it,
he wants to see what’s gonna happen,
so he takes his face,
and he puts it in the planter.
And this is why I’m pissed Youtube
didn’t exist when I was a child.
Cuz this is,
this is sponsorship money right here.
And he lights it,
and before he can move a millimeter,
goes SHHHHOOPPPPHHHHH!
Yeah...yeah.
And when he stood
up – he was tan.
Eyebrow-less.
And the center part of his
hair, right here, was missing.
He looked like a 10-year-old
middle-aged accountant.
With hair plugs.
Just ash on top of his head.
And I come home like an hour
later and he is freaking out
“OH MY GOD, LOOK WHAT I
DID – DAD’S GONNA KILL ME!”
And I’m the older brother,
I said “Calm down, Dad IS gonna kill you.
But why stress if you
know it’s gonna happen?”
“Shut up man,
you gotta help me!”
“I can’t help you – you’ve
disfigured yourself.
I think we can’t like, shave the dog and
made a tiny toupee, it’s gonna be stupid.
I mean, I’ll get out a Sharpie
and draw on your eyebrows for you,
you’re gonna look like a pirate
on chemo that’s all I’m gonna say.
ARG!”
Remember when you were a kid and
you committed that household felony?
We all did it, the big one.
I’m talking the big one.
You had the water fight in
the house with the hose.
Drywall had to be replaced.
Threw a firecracker in the toilet
“Just to see what’s gonna happen.”
Gave one of your friends antifreeze
and told him it was Gatorade.
Had to watch the EMT’s drive
off to get his stomach pumped
AND YOU KNEW PARENTS
HAD BEEN CALLED.
And all you had to
do was wait for Dad.
And I wasn’t in trouble, so it was fun.
I got to observe.
And you could see the stress tumors
metastasizing in my brother as it got closer.
And at 5:30 you hear the car
pull in the driveway and,
I have to admit,
my brother took it like a man.
He went and stood right in
front of the front door just
he looked like a guy on death
row in a Johnny Cash song just
“I’m gonna have to pay
for what I done...”
And my father opens the door, puts his
briefcase down, looks at my brother and goes
“HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!”
And my brother goes “Dad,
let me tell you what happened”
“I don’t care what
happened – hahhahaha –
whatever you did, you paid for it.
Haha.
DON’T DO IT AGAIN GOD DAMMIT!”
We’re idiots.
As a species it’s
just, we’re idiots.
And I am a father, which just,
you know, was just a mistake.
And frightens people.
When I tell people I have kids,
they don’t go “boys or girls?”
they go “Really?
They okay?”
“Ehhhhh,
compared to me? Uh, yeah.”
I have two kids.
Uh, two marriages.
And a parade of stress polyps
in my colon having a rave.
And if you’re a parent tonight,
you know what a joy having children is.
And if you’re a parent tonight, you know it’s
hard to say that sentence without laughing.
Every parent in this room
at one point has stared
into their children’s yellow,
hazy, sugar-fueled eyes and thought
“I was tricked.
I could have been something.
Next Thanksgiving I’m punching
my mom in the throat."
And that’s where
love comes from.
And I want to be clear – I do love
my kids because I... hate jail.
And this is about the time of the show where
women tend to get a little stink-face going on.
They’re like “Oh my God what’s
he talking about? Kids are great.
What is he talking about? They’re amazing,
they’re little Jesus tears, that’s what they are.”
No, not all. No.
They’re little Jesus hemorrhoids,
that’s what they are.
Yeah. They are painful,
annoying and hard to get rid of.
I just described a hemorrhoid.
That’s a hemorrhoid.
Alright, let me ask you parents who actually
think their kids just “rule the world,
they’re the greatest
thing ever.”
When’s the last time your kid
walked in the room and said
“Mom, Dad,
can I help you with anything?
Mom, Dad what would YOU
like for Christmas?”
Do you realize if you had a
friend that borrowed $20 from you
so he could go out and buy
you a shitty birthday present,
you would stab him in
the face with a fork?
Yeah I want to be clear about what
tonight’s show is gonna be about.
If you are a parent,
tonight’s show is therapy.
If you don’t have kids, tonight’s
show is 90 minutes of birth control.
You’re welcome. You.
Are. Welcome.
They’re horrible, man.
Having a kid is like putting
all your money into asbestos.
Dangerous, causes disease and if
it’s yours, you’re liable for it.
They are. They’re just little
disease-filled skin-bags,
passing onto you every disease that’s
floating through its preschool, man.
Preschool, just a viral hot-zone full
of patient zeros, that’s all it is.
A room full of
sociopathic humans
who can play board games while
SITTING IN THEIR OWN FECES.
THAT’S MENTAL PATIENT BEHAVIOR!
And every parent in this room
at one point has had a sick kid,
and sent it to school anyway.
Yeaaah. I know you people without kids are
thinking “That’s horrible, that’s irresponsible!”
Well, maybe, but also,
sometimes you need a couple fuckin’ hours.
The problem is every other
parent did the same thing,
or that joke would
have gotten one laugh,
and we would have beat the Hell out of
that person for making our kid sick.
The problem is we all send them to
school, put them in one room,
see what kind of Ebola
cocktail they can come up with…
I’m not worried about terrorists
coming up with a super-plague
– I’m worried about it being weaponized at
naptime. That’s when it’s gonna get weird.
You know who’s going to
survive the apocalypse?
Cockroaches and
Kindergarten teachers.
Cuz their immune system
is just AMAZING. Yeah,
“Knock her down,
we gotta get the antidote.”
They’re horrible. Any why is every little
kid under 6 always oozing something?
What the Hell is
coming out of them?
It’s not a solid,
it’s not a liquid,
it’s nowhere on the element
chart, what is it?
How come every kid under 6
is just a little bit steamy?
Have you ever
touched a little kid?
It’s like Ch-Chhh “Ahhhhhh.”
Trying to pull your hand out is like
trying to get Velcro off a poodle
– Ch-Chhhh “Ehhhh!
What the Hell is on you?”
“There’s nothing on me!”
Pppppfffthhhhhhh-pppffffffff.
And they love it.
Whatever goo that is,
they love it. They love it.
I can prove it.
Try to wipe any kid
under 6 with a napkin.
It’s like you’re
pepper-spraying them.
How defective is that?
You’re literally covered in slime that
could wipe out an indigenous people,
and you just keep eating
your fucking cookie.
That joke came from
a real place – I,
I was doing bills one night,
I was doing all the bills
and I did all the like, the household
bills, then I did my wife and I bills,
and then the kid bills, and there was
more kid bills than the adult bills.
And I got – I went
to a bad place,
and I was walking through the house and I
walked past the living room where my kids were
and they weren’t digging ditches
or putting an addition on the house
they were on the couch, wrapped in blankets,
eating the tray of cookies in front of them.
And I just stopped
and “Look at you.
Sitting there eating
your fucking cookies.”
And then in my head went, “back out of the room,
you don’t want to be in the news like this."
And I walk away.
Just little disease-filled skin
bags that want you to hug it.
That’s all that they are.
People complain all the time “Ah, I wasn’t hugged
enough as a child, I had to go to therapy.”
Hug you? Until you were 10 you
were a pathogen with legs, man.
Between 1 and 3 all of us were just war
crimes in plastic pants, that’s all we were.
Ahh, and I don’t care
if you have kids or not.
Everybody in this room at one point has walked into
someone else’s house who has kids and said this sentence
“What is that smell?”
And I don’t mean the baby
smell when they’re little,
the talcum powdery,
that’s kinda cute.
I mean once they hit
the larvae stage.
And the first time it happened to
me, my son was 7
and you’re not ready for it,
I didn’t know what the Hell it was,
I walked in and went “Oh, ahh, uh.
Honey, call State Farm!
We have toxic mold – everyone get their masks
on, we’re gonna be Japanese for a couple weeks!”
Did you hear that pause?
That was that pause, you guys checked
to see if that joke was racist.
You went “HA...uhhh...heh."
Don’t worry, I got this,
relax, I cleared it.
You know, whenever I see 12 Japanese
people in the airport with masks on,
I never think “That is
so cute culturally.”
I always think “What
the Hell do they know?”
I’m gonna go down to the Rosetta Stone
kiosk and get some God damn answers.
So you walk into the house as
a parent and you’re thinking,
“Ok, what is that smell?
Oh, I know what that smell is –
that smell is one of the
tiny pets that disappeared.”
Cuz when they’re little
you can’t talk about death.
When a pet dies when they’re
little, it’s like a mob hit.
“Daddy,
what happened to Mr. Pickles?”
“Mr.
Pickles got a job downstate.
Why you aksing so
many questions?
How ‘bout you go in the other room and
eat your fuckin’ cookie, how ‘bout that?
How ‘bout that, huh?”
And then you walk into
the house and you go
“OK, I know what I’m looking for now, I’m looking for
a guinea pig corpse, that’s what I’m looking for.”
And after a while you think,
“That smell is too big,
maybe someone left a tuna fish sandwich
in the vagina of a sperm whale, cuz…”
Yeah, that one’s a little tart isn’t it?
That one?
It’s one of those special
laughs “Hahaha-thpthtpthpthpt”
I have two children,
I have two children.
I have a uh, 12 year old boy
and a 14-year-old girl, uh,
so my house is the thunder
dome of stink right now.
It is a dueling piano bar of odor and they are trading
the title all the time, it’s really interesting.
My daughter is also going through
the change which is just amazing.
Amazing, oh.
“Hi Daddy.
Hahaha, herherher, arhaahaha.”
“Honey, calm down,
I know what this is.
You are very pretty.
And here are some M&M’s.”
I’m a good dad.
My son is 12,
which means he is Olympic-level dumb.
10 to 14-year-old boys,
man, I don’t understand.
I thought he was on the
spectrum for a long time.
“Well, I guess we
just got to love him.”
And then one day a bunch of his
friends came over and I'm like,
“Oh, they’re ALL idiots!
Honey, we’re ok,
he’s just normal stupid, we’re fine!”
Stupidest group of
kids I’ve ever seen.
10 to 14-year-old boys man, if aliens
landed at my kids’ school and JUST
interviewed the 10 to 14-year-old
boys, they would vaporize the Earth.
I mean “Nah, this species is going to die out on
its own, let’s just end it here with these guys,
my God. Look at it. The socks don’t match, they’re
wearing cargo shorts with long sleeve shirts.
Jesus, they think they’re funny and
they’re not and WHAT IS THAT SMELL?”
I came downstairs on a
Saturday a while back
and my son’s sitting on the
couch watching television.
And he has on no pants.
I don’t mean he has on
underwear and no pants…
I mean, he’s got a long t-shirt
on, and ABSOLUTELY NO PANTS.
And he was 11.
He knew about pants.
I go “What are you doing?”
“I’m watching cartoons.”
“You have no pants.”
He looks me right
in the face and goes
“OOOOOOOOHHHHHHH.”
Like it wasn’t even in the
top 5 things buggin’ him…
and then…
HE GOES BACK TO
WATCHING TELEVISION.
To you people that
don’t have kids
you think you’ve been
angry in your life?
That’s adorable.
That is soooo cute.
I’m not saying you’ve never been
angry, I’m just saying…
your normal, single,
non-kid anger is a 10 here…
when you have a child, it’s like adding a
four-inch layer of bitter frustration icing…
that smells like almonds
and tastes like aneurism.
And you can’t do anything because they’re
little kids, you can’t… they’re little kids.
You can’t knee ‘em in the face
because the laws are different now.
My dad didn’t have those laws,
that’s why I’m not symmetrical.
And you, you just can’t start screaming
because you lose all credibility,
so what I find myself doing
now, so nothing bad happens,
is I turn and I walk out of the room
having a mumble argument to myself.
“You know, really, ok… wow.
HA HA HA.
You know what pants are. And you’re
too young to have to air it out,
I don’t know what
you’re thinking.
And what makes you think it’s ok to put your greasy
little boy-taint on my leather couch, my God?
I mean, Jesus Christ,
you left a racing stripe
the dogs won’t go near.”
I don’t think we have a homeless
problem in this Country…
I think it’s just parents roaming
the streets talking to themselves.
Trying to figure out what
the Hell their kid just did.
And thank God I have a spouse because
I can go find her. say to my wife
“Did you see what…? Cuz that… Did you tell him it was…
cuz I didn’t...I don’t even know what the fuck… you know,
I’m gonna go for a walk.
I gotta go, I gotta go.”
And then I find myself in front of my house
just walking down the street going like
“Why would you put every piece of clothing
you own IN the washer at one time?
You heard the washer going
‘YEEAAOOOUUUWAAAAOOOUH’
and you saw the smoke and the FLAMES
pouring out of the back of it,
after you filled it with DISH
SOAP, you little dumb-ass, my God.”
And while I’m in front
of my house spaz-ranting,
someone slaps a
dollar in my hand…
I’m gonna stay out
here and do THIS.
This is WAY easier
than raising a kid!
And I MADE money!
So I come back downstairs
after I’ve calmed down,
I go “Go get on some pants!”
And here’s what pissed me off worse –
he got up like I did something wrong.
He got up like “Oh, Dad lives in the
40’s where people gotta wear pants.”
I go about my Saturday…
I flick through some channels, I check some
emails, and blah blah blah, and I forget about him.
For 90 minutes.
Yeah, and THEN,
all of a sudden I realize,
I haven’t heard a noise out of my
son in over an hour and a half.
Now, to you people without kids –
that sounds amazing, doesn’t it?
“Oh God, how great was that?”
Noooooooo.
No. Until you have one,
you will not know the bone-chilling terror
of that first nano-second you
notice the death-like silence
of a free-range 11-year-old boy.
It’s like waking up on a flight,
and noticing the engines just quit.
And I start bolting through the
house, I get to his room,
I was like “DAAAAAAAAAAAAHHH!”
And you know when I found him?
I wish to God he was doing
something diabolical, evil…
building a bomb, worshiping Satan...
something.
Cuz at least then I know he was doing
something productive AAAAAAAAAND
he’s gonna be the leader
of the prison gang.
“What’s your son doing?”
“He’s running Chino.”
That’s a conversation
that I’m willing to have with
somebody if that’s where it ends up.
INSTEAD, I look into my son’s room,
he’s standing in the middle of the room
simply doing this –
“ ”
What the Hell is he doing?
“What are you doing?
What are you getting ready for an
early 20’s crystal meth addiction?
What is that?”
I look down, still no pants.
But progress has been made.
And this happened.
My son is NOW,
wearing TWO pair of underwear.
I don’t have a context
for that conversation.
I can’t even sit down and
give him a Dad life lesson.
“I remember when I put on
two pair of underwear…”
I – I – I just went…
“You get, what the f—ahhh.
Wow. Don’t you have nerve
endings in your ass?
You didn’t notice that you
put underwear over underwear?
And just because you put
underwear over underwear
doesn’t make the second
pair of underwear pants,
oh my God,
what does this special school cost??
Jesus.
I can’t spell
Montessori, God Jesus.
AND WHAT IS THAT SMELL?!”
That smell, I swear I wasn’t
gonna be one of those parents.
Everyone has a friend who had
too many kids – they regret it.
And when you go to their house, it
always smells like they are cooking eggs.
“Would you guys like to
eat out on the patio?”
“Please. Thank you.”
And I wasn’t gonna be that
– they had just given up.
You could tell they
had just given up.
That their house is gonna smell like that
until everyone leaves and they… burn it down.
And I wasn’t gonna
be that parent.
So the first time that it happened, I went
in his room and I went through everything.
I went through his drawers,
I went through his closet and “Ha-HA!”
I couldn’t find the smell.
I WISH there was a 12-inch
human turd under his bed.
Cuz then I could go “VICTORY!
I HAVE FOUND THE SMELL!
Get the hazmat suits and the
bleach and then we shall dance!”
Instead I just walked out
“Why… how does it soak into latex?
It’s impossible, oh my God.”
If you have kids – that smell – if
you have boys especially – UUGHH.
Girls have it too.
My daughter has a weird thing.
Her room looks great,
but you open her closet and it’s like
HEHHHRRAGGHHH “Ok, alright.
Your clothes have fumes, honey.
They shouldn’t have fuuumes.”
The smell is worse than a
hospital, or a nursing home,
or a, or a death camp.
Like, I could save some people from
Dachau, hide in my son’s room
“Stay here,
the nazis’ll never get you here!”
And after about 10
minutes they would go
“You know,
we’re gonna go back to the camp.
Do you smell that? Uhhehh
Eckhhhh.
I think I need a shower. Eh.”
No
No. No.
Nooo.
No.
Don’t you “ew” that – that
joke tracks perfectly.
I put ‘em in my son’s room –
they smelt something horrible –
they felt disgusting –
they needed a shower.
But then YOU GUYS
added history.
Yeah. That’s on you bitches.
As a matter of fact “Oooooh.
OOOOOh. Yeah. Ohhhhh.
Yeah. I’m a little disappointed
in all of you, frankly.
Yeah, yeah. How’s that feel?”
To you people that do not have
children, listen up,
cool Uncle Titus is gonna
help you out right now.
Between 1 and 18,
a child’s gonna cost you roughly $300,000.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Do you know what you
can get for $300,000?
A Lamborghini.
Do you know what you can
get with a Lamborghini?
Anything you want.
Are you kidding me, man?
You got a Lamborghini, park in front of
any restaurant or store in this town,
“Park it right here, sir. We’re
gonnawipe it down while you’re inside.
Get that man a glass of champagne,
for he haaasss aaaaaaa LAMBORGHINI!!”
Pull up to a job interview
in a Lamborghini. Vvvrrroom.
“You’re obviously
management potential.
Please go talk to the boss,
we’re gonna give you the corner office
because you have
aaaaaaa LAMBORGHINI!"
Gentlemen, you’re driving a
Lamborghini, who's sitting next to you?
Way-out-of-your-league-chick,
that’s who’s sitting next to you.
Smokin’ body, she got
money, she got class,
she doesn’t like you,
but you have aaaaaaaaa LAMBORGHINI!!!
And you’re living the
Lamborghini life, man.
VVvvvvrrrooomVVrrrrmmmmVvvvvrrrr.
Doing what you
want, when you want.
Stayin’ up all night and getting’ up
early because you’re not tired at all.
That’s right. Because you know
what a Lamborghini doesn’t have?
A FUCKING CAR SEAT.
THAT’S WHAT IT DOESN’T HAVE.
Drivin’ through town just…
VVvvvvrrrrrooomVVvvrrrrVrrrVrrrr.
Driving past parents in
mini-vans with bald tired because
“Connor needs braces”
and they’re watching you drive by
like starving African children.
Flies buzzing around their head…
because WHAT IS THAT SMELL?
Because you’re out there
living the Lamborghini life.
Doing crazy stuff. Taking vacations
that actually feel like vacations.
Ahhhh, you’re staying in
the top floor of the resort,
in the kids-not-allowed suite – I’ve
been there once, it was INCREDIBLE.
Out on the balcony with the one.
$60 bottle of pinot noir
“This is an amazing life,
I love you, you love me.”
And then 18 rooms down the hotel…
Waaaaay in the distance you hear
“GOD DAMMIT BRIAN,
STOP JUMPING ON THE BED!!!
WHO SAID YOU COULD
OPEN THE MINI BAR?
$32 CASHEWS?!
YOU KIDS ARE KILLING ME!”
“That is never gonna be us.”
“Let’s go in that room and
have some Lamborghini sex –
AAAAUUUUGGGhhhh
And you go in that room and
you take off your clothes and
you still look good 'cause you don’t
have the stress-fat that kids give ya,
and you leave the door open because
NOBODY’S GONNA WALK IN ON YA.
And you get out the ropes and
the chains and the lava lamp and
YOU’RE DOIN’ IT LIKE YOU WANNA DO
IT, YEAH. YEAH.
Ride this more than 8 seconds!
WOOOOO!
YES!
Yes! Makin’ noises
from Cro-Magnon times –
HERRRAAAAUAUUUGHHH!
BUT…
you drank too much and forgot
to be careful that night.
Now the Lamborghini’s
on Craigslist.
And you’ve burned through that
Lamborghini money like THAT, you know why?
Because the kid has allergies and needs meds,
and a tutor, cuz he’s missed so much school,
and you can’t have a damn
PEANUT in your house ever again.
Yeaaaah. And now that amazing relationship you
had where you guys did EVERYTHING together,
now, you’re still doing that, but now it’s
getting’ fat and losin’ your hair “WEEEEEEEEEE!”
And you’re going to sleep
before the nightclub opens.
And your friends that don’t have
kids won’t come over anymore.
“You guys wanna come
over for dinner?”
“UH. NO. We…
hafta… go to… Canada.”
And you gotta take a job
you hate down at the Mill
cuz you’re living in a
Bruce Springsteen song now.
And not the first verse,
the third verse, where it gets weird.
And every morning,
you leave at 4 a.m.
you leave for work with
your tiny little lunch box,
but you always glance back at the electric
guitar you bought right before she got pregnant.
Behind that, fading into the wallpaper with
the rest of your crushed hopes and dreams.
And now… you gotta start
hanging out with other parents.
Ahhhhhhh.
The most unreasonable
group of delusional humps
I have ever met in my life.
Some of you are in here tonight. That’s why
that joke got a little bit of subdued laugh.
“I’m not delusional.”
Yeah, you are, holy shit.
And you’re out there with
them, you know.
They’ve also balled up
their hopes and dreams.
Instead of tossing them away like you
did, they took their hopes and dreams
and started RAMMIN’ THEM DOWN
THEIR KIDS’ THROATS, YEAH.
“You’re going to soccer camp
three times a year because
DADDY DIDN’T GET
TO PLAY IN COLLEGE!
Ha Ha Ha Ha.”
And you’re out there with ‘em.
You know,
your kids on the team too,
and you LOOOOOVE gettin’ up at 7 a.m.
on a Saturday WEEEEEEE!
And I’m just out there – “God,
please… I hope somebody breaks a tibia.”
I don’t even care if it’s my kid because then
we won’t have to come back next Saturday.
And while you’re standing there,
praying for it to be over, that one dude
“You see my little Brian out there?
He’s amazing, you see my Brian?
He’s badass… BADASSSSS!!
Kids’ gonna be in
the world cup.”
“The kid that just ran full-speed
into the goal post? That kid?”
“Yeah, he always gives 110
percent – 110 PERCEEEEENNNT!!”
“Hey, did you guys see my little Stanley?
He’s a badass, gonna play in the NFL.”
“Hahahaha.
Stanley weighs like 17 pounds.”
“Hey hey hey hey,
Stanley’s life coach said –
don’t talk about
Stanley’s weight.”
“Oh my God, did you see my
little Tanya’s test scores?
She is amazing.
Oh my God, Tanya, oh my God.
That little girl is
gonna work for NASA.”
“Nobody’s gonna tell her?
Uh… N-No,
she’s not gonna work for NASA.
We’ve all known Tanya for
about four years now and, and,
we’re pretty sure… Tanya’s gonna
leave a baby in a dumpster.
Cuz you guys have dressed her like
a tiny hooker since she was two.
And my kids can’t stop watching her
because he’s obviously a FOLLOWER.
PAY ATTENTION TO THE
GAME, IDIOT!”
And you do your best, parents. Everyone,
every parent in this room is doing their best.
And if you get ‘em to 18, yes!
You get to kick ‘em out!
And you never have
to see ‘em again!
Hahahaha.
Hahahahaaahahahahahaa.
I’m sorry,
I couldn’t stop laughing.
Yeah, they go away
for a little while.
But then at 19 and a half you get a phone
call from the local police department.
“Mr. Titus,
we’ve arrested your son…
and his girlfriend Tanya…
for drug trafficking.”
“WHAT?” You go to the jail –
“Drug trafficking?
What the Hell were you doing, idiot?”
“UH, me and Tanya went to Mexico,
and she met this guy with a backpack
and .”
And I’m at the front desk filling
out paperwork, bailing him out,
the cop goes “We know
your son’s an idiot.
He didn’t do anything wrong. He helped
us catch the drug dealer, though,
we caught the drug dealer cuz of h-
yeah, we impounded his car,
you should check it out.” And
you glance at an impound and
THERE’S YOUR LAMBORGHINI
FROM TWENTY YEARS AGO.
And the cop goes “That thing’s
like 20 years old, it’s a classic,
it’s worth like 1.2
million dollars now.”
"Um...
where do you guys
keep the extra guns?
And can I talk to my
kid one more time?
Cuz I love him so much.”
Now, granted,
that’s worse-case-scenario. BUT,
I have two, I have two children.
I stopped at two children,
because my ex-wife’s
vagina was busy elsewhere.
It had a guest list and I wasn’t on it.
There ya go.
You can ‘Ooh’ that joke all you want but
I could say a lot meaner s tuff than that.
Instead I chose to use
the King’s English.
“HER VAGINA WAS BUSY ELSEWHERE.
HER WIZARD SLEEVE WAS FILLED WITH
THE WANDS OF OTHER SORCERERS.”
When I call someone a cheating
bitch, I do it classy!
Be careful who you marry, people.
Make good choices.
When you get married,
make REALLY REALLY good choices.
You know. You know something
else weird about that?
I found out she was cheating on me.
I found out on a Friday.
I was in court by Tuesday.
Because I’m a knee-jerk person.
I just, I filed for divorce instantly.
I just react. Cuz my dad had a
good jab and you had to move.
And I went to court that Tuesday. It was
like, literally four or five days later
“I WANT A DIVORCE!” Cuz my
– the switch got flipped.
You know in a relationship,
switch flip, “I want a divorce!”
And this woman stood
up, IN COURT, and said
“Your honor, this man’s been
beating me for twenty years
and beating the children
since the day they were born.”
Now,
let’s deal with the first one.
If YOUUUUU let me BEAT YOU
for TWENTY YEARS,
THAT’S not abuse.
That’s a fetish.
But then she lied again and
said I beat my children.
So I spent every dime I ever
made on my fine television show
and I spent every dime I’ve
made in comedy for six years,
and I PROVED after six years
that it NEVER happened.
But, to this day, like 9 years
later, she’ll be like
“Can I have the kids an extra day,
I’ll bring them home on time.”
I’m like “No you won’t,
you cheating liar.” And she always goes
“Oh my God,
are you still talking about THAT?
That is in the past,
when are you gonna let that go?”
My answer always is
“When the Jews let it go.”
It’s gonna be a minute.
Be careful who you
marry, be careful!
Be careful!
Pick well, pick well!
Don’t get married FAST.
People get married so fast, too.
“Oh, we knew each other 18 months,
we got married, it’s gonna be great.”
“Did you really risk THAT MUCH? Did you go to
Vegas, put everything on Red, too? Did you?
Wow. Did you fly Southwest to Vegas
and just REALLY risk it all, did ya?
When you landed, did you eat at Chipotle burrito?
Just fucking go for it, if you’re gonna live…”
You can’t know somebody after 2 years!
In two years?
You can’t know anybody
after two years.
You know why? Your brain for the
first 2 years of a relationship,
is producing a chemical that’s like
heroine. That’s why you feel like that.
Look at your behavior when you first
meet somebody and fall in love.
What do you do? You go out and you
get cheeseburgers. You come back,
you have sex for 4 hours,
then you go out and get frozen yogurt.
Then you go back and have sex for 4
hours, then you call into work
while you’re still
inside somebody,
then you go out and
have cheeseburgers again
– THAT’S CRACKHEAD BEHAVIOR
– THAT’S WHAT THAT IS.
But nobody tells you that.
No one tells you –
“Oh, it’s gonna be
great, you know.”
Cuz once you’re married, that heroine
feeling doesn’t last all day anymore.
At most – AT MOST – you
get 15 minutes a day.
And you spend 23 hours and 45
minutes trying to get the next fix.
Why do you think
flower shops exist?
It’s expensive dead plants.
“Here you go,
baby.” “Oh my God.” “YEEEAAAAAAH.”
Gentlemen – every woman in this room knows
that fishnet stockings keep nobody warm.
“YEAH THEY DO.”
It takes eight years
to know somebody.
And I know a lot of us are thinking – “Wow,
I can’t hold the crazy back that long.”
But you have to – you have to.
Because two-year-relationship-you,
is not eight-year-relationship-you
Two-year-relationship-you is…
gentlemen, you’re in the car with her – two-year-relationship-you,
get cut off by a psychopath, what do you do?
“Oh my God,
look at this silly son of a bitch.
How goofy is that, right? Wow. Let’s
go to Dairy Queen and get a blizzard.”
Eight-year-relationship-you,
same guy cuts you off,"
“MOTHERFUCK—GET ME MY
SHOTGUN, RIGHT NOW!!”
CHHHH-CHHHH.
“Oh my God.”
“What are you doing?!”
“Texting my mom
about the wedding.
No, we’re still gonna get married, I’m
just gonna go with a Kevlar theme, now.”
Ladies, what are you laughing about?
Two-year-relationship-you?
We LOOOOOOOVE two-year-
relationship-you.
Two-year-relationship-you
is amazing.
“You going to Vegas with your buddies?
Well, just go have a good time.
Don’t even take your phone – what
happens in Vegas, stays in Vegas,
I don’t care…
Go, just go!”
“I love you,
you love meee yaaa.”
Eight-year-relationship-you –
“Where WERE you?”
“You sent me to Rite Aid.”
“27 minutes ago.
And I said the ones
without wings…”
Pick well, man, pick well.
You know it’s funny, your parents want,
everyone wants you to get married.
Everybody wants you to get married.
That’s why people rush into it –
because you were pushing ‘em.
“Oh my God, are you going to make
my daughter and honest woman?”
“No, I prefer the untrustworthy
whore I have now, thank you.”
“You’re gonna make
my son a real man?”
“Why? You worried about
the yoga pants too?”
If a mother SEES you
getting along with somebody
“Oh my God, you guys are so cute! They’re
gonna get married! Take the journey…
OH MY GOD TAKE THE JOURNEEEEY!”
They never say “It’s
a fun journey…”
And like all journeys you
should strap your ass in.
Because if marriage is a journey,
divorce is a plane crash.
And if you have kids,
it lasts 'til they’re 18 years old.
To you people in here tonight that
got divorced, but never had kids.
I want you to know something
– you didn’t get divorced.
You had a long-term booty-call with
paperwork, that’s all that was.
Yeah, that’s all it was. Sorry.
Was it hard on ya? To split up the CD’s?
Was that a bitch for you? Was it?
“Oh my God, who’s going to get the Matrix
boxset? We need to hire an arbitrator.”
It is NOT a real divorce until
you shred the chi of an innocent.
“Mommy said my chi used to be
aqua, but daddy made it charcoal.
He lives with my first
grade teacher now.”
That’s a divorce right there.
Ha Ha Ha Ha.
I’ve gotten to a very
sick place with comedy.
I’ve done this so long now – this is my
seventh special – I want you to know something.
So, I WANT you guys to laugh.
And I’m used to that – I’ve
been doing that a long time.
Now I’ve got to
this weird place,
like a guy who’s had way to much
sex where I need it a little weird,
so I write a joke
where, when you guys go
“Ha ha ha… Aaaahhh… Oooooh."
Hhhrrr.
It’s not good – it’s not good.
I have a problem, it’s not good.
Cuz a lot of people do
that to a lot of people…
like a lot of people like, ahh,
“Oh my God, I don’t like you,
we got married too fast, let’s have a kid
so we can slowly destroy
the soul of a child.”
You think a child is going
to fix your relationship?
You’re just strip mining three souls
now, good job, man.
Cuz, by the way, when you have
kids, that heroine thing, like
“Did you cut this with children?
I don’t feel anything at all.
I’m tired,
but that’s all I got."
Cuz once you have a
kid, that is for real.
People don’t understand that. People pop
out a kid thinking it’s gonna be fine...
Oh my God. No, man.
If you have a kid, that’s for real.
Once you have a child,
here’s the deal.
You now OWN a human being.
Look at it.
And it does THAT A LOT.
You have now basically created
a totalitarian government
in your own home and that
little fucker is Stalin
It wants what it wants.
It wants it NOW.
And you better be movin’.
And then what it does
is also your fault.
And there’s no receipt,
you can’t take it back.
And you have one job
as a parent – ONE JOB –
don’t raise
douchebags, that’s it.
That’s it. That’s all there is.
You don’t raise douchebags.
If at the end of
18 years your kid
can cook a meal, pay a bill and wipe
his own ass, GOD BLESS YOU, PEOPLE.
That’s all you need.
Can’t do anything anyway.
I’m watching my daughter…
I can’t tell my daughter “You’re
gonna do this… You’re gonna…”
She’s going off on her own,
she’s gonna do what she’s gonna do.
Don’t raise douchebags,
because you don’t want to be the parent
that gets interviewed
after the verdict.
“Yeah, I don’t know,
I just thought he liked trench coats. Uh.
No, I read his journals,
I thought they were song lyrics.”
Don’t raise douchebags – so you
don’t know how hard it is – again,
cool Uncle Titus is gonna help you
people that don’t have kids yet –
from the second they’re born,
the second they’re born –
all you’re doing – from
is downloading life programs
into tiny retarded people.
They’re not on the same
operating system you’re on…
their download speed sucks ass…
and there’s a ton
of error messages.
From the second,
the SECOND they’re born –
go to sleep when we tell ya,
take the nipple when you’re supposed to,
coffee tables hurt when you
run into them full speed.
Stitches hurt going
in AND coming out.
Then they get older – do your homework.
Error. Do your homework. Error.
Quit lying. Error. Error.
Error. Error. Error.
Wipe your ass! WIPE YOUR ASS!
WIPE YOUR ASS!!!
Yeah, and that wipe your
ass download as a parent,
as a man you’re gonna be getting
upgrades on that one your whole life.
As a MAN, your last wipe your ass upgrade
will be given to you by your NEW WIFE
while you’re standing
in the laundry room
I like that joke cuz it
humiliates everybody.
You see a couple just…
And that’s all you’re doing,
just downloading programs,
constantly,
constantly, constantly.
And the only thing I really enjoyed about having
kids, I really enjoyed for the first 10 years
was, for the first 10 years,
I was the smartest person they knew,
and that’s never happened
in my whole life.
Like, I had an answer,
I knew everything they wanted.
Two little beings had to
ask me – I had an answer.
Even if I was wrong,
they had to believe me
because I control the
food and the shelter.
“You don’t think I’m right? How ‘bout
you go stand outside and figure it out?
How ‘bout that?
Leave the jacket,
I paid for that.”
For 10 years I knew everything!
I was a genius!
I also got to run them.
If I had a bad day, I could
“Do what I tell you to do because
I’m your father, blah blah blah.”
I had to run them,
I was the dictator of the house.
I got to be the
Hitler of my own home.
And I gotta be honest –
sometimes kinda fun to be Hitler!
Only me and Hitler
have ever said that.
But you were – you get to be,
as dads, you get to be Hitler.
“Clean your room!
Go to bed when I tell you!
Empty the dishwasher!
Invade Poland!
Let’s Do This!”
And if they’re really bad – you
get to lock them in their room
like Hitler did
for a little while.
“You vill stay in zere.
Und you vill give me ze
information I am requesting.
Und you vill stop LYING.
Und if you do zat,
und tell me ze truth…
maybe UND ONLY MAYBE…
you can have a fucking cookie.”
Yeah. Pretty scary voice coming
out of this mug, isn’t it?
“He does that really well.”
And then they get older,
that’s the problem.
When they get older, they start asking
you for upgrades that you don’t have.
And that’s what I didn’t like at all.
10, 11, 12, 13…
my son started about 10, we’re
driving home one day and he just goes
“Hey dad, how do rockets work?”
“You know I’m going to San Diego
to tell jokes about you, right?
That’s what I do.
I’m not taking a rocket.
Google it.
It has two K’s that’s all I know.”
Shut up.
I know it doesn’t have to K’s…
And my daughter tooootally
screwed me up bad.
Man, just when I stopped letting
them ask me questions anymore,
I was like “We’re done talking.”
We were home one night,
she was 13 at the time, it was last year,
and we were watching –
the TV was on and uh,
and I have a podcast and we
talk about the world a lot
and so I watch a lot of news and I want
to see what’s going on in the world.
And we’re watching it and
we’re sitting there and uh,
the Ferguson thing was
on, you know…
oh, sorry, no, sorry, it was the Baltimore
thing, the Baltimore thing was on.
Wait – so… no…
it was the North Carolina
thing where that guy got
– no… sorry, sorry,
it was the New Jersey
thing where they… No?
Sorry,
it was the Florida – wait.
No, it was the Louisiana… no,
that was this week. Uhhhm.
All I remember is some black people were getting
soul-raped by bullets – that’s all I remember.
Yeah – this bit’s going
to be uncomfortable.
And I’m making ‘em watch the news,
I’m just making them watch it, you know.
And they wanna watch Spongebob
because they’re so civic-minded.
I’m like going “Shut up, we’re watching
this. Stop it, we’re watching this.”
Cuz I believe you need scars to
survive this world, you know?
You parents that are
raising shiny kids
“Oh my God we block his internet if it has
the word ‘sex’ in it he can’t access it…
even if it’s got an s we don’t
let him get to that, Ugh.
He’s got two channels: he’s
got PBS and PBS Latino.
UNO DOS TRES! Ohhhh,
he loves Burt and Ernesto.”
So, yeah.
And by the way, those kids?
Those kids you’re raising?
They’re gonna be shiny.
They’re gonna be great kids.
High self-esteem,
not afraid of anything,
prolly get scholarships to
Ivy League Universities.
And then at 18 you’re going to
send them off into the world –
and they’re gonna get hit by a
bus because you didn’t teach them
THE WORLD IS DANGEROUS.
You need scars! You need scars!
Scare ‘em, a little bit!
My dad did not have a
child-worship thing AT ALL.
I went where he went and I
better shut the Hell up about it.
When I was six years old,
he took me with his date
to a drive-in movie theater to see
a Clint Eastwood Dirty Harry movie
called Magnum Force.
YEAH.
I was wearing FEETIE PAJAMAS!
And in the first three minutes of
this movie, a dude in a cop uniform,
a guy I’ve been taught
to trust my whole life,
kicks in a door and
shoots two people
having naked bushy 70’s sex…
the dude falls off the bed.
The woman turns - full-boob-shot.
I went through puberty at SIX!!
Then, he shoots her in the boob.
So now I gotta buy weird
magazines the rest of my life.
THEN, then she falls out a window
and bleeds out into a pool.
I went into that movie six years
old, I came out SMOKING.
“Yeah, that was a nice piece of
cinema, daddy. I enjoyed that a lot.
I do have to say, that although Clint
Eastwood’s anti-hero is violent,
it’s just a
reflection of society.
Now I’d like to go home and burn my
Dr. Seuss books because there is no God.”
I’m gonna be seven in a couple
months, I was done with whimsy anyway.
Not the worse one.
My mom was mentally ill, in and out
of mental institutions my whole life.
So between the ages of when I was
8 and 12 she was out for a while.
At 9 years old, we go to the drive-in
movie theater, just me and my mom,
and we see a movie called One
Flew Over the Cuckoo’s Nest.
Yeah… yeah. I think for mom it
was a research trip of some sort.
And I’m just a kid watching a movie.
I’m just sitting there watching the movie
and it’s the scene where
Nicholson’s getting shock treatment
– and I look over –
my mom is sobbing.
And I go “Mom,
what’s the matter?” And she goes
“That’s what they did to me.”
“Did you get to meet
Jack Nicholson?”
So we’re watching
the Ferguson thing
and it’s going off, man,
it’s just going off and eh
people are screaming and
burn - buildings are burning,
cops are shooting bullets at
people, it was crazy,
and then – we’re watching it.
And I FEEL like I’m doing
the right thing as a parent.
I feel like, you know what?
They’re seeing the world as it is, good.
They need to see it so they know
what the world’s like. Alright, good.
And I’m just sittin’ there, not thinking
anything, and my daughter looks up and goes
“Dad?
Why are black people so angry?”
“What channel is Spongebob on?”
Cuz it should be illegal
to ask me that question!
Do you see what color that is?
You can only find that
at a napkin factory.
I wanted to turn
to my kids and go
“Guys, we can’t talk about
this, we’re almost clear.”
But I don’t want to be that
parent, man.
I don’t want to pull the ripcord.
So many parents just pull the ripcord.
You know – it's
like-especially now
“Oh, mommy’s going to take a Xanax, you guys
go play video games, we can’t talk about this…”
Or that other show,
man… Beyond Scared Straight.
What a crap-show that is. You know
what pissed me off about that show?
Every parent is the
victim in that show.
“Justin was going to school and
he wasn’t doing what he said,
and he was getting F’s and D’s and he was
selling drugs and he was beating up people,
and he was just horrible,
so I think the best course of action
is to send him to a
maximum security prison so
rapists and murderers can teach him
because I suck that bad as a parent.”
Listen, if your kid ended up
on Beyond Scared Straight–
you fucked up.
And you have no excuse because
there are sporting goods stores
ALLLL over the place and
they’re full of baseball bats.
As my dad said,
“Sometimes respect comes from Louisville.”
That joke’s gonna be in court
with my ex-wife, trust me.
So I don’t know what to
say, man.
I’m like - and I don’t want to be
that parent. I want to do my best,
so she asked me, and she’s looking at
me, and the riots going on…
and I’m just like, I like, I,
uhm, I’m gonna Chuck Yeager this,
“Alright honey, alright –
why are black people angry? Well, let me
tell you – black people are angry because…
bla... bla... black people
– black – black people.
They’re An-An—Angry.
Because of people like your father,
let’s just be honest, because…
because this exact face has been the face
of the white devil for 500 years now.
I guarantee you, honey, you could
open a history book and find this face
on a Sepia-toned garret-type
of a guy standing in front of a
cotton field being photobombed by
three guys hanging from an oak
tree, I’m pretty sure.”
Yeah, yeah… read a history
book, it sucks.
But then… and then she
asked me about slavery.
But she doesn’t ask about the history
of slavery, I got that… she goes
“Dad, can you explain to
me the concept of slavery?”
Like, Spongebob is one channel
away, right there, one button.
I mean, ask me something that’s easy to
talk about that’s not gonna freak me out
– butt sex, I’ll tell you about that if
you all go – something horrible, really?
“Alright, the concept of slavery.
Ok, oh God,
ahh K, here’s the CONCEPT
of slavery… Uhhhhh, huh…
This person who’s black, because
their skin has too much melanin in it…
and this person who’s white, who if they go
outside for 40 minutes turns into a pot-pie…
that’s the difference…
and because of that,
this person gets
to OWN this person.
And THIS person has to do
everything this person says,
because if they don’t,
the job benefits include
whipping,
raping and selling off your family,
which is the worst High
School job fair ever.
I wouldn’t even fill
out that application.
Unless it was good health care.”
And I get—she’s just as
uncomfortable as you guys are –
and I get up and I go “And
Lincoln freed the slaves!”
And she goes “So it was
all cool after that.”
“Yeah, kinda like Israel
and Palestine is all cool.”
“What’s going on in
Israel and Palestine?”
“CAN WE JUST WATCH
SPONGEBOB, PLEASE?!”
And I realized –
and you do this as a parent
sometimes – you realize -
“Oh,
I’m digging a hole right now.”
I’ve driven it back a way, and I’m just
digging a hole of stupidity right now.
And I know if I keep talking I’m going to sitting
across from her Principal in a couple of weeks,
“Mr. Titus, did you have a long talk with
your daughter about black people and slavery?
Cuz there was a
riot on Thursday…
and your daughter organized it.”
“NO SHE DID NOT.
What side was she?
She wasn’t doing this, was she?”
“No, no… we have one of her
picket signs right here – it says
‘We’re all pink on the inside like Salmon’.
Did you tell her that?”
Eh… I pulled the rip cord
pretty much on that one, yeah.
So I did something creepy to my daughter
in the middle of this conversation
that my dad used to do
to me whenever I asked
my dad something that he didn’t
want to talk about, he would just go
“WHY THE HELL DO
YOU WANNA KNOW?”
And I was so scared
of my dad I would like
“I don’t. I’m good.
I don’t need to know anything, I’m fine.
I’m prolly gonna be a
standup comedian anyway,
I’m just gonna go over here,
learn to hit on waitresses and write some
fart jokes, that’s what I’m gonna do now.”
But I didn’t raise my daughter like
that, but I did it, I go
“Why do you wanna know?”
And she looked scared
of me and she goes “Oh,
I wanna understand the
black kid at my school.”
“THE black kid?
You have ONE black kid at
your little private school?”
She goes “Yeah, her name’s Sarah,
she’s in 6th grade, she’s pretty cool,
I wanna understand what
her people went through.”
“Uh, well, I can tell you
why black people are angry…
because we have ONE black kid
at your little private school.
Yeah,
that’s probably in the top 5.”
And I realize I’m not
getting out of this, man.
And I gotta do it. And sometimes
as a parent you just gotta dive in.
I was like “Alright, hon.
Alright, imagine this,
imagine living in your own country,
everybody’s the same.
And a bunch of boats show up,
and a bunch of people who are a,
photo negative of you, get out.”
I did my best.
“And you waive to them from the
shore, and they shoot a bunch of you.
And then they put you in a boat and take
you THOUSANDS of miles across the ocean.
And you weren’t riding
on the lead-oak deck.
There was no shuffleboard
on the Amistad.
Now you’re in another country you’ve
never been to for hundreds of years.
And you’re slaves for hundreds
and hundreds of years.
And then one day you were freed.
But you weren’t freed because people
had ‘insight’ to the human condition.
You weren’t freed
because someone said
‘My Land, Mary-Beth,
I woke up on the plantation this mornin’
and I-I just realized that one
man should not own another.
You-you tell Rastis and Jolene
to meet me in the kitchen,
I’m gonna write them a check and make
them some chocolate chip waffles!’
Sadly, honey, slavery did not
end with chocolate chip waffles.
In fact, some people
wanted their slaves SO BAD
they were willing to die for them, go
to war, almost split the country in two.
You know, and then once they were
freed, they never got paid.”
And my daughter just goes
“Wha— they NEVER got paid?”
I said, “No. They were promised
to get paid, but they never did.”
And my daughter, who was raised
in way too much privilege says,
“Well, why didn’t they hire a lawyer
and file a class action suit?”
Wow, one semester at Compton Junior
High would’ve taken care of all of this.
I said “They couldn’t file
with attorneys because
had to follow the slave
laws.” And my daughter goes,
“Dad, you said they were freed.
There was no slave laws.”
“I know, they had these things called
‘Slave Laws’ and then when they got freed,
they didn’t change the
laws, they changed the name,
to ‘Black Laws’”
– it’s like now,
when you say ‘WARMONGER’
– you mean Republican.
AND, when you say
‘DEMOCRAT’ you mean pussy.
See that?
See how I lost you all
and then got you all back?
And she says, she asks, she goes
“Well after those laws went away, it was
all, it was all, it was all cool, right?”
“Yeah, after those laws went away,
things got a lot better, you know?
I mean, except for the hard
stuff, like, you know…
drinking out of the
same water fountain, or…
riding in the front of a
bus, or…
using a toilet that a
white butt had touched, or…
eating at a restaurant
with all white people…
playing sports with
white people… marrying –
Oh my God it’s never gonna get
better, is it?”
And my daughter sees me
flailing, I got nowhere to go.
It’s not better.
As we saw, as what’s happening right now,
and, and I start to flail,
and my daughter saves my ass.
My kid, I love my
kids, she just goes
“But Martin Luther
King made it better!”
And I go “YESSSSS!!
YESS! YES!
MARTIN LUTHER KING!
HE DID MAKE IT BETTER!
HE WAS AN AMAZING LEADER!
And we marched together!
And we knew we were all the same, yes,
Martin Luther King was
incredible!” And she goes,
“What happened to
Martin Luther King?”
God Dammit.
"He was assassinated
by a white guy… uhhh…”
My little girl – who never
heard it like this – it’s weird.
We spent an hour and a half talking
and I – I pay for her school,
she should know ALL of this
but I guess the
school I sent her to –
all the textbooks
were written in Texas.
I mean, cuz all I can imagine
it says is 'slavery was bad.
Lincoln freed the slaves.
Good job, white guy!”
And she goes,
“Is that how it really went down?”
“Pretty much, babe.
The best I could tell ya.”
She goes, “Oh my God,
dad, that’s horrible.”
And my little girl,
starts to cry… she’s never
heard it like this before.
Yeah.
And I go, “It’s ok, honey.”
And she goes, “No,
it’s not ok, dad.
It’s not ok at all.
If that’s how black people…
were treated for 500 years…
that’s horrible.
That means that one day…
they’re gonna kill us!”
“Um, did they teach you what we did to the
Indians in your little private school, there?”
“NO! WHAT DID WE DO
TO THE INDIANS?!”
“We had Thanksgiving
dinner with them…
and then we cleaned up
the dishes together…
and then the Indians
dealt blackjack.”
And I pulled the ripcord
HARD, man.
Best Spongebob marathon I
have ever seen in my life!
Told you it was gonna
get uncomfortable.
I didn’t write this show to make
fun of your kids or my kids,
I wrote this show to
make fun of all of us.
Because everybody in this
room, right now,
was one of these little
douchebags I’m talking about.
At one point you were,
so I’m gonna give you a gift tonight,
that I can’t use anymore because
both my parents are gone.
But if your parents are still around
tomorrow morning, I want you to get up,
and I want you to call them.
And say “Hey mom, hey
dad, how you guys doing?
By the way,
did you need help with anything?”
Now, they’re gonna
say, “What’s wrong?
How much money do you need?”
That was really giving
up too much honesty, bro.
And I want you to say, “No, I’m good, actually I called
because I want to ask you something, mom and dad.
I want you to tell me the story of the worst,
stupidest thing I ever did when I was a kid.”
Or, you can tell them something
they don’t know that you did.
That’s what I thought.
And then you’re gonna let them
talk, and you’re gonna listen.
Because we stopped listening
to our parents at one point.
Listen to them. You know.
Cuz if I could, I would LOVE to listen
my parents, and I can’t anymore.
And listen to them. Let them tell the
story of the stupidest thing you did.
It’ll surprise you.
Cuz you’ll think something that
wasn’t that bad is HORRIBLE to them.
And, and if they’re laughing while
they’re telling you that story,
you get to laugh with them.
If they’re still pissed –
you shut up. No excuses.
And you let ‘em talk.
And then when they’re done I
want you to apologize to them.
Because no matter what
you think of your parents.
No matter how good or
bad they raised you.
If they didn’t send
you to college.
If they were abusive.
If they were alcoholics.
It doesn’t matter.
Because at the end of the
day, your parents
gave you the greatest gift.
They gave you LIIIIFE.
And you – RUINED theirs.
RUINED it.
I know you don’t believe
that, but it’s fuckin’ true.
They had dreams,
and then you were born,
and that’s all they had.
Dreams.
Well, thank you little bastard…
“WAAAA!”
I didn’t get it.
I didn’t get it until becoming a parent.
You know why?
If you’ve seen my comedy, in the past,
I have not been very
nice to my father.
I have said some horrible –
I have basically said
my father was abusive.
But I have now had kids…
and they’re both over 10
years old… and I realized…
my father wasn’t abusive…
he was trying not to murder me.
If you’re abusive,
you’re kicking someone down the stairs,
you’re punchin’ ‘em,
you’re burning them with a cigarette.
My dad didn’t do that.
Even when I did something stupid,
he would just come
over to me and just go,
“AHHHH!! MOTHER-OH MY GOD
- YOU MOTHERFUCKER-AHHHHHHH,
GOD, AHHHHHHHH,
MOTHER…!!”
I used to think my dad
was angry cuz he drank.
NO. He drank cuz he was angry.
He swore to the day he died,
that when I was 22 years
old I tried to kill him.
Used to tell everybody,
used to tell everybody.
I was successful,
I had a TV Show,
“Mr. Titus, your son’s really doing
well, he’s got his own television show,
he’s done a bunch of comedy
specials, you gotta be really proud.”
“Yeah, would be proud, but dumb-ass
tried to kill me when he was 22.”
“Thanks dad, that’s the network
president, that’s not helpful.”
What happened was, well,
when I was 17 and a half,
my dad and I used to get in fistfights.
We would brawl, it was bad.
And I got my ass handed to
me pretty much all the time.
So, at 17 and a half,
I had moved out, I said,
“I’m moving to San Francisco,
I’m going to become a stand-up comedian,
and I’m going to be
the best comedian ever,
and I’m gonna stuff it up your
ass, old man!”
And I moved to San Francisco,
and I worked for 18 months,
4 shows a night, wrote ‘til 4 a.m.
in the morning.
Yeah, and after 18 months.
HA HA!
I had to move back
to my dad’s house…
cuz it hadn’t gone
how I had thought.
And I went to my plan B, which was
working at Kentucky Fried Chicken.
And if the humidity’s right,
you can still smell it on me.
And I was a closer. And I’d drive
home every night in my little P.O.S.
and I’d drive it home and,
and after about 2 months,
this guy had parked his ’56 Chevy
on his lawn on my route home,
and it said ‘For Sale $1,800’
I stopped the car every night, and I would
just stand across the street, staring at it
And I fell in love with
the car – I had to have it.
It was a mistake.
It was that first guy, love,
car thing and I just – I had to have it.
So I saved up for 3 months,
and I get enough money, and I said,
“Dad,
I’m gonna go buy this car.”
And he said “The Hell you are.”
And I said “I’m over 18 now,
you can suck it, old man.”
With respect, because he controlled
the food and the shelter, though.
And my dad said something he
never said to me before, he said,
“Let me go with you,
I’ve made more mistakes
in my life than you have,
let me help you buy the car
so you don’t get ripped off.”
And I was 18,
and my first thought
was “WOOOAAHHHH.
I’m so suspicious.”
But I had to admit it – my
dad was a great salesman.
He was a GREAT salesman.
He got married 6 times,
he was a GREAAAT salesman.
GREAT salesman.
I still don’t know how
he got number 6 to go
“I’m a unicorn!”
So we go to this guys’ house,
we go to this guys’ house
and, you know the car,
and I’m just all amped
up cuz I got my dad,
and I’m feelin’ cocky, and I go,
“How you doing? We came to look at the car.
Brought my dad.
He knows karate.”
And my dad just goes,
“Shut up, idiot!
I’m not letting you sell
my son this piece of crap.
Dad, are we gonna beat him and take it?
What are we doing?”
“Shut up! And he starts
walking around the car.
He just starts tearing it apart.
“Bumpers are twisted,
rims don’t match,
oh my god, the upholstery by
a blind Mexican in Tiajuana?”
“Dad, is this a technique?
Why are we making fun of handicapped
Hispanic people now, what are we doing?”
“I told you to shut up!...
I’ll give you a thousand bucks for the
car, that’s it, take it or leave it.”
And I’m just waiting
for this guy –
he’s being so aggressive –
just, I want this guy to,
please punch my dad in throat.
Go ahead.
And instead,
the guy just goes “Hold on.”
And he walks in his house.
What we heard next,
for the next two minutes
was like a radio cartoon.
And the guy walks
in and we just hear,
“Hey,
herraahherrraadaaahowwwyaa.”
Then a pan bangs on
the front window.
And I’m 18,
so the look on my face…
my dad, “This is how it goes…”
And he downloaded
another program.
And the guy walks back out,
and when the guy hit the door, it looked like
someone had injected him with three decades.
“Ok, I’ll take a thousand.”
And I thought, “I LOVE MY DAD!”
And I remember it clearly because
it was the first time I thought it.
And we were driving home,
and he was right, the car was horrible.
But I’m like, I can’t believe you got
me this car! I can’t believe it, dad!
You saved me 800 bucks!
“I saved you 600 bucks.”
“No, dad,
1,800 minus a thousand is 800.”
“I’m keeping 200 bucks
for negotiating the deal.”
And he downloaded
yet another program.
And he was right about this
car, he was so right about it.
It was horrible. The car, the steering
wheel was vaguely connected to something.
You’d spin it and it was like
the car had broken a hip,
it would just go – ehhhhhhh-
but if you hit the brakes,
it made a HARD left,
because…
because the left front brake
was the only one that operated.
Remember that first car you had, guys?
That horrible one, man?
But you bought a fire extinguisher, mounted
inside cuz it looked so high-performance,
but also because you really
needed a fire extinguisher.
Cuz you’d done some
wiring by yourself,
and now when you hit the blinker,
the windshield wipers stared up and,
you left it like that so you didn’t
screw something else up. You’re like,
“No, it works, watch. I’m going that way,
I’m going that way, I’m going that way.”
Yeah.
Spent all that money on that
stereo, that really nice stereo,
but you couldn’t figure
out how to mount it,
so it just sat on the
passenger seat for 3 months.
Wires snaking out of the dash.
You ran out of electrical tape, so you
used clear tape – which was a bonus,
cuz now on Friday night when you’re
hanging out with your buddies,
you could roll joints to the
sparks coming off the dash.
My dad had a client that gave
me this big spool of red wire…
I rewired the ENTIRE car
with one color of wire.
SHUT UP GUYS WHO KNOW
WHAT I’M TALKING ABOUT.
I knew it. It was perfect.
Power, ground, power, ground.
PERFECT.
Then, when I turned the key
on, it went
And… thank God I had
a fire extinguisher.
So I spend 4 years
working on this car.
And I’ve changed –
I fixed everything.
Because I broke everything in the
car, I ruined it.
From the rear-end to the
train, everything.
I had to fix everything. The suspension.
I broke everything in this car.
But after 22 it was
badass… lowered down…
motor, brand new motor,
new tranny, it was great.
Burned tire, it was like 360,
460 horsepower, it was badass.
But the dumbest
car for a comedian
because I gotta drive to these
one-nighters all over California,
and every dime is going to gas.
Cuz the carburetor was a toilet
bowl, basically.
And I was in Northern
California where we lived
and I had to get down here to
LA to do a gig, one-nighter.
And I had just
enough money for gas.
And the car, the ballast
resistor in the car had gone bad.
The ballast resistor basically,
it’s the thing that takes the
battery voltage and lowers it,
so it goes into the distributor
and doesn’t burn... the point –
CAR NO WORK GOOD NO MORE.
And I couldn’t afford the part.
I wouldn’t have made the gas
money, and my dad’s boat,
it was January, my dad’s boat was
parked on the side of his house,
as I learned earlier in life –
it aint stealin’ if
they ‘aint usin’ it!”
Be careful what you download.
So, I took the ballast resistor to put
on the car, VROOM, made it to LA, woo!
And I don’t think about it
again, for 6 months.
And then it was brought
to my attention.
It’s now June… my dad, uh,
had gotten rid of stepmom number 5,
was looking for number
6, uh, playing the field,
and he was gonna take
her out in this boat.
And he backed his boat out and he
washed it up and it wouldn’t start.
So he took the gas out,
put fresh gas in and it wouldn’t start.
Now, it’s a hot, California day.
He’s got a twelve pack of
beer that he’s drinkin’
– or, snack pack of beer
that he’s drinkin’.
And he’s just working in the hot sun
and he’s getting angrier and angrier,
and he takes the spark plugs
out, won’t fix it,
he takes the distributor out,
checks all the wiring out,
get on the top, can’t fix
it, changes the coil,
he’s going back and
forth to the part store,
this goes on for four
and a half hours,
and finally he gets pissed and he
starts tracing the wiring harness
and he finds two wires
just hanging out in space.
And I know what he did,
he started spazz-mumbling
like I do.
“You son of a bitch.
He’s a grown man now,
I can’t believe he just went…
I’m gonna find a
drill and cordless,
I’m gonna put it through his skull.
And you know what?
It’s not child abuse now,
now it’s manslaughter, haha!
Yeah! I’ll run cell block D,
you kill your own kid,
you can run the prison, sir!”
And he got angrier and angrier
and angrier and angrier,
and my dad, uh,
didn’t do a whole lot of cardio.
And his heart went
Union and took a break.
He had a heart attack.
They called me and said,
“He had a heart attack”
I said “Oh my God,
he had a heart attack,”
“It’s a mild heart attack,” That’s
what they told me. I’m like,
“UH, shall I bring yogurt, then?
What’s a mild heart attack?”
And I was 200 miles
away in Fresno,
and just like tonight,
I was just doin' a show,
I get off stage, the club manager’s
got the phone out like this and he goes
“Take the phone,” I go
“What...” “TAKE THE PHONE.”
And I take it, it’s my fifth stepmother,
and this is how the conversation goes,
I go, “Hello?” She says,
“You killed your father!”
“I have been here
the whole night!
No...
I understand why I’m a
suspect, but I have witnesses.”
Then she says,
“Did you take something off his boat?”
“OOOOOOOHHHH.”
And I check how far Mexico is…
and I don’t have the gas money.
So…
I get up the next morning,
I drive to the hospital,
I walk into ICU, my dad is,
is hooked to machines, he’s grey.
It’s weird, man, he’s grey.
With fathers and sons, there’s a
weird thing like mothers and daughters
and I walked in and I’m
just looking at him,
and he’s grey and he’s hooked to
machines, and he looks weak and…
you gotta remember,
he’s my Hitler, you know?
And I go, “Dad, this is horrible,
oh my God, I can’t believe this.
What did this feel
like?” And he says this,
“Felt like somebody parked
a garbage truck on my chest,
I couldn’t feel anything.
I couldn’t move, it was horrible.”
I said, “Dad, you’ve been smoking
and drinking for 40 years, you know?
I mean, you start the
morning with pork rinds.
I think maybe it’s time…”
And before I out the next
word, he goes
“How’s your fuckin’
car running?”
THAT’S HOW ANGRY
CHILDREN WILL MAKE YOU.
HE WAS HOOKED TO MACHINES!!
HE WAS ABOUT TO GO INTO
THE LIGHT TO MEET JEEEESUS
and he went – HOLD ON, JESUS.
LET ME DEAL WITH DIPSHIT FIRST.
That’s how angry.
I don’t want this
show to scare anybody.
This show, uh,
I’ve had pregnant women
leave this show like,
“Thanks dickhead, that’s great.
Thank you.”
Don’t let this show scare you,
because if you do
your job as a parent,
keep downloading programs,
don’t raise douchebags,
you’ll be fine.
It takes a while.
I didn’t realize I was doing
ok until my daughter turned 13,
she graduated 8th grade,
and they had a ceremony,
because they all
get ceremonies now…
for everything. Oh my God,
she had a preschool ceremony,
a kindergarten ceremony,
a sixth grade ceremony, eighth grade…
because they’re all so special.
“Thomas, you’re going to be the
best roofer ever, yes you are!
You need a ceremony.”
That’s right, “Ethan, you’re going to put those
cones on the freeway like nobody’s business, Ethan,
yes you are!
Margie, you are going
to be the BEST strip-
Exotic dancer, ever there was!”
Yeah, yeah,
they’re all really special, ok.
She’s going to have, they have eighth grade
graduation ceremony, uh, so we’re gonna go.
Now,
I have to set this story up.
Everyone in this room has a psychotic
relative that lives too close to them.
The problem is you have to invite
them to Thanksgiving and Christmas,
because if you don’t, they may drive
by, notice they weren’t invited,
and then there’s
gonna be a drive-by.
In my family it’s my
Aunt, she’s 63,
she’s my mother’s sister,
my mom was crazy, used to hear voices,
and my aunt also hears voices,
but she calls them ‘her guides.’
And her guides
PREDICT THE FUTURE!
THAT HAS NEVER HAPPENED, EVER!
5 years ago, she said down at the
dinner table with us and said this,
we’re just eating
dinner, she goes,
“My guides told me I’m
gonna die in August.”
“Well, tick tock.”
She also doesn’t have a job,
“Cuz I aint payin’
Obama’s taxes!”
But she’s willing
to live off of ours.
I will say this, you know,
she’s also got some great skills.
I told her, I said, you’re a great
cook, go work at a bakery,
under the table for cash,
it’ll be phenomenal.
She goes, “I can’t,
if I stand too long, my back hurts.”
I said,
“I got a buddy who works at Hulu,
you could actually do like,
tech support in the morning.”
“Ah, if I sit too
long, my back hurts.”
“Well, that leaves, hooker.
And… at 63, you’re not really
a first-round draft pick.”
Now, don’t get me wrong,
I love her to death.
She’s my aunt, been asking to be in my
show for a long time...there you go.
Now, something else has
happened in my life.
I – uh, I got married again.
Uh, for the second time.
Because love is possible – you just
gotta get rid of your first wife.
Or, first husband,
depending on the sexual organ, either way.
So, I married… she’s amazing.
And my kids… I have ‘em 50/50…
so my ex has them half the
time, and then half the time,
me and my new wife,
WERE LIVIN’ THE LAMBORGHINI LIFE!
We were going to
concerts, and partying…
and going,
and have resorts… it was AMAZING.
And then her MOM got sick,
and moved in with us.
And – and that’s good too.
Her mom was also 63,
but her mom and my aunt
are different people.
Her mother’s got a
Masters degree in fine art
she’s an amazing artist. She was running
a department at an American University,
and she’s, she’s hardcore.
She’s pretty hardcore.
Her and I argue sometimes.
And, she’s always,
she’s always right.
I don’t mean, she thinks she’s always right,
I mean, I go look it up and fuck, she’s right.
It’s annoying.
It’s really annoying.
And her and my aunt…
don’t really… get along.
They don’t play Gin together.
It’s like… it’s imagine…
how I imagine Charlie Sheen and
Ghandi would get along. Like…
“WINNING!!” “NO,
YOU ARE NOT WINNING TODAY!”
So, her mom is sick,
and I call my aunt, and I go,
“Hey,” now we’re back to this story,
“Hey, would you do us a favor?”
Uh, my kids go to
a Christian School,
“Would you reserve us seats in the chapel
for the 8th grade graduation ceremony?"
My aunt says she
would, and uh, we go.
So, we show up at the ceremony.
My aunt has saved us seats
for my daughters’ graduation.
DIRECTLY
behind my ex-wife.
We don’t get along very well.
We hate each-others guts.
And she hates my new wife,
and my new wife LOVES that.
And then my wife’s mother and
my aunt have this weird thing.
If the church knew how much
EVIL was in that little area…
like, the Jesus on
the cross was like,
“Does anyone see what’s
going on over there?
Right there.
Oh my…
Why has thou forsaken
me, again?”
So we just sit down, and I’m just
grumbling, and they start the ceremony.
Here’s how the ceremony starts
for the 8th grade graduation.
Pastor gets up and goes,
“You know, tonight,
I want to talk about mothers.
Cuz mothers,
are the most amazing
thing in the world.
They give birth, they give life,
then through love and nurturing,
raise the amazing young adults behind me.
Without mothers, we have no Earth,
without mother, we have no species.
Now, in my head, I’m thinking,
“So, I guess fathers, what?
Fill the car with gas and wash it?
Is that our gig?”
But,
you can’t heckle in a church.
Only gotta tell me once...
So it continues like
that for a while,
“Mothers, mothers, mothers,
mothers, blah blah blah, mothers.”
And then they say,
“We would now,
like all the mothers
to please stand.”
Well, my new wife has raised my
daughter half the time for nine years.
So, she stood up.
And my ex-wife stood up
right in front of her
and I went – HMMMMMMM
and I can feel the
tumor starting.
And my aunt goes, “Oh my God,
it’s the mom and the evil stepmother.
It’s the mom and the evil stepmother.
It’s the mom and
the evil stepmother.
And her mother,
who’s on chemo goes,
“SAY IT ONE MORE TIME.”
I look up, Jesus is weeping.
They then said, “We now,
are gonna give each child a yellow
rose to walk out to their mother.”
Jesus got out a pry-bar.
“I’m not doin’ this, nope.”
And they start handing
roses to children,
and they’re going down the center
aisle, and he’s the scene.
Church music,
church lighting and mothers weeping.
It was beauuuutiful.
And then I realized, Oh,
that’s why they didn’t bring up fathers.
“Dad, here’s a yellow rose.”
“Shut up and sit down.
Tomorrow we’re getting
you some yoga pants…
fruit cup.”
So the kids are
walking the roses out…
And it just… it’s just mothers
weeping and it’s beautiful.
My daughter gets up to her turn.
And the pastor
holds up the rose,
and my daughter doesn’t take it.
And I thought, “Well,
let’s see where this goes…”
Now, while my ex and my new
wife are standing there,
I have a moment to
compare and contrast.
My new wife,
is 13 years younger than my ex-wife.
I think,
I think that’s a win in my column.
My ex-wife didn’t even go to college.
My new wife has two college degrees
doesn’t use ‘em and is
still paying for ‘em.
I think that’s a win
in my ex-wife’s column.
And they’re different, you know,
my new wife is uh, she’s very beautiful.
She’s very tall.
She’s smart, she’s funny,
she loves me more
than anybody ever has.
And she’s, tall,
she’s this tall.
And my ex-wife is…
Closer to Hell. Anyway.
That’s how I say
shorter, anyway.
So, we’re all just
watching my daughter
like, what’s gonna happen here,
and we see my daughter,
while the pastor’s holding the rose,
she just mouths,
“I have two moms.”
Yeah, California, you think they
would’ve thought about that.
“I need another rose.”
And the pastor kinda
shakes the rose angrily.
And the kids behind my
daugh-everything stopped.
The kids are like
And my daughter goes – my daughter
just stands her ground and goes,
“I haaave TWO MOMS.
I NEEEEED ANOTHER ROSE!”
And we hear the pastor go,
“We don’t have any EXTRAS.
TAKE IT.”
And there’s this beat, and then my
daughter looks him right in the eye,
snatches the rose, holds it up,
and RIPS IT IN HALF.
She walks down the center
steps, man.
And I KNOW what everybody
was thinking in the church,
“Oh well, there’s the Titus kid.
Wow. Wow.
Who had their money on
‘rips the rose in half?’”
And as my daughter is
walking down the aisle,
she’s snapping the stem. She takes
half the petals and rips ‘em off.
Takes the other
half, rips ‘em off.
She walks up and hands her
two moms this destroyed rose.
And hugged them.
And I thought - My God…
in an impossible situation,
in front of a live audience,
this kid had the
calm, the courage
and the love to make sure no
one got their feelings hurt.
OR, I have raised
the biggest a-hole…
who just wanted to make a point about
the shitty divorce we put her through.
Like, by the way… this
rose, it’s a metaphor.
It’s me. Snap. There you go!
You happy now?
I want you to know that everybody in this area
just bought future therapist a ski-boat, suck it!
Now,
I hope that’s not it.
But, I’d be ok with that too.
Now, that’s a great story.
Now, if you have a kid, and you think
my kid would never be that cool.
My kid will never have that
kind of insight or calm…
you’re wrong.
Just keep doing your job.
Because… this… that
was a girl that’s 13.
At 11, my daughter’s the same kid
that got the cops called on me.
I’m not sayn' they
didn’t need to be called,
I’m just sayin she
made it happen.
Now, I have my kids 50/50.
Which means my ex has them for a
week, and I have ‘em for a week.
So my ex has 7 days to poison their
minds, and make them HATE me…
and then I have 7 days…
to do absolutely
nothing, your honor.
But I will admit this… my
ex-wife and I are infants.
We are immature idiots.
We, we can’t get along at all.
We can’t even drop the kids
off at each-others’ houses.
The court has said
that we fight so bad,
that they only way
we get the kids
is go to McDonald’s and
have a hostage transfer.
It’s like getting your kids out
of North Korea every Monday.
I pull up on the South side of the
lot, she pulls up on the North side.
I stand in front of my car,
she puts the kids
in front of her car,
then I gotta hold up
the child support check.
She sends my son over, cuz she doesn’t
think he’s smart enough to escape.
I think he’s a
double-agent, frankly.
He walks back,
she checks the amount,
and the kids clasp hands
and slowly make their way,
across the Mickey DMZ.
So, I show up one
morning at ‘the drop’
and as I get out of the car, my daughter’s
already out of her mom’s car yelling at me.
She… and I get out and… I
go, “What?”
And she goes,
“I’m not going with you today, dad.
Mom’s been quiet all
week, and she said that,
if I leave,
she’s gonna go crazy,
and she doesn’t know,
so I can’t leave cuz she’s upset,
SO I’M NOT GOING WITH YOU!”
And, I learned something with
kids early on. Don’t yell at ‘em.
Can’t yell at ‘em.
If it worked I would do it ALLLL day long.
But it doesn’t. And if you yell too
much, eventually they get your frequency.
And all of ‘em, have this weird
internal Bose noise cancelling system.
And once they get your yell
frequency, it’s over.
To them, you just sound like
a Yamaha way in the distance.
“I TOLD YOU KIDS TO TURN THIS
TELEVISION OFF AND CLEAN YOUR
ROOMS AND... ANOTHER…
…”
I have stood in front of
my children and realized,
wow, they’re watching
television THROUGH me right now.
So as a parent you need
to develop a second voice.
I call it the you’re dead voice,
there’s a lot of dads here that
know what I’m talking about.
It’s a voice you only
use once in a while,
when you have a big life lesson a big
life download. That’s what you use it for.
First time I used it on my son,
he was 7
my voice is a combination of Barry
White, Clint Eastwood and Darth Vader.
And we caught him lying.
And he was at the age where
he thought he invented lying.
Turns out, if you don’t tell
them what really happened,
you could get away
with anything.
He’s such an idiot.
And we had him, it was like CSI.
Here’s the blood spatter,
here’s the fingerprints, here…
he’s like, “NOPE!
I didn’t do it.”
And I lost it, I just went,
“DID YOU LIE TO ME?
OH, I’M GONNA ASK
YOU ONE MORE TIME.
DID YOU LIE TO YOUR FATHER?
DID YOU??!!”
He came off the
ground, it was great.
His legs shot up,
I know he pooped himself a little bit.
I can’t prove it, because he was
wearing two pairs of underwear
but I suspect!
So my daughter’s standing in the
middle of McDonald’s parking lot.
Screaming at me.
And I just went,
“GET IN THE CAR.”
She goes,
“NO!” But her body started moving.
That’s when you know
I got the voice right.
When you override their nervous
system… that’s the voice.
She goes, “I’m not getting in
the car.” Poof. She’s in the car.
My son’s been in the car three
minutes,
And now, my ex-wife says
something horrible to me
and I say something horrible back,
we get in the car and I’m like,
“God this is so stupid,
two adults can’t even get this handled,”
and I’m grumbling to myself,
and I go to start my car,
and my daughter gets her
facilities back and goes,
“I’m not going with
you, I told you, Dad.”
And she gets out of the
car, and I had enough.
I pick up the phone, I dial 911.
Because LAPD has
SO much free time.
“911 emergency,
what’s your emergency?”
“Uh, yeah.
We’re having a custody situation,
over here at the McDonald’s
on Ventura and Sherman Oaks…”
And here’s when I know
I’ve gone too far.
I hear the 911 operator go,
“Ughhhhh…
Sir, are the children
in any danger?”
“Uh, yeah… cuz they’re with
a bitch in my opinion.”
And again you just
hear, “Ughhhhhh…
Alright, sir,
I will send a unit and two uniforms.”
“Yeah, make sure there’s people
in those uniforms, thank YOU.”
Just an idiot.
Now, my daughters been standing by the
door listening on the Bluetooth in my car,
and she realized it’s getting serious.
She gets back in the car.
“Fine, dad, I’ll go with you.”
We start driving to the
house and I’m just so…
and by the time I get to
the house I’m at an 11,
I’m so pissed off.
And I walk in,
I grab her backpack and I put it
in front of her bedroom and I go,
“You’re grounded, that’s it,
get in your room right now!”
And my new wife is
standing right there.
My new wife – who’s never had
children and she married me.
So she’s livin’ the nightmare!
To you people in here
tonight that decided to
marry into someone
else’s horribly broken,
destructed divorced family…
I want you to know something.
You are heroes. Heroes.
Yes. Yes. Yeah.
And I mean that in a Special
Olympics kind of way…
Cuz you’re obviously
very sweet and loving,
not that smart,
yet you all deserve metals.
Yes you do! Yes you do!!
So, she sees me flipping
out, and she goes,
“What’s the matter?” And
here’s what I said, I went,
“OH! This… you… and she comes
out… ‘I can’t’... AHHHH!!”
And I just walk away.
I was SO PISSED.
I couldn’t speak English.
And I walk into the
kitchen, I’m just mad…
I go, “Give me a second!”
And I open the cupboard,
I grab the first
glass that was there,
it was just this weird
round, stemless wine glass,
and I grab some pomegranate
juice and I fill it up –
I started juicing, Ahhh,
because kids give you tumors!
And I put it in and I put
it back and I close the door
and I start walking back to my new
wife, I’m like,
“You won’t believe
what just happened.
I get out of the car, she’s like
‘I can’t go with you’ and her mom’s behind
her just shoveling crap on top of her,”
and as I get to my new wife,
we hear
and I go to the peephole,
and there’s two LAPD
officers standing outside.
And they’re standing
like cops stand,
when they want you to
know that they’re cops.
What are you a human
puffer-fish, what are you doing?
I just kept waiting for one to
go, “BAAAA-KAAAAAW!”
So I open the door and it
gets real serious real fast.
I go, “Yeah,” He goes, “Mr.
Titus?” I go, “Yeah.”
“Step back, right now,
where’s your daughter.
We were told you’re abusing your daughter.
WHERE IS YOUR DAUGHTER?”
I look behind them,
and sitting in the back seat of
the cop car, in front of my house,
is my ex-wife. Which is not the last time my
ex-wife’s gonna be in the back of a cop car.
I’m working on that now…
I go, “What’s this about?”
And he goes, “Where is your
daughter, RIGHT NOW?”
And I don’t realize it,
but I’m standing in front of the cops,
holding a wine glass,
full of red liquid, to the top.
And it’s noon.
Cuz nothing says abusive father more
than a little side of raging alcoholic!
And I go,
“Can we talk…” He goes,
“RIGHT NOW, WHERE IS SHE?”
I go, “She’s in her room, right
there,” and I’m starting to get shaky,
“She’s right there, go talk to
her, she’s right there.”
And they go,
“You stand right here.”
And the cops go to the door,
and they look back at
my new wife and they go,
“Would you go in with us?” Because even
the LAPD is afraid of an 11-year-old.
And they walk in,
and they do stuff for like 7 minutes,
and... be cool to your kids.
Don’t be the parent
that causes the psycho.
Cuz, despite your
daughter, if she wanted to,
she could have sailed me down the river, she
could have made up some lie, but she didn’t.
She said, “No,
Dad just… picked me up.
Mom got me amped up,
it’s my fault, I flipped out.”
So, cops come back out.
But they’re still all roostered up on me.
And I go, “Is everything ok?”
and they, “No, it is not ok, where’s your
son? We’re told you’re abusing your son also.”
and here’s my problem…
that’s fair.
Here’s one of my problems…
I was raised in a lot of stress.
My mom was mentally ill, I used to go visit her
at mental institutions when I was a little kid.
My dad got divorced six times,
three of them before I was 10,
so at one point,
while being raised by my dad…
there was so much alimony going
out… food got a little bit rare.
But my father never let on…
unlike today, where everyone’s
depressed, “I have depression…”
My dad never let on once.
At one point, we have my second,
my dad’s second wife cleaned us out.
We had just had a,
we had rubber raft for a couch
and all my dad would
do, is cracking jokes.
“Hey, we’re gonna sleep in
the Titanic tonight, ha ha.”
Never stopped being funny,
no matter how weird…
I knew as a kid… I
knew it was weird.
You know, cuz I had friends who
had other... you guys have shit!
But he never let on that it was
weird, and I love him for that.
You know,
he never let on it was weird.
So, as a child, I learned very early, that
in a high-pressure, high-stress situation…
you’re supposed to be funny.
But sometimes the LAPD…
doesn’t get it.
Now this’ll sound like a joke
– this is what I actually said,
I turn and I go,
“SON, GET OUT HERE.
I WANT YOU TO TELL THE
COPS HOW OFTEN I BEAT YOU.”
Not realizing – Oh, wow… I just
gave them testimony… that’s amazing!
And the cops don’t smile at all,
but my son, thank God for my son,
my son knows me so well…
my son walks out and goes,
“Ok, dad. I’ll tell ‘em.”
Yeah, the older cop goes,
“Why doesn’t he have pants on?”
“We’ve been home 9 minutes,
what are you doin’?”
“I was getting ready
to go play soccer.”
“Why did you stop that?”
I started watching trick
videos on Youtube.”
“Really?
In the middle of changing
clothes, you got side-tracked?
Do you know what makes me CRA...
Could you please
put on some pants?
He is such a scamp, is he not?”
Son disappears,
comes back with some shorts on
walks into the room with the cops,
and right before the door closed, I hear,
“What is that smell?” click.
And I don’t know what
my son said to the cops…
my daughter was
in there a while…
she was in there like 7
minutes, it was tense.
My son was in there less than a minute.
I don’t know what happened.
All I can guess is they
went, “What’d your dad do?”
“Dad’s cool. ”
and the cops went “Ugghhh.”
Cops come back out and
they’re not mad at me anymore.
They’re pissed now, but different.
It's different.
And the young guy walks right up to
me, gets this close to me, and he goes,
“Mr. Titus,
I want you to know something…”
“If THAT was MY ex-wife…
I’d be drinking this early too.”
Thank you guys so much!
Thank you guys!!
You guys were amazing!!