Nice.
I can't find a spot.
All right, just lean back...
and I'll help you down, okay?
Okay.
Lower away.
- All right, lowering.
- All right.
Nice.
Whoo!
All right, all right.
Good job.
Ugh, it was a little scary
up there.
- Not as easy as it looks.
- No.
All right. Who's next?
- Zoe Best is in the house.
- Harris!
It's nice to see you.
How are you?
Never better.
- What do you think?
- It's wonderful.
I heard the book-signing
was a huge success
Yeah, I couldn't
believe the turnout,
especially after
that one newspaper
called my photos
"high school yearbook poses."
Ahh, forget about
that one review.
Your photos are great
and your book is selling.
Hm. I can do better.
Of course. That's why
I wanted to see you.
I've got an idea
for your next book.
Really?
You've done a great job
documenting Chicago
and the Midwest.
Now I want you
to take on the West,
starting with
Yosemite National Park.
Wow. Yosemite?
I... I've never even been there.
All the better.
You'll bring fresh eyes
to the place.
I want you to reveal Yosemite
like no one else has ever done.
I like the idea
of focusing on photography.
Nature photos as art.
But here's the thing:
I need everything in two months.
- Two months?
- This will lead
our fall collection.
Leave that to me.
But I need you
to get started ASAP.
- How many pages?
- A hundred or so photos
with very brief essays
this time.
Okay. As soon as
I get your contract.
It's all right here.
This could be the start
of a whole new line.
Zoe's Best of the West.
Yosemite... then Santa Fe,
Big Sur, the Rockies.
But Harris,
it's impossible to do
any better than Ansel Adams.
He was and always will be
Yosemite's master photographer.
And a national treasure.
But this book will be
your vision of Yosemite.
I know, it's just...
it's a little intimidating
following Ansel Adams'
footsteps.
This will be a breakout book
for you, Zoe.
I really believe it.
Okay!
Awesome.
Hello?
Hello?!
- Zoe?
- Harris!
Just checking to see
if you made it to Yosemite.
Yes, I, uh, got here
a couple hours ago.
The drive was fine.
I love it here already.
Good, good.
Can't wait to see the photos.
Keep me posted.
Will do. Okay, bye!
Man...
- Hi, good morning.
- Good morning!
- My name is Zoe Best.
- Sage Morning Star.
It's my first visit,
and this place is spectacular.
Welcome to Yosemite.
Thanks!
Are you here for a permit?
- A permit?
- Yeah,
for campsites in the wilderness.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm working on a book.
My publisher sent me out here.
- A book on Yosemite?
- That's right.
I'm taking photos
of the park as it is today.
Well, this place is
a photographer's dream.
It really is.
Listen, I was wondering.
Do any of your park rangers
offer guided tours?
Oh yeah, there's
lots of organized hikes
led by rangers.
Well, I think I'm looking
more for a guide,
someone who understands
the ecosystem
and the famous landscapes.
You could hike to most of
the famous vistas from here.
You've got Yosemite Falls,
you've got the valley,
El Capitan from the Meadow.
Hm. That sounds easy enough.
But, hey, the ranger talks
really do help.
I would check it out.
Thank you so much.
Actually, I think
I might know someone
who can help you.
He knows the ecology
better than anyone.
He used to be a climber.
- A climber?
- A rock climber.
But he's sort of, um...
off the grid.
But if you can get
his attention,
he really knows his stuff.
I'm intrigued.
What's his name?
Jack Hawkins.
He's a naturalist.
A naturalist?
He knows the natural order
of things,
from plants to people.
My grandfather actually runs
this small little outfitter shop
just outside the park.
He might know
where to find Jack.
Where's the shop?
Hello?
Over here.
There we go.
You ever seen a woolly bugger?
No, I think that's my first.
You lookin' for a guide?
As a matter of fact, I am.
Well, you've come
to the right place.
Springtime fishing is great,
but you're gonna need some help.
Oh! No, I'm...
I'm not here for the fishing.
I'm looking for a guide
named Jack Hawkins?
Are you?
Is he in some kind of trouble?
No, no, no, uh...
your granddaughter,
the park ranger?
- Sage?
- Yeah.
She said that you might be able
to connect me with Jack.
Hm.
I haven't seen him
in a few weeks.
He pops up, then disappears.
Huh.
I, uh... the next time I see him,
I'll let him know
you were looking for him.
Thanks.
It's a great shop.
Do you get a lot of climbers
in here?
Oh yeah, all the time.
Hm.
I understand Jack is a climber.
Climber, guide, carpenter.
Interesting.
Jack's one of these
all-around capable guys.
Does a little bit of everything.
Do you happen to know
where he lives?
We did a blessing of his land,
up in the mountains.
A blessing?
I love that.
There's an unmarked road
back towards the park
off Highway 120,
just past Coldwater Springs,
on the left.
Thanks...
Kosimay Wilson.
Friends call me Kos.
Zoe Best.
It's lovely to meet you.
Zoe, give me your hand.
This will take you there.
Thank you.
Beethoven's Ninth
from Chicago's Orchestra Hall,
June 27th, 2017.
Bravo!
What the...
Stop that!
Okay, okay.
That was really magnificent.
Wait a minute.
First, you ruined my fishing,
and now this?
- That was you?
- Yeah!
I don't know who you are
or what you're doing here,
but now would be
a good time for you to leave.
I'm sorry about the fishing,
but your performance
here today, wow.
Are you Jack Hawkins?
Yes.
I'm Zoe Best, a photojournalist.
Kos said I could find you here.
Kos.
Yeah.
I don't care
what Kos said, okay?
It's time for you to leave.
Okay. I hear you
loud and clear.
Don't worry,
I'll show myself out.
Good. Bye!
You know, I was there,
by the way.
Orchestra Hall in Chicago,
June 2017.
It was incredible.
You know...
I was there too
at Orchestra Hall.
Best concert ever.
Top ten.
Are you from Chicago?
No. I was just there
that weekend for the concert.
What is it that you want?
I'm looking for a guide.
I do coffee table books
based on my photos.
Picture books
for couch potatoes.
Uh, no!
People really like them.
Yeah, armchair adventurers.
My last book was on small towns.
It sold really well, too.
What do I know?
My next book...
Your next coffee table book.
Is on Yosemite.
I wanna capture the history.
John Muir,
how it was discovered.
Art-like photos of everything.
You know, a million photographers
have been here and done that.
Well, I just need help finding
the famous landscapes.
You should buy a map,
they're all on there.
I wanna go off-map.
Finding new
and different images.
This isn't a theme park, okay?
People die when they go
all gung-ho into the mountains.
Well, that's why I need you.
You know the park and I don't.
Fine. I get it.
You're not into it.
Probably not.
You know what I think?
No, I don't know what you think.
I think that you're naive
and a little dangerous.
But I also think
that you need some help.
How long do you need?
A week, give or take,
just to get the photos.
Okay.
Okay, you'll do it?
I'll do it, but I have one rule.
Which is?
You do what I say when I say it.
The mountains are dangerous.
You got yourself a deal.
We get started tomorrow.
Mm, a week from tomorrow.
After I take care
of a few things.
No, no, no, no,
I... I have a deadline.
We need to get started now.
Sorry!
This was a giant waste of time.
You know, I'm gonna go
discover Yosemite on my own.
Suit yourself.
Just be careful
where you're going.
Thanks...
for nothing.
- Morning.
- Hey!
- So, did you find a guide?
- Uh, that would be a no.
Jack was tied up?
Jack was insufferable.
Yeah, he can be a little testy.
- A little?
- Well, he's got that
confirmed-bachelor edge.
But he's the best I know.
Too bad it didn't work out.
I did some research last night,
and I'll be just fine on my own.
You wouldn't happen to have
a map, would you?
Um, a few. Here.
Thanks.
I assume you're starting
with day hikes,
- no overnight permits needed?
- Right.
I'm going to take the trail
to Cascade Falls
and from what I read,
should be a pretty easy hike
on a beautiful day.
Careful... it gets a little
slippery up near the falls.
- Thanks, Sage.
- For sure.
Hello.
Gah! I'm stuck.
Help!
- Whoa there, bear.
- Help!
Go on, bear.
Get outta here, go on!
Help!
What are you doing down there?
Jack!
I'm stuck.
All right.
Gimme a minute, all right?
All right, Zoe, I'm gonna
throw the rope down.
Keep clear.
What happened?
My foot is stuck.
All right.
I'm gonna put some chalk on it
and it's gonna come
right out, all right?
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
On three.
One, two, three!
Oh!
Thank you.
I thought I was a goner.
You know, that bear was
staring right at me.
Do you have food in your bag?
I had a protein bar.
You're lucky.
That's all I can say.
Now what?
- Start climbing.
- How?
You go hand over hand
and your feet will just follow.
What if I slip?
If you slip, I have the rope.
Just reestablish your footing
and keep going.
Okay.
Good, you're doing great.
Don't look down, look up.
Okay, Mr. Grouch.
Great.
All right, you're doing great.
Keep it up.
Almost there!
Yeah!
- Good job.
- Yes!
Okay.
I made it!
You must think
I'm a real knucklehead.
Yeah, something like that.
Someone said
they wouldn't help me!
Never go into the mountains alone.
Okay.
But you said
you wouldn't take me.
Don't even go there, okay?
You could have died.
Well, I didn't expect
to see a bear.
They live here.
We're the visitors.
Yeah, well, it'd be nice
if they'd let us
- just roam around.
- Most of the time, they do.
Just don't carry
unsealed food, okay,
especially protein bars.
I'm really, really grateful
you showed up.
Thank Sage.
Sage?
Yeah. You told her you were
hiking to Cascade Falls,
she got to worrying
you might do something stupid.
I don't know how
she got that idea.
You know,
you can stay mad at me,
but we're kinda bonded,
aren't we?
What are you talking about?
Well, you just saved my life.
That's kind of a bonding thing,
don't you think?
Jack.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly grateful.
I don't know what I
would have done without you.
I'll give you five days.
That is it.
You will?
I'll take you
where you need to go,
you'll snap your photos,
you'll head back to Chicago
and never come back again.
Ah! What a charming proposal.
Oh, and one more thing?
Gear.
You can't get where you wanna go
without these.
And this.
Are we expecting rain?
- Just trust me.
- Okay, is this where I go
from being a city girl
to a mountain girl?
Something like that.
There you go.
Here you go.
Changing room. That way.
Kos, looks like
I'm your best customer.
Today, you are my only customer.
Hate to ask, but when...
Tomorrow morning, 6 a.m.,
Sage's office.
I'll be there, all geared up.
Great.
- Hello!
- Hey!
So I heard you had
quite the adventure.
If you hadn't sent Jack,
I can't even think about it,
so... thank you.
You really need
to be careful out there.
Things do happen.
Yeah, and after all that,
he still agreed to be my guide.
Well, you'll be in good hands.
- Hello, by the way.
- Good morning.
You've met my grandfather, Kosimay.
It's nice to see you again.
Sometimes, Jack asks Kos
for advice.
He knows Yosemite
better than anyone.
I was born here.
My family goes way back.
- Four thousand years.
- Oh! Is that all?
Give or take.
We're part of the Miwok tribe.
- Good morning!
- Morning!
- Hey, Sage, how are you?
- Doing well.
- Nice to see you, Jack.
- Yeah, you too.
Well, if you guys need any help
with your planning,
just let me know,
I'll be over there.
Awesome.
- Thanks.
- Thanks, Sage.
And thank you for stopping by.
He knows every trail.
- Don't you?
- Most.
Here you go.
I wanna make things official.
Five days.
Looks good to me.
Let's get started.
Here's a list of the places
I wanna visit.
The closer I can get,
the better.
Yosemite Falls, El Capitan,
Cathedral Rocks...
No problem.
Yeah, I think we can knock
the first three or four
of these off today.
Really?
That's the good news.
Tenaya Creek,
very hard to predict.
See, right here, easy access,
but shadows, clouds, mists,
who knows?
Well, we can at least try, right?
- What do you think?
- Maybe,
depending on the weather.
I have this idea.
I wanna get a photo
of Half Dome,
one that no one
has ever taken before.
That's only the most
photographed mountain
in the world.
- Even Jack managed a shot.
- Oh.
Half Dome at dawn.
Getting close to Half Dome
can be real hard.
But there's a great view
from Mirror Lake.
That's a great idea, Kos.
You need his blessing
and his wisdom.
- Hm.
- Thank you.
All right, let's get going.
Did you remember your rain gear?
You know it.
Wow.
Yosemite Falls.
What a shot.
I'll use my 4x5 camera for this.
It's a wide-angle lens.
Great for landscapes.
This is the shutter control.
See the bellows?
I love this camera.
Now.
Viewfinder...
Okay, now focus...
This is incredible.
There it is.
Wow.
The quintessential
Yosemite photo.
It's almost too easy.
Get your rain gear on,
we'll get a little closer.
I've never seen
anything like it.
All those boulders?
It's called talus.
It's been here since
the last ice age.
They're huge!
You can't see from here,
but there are two more
waterfalls up above.
The falls are terraced?
Yeah.
The noise is overpowering.
The fountain of life.
Magical.
Huh!
Hey! None of me.
Please?
Nope.
Look, this book isn't just about
nice scenery.
It's about people like you
trying to conserve it.
Later, okay?
Come on, one shot.
I hate posed photos.
So don't pose.
Just jump up there
and look like a guy.
Perfect!
You handle those cameras
pretty well.
Tools of the trade.
So what are you?
A journalist or a photographer?
I went online.
Oh, you did?
My first love was painting.
That's why I went to art school,
but then I realized
that you can't make a living
as a fine artist.
Yeah, not easy.
Yeah, so I took some
photography classes
and I realized
I have an eye for it.
I'm sort of a tech geek.
So no training?
Well, I was in journalism
before I went to art school.
So lemme get this straight.
Your goal is to find
Yosemite's famous locations
and take artsy photos.
I am an artist.
My goal is to find new ways
to capture interesting images.
Hm. Well, I'm a scientist.
Wait.
I thought you were a musician,
you know,
conducting the orchestra?
Okay, you got me.
Music is my passion,
especially classical.
Don't get me wrong,
I love your art and all,
but your photos just don't tell
the whole story.
What do you mean?
I mean, Yosemite's ecology
is changing.
There are conservation issues,
environmental concerns.
Well, I was focused on the art.
Gotcha.
I saw your article
about water conservation.
I Googled you too.
- Huh.
- And I also saw
that you wrote a book
called Conserving the West.
What's that about?
Sustainability.
Of the park?
Of the West.
Its water, its land,
including Yosemite.
Huh. That's interesting.
The science, you know, conservation.
It's about testing
and measuring, you know?
Data analysis.
Your art, your photos
are beautiful,
but science reveals
what's inside the photo.
Okay, well,
this might surprise you,
but I'm intrigued by all that.
Do you ever collaborate,
you know, with other writers?
Not big on collaboration.
Oh, all good.
I don't need your help.
Look, I can get you
to the famous locations,
then you're on your own.
Great. Just how I like it.
So are there any places that
show conservation at work?
Oh, so now you want my help?
Well, only because
you're Mr. Conservation.
Hey.
I can show you what's happening,
just no collaboration.
I wouldn't think of it!
- Good.
- Mm!
Look at those spires.
It looks like they're
reaching for the heavens.
Cathedral spires.
When John Muir arrived here
in the 1860s
and saw this valley,
it was a full-on
religious experience.
Feel like I'm having one
right now.
"The range of light."
That's what he called
the Sierras.
I mean, being here was like
being in a cathedral.
Every read any John Muir?
I started reading
My First Summer in the Sierras
on the plane.
I love his writing.
He was a scientist,
but he connected man's soul
to nature.
It's where he found God.
Huh.
"The grand show is eternal."
That's how he described Yosemite.
When I was driving
through the tunnel
into the valley,
it was sort of like
a religious experience.
That's a gift.
Like the Garden of Eden.
And our job is to protect it.
And my job is to capture it.
Nice!
Come on.
There's a great spot for
an artsy photo of El Capitan.
Hey!
Wait up, roadrunner!
We got a schedule to keep.
Hi.
Merced River's at its best
this time of year.
How's the fishing?
I wouldn't know.
Someone's phone
scared them all away.
Oh, yeah. Uh, okay.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
El Capitan.
How's that?
Right in your own back yard.
Do you ever take it for granted?
I take it all for granite.
Really?
Sorry, bad pun, okay?
Look, I get to see new things
every day.
Weather patterns,
changing of the seasons.
- I get it.
- But there's a harmony
to this place,
how it all blends.
It's almost mystical.
The sheer cliff is stunning.
El Cap.
It's like a massive anchor
holding everything in place.
And people climb the face?
Every day.
When I drove by yesterday,
there must have been
50 photographers
in the Meadow taking photos.
Yup. All trying to be
Ansel Adams,
none of 'em coming even close.
That's exactly how I feel.
El Capitan above the Meadow.
Art?
Art.
Hey, look.
About halfway up.
Oh, I see them!
How do they do that?
Lotta chalk and strong forearms.
They look like toy figures
against a fake backdrop.
They're very real.
Over 30 people have been killed
trying to summit El Capitan.
Wow.
Sage said you're a climber.
I was.
Have you ever scaled El Capitan?
Several times.
Insane.
Yeah, it's not for everyone.
Hey.
Do you think I could go
to the basecamp or something?
I would love to take some photos
of the climbers.
Yeah. I'll take you to Camp 4
where they all hang out.
It's a good bit
of social history as well.
- Let's do it.
- All right.
So cool.
You know, in climbing circles,
Camp 4 is Mecca.
It started after World War II.
Some burnt-out soldiers
moved here.
Some became climbers,
others were just hanging out.
What did the park rangers think?
Well, there was tension
for years.
The rangers tried to evict 'em
but the Gis just wouldn't leave.
What happened?
Well, one year,
the river flooded,
washed away a lot
of the staff cottages,
so the park services built
a dormitory over here.
Suddenly, the park rangers had
a strong presence in Camp 4.
And the climbers?
Today, it's first come,
first served
for a seven-day permit.
Howdy.
- How's it going?
- Good.
How's the climbing today?
- Splitter.
- Right on.
Either one of you guys
summit El Cap?
I did last summer.
Yeah, me too.
She went the nose route.
In the rain.
Any ascent of El Cap is major.
Totally.
Uh, I'm doing
a photo book on Yosemite
and I'm wondering
if I could grab
a few shots of you two?
- Sure.
Awesome.
Hey, where you from?
- Chicago.
- Me too!
- No kidding.
- Clark Street.
Lincoln Park.
What's your name?
Uh, Zoe Best.
Ah! I have your book.
Super good.
You should put us in.
I... let's do it!
I would love that.
♪ So keep your head up ♪
♪ Don't ever give up ♪
♪ It's what you make it ♪
♪ It's now or never ♪
Maybe, um,
let's come together and get
a million-dollar smile.
Say "Yosemite"!
Love it, we did it!
Fantastic, I love it.
♪ Letting go right now ♪
♪ 'Cause it's your day
right now ♪
♪ Yeah, you got what it takes
in every single way ♪
♪ If you can just believe it ♪
♪ And leave it all behind ♪
♪ Yeah, let it go, let it go ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ Don't ever give up ♪
♪ It's what you make it ♪
♪ It's now or never ♪
♪ Leave it all behind ♪
Will that add to your book?
Absolutely!
You know, I love
that kind of serendipity.
Let me ask you,
'cause you're a climber.
Why do they do it?
It's just so insane.
Well, there's free climbing
with ropes and harnesses.
That's what I used to do.
It's fun.
And dangerous.
Not if you're cautious
and prepared.
And some climbers don't use
ropes or anything?
That's free soloing.
I did a little bit of that.
Never again.
Wow.
El Capitan is one
of the most difficult
rock climbs in the world,
but that's what draws people.
I guess it's all about
the challenge.
As for me, I like to keep
my feet on the ground.
Well, come on.
I'll get you to a mountaintop,
no climbing needed.
Oh, sounds like
my kind of mountain.
That's Half Dome
in the distance.
I've run out of superlatives.
Hey, check it out.
Aww.
Aww, I love this photo!
Sometimes,
Mother Nature shows off.
She's putting on quite the show.
You know,
it's hard not to appreciate
the park founders.
I mean, their entire goal
was to preserve and conserve.
I want my photos
to tell that story.
Oh. So they're not just
art for art's sake.
Places like Yosemite,
where nature is protected...
it is a great model
for sustainability.
Landscapes are for observation
and conservation.
Not just beauty,
but what's inside the photo.
Art and science.
If we're good to the land,
then the land will be
good to us.
Oh. I almost forgot.
Sage invited us over for dinner.
Well, more you than me, but...
I figure I'll tag along.
A home-cooked meal sounds great.
We're here!
Come on in!
Nice to see you again.
Nice to see you!
I'm so glad
you guys could make it.
Thanks for having us.
This place looks great.
Staff housing.
You know, those WPA guys really
knew how to build a cabin.
I love the Craftsman look.
Come on, make yourselves
at home.
Uh, Jack, there's wine
on the table for y'all.
Awesome. Thanks.
Um, so, how was your day?
Now I know how Alice felt
when she arrived in Wonderland.
Look at that!
"Moon and Half Dome."
You know, I've taken
some spectacular shots,
but none of them are this good.
Ansel Adams was
something special.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
So, any highlights
from your day?
The whole day was a highlight!
But I loved getting close
to El Capitan.
- And Cathedral Rocks.
- Mm, where we met John Muir.
Jack's muse.
We all follow in his footsteps.
You know, back in the day,
developers had turned Yosemite
into a tourist trap.
- Really?
- Yeah, it's true.
So John Muir knew he had
to do something about it,
so when Teddy Roosevelt
visited in 1903,
he took him camping
down in Mariposa Grove.
That photo's incredible.
That camping trip
led to the preservation
of Yosemite Valley.
It's true.
No John Muir,
no Yosemite National Park.
Here's to John Muir.
And to those who were here
before him.
- Aho.
I see that you've added
to your library.
Zoe's Best of the Midwest.
Yeah, I picked it up
at the Ansel Adams Gallery.
I didn't know that.
Thanks, Sage.
I understand why
you're like focusing
on Yosemite's landscapes,
but most of the photos
in your book are of people.
I want to get beauty shots,
but I also like human stories.
Like, today we ran into climbers
at El Capitan.
I had to restrain her from
getting into a harness herself.
The climbers had great stories.
Maybe your book
can also tell our story.
Absolutely.
It's part of history, right?
I like your Alice in Wonderland analogy.
You know the line
"curiouser and curiouser"?
When you dig below
the surface here,
it can get a little complicated.
Like?
White people tend to think
they discovered Yosemite.
It was never undiscovered.
My great-grandfather
was born here,
and his father was born here
as well.
The Ahwahnechee
were here all along.
Ahwahnechee?
The original people
of Yosemite Valley.
Part of the Miwok tribe.
There were hundreds of them
living here, right?
Their cedar huts were scattered
throughout the valley.
One family here,
another family there.
Plenty of fish and deer
for food.
It was a good place.
Then the miners arrived
during the Gold Rush,
thought they'd discovered paradise.
That's when trouble began.
There were a lot of tragedies,
and not just a culture clash.
As I understand it, there was
a bounty on our people.
A vigilante group
called the Mariposa Brigade
led sort of an invasion
of Yosemite.
Many were killed
or forced onto reservations.
That's so sad.
America's past is not perfect.
It's complicated,
and there is a lot of pain,
but it's all a part
of its story.
Do any Indigenous people
still live in the park?
The last were gone by the 1960s.
But their spirit is still here.
They'll never leave.
I want to take photos of some
of the historical places.
There's plenty in the park.
Tenaya Lake and Creek.
The Ahwahnee Hotel
and even Half Dome.
And as they say, a picture's
worth a thousand words,
if it's the right picture.
- Harris.
- I'm looking for John Muir.
Is he around?
- He's everywhere.
- Good, good.
- He's the man, you know.
- So I hear.
You need to dig
into his writing.
I'm on it.
I'm also digging into
the Native American past.
It's tragic but it's important.
I agree.
So it's going well?
This place is spectacular.
I mean, you should see
El Capitan.
Send some photos.
We ran into some climbers
scaling the wall.
It's intense.
- Did you find a guide?
- I did!
Yeah, he's an interesting guy.
Former rock climber.
I think you'd like him.
- He was even quoting John Muir.
- Hm, sounds perfect.
Yeah, he also did some writing.
Wrote a book called
Conserving the West.
- Hm, I've heard of it.
- And we're just getting started.
I can't wait to see
where it leads.
Don't forget your deadline.
Right.
Right, right.
I'm on it.
I'm just imagining 200 years ago
when the Ahwahnechee people
lived here.
They just picked
such a beautiful place.
So peaceful.
Yeah, it's like Sage said.
History can be painful,
but the more we know
about our past
the stronger our future can be.
- How's this?
- Yeah, that's great.
- Great.
- Perfect.
I went to the gallery today.
A present.
Conserving the West
by Jack Hawkins.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
There's a whole section
on water conservation.
Our most important resource.
Look.
I know I said
I don't need your help,
but I was wrong.
You know more about Yosemite
than I ever will.
How 'bout you help
co-write the book with me?
Like I said, I'm not big
on collaboration.
I know.
But...
If I were to get involved,
I write as a scientist
and you write as a journalist.
And you're good, too.
Thanks.
But I don't think our styles
would mesh.
How about you write sections
under your name
and I write sections
under my name?
I might go deeper than you want.
I'll take my chances.
This might work out.
You can highlight conservation
and help me find photos
to go with your points.
Maybe.
I do have one ground rule though.
Here we go.
I'm in charge.
You do what I say when I say it.
You're the book boss,
I'm the trail boss.
Even-steven!
Okay, Zoe Best.
You got yourself a partner.
Yes!
Woo!
That shot is incredible.
Do you see that rainbow?
We do what we can.
Jack.
I think this is the best photo
I've ever taken.
Really?
It's pure magic.
Ah.
Is this your
art-at-a-new-level shot
for the cover?
Maybe.
Well, I'm glad for you, seriously.
I've always wanted to know
what's at the end of a rainbow.
Me too.
Woo!
Careful.
Whoa!
Careful, Zoe.
- Oh.
- You all right?
- Yeah, sorry.
- It's all right.
Let's just take a break
for a minute, yeah?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Everybody should have
a guide like you.
You've been awesome.
Well, I bet you say that
to all the boys.
I do, but this time
I actually mean it.
Well, I don't love guiding,
but sometimes it works out.
Thanks to your friend Sage.
I'm glad she connected us.
Yeah, you weren't so happy
on that first day.
You were such a grouch.
Yeah, you were invading
my space.
I needed a little help.
Yeah, you were pretty lost.
I was lost.
I was hoping that you would
just turn back around
and head back to Chicago.
And now?
And now...
I'm seeing the park
through your eyes, as art.
And I love it.
Sage says that you are
a confirmed bachelor
who lives alone in the woods.
I'm happy.
Okay, so I'm just gonna
ask you this.
Between us and the mountains...
Does it ever get lonely living
there alone all year round?
No.
No, I mean...
It just seems like...
There's plenty going on
even in the winter.
But no love life up here?
If you're trying to make me
a profile in your book,
let's just stop right there.
I agreed to write about
Yosemite, not about me.
No, it's just inquiring minds
want to know.
Have you ever been in love?
Are you always this nosey?
I'm a journalist.
No.
You're kidding.
You asked, I answered.
And the reason is...
I don't need a reason.
So you like living alone?
- How 'bout you?
- Me?
Yeah.
Well, if I'm gonna be honest...
my work is my love.
Okay, well...
There was Harley, a sculptor
I met in art school.
But that didn't work out.
And then there was Billy.
Well, actually,
there were two Billys,
but I didn't really love them.
Look, I guess
I'm just old school.
I have a different view
of what love actually is.
You know how I'm about nature
and weather patterns
and what each day brings
to Yosemite?
I do now.
Well, for me
it's all about the land
and the details within it.
And if I ever do fall in love,
it'll be because
of the little things.
Do her eyes sparkle
when she laughs,
and does her smile
touch my soul?
What sounds does she make
when she's sleeping?
And how does she react
to a sunrise
over a mountain ridge,
or when the Alpine glow
washes over the face
of Half Dome?
What brings her joy, you know,
and how does she accept sadness?
And what does she see
that I don't see?
When I wake up next to her
in the morning,
am I excited to share
a new day with her?
And is there this unspoken look
between us that says,
"Yes, the world
is a better place
because we're in it together."
It'll be like that, you know.
The details.
I guess you never
really thought of it.
Look.
The Alpine glow.
It's beautiful.
Exactly perfect.
Look.
I have an idea
if you're up for it.
Try me.
There's this great little
country dive bar
not too far from here.
Food's pretty good
and there's live music tonight.
I'm in.
So, are you getting
what you need?
I have a ton of beauty shots
and a lot of stories, but...
I still need that one photo
that takes it to another level.
Hmm.
We're still on art patrol.
Something like that.
Mm.
You sure were right
about the food.
I'm glad you like it.
This place is amazing.
What, no country bars
in Chicago?
Not like this.
Grab your partners, ladies.
Here we go.
♪ With everything I've done ♪
♪ Too much and then some ♪
♪ I ain't too much
worse for the wear ♪
♪ Between learning my lessons
and counting my blessin's ♪
♪ I realize
I really don't care ♪
♪ As long as I wake
with a smile of my face ♪
♪ From some dream
in a rear-view mirror ♪
♪ I could have ended up
anyplace else ♪
♪ But I know
that I'm better off here ♪
You dance pretty well.
For a mountain guy who spends
his winters alone?
Yeah.
For that guy.
You dance pretty well too.
Hm.
For a Chicago girl
who doesn't get out much?
Yeah, for that girl.
♪ Oh, as long as I wake
to your smiling face ♪
♪ The rest of the world
disappears ♪
♪ I wouldn't trade this
for anything else ♪
Woop!
Hey!
Oh!
♪ I wouldn't trade this
for anything else ♪
♪ I know that I'm better ♪
[]
The rainbow photo is incredible.
Thanks.
I love that one too.
Zoe, this book's
gonna be spectacular.
I'm excited.
Have you found
the structure yet?
I mean, the shots look great,
but where's the book heading?
I'm not sure.
I'm adding a conservation angle
with Jack
and I'm building
an emotional arc
about the people I've met.
- I still need that one photo.
- To show off the park.
To show that I'm an artist,
not just another photographer.
What about the park
and what it means?
Don't worry,
it's all about the park.
I just want an image that soars.
Sounds good.
How's Jack working out?
Better than
I could have imagined.
He just have all this insight
about the land.
In fact, I have asked him
to co-write the book with me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I think he's perfect.
Keep those photos comin'.
I will.
Bye.
Yes.
Back when I was rock climbing,
I used to come down here
to swim,
just to cool off.
Have you always lived up here
near the park?
I've been coming up here
since I was a kid.
My father taught biology
at Cal State Sacramento.
We spent our summers here
camping and hiking.
I caught the climbing bug.
Your parents let you?
Not at first.
I majored in Natural Science
at Berkeley,
but my father always complained
I was majoring in climbing.
Sounds like you were.
Well, I climbed my way
through graduate school.
That's when I became interested
in conservation.
And started writing about it.
Writing was like climbing.
Put one step in front of another
and then another,
and pretty soon I had
a best-selling book.
That's how you got
your mountain cabin.
Somethin' like that.
Let's talk about you, though,
and what you're missing,
that photo.
What about that shot
of the rainbow at the falls?
I love it, but...
Mm, doesn't define you
as an artist.
I need a photo of Half Dome,
one that no one
has ever gotten before.
I am really stuck on this one.
What if we backpack
towards Half Dome?
Let's do it.
All right.
Let's check in with Kos.
We need some gear
and he may have an idea or two.
- Okay.
- All right.
I saw this photo of Half Dome
in your book.
It's a beauty.
I got lucky one day.
It's nice but there's a million
just like it.
I think it's a masterpiece.
Think of all the times
you've seen Half Dome.
Do you ever see anything new?
I always look for the face.
The face?
A legend has been passed down
about a woman named Tis-sa-ack
who quarreled with her husband.
She was very upset,
so she ran off to the east
and formed a huge mountain.
But her tears of guilt
forever stained her face.
You see what happens if you...
Don't go there, Jack.
I'm just saying.
Later, her name got changed
to Half Dome.
And from a certain angle,
you can see her face
and the tear stains.
But getting that photo,
well, I don't know.
That's it.
That's the photo I need to get
of her face.
The problem is,
Half Dome faces west.
Most photos are taken
from the south,
from the John Muir Trail,
- right?
- That's right.
That's where Jack took
his photo.
From Nevada Falls.
Long ago, my grandfather
helped John Muir
create a different trail
all the way to Half Dome.
- From the west?
- Right.
But that trail was closed.
Yeah, the Park Service
closed that trail
several years ago
because of a big accident.
So, that's it, there's no way
for me to take the photo
- of her face from the west?
- Not safely.
What's that saying,
"the better part of valor"?
So, I guess that's that.
'Fraid so.
The idea hit me
early this morning.
He called and said
the look on your face
yesterday hurt his heart.
Kos.
Thanks.
So what's the idea?
When I was a boy,
my grandfather took me camping
way up Tenaya Creek.
That's when he told me
about the old trail.
- The one that's closed?
- Past that one.
It's a long hike,
but we kept going,
above the creek,
up a little ridge,
and there it was.
The face of Half Dome.
- Close?
- Close enough to see her tears.
How was it?
Was it steep?
Not too bad.
Jack, what do you say?
Can we get a wilderness permit
to camp up there?
There's campsites
along Tenaya Creek.
- There you go.
- Awesome.
Thank you so much.
All three of you.
Well, time's a-tickin'.
Let's pack up and hit the trail.
- Bye.
- See ya.
Bye.
Be safe.
Good luck.
What a great view.
See that canyon over there?
Uh-huh.
That's Tenaya Creek.
That's where we're headed.
All right.
Come on, roadrunner,
let's get to it.
This looks like our spot
right here.
Oh.
Is this where we're camping?
Yes, ma'am.
All right.
How far is the photo ridge
from here,
the one that Kos
was talking about?
Well, I'm guessing that we take
the trail up as far as we can
and then, if we're lucky,
we'll find it.
I'm feelin' lucky.
Come on, let's find a spot
to pitch our tents.
Okay.
Whatever it is you've made,
it smells delicious.
Pre-cooked chicken alfredo.
My fave.
The thermos right there
has got some Chardonnay in it.
Would you care to pour us
a couple of glasses?
What do you think
of our dining room?
Perfect.
- Bon appétit.
And Jack, thanks.
Mm, not bad.
Did I mention I was serving?
You've come
to the right restaurant.
I heard the chef is amazing.
So, tomorrow morning
we're gonna find
the face of a young girl
stained with tears,
the Holy Grail of photos.
Do you think Kos will put
my photo in his shop?
Absolutely.
So, I was thinking,
my book is gonna tell
the story of Half Dome.
But I also want to tell
your story.
No, I don't think so.
I mean, I can't stop
thinking about you.
Your story is amazing.
And you've been coming here
as a boy
and becoming a climber
and a conservationist.
There's a romance
to who you are.
Well, I have to admit,
I've been thinkin'
about you too.
- You have?
- Yeah.
Like what?
How do you feel
about lemon cookies?
I thought you'd never ask.
See this band of stars
right here?
- Uh-huh.
- That's the Milky Way.
Oh, and these three stars
in a row right here,
- you see 'em?
- Yeah.
That's Orion's belt.
- Is that the Big Dipper?
- Uh-huh.
And that's Cassiopeia
just below it.
- A shooting star!
- Yeah.
Jack.
Huh?
I love this.
Me too.
I wish I could preserve
this moment forever.
So, what's next?
I mean, after the face of tears.
Tomorrow's my last night.
Back to Chicago.
I've done so much this week.
Thanks to you.
Went by too fast.
Do you think we'll mesh?
No.
But complement, yeah.
There is something else.
There is?
It's just...
the other night
when we were dancing...
I looked into your eyes
and it was like
looking into your soul.
Never had that feeling before.
Like knowing
if we're together...
the world is a better place?
Yeah, like that.
Like that.
We should probably
get some sleep.
- Big day tomorrow.
- Yeah.
Good idea.
- Jack.
- I hear 'em.
What should we do?
- Let 'em howl.
- Jack!
Scram!
Get out of here!
Get, get!
You know, they live here,
we don't.
Do you think they would hurt us?
No.
Just hungry.
Probably smelled our food.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Back to bed?
- You okay?
- Yeah. I'm fine.
- Good.
- It's just coyotes, right?
Right.
I mean, nothing to worry about.
Nothing to worry about.
Okay, good, well,
I'll just, uh...
snuggle back into my bag.
- Okay.
- Jack.
- Yeah?
Are you gonna be okay?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Okay.
Good.
- Zoe.
- Yeah?
Goodnight.
Good morning.
Mornin'.
- How'd you sleep?
- I kept hearing coyotes.
- I was lights out.
- Hm.
You made bacon and eggs?
How are you not married?
- Grab a seat.
- Thanks.
Ooh, this muffin looks good.
If only I could find
some coffee.
Well, ask and you shall receive.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Cheers.
Whew, that's strong.
Mm.
Shall we dig in?
Let's do it.
We'll grab our stuff
on the way back.
Okay, thanks.
Yeah.
All of this,
this beautiful canyon.
It's life-affirming.
You just paraphrased
my favorite John Muir quote.
Yeah?
What's his version?
"Never again will one faint
by the wayside"
who gains the blessing
of one mountain day.
Whatever his fate,
long life, short life,
"stormy or calm,
he is forever rich."
What a writer.
I got goosebumps.
John Muir lives.
I think you're gonna like this.
Jack!
Wow.
Worth the walk?
More like "Full Dome"
than Half Dome.
This is it.
This is the shot
that you've been waiting for.
It's so immense.
One of the largest rocks
in the world.
Look at her face and her tears.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
See how Half Dome bends
outward toward the left
near the tears?
Yeah?
That's the shot.
That's it.
It's perfect.
Great shot.
Thanks.
Kos was right.
It was worth the effort.
It's quite a shot.
I'm absolutely wiped out.
You know, if you're not
feeling up to it tonight,
- I totally get it.
- It's our last night!
- No, I just...
- A hot bath and a quick nap's
all I need.
I'll see you on the patio
at seven?
Perfect.
- Bye.
- See ya.
- You look amazing.
- Thank you.
You clean up very well.
This is really nice.
So, before I forget,
what's the deadline?
Uh... photographs
by the end of the week.
And the essays?
I hope you're a fast writer.
Get me some photos,
I'll start hammering.
Okay, I'll send some tonight
and an outline of what I need.
I really wish
you weren't leaving.
Yeah.
I feel like we just got started.
You think this will beat
the Chardonnay in a thermos?
Oh, nothing will ever beat that.
But it will come close.
To Zoe's Best.
It's been magical.
You really nailed that photo
of Yosemite Falls.
Our first day.
How's that Half Dome shot?
It's so beautiful.
Oh, and Harris
loved what you wrote
for the introduction.
"This valley, caretaken by
our Native brothers and sisters"
for thousands of years,
now preserved forever
and for everyone
"as a magnificent national park."
And the teaser you wrote
about nature on the move
and El Capitan,
the Pillar of Power,
I love it.
Great.
I mean, this is great.
So, you like
my first three essays then?
I loved your intro...
but your essays...
there's just so much science.
It's a coffee table book,
not a text book.
I'm a scientist.
I mean, we agreed that I would
write the way that I write.
I know.
I kn... I know.
I'm sorry.
I can't use your essays.
They just don't fit.
I'm really sorry.
No, I mean, I get it.
You're the book boss, right?
Look, uh...
- I'll talk to you later.
- Jack.
- Hey, Zoe.
I'm so glad you called.
Yeah, I am sorry,
I've just been...
Oh, no, no, no, it's okay.
I'm just happy
to hear your voice.
I'm really sorry
that my essays didn't work out,
but I'm sure you can
finish this on your own.
Oh, but Jack,
I... I was thinking...
No.
Zoe, I'm done, uh...
I'm sorry I couldn't help.
But, Jack... you did help.
You're on every page
of this book,
every photo, and I...
I'm sure it's gonna be great,
and I've loved spending time
with you,
but we're in different worlds, Zoe.
It's time for us to move on.
Goodbye.
Bye.
I know, Harris,
but I need more time.
I'm glad that you like
the photos,
but they're not gonna make
any sense without the narrative.
What happened to Jack?
We had creative differences.
I see.
Okay, okay.
Look, I'm sorry, but...
I can only give you
two more days.
That's it.
I understand.
Thanks, Harris.
- Hello.
- Jack.
Uh, what a surprise.
- Um, come on in.
- Thanks.
You sounded a little stuck.
And that bear
keeps staring at me.
Well, I did some rewriting,
simplified some things.
There were sections
of your essays I loved.
We got work to do.
Do you have a printer?
That's it.
Finished.
I couldn't have done it
without you.
You're the one
that made it great.
Oh, so now you like
armchair adventure books.
I liked the adventure
of making this one.
To our adventure.
Zoe's Best of the West.
Yosemite.
Well...
I gotta catch a flight.
Back to the mountains?
Yeah.
Who am I kidding? I...
I came back here
because I'm in love with you.
I'm in love with you too.
Whatever happens
for the rest of my life,
I want it to be with you.
Me too.
Forever.
So, your book did well.
Very.
What's next?
Have you ever been
to the Grand Canyon?
Your next book.
Our next book.
Harris sent me off
with a contract.
The Grand Canyon.
And I also have
another question for you.
As a journalist?
As the woman
who's in love with you.
Okay.
Will you marry me?
Are you always this forward?
Only with you.
Yes, I will marry you
in front of these mountains
and Yosemite Falls.
Do you, Zoe Best,
take Jack Hawkins
to be your lawful
wedded husband,
to love, honor, and cherish
from this day forward?
I do.
And do you, Jack Hawkins,
take Zoe Best
to be your lawful wedded wife,
to love, honor, and cherish
from this day forward?
I do.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may now kiss the bride.