Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
MAN ON RADIO: Tango Foxtrot closing
in, attempt is 100 yards.
You have to go.
I repeat, you have to go.
SOLDIER: Target is on
the other side of this clearing.
Petro, Vandewege,
go on.
Take the right.
Snowden and Silva,
you're with me.
We got this, brother.
We always got this.
It's hard.
[GUNS FIRING]
- SOLDIER 1: Taking fire!
- [SOLDIER 2 YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
[GASPS]
- ANGEL: Daddy?
- Hmm?
- You'll help them?
- Help who, honey?
Those children, they're sad.
WOMAN ON TV: For just
30 cents a day.
Less than one cup of coffee.
What does your
daddy do for a living?
Child protection.
So, what do you think
I wanna do?
Help them?
Exactly.
[WOMAN ON TV
CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
Hello, everybody,
And thank you for coming out today.
Now being a more than
occasional reader...
Why'd you do that?
There's a lot of bad things
going on in the world, babe.
Got to protect energy
at this house at all costs.
You know what?
Let's go get dressed so we can
have some breakfast. Bring it in.
Shh.
KYLE: Father God, thank you for this
meal and thank you for this moment.
Being able to eat
what we want when we want,
where we want and with whom
we want. Thank you.
- Amen.
And please, Lord, help Daddy save the
sad children inside the bad places.
That's really sweet of you.
And Lord, please bring
Mommy home.
Amen.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[ROOSTER CROWING]
[ENGINE STOPS]
Some of you have preferred
to be smug and greedy,
but let me ask you, would someone
greedy build this? Come on, man.
This store is more than just a store.
Nelson's is a symbol...
A symbol of all the opportunity
I've created and provided.
You had 18 years, Pops.
I'll make sure he pays for this.
[GUN CLICKS]
[GUN FIRES]
[SPITS]
[PHONE VIBRATING]
Hey, girl, what's up?
I'm at work. You good?
Yeah. Calling to see if you want
to have cousins dinner tonight.
It's your birthday, chica.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
- Sunny, my birthday was a week ago.
- What?
We can still celebrate.
I'll try, but I'm buried
in bile over here.
All right, well, if not,
at least come by in the morning.
Sam's doing his
big giveaway tomorrow.
In fact, bring Kyle with you.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sure he'd love that.
- I'll try to make it, okay?
- Okay.
- Bye, chica.
- Bye bye.
Sunny says hi.
- Tell her I said hello.
- Uh-huh.
I got a call from a guy who says
he has a little Spanish boy,
parents just disappeared.
Just wondering if you could go with me in the
morning to help me with Spanish a little?
Yeah, sure thing.
I'm gonna head out early.
Got some stuff I need to
take care of at the house.
SPARKS: Please consider
more security if you want
to keep doing
these public appearances, Sam.
You're all the security
I need, Sparks.
I don't want to seem like a big
shot surrounded by a bunch of suits.
You know, we're going for
a man of the people.
Think, it's an election year
and my customers are my voters
and they love me and they love
getting their shit for cheap.
They're saying it's getting kind
of dangerous out there, isn't it?
- I'm not the President.
- Yeah, but you're on your way to.
Well, let's put it this way. Americans
are crazy, but they're not that crazy.
So, what do you wanna do
about Kyle?
We're just going to swing by,
pick up Angel
and Kyle always has a bug
up his ass or something.
SPARKS: Yeah.
Grandpa.
Where's your dad?
Inside, asleep.
[GUNS FIRING]
Kyle just...
Sparks, stay with her.
Kyle, Angel is out there completely
unsupervised, all on her own.
Is she ready to go?
What the hell
are you doing here?
Uh, for the slumber party
at Grandpa's house.
You know, before the promotion
at the store tomorrow morning.
Okay, I get it.
Well, you don't care because I'm the man
who married your mother so you hate me.
So it's okay.
I'll deal with it.
But, Jesus, Kyle, don't let her
see you like this.
Get him out.
I know he's got a gun on him.
I don't like guns in my house.
Get him out.
Kyle, I know your wife left you,
and that sucks.
I get it.
But Angel's mother left her,
and that sucks more, okay?
That's what you have
to think about now, son.
And drinking like this.
You never even used to drink at all.
- Do you know what your mother would say?
- Don't talk about my mother.
The kind of hell she would raise
if you saw you
- in this condition.
- Don't talk about my mother
Kyle, your mother was grateful
for everything I did.
I took you both out of poverty.
You're the man in war
because of me.
Where do you come up
with all this shit?
You know what, Kyle? I think you
need to find your purpose again.
A purpose is what makes
a man great.
I had a lot of shit on my mind.
I'm doing the best I can.
Yeah. You know,
what scares me, Kyle,
is sometimes your best
is the worst I've ever seen.
All right. Let's do this.
[CAR ENGINE ACCELERATING]
CLOVE: So Janine just left?
No reason, no nothing?
Nope, nada.
Wow.
Is Angel okay?
Yeah, she's okay. I mean,
this all gets difficult at times but...
Guess it's a blessing
that she's still so young.
CLOVE: You know
that's not how that works.
I'm sorry.
- I'll shut up.
- It's okay.
You're just looking out for her.
It's why you're so good
at your job.
I can't help myself.
I just wanna save every kid I can.
We help them.
We don't save them.
That's the way we have to think
of this in order to survive.
I know you don't believe that.
You know who
Saint Christopher is?
They say he carried a child
across a dangerous river.
They got to the other side,
that child revealed himself to be Jesus.
So now Saint Christopher is known as
the patron saint of safe journeys.
I think we've got
to be like him.
We have to believe that every single
child out there is worth saving.
Here.
- Take this.
- Clove...
- No.
- You're on a rough journey right now. Maybe this will help.
Thank you.
You're the
child services people.
I'm the caseworker
you spoke to earlier.
Yes. This is my colleague.
Clove Martinez.
About time you got here.
So is the child injured, hungry?
- Afraid?
- What do you mean?
I didn't hurt him, all right.
I didn't cook breakfast for the kid,
- but he didn't ask for anything.
- Okay, sir. Let's calm down. Okay?
What the fuck you talking about?
I'm calm.
Sir, do not talk
to my colleague like that.
Me and you spoke earlier.
You said that the parents left
the child in your custody, right?
It's just a dad and a kid,
but the dad freaks out, disappears.
Where's the kid now?
Somewhere inside.
I keep him in the basement.
- If I let him up...
- You keep him in the basement?
But he's got a knife.
He tried to hurt me.
All right? What if he tries
to use one of my guns?
You keep guns in the house
with a child?
It's my God damn house.
If you don't like it, you can get
this kid out of my house right now.
- What's the child's name?
- Manny.
Manny.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Come on out, kid.
- Don't yell at the kid, okay?
- I'm not yelling.
I'm not asking. That's an order.
KYLE: Stay right here.
You see him?
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Is that him?
[GASPING]
Manny...
is that knife
to keep you safe?
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
CLOVE: His dad gave it to him
for protection.
Manny, listen.
You can keep the knife.
It's okay, all right?
We're here to help.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
My mom died.
My dad brought me to America.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
He said that
if anything happens,
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Just stay with the man
until he comes back.
- [SPEAKING SPANISH]
- But the man is mean.
Listen, tell him
we're going to do whatever we have to do to
help you to get back to your father, okay?
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
- Okay, come on out.
- [SPEAKING SPANISH]
Christ sake, are you leaving
or what?
Huh? Get this kid out.
[GROANS]
Shut the fuck up.
You understand me?
- I'm not playing with you.
- Kyle, stop.
Calm down.
[GASPS]
I'm calm.
Go, go, go.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEEPS]
Excuse me, sir.
Hi. I don't think repairs
were scheduled for today.
You are correct.
Just a work mix up.
But we're already done.
[GUN FIRES]
Clothes and food is on us,
little man.
You're a hero.
How do you say,
"Little strong man"?
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
[IMITATING AND TRYING
TO SPEAK SPANISH]
[CLOVE CHUCKLES]
That's you.
[REPEATS IN SPANISH]
[CHUCKLES]
Are we gonna let him
keep that knife?
Let's just get him some food.
We'll take care of the knife
in a minute, okay?
- Let's go to Nelson's.
- Clove, no.
- Nelson's is right there, Kyle.
- They're not even open yet.
Come on. He's hungry.
- Send the bill to Sam.
- You know how I feel about Sam.
Ever since I got back,
he calls me weak and a freaking coward.
CLOVE: What happened
to you over there?
You know you can trust me.
[ENGINE STOPS]
It's the worst moment
of my life.
[GUNS FIRING]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
Thank you.
Just breathe. Breathe.
[COUGHING]
Please, please, please.
[GASPING]
[GUNS FIRING]
[GUN FIRING]
[INAUDIBLE]
[HORN HONKS]
KYLE: You're the only person
I've ever told that to.
I am so sorry
you had to experience that.
You know what?
Since we're so close,
let's just get him something to eat.
We'll be in and out.
But you're paying.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[DEVICE BEEPS]
- Can I help you?
- You're the manager?
Yes. My name is Sunshine.
Is there a problem?
I'm Mr. Nelson's press manager.
Can you please do something about them?
I don't want the camera
picking them up.
You want me to tell my employees
to stop doing their jobs?
Well, they're Sam Nelson's
employees, so, yes.
They'll be done and out
of the way by the time we open.
- Eagan.
- Who?
This high school kid Sunny
used to tutor back in the day.
He tells her, he's living in the woods.
He wants her to live with them.
She called the cops.
She never saw him again.
KYLE: Come on, little man.
It couldn't be him.
He disappeared years ago. It's probably
just somebody who looks like him.
She okay though, right?
Yeah.
What's it with the service?
I'm getting no signal.
- I need my phone.
- There are full bars all the time.
- I don't know why our phone...
- You should provide wifi then.
Yeah.
Hey,
- Hi
- Welcome. Hi.
I'm so sorry,
I missed your birthday
- [SPEAKING SPANISH]
- Oh, my God. [SPEAKING SPANISH]
- Good to see you.
- Hey.
We have a hungry young man here.
Oh, well, food will be ready
any time.
You want to just go
wander around?
- Yeah.
- [SPEAKING SPANISH]
WOMAN: Hey, Sunshine, our clepto in
Home Dec is stuffing her pockets again.
Oh, yeah.
I'm getting her this time
Gotcha.
You little shit.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
You and I are gonna have
a little talk.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
I was just putting returns back.
Come with me. Now.
What is happening?
I don't understand.
- You don't understand.
- No.
SUNSHINE: Sit.
Do you know how long I've been
trying to catch you in the act?
What are you talking about?
You're on camera, sweetie.
Now, do I need
to call the police
or are you gonna show me
everything you have on you?
Seriously?
There's more.
I know there's more.
Serial killers, pirate radio,
Halloween...
I don't know.
Sunny and I watched it.
Fun movie.
Definitely not for kids.
Not on my watch.
Nope.
Let me check this rack.
Wow.
The hero always gets the girl.
[MACHINE BEEPS]
Howdy, everyone.
This is the one and only,
Sam Nelson.
May I have all the employees
up front?
SAM OVER PA:
All the employees up front.
Wow.
- Are you gonna fire me.
- Um, yeah.
MAN OVER RADIO:
Hey, Sunshine. You there?
- What's up, John?
- Did you put a lock on the back door?
What lock?
We're about to open the door.
Everybody up front.
Well, look who's here.
[ENGINE ACCELERATING]
Raffles, giveaways, the whole
shebang, same thing we do every year.
I want you on top of your game.
- [GUNS FIRING]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Angel!
[MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[GUNSHOTS CONTINUE]
You got any parents I can call?
I'm a foster kid, all right?
Is that your excuse
for being a thief?
- What the hell?
- Shit.
Rainey, where are you?
- [BEEPING]
- Shit.
Oh.
You okay?
MAN: Back against the wall,
let's go!
Clove? Clove.
- Sam, we're blocked.
- What about the side exit?
Follow me.
Good job, everybody.
Way to to follow orders
Attention shoppers.
Nelson's is now mine.
And you all belong to me.
Doors are packed with C4.
If you try to open them,
you will level this building.
But you can survive all of this
if you do as I say.
Everyone must come to
the front of the store now.
If you hide, we will find you,
and you will be shot.
You hear me, Sam Nelson?
I know you were here.
- Come out, come out, wherever you are Sammy boy.
- No.
You're not going anywhere.
We stay put.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I am also wearing
a suicide vest.
The button in my hand
will detonate everything
if for any reason, my thumb
is raised of his button.
For example, if I'm attacked
or killed.
So be wise and do as I say.
Front of the store.
You have one minute.
What do we do, Sparks?
They're looking for you, Sam.
For all we know, it's to kill you.
Sam.
You're a bargaining tool.
Play ball and they'll let us go.
- Yeah. No, I know.
- No.
Absolutely not.
Yeah, she's right. I can't leave the
employees out there on their own.
Okay.
But stay right next to me.
The moment I think
they're going to shoot,
get out of my way.
Come on. No signal.
We're trapped in here.
We should go.
No, we're staying right here.
The door is reinforced.
- Call 911.
- The line is dead.
Okay.
Something like this
is a good chance
that police are already on their way.
They may even be outside already.
What are you doing?
Look, my wife and my cousin
are out there.
I won't leave the one safe place
we have if there's a chance of me
getting them in here
with us, okay?
- Okay? You understand?
- Uh-huh.
Okay.
[GROANS]
You ready, okay?
- Where's Sunny?
- She's somewhere in the store hiding.
She's here. Okay.
Don't die, please.
I'm not gonna let you die, okay?
Stay with me, Clove.
Stay with me.
MAN: You.
Move over there.
Now.
Stop trying to move. Now!
Get against the wall.
I told you to stop trying.
[SCREAMS]
Don't be shy.
Come on down.
Come on. Join the family.
[GROANS]
Kyle, you have to save Manny.
I'm gonna get him out of here.
[CLOVE GROANS]
Come out.
Manny, no!
[GUN FIRING]
Let's go.
I'm not leaving her.
- Move.
- No... Manny.
Let's go!
[GROANS]
Faster. Let's go.
Everything okay?
Yeah, some little shit
ran into the store.
- He was scared for his life...
- Shut up.
Angel.
Just stay right there, okay?
I don't see anybody.
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- MIKKI: Sunshine.
- Sunshine, please.
- Mikki?
Please. [SOBBING]
Thanks. Hurry.
[SNIFFS]
Come here.
You're okay.
You're safe.
Where is Sam Nelson?
Our great Congressman,
Sam Nelson.
The multimillionaire founder
of Nelson's Corporation.
Businessman Sam Nelson.
Loyal friend, father,
grandfather and foodie.
Step aside.
Sparks, it's okay. It's okay.
It's okay, Sparks.
[CHUCKLES]
Congressman.
Right this way.
Go with Sophie.
EAGAN: Where's the cameraman?
The one in black.
- Start recording now.
- What is this, God damn it?
- It's confession time, Congressman.
- What? Confess what?
You're going to look into
that camera and tell the world
that you framed
your business partner.
I don't have a business partner.
You admit to what you did
or all these people die.
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
- Tell us about Luther Raize.
- Luther Raize?
Jesus, he embezzled money
from me.
I haven't thought about
that loser in 20 years. [GROANS]
- What are you doing?
- Sparks.
Please just think
about my daughter.
[GROANS]
I can't risk Sam getting killed.
Stop.
Sparks, no!
Back up.
Come on.
Come on. You want to blow
this place up?
You're bluffing.
Only one way
to find out, bodyguard.
Daddy.
Sparks, put the gun down.
- He's lying, Sam.
- Sparks, please.
No just...
- [GUNS FIRING]
- [SCREAMING]
Please, please.
How many more people
are gonna die because of you?
Sunny.
- Rainey.
- RAINEY: Where are you?
Rainey, thank God you're okay.
We're in the security office.
You have to get here.
- I can't.
- EAGAN: Let's go.
SUNSHINE: Rainey.
One of you is dying next.
You.
I got no problem with you.
What? I can't hear you.
What'd you say?
I ain't got no problem with you.
Good.
You don't mind dying if Sam
Nelson doesn't start talking.
What's going on?
Sunshine's in the
security office.
Ready for your confession?
MIKKI: What's he doing?
Probably delivering
his manifesto.
Psychotic narcissists
love that shit.
Exactly one hour from now,
a series of blasts will bring
this place to the ground...
unless I see on the news,
a prosecutor
bring charges against
Congressman Sam Nelson.
Kyle.
Something you know?
[GROANS]
As a sign of good faith.
I will release some hostages.
But if anyone tries to enter or
negotiate with me, I will kill everyone.
Clocks are ticking.
You got that?
Yeah, it recorded.
All right. Here's the deal.
Some of you are gonna go home.
Some of you are going to stay
here and help me. Any volunteers?
All right.
You all are staying.
You get that recording
to the police today.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Move!
That means you too.
Nice and slow.
Take Sam and the others
to electronics.
Wait.
- I know you.
- Why are you doing this?
I know you. Don't I?
You're the black stepson with a cute little
girl who got Sam Nelson the minority vote.
Me and my daughter, don't have anything
to do with Sam and his politics.
Tell me is that Mexican boy
he yours too?
- I work for Child Protective Services.
- Kids don't need protection.
A man like you came for me
when I was a boy,
and I wouldn't let him take me.
I'm a product of chaos.
And violence is the only voice
that a man hears.
You know that. I know that.
So I take it this ain't
your first time doing this.
[CHUCKLES]
Come here.
- Come on, baby. Just stay with your daddy.
- Now.
Daddy's gonna work it out.
Why don't you read this?
"Remembered?"
Past tense?
I want you to give that
to the police.
Today is your lucky day.
You both get to go home.
Everyone back. Back.
[SIREN WAILING]
That recording that needs to get out to the
police. So make sure you get a copy fast.
Sir, listen.
I get it. You have a message.
Surely we can deal
for Mr. Nelson's safety.
I've had criminal clients.
- I've gotten very good re...
- You work for Sam?
I'm a personal media and communications
manager, not a Nelson's employee.
Because now, you belong to me.
Move. Let's go.
You're next. Let's go.
You. Move.
Listen.
Everything's gonna be all right.
I need you to go outside
with this woman.
She's gonna keep you safe, okay?
What about Grandpa?
I got him.
I got everybody. I'm gonna go back
in there, make sure everybody's okay.
- Please.
- SHANE: Let's go, slow.
Take care of her for me.
Look at that.
Jesus, Kyle.
I swear that guy
looks like my CPS officer.
Y'all got one out.
One out.
Come on, Rainey.
Where are you?
I need to know you're okay.
How do you know so much
about people?
I'm a psychologist.
I moved back here to
be with Rainey while
she finishes veterinary school.
I tried to give it
a shot here, but...
I knew it was a long shot but...
MIKKI: It must be hard.
Yeah.
But I'd do anything for her.
Did my granddaughter get out?
Of course she did.
Did I? No.
What? Are you kidding me?
You're one of my employees.
I was never one of your slaves.
All right, team.
This is the outsourcing
part of our adventure.
Before I send you home,
I got a little shopping
I need you all to complete.
Let the work set you free.
Let's go. Start movin'.
Turn the TV on.
Oh, the lesbo.
The one with Sunshine.
So tell me,
where is our little Sunshine?
What's that little secret
you're hiding from me?
You are the sunshine of my life.
Didn't take you
as a Stevie Wonder fan.
It's a Sinatra song.
I stand corrected.
Well, if you wanna
keep standing,
you better tell me where she is.
I swear.
I don't know where she is.
I know you've been talking
to her in the security office.
And I know it's reinforced.
We'll get her to come out
one way or another.
No?
You're staying here with me.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
The scene here at the Nelson
Store is escalating rapidly.
While police
are still securing the area,
demands have already
been received from inside,
which suggests this very dangerous
situation could come to an end quickly...
You two go check the perimeter.
I know the kid's still out there
and I wanna make sure no one else
is trying to get their way out.
What we do if we find someone?
Kill him.
If you don't have the balls to do
it, hold them till I get there.
[SOFTLY] Showtime.
WOMAN ON TV:
...act of terrorism
or is it the violence
of disgruntled employees?
To answer that, we go to a
video that has just surfaced...
Our moment of truth, Sam.
SAM ON TV:
My name is Sam Nelson.
Fifteen years ago, I framed my friend
and business partner, Luther Raize.
He was an innocent man,
but I made sure he spent most of
the rest of his life in prison.
And that was only the first
of my many crimes.
[WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
ON TV]
WOMAN ON TV:
Police are telling us
that there may be
up to three gunmen inside.
- What do we do with all this stuff?
- Shh.
EAGAN ON TV: Exactly one hour from
now, a series of blasts
will bring this place
to the ground.
- So how'd we do?
- Unless I see on the news...
Good work, team.
...bring charges against
Congressman Sam Nelson...
Now...
you take those.
I'd like you to tie her up.
[EXHALES]
I'd like you to tie
your friend there too.
Mmm.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN FIRES]
What are you doing, asshole?
Give yourself up.
You got it coming, old man.
- [GUN FIRES]
- [GASPS]
JEB: Next time I won't miss.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I knew something was up,
but he's crazier than I thought.
Jeb! What are you doing?
[SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Why are you all doing this?
We're gonna burn this place to the
ground for what Sam did to Luther.
So you're all doing
all of this for Luther?
- Why?
- JEB: He saved us.
Don't move.
[GROANS]
Don't move or I'll shoot.
JEB: Do it!
Oh, my God.
You can't do it.
[JEB GROANS]
[GROANING]
You had it coming, old man.
SUNSHINE ON RADIO:
Can you hear me?
Kyle, it's Sunshine.
- Sunshine?
- Yes.
Sunshine, where are you?
SUNSHINE: We're in the security office.
We're safe.
- Who's we?
- Me, me, Mikki Foss.
You know,
Mikki "Sticky Fingers."
You all see me right now?
MIKKI: Totally.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
Because all the wrong people
get all the best things in life.
Nice jobs.
The most money.
Women.
And people like you get all
the preference and opportunity
while hardworking white men
get used up and die.
Preference?
I go to vet school,
I'm in debt,
and I work at Nelson's.
Not anymore.
I'm gonna take everything he's
got if it's the last thing I do.
RAINEY: If it's
the last thing you do.
You wanna get back at him.
Not at us.
- Let us go.
- Not yet.
I want Sunshine
to come and get you.
KYLE: Listen to me.
I need you to stay right there.
Don't move from that office.
Hear me?
MIKKI: Got it.
[SOFTLY] Kyle, Kyle.
One of them
is coming toward you.
What? Where?
MIKKI: Two aisles ahead of you.
Okay, get off the mic right now.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING]
[GAGS]
[PANTING]
Damn, he's a badass.
Yeah.
Everything's going
according to plan.
I know. And we go out before
anyone knows what happened.
TERRY: I wanna get back
to the farm.
Stay true to the family.
Farm it is.
Let's bring Jeb and Shane
with us.
Where are they?
SOPHIE: Will this do any good?
You got balls.
SUNSHINE: Kyle, we have to be
careful now, more than ever.
KYLE: I know, I know.
Where are they?
Electronics.
Please tell me Clove got out.
I'm so sorry, Sunny.
She's gone.
I promise I tried.
[GASPING]
Sunny, listen to me.
[SOBBING]
KYLE: We have to get
everybody out.
Now.
He's gonna blow himself up.
There's explosives
all around the store.
We only have 30 minutes.
- [SOBBING]
- I need you.
We need you.
KYLE: Hello?
Sunny.
He's gonna kill my stepdad
and everyone connected to him.
He's making some statement.
[EXHALES]
He's not gonna blow himself up.
KYLE: What do you mean?
Suicides don't take
cash and jewelry.
It's time for phase three.
Everybody, up!
Good.
I see you're listening!
You, you come over here!
What about those two?
No, you two stay.
He made them take
money from the registers,
jewelry from the cases.
If he's saying this is a suicide
bombing, he's full of shit.
Kyle, wait. No.
- What's going on?
- SUNSHINE: You have to go back. Hide.
Stop!
What the fuck
are you all looking at?
[GUN FIRING]
He's coming right at you.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
MIKKI: He's in Home Goods.
Kyle, they're hiding
at the back.
No one can see you unless you
walk right on top of them.
[WHISTLES]
[GUNS FIRING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELECTRICITY POWERS DOWN]
What's going on?
Police cut the power.
It doesn't change anything.
Eagan, is this the little shit
you've been looking for?
Found him
hiding around the corner.
You run away from me again
and I will kill everyone.
You run, boom!
You got me?
Don't let him out of your sight.
Let's go.
Now!
Mikki, can you hear me?
What's going on right now?
MIKKI: They're headed off
to the storerooms.
Move it.
[GASPING] I'm helping you.
Don't leave me in there
with everybody else. I just...
Get inside.
[WHIMPERING]
[BEEPS]
Boom.
Sparks?
Man, what you doing?
How did you get my gun?
Long story.
Shoot them.
What?
That bomb vest is bullshit.
I've seen suicide bombers.
He's lying.
But what about
all the other explosives?
Ones on the doors
look legit,
but you're not gonna be
shooting the doors.
[SIGHS]
Sparks, if the vest is fake,
why are they doing all this?
Your guess is as good as mine.
Maybe they're only intending
on killing Sam...
but you could take him out
before they hurt anybody else.
The neck
or the back of the head.
No.
Once a Marine, always a Marine.
Whatever happened to you
in Afghanistan,
you're still a fighter
and you still know how to shoot.
- I'm not doing it.
- Look, look.
Enough of your pussy
liberal shit, brother.
The world is not safe.
How many bullets you got left?
Empty.
One in the chamber.
They sell ammo here?
You know
you get a discount, right?
You may not believe this
but Sam does love you.
Always has.
SUNSHINE: Kyle, we need you.
Kyle, are you still there?
Sunny, wait.
What's going on?
- SUNSHINE: They're headed off towards the storeroom.
- [GUNS FIRING]
Go. Go.
Let's go, soldier. Go.
Go, soldier.
He got away. I'm getting by.
What is this?
Look at my leg.
[GROANING]
Bring me Sunshine or you die.
Where the hell's Shane?
He's either dead or he's hiding.
Find him.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
KYLE: Sunshine, it's me, Kyle.
Are you okay?
No.
I'm sorry about Clove.
It's okay.
I gotta get us out of here.
Where is everybody?
Psycho locked them up
inside the storage room.
He still has Nelson and Rainey
in Electronics.
- And that boy you were with.
- Manny?
- He's got Manny?
- SUNSHINE: Mmm-hmm.
I know you're listening to me,
you sick son of a bitch.
[HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Yeah, I hear you, little piggy.
And pretty soon,
I'm gonna blow this house down.
Tell you what.
You bring me Sunshine
and I'll give you
two of these three.
What do you say?
Me?
What does he want with me?
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
He looks familiar to me.
He's taking money.
Means he has to get out of here
before the bombs go off, right?
Okay, so what do we do?
We tell him to go fuck himself.
Listen to her. She's smart.
I promised Clove
I'd save that little boy.
I gave her my word.
That's all I got.
Kyle...
Please get Rainey out.
I'll handle it.
I'll go get
all three of them out.
Y'all get the rest.
Let's do it
Hey, brother.
Go fuck yourself!
You're pathetic. No one will even
remember your name in a month.
Shut up. You're wrong.
I'm making a statement here
that's gonna outlive us all.
Oh, it's time
to say goodbye, Sam.
No, wait, please!
Boom!
That's for Luther.
No one is even gonna recognize
your corpse, Congressman.
How's that for a legacy?
After you're gone and
everyone thinks that I'm dead,
I will be crawling
through a tunnel to freedom
so that I can survive
and strike again.
Because I am going to destroy
everything you love, Sam.
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
- Watch out.
- [SCREAMS]
[MANNY SHOUTING IN SPANISH]
[GUN FIRES]
- SUNSHINE: Shit...
- [GUNS FIRING]
Come here. Get down.
[GUNS FIRING]
What do we do?
- Find the hostages and get them out of here.
- Okay.
[GUNS FIRING]
JEB: Where are you gonna run to?
Give me that, son.
Give me the gun. Come on.
Let's go.
[GUNS FIRING]
- Sunny, can you hear? Where are you?
- Come on.
SUNSHINE: Rain, we're going
to the east exit.
[SCREAMS]
Go ahead and shoot,
you'll all be charcoal anyway.
SAM: I've had enough bad press
for the day.
- Come on, let's get it.
- RAINEY: You can't just leave him!
Yes, we can. Come on.
[PANTING] Shit.
This isn't one of ours.
Okay. Um, I need something
to cut this with. Like a...
- I don't know.
- Here, here, here. How about this?
Oh, okay.
Hey, hey.
What is that? What is that?
It is a bomb.
Be careful.
Okay. Come on, guys.
Let's go. Let's go!
Everybody, out. Everybody, out.
Just keep going toward the door!
Toward the...
Okay. Come on, let's go.
[WHIRRING]
JEB: Given up?
Tired of running?
You're out of bullets.
[GUN CLICKS]
You had it coming.
I told you.
[SCREAMING]
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
- Sunny.
- [GASPS] Rain.
Oh, my God.
[SOBBING]
Shh.
Are you guys okay?
Yes, we're okay. Yes.
KYLE: Rainey?
Where's Manny?
He still has him.
[STAMMERS] What are you doing?
It's my job to protect him.
You understand that, right?
Go on, make your mother proud.
But do it fast, God damn it.
Jesus. Now what?
We need something
to pry the door open.
Huh? Well, inside that door,
are all the tools in the world.
Go get one.
[SOFTLY] Manny?
Manny?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
TERRY: He's with Eagan.
He's innocent.
He's got nothing
to do with this.
TERRY: You're Sam's son.
You brought him here.
That makes him a part of this.
I know you don't like Sam.
It was Luther that was guilty.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
Uncle Luther did it.
Sam put him up to it
and that makes him guilty.
Uncle Luther?
- That's your family?
- Yeah, Uncle Luther.
Rotted away in prison
for 18 years.
I had to raise myself,
Egan had to raise himself,
and somebody's gotta pay.
Right now that's you.
[GUN FIRING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[HAMMERING]
- Get that door open!
- They're trying.
Just shut up!
You're not in charge.
- [GASPS]
- She may not be in charge, but I am.
[MIKKI CHUCKLES]
You are so cool.
[HAMMERING]
So all the precision tools
in the world in this store
and you pick a hammer.
Nice touch.
KYLE: Sunshine, it's Raize.
- What?
- KYLE: The leader, it's Eagan Raize.
- Luther's son?
- Kyle, are you sure it's Eagan?
KYLE: Clove thought she saw him
in the parking lot.
Now one of his gunmen
confirmed it.
[GRUNTING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MANNY GRUNTING]
[SPEAKS SPANISH]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
Stop it!
Shall we try someone
with a brain now?
Kyle, where are you?
Kyle?
R-A-I-Z-E.
- [LOCK OPENS]
- Narcissists always use their own names.
We've got about ten minutes
until this place blows.
I have to help him.
You'll need this.
Let's go.
Where's the little boy?
I don't know.
Dead maybe?
Like your cousin?
You killed Terry?
He had it coming.
You know this place
is about to blow up, don't you?
Tick-tock.
What?
[GRUNTING]
SUNSHINE: Eagan, stop!
You said you wanna see me?
Here I am.
Sunny...
You look so beautiful.
I know you're angry and afraid.
I have a good escape plan.
You don't need to do this.
Everyone got out. It's over.
I want you to come with me.
Okay.
Just let me get Kyle out first.
No, you're coming with me now.
Go to hell.
[GUN FIRES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING]
Don't come any closer!
I earned this.
Earn this, you piece of shit!
SUNSHINE: Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You okay?
Are you okay? Rainey?
- [GROANS]
- Oh.
KYLE: Manny?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Come here.
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
Time to die, you little shit.
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's over.
[GUN FIRES]
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
Let's get out of here.
[BOMB EXPLODING]
[POLICE RADIO
CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[SIREN WAILING]
Authorities are saying the
evidence against Luther Raize
is ironclad, indisputable,
and Sam Nelson had
no wrongdoing in the matter.
This was not
an act of terrorism.
I'm telling you,
the guy's a lunatic.
I mean, the idea that he had
some great message is bullshit.
I mean, look, the guy
just wanted to steal money
from my business and he...
Are you gonna say something?
Yeah, Sam. I quit.
This was full of money
ten minutes ago.
I guess this means
we're unemployed.
Yeah.
No more Nelson's.
So what if you opened up
your own practice?
With what money?
I've been doing a little saving.
Mikki "Sticky Fingers."
- You don't see me steal this.
- She has a point.
You're putting that back, right?
Maybe?
[CHUCKLES]
All right.
Everything looks good.
Vitals check out.
You're cleared.
- Thank you.
- ANGEL: There he is.
Baby.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Did you save them, Daddy?
I gave you and Clove
my word I would.
I did the best I could.
Looks like maybe
you've found your purpose.
I guess I just made it up
along the way.
You know,
you should come by sometime.
Maybe me and Angel can put a little
something on the grill for you.
- What do you say, Grandpa?
- I'll bring the steaks.
Angel. Come here, come here.
I want you to say hi to Manny.
Manny, this is Angel.
Angel, this is Manny.
Hi, Manny.
Manny helped save
your dad's life.
I owe this little man
everything.
His father has been lost
and, um,
I'm gonna go to the courts and see if
they'll let him stay with us for a while.
Would you be okay with that?
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
We're good.
Okay.
See, I told you
private school would pay off.
Somebody's gotta
teach me Spanish soon.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull