(dramatic music)
(tense music)
(train whistle blowing)
(speaking foreign language)
(gun firing)
(gun fires)
(speaking foreign language)
(guns firing)
(explosion booms)
(man yells)
(explosions boom)
(explosions booming)
(speaking foreign language)
(explosion booms)
(people shouting)
(grunting)
(people chattering)
- All right, hold it!
Listen up.
There's no more
choppers at the airport.
Now get us out of here.
You guys make sure
you look around.
You don't leave nothing
for Charlie, okay?
(subdued music)
(people chattering)
(speaking foreign language)
(suspenseful music)
(man grunts)
(man laughing)
(people chattering)
(gun firing)
(dramatic music)
(yells)
(speaking foreign language)
- Come on!
(guns firing)
Move, move, move!
(speaking foreign language)
(explosion booms)
(gun firing)
(guns firing)
(speaking foreign language)
(explosions booming)
- Jimmy T!
Come on!
Go, go, go, go!
(speaking foreign language)
- Gonzo, you all set
with the code books?
- Yeah.
Let's get this stuff
down to Mr. Henderson.
Help me with this stuff.
Let's go.
- This makes a man
sicker than shit.
That the last of it, Gonzo?
- Almost, Chief.
- You still pulling out
at 18:00, Mr. Henderson?
- If Ben has set the charges
by then, we're out of here.
- Go fetch the rest, Gonzo.
- Aye-aye, Chief.
- Thomas, if I find
anything readable
in there when it's
done, it's your ass.
- Aye-aye, Chief.
- I don't know.
I was getting to like it here.
Goddamn it.
- Well, let's just make
sure we're not the last two
to die in this hell hole, okay?
- [Chief] Aye-aye to that, Sam.
(tense music)
- I lost my glasses.
- Hey, come on, you guys!
Let's go!
- I wanna go home.
- Come on, come on.
- Did you check him?
(explosion booms)
- [Soldier] What the?
What are they doing?
- Come on!
Come back!
(tense music)
(woman crying)
(speaking foreign language)
(man yelling)
(explosions booming)
(guns firing)
- [Soldier] Incoming!
(explosions booming)
You mothers!
(men shouting)
(guns firing)
(explosions booming)
- [Soldier] I need a stretcher!
(guns firing)
- Three-five, Binh.
Give me Three-Five.
- Come in.
Come in Three-Five.
Come in.
(explosions booming)
(man yelling)
- Where's our goddamn air cover?
(guns firing)
- That's it!
Hey, pull back!
Pull back!
(men shouting)
- [Soldier] Fall back!
Start getting down!
Get under cover!
- Tango Victor Three-Five,
this is Bravo Three-Seven.
Come in Three-Five.
Come in.
- Go ahead, Three-Seven.
This is Three-Five.
- I need a medevac, Three-Five.
And where the
hell's my air cover?
- Request temporarily
denied, Three-Seven.
No can do.
- Three-Five, this is Holland.
I've got wounded up here and
I can't hang on much longer.
You're gonna have to
pack up 40 more body bags
if I don't get some
help up here and now.
- [Soldier] Zebra One,
this is Alpha Tango.
We've been overrun.
I repeat, we've been overrun.
The enemy's taken
over the village.
- [Soldier] Move it, damn it!
I said, move it, soldier!
- I don't need this shit.
- [Soldier] Let's go!
Get the lead out, damn it!
- I don't need this shit!
(helicopter blades whirring)
- In my estimation, now's
the time to finish 'em off,
but my hands are
ties on this one.
A Company from 101st Armored
Division's on the move
and we're gonna have to move
way faster than this, Captain.
VC have taken the city of Wet.
They took the radio station
and they blasted the
Presidential Palace.
Counting on you to get
Bravo Company out of here.
Let's go, Captain.
Good luck.
Let's get moving.
- Their defenses
are in shambles.
Their morale, broken.
Very soon the South will fall.
(men cheering)
- [Soldier] To victory!
- Are we ready to
march through Saigon?
(men cheering)
- [Soldier] Bash anybody
who stands in your way!
To victory!
(subdued music)
(horn honks)
(people chattering)
(horn honking)
- Come on, you guys.
Move it!
Let's go!
I know if this captain's
gonna wait for us.
- I know.
- Come on!
- But I don't think
they'll wait for us.
- They better wait for us.
Otherwise, I don't know
how the hell we're gonna
get out of here
and up to Saigon.
(horn honks)
(siren wailing)
(people chattering)
(horn honking)
- [Soldier] Stop!
Stop!
- What's going on?
- [Soldier] The road is closed.
You cannot pass this way.
- [Woman] Fuck!
- Where are we going?
- Just keep going straight.
We've gotta get
to HQ to find Len.
- HQ?
- Yeah, maybe he can help us.
- Okay.
- Could you just move?
Can't you go faster?
(horn honking)
Back it up!
Move it!
Can't you back it up?
I mean, just move!
What are doing?
Get away!
No, get away!
Let's go!
Stop it!
What are they doing?
Just stop!
Move, move!
Just stop it!
Get your hand out of the window!
- [Man] We've gotta
get out of here.
- Leave us alone!
We're not doing anything!
Stop!
- Come on.
Come with me.
Come on!
(speaking foreign language)
(people shouting)
Come on, this way.
Come on.
Hurry, hurry!
Go!
Inside, inside!
(banging on door)
- Children, go to your rooms.
(wolf whistles)
- Hey, baby.
How about some action?
- Welcome to the Church
of Our Lady of Lord.
- Thank you.
He's a...
He's a pretty smooth talker.
- Mickey picked up quite a lot
from his mother's clientele.
Are you a photographer?
- No.
Actually, I'm down here
shooting a documentary
on Len Jordan.
Now we're just hoping
he can help us get out.
But first, we have
to get up to HQ.
- God works in mysterious ways.
I believe we can
help each other.
- Let's go home, boys.
Let's head due south.
Let's move.
Let's go!
(subdued music)
- Five, four, three, two.
(explosions booming)
- 7th Fleet for you, Sam.
- Jehovah, this is Able Team.
- [Man On Radio] Able
Team, this is Jehovah.
You are instructed to
go back to Soc Trang
to pick up Len Jordan.
Repeat, pick up Len Jordan.
- Roger.
We've gotta turn around
and go get Len Jordan
out of Soc Trang.
- Fuck.
Let him grab a chopper.
- He's bringing full dossiers
of all the locals
that helped us.
- Can he hang on
until we get there?
- He's gonna have to.
- I hope he has
enough fuel up there.
Fuck, we've got hardly
enough gas and ammo as it is.
- What the hell, Gonzo?
We did come here to
fight a war, right?
- Fuck that hero shit.
- Let's go get him.
- All right.
Probably take us a
day to make it to sea.
They're be a chopper there.
Hopefully, the Navy
will send a ship.
Take us back to the real world.
(speaking foreign language)
(tense music)
(engine sputtering)
- [Man] Hello, GI.
Hello.
Hello, GI.
(guns firing)
- Shit!
(men yell)
(speaking foreign language)
(explosions booming)
- Spin it, Chief.
(guns firing)
(explosion booms)
- Let's hope your Len
Jordan is a miracle worker.
(kid crying)
(explosions booming)
(guns firing)
(speaking foreign language)
- There's Len.
Follow him.
(tense music)
- Something's up ahead.
- [Man] GI!
GI!
- [Woman] Hello, GI.
Hello.
- Binh.
(people shouting)
- South China's about to fall!
(explosion booms)
(guns firing)
(explosions booming)
- Don't cry.
It'll be all right.
(speaking foreign language)
(explosions booming)
(kids screaming)
(explosion booms)
- We lost the other truck.
(speaking foreign language)
- [Sam] Jordan, it's a
pleasure to meet you.
- Yeah, you too, Henderson.
- I thought there'd
be more of you.
- Had a little trouble
with the trucks.
(explosion booms)
(kids screaming)
- [Woman] Okay, get the kids.
Get 'em, come on.
- [Man] Okay, come on.
- All right, kids.
Come on.
- Come on, come on.
All right, let's go.
Len!
- Mary.
- I've got these
Amaratian kids with me.
- Yeah?
- Their fathers are
all in the States
and you know how the Vietnamese
feel about these kids.
I mean, what do you
think's gonna happen
when the NVA takes over?
- Well, Mary.
- No, no, no, no.
Wait, this is great.
This is the ending
to your story.
I mean, just think about it.
The last American to leave
and he takes all
these kids with him.
- Oh, Mary, I'd
really like to help.
I really would, but.
- It's okay.
We can go ahead and
take 'em with us.
It's gonna slow us
down a little bit.
We'll have to move
now, but it'll be okay.
- Good.
Who are you?
- I'm Sam Henderson,
the skipper.
How you doing?
- Mary.
Fine.
So, it's okay?
- Come on, kids.
Move out.
(subdued music)
(explosion booms)
(kids scream)
(dramatic music)
(explosions booming)
- [Binh] Come on.
Hurry up.
Inside.
(dramatic music)
(speaking foreign language)
(tense music)
(guns firing)
(dramatic music)
- Hey, you're
gonna have to move.
I can't see a thing.
- Just another minute.
The light's really
good right now.
(engine revs)
Goddamn it!
I told you I'd be
just another minute.
- Look, I am probably blowing
my chance at immortality here,
but we've got a job to do.
It's called get the
hell out of here
and your career is not a
high priority on my list.
All right?
- Hey.
Why don't you just chill out?
Stay out of his face.
Go back and film the
nun, and those kids,
and stuff for a while.
Okay?
(dramatic music)
What's going on
here, Lieutenant?
- We've gotta go
back another way.
- We gotta get the hell
out of here right now.
The fastest way is
straight down the river.
- Well, ordinarily
I'd agree with you,
but on the way back up here we
ran across some NVA sampans.
If they know we're around,
they're probably waiting right
around the corner for us.
- You know, I'm still the
senior officer here, son.
- No.
- What the hell you mean, no?
- You're not the
senior officer here.
Look, Jordan.
I know you've been doing
a bang-up job around here,
but you've gotta
remember one thing.
You're ex-military.
The Comm 7th Fleet sent me
back here to pick you up
and I gotta get you out.
If anything happens to you,
they're gonna hang it on me.
So, we're gonna do
things my way, okay?
- They're gonna hang
your ass, Henderson.
(explosion booms)
- Off starboard!
- [Mary] Help me!
(guns firing)
(dramatic music)
(kids crying)
(explosions booming)
(kids screaming)
- Chief!
Chief!
- Yeah.
- Check the port bow, quick.
- Here you go.
- How many, motherfuckers?
You want me to puke?
Turkey loaf or nothing.
- Gonzales, why don't you go
see if we have any turkey loaf?
- We'll see.
- You make me a movie
star in Hollywood?
- It's not for Hollywood.
- You got cigarette?
- [Mary] How old are you?
- Old enough.
I'm like seven.
Too bad.
- [Gonzales] Here.
- Hey, good feature, huh?
Hurry up.
- So, you're name's Mickey.
- Real name's Quang.
Chase used to call me
Mickey, like Mickey Mouse.
- Do you know your father?
- Ma say his name's Bill.
He's come from Minnesota.
- Maybe we can
help you find him.
- [Mickey] Minnesota
is close to California?
- [Mary] No.
- Forget it.
I want California,
Hollywood, Disney Land.
- Animals and kids, huh?
- Yeah, there's one
back there that can give
Dennis the Menace a
run for his money.
Hey.
Hey, you guys.
You thirsty?
Here's some water.
Hey, Henderson.
I'm gonna hand you my camera,
but don't get it wet, okay?
Lieutenant Henderson, what's
your opinion of Len Jordan
and his private war
in the Mekong Delta?
- I'm sorry, what's
the question?
- What is your
opinion of Len Jordan
and his private war
in the Mekong Delta?
- Uh.
Well, I guess it
takes a lot of guts
to resign your commission and
take on the war by yourself.
A lot of people think
that if the top brass
would've listened to Len Jordan,
South Vietnam would
come out on top.
- Um.
I think something just bit me.
- What?
- There's a lot of these things.
- Probably leeches.
- Leeches?
Can't you just be careful?
- Would you just hold still?
We only have one more.
Hold on.
- They're the most God-awful
things I've ever seen.
- You're welcome.
- Thanks.
- I've gotta get back to work.
- Hey.
You better now, kiddo?
Don't worry about it, Mary.
I've seen real strong
men come undone
when they run into those things.
- Well, it doesn't make me
feel any less humiliated.
- Aw, come on.
Cheer up.
- What's the matter?
- It's a little public around
here right now, you know?
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
I'll just wait till
dark before attacking.
- That's better.
(tense music)
I figure we ought to
make pretty good time
after it gets dark.
Won't be able to tell us from
the rest of the refugees.
You know, I was thinking.
About 10 clicks down this river,
there's an old special
ops cache we used to have.
Got gas, ammo, guns.
We ought to pull in there.
- Sounds good.
(tense music)
(kids laughing)
- Henderson.
- Yeah.
- We got a welcoming
party up ahead.
You listen to me.
Drop me and the
boys off down river.
You go back, draw their fire,
we'll come in from behind.
- What makes you so sure?
- Just a hunch.
I know what the hell
I'm talking about.
- Okay, Chief.
Take us in.
(suspenseful music)
(speaking foreign language)
(explosion booms)
(dramatic music)
(guns firing)
- Hold your fire!
(grunting)
(gun firing)
(punches thudding)
(guns firing)
(soldier yells)
(tense music)
There he is.
Okay, let's get
out of here, Chief.
(subdued music)
- I was so worried about you.
- (chuckles) I don't know why.
I always land on my feet.
- My camera was ruined.
It doesn't matter.
As long as you're okay.
What's gonna happen to us?
- What do you mean?
- We've meant so
much to each other.
I just don't want it to end.
- It doesn't have to, honey.
I'll be back with the
wife and kids, I'm sure.
But when I come to Los Angeles,
will you still be there for me?
- That's all?
- Mary, you know
I'm a family man.
- So, I'm not good enough
for your image, huh?
- Baby, don't.
(kids chattering)
Well, there you go.
5,000 rounds of 50 caliber ammo.
There's five grand
more back there.
- The way we went through
all the ammo getting here,
I figured if we got into another
firefight, we'd be history.
(speaking foreign language)
(tense music)
- Hi.
- Hey, Sam.
What do you think about this?
- I like it.
All right, grab what you can.
Let's get out of here.
Come on.
Now.
- What the hell do
you think you're doing
going around scaring?
- You're making too much
noise in the jungle.
I could've been Charlie.
- But you really just like
showing my mistakes, don't you?
- It's kind of fun.
- I can't do anything.
I can't steer a boat,
I can't shoot a gun.
Without my camera, I can't
even record this damn thing.
- Look, in wartime,
people have a habit of
rising to the occasion.
But do what you have to
do and you'll do it well.
- Lieutenant, what...
Could you tell me what you
really think of Len Jordan?
- My name is Sam.
And you can forget
the lieutenant stuff
because I'm trying to get used
to being a civilian again.
- You're avoiding my question.
- I know.
(suspenseful music)
- What the hell?
I wasn't doing anything, turkey.
- Hey, what the hell are
you doing with these?
- Nobody else wanted them.
- You'll die of lung
cancer before you're 30.
- 30?
It's a long way off.
- Hey, you know something?
It gets there a lot
faster than you think.
- Give back my Salems.
- You believe this kid?
Oh, what the hell.
There's a war on.
Here, but you only
get one at a time.
(tense music)
- What's that?
- You tell me and
we'll both know.
(gun firing)
(dramatic music)
- Sister, get the
kids on the boat, now!
Move, come on!
Let's go!
(guns firing)
(explosion booms)
(explosions booming)
(speaking foreign language)
- Mary, get to the boat.
Go on, move.
(gun firing)
(explosion booms)
(speaking foreign language)
(Mary grunts)
I'll get her.
(guns firing)
Okay, move.
(gun firing)
(men yelling)
- [Mary] Mickey!
- Let's get the
hell out of here!
Come on!
(speaking foreign language)
(guns firing)
(men yelling)
(kids laughing)
Hey.
- Children, stop that.
Come on, let's go.
(tense music)
- Can't wait till we
hit those sea breezes.
- I just hope the Navy
hasn't pulled out.
- How could they?
I mean, especially since
we have a war hero onboard.
- Back home I don't
think people give a damn
about this war anymore.
I've got a feeling the Navy
brass feels the same way.
Even about war heroes.
- I...
I really want them out.
- I know.
♪ Amazing Grace, how
sweet the sound ♪
- Hey, Gonzo, I saw a dog.
A big dog.
- Yeah, right.
- You.
- I remember, that was you.
(both laughing)
- Doggie. (laughs)
♪ I once was lost
and now I'm found ♪
- [Mary] It's okay.
Don't cry.
Come on.
(kid sobbing)
♪ Amazing Grace, how
sweet the sound ♪
♪ Who saved a wretch like me
- Shh, it's okay.
- [Chief] Oop, oop,
that's this one.
- Good to see 'em
having fun, isn't it?
- First time I've seen
him have a good time
since his kid died.
(helicopter blades whirring)
(dramatic music)
- Chopper.
NVA!
(gun firing)
(kids screaming)
- [Mary] Down below!
(guns firing)
(explosions booming)
(explosion booms)
- Yeah!
(subdued music)
♪ Amazing Grace, how
sweet the sound ♪
♪ That saved a wretch like me
♪ I once was lost
♪ But now I'm found
♪ T'was blind, but now I see
♪ Amazing Grace, how
sweet the sound ♪
♪ That saved a wretch like me
♪ I once was lost
♪ But now I'm found
♪ T'was blind, but now I see
- How's it going?
- I think we're in
the homestretch,
but there may be a catch.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, right here.
We're gonna have to pass
under the Duling Bridge
before we get out to the Delta.
- That's the last choke point
before they can bottle us up.
- I reckon you can count on it.
- Well, let's check it out.
- We're gonna have to
get in a little closer
while we still have
some light to see by.
- I'll send a couple of my boys.
- I don't know.
We're gonna need
a demolitions man.
Gonzales, well, he's an expert
in what we're gonna need.
- Then do it.
- All of the kids have
marks on their arm.
Big, big scars.
Hey, you listen to me?
I'm telling you a story.
- Well, it's you and
me in the barrel.
(suspenseful music)
What?
- It's the kid.
What the hell are
you doing here?
- Hey, Gonzo.
Take me with you.
- Are you crazy or something?
Get On back to the boat.
- Okay.
Good luck, huh?
- I'm coming back.
I promise.
Look, I have a present for you.
But if I do make it back,
you're gonna kick
this habit for good.
Is that a deal?
- It's tough, but I'll do it.
- [Gonzales] Good.
- Gonzo.
- Yeah?
- You've got to quit, too.
Deal?
- Yeah.
Yeah, that's a deal, kid.
(tense music)
- I've gotta get closer.
You stay here.
(speaking foreign language)
(gasping)
(dramatic music)
(speaking foreign language)
(grunting)
(tense music)
Move, Gonzo.
- Mr. Henderson.
- [Mickey] Gonzo, you're back.
(Gonzales chuckles)
- Hey, I told you I'd come back.
- Mm-hmm.
(both laugh)
- Come on.
- Yeah.
- Henderson, your idea stinks.
- You got a better idea?
- Yeah.
Go back up the river.
Try and find another way out.
- We'd just get
more of the same.
- I don't buy that.
- It's not your
decision to make, is it?
Gonzo, charges ready?
- All set, Sam.
- Chief, you a good swimmer?
- I'll go, Mr. Henderson.
I was the best swimmer
in my class, sir.
- Okay.
All right, Chief.
I want you at the helm.
First light what I'm gonna do
is I'm gonna send up a flare.
That's your signal
to start the run.
When we hit top speed, that's
when we'll blow the bridge.
If you get through,
we're home free.
(suspenseful music)
(speaking foreign language)
Okay, Gonzo.
Get back to the boat.
Tell Chief we're on schedule.
- See you on the other side.
- Okay.
- [Mary] Those should buy
somebody a nice retirement.
- Buy a hell of a lot of
weapons for the resistance.
- Well, if I were you, I'd
be real careful with that.
I mean, you don't want it to
fall into the wrong hands.
I keep hearing these rumors
that the war's over with
and there may be some people
who lack your patriotism.
- Hey.
Believe me, I'll
do what's right.
- [Gonzales] Chief.
- What's happening?
- Everything's set.
We're on schedule.
- Let's get ready.
Let's go.
- Whatever happens later, I
want you to stay down below.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
- This is for you.
This has always kept me safe.
Now it's going to protect you.
- Are you giving me this?
- [Gonzales] Yeah.
- To keep or just to wear?
- It's yours.
(tense music)
(speaking foreign language)
- Here we go.
- Okay, boys.
Let's move it.
(dramatic music)
(speaking foreign language)
- Gonzo, what the
hell's Sam waiting for?
If he doesn't blow it now,
we can kiss our ass goodbye.
- Cover me.
(guns firing)
(explosions booming)
(men yelling)
(kids crying)
(explosions booming)
(gun firing)
(yells)
(explosion booms)
(explosions booming)
(gun fires)
(kids crying)
(guns firing)
(men yelling)
(speaking foreign language)
Hit it!
(explosions booming)
(grunting)
(explosion booms)
(men yelling)
(explosions booming)
(man yells)
(yelling)
- Where's Thomas?
- [Sam] He didn't make it.
(tense music)
Chief, what's the damage?
- She took a hit
on the port engine.
She's taking in a lot of water.
- All right, we're gonna
have to lighten the load.
- Not that one.
That one stays.
- What?
- So, why do you want to
hold onto these dossiers?
We just throw 'em over,
they go to the bottom.
Go ahead, guys.
Now.
- If this goes, I go with it.
- [Sam] I don't know what
you're talking about.
- I do.
Our American war hero figured
he could clean up on this war.
He's got a crate full of gold.
- Yeah, I ain't leaving
here empty-handed.
- A real war hero, huh?
(guns fire)
(yells)
- What do you wanna do?
- Fuck you.
(gun fires)
(grunts)
- Skipper.
(grunting)
You're okay, Chief.
We're going home.
(dramatic music)