Please, sweetie, tell
me more about your day.
I saw Elmo at the zoo
and monkeys...
Really?
- Next to, to lot
of scary monsters.
I have to go.
Hey, hey, where you going?
Sweetie.
Hey.
- Hey.
You know, I need you to
level with me on something.
What was Elmo doing at the zoo?
He wasn't.
She just had way too much
sugar, mixing everything up.
It's driving me crazy.
Well, you know, I guess
this Elmo is a lot more
important than Daddy these days.
You know she misses you.
Not as much as I miss you.
I know, yeah, but
look at the bright side.
I mean, I'll be home in 23 days.
22 days and 45 minutes.
I have a surprise for you.
Really?
- I'll be right back.
Hey man, I'm gettin'
some strange readings
from the bottom.
Should we stop drilling?
No.
We could be at the
cusp of a reservoir.
Okay, but safety procedure
says we should shut
down if we can't
determine the cause
of the fluctuations.
- The safety procedure
also tell you that some jackass
from Holter Energy's gonna
call and get me fired
unless I start her up again?
Well then if you shut
her down now they may
offer you a bonus to
turn it back on again.
I'm not debating with you.
All right, I'm shutting it down.
Hey, hey, hey!
Relax, okay?
Look, man, I'm
gonna go get Billy.
The two of you can
figure it out, okay?
Billy's gonna say keep pumping.
Yeah whatever, man.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
So do you like it?
Baby.
Baby, baby, baby.
Billy.
Man, I'm on my lunch break.
I know, man, we got a
possible blow out on deck.
Honey, I gotta go.
- You don't like my surprise?
- No, no, I love your surprise
I just really gotta go.
I'll call you back.
- No, no, no, don't hang up!
- What's going on, Jack?
- We got the motherload coming.
- Even now while a
well was about to blow.
- Shut up, man.
- Move over.
Great, shut her down.
You should know better.
Shut her down!
Geez.
Get outta here!
Get down to the third floor!
- Come on, man,
what are you doing?
- Jake.
Go!
Get outta here now!
Go on, get out!
Come on get out!
- Come on, we gotta
get out of here.
- Come on.
Come here, I think this
place is gonna blow!
Leo!
- The right temperatures
and conditions have
to occur precisely in order
for these tubes to form.
Now, the lava on the surface cools
while the flow
underneath continues
eventually draining
into a catch basin,
which allows these
tubes to become hollow.
You know, these
tubes run for miles.
Now, there is a theory that there
are larger and longer tubes
that are below the surface,
which apparently occurred
during the Ice Age.
Okay, well, that's
all we have time for,
which brings me to
the announcement
of the students that'll be going
on the research trip
with me tomorrow.
Your names are on this board.
- Yes!
- Okay, class dismissed and I will
see those of you at
6:30 AM tomorrow.
- Hey, I'm sorry I'm late.
My car wouldn't start.
- You weren't late,
you were absent.
- Can you please give me
a break just this once?
- Do I treat anybody
differently in this class?
- This is really
gonna affect my grade?
- Yes, it will.
- You promised me I could go.
- You promised that
you wouldn't be late.
- Is Brandon going on the trip?
- Yes, Brandon's
going on the trip.
- Well, what if I go
and I just observe?
No extra credit.
- Observe Brandon or the research?
- Come on, please.
Please, I really need this.
- Look.
- Please.
- One last time.
I swear, if you're late for
one more class you're out.
Sister or no sister.
Right.
- Okay?
- Thank you.
- Come on.
- I'm gonna make a brief statement
and then I'll take
all your questions.
Last night at
approximately 11:30PM
the Holter Energy offshore
rig Transocean Alpha
lost contact with
our central office.
Telemetry from the vessel
was lost at that time.
We sent out helicopters at dawn
to the last known coordinates
of the Transocean Alpha.
We have been unable to
locate the platform.
We're coordinating
with the Coast Guard.
We have four helicopters, 30
vessels searching the Gulf.
We will do everything
humanly possible
to locate our workers and
deliver them safely to shore.
- Is there an oil spill?
- Now, there's no sign of
an oil spill on the surface.
The Transocean Alpha has an
emergency release mechanism
that detached the rig
from the pipeline and cap.
We believe that the crew
detached the rig itself
and it's now free-floating
in the ocean.
We've set up a
search grid and we're
confident that we'll find her.
I'm gonna turn over the
rest of the press conference
to our chief engineering
officer, Ray Miller.
Ray, could you?
- The Transocean Alpha is the
most technologically-advanced
oil platform on the planet and we
are certain that we
will locate her soon.
- Sir, is it a possibility
that the rig sunk?
- It's possible, but unlikely.
Transocean Alpha is a 40,000
ton, 250 foot tall platform.
Now, right now we are
speculating that a rogue wave
may have hit the
platform and caused it
to become dislodged
from the pipeline.
It is highly unlikely
that any wave
can capsize the platform,
however we are sending ROVs
down to the well cap to make sure
that the Transocean
Alpha did not sink,
and we will be updating you
as soon as we know anything.
So if you'll excuse us, we
do have a lot of work to do.
- Okay, how about one question?
- Mr. Capilla, can I get
a one-on-one interview?
Mr. Capilla!
- Mr.
Miller, the people
have a right to know!
Mr. Miller!
- Yes.
Yes, Vernon, you genius.
Handsome and brilliant.
- Handsome maybe, but brilliant,
that's a bit of a stretch.
- I knew that you
were attracted to me.
- Serious, what have you found?
- I cross-matched the
samples from the Gulf
and then I ran that
against the Arnold samples.
- And?
- And...
chemically they match 99%.
- Yeah, but there's no way
the explosion in Arnold
would have left
deposits in Florida.
- I know, unless...
- It was an extinct
volcano in the Gulf.
So I was right.
- Right.
And maybe we'll find
that volcano on our trip
to Black Point, then you can
call it the Vitrini Volcano.
- Now that would be
very interesting.
- Did you book the
satellite time for INSA?
- Yes.
- Okay, great.
Thanks.
- I told you so.
Told you.
- Look, I still think we
should shut down the other rigs
till we find out what happened
to the Transocean Alpha.
- Are you crazy?
Those rigs are pumping half
a million barrels a day.
I'm not shutting anything down.
- It could cause an
ecological disaster.
It could fill the entire
Gulf of Mexico with oil.
- Safety valve on the ocean floor
would prevent anything
like that from happening.
Yeah, but it could fail.
- Not possible.
Thank you.
- Where are we?
- Well, ROV is
remaking its descent.
We should reach write
off some time tomorrow.
- Good.
Call me when it
gets to the bottom.
I'll be hiding from
the press till then.
- What about Project Subterranean?
- Would you excuse us?
Would you come into the
office for a second?
Never bring up
Project Subterranean
around anyone without
the proper clearance!
- I'm sorry.
I just think we need to step
things down until we find out
what happened out there.
- Subterranean is pumping
more than the other
rigs combined and I
am not stepping anything down.
If you break protocol
again, I will fire you.
Now, get out of my office.
- Hey, what's up?
- I know how you can
forget to eat sometimes
when you're all wrapped
up in your work.
- Thank you, that's sweet.
- You're welcome.
So are you going on the trip?
I'm tagging along,
but there's not enough
room on the short bus
for me so I have to ride with you.
- I don't think that's
the best of ideas.
- Why not?
- You're a student
who also happens
to be my boss's little sister.
It's not right.
- Okay.
Well, what if I rode
in the back seat?
It would be like Driving
Miss Daisy only sexier.
- Are you here to visit
me or harass my staff?
- I was just bringing
Brandon coffee and a muffin.
- I know how much
of a slave driver you can be, sis.
I mean, look at the poor guy.
He hasn't seen the outside
of a lab in six weeks.
- I know, poor thing.
Is that true, Brandon?
You're a little pasty.
- I can take it from
you guys one at a time,
but when you gang up
on me, it's not fair.
Can I just?
- Okay, we're getting
an early start
in the morning so get some rest.
And, Brandon, you're taking her.
What?
- Yeah.
- See, that wasn't
so bad, now was it?
- It depends on your
grounds of comparison.
That's Antoinette's.
This is mine, thank you.
Here you go.
- Thanks.
Okay, so everybody gather around.
So I've been thinking
that the Gulf itself
was created by a giant volcano.
Yes, Nelson?
- What about the meteor that
killed the dinosaurs theory?
- Well, that's not proven.
Yes, it could have
been an impact crater,
but I'm saying that it
was a reverse caldera.
Now that's kind of like
when a soap bubble pops
leaving an indentation
on the surface tension
of the water for a split second.
That's the Gulf and the
indentation is a volcano.
Okay, so we have a
grid for you guys
to follow and you
need to stick to it.
Use your GPS and don't
go out of the square.
I need soil temperatures,
rock samples,
tilt and swell
measurements every 15 feet.
Any questions?
Okay, I'll see you
back here at three.
Be observant and be safe.
- Do you wanna be my partner?
- Because you like me or
because you need an A?
- Actually, both.
- I don't think so.
- SO2 reading is 5 point ppms,
which is significantly
above average considering...
- Hey, Emily, check
this out, check this.
What does this say to you?
Ha, that's very funny, very funny.
Okay.
- What are you gonna give me?
- What's your deal?
- My deal is that you can't
stop focusing on science
for one second and
focus on biology.
- Thank you.
- You're such a schmuck sometimes.
- All right, everyone,
back into the vans.
Becky, can you get
a headcount for me?
- Sure, Dr. V.
- How is it for you?
- I don't know, just
everything seems abnormal.
Just not right.
- Yeah, same here.
- I found an
alligator on the shore that
looks to have been boiled.
- Three, four, five.
- Now we'll see when the
samples get run through the lab.
- You don't even have
to run the samples.
I tell you it smells like
sulfur dioxide all over there.
You were definitely right.
There's something
going on out here.
- All right, I'll
see you back there.
- Okay.
Here, I'll take that.
No, no, no, no, no, you don't.
No, you don't,
you're skinny enough.
They can squeeze you in the van.
- You think I'm skinny?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
- Seven, eight, nine, 10.
We're all good, Miss V.
- Great.
Buckle up.
- How can I help you, Ray?
- Something you need to see.
- All right, what am I looking at?
- Video from the
ROV descending down
to the well site of
the Transocean Alpha.
- My god, what is that?
What happened?
- I won't really know
until I get a sample up
to the surface but
that looks like magma.
We must have drilled
into a pocket of lava.
- Who else knows about this?
- I dismissed the technicians
from the telemetry lab
before the signal came in.
- No one can know about this.
- Well, what are we gonna do?
We can't just say we lost
a 40,000 ton drilling rig.
- I'll handle that.
- We are drilling on
extinct lava tubes
and apparently some of
them aren't so extinct.
We need to tell the authorities.
- You need to get
with the program, Ray.
If the authorities investigate
then they're gonna find out
about Project Subterranean,
and if they find out
about that then we are
both going to jail.
You weren't worried about
safety when you got your profit
participation check from
the project, were ya?
We can pump out of
there for generations
and no one would know.
- We have a press update
on the Transocean Alpha.
What am I supposed to tell them?
- Well, you tell them
that we have reason
to believe that the rig was hit
by a rogue wave, washed hundreds
of miles out to sea
and presumed sunk.
- They're gonna want
confirmation on that.
- And they will get it.
I'm gonna have the Beta
Horizon decommissioned,
towed 200 miles out, just edge
of the ocean shelf, scuttled.
Tomorrow, you go down
and take pictures
and I will issue a sad
statement of condolences
to the members of the
families of the workers.
- That's a huge undertaking.
- I'll handle that.
You go handle the freaking press.
And meet me at the bone
yard tomorrow morning.
- Yes, sir.
- Get me Butch Sanders.
- See anything interesting?
- What are you doing here, Brad?
I thought you were
somewhere in Iceland?
- Can a guy say hi to his
ex and not have a reason?
- That's right, you always
had a reason, right?
- I've been analyzing your data
and I think you may
be on to something.
- You've been looking
at my research?
- I still have
access to the server.
You son of a bitch.
- I told you to
change the password.
Look, easy, I'm a good guy, okay?
I'm here to help.
You want me to help?
- Obviously you haven't traveled
halfway across the world
because you don't know anything.
So why don't you just spit it out.
- How about over dinner tonight?
- No.
- Coffee?
- Fine.
- Come on, I'm buying.
- Don't touch me.
- Sorry, sorry.
Just coffee.
- No, I can't right now.
You just have to go onto FTP,
download the Black Point doc.
Okay?
I gotta go, I'll call you back.
Thanks.
Hey.
- Hey.
Antoinette told me you weren't
feeling very good so I
brought you some things.
- Well, I'm better
now but thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Yeah!
- All right, welcome to the Back
to the Beach Bikini Contest.
I want you to do me a favor.
Watch where you're
walking at 'cause things
can get slippery when wet.
In about five more
minutes we're gonna
bring out the fire round of girls!
- I don't know, Shauna,
a bikini is one thing,
but being sprayed down by
a water gun is another.
- Come on, live a little!
You're not gonna have
that rocking body forever.
- What if my parents see this?
Or worse, what if
your brother sees it?
- He'd probably flip
out and kill me.
- Hey, my bathing suit, girl.
Give us a big smile,
give us some love.
Show us who's winning $1000.
- Relax, no one's
ever gonna see that.
- He had a camera.
- All we need is a
little liquid courage.
Tequila.
- I hate you.
- That's my sorority sister.
- No!
- Okay, ladies, this is it.
We're gonna march
you out one at a time
so Tommy the fireman
can hose you down.
And do me a favor, sell
it, because there's
over $1000 up for the
winner, all right?
Are you ready?
No!
- Yeah!
- So I tell the Sherpa
that I wanna try
to reach the summit
before nightfall,
but my command of the Nagari
language isn't that good
and so he's looking at me sideways
and the other
Sherpa's cracking up.
- So what did you say to him?
- Apparently I asked him
to spend the night with me.
No?
- Yeah.
And he looked like he was up
for it until I cut him off.
- You know, we've been
sitting here for over an hour
and you've been regaling
about all your adventures
and travels but you haven't
gotten to the point, Bradley.
- You remember our
supervolcano theory?
- Yeah, my theory.
- Whatever.
Yeah, the theory that
the Gulf of Mexico
was created by a
supervolcano millions
of years ago during
the continental drift?
That theory, the one laughed
at by most scientists?
- Yeah, and I'm still
trying to prove it.
- I think you may
have found proof.
- How?
- I was analyzing your data
on the chemical composition
of the Alvera Volcano
and the samples you
took from the Panhandle.
- Yeah, I know they match.
- That's not all they match.
- What do you mean?
- They match the chemical makeup
of the crude oil being
pumped by Holter Energy.
I got a sample of it
from a friend of mine
when the drilling
platform went missing.
- And it matches exactly?
- Yeah.
That means that wherever
Holter is drilling,
it must be over some old vents
or lava tubes or something.
I mean, this could
lead to the big one.
- But how do they
know where to drill?
I mean, the alignment
of the platforms.
I mean, how can they tell?
- They must have
access to the ground
imaging scans you've been making.
- Yeah, but I haven't
published those yet.
- Yeah.
- Have you seen the seismic
readings we've been getting?
They're disturbing.
- The president is on the brink of
declaring a moratorium
on drilling.
That's what I find disturbing.
What's going on, Butch?
- Rumblings here and there.
Real concern is the oil
temperature heating up.
- What's causing it?
- I don't know yet, but
we'll figure it out.
- Did you take care of
that other little problem?
- The decommissioned rig
was scuttled last night.
No witnesses.
- It looks like you
have a job to do, Ray.
Take pictures, schedule a press
conference for tomorrow morning.
- That can wait, this can't.
We need to shut down
this facility now!
It's too damn dangerous!
- That wasn't a request, Ray.
I will handle this
down here now get going
unless you wanna check out
my early retirement plan.
- All right, all right, I'm goin'.
- The guy is such a wimp.
- I can take care of him.
- Forget about him.
How many barrels of oil a day
are we pumping outta here?
- 277 barrels a minute.
- That's good, good, but we need
to get as much product outta
here as quickly as possible.
Are your men all in line?
- My guys are tight as a drum.
- Good.
- They're making
more money in a week
than they normally make in a year.
Nobody's talking.
- Then increase the flow.
Can you give me 600,000
barrels of oil a day?
- I can push it as
far as it'll go.
470, that's the best I can do.
- When was the last
time you manually
aligned the conductors?
- Never.
That's what computers are for.
- Let me show you how I became CEO
of the most profitable drilling
company in North America.
It wasn't by sitting
in front of a computer.
Crank it up when I tell you.
Now!
- 520!
- More!
- 600,000!
- What I tell ya?
- All right, without further
ado, we have Kimberly from LSU!
Go Kimberly, go Kimberly,
go Kimberly, go Kimberly!
Go Kimberly!
- Look at how how she is.
I can't do this.
- Please, you are so much
prettier than she is.
Okay, well, you don't
have to show 'em
the girls if you don't want to.
- Do I have to be assaulted
by a water pistol?
- Yes, but I promise I'll look
like a bigger slut than you.
- Is that supposed to
make me feel better?
No, but $1000 is.
- Yo, Tommy, cool her off!
Next up we have Annie
from Florida State.
- All right.
- Annie, Annie, Annie.
Now, for our final contestant,
Shauna, Queen of the Jungle!
Show me what you got,
show me what you got.
Woo, ooh, that's what
I'm talking about, baby!
Go Shauna, go Shauna!
Go Shauna, go Shauna, go!
Go Shauna, go Shauna,
go Shauna, go Shauna!
- Help!
Help, help!
Help, help, help me!
- Shauna, are you okay?
We gotta go, come on.
Come on!
Shauna!
- Annie!
- Shauna!
Shauna, Shauna!
- No.
- A magnitude 5.6 earthquake hit
off the coast of
Miami this afternoon.
What followed on the
beach has scientists
and local officials
scratching their heads.
Over 100 people were killed
by what some observers
describe as a
superheated wall of steam
that hit the beach shortly
after the earthquake.
We now go live to
Colonel Anderson.
- Mayor Alvarez has
enlisted the services
of the National Guard to
investigate what's going on.
As soon as we have
some information,
I will release a press statement.
- About a dozen
Downtown businesses...
- A steam tsunami.
- Is that possible?
- I've seen the results of
one once off of Micronesia.
- So we have a
supervolcano on our hands.
- I know of a abandoned
missile silo off the coast
from the Cuban Missile Crisis.
It's deep.
I can get good gas and temperature
and tilt readings from there.
Okay.
- Wanna come?
- No, I can't.
I mean, they're gonna warn people.
I kinda need a
better understanding
about what's happening too.
- I'll go with you.
- All right, let's go.
Hey, be careful.
- I will.
I'll see you guys later night.
Brandon, we need to
go to Holter Energy
to see if they know anything
about the situation.
- What, why them?
- I don't know, I
just have a hunch.
The choice of drilling sites
is a little bit suspect.
- Well, can you fill
me in on your hunch?
- Yeah, I'll let
you know in the car.
- I'm sure you all
are aware by now
that Jacob was killed in the
blow-off at Subterranean.
So until we can figure
out what happened
that facility will
remain decommissioned.
- Understood.
We're depending on you now, Ray.
Matter fact, we took
a vote of the board
and if you're willing we'd
like to nominate you as CEO.
- There are some things that Jacob
did you all should know about.
- We know about everything, Ray,
and we're all liable if this
thing should get outta hand.
We wanna give you Jacob's cut.
And as an added
motivation we're gonna
give you 40% of all the revenue
produced by that facility.
Now we need you to
pump everything out
of there you can in a month
and then we shut it down.
Then we fill that damn thing with
concrete and nobody
knows anything.
- 50%.
- Done.
- I have the ROV video
of the scuttled rig.
At my news conference today I will
announce the loss of
the Transocean Alpha.
I will also inform
the public that Jacob
died of a heart attack
upon hearing the news.
- That is a nice touch.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Meeting's adjourned.
You can invite the press up
to the conference room now.
- All right, we're here.
- So what happened?
- What do you mean?
- Antoinette never talked about
you two after the divorce.
- We divorced,
that's what happened.
- But you still
love her, don't you?
- Yeah, probably always will.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
And it's good to see
you again anyway.
Last time I saw you...
You were just an awkward
little high school girl
with a mouth full of braces.
- Thanks for reminding me.
- That's what I'm here for.
- We have confirmed the location
of the Transocean Alpha.
There were no survivors.
It was washed out to
sea by a rogue wave
and sank from the
damage it had sustained.
Our hearts go out to the
families of the crew members.
Recovery of any remains
is highly unlikely,
but our search and rescue teams
will be combing the
waters through Tuesday.
- Why isn't Jacob Capilla here?
- That is the other reason
why I have gathered you all.
There is other sad news.
Upon discovering the fate
of the Transocean Alpha,
Jacob Capilla suffered a massive
heart attack and died last night.
I have been named as interim CEO
and will be in charge
of recovery efforts.
Our thoughts and our prayers
go out to the Capilla family.
That is all for now.
- Tilt meters are setup and ready.
- The gas chromatograph
and thermal
imaging sensor are ready.
- All right, good.
Just stick close behind
me and do as I say.
It's gonna be a long climb down.
- Don't worry, I've got your back.
- Yes, but not all of the wells
are necessarily congruent
with the radar maps.
I mean, coincidence may
still be a possibility.
Don't we wanna investigate?
- Yeah, I do.
That's what we're doing.
- Dr. Vitrini, I
don't have much time.
Frankly, I wouldn't see you
at all during this crisis,
but the outrageous
messages you left
with my secretary,
they got my attention.
Who is this?
I'm Brandon.
- This is Brandon Rice,
my research partner.
- You got five minutes.
- I'm sorry to hear about
your Transocean Alpha.
So am I, but that's
not why you're here.
- No, it's not.
I wanna know exactly how
you got hold of my research.
- Excuse me?
- My research, how exactly
did you get hold of it?
- I don't know what
you're talking about.
- I think you do.
I mean, you're the chief engineer
and scientific officer of Holter.
Your department is the one
who placed the well sites.
Now each one of those well sites
matches the ground radar
scans that I have been mapping
in the Gulf Coast for
the last 10 years.
But do you know what I
can't quite figure out?
Is how those volcanic tubes would
lead you to the oil reserves.
- This is preposterous.
I don't waste my time
on academic research.
I conduct my own.
I choose the spots based
on mineral deposits.
You know, you are
as crazy in person
as you sound on those messages.
Well, I guess I had
to hear it for myself.
Five minutes are up,
there's the door.
- If you have discovered
volcanic activity and you're
putting millions at
risk for the sake
of your profit I will find out.
And when I prove it I will make
sure your ass ends up in jail.
- I suggest you leave now
before I call security.
- All right.
I just used these
a few months ago.
They should be good.
- Let's hope so.
- All right, just
stay close behind me.
- I got your back, remember?
- All right.
- Got it?
Okay, let's do this.
Doing okay?
- Something's not right.
It's hot as hell in here.
Go back!
Go back, come on!
- What?
My god, my god!
Go back up!
- I'm going!
Go back!
- I'm going, I'm going!
- Go, hurry!
Go!
Keep going, keep going!
Keep on going!
- It's so hot.
- Keep going!
Keep going!
Go!
Go, hurry!
Run!
- I'm confused.
I'm confused, did that go well?
- I got what I wanted.
- What was that thing you
planted under his desk?
- We need to get evidence.
- What are you doing right now?
Are you doing this here?
This is not legal,
I don't think it.
- Well, despite popular belief,
two wrongs do make a right.
- Yeah, it worked out fine.
Wait till the cost
reports come in.
The scrap metal alone is
worth more than my house.
I'll come by after
I finish up here.
What the hell?
Let me call you back.
Get me Butch!
- Damn!
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on!
Come on!
- It's a wireless repeater.
That means whoever was
downloading information
from your computer had
to be physically close.
It was that woman from
the university today.
She knows we stole her research.
- How long ago she plant this?
- 10 minutes.
- Depending on her network,
she coulda copied a quarter
of your hard drive
before you shut her down.
- She was looking for
proof and the way my luck's
been going today she's got it!
I like you, Butch.
Question is, can I trust
you the way Jacob did?
- Anything you need.
Anything.
- I want you to find
this bitch and kill her.
And I want you to destroy her lab
and every ounce of
research you find in it.
- Consider it done.
This is important.
I need you to go
to the university.
Find Dr. Vitrini's lab.
Burn it.
And I mean to the ground.
Something's not right.
- Yeah, the repeater's
not working.
- Let me try something,
let me see this.
- Son of a bitch!
- They're shooting at us.
Go, go, go!
Go!
- Is anyone behind us?
- I don't know.
I think we lost him.
- What the hell is going on?
Why the hell are
they shooting at us?
- I don't know.
Obviously we're on the right path.
Who are you calling?
- Emily.
You call the cops.
Emily, neither one
of you are picking up
your phones right now.
I need to speak to Brad.
- Yes, I'd like to
report a shooting.
- Give me a call when
you get this message.
- No, no, no, we're okay.
Yes, my name is Brandon Rice.
And Antoinette Vitrini.
V-I-T-R-I-N-I.
Yes, that's her.
Yes, she's sitting
right next to me.
Okay, we'll be right there.
- What?
- We need to go
back to the campus.
- Why?
- Our lab is on fire.
- Where, in Miami?
- According to a theory
that I've been working on,
and that's why Holter Energy's
drilling is so reckless.
I mean, look, this
is no coincidence.
They have my files.
- Why haven't there
been any eruptions?
- Look, the tragedy at
Miami Beach was the result
of eruptions and
there's gonna be more.
Someone is trying to kill me.
It's not because I'm crazy.
It's because I know something and
they don't want anyone to know.
- Look, I can call Colonel
Anderson at the Guard Bureau.
Let them know your theory on
Holter Energy and Miami Beach,
but that's the best I can do.
- Okay, so why the National Guard?
- They're investigating
the incident.
I'll let you know what they say.
Yeah, yeah, tell him
I'm working on it.
I know, just do what you can.
- Is anything salvageable?
- Not much.
- What about my computer?
- The LCD is toast, but the
hard drive should be okay.
- Is that Emily?
- No, I gotta take this though.
- All right.
- Have you lost your mind?
- We've got a problem, you and I.
- I figured that much when I saw
your guy point an AK at my head.
Let me guess, you
torched the school too?
- Look, you march into my
office with that psycho
then you plant a
bug under my desk?
- I didn't do that, she did.
- And we were trying
to kill her not you.
- Coulda fooled me.
- You are on those files.
I paid you well for that research
and you're gonna go
to jail right along
with me if you don't do something.
- What do you want me to do, Ray?
- You get the files from
her then you silence her.
- What?
- They're gonna be
looking at me closely now,
but if there are no
files there's no proof.
And if there's no
Dr. Vitrini then
there's nothing that they can do.
- I didn't sign up for this.
- I don't think you have
a choice here, Mr. Rice.
- Okay.
I'm gonna, I'm
gonna need a minute.
I'm gonna call you back, okay?
- You got 30 minutes.
- Okay, so the police have
the National Guard coming.
- We need to get as much
info off that hard drive
as we can to make this
case against these jerks.
- Okay.
- You know what,
I'll deal with it.
- Are you sure, I
can do that quick.
- No.
- Come on, come on, go!
Into the ball!
- I'm trying, coach!
Come on!
- There's no license
plate on the front, okay?
- Right, right, right, yeah.
Sure, sure, we'll.
We'll finish it later.
- Okay.
- Sir, Chief Michaels,
Brandon Rice.
- Thank you.
I'm gonna grab
Antoinette real quick.
- As soon as they're done we'll
head back to the base with you.
Ride's here.
- That was quick.
- Yeah.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing, I'm just seeing
what we're working with here.
- Okay.
- What's the plan once
we get to the base?
- Well, we need to
find the main door
and relieve the pressure
if we get the chance.
- Wait, like lancing a boil.
- Correct, if we find it.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna download the
EDMS for the harmonic tremors
and that'll narrow
our search for us.
- Do you have the GNS hardware?
- It's right here.
- Great.
- Okay, I'm gonna
run to the truck.
- How long do you need?
- 10 minutes.
- Perfect.
Come on.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Got it.
Antoinette!
- What's wrong?
Where's Brad?
Look, I need you to
calm down, Emily,
and tell me what happened.
- He's dead.
- What?
Who did this?
- I tried to.
I'm so sorry.
He almost made it.
I tried.
I'm so sorry.
- Yeah.
- Is it done?
- What do you think?
- You're running
out of time, Brandon.
- So are you, Ray.
- What do you mean?
- I'm not a killer, never
have been and never will be.
- You are making a big mistake.
- No, no, no.
You made the mistake
when you chose
to build an illegal
drilling facility
in the heart of Downtown Miami.
- How do you know
about the facility?
- I'm not stupid.
Out of all the images I gave you,
the most promising were in
the heart of Downtown Miami.
And that's when
Holter bought up all
that factory space and
spent all kinds of money
in construction trying
to refurbish it.
But there was never
anything in the press
about what it was for.
That must have been a
bitch to keep quiet.
- You are smart, Brandon.
You gonna die smart.
- I'm smart enough to tell the
authorities everything I know.
That's exactly what
I plan on doing.
Hey, five minutes, guy.
Ready to go.
- Look.
This isn't your fault.
I really, really
need you right now.
Look, there's a truck
outside taking us
to the National Guard.
Let's go, okay?
- At ease.
Tactical Team Bravo,
I have Mayor Alvarez,
the chief of police, and two
civilian scientists on the way.
I want the command center
up and operational,
running, in 30 minutes.
Fall out!
Yes, general, it's done.
30 minutes.
Yes, sir.
- Anybody out here?
Are you crazy, lady?
Get outta town,
gotta get outta town.
- Gentlemen, this
is Dr. Vitrini.
- Dr. Vitrini, Colonel Anderson.
This is Mayor Alvarez.
Private, park that vehicle.
- Well, first we have
to locate the lava dome.
It's gotta be somewhere
in Miami, obviously.
I need a helicopter and
some radar equipment.
- Lieutenant, make sure
there's a pilot on alert.
The airspace will be
closed within an hour
because of the air so you
better do this quickly.
- Brandon, go and
get the GNS setup.
- Okay.
- All right, I got a theory.
It's the cold cap, which you guys
tested during the
BP spill in 2010.
- Didn't work.
- That's 'cause you injected
directly into the sea bed.
- What is a cold cap?
- It's liquid nitrogen.
We attempted to
freeze the oil spill
at the epicenter, turning
the water into ice
and the oil into a solid.
- Creating a cap made
of ice thus containing the oil.
- And who are you?
- Her accomplice.
- Okay, the cold cap doesn't
work under the water.
It works underground,
but I'm gonna
need massive amounts
of liquid nitrogen.
- That shouldn't be a problem.
Every oil company in the state
owes us from picking
up their mistakes.
Lieutenant Sanborn, get Eldridge
from the 143 on the horn.
Tell him we need immediate access
to the nearest
chemical plant stat.
What else?
- Okay, I'm gonna
need heavy digging
equipment and a
platoon or two of men.
- And what are you
gonna do with them
- I'm gonna find
the access and the
spill-off point of the lava dome.
- I'm gonna open it
up and cool the lava
that comes out with
liquid nitrogen.
- A liquid nitrogen bomb.
- More or less.
- You find the dome, you'll
have the equipment and the men.
- All right, thank you.
Emily's gonna stay with you.
She knows everything
that's going on
so utilize her as you want.
- There's a tactical
uplink in the chopper.
Radio us when you
have the coordinates.
- All right.
- Emily, come over here with me.
- Wouldn't wanna be
in your shoes, mayor.
- Okay, the cold
cap's in progress.
- Why, that's never
gonna work, you know it.
- It's gonna give us some time.
- Okay.
GNS is in sync.
- Okay, so you're good?
- We just crossed
the dome's perimeter.
We're in it now.
- Okay, move to the next grid.
- Antoinette, there's something
that I need to tell you.
- What?
- It was me.
- What are you talking about?
- I sold your research to Holter.
- Come on, Brandon, get serious.
What are you doing?
- I am serious.
They contacted me and
I needed the money.
And...
I'm sorry.
- Next grid.
- Did you hear what I said?
- You know what, I don't wanna
ever see your face again.
- I know.
- So who was your contact?
- Ray Miller.
- So when we went to his office
to confront him you just
pretended not to know him?
I mean, he tried to shoot us.
And that thought didn't
even cross your mind?
- One thing I can think
of is why the hell
is this happening?
I know I screwed up, I'm sorry,
but you need me and
we're the only people
who know how to stop this thing.
- So why did they need my data?
- They theorized
that in areas where
there's high volcanic
temper and sediment,
there's also greater possibility
of large oil reserves.
- So Brad was right.
They were using my mapping
data to place their wells.
- How did Brad find out?
- Well, the oil samples at Holter
matched the chemical
components of the Alvera rock.
- Right.
- Damn it, Brandon!
Next grid.
- Where is she?
- She's in a helicopter
surveying the area.
They're meant to land back
here when they're done.
- Look, I need to get her alone.
- Yeah, well, she's
been surrounded
by the top brass ever
since she got here.
- You think of something
and get back to me.
- Aye, aye, sir.
- That's it!
It's on Olive and Third.
- That's the worst place possible.
- Yes, smack bang Downtown.
Let's get back to base.
- How are we supposed to vent this
in the middle of the city?
- When we get it back I need you
to map out various
venting scenarios.
Anything on land's gonna be dicey.
Dr. Vitrini to Colonel Anderson.
- Colonel Anderson, over.
- We located the lava
dome at Olive and Third.
- Olive and Third, copy.
- Did you manage to locate
the liquid nitrogen?
- We've located
about 400,000 gallons
in containment units at
the O'Hare Chemical Plant.
- How quickly can you
get that downtown?
- I have four semis waiting
on their loading dock
as we speak.
- Are these trucks
temperature-controlled?
- Yes.
- We're just seeing where we're
gonna pinpoint the cold cap.
- I'll have my men shovel
out to Olive and Third
and wait in the center
till further notification.
- Okay, sounds like a plan.
- How far is the
chemical plant to base?
- It's close, right
across the freeway.
- Okay, great, is Emily there?
- Yes, standing right next to me.
- Emily, look, I need
you at the chemical plant
to run the static air against the
thermal protection of the trucks.
These need to be at
200 negative degrees
to maximize the LN2
that we're using.
- Copy.
How do I get to
the chemical plant?
- I'll have someone escort you.
Private, take Miss Vitrini
to the chemical plant.
- Right away, sir.
- We're out of time!
- I'll monitor the harmonic
tremors to determine the
speed the lava's moving
through the conduits.
It'll be on clock.
- Yeah, but it's a
ticking time bomb.
How far away are we
away from the base?
- All good?
- Cooler's on as low as it'll go.
- I hope it's enough.
We should head back.
- There's supposed to be another
platoon at the south dock.
Should we check?
- Let's do it.
- This way.
- Colonel, Chief?
All right, so this
is the lava dome.
This is the area that we're
gonna be penetrating carefully.
- That's a big area.
Where exactly do you
plan on piercing it?
- Well, Brandon and I are
working on that right now.
- The team on the ground is
using a gravity gradient meter
to determine actually how deep
below the surface the dome is.
- Well, now, hold
on, there are some
high rent districts
down in that area.
- Well, not anymore.
Colonel, I assume you have
the explosives and the
engineering teams on standby
with the liquid nitrogen.
- We have some, it all depends
on how deep we have to go.
- Okay, we need to get prepped.
- Well, I don't know about
blowing a hole in South Miami.
- There's going to be an eruption
in Miami in the next few hours.
Now we can let it
destroy the entire city
or we can tell it where to
erupt and contain the situation.
It's your choice.
- Which way to the South Dock?
What are you doing?
- His job.
You Vitrini girls have
become a liability.
- Who are you?
- Shh.
- What's going on?
- Patience, you'll find out.
- Hello?
- I need you to listen closely
if you want to see your
sister alive again.
- Who is this?
- Ray Miller.
- Don't listen to
him, it's a trap!
- Shut her up.
Come here!
- No!
- What do you want,
you son of a bitch?
- Come to the chemical
plant and you come alone.
Bring the laptop with the
files that you stole from me.
Fair exchange.
You got 15 minutes or she's dead.
Kill her, get rid of the body.
- No, let me go!
- Shut up and move, darlin'!
- What are you doing?
- Just get me a timeline of
the best way to vent the dome.
- Where are you going??
- I'll be back.
- Move it, cupcake.
Move along.
- Help, somebody help me!
- Bitch, shut up, shut up!
Play nice.
Bitch!
- Miller!
I've got what you want!
- Bring it up here.
- You come down.
- Look, this is not a negotiation.
The stairs are to your right.
- You can't hide forever!
You are really trying my
patience, pretty girl.
- Six, two, five, zero, zero.
You son of a bitch.
How's this coming?
Come on, come
on, come on, come on.
We don't have time for this.
Got you.
Okay, go to the next screen.
- I have your files
on my computer.
- Hand it over.
- I wanna see my sister.
- She's safe, trust me.
- No, I wanna see my sister now.
I have them backed up.
They're on my server,
they're encrypted.
- Now why in the hell would
you wanna go on and do that?
Fine, I have someone who
can retrieve them for me.
- Brandon, I don't think he's
gonna be any help to you.
He told me everything.
So either you're gonna kill
me or you're gonna hand
over my sister and I'll
give you the backup files
with the encryption
key to the server.
- All right, look, I'm
gonna count to three.
If you don't hand me that computer
by then I'm gonna shoot
you and your sister.
One!
Come on, two!
Three!
- Let go of my sister.
- You bitches!
- Colonel!
- What happened to you?
- It's a long story.
She needs a medic.
- Get a first aid kit.
Here, sit down.
Now, hold on a second.
If there's something you need to
tell me now is the time to do it.
- You guys, I have something here.
This dome is roughly
2500 cubic yards wide.
It's 200 feet below the
surface, but look at this.
- Smaller and
stronger every minute.
- We have an hour at best
before this volcano erupts.
- Please tell me you
have a venting scenario.
- Wait, wait, venting?
I thought we were
preparing for a cold cap?
I have to evacuate the base.
- Wait, we're gonna
use the nitrogen,
but only to direct the lava flow
from the eruption to
here in the Miami Canal.
- And the Miami Canal runs
into the Biscayne Bay.
- Right, and we're gonna vent
the dome next to the canal.
- And then the magma's gonna run
down this canal like a lava tube.
Fill up that bay.
- There's only one problem.
What?
- It's 200 feet
beneath the surface and
we have no time to drill.
- We don't have to.
- Colonel, send your
company, send the trucks.
Get all hands on deck to
1101 North River Drive.
- I do not want to send 100
men on a suicide mission.
Are you sure this
is the right call?
- There's a well down there.
- It's 150 feet deep.
It's the only chance that we have.
- Colonel, I have
never seen this man
miscalculate mathematical
scientific equations.
I will take full responsibility
for his findings.
- Okay, leave now.
I'll be right behind you.
- Thank you, thank you, sir.
- Sergeant, get some
Humvees available.
I need an open channel.
Attention
all companies and lieutenants.
Your immediate orders
are to take all equipment
and vehicles to 1101
North River Drive.
I repeat, 1101 North River Drive.
Company, move out.
- All right, let's go.
How did you know about this place?
- I did the blueprint
design engineering.
Ray would never tell me where
it was, but I figured it out.
You're full of surprises.
- Follow me.
Let's move.
There's 20 pounds of C4
on the bottom of the well.
400 canisters of LN2 on
the ground each rigged
with its own C4 to blow two
seconds before we blow the well.
And on the far wall
it's five pounds of C4
to breach the well and detonate.
- Okay, and the nitrogen's gonna
coat the walls of the facility.
- And the lava will flow
right into the canal.
- So how are we gonna blow it?
- Long range, half a mile.
I'm looking for a signal now.
Okay, let's go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
- You okay?
- Yeah, for now.
- I'll meet you at
Olive and Third.
- All right.
- Take cover.
- Are we at a safe distance?
- I don't know,
we're gonna find out.
- Three, two, one, detonate!
- What happened?
- It's not going off?
- Damn it, I don't have a signal.
We must be too far away.
All right, folks, it's time
for us to save our skin.
Move out.
Brandon, I said move out!
- I just need to take this
close enough to get a signal.
Don't let them out of the car.
- Deville, follow me!
Drive.
- Why are we leaving him?
- He has to get
closer for a signal.
He will be all right.
Damn it!
Okay.
All right.
Damn it.
Damn.
Come on!
Shh.
Damn!
Come on, you son of a bitch!
No!
Of course.
All right.
Okay.
- He dit it, and it's working.
Mission accomplished, all
personnel return to base.
I repeat, mission accomplished.
All personnel return to base.
- One year ago, Miami
averted annihilation thanks
to the brilliant mind of
Dr. Antoinette Vitrini.
- You're a celebrity.
- Yeah, I think we
need to get away.
- Where are you thinking?
- I don't know, somewhere cold.
- North Pole.
- No, that's too cold.
- Alaska?
Yes, that sounds good.
- Okay.
Will be standing by
to bring you the very latest.
John, back to you.