[twangy rock music]
- Yes, yes, Claude, you
don't have to worry.
Have I ever let you down before?
The diamonds are safe and
sound here at my villa.
Take a hike.
We'll meet at the regular place
as soon as the heat cools down.
Say, two weeks.
[bluesy saxophone music]
- Now, if I were a
priceless diamond necklace,
where would I be?
Oh, darn.
[bluesy saxophone music]
[beeping]
- Listen to me, Claude,
there's no reason
to get your panties in a twist.
You want your
diamonds now, fine!
I'll grab them and I'll
meet you in an hour!
- You know, you really
shouldn't get upset, Rico.
You know what the doctor said
about your blood pressure.
- It's this damned Frenchman.
He's driving me crazy!
- I thought you said
Claude was Belgian.
- He can be from Outer
Mongolia for all I care.
I am never doing
business with him again.
- You know what, why don't
you let me help you relax.
- Sandy, you are too good to me.
What did I ever
do to deserve you?
- Oh, I wonder.
- I am tempted,
but I've gotta go
meet the silly Bulgarian.
- Belgian.
- Whatever.
He wants his stuff now, and,
the sooner I'm done
with him, the better.
- Sure I can't convince
you to take a break?
[bluesy saxophone music]
- Well.
- That's more like it.
- I do gotta go.
- Not until I help
you calm down.
Doctor's orders.
- Well, I wouldn't wanna
disobey the doctor.
[mysterious, tense music]
- Bingo!
- Oh, come on, Rico,
just one more time.
- Listen, Sandy, I appreciate
your enthusiasm, okay?
I gotta go.
That crazy Bavarian won't wait.
- Belgian.
- Whatever.
- Hands up, Rico.
- What the?
- Did you get the diamonds, Jas?
- Yep, right here.
- Wait.
Where did you have that gun?
- Wouldn't you like to know.
- Well, well, Rico Martinez,
biggest jewel thief on
the western hemisphere,
and we caught you.
- Wait, Jasmine,
Sandy, you girls
have been with me
for over a month.
And, Sandy, we were intimate.
You're saying all
of this is an act.
- When we go undercover, we go
deep, deep, deep undercover.
- Hands up, dirt bag!
- It's okay, Nikki, we got him.
- Where were you
this whole time?
- You told me to blend in.
- Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Who the hell are you girls?
- [Women] We're the
Teeny Weeny Bikini Squad.
[mysterious, tense music]
- Well done, ladies.
Rico Martinez has been taken
into custody by Interpol,
and the insurance
company who hired us
has deposited a nice fat check
directly into our bank account.
- Glad to be of service.
- Of any kind.
- So, does that
mean we finally get
to take that vacation,
because there's a beach
in San Trope that's
calling my name.
- We really could use a break.
We've had four cases
in as many months.
Sometimes you gotta let
the batteries recharge,
if you know what I mean.
- I do, I do, and I wish
I could help you ladies,
but I just have one
small little problem.
You have another assignment,
and it just can't wait.
- Well, what do
we got this time?
- This one is right
up your alley.
I'm sure you've all
heard of Tony Tefflor?
- Tef, the owner of
Playpen magazine?
- That's the one.
- Oh, boy.
I sense a lot of
nudity in our future.
- Are you psychic?
- You don't have to
be psychic to know
that Playpen magazine and
naked girls go hand-in-hand.
Benny, you have a
subscription, don't you?
- Well, yes, but I
only read the articles.
- There's articles?
- Anyway, Tef doesn't
just own the magazine,
he also has his social
club called the Playpen.
- Okay, Benny, let's
get to the point.
- Well, there's been
a series of accidents
at the club and the magazine.
At first, it was just
some broken equipment,
a near miss or two, but
it quickly escalated
into the accidental death
of one of the waitresses
at the club and a
model on the shoot.
- Why would someone wanna
kill some of Tef's girls?
- Tefflor thinks
that someone's trying
to put him out of business,
and, if these accidents keep up,
that's exactly
what might happen.
In three days, Tefflor
is going to announce
the Playpen Girl of the Century.
If someone were trying to
drive him out of business,
this would be the
perfect opportunity
to sabotage the event.
- Sounds like an undercover job.
- Exactly.
Jasmine, you will pose,
literally, as a model.
We have arranged an
appointment for you
with Tef's top
fashion photographer.
- Oh, great, another
aging shutterbug
who can't wait to get his paws
on my little flashbulbs.
- Not exactly.
Tef's top photographer
is a young woman
named Laura, and
she's very good.
- Wow, attractive, too.
This might not be
so bad, after all.
- Nikki, you will go
undercover as a waitress.
Your ample assets make you
perfect for the topless club.
- Got it, chief.
- And, Sandy, you will
be a businesswoman.
Your job will be to find
out if there's anyone
who has a financial
incentive to try to
topple Tef's empire from within.
- Are there any
suspects in that arena?
- One, Frank Devlin.
He not only manages the club,
but also Tef's
production company.
- Production company?
- Adult videos, late
night stuff, fairly tame,
by today's standards,
but some, Frank included,
have tried to get Tef to venture
into more explicit films,
but he's always resisted.
- What a classy guy.
- All right, ladies, you
have your assignment.
Next week, Tefflor will announce
the Playpen Girl of the Century.
Let's make sure that that
goes off without a hitch.
- Girls, this would
normally be when I tell you
to pack your bikinis,
but, in this case,
I think you might
be overdressed.
[camera clicks]
- Great, great, great.
Hold that.
[camera clicks]
[light music]
Good, good, come up.
Pick one knee up.
[camera clicks]
Nice.
[light music]
Great, great, great.
[camera clicks]
[light music]
Love it.
I love it, I love it.
[camera clicks]
[light music]
All right, I think we're
good in that outfit.
Let's get you in the next,
and then I'll finish this up.
- Okay, sounds good.
What's the other outfit?
- Okay, we've got it right here.
- Gee, that's a
bit much, isn't it?
- Well, it's the winter edition.
- Well, I really
appreciate this.
Tef says that if he
likes the photos,
I have a shot at
being centerfold,
and you know what that means.
- Yeah, did he tell
you you might be
in the running for
Playpen Girl of the Month?
- Yeah, and, after that,
the sky's the limit.
- I wouldn't put too much stock
in anything that Tony
Tefflor tells you.
Being Playpen Girl of the Month
isn't all it's cracked up to be.
- Wait a minute, I
thought I recognized you.
You were Playpen
Girl of the Year
like, what, two,
three years ago?
- Three.
A lifetime in this business.
It's not today's
news, it's old news.
- Weren't you also
dating him, as well?
- Yeah, it kinda
goes with the title.
I mean, he's a lot older, but
he's got quite a bit of charm.
- And his hefty wallet
probably doesn't hurt.
- [chuckles] Yeah, it does help
to overlook some of
his inadequacies.
And everyone knows that he
dates most of the models,
so I shouldn't have
been surprised when-
- He dumped you.
- Like a hot potato.
- That sounds painful.
- Yeah, he threw me
over for the latest
Playpen Girl of the Month.
- I'm so sorry.
- 19 years old.
- Well, you still
work for the company,
and you're an
amazing photographer.
- This photography
thing, it's just his way
of keeping me on a leash.
- Oh, he's into that
rough stuff, too?
- Not that kind of leash.
- Oh. [chuckles]
Well, you sound like you're
quite bitter about it,
and I wish there was
something I could do to-
- No, there's nothing.
- Are you sure?
- Well, it would
serve him right.
- Exactly.
[pounding rock music]
♪ You're sitting there
♪ Snorting all your blow
♪ How far are you gonna go
♪ Just one thing I
want you to know ♪
♪ I'm gonna push
you out the window ♪
♪ You push me and
push comes to death ♪
♪ You push me and you'll
take your last breath ♪
♪ You push me and
push comes to death ♪
♪ You push me and I'll
take care of the rest ♪
♪ Oh yeah
- All right, here you go.
[gasping]
- I'll never get
the hang of this.
- Don't worry, sweetie,
most of the customers here,
they don't care about the
quality of the service
but the quantity of the server,
if you know what I mean.
- Huh?
- Don't worry, you'll
be fine, go ahead.
♪ Push comes to death
- Here's your drink, sir.
Oh!
I am so sorry, sir!
- That's quite all right, Miss.
- I'm really, really sorry!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
- Listen, listen, hey!
- Oh!
- Sweet cheeks,
get this cleaned up right away.
- Yes, sir.
- What is wrong with you?
- I'm sorry, sir.
- You know what?
It's a good thing you've
got the tits for this job.
Otherwise, your little
ass would be out of here.
- Give her a break,
Frank, it's her first day,
and I don't see that
customer complaining.
- Oh, no, no, no.
- Well, it's gonna
be her last day
if she doesn't get
her act together.
- Frank Devlin, I have had
just about enough of you.
You may manage this place,
but Tony, he owns it.
[pounding rock music]
- Maybe you oughta be
careful how you talk to me.
- You better watch
how you talk to me,
and don't think for a moment
that I won't call Tef.
He and I share
something very special.
- Huh, well, you know, I
wouldn't count on that.
That road's seen a
lot of travelers.
[quiet rock music]
- I'm really sorry.
- It's all right, he's
all bark and no bite.
- Really?
- Maybe a little bite,
nibble here and there,
but he's nothing to worry about.
[bluesy rock music]
You sure you're in the
right place, darling?
- Yeah, I am here
to see the manager.
I'm Sandy Banner, I
have an appointment.
- Hmm, well, that piece
of work right over there
is the manager.
Good luck.
- Hi, are you Frank?
I'm Sandy Banner, we
have an appointment.
- Oh, yes, hello, gorgeous.
Please, step back in my office.
[bluesy rock music]
So I hear that you're
interested in investing
in Playpen Incorporated.
- Possibly, I recently came
into a large inheritance,
and just looking to
diversify my portfolio.
- Is that so?
Well, perhaps I can help you
diversify anything you like.
- Well, that's very
interesting, Mr. Devlin,
but I was thinking
more along the lines
of acquiring shares of
Playpen video production unit.
I hear that's a quite lucrative
division of the company.
- True, print is dead, but
no sense telling Tef that.
He refuses to acknowledge that
which everybody already knows.
Besides, his movies
are like last century.
- What do you mean?
- To tell you the
truth, I'm looking
to start my own video
production company.
If you're looking for
a good investment,
this is the right place
to put your money.
- Don't you direct
films for Mr. Tefflor?
Wouldn't that be a
conflict of interest?
- It would be if
there was anything
of interest in Tef's films.
Well, look, sweetie,
I'm not going
to be with Tef forever, and,
the way things are going,
hell, his company's not
even going to be here
long enough for me to have
to get out of my contract.
- Contract?
- Yeah, you see, Tef likes
all his longterm employees
to sign this
exclusivity contract.
You know, especially
with all the accidents
that have been happening.
- Oh, yeah, I've heard
about those, strange.
Do you think that they could
be more than just accidents?
- I don't know, but it
just goes to show you
that Tef's on his way out.
Now, if you're looking
for a good investment,
Devlin Productions
would be a good place
to put your money
because our movies
have a much more wide appeal.
- Really, how so?
- The modern video market
demands more explicit material.
Tef's stuff is just too tame.
His stuff will play
on any basic cable.
- And your films would
be more explicit.
- More explicit
means more money.
- Well, I like
the sound of that.
You interest me, Mr. Devlin.
- Call me Frank, and
I'd love to show you
the difference between our
two production companies,
but, unfortunately,
I don't have any
of my product here with me.
- Well, maybe you could
show me in person.
[bluesy music]
- I'm really sorry for
all the screw-ups today.
- Oh, you did fine, sweetie.
You can't let old
Frank get you down.
- Thanks, you're really sweet.
- Besides, I can tell
you're no waitress.
- Oh?
- Let me guess, you
wanna be a Playpen model.
- Oh, yeah, you got
me, what gave it away?
- Well, there's a
couple of obvious clues.
- Oh, [chuckles] yeah, well,
you know, I always wanted
to model for Playpen
and I thought
that working here
would give me a leg up.
- You'll definitely have
your legs up all right.
- What do you mean?
- Look, Nikki, you seem
like a really sweet girl.
I know that being a
Playpen model seems
like a really glamorous thing.
- You bet!
- However, what you
have to do to get there,
well, I'm not really
sure that it's worth it.
- What do you mean?
- Tony Tefflor.
- Oh.
- You know, I used
to be a Playpen mode.
- Really?
- Actually, I was the first
Playpen Girl of the Year,
and that's what
started the tradition
of Tef dating the
girl of the year.
- Oh, you're dating Tef?
So is that why you're
not afraid of Frank?
- Was dating, but, as
time goes on, he moves on,
and now he's dating
some 19 year old
while I'm stuck here
schlepping drinks
for all the pigs
here at Playpen.
- But you're still so beautiful!
I mean, you could be
a Playpen girl now.
- You're sweet, but
I don't think so.
- No, seriously.
- Really, you think so?
- Yeah, yes!
Look at you, that face,
those eyes, those lips.
- Yeah, I should
probably lock that door
before you get to my
milky white thighs.
[birds tweet]
Laura the photographer,
I'm sure of it.
- No, no, no, it's
Mo the waitress.
She hates Tef for
what he did to her,
and who could blame her?
He used her up and
threw her away.
It's just like this plot I
saw on my soap the other day.
- He did the same
thing to Laura,
and she's really, really
bitter about the whole thing.
- Ladies, ladies, please,
now, if we're gonna
start accusing every
former centerfold
that Tef dated and
dumped, we're gonna have
half the models in this
town on our suspect list.
- Well, maybe they should be.
- Look, Tef dated
a lot of models,
and none of those
relationships ended well,
but only Laura and Mo were
present at the accidents.
- That's true, but they
weren't both present
at all of them.
Laura was on the film shoots
and Mo was at the club.
- She's got a point.
- Maybe they're working together
in some sort of
evil, twisted plot.
- No, but there was one
person who had access
to all the places
accidents happened.
Frank Devlin.
He manages the club, and
he shoots the videos,
and, if his contract
becomes voided,
he can start his own production
company free and clear.
- All right, we have a
long list of suspects.
There's nothing to do but
just keep on investigating.
- Absolutely, we're headed
over to the club right now.
I think it's time
we meet Mr. Tefflor
and find out what he
has to say for himself.
- I think that's a good idea.
But be careful!
- Do you think maybe there
could be evil twins involved?
You know, you can never
trust those evil twins.
- Yeah, you should know.
[Nikki giggles]
- Hello, ladies,
I'm Tony Tefflor.
Playpen magazine,
Playpen nightclub,
Playpen Productions, all part
of the Playpen
Incorporated family.
- Mr. Tefflor, we need
to make this quick
before Frank
returns to the club.
- I sent him across
town on an errand.
We have plenty of
time, and, please,
everybody calls me Tef.
Ah, I see you've noticed
my trademark PJs.
Oh, it's just part of the image.
You know, sexy man
about town who spends
all of his time in
bed and seldom alone,
if you know what I mean.
Women find it irresistible.
- Really?
- Oh.
- Mr. Tefflor, I'm sorry,
Tef, let me introduce myself.
I'm Sandy Banner.
This is Jasmine St. James.
And Nikki Resnik.
- Such beautiful women
to be private detectives.
Perhaps I have some privates
you would like to detect.
- We are not that good.
Tef, as you know, we've been
undercover the last few days,
investigating your operations.
- Yes, how's that going?
Oh, I saw your
pictures, by the way.
They're wonderful,
just wonderful.
- Aw, thanks, I think.
- So far we have a
lot of suspects, but
not a lot of proof.
- Well, when you're as
fantastically successful,
as filthy rich, and incredibly,
incredibly sexy as I am,
you have a lot of enemies.
- Sure.
- So who are your suspects.
- Frank the club manager.
Laura the photographer.
And your head cocktail
waitress Maureen.
- Perhaps you've already
heard I used to date
both Laura and Maureen.
- Yes.
- They may have cause
to hate me, but kill me?
That's preposterous.
But when you're as
fantastically successful, as-
- Filthy rich and
incredibly, incredibly sexy,
yes, we know.
- So you do find me sexy?
Of course you do, my dear.
- I'm sorry, Mr. Tefflor, can
we just stick to the case?
- As I said, Sandy, I
have a lot of enemies.
Any one of the people you
named could have it in for me.
Tomorrow night, I'm
going to have a ceremony
to unveil the Playpen
Girl of the Century.
I can't afford any
more accidents.
Do you understand?
- Oh, yes, sir, we
will do our best.
- I hope that's good enough.
- My best is always good enough.
- I'm sure it is.
- Tef, you don't by
any chance happen
to have an evil twin, do you?
- Oh, come on.
- He might be the evil twin.
- Okay, let's get out of here.
Frank.
- Sandy.
What are you doing here?
Come back to accept my proposal?
- Proposal?
- Business proposal.
- Oh.
- What are you doing, Nikki?
- Huh?
- Why am I paying you
six bucks an hour?
I should have you
arrested for loitering.
Get busy, we open for
dinner in half an hour.
- Yes, sir!
- I better get going, as well.
Big day tomorrow.
- Bye.
- You know these girls?
- Oh, I'm just trying to
get to know the business.
You know, doing my due
diligence if I'm gonna invest.
- Still thinking about investing
in this old broken down company?
- Oh, you know, there is
some name value there.
Playpen magazine is
known around the world.
- Past tense, baby, past tense.
Devlin Productions is gonna
wipe them off the map,
until Tef is just a distant
memory in some erotic museum.
- Wow, sounds personal.
Is there a problem between
you and Mr. Tefflor?
- Tef got me started
in this business
when nobody else
would, gave me a break.
- Sounds like you owe him.
- Yeah, it's that
damn contract of his.
He thinks that if
I work for him,
I'm gonna work for
a lifetime for him.
It's not gonna happen, baby.
I'm gonna break
free, break free now.
[quiet music]
- What the hell's going on here?
- Hello, my dear.
- Get out, now.
- I don't think so.
I found this.
I'm well aware of
who you really are.
- So now that you
know who I really am,
what exactly do you
plan to do about it?
- Not sure yet.
If I tell my boss that you've
been investigating him,
he's probably not gonna
take that too kindly.
- Do you have to tell him?
- Well, maybe I could
be convinced not to.
- What exactly do you
want, do you want money,
'cause I don't have any.
- I don't want your
money, I want you.
- You mean?
[sultry music]
[Jasmine moans]
- Cut, cut!
Cut.
- How was that, Mr. Devlin?
- That was awful!
That was horrible!
People wanna believe that you
are in love with this guy,
not that this guy is
here to do your taxes!
- What do you mean?
- What do you mean
what do I mean?
Look, you have to be sexy.
You have to make
love to the camera.
- Well, I thought I was supposed
to be making love to Burt.
[Frank sighs]
- Ah, why no one
ever thought to put
a brain in a beautiful
head is beyond me.
- That's not very
nice, Mr. Devlin.
- Shut up, Burt.
- Yes, sir.
- Okay, we're gonna
do this again, okay?
We're gonna do this
again, all right,
from where we left off, and
you two are on the bed, okay?
This time with passion,
okay, with passion!
- Don't worry, I've done
a million of these things.
Frank yells a lot, but he
doesn't mean anything by it.
- I hope so.
- We're gonna do this one great.
- Thanks.
- And action.
[dramatic music]
- Jas, look out!
[Jasmine screams]
[shattering]
- Did you get that?
- [Jasmine] I
could've been killed.
- Thank God you're okay.
- Well, if it wasn't for that
hunka hunka horrible actor,
I wouldn't have been.
- Well, that certainly
does narrow down
our list of suspects.
- Laura was working with the
light just before it fell,
but that Frank.
- Yeah, he definitely
has a motive.
He thinks Tef is
holding him back,
and that contract he's under
is really frying his ass.
- Okay, so it's got
to be Laura or Frank.
They were the only
ones who were present,
except for the hunka actor.
- Not quite.
Mo didn't show up for work
today, called in sick.
Very suspicious.
- Great, we're
back to square one.
- Yeah, it looks like it.
- This is ridiculous.
We're getting nowhere
with this case,
and, tomorrow
night, Tef announces
the Playpen Girl of the Century.
- Yeah, they were talking
about it all day at the club.
It's being held there.
- Okay, we've really got to
turn up the heat on this.
You've got to come up with
something before then.
If ever there was an
opportunity to drive
Playpen Incorporated
into the ground,
that would be some sort of
deadly accident at this event.
- You're exactly right, Benny.
We're all gonna be there,
and we've gotta be on our toes.
- I'm telling you guys, I'm
convinced that it's Frank.
Those beady little eyes
and his furrowed brow?
He just looks like a killer.
- Not exactly evidence that
will stand up in court,
but your instincts
have been right before.
We're gonna keep a
very close eye on him.
In fact, I think I have a plan.
- Ooh, I love plans! [giggles]
[quiet music]
- Hey, Mo.
- [Mo] Laura.
- Getting ready for
the big night, I see.
Think you got a chance at
Playpen Girl of the Century?
- I was Tef's favorite
once, so you never know.
- [chuckles] Well, we were all
Tef's favorite at some point.
- What about you, you
think you have a chance?
I mean, it's the girl in front
of the camera that counts,
not the girl behind it.
- Ah, said the girl
behind the bar counter.
- [sighs] Let's face it, Laura,
neither one of us have a chance.
I mean, Tef, he used us
up and tossed us aside.
- I know, this whole
Playpen Girl of the Century
is just his last ditch attempt
to save his crumbling empire.
- Is the company really
in that much trouble?
- Would you care if it was?
[chuckling]
- Are you kidding?
I mean, let's face it,
Laura, he screwed both of us,
literally and figuratively.
- Yeah, so, you think a little
payback might be in order?
- Mm, I like the way you think.
- Yeah, and you are very
sexy when you are devious.
- I know.
- What is it with me and
Playpen girls this week?
- Ex-Playpen girls.
- Oh, even better.
[soft music]
[patrons chattering]
- Okay, girls,
you know the plan.
When Frank gets
here, we have to keep
him occupied until
the announcement.
- Right.
- Got it.
- My, my, my.
- Hello, Mr. Tefflor.
- Please, call me Tef,
everybody calls me Tef.
Are you to be my bodyguard
for this evening?
- Oh, no, Jasmine here,
she'll be your side all night.
Nikki and I will be around
making sure nothing happens.
- Jasmine, my latest
Playpen Girl of the Month.
- Well, thank you.
- Oh, no, no, no, no, thank you.
Tell me, my dear, do you prefer
the month of
October or November?
- I can see that
she'll have no problem
staying by his side.
- Yeah, the problem's
gonna be detaching
herself at the end of the night.
- Sandy, how you
doing, good to see you.
I didn't know you were
gonna be here this evening.
- Oh, you know, I'm
just keeping an eye
on my prospective investment.
- Oh, still thinking
about investing
in Playpen entertainment?
I was hoping I'd
convinced you otherwise.
- Well, maybe I just need
a little more convincing.
Wanna go to your office?
- [chuckles] That's very
tempting, Miss Banner,
but, unfortunately,
I've got a ceremony
I must attend to, as I am
the manager of this club.
- Oh, I know you are
mighty important.
No, I've just got all this
money floating around,
I'd really hate to waste
it on a bad investment.
- Yes, well, I don't know.
- Well, Nikki here, I
think she wants to join us.
- Okay, all right,
let's make this quick.
Now, girls, this really
can't take long, okay?
- Frank, look at us,
is this really something
you wanna rush?
- Oh, is this thing on?
Hello, everybody, and welcome
to the Playpen Girl of
the Century extravaganza.
[clapping]
As everyone know, for
decades, the dream
of every little girl
in every little town
across this great nation
has been to become
a Playpen Girl of the Month.
Nothing says success like
a staple through the navel.
[laughing]
And once these fine
girls have attained
Playpen Girl of the Month,
the next step is Playpen
Girl of the Year.
For years, that has been
the pinnacle of achievement
for a Playpen girl.
But, now, by popular
demand, I introduce
the Playpen Girl of the Century.
[clapping]
The model that I have
chosen epitomizes
everything that I love
about a Playpen girl.
And so, now,
without further ado,
I bring you the Playpen
Girl of the Century,
Jasmine St. James!
- [Jasmine] Wow!
[clapping]
Wow!
- What?
Wait a goddamn minute, Tef!
How, how can she be Playpen
Girl of the Century?
I only photographed
her a few days ago!
- Yes, and you did
such a good job.
She's beautiful and charming.
- Oh, you son of a bitch!
- Mo, you, too?
- Yeah, you thought I was
beautiful and charming
and everything else
I'm sure you told
that little chippy when
you were screwing her.
- Ew, I've never had
sex with this guy.
- Like I believe that.
- It's all coming back
to haunt you now, Tef.
All the sleeping
around, all the lies
to every girl in a skirt who
dreamed of being somebody.
- Listen, listen to me, I
never had sex with that girl.
- And why would she be
the exception, huh, Tef?
- What would stop you
now from fooling around?
- Listen to me,
I haven't been able
to have sex in years.
- [Crowd] Ew!
- Really?
Oh, how sad for you.
- All right, sister, game's up.
- Where's Frank?
- Oh, he's all tied up.
[funky music]
- Tef, hello, Tef,
hello, anybody?
Help!
Help.
Tef?
I'm tied up. [cries]
Mo. [cries]
- Oh, Jasmine,
you saved my life.
How can I ever thank you?
- Hands off, creep.
This case is over, and,
apparently, so are you.
- Well, girls, we
did it, well done.
- Yay!
- Well, looks like another
successful assignment
for the Teeny
Weeny Bikini Squad.
- Sure was.
Frank admitted he was
behind the accidents.
He wanted Tef out of
business so he could
start a competing
production company.
- But what persuaded
Frank to spill the beans?
- Oh, I can be very persuasive.
[giggling]
- Okay, but what about
Laura and Maureen?
- Oh, just disgruntled
former girlfriends.
Pretty much every girl Tef
ever dated wanted to kill him.
So, right now, there's
a booking sergeant
at police headquarters
getting quite an eyeful.
- Yeah, well, I guess it
didn't do Tef much good, huh?
- [Women] Aw.
- Yeah, his image was
that of a virile man
who could bed any
woman he wanted.
Now that the truth came out,
nobody really cared anymore.
- So I guess that smoking jacket
really was a turnon
for women, huh?
Amazing.
- Well, at any rate, now
that that's all wrapped up,
we can finally go
on our vacation!
- About that vacation-
- Oh, no, Benny!
- Come on!
- Not again!
- We have another case,
and it just can't wait.
- Well, what is it this time?
- There was a skydiving
accident about a week ago.
Two people were killed.
They're thinking it
may be foul play.
- Skydiving, what does
that have to do with us?
- Well, it's nude skydiving.
- Oh, come on, get him, get him!
- Come here!
- I wanna go on vacation!
You said you promised!
- Girls, this would
normally be when I tell you
to pack your bikinis,
but, in this case,
I think you might
be overdressed.
[soft music]
- Do you think maybe there
could be evil twins involved?
You know, you can never
trust those evil twins.
[soft music]
- Oh, boy, I sense a lot
of nudity in our future.
[soft music]
- Most of the customers
here, they don't care
about the quality of the service
but the quantity of the server,
if you know what I mean.
[soft music]
- [Jasmine] Gee, that's
a bit much, isn't it?
- Well, it's the winter edition.
[soft music]
- Tef, Mo, Tef, Mo, anybody!
Help!
Help.
[soft music]
- Listen to me, Claude,
there's no reason
to get your panties in a twist.
[soft music]
- If I tell my boss that
you've been investigating him,
he's probably not gonna
take that too kindly.
[soft music]
- [Jasmine] You have a
subscription, don't you?
- Well, yes, but I
only read the articles.
[soft music]
- I haven't been able
to have sex in years.
[surf rock music]
[funky, mysterious music]
[light music]