♪ Ah ♪
♪ Webbo ♪
♪ Iced Out Records ♪
♪ I always told my mama ♪
♪ One day, we gonna be rich ♪
♪ And I'm a stand on that ♪
♪ Real talk ♪
♪ I just wanna be a millionaire ♪
♪ Got a million on my mind ♪
♪ While I'm on the grind ♪
♪ God bless the trap niggas
we just wanna shine ♪
♪ I just want to be
richer take care my fam ♪
♪ Make another 50 ball
and post it on the gram ♪
♪ Anything I rap about
that's my ghetto story ♪
♪ Six rings on my fingers
like I'm Robert Horry ♪
♪ I'm a young nigga balling
call me Steph Curry ♪
♪ Heard you niggas talking down ♪
♪ Cause you niggas corny ♪
Growing up in the hood,
you never know who you can trust.
- What up though?
- Family.
Friends.
Hell, you can't even trust your damn self.
Shit
nigga, you was supposed
to been pulled up on me!
- Shit, we leaving the West right now.
I'm headed to you right now as we speak.
- Aye, nigga.
I just go the call on a
sweet ass dice game, lic.
Nigga, are you ready for this shit nigga?
- Nigga you already know.
- Nigga, this the type
of shit we do right now.
Ooh wee!
Let's get this shit man.
- And I bet you they ain't
got they pistols on them.
- Man, I don't give a fuck
if they got 'em or not.
- You don't take.
Nigga, no bullshit.
When you get out here nigga,
you know what to do nigga.
- Aye nigga just make sure
that nigga don't point nigga.
- All right, be on your shit man.
- Nigga right now, nigga.
Matter of fact, nigga
pull up right there, dog.
- Right here?
- No, to the left, nigga.
You see that
round ass nigga right there?
That's my fat ass fucking cousin, Webbo.
He the fucking plug right now.
- Aye that's them niggas right there.
Nigga let's get out, and end
this shit right now, nigga.
- Oh word?
- My nigga, let me holler at you, bro.
Let me holler at you real quick.
- What's the deal, you good?
- Chilling like a motherfucking, man.
- What you been in to?
- Shit, it's slow around
this motherfucking man.
- Hell, yeah.
Ever since dude been gone,
shit done slowed up, huh?
- For real, for real.
You know, bro he used to hold shit down.
I probably aint know the shit.
Really, I'm just grinding right now
Bro, that music shit wasn't
really paying no bills,
So I ain't have the same
love emotions as all of them,
You feel me?
- Yeah, for sure I know
how that shit is bro,
you know what I'm saying?
- I pop in and I come over,
I come up with me a hit,
I can jump back in the game
because he held the fort down,
all the way, you feel me?
So I just be in and out
with that shit, for real.
- What's going on with that one situation
you was telling me about?
- Man people hit me from down the way say
come through and holler at him
and see what he was on, so.
I called Unc, he told
me come through later on
when I'm with it.
So I'm a shoot down
there and see what he on.
Yeah, I take it from there.
- You got to make it happen man,
we can't fall off around this bitch.
- You can't fall off.
These niggas get to laughing
around this motherfucker for falling off.
- And that's what they
waiting on for sure.
- They want a nigga to fall off,
I swear to God they do, man.
- Hell yeah.
- Real talk.
- All right, that's a bet, say no more.
- So what's up, are you ready?
- Aye, we can't hit this one, man.
- Why not nigga?
- Man, 'cause bro we got
something big and better.
- Man fuck that, let's get everything.
- I just got the motherfucking call nigga!
What the fuck you want this little shit,
or you wants some big shit?
- Nigga you said be ready, motherfucker!
- Man, fuck this shit!
- All right, man.
- We can get some bigger shit!
Saved by the bell.
- Little nigga, let's get it.
See to a nigga like me,
timing is everything.
One false move,
could cost you your life.
Webbo.
- Nephew, finally made it huh, man?
- What's going on man?
- Good man, good to see you, man.
How you been doing?
- Good to see you, too.
- Enter man.
Mi casa you casa, man.
See,
this a made nigga right here.
That's our uncle Cat.
Don't nothing moved through
the hood without his say so.
- Aye, where that nigga Six at?
- Aye, Six, bring your
big ass out here, bro!
Bro out here nigga.
- What's up with y'all boys?
- What's good, dog?
- That big ass nigga right there.
- Let me holler at you nigga.
Hey come here, man.
Let me talk to you on this
private shit real quick.
- Aye aye, on some real shit.
Hey man, what the fuck is that man?
Where the fuck the whip at?
- Man, dog don't worry about that.
That shit was too hot anyway man.
- What the fuck you
mean that shit too hot?
- I got something bigger than that.
- I need that bread, man,
should've got that fat motherfucker
when we seen him right
then and there nigga.
- Now where your strap?
- Nigga that shit in the house man.
But anyways dog,
why the fuck I'm not
we hit that lick nigga?
- Look man.
Remember the one I was
telling you about that one-
- Man, fuck that one nigga!
How the fuck are you gonna
tell me is you ready nigga
and I was ready nigga?
What's your problem?
- Shut the fuck up nigga!
You want this big shit, or you
won't that small petty shit?
- Nigga my kids got to eat right now!
I need it now!
- And I guarantee when we hit this shit,
your kids ain't gotta
worry about shit, nigga.
- All in, bro.
- The nigga I was locked up with
nigga he about to get
out nigga in a week, bro.
- So what that mean?
- And he got the whole thing planned, bro.
We gonna get all that shit in one.
- Everything?
- Everything nigga.
- Hey, you gotta get his man's, too.
- Man them niggas all gotta go, nigga!
Is you down or what, nigga?
I been down right now, nigga.
All right, nigga, say no more bro.
Let's get it.
- Nephew, heard you been out here
moving around real good, man.
- Trying to, man.
- Trying?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's always good to hear,
you know the streets talking
good about my nephew, man.
- Yeah.
- You know you family, man.
What the fuck's going on with Ice, man?
- He'll be home in a little bit.
- I mean they said like the
dude got 50 years or something.
- No man.
You know he always late.
He'll be home in no time.
For real for real.
He'll be home shortly.
- So what's your plans man
when he touch down, man?
That's what I need to know.
- I mean really move
forward with our music
and sign this deal for real, man.
- Deal, what do you mean deal?
- I mean this rap game, you can't.
I mean, he going to get
signed for sure, for sure.
I got faith in that.
And
see this nigga right here?
Yeah that's Baby, he
the other side though.
He been wanting us rock
with him for a minute,
but it's something
about him I don't trust.
♪ Head, shoulders, knees and toes ♪
- Yo big baby let me holler at you!
What's up Baby?
- What's going on?
- What's up my nigga?
- I don't know man, what
you doing with it man?
Talk to me, man.
- I'm chilling right now man.
- Yeah.
I've been hearing you
been making a little noise
around this motherfucker, man!
- You making the noise.
Look how you riding.
- Nah.
- You making all the noise.
- I ain't making no noise my nigga,
but you know your name's
been ringing baby.
You feel me?
So if the names is ringing
I gotta see what's happening, you feel me?
- I'm chilling, you're
making the noise man.
I'm chilling.
- Come on man be straight up with it.
- I'm straight up.
I'm not doing shit bro.
- What you getting for?
- I'm not doing nothing.
- So you ain't doing nothing?
- A little something man
but I ain't, you feel me?
I ain't riding like you.
- Man fuck all this man.
This for play play, man.
I heard about you.
You got some shit you put up
and all that, you feel me.
- I'm chilling man for real.
- Man we'll cut to the
small talk my nigga, listen.
I'll beat them things that you are getting
from dog over there by a thousand.
Fuck with me.
And I'll have it to your doorstep.
- Man you know I'm fucking
with Fat Cat right now.
For real, for real.
- I mean no disrespect
to dog and all that,
and I'm not really trying
to mention dog, you feel me?
I'm saying my nigga,
but the only way to win
is the win big baby.
You feel me?
Cheaper number at your doorstep
you can't be it my nigga.
- I'll just hit your line up, for real.
- I can dig that, that's respect.
- I'll holler at you.
For sure.
- Bae come here.
What we doing?
I'm washing dishes
right now.
All right I got you baby.
- All right.
- Fuck.
All right?
- What?
- Let's do something to
eat when I come back.
- When you get back?
From where?
- You ain't gotta cook no more
because I got to go get
my cousin from jail.
And it's probably gonna take
me about two, three hours.
'Cause he keep calling my phone, forgot.
- Two, three hours?
And why can't you just have
someone else pick him up?
I wanted to make some
good ass breakfast for us.
- If the shoe was on the other foot,
he would've came and got me.
So I'm gonna go get him,
and I'll be back.
You cook dinner.
It will be well.
And I'm out man.
- Yeah right.
You do this shit all the time.
You know you gonna be gone
all damn motherfucking day.
- I'm not going to be gone all day man.
- Yeah, you is.
I'm not man.
- Go.
- I'll take you to Ruth Chris.
- I was gonna make myself
some fucking breakfast.
Shit.
- Oh fuck.
For
the last five years.
This is the moment a nigga
been finally waiting for.
And look at this shit here,
these niggas still ain't on time, damn!
I got some plays in motion, though.
First day out, and it's
time to get back to it.
- Niggas can't even be on time dog.
I swear to God, man.
Wait til I see this nigga, bro.
Damn!
Got some words for that ass, nigga.
Called these niggas three times bro!
I swear to God bro.
You know who your niggas is
when you get locked up, nigga.
I'm done with niggas bro.
Done with niggas.
On everything I'm done.
Nah fuck that get me a cab.
I can't even fucking whistle no more, bro.
Nigga forgot how to whistle
when he got locked up, bro?
Damn!
♪ From the fights to the shoot outs ♪
♪ And the struggles God damn it ♪
♪ Been a long time coming ♪
♪ From the robbing to the stealing ♪
♪ Tryin' hustle God damn it ♪
- You gotta be fucking kidding me dog!
Are you serious nigga?
Damn!
♪ Been a lot of road running ♪
♪ First you stack your first 10 ♪
♪ Then you grind up on a 100 ♪
♪ Rest in peace my cousin Ryan ♪
♪ Yeah I love you ♪
♪ Yeah we miss you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
Oh, shit, cuz!
What's up cuz?
- What's up my nigga?
- Hell yeah. cuz what's up nigga?
- What's good?
- Come here, what's up nigga.
Give me some love nigga.
It's been five years.
- It'll be all right.
- Get back to it
- Ready to ride man.
- Come on get your shit, get back to it.
- Yeah let's move out
of this motherfucker.
I know you had to finance
this bitch or something.
Let's get it.
Welcome home man.
- Thank you.
- Man you know it's supposed to be
a good number on that shit.
I'll been down in a minute.
- Our shit?
- Yeah, I'm let y'all boys know
when that shit come through
- It's about that time for sure.
- I'm home baby!
What's up cuz?
- What's up cuz, you all right baby.
What the fuck, shit.
Motherfucker.
- What's up nigga?
God dammit, what's happening?
Aye, you looking good man.
- Look at you nigga, you got big.
Hell yeah.
- Nigga, I got big than a motherfucker.
- Eating your push ups and shit nigga?
- That little Tae Bo shit-
- Damn what's happening with you baby?
- Damn, shit I'm trying to get right man.
- I see you.
- You got me drop me off some shit man.
If y'all niggas got
something for me my, dog.
- I'm a hit your pockets
with something, man.
I ain't got it right
now bro, but I got you.
- My nigga.
- You know what I'm saying?
- Shit, I know I can
hit something right now.
Nigga, I can smell that shit right there.
Nigga, let me hit that motherfucker, nigga
- Hold on, hold on, cousin nigga hold on.
- Hold on man.
- Nigga this is my hood nigga.
Who is these niggas?
This my hood nigga.
These little ass niggas over here.
Nigga, this is my shit, nigga.
Look at this shit.
My first day out.
They lucky a nigga on probation,
I'm a have to drop one of them niggas.
- That's my cousin.
That's my cousin dog.
- That's how niggas playing it!
This is my hood!
The fuck!
It's my shit.
- Jay, what's up my nigga?
Hey, what's going on man?
- What's been going on with it?
Now that's Jay.
Real low key, but he a
hustling motherfucker.
- Where the fuck you been at man?
Heavy on the paint.
Heavy on the weight.
- Let me holler at you....
- What's up man?
- I picked him up from prison for real.
- Ever since you've been gone, you know,
a nigga had to go out here,
and do what he has to do.
And I found somebody that's good.
where I'm getting them at
a nice number too, Web.
All right, for sure.
You on bullshit man.
- I mean the quality that
I'm getting right now
and after numbers bro,
it would be kind of a fool.
But you know, you've been my mans.
I've been fucking with
you for a long time.
So, I'm sitting here listening.
I'm trying to see what you got.
Maybe we could both can
make something happen.
- How 28 sound?
- 28 sound good, man but I think
if we go holler at my man's and shit,
you know what I'm saying?
If we both put some in together and shit,
He'll drop the number a little
bit and thrown us something.
- You know I don't do business
outside the family though.
- Man, I know how you is Web.
But man, that's an
opportunity to make man.
Look man, you see how I was, man?
I was a worker.
I'm like the fucking boss now.
♪ Just counted up 20 racks ♪
♪ My new Rollie worth 10K ♪
♪ Hit the bar threw 20 stacks ♪
♪ Got 20 traps that's full of yay ♪
♪ Shot it out with a fuck nigga ♪
♪ That wanted beef
'cause he full of hate ♪
♪ I put cheese on a nigga head ♪
♪ If you want to eat
come fill your plate ♪
♪ Any problems my nigga solve it ♪
♪ Running shit like my niggas jogging ♪
♪ 50Gs in the pillow cases ♪
♪ Money talk, that's pillow talking ♪
- What's going on baby?
- Everything good?
- Yeah, everything good,
I can't complain at all.
- See, business is good.
- Yeah, man.
Business is good.
- Business good and all that.
- Got the new chains, I see that.
You doing all right?
- Yeah, man.
Thanks to you man.
- You know how we do it man?
You know we got to eat.
- Yeah.
- What's on your mind Jay?
- Man, well I'm coming down here, man.
I got a proposition for both of us now.
And I think it's a good
money making opportunity.
- What's your proposition, Jay?
You know, I'm always here to hear it.
Well, you know how,
since you helped me out and shit.
I been turning up in the spotlight.
In the zoo, I got it locked down and shit.
Well, I bumped into one of my old guys,
who was up in the Detroit area.
And I know you said you was looking
for something out there
in the Detroit area.
I love money, Jay.
You know, talk to me, man.
- You know what I'm saying?
So my guy, he move like me.
He said he got a good number,
but I don't think he could beat you.
'Cause I see how you move
and I see how you work.
But this guy, he move like me and shit.
It'd be beneficial and shit.
Cause he said-
- You really think we should
expand this Jay right now?
- What you think?
- It's a good cause.
- Is he a stand up dude?
Do you know this guy like that?
- Yeah man.
- You fuck with him.
He was my guy hitting them off to me
before I started fucking with you.
If it wasn't for him,
you know what I'm saying?
I wouldn't have got in the limelight
for you to be able to notice me.
- You doing good over here.
You my number one right now.
Shit.
- So what you want to do?
You want me to bring my mans in,
and we can set up a meeting or something?
- Listen man.
All money good money.
But you going to stand up for
this motherfucker right here?
- Yes.
- You vouch for his ass?
- Man, I personally vouch for him, man.
- Jay, I don't need this shit, man.
I don't need no motherfucking heat.
I don't need no motherfucking problems.
We were already doing good.
We got a good business going right now.
Man, the guy he moves smooth.
He move like me man.
And he move fast, man.
Real money getter.
- As long as you vouch
for him man, we good.
All right.
- What do you want me to sell you fam?
- Shit, it's 100.
Let's get it on.
- Let's get this.
- My man.
- Think this through man.
That put me in a fucked
up position, my nigga dog.
- Cuz, I don't care about that.
- Nigga, you just did five years dog.
You don't need to know them niggas, man.
You don't know what a nigga capable of man
or nothing man.
- Them niggas ran up on me.
- Cuz.
Listen, I could have handled
that, a fight is a fight.
Once you pull out a gun, 'cuz.
Then you shooting at the
motherfucking ground man.
- Shit it's better than
shooting at the sky.
- You ain't even shooting
nobody though, cuz.
So what the fuck you shooting a gun for?
How you gonna pick up a nigga strap
and start shooting my nigga?
- Oh okay. You Pablo now?
- No, ain't say I'm Pablo dog.
But this my shit over here, nigga.
This ain't your shit, nigga.
You've been gone for five years, my nigga.
I ain't trying to disrespect or nothing,
but dog this my shit, nigga.
- Cuz, don't forget-
- Don't be doing that shit man.
- I'm the big cousin nigga.
You the little big cousin, nigga.
I'm the big cousin.
- No, that don't matter cuz.
I got structure out here man.
- Oh, nigga's got structure.
- Yeah, I got structure.
- Now nigga wanna use big words.
Niggas get locked up-
Nigga do five years, five years,
and now niggas want to
talk about structure.
- This is my shit over there, man.
This my shit, man.
You weren't even out
fucking 20, 30 minutes.
You get into a scrap already dog.
- I feel you.
- You can't be doing
that shit my nigga man.
- I feel you.
Fuck them niggas though.
- Cuz, listen I'm a squash this shit man.
- All right.
- I'm squash this shit
before it even get too far.
- All right.
- Nigga you already shot a nigga gun dog.
- My bad man.
- Goddamn man.
- We got to get rid of that bitch.
You right, you right.
- Get rid of it for what my nigga?
- Shit, my hand prints on it.
Even though I ain't catch no body,
nigga I still-
All right.
- Come on man.
- Damn man, all right, dog.
Five bro, five long ones too, cuz.
Damn.
My bad my bad, man.
I ain't trying to fuck up the spot dog.
I'm a chill dog.
I'm a chill, I'm a chill.
- Everyone doing all right?
- What's up my nigga?
- Who the fuck is this nigga?
- Chill out man.
- Bro, I was in the old hood.
Overhead some niggas talking about
the shit that went down earlier.
You know what I'm saying?
They say they heavy though,
not too much you, but gray head.
You ain't hear that shit from me.
- Fuck them niggas man.
Man, you know what it is.
- That's what the fuck I
been talking about, dog.
You hear that shit?
- I keep telling you to chill out, man.
- This is my shit bro.
- This my shit.
- Nigga, Donald Trump don't
got shit on me, nigga!
- Man fuck that man,
you're talking that shit.
This is real life, nigga.
This is real life, man.
- I'm taking you to the crib.
- Hoe ass nigga, man.
Hoe ass nigga.
- I'm taking you to the crib.
Come on man.
You don't even know that nigga.
- I just want some hoes,
let's go to the fucking crib dog.
Ah shit.
Hey cuz.
What's up nigga?
- Why the fuck you not tell me
there ain't no TV in that motherfucker?
I'm ain't trying to go to
sleep that early nigga.
Goddamn, fuck you watching?
- It's a guest room, man.
- It's a guest room man, what's up man?
- Let me I ask you a question?
- Shoot.
- Why the fuck do you still play
like we kids my nigga?
When we grown as fuck my nigga?
- We stuck in our youth cuz.
That's the key to living
life for a long time.
Man I was in there reading the Bible, man.
You know want one of the scriptures said?
- What?
- I don't know 'cause
they smoked them niggas.
They was smoking them niggas, cuz.
They was smoking all them niggas, cuz.
I swear to God!
- Is you drunk bro?
- I don't know let me ask is this nigga?
Is you drunk bro?
Is you drunk?
- I'm done talking to you.
- Cuz listen, man.
I ain't gonna lie to you man,
I sent a couple of text messages out,
and niggas said that
you really on that man.
And it's like-
- Man.
- You on for real.
Like the crib nice.
And the floors is nice and marble,
and you got all that shit cuz.
But I'm saying like,
I'm really trying to you say is,
nigga when you gonna look
out for your family nigga?
- Man, listen.
I'm gonna look out for you.
I already told you that, nigga.
But you gotta move right bro.
You moving all wrong
you just got out bro.
You moving all wrong, man.
Nigga you're drunk too, bro.
Like, What the fuck man?
- Man this motherfucker
recline at all, man?
Does this motherfucker recline?
- Bro, I'm trying to talk to
you about some serious shit.
You out here just drinking
and all that type of shit, man.
- Nigga, I never heard of a nigga
being serious on another
nigga first day out.
Nigga, it's party time nigga.
You said we was gonna ride,
said we was gonna have some bitches.
And you don't got no TV in the guest room.
You bullshitting cuz.
You bullshitting, man!
Man, where the
fuck is the money at man?
Where's my money at man?
Now this Rico.
You can't trust him as far
as you can see.
- Where my money at man?
- Cuz a hothead.
- The money you and motherfucking Mitch
ran off with motherfucker.
- I don't know what
you talking about, man?
- You know exactly what
I'm talking about, man.
Where the fuck is the money, man?
You ain't got it on you?
- No, man.
- What you mean you you
ain't got it on you?
Man, where's the money man.
You gonna die in here, man.
Open your mouth.
Okay?
Where's the money at man?
Open your mouth man.
Open your mouth.
Where the money at?
Back at your mama house, man.
- Yeah, I hear you.
- Have that money.
24 hours.
You hear me?
- Right, right.
- Or this is gonna
happen to your mama man.
Okay?
Go clean yourself up.
You're a good guy.
I don't want to kill you man.
Have my money in 24 hours man.
- All right.
- All right?
- Come on.
Get the motherfucker front door man.
Debo, come here.
Rico, what the you got
going on over here man?
- Hey man, who the fuck is this man?
Who is the this?
- What the fuck you got going on here?
That's my motherfucking body guard nigga.
- I tell you every time.
- What you got doing on here?
- Every time I do something,
this motherfucker show up.
- Every time I establish-
- This motherfucker stole money from me!
- Now who the fuck is this motherfucker?
Man get the fuck up!
Who is this motherfucker right here man?
- You take care of the business then.
- Every time you get yourself
into fucking shit man.
- You take care of business.
You take care of the business.
- Man fuck this motherfucker.
- You want to argue all the time?
Take care of him.
You always come and fucking me up.
You fucking me up.
- Get the fuck out of here.
In my establishment motherfucker?
- It's my money!
- In my motherfucking establishment?
- Man, lights out motherfucker.
Man, if you ever do that shit
in my motherfucking establishment again,
I'm gonna smoke you my goddamn self.
- I swear to God I'm gonna
smoke you my goddamn self.
In my motherfucking business,
my establishment motherfucker?
- Who do you call?
- I don't give a fuck.
Not at my establishment!
- Give me my gun man.
- Get rid of that fucking body,
- and get rid of the fucking gun man.
- You know what?
- What motherfucker?
- Motherfucker.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Charles, Charles.
- You know what, you next.
- We'll see, motherfucker.
- What the fuck Charlito?
- Hey Jay.
- What's been going on?
- Aye Jay, I got some crazy shit going on.
Give me a minute man.
Go to my office dog.
Step into my motherfucking house.
I'll be there in a minute.
- Man, what the fuck.
- Debo, let's go.
Jay.
Man.
Charlito, I don't know what
the fuck you got going on here?
- Fuck all that,
let's handle motherfucking
business right now.
That's another damn day, cuz.
- That's what I came to do, man.
- What's up, hat you got for me?
Talk to me.
- Here man.
This the payment for the last shipment.
- That's all set on that, what's going on?
- Hey man, I came to talk business
about my motherfucking
guy in the city man.
- The guy you were talking about
from Detroit and shit?
- Yeah man, he ready to make a move.
I'm ready to make a move.
You said you ready to make money,
let's make this shit happen.
- All right, set it up man.
Give the time and
motherfucking place, man.
We do this in a week.
- All right, let's make it happen, jack.
- All right bet.
- So what about that
shit the other day, man?
- You see this silly ass nigga on TV man.
I told you bro, listen bro,
let me tell you something.
I told you bro I supposed to
been wiped this nigga ass man.
- I understand that bro.
But listen, you get to
doing all this wild shit.
- Let me tell you something.
Let me break something out to you.
- Is you still talking
about that shit, pops?
What shit?
- About Charlito.
How you know about that?
- The street's talking,
keep your gun on you, pops.
- Man, get the fuck out man.
Take your ass in the room.
Anyway, like I was saying-
- That's the shit I'm
talking about, the streets.
Bro, you see what I mean yo?
Bro, listen to me bro.
You fuck with the money bro.
You start dropping niggas
doing all this extra shit.
- Listen bro, listen bro.
- Here, keep mine.
I don't trust that motherfucker.
What the fuck?
- Damn man, this block
ain't changed a bit.
Make sure my baby still
live there though, man.
Shit, if she don't answer fuck it,
I'm a just say shit,
I'm gonna sell her some shit.
Damn, that nigga got
some big ass rims, bro!
Everybody getting money but me.
Yeah I know she still live there.
She better not have no new nigga.
That's all I'm saying bro.
'Cause shit, I'm on it, flat out.
Watch my fucking steps.
She better not have that bad
ass dog back there no more.
Oh no, we good.
Woo hoo!
She ain't got no doorbell?
- Who is that?
Who is it?
- Open the door and find out.
Damn!
What's up?
- Mm-hmm.
- Damn, girl!
What are you doing here?
The ass bitch lives down the street.
You want to come here now?
- Wait, what bitch down the street?
- Keisha, you know who I'm talking about?
- Oh my God, Keisha who?
- Don't play with me.
- Keisha who?
- The one and only Keisha.
- First of all, Keisha can't spell
so I can read none of her letters.
- I'm sure she can't.
- You my heartbeat girl.
Damn look, I done Uber-ed over here
Shit I don't got no ride home.
I need something to drink.
- That's not my problem.
She was there for you
when you was writing her.
You wasn't writing me.
So-
- 'Cause I didn't have enough commissary.
You didn't write me either.
You ain't put nothing on my books.
- Because I heard about Keisha.
- I heard about your little
play that you got going on too.
- Don't worry about me.
- Damn!
Can I get some lemonade or something?
I know you've got something to drink.
You always got something to drink.
- Cliff, you always do this.
- Do what?
- You've done this before
you even was locked down.
- Babe, baby I'm sorry.
- No. No.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Can I get something to drink?
- Oh my God.
- Fine ass.
Come on girl.
I know you got some Kool-Aid
in there or something.
Damn!
Woo hoo!
- I ain't worried about
that bitch ass nigga.
- All right, man.
- On your ass boy.
- Better watch that guy.
- Ball up man, ball up man.
- That nigga ain't hitting on shit man.
- Dumb ass nigga man.
- Take that shit back man,
stop hacking him, man.
- Shoot the fucking ball, man!
- Man!
- Where that bag?
- You ain't even give me-
- You owe me some money, man.
How long you gonna owe me that money man?
- Hey, you ain't even
give me no time big fella.
- You around this bitch
draped up and everything bro.
Give me my money, strip nigga!
Give me my money.
- Hell no!
Man take this shit off, man.
Take that shit off man.
That this shit off man.
Take it off man.
Take this shit off nigga.
I ain't playing with you nigga.
Run that way nigga.
Nigga run!
Go that way, go that way!
It's because of you nigga?
- Hey, bro you better watch
where you pointing that bitch man.
- Where did you get that bag
thinking you run it
around this bitch nigga.
That's your people nigga.
I was already up nigga.
- All right now.
- All right now what?
- Who the fuck is this nigga, man?
- This coward ass nigga, man.
- I'm telling you.
- Yeah, okay.
- You know what time it is.
You know what time it is.
You know what, I'm a
see you in a minute man.
It's on.
Okay.
What you talking about man.
Yeah ride that bike on somewhere, man.
- The next time-
- Get on up out of here, playboy.
Man that nigga Rico
always on some bullshit, man.
- Hey chill out, that's my pops.
I'll blow your ass!
- Ain't that your gun round the corner.
- Whoa!
Man I
told y'all that nigga Rico
was a hot head.
- Give this to Mikey.
I'm out of here men.
Word on the street,
he made that nigga strip for $50.
I got one of my wild homies
pulling up on me from the pen.
I'm home now.
Still broke as hell.
This time we put a play out.
- What's up nigga?
- Who the fuck...
Oh shit! That's my
motherfucking dog nigga.
- Don't know nothing about that ball.
- What's good nigga?
- What's good with you man?
- Want you on nigga,
one on one, what's up?
Trying to shoot seven's niggas.
- Man, y'all cry baby ass
niggas get y'all ball.
- What's up man?
- Let me holler at you over here, man.
- What's good nigga.
Good to see you, dog.
- That aint no motherfucking Lamborghini.
Nigga you said you had a
Lamborghini in the joint nigga.
- Yeah man.
- Fuck it.
It's cool. It's cool.
- What's going with you though bro?
I've been calling your
motherfucking phone man.
- Man, slow motion dog.
My shit was off.
My girl was tripping and shit.
But I got a new number.
I gotta get that bitch to you.
- Everything looks good?
- Everything been straight.
Slow motion.
Trying to get back out of here.
- Check you over here man.
I don't want....
- Them your niggas?
- These niggas be talking.
I just met these niggas at the court dog.
Non hooping ass niggas.
Hell yeah dog, fucking up.
- So, what's up with
that little one lic man?
- Oh, shit man.
We good, but I just need a
little bit more time dog.
This nigga, that nigga on now bro.
I mean, when we was locked
up, it was slow motion.
- Nah man, fuck all that man.
I need the shit now, bro.
- Let me build some
chemistry with the nigga.
You know what I'm saying?
- But you said you had
everything all together man.
- I got it bro.
I got my niggas ready.
They waiting on you.
You making me look bad, bro.
- Just tell them niggas we need
a little bit more time, bro.
We get a little more time,
we milk this nigga a little bit more bro.
and then we gonna get that nigga bro.
- So he getting it like that?
- We gonna get more.
He on right now, bro.
We gonna get that nigga, bro.
I just need a little bit more time bro.
Tell them niggas to hold
their horses a little bit.
And we going to that nigga for sure.
- All right man, say less.
So what's up nigga?
What's been good nigga,
welcome home, buster.
- Yeah, I'm home bro.
I feel good dog.
Where the hoes at niggas?
Who
would have ever thought,
me linking up with the
neighborhood Jack boy?
Desperate times calls
for desperate measures.
Now, see I met this nigga in the pen.
Some thought I was
sweet, and they tried it.
No, I ain't saying I needed that nigga,
but he did have my back.
So I kinda owe him a favor,
and he made a proposition
that I couldn't quite refuse.
- Big nigga.
- Nigga, you look like a fucking stick.
The fuck you talking about?
That's the same way you
had when you went in.
- Nigga fuck you, nigga fuck you!
- You gonna eat good
though off that shit though
if you ain't bullshitting.
- We is going to eat good bro,
'cause we going to get that nigga.
Like I said, we just need
a little bit more time man.
- A little bit more time, nigga.
We need a little more time, and time,
niggas like us man, we rushing.
I know man. I know.
Shit, what the fuck you been on, man?
- I've been on shit been
hitting these little
petty ass lics from here and there
trying to get it up.
But these niggas around this bitch
ain't got shit for real.
- It's a drought?
- Yeah.
We done took everybody shit.
- Damn.
Nigga, you don't even need this lic.
- Hell no, yes the fuck I do nigga.
I'm fucked up too.
- Why you think the Lamb gone and shit?
Damn.
I ain't got shit.
- Tie my fucking shoe up dog.
Let me hit water bro, I'm thirsty as fuck.
We was hooping and shit earlier.
Damn nigga, you done drink it all.
The fuck.
It ain't shit in here.
- T what up fool?
- Yeah.
Let me holler at you right quick.
Get in real quick.
Cool.
- Damn bro. Y'all niggas
be playing it dog.
I swear to God bro, on
everything I love bro.
But shit, you know what I'm saying?
I swear to God on these niggas.
Who the fuck?
♪ Wild nigga ♪
♪ woo hoo ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm a wild nigga ♪
♪ Catching body ♪
♪ Wild nigga huh ♪
♪ Bitch I'm a wild nigga huh ♪
♪ Yeah I'm a wild nigga ♪
- I told you Keisha.
You like a pencil without no lead baby.
Without you it's no point.
Hold on.
Nigga I have been fucking...
Man bro where you at dog?
Nigga I've been calling
you for three days.
Nigga I know you...
Man pull up man.
Fuck that.
Pull up.
Bye dog.
Yeah so like I was saying though.
Oh at my motherfucking cousin.
Man you know I told you
these niggas shout at me and shit.
I might have to get my lethal weapon
on in this motherfucker.
Yeah.
Hold on.
It's this nigga right here.
I'm a call you back baby.
I know, I'll call you back.
- Cuz, what's up man?
- Man what's up nigga?
I been calling you dog.
Damn!
I know you heard that shit bro.
Them niggas fucking shot out at me,
killed Bean Dip and everything, bro.
- What I tell you the other night, dog?
You act like them niggas
wasn't gonna come back?
- Man these niggas-
- Dog listen, cuz you
been gone for five years.
I know how niggas roll over here cuz.
- These niggas tripping.
- Man listen, dog...
Dog, listen we gonna take care
of that shit for real though.
- I swear to God, bro.
- I don't let shit slide
like that my nigga.
- My fucking life flashing before me.
- When you jumping you're jeopardizing
what I got going on.
I told you the other night, my nigga.
- What I'm supposed to do?
- And you sitting out
here drinking and shit.
- These niggas shooting at me though.
What I'm I supposed to do?
Nigga this ain't he matrix
I can't dodge bullets.
- Listen bro, keep this on you.
- That's what I'm talking about, nigga.
- Keep that on you man, keep that on you.
- Nigga I got the juice now, nigga.
Yeah.
- Nigga why you always
think shit like game, dog.
- There ain't gon be
no game no more, nigga.
War!
- Cuz, listen man, chill out, man.
We gotta go take care
of this business man.
- Right now?
- I about to introduce
you to my nigga man.
- Oh hell yeah, let's do it.
- Nigga remember the dude
I was telling you about
that's been doing everything
you were doing before you left?
- Okay.
- I gonna introduce you to my man.
- Oh, the nigga that took my job?
- Man listen bro.
I'm a introduce you to my man, bro.
- Let's do that shit.
- Don't be all that...
- I'm gonna let you talk.
- Talking crazy and all that shit, man.
- You handle all the business then.
- Cuz, you done became a clown
since you got locked up my nigga.
- Clown red nose nigga now, huh?
- Yeah, man you act like a clown my nigga.
So word in
the hood is I'm a clown now.
Niggas pulling up in
white Vettes, new trucks.
And here I am broke as hell,
sitting on another nigga porch
talking to another nigga bitch.
These niggas got me fucked up.
You all right?
This is my cousin Cliff man.
- What's the deal man?
- What's up with you?
- You all right?
- Chilling.
- This my nigga Jay I
was telling you about.
This is Cliff bro.
- Damn, y'all niggas eating good!
- Yeah.
- I'm ready to get back in nigga.
- All right, let's get on her bro.
- Come hop in with me.
- Let me move my shit.
- Damn nigga, what's that a 2020?
That bitch cold nigga.
♪ Shit got slow ♪
♪ I gotta make some shake ♪
♪ A lot of turned their back ♪
♪ So I went the other way ♪
♪ They locked my niggas Ice up ♪
♪ And this rap shit slow ♪
♪ I had to hop on the road ♪
♪ And head to the nearest pros ♪
♪ I ran into a white boy in Kentucky ♪
♪ He said he can make a
nigga rich before I'm 30 ♪
♪ He said grab some puppy cat ♪
♪ And have a few babies ♪
♪ Cop a trailer, sit back and
watch this town go crazy ♪
♪ Started off down a 100 ♪
♪ Then we make the shit triple ♪
♪ All from me what I buy 100 ♪
♪ How can I lose, I can't lose ♪
♪ I been winning I'm a winner ♪
♪ Bitch I ball you niggas D up ♪
♪ Now I sit back and call the plays ♪
♪ With my feet up ♪
♪ That fatigue I'm plotting on it ♪
♪ That's your main bitch ♪
♪ I hit her for a couple of 100 ♪
♪ That ain't tricking my nigga ♪
♪ I just like the share the wealth ♪
♪ Because I get it my nigga ♪
♪ I'm a go and get it before I do it out ♪
♪ Ain't no other options
in these streets ♪
♪ I can't fall off ♪
♪ Rather count it up ♪
♪ I ain't trying to beef ♪
♪ Only thing that matter
is the money to me ♪
♪ I can't fall off ♪
♪ I got kids and a bitch
who like expensive shit ♪
♪ All I really trying to do is eat ♪
♪ I can't fall off ♪
♪ I'm a run it up ♪
♪ While I got the chance ♪
- What's up man, you good.
- What's up man.
- Good.
- Drop off the pick up.
We'll do it right here.
They'll be meeting with him.
Everybody getting money,
everybody go home happy.
You know how we do it, man.
I'll see y'all on the next drop off.
- All right.
Get your ass in the back man.
- Big Country, what's up baby?
- What's the deal my baby?
- What's going on with it?
- Chilling.
- These are my partners I
was telling you about man.
- What's up dog.
- What's up man.
- That's my man.
- That's my cousin Cliff.
- What's up big dog.
- Hello bro.
- I got the big bag here, right.
Big bag here.
Man, dog, what we're gonna do.
- We gonna be doing a
drop off and take down.
You know, we're all getting money.
Everybody go home happy.
- You feel me?
So that's all we on.
- That's what we on.
This my cousin, nigga.
- What's up nigga?
- Country smoking big blunts,
shit let me hit that motherfucker.
- Just meeting this nigga,
and asking him to hit his
motherfucking blunt and shit.
- Motherfucking Cuban cigar.
- Just met this nigga.
Come on man, man we come
over here for business man.
- Country got that shit,
I just wanted to see
what that motherfucker was hitting on.
- Help yourself man.
- Appreciate you man.
This the nigga I should've
met first right here, nigga.
Damn man!
- You see we here on business,
you always playing around.
Nigga, I'm a show you how to do
this shit over night, nigga.
I'm telling you bro, telling you.
- With your overnight dream,
you must plan on hitting
the power ball or something.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, do you feel me?
Presentation is everything man.
- Country I'm good on this?
- Hey man, come on man give me my weed.
- Damn dog!
Hey bro, get your cousin bro.
That nigga can't be getting no money
doing all that man.
I'm a get with you nigga.
- All right.
Now you know every nigga got
that one female they used
to rock with real heavy,
and mines was Keisha, soft on the lips.
Somehow I got her to think
that all of this was mine.
All I can do is go with the flow.
Welcome to my mansion.
- What happened to your hair?
- Shit, I got one gray hair
for everyday I did in that bitch.
You ain't write me either.
We'll get to that later.
We'll get to that later, Keisha.
- Oh my goodness, just come on.
- Stop, you all right?
- This is amazing.
- You've been drinking?
- What?
- I'm just saying.
I got something to drink.
- But I could have, use a drink like-
- I got some shit over
here for us, come on.
This my custom-made couch
the shit just got shipped.
So just be careful.
You can you sit right here.
- Why do we have plastic
cups in this big old mansion?
- The dishwasher broke,
don't even worry about that.
We'll be all right.
- Oh, okay.
- You ain't too good for plastic.
You all right baby.
- Anyway, it is so good to see you.
- You too.
You're so damn fine.
- Thank you.
- What you've been up to?
- I'm just getting my business together,
you know, catering Kia's Kitchen.
- Okay, so you cooking, you hot.
- You hot too.
- Is that so?
- Mm hmm, you're hot too baby.
- You know, I got the artwork.
I just got that from Zimbabwe.
I killed like three lions.
They gave me that she as a trophy.
When did you go to Africa
if you just got out of jail.
- Oh, no.
See, they did this prison project,
where they sent some of
the prisoners to Africa.
that's like some test dummies and shit.
So we had to like kill
them niggas in the wild.
- Oh my God.
- Don't worry about all that.
Yeah, that's from Zimbabwe.
- That is risky.
Like did you have to sign off for that?
- No, they didn't care if we died.
That's what I'm saying.
They just threw us out there.
We had to do what we had to do.
- I'm so happy that you are all right,
and you are doing your thing.
- I'm doing my thing, baby.
I'm doing my thing.
- Yes.
- But, let me pour us a drink real quick.
I'm sorry.
- Do you have any juice?
- No, we ain't have no juice in prison.
We gonna drink this straight.
Come on, Keisha don't do like that.
- You've ain't never been in Hollywood.
- Boy, now you know.
- You ain't never been in
Hollywood, come on girl.
You know, how we used to do this.
You know how we used to do this shit.
- Give me a break.
- We had Kool-Aid or something.
You better go get some red,
or some purple, some grape something.
- Kool Aid, you ain't
gonna toast, come on.
- I was just about to say that.
My bad.
I need to be all the woman you need.
I am so sorry.
Big mansion like this?
- Hell yeah.
I'll toast, put butter on
the bread, everything baby.
- So listen, this is to
this mansion and to tonight.
- Yes.
Anyways, show me around.
- Okay, you want to see some shit?
- Yes. I'd love to see where
I'm a possibly be living.
So, I don't wanna be there.
- Hold on, where we going?
- To my room.
- Cool.
Hold on, what we going to your room for?
You were supposed to
be showing me the pool.
- You wanna see the pool?
- And the top floor.
- I'm a show you that after that-
- I told you I like watching HDTV.
- I got all that in my room.
I got all that shit.
I got flat screens on all walls.
- Do not be on this bull crap.
- Well, come on, let's go to the room.
Come on girl, come on.
- I guess.
- Let's do it.
- You need to find some juice.
- I think I got some here in the room.
Don't touch that refrigerator
when we get in there.
That shit, that shit cost.
- Why would you refrigerator cost?
Don't worry about it.
Damn Keisha!
Did I give you my key?
- No, why did you have
your door locked anyway?
- People can't see that's confidential.
It's only for the best.
Damn I gotta go back to
the car and get my key.
You wanna walk back to the car room?
- Well, I guess so.
You know what-
- You wanna stay here.
- I'll stay here, go ahead.
- I'll be right back baby.
I wanted to look at you one more time.
Damn!
- Thanks so much.
- So how does this work?
- They will contact you...
They should contact you by tomorrow.
I'm putting it in today.
- Okay, all right.
- All right.
- Anyways, you seen Cliff?
- Could you hold one second for me?
- Hi.
- Hey, how are you?
- Fine, you Cliff cousin?
- Who?
- Cliff.
- Who's Cliff?
- The person who own this mansion.
- This hotel?
- I knew this.
That's why he got locked
up the first time.
That scamming ass nigga Cliff.
Did you see his old raggedy gray hair ass
walking around here?
He's gonna tell me going outside
to get a key to his room
and then gonna act like this a mansion?
Had me coming over here.
I paid for a Lyft.
I guess y'all supposed to
be Cliff's cousin's, huh?
- You sene Cliff?
- Yeah.
- I'm right here, what's going on?
What's up?
- Hey.
- What's up?
Where you going?
- Baby nothing, y'all can come back.
- What are you doing?
- They are white, these
are not your cousins.
- My mama was white.
- Where you been man?
- I had two mamas, I had two mamas.
Wait a minute, Keisha, Keisha.
Okay, listen.
You ever heard there's
white chocolate too, listen.
Keisha, Keisha, Keisha,
Keisha, Keisha, Keisha.
♪ Please don't go ♪
♪ Please ♪
Keisha, damn straight up?
- Don't be a black girl.
- All right, you're gonna be in Room 315.
You're gonna go take the elevator
right here to the third floor.
- Aha.
Okay, thank you.
- No problem.
- Yeah, to the third floor,
I can you to the third floor.
My name Cliff, how you
doing, this is my mansion?
- Oh it is?
- Mm hmm.
- Well, you can give me a room here.
- A room?
- A room.
- You got a phone you
better get on Expedia.
You got the app?
Where you going, that's what I'm saying!
Oh my God!
- Where is my Lyft?
Damn! I should have called Uber.
Got me at this week ass hotel
with this nigga with
this old bird flu ass-
- Now the date
night was fucking horrible.
Got caught in a big ass
lie, dirty ass shirt.
Keisha left me, back to square one.
We got to drop it in the pot like.
Ramen noodles it is.
Yeah.
Oh, I gotta add some
seasoning in this bitch.
♪ You've been hit by ♪
♪ You've been struck
by a smooth criminal ♪
Oh shit, we gotta have something
to drink in this bitch, man.
Nobody want that nasty ass shit.
I knew he was a real nigga man.
Hell yeah cuz.
Henny the first day.
Patron the motherfucking second day?
Ain't shit change, steak and potatoes
We eat good out here.
Hell yeah, the fuck!
- Chris, at my house.
- Oh, shit, what are you doing?
- What are you doing?
You supposed to be in your hotel room,
and you aint got no clothes on?
- You don't got shit on either.
- Man go put some fuckin' clothes on.
You ain't gotta put shit on
if you don't want to though.
That nigga got a bad motherfucker.
Shit!
Mm mm mm.
Can I get you something?
- Let me get some chicken bites
and some Patron on the rocks.
Why are you looking like that?
What's the deal with you?
- Can you go Kansas?
Kansas be a good look.
We got all them other spots locked up.
You know what I'm saying?
Now all we gotta do is get
dog, and we'll be good.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm trying lay back.
Shit getting hot, all that.
You feel me?
I mean, I'm a think on it and
know we'll figure that out.
You know what I'm talking about?
That look like dog.
I've been trying to fuck with
this nigga for a minute, man.
Now, I told y'all
I don't know nothing move
in the hood, unless Cat say so.
So for Baby to go behind him
to recruit Web was some sneaky ass shit,
but you know how it go.
What's done in the
dark, stays in the dark,
until somebody cut them lights on.
- Got Baby in the back,
he wanna holler at you.
- You said what?
- What's up baby?
- What's going on man.
- Just chilling man.
- You already know what it is.
- The fuck you are doing here?
- You know, this is my place, man.
- I got all this shit over here on Warren.
You feel me?
This is my shit right here.
I got the barber shop across the street.
- I've come to pick up something to eat.
- Yeah man.
You know what I'm saying?
This could be you really?
You know what I mean?
I'm trying to get you
to fight with me, man.
But it's like you're making
this shit all hard for me, man.
Talk to me.
- I ain't doing shit for cap.
I got something going on all ready.
- I mean what's the problem
a couple of players meeting, man?
We do a little something here and there
that shit don't work for you.
You know what I'm saying?
- I mean, we put something together man.
Right now, I'm cool though, for real.
- I hear you talking,
man. I hear you talk.
All right, every time
I see, you know, hey,
I'm gonna shoot this word to you my dog.
- That's all good.
I fuck what you though.
- I don't give up.
I got my dog and Ken,
he running over there.
I've got dog, over here.
You know what I'm saying?
This shit fixing to be all me.
But I'm really trying to fall back.
I got my young dog fixing
to run my whole operation,
but shit you really can
run that shit with him
and you can take over.
You know what I mean?
- I told you I'm good right now.
- You funny man, you're funny nigga.
I love you though man,
'cause you're loyal.
I know you're gonna be fucking with Cat
and all that shit, man
and I'm ain't really trying
to bring dog name up man.
Matter a fact, I think I
seen that motherfucker man.
You know what I'm saying?
And dog-
- What the fuck do you run into him at?
- That don't even matter.
He just, it just didn't seem
like he was fucking with me,
you know what I'm saying?
What's up with him?
- He don't be out nowhere.
- Huh, no, I seen him.
But see, you know thing about me,
I see a lot of people,
and they don't see me.
You feel me?
- You know how it go man.
- All right, just get with me though, man.
You know, enjoy your meal.
Matter of fact, when you go up to the top,
tell them everything on me.
- Thanks man, you got
some good food too, man.
- Appreciate it, for sure, man.
Good looking.
Damn!
Get that motherfucker.
- What's up nephew?
Yeah, yeah, I'm ready, I'm ready.
- All right man.
Life's good how come he's
been going on your end, bro?
- Shit, we're good,
we're been eating good.
You know what I am saying,
taking care of business.
But you said you need to
holler at me about something.
What we got to do?
- I pretty much man,
I need you to give a couple of individuals
an early Christmas present, bro.
- Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah, that ain't shit man.
All you gotta do is
give me the info, baby.
I'll take care of that shit, man.
Drop down on them niggas.
Let you know when it's done my nigga.
- I mean dog, bless him for Christmas.
Leave it alone, I got you.
- We gonna cancel them
niggas Christmas, cuz.
You heard me?
Ain't gonna be no Christmas.
That's gonna be the early
Christmas party my baby.
Let's get it.
You know you got that paperwork?
We gonna get it in.
- No, paperwork gonna be official baby.
You know how I rock.
- All right, for sure.
- I got you.
- 100 baby.
Cuz said he was
gonna put me in position.
Now I'm here with the plugs.
We took a quick trip to the A
just to celebrate our progress.
Little do he know we gonna have to take
two steps backwards just to get ahead.
- I swear to God they
ain't fucking with us.
- These niggas right here, boy.
- My niggas.
- Oh, I knew I smelt your musty ass!
Why you ain't tell me
your cousin was here?
- Yeah, nigga, that fuckin'
money stink now nigga.
What's up, nigga?
- Oh! I see you've got them
old rusty ass sticks, man.
- Ah, you know what I'm saying nigga?
- I see you Cliff.
- That 40/40 vision, nigga.
Yeah.
- You got your first time
five thousand, I see.
Got the buffs on, it's all good.
- We're heavy, we're heavy.
- We're good, we can get back to the city
you already know what time it is time.
- You know, I told you. Let's get it.
- That's all baby.
- Hey, we on this shit.
- Hey man, you gotta quit
talking all that shit, man.
- Hey.
- Say no more.
- Get it.
- What's up big homie?
Yeah, yeah, we all set.
We already put the play down cuz.
Yeah, I've been seeing
the niggas in the front.
They 'bout to pull around to the back.
We 'bout to knock them niggas loose.
- Push one of these niggas shit in.
- About to get this bitch beamed up.
- Oh, no. hell yeah!
Now see, where I'm from,
when there's money on your head,
ain't no escaping that.
But see now look at karma,
the same niggas who shot at me,
got one less nigga now.
Take one of ours, we taking one of yours.
This chess, not checkers.
- Snap, what up though baby?
- Yeah, nigga.
I got that info you needed though bro.
I got the info you need.
Listen though, I need you
to meet me at the court-
- Now see
Keisha, Keisha was special.
I've known Keisha since
I was 14 years old,
and grandparents owned a laundromat
right by my mama crib.
- Hey, hey, hey Snap,
I'ma call you, all right.
It just seemed
like the weather was right,
but the season was wrong.
No matter what I couldn't
seem to do right in her eyes.
Or mine.
Get away from
me, get away from me.
- Damn.
- Yo cliff, get away from me.
- Damn! You look better
every time I see you.
What's this, what's this
like some distance shit.
I gotta stay back?
- Stay back, yeah.
You know how you played me.
- You know I can't stay away from that.
You all right?
How you been?
- Yeah, I'm all right.
How's your mansion?
- Don't start bringing up old shit.
- Um, that was two weeks ago.
- Listen, listen.
I had to go out of
town, get my mind right.
To get my bag right.
I just wanna take you out.
I just want a second chance.
You're acting like you don't
believe in second chances.
- You think you're finna play me again,
after I done got over you.
- You over me?
- You see me running
'cause I'm tryna run into
something right now, okay.
And it's not you.
- Well, you done ran into me.
So let's do something about it.
Can we go out?
- Why should I?
- I just think that you should
give me a second chance.
I can't stop thinking about you.
I was trying to call you.
You done blocked my shit.
You ain't texting back.
I'm on read receipts is on and shit.
So I know you're seeing the shit.
- Whatever.
- So can we go out?
You got a new nigga now?
What's up.
- Don't hit me with that,
'cause you was on some bull crap.
- I was, I was.
If I give you another chance,
oh, you better come correct.
I am not playing with you.
- I'm a come correct,
all the way correct.
Just how you look.
So where are we going?
Where you wanna go?
- Um, I don't know.
- You can just figure that shit out.
- Whatever you can afford.
- Unblock.
Don't worry about the
money, we got the money.
Unblock my number.
I'm gonna call you and we
can iron out the details.
We gonna have a nice night.
- All right.
- 'Cause you miss me.
- Look like you want a hug.
You want a hug?
- What!
Now you're pushing it, do not play.
Or there will not be a second time.
- Motherfucker is soft though, damn!
- Stupid!
- Bye baby.
- Guess who I just ran into
when I was jogging on the River walk?
Cliff, old, fake mansion having ass.
Yeah, nah, he gonna tell me he changed
and he trying to be right or whatever.
No, I told him I'll see,
but this is what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna call him and tell him
to get over my house in 20 minutes,
and if he don't make it,
that's going to be my excuse
to leave his ass alone again.
I wish he would have
try to get some, please.
Negative.
Girl, call me when you get on your break.
All right, I'm about to call him now.
- Hello?
Who is this, Keisha?
- Yeah.
Damn, what's up baby?
- What are you doing?
Shit at the liquor
store, playing my lottery.
'Bout to have a bottle with the homies.
- Well, I need you to grab
me a bottle of champagne
and leave them and come over right now.
- Oh, okay.
Hey, bro put that shit back,
and run them numbers back, bro.
I don't need them.
I don't need none of them.
Put that backwoods back, bro
Put them Uncle Ray's back.
I don't need none of that shit, bro.
All right, hey I'm on
Morris, send me your address.
- Ah, okay.
He really about to come?
Who the hell is this knocking on my door?
Who is this?
- Who is it?
- Cliff.
- Boy, how did you get
at my house so fast?
You stalking me?
I just called you, are you serious?
- I am, come on.
Big everything.
I got you the champagne
that you asked for.
- What in!
What in the world!
- We can work on that all night.
- Hold down.
- What's up?
- I like this now but you
gotta take them shoes off.
- Yes. ma'am
You came real quick.
And this bottle is so big.
Like my goodness, size of a a kid.
Like-
- Big everything.
Big bottle, big chain, big everything.
Oh, hold on.
- Big everything, don't put-
- You told me to buy the biggest iPhone
so here go the biggest iPhone for you
- Oh my!
- So you can keep my number
blocked on the other phone.
That's all, that's all I want.
- I would give you a hug but
you're playing too much but.
I guess I get rid of that droid.
- Yeah, get rid of that.
You can keep everybody
else on the other line.
That's just for me and you.
- I can't believe this.
Oh my!
Wait till I tell Val about this.
- You've been talking good about me?
- No, but-
- You right, I ain't
been doing no good shit.
- I mean, I can start
talking good about you.
- So what's been going on?
So how you been doing?
- Um, just working.
- Working, where at?
- I work at a titty bar.
- You a stripper?
- No, I bartend silly.
- Oh, God damn!
My bad, my bad.
- But I mean, it's cool
'cause it's all good money.
If I wanted to strip I can.
- I know you can.
I don't think you should.
When the next time you gotta go to work?
- Um, this weekend.
- Okay. I'm probably come
through with all my homies.
We gonna shut that bitch down.
That's cool?
- It will be lovely.
You know what, I'm a stop.
I'm a start believing in you.
I'ma start believing in you.
- That's all I want you
to do is believe in me.
- Come here, give me a hug.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
So soft, Keisha.
- You just can't get it right.
But anyway...
Yeah, anyway, what's this I hear
about you fuckin' Snap
while I was locked up?
- What?
Who told you that?
- Don't worry about who told me that.
- First of all, I've never been
in a room by myself with that man.
So you can go with that
bull crap and whoever else.
- I ain't trying to hit all that shit.
- You know how many times dudes say
they done messed with me
and I don't even know them?
Are you serious?
- Did you fuck Snap or not?
- Do you believe that?
Do you?
If you did you wouldn't have
bought me all of this stuff?
- No.
- Whatever.
- Let's go get something to eat.
Talk about this shit over some dinner.
Let's talk about some other shit.
- Where you wanna go?
- Wherever you wanna go.
It's on you.
- It's on me?
- It's on me.
It's on me.
Keisha damn, you know it's on me.
- Because you have to redeem yourself.
- Get your fine ass upstairs,
put something on so we can go.
- Whatever.
- Damn!
God, please let this go right.
Please, you know a nigga need this.
It's been five years.
Amen.
Damn baby!
You're looking good.
- Why, thank you.
- What's up, you're ready to go?
- Yeah, but first I need
to go find me some shoes,
grab me a bag and I'm gonna need
my nails done while we're out, okay?
- I'm paying for that too.
- Um, yeah.
- I'm a help you find some shoes then.
Whatever.
Hold on, I know you is not
walking through my house.
What, I took my shoes off.
I don't care, just go
over there and sit down.
Phone ringing anyway.
What's up lying ass nigga?
Nah, you know what you lied about?
What's the word?
Right now?
All right.
All right, bro.
I'll be there in about 15 minutes.
All right, yeah.
- Cliff.
- What's up babe?
Guess what, I forgot.
My girl Savey was telling me
about this upscale restaurant.
So, I might need to change,
'cause I'm not giving
them all this pa pow.
All these Caucasians, can't do it.
- About the restaurant,
we're gonna have to reschedule babe.
- Hmm, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Rescheduled what?
- The dinner date.
- Didn't you just ask me to go out to eat?
- I did.
- So you knew what you had to do
and when you have to do it right?
- Money calling.
- I don't give a hell.
Don't you got money already?
You bought this big ass, little kid
of champagne up in here.
- So, it's gonna stop right here
or I'm gonna have to keep getting money?
Let me ask you something.
You want a nigga with a
lot of time and no money,
or a nigga with a lot
of money and no time?
And the little bit of time
I have I'ma give it to you.
- I need a man that's gonna support
and be there, and have his stuff together.
I'm getting my stuff together.
- Schedule.
- I'm just trying to
keep you in the picture.
- So sick of this.
- We gonna reschedule it or not?
- Whatever.
- You got the new iPhone,
go take some selfies.
I'm gonna call you and
we gonna reschedule.
- You really pushing
it, trying to be funny.
- I ain't tryna be funny baby.
- You just can't get it right.
- I'ma see you later.
- But anyway, whatever, bro.
- Hey, don't walk away from me like that.
- I shouldn't have never called you.
That's my bad.
I wouldn't be going through this and that.
- So we gonna reschedule or what?
- Come on, come on, so you can leave.
- You kicking me out?
All right, I'll see you later.
- Hurry up.
- Keep your hands and
you're feet to yourself.
- Hurry up.
- Call me tonight.
- Whatever.
Are you still coming up to the bar?
- Yeah, I'll be there.
- Y'all gonna show up?
- We're gonna shut that place down.
- Yeah, okay.
Make sure I get tipped well.
Yeah.
I got you babe.
So, you know, we had to pull
up to shut that bitch down.
And when I say everybody was there,
nigga, everybody was there.
All the dope boys, all the dope girls.
I ain't know she was
pulling up on me though.
Fuck it.
I guess I might have to
get my bill Bellamy on.
Who's that?
Who's your friend?
- This is my girl.
Don't worry about her name.
- Fine, too.
- Yeah. I'm with my girl, right.
Cliff, you're not my man.
I don't drink Patron.
- I'ma gonna get some other
shit, but we don't go up there.
Just meet me up there. I'll be right back.
All right. I'll be right back.
Keisha, what's up, girl?
- Oh, hey.
Three bottles of Patron, and some water.
Fuck them niggas, just say five.
- Hey, look, I bought
everybody out tonight.
You know we're gonna lock this shit up.
Listen, we are gonna toast to
her, drink up these drinks,
and y'all know what it is, man, real talk.
Now all get your glasses
and toast up, man.
- We're drinking that shit man.
You know how we play it, my nigga.
- Come on man.
- Y'all gonna have this
bullshit right here, man
I don't want none of that.
Somebody save some money in here tonight.
What the fuck
is going on over here?
I thought you said you don't
drink Patron lying ass.
What the fuck is y'all off of?
What is your problem, what?
- I don't drink Patron,
I don't drink Patron.
- Worry about your girl,
don't worry about me.
- What girl is you talking about?
What is all you niggas-
I thought y'all was my niggas, damn!
I thought we was a team.
We not no team no more.
I'ma go and get a Long Island,
fuck y'all niggas bruh, real talk.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Hey, hey, what the
fuck wrong with y'all!
Chill out, they got this shit all om me!
- Hold on, hold on, hold
on, chill out, chill out.
- Go get the strap.
Go get the straps and the burner now.
- Come here, come here, come here.
Look, look, look, one second, one second.
You know Cliff be on some bullshit.
- Epic bullshit.
- But listen, listen.
- You can come with us if
you want to, but we gotta,
we gotta go now.
- Okay.
- Come on, come here, come
here, come here, Keisha.
- No, look, you're coming to
my job with this bull crap.
I can get fired.
You know what I mean?
- I'm not trying to fuck up your money.
Listen, I keep fucking up.
I'm trying to get it right though.
That's what I'm tryna do.
- You do too much.
I'm trying to believe in you.
- You don't believe in me?
I'm not worried about
what's going on in there,
I'm worried about you.
I fucked up and now I'm
just trying to get back.
- When are you gonna get right?
- I'm trying to get right.
- All the way.
- You gotta be patient.
- No more run ins, no more issues,
no more lies, no more girls.
- Come here.
We gotta start focusing on us.
Just me and you.
That's it.
Are you down?
Come on, I'm fucking up your money.
We gotta get back to your money.
- Buy me another bottle.
- We can get whatever you want.
Shauna, Shauna.
How you gonna tell me five
years ain't a long time?
Hold on, hold on babe.
Hold on, hold on.
Man, what the fuck!
Man y'all niggas better announce yourself
before y'all walk in this bitch.
- What's up, nigga, I
bought you some shoes boy.
- Some shoes?
- Yeah, some shoes, nigga.
All this nigga just left Jimmy Jazz
with these fake ass 11's.
Count that shit out, nigga?
- You said what?
- Count that shit out, nigga?
- I ain't counting shit, nigga.
I ain't your fuckin' worker, nigga.
I got my own bag, I ain't countin' shit.
- Fuck wrong with you.
You can have this shit.
This light ass shoe box.
What's in here, the baby shoes, nigga.
- Fuck you motherfucker.
- Shut the fuck up.
- Who the fuck is this?
- Y'all niggas went baby
shoe shopping and shit.
This light ass box, man.
- This is real money in here.
- I got real money, nigga.
What's up, nigga?
- What you got in there?
What you got in there?
- Try a cool 60 in a couple of hours.
- Oh, that's heavy.
- Cool 60, nigga.
- A couple of hours nigga.
- All right, all right.
- Cool 60 nigga.
- That looks good right there.
- Cool 60.
- Nigga, this my shit too.
What's up, we're a team ain't we.
- Now we a team, huh?
- Cuz...
- I don't need this shit.
I told y'all niggas I'd leave that shit.
What's this shit right here?
- What you working with?
What's this your shit, some separate shit?
I ain't never met this nigga before.
Who is this nigga?
Man, what you mean
walking up on you nigga?
Come on man,
chill out, chill out man.
- This nigga trying to
make today his last day?
Chill out man.
- And you cocking shit, nigga?
- Yeah, nigga.
- Yeah, goofy ass nigga.
- All right?
- Let's count this motherfuckin' money.
- Yeah, count it.
- Looking motherfuckin' good.
- Still talking shit.
- Man, shut the fuck up, man.
- What are you all doing?
- Snatching shit now, damn!
- This nigga got a little Rollie,
think he doing something now?
- Little Rollie, you see
my shit dancing nigga.
- Prezi, nigga!
- Ain't nothing wrong being a
vice president for a minute.
- Oh yeah, okay.
- I'ma out of here.
- Yeah, you know what
it's best y'all niggas
gone ahead and get the up
outta here then, nigga.
Nigga, fuck you.
- Yeah, fuck you nigga.
Hey you know what cuz, this shit ain't,
you know what I'm saying?
You've gotta stop
bringing them fake ass niggas around dog.
I ain't gonna lie.
- Hey, why are you controlling
my people, my nigga?
- Man, you keep bringing these
old ass niggas around man
and you're standing up for these niggas.
The shit look a mess my nigga.
- Nigga this is how you left it.
Bro, I'll be back in a minute,
clean this bitch up.
- Be back then, nigga.
Be back.
Don't come back too soon.
Shit.
Man,
I ain't had no pussy
since I've been home.
She don't know that though.
I gotta play it smooth.
Gotta play it smooth.
Play it smooth.
Finally, gonna get some pussy.
I know you heard me nigga.
Been trying to fuck for two weeks.
- Yo.
Shit, you 'bout to dip out?
Oh, shit nigga hell yeah nigga!
Send them motherfucking address nigga,
and I'm on my way.
Oh, that's a green light.
For sure, straight up.
Yeah, what's the deal nigga?
Hell yeah, man.
That shit done man.
Aye, and I found a
motherfucking extra piece
in that motherfucker too.
that's a reward to me.
You can't get that shit.
Yeah, yeah.
The whole 60 boy.
Yes, everything.
All right, bet.
Well shit nigga,
just meet up with me and get your cut,
and shit we go from there.
All right, bet.
- I'm a call you right back.
- Who the fuck in here?
Who the fuck in here dog?
Who fuck with this bitch, dog.
Fuck!
Oh my, fuck man!
- Fuck, where this nigga Cliff at?
- Hello.
What's up cozzo?
I'm at the liquor store.
I'm playing my numbers.
I'm playing my numbers
- Somebody just hit the stash house man!
- Say swear to God.
- Come on man, hurry up!
- All right, I'm on my way.
Nevermind dog.
Damn why the fuck the
door still open, cuz?
- That's how it was when I got here, dog?
- Damn man, they took everything?
- Stop playing.
- Ain't nobody playing cuz.
- Who the fuck you had over here man?
- Nigga you're the only one over here.
- Man, I'm talking about last night.
Not right now nigga!
- Oh shit. I mean, shit-
- When I came in
the fucking door was open!
- I don't fucking know.
I just got here, you called me.
- Who been over here though, man?
- Just me and the little bitch
you seen me with the other day.
- How the fuck you got a bitch here man?
- Where the fuck else I'm a take her?
I'ma fuck her in the car?
- It doesn't matter, how
you got a bitch here, dog.
You know we stash here, dog?
- Since I got out,
y'all niggas been blaming this shit on me.
- Listen, I got 60,000,
blowing down the
motherfucking drain, nigga!
- You're gonna blame that shit on me.
- Come on man.
God damn, dog!
- Blame that shit on me.
That's all you do nigga.
Blame that shit on me.
- Use your head!
The bitch probably sent
somebody over here!
- So, it's my fault?
- Man, I lost 60000.
Did you have part to that?
No.
You still got your money with you.
- I do got mine.
So what did you mean?
Gone the way you just came from.
- That's what the fuck I'm a do, dog.
'Cause you don't know how
to talk to motherfuckers.
- This nigga think he slick.
- Took all motherfucking day, man.
Shit, I got these mosquitoes
tearing me up, shit.
Fat boy where you at?
You told me a minute, a
minute ago, come on man.
Yeah, I'm out here.
All right, cuz.
Goddamn fat boy.
- Man, I've had a lot
of runs to make, boy.
- What's the word?
- What's up cuz, that's your man?
You good?
- Lay your bitch ass down,
lay your bitch ass down!
- Damn, it's like that cuz?
- You know what time it is nigga.
- You gonna do me like that cuz?
Yeah nigga!
- You, I needed that shit!
- Get the fuck out of here nigga
We hit that lic.
- No, I hit the lic.
- You didn't.
You couldn't do that
shit without me, nigga.
You been talking crazy,
cuz, I ain't gonna lie to you.
You've been talking real crazy.
- Just check it out, nigga.
- This ain't the time for pictures cuz,
you been talking real crazy lately.
- Just check it out my nigga.
Yeah.
- So what you trying to say?
Seem like you already got your cut.
- I aint got shit.
- I found that phone the
same time my door was open-
- 'Cuz to be honest with you,
cuz, to be honest with you.
I ain't ate since I got home my nigga.
I've been starving nigga,
I'm starving my nigga.
- You got a Rolie on your wrist, nigga.
- This aint shit nigga, this time.
- Talking 'bout hoes, you
been going out of town.
- Man, fuck them hoes,
and fuck this time nigga.
I don't got time for this shit cuz.
- I let a leech kill himself man.
You let a leech eat too much,
they gonna get they self that's greed.
- So I'ma leach, I'm greedy?
How the fuck are you gonna be greedy
when you not eating nigga?
So what I'm greedy off of?
- I'm always gonna love you, man,
I just can't fuck with you no more man.
- So what you tryna say?
- I could have killed you right now.
- So, I can't make this shit right?
- I could kill you, right
now for this shit, man.
- So you open burner on me too?
- All right, you might need that man.
Aint no love lost, man.
- Man, cuz.
Cuz, cuz.
- Hoe ass nigga.
I told you I was gonna
get your hoe ass boy.
♪ These streets don't love nobody ♪
♪ I can't trust nobody ♪
♪ Pray I don't catch nobody ♪
♪ Growing up in the ghetto ♪
♪ They took my dog ♪
♪ All we wanted to do is ball ♪
♪ So we gonna ball to we fall ♪
♪ I'm here to motivate the ghetto ♪