You're fast.
I could make lots of money off of you.
Where’s your friends ?
Astafy, Betsy's Revenge.
$100 on Betsy's Revenge.
Ready ?
Go!
Come on!
Come on Betsy!
I lost again.
If Harry is still alive I am gonna kill him.
I'll tell you something, never ever trust a gambler.
Bet's a bet.
What was he thinking ?
Were they trying to shoot it or fuck it.
why you think he did it ?
16.
No he couldn't done it for less than 20.
18 the most.
Who the hell cares ?
Let's get out of here, it's gonna 120°.
Can I put that  one over for 10.
$20.
50$
Make it fall to the left.
$50 it is.
I want a piece of that.
This guy is gonna rot pretty quick you guys.
He doesn't mind.
I'll pay you on Friday.
Friday then, Mr. Henshaw.
Don't make me come get you.
And you sir ?
I put it on the one down there.
you cocksucker son of bitch, You almost electrocuted me.
Can't take anymore of your crap.
He put baby oil on a wet floor
and I hit it and my ass must have slipped for like 10 15 fucking feet.
Are you through in here?
Hey, lieutenant, how you doing?
Get back to work.
I am telling you Loony Tunes are not written for kids.
I learned a word like 'pole trune'.
- What?
- Pole trune, it means face coward.
'Craven', here's another one.
The fuck is a craven'?
'Craven' also means coward
You learn these words watching cartoons ?
I learned them from watching cartoons.
Porky Calls Sylvester the cat a shameless p..p...p pole trune.
It's good, You know any others ?
All right, here's another one: from little red riding hood,
The wolf shows up and tells granny to scram.
Granny puts her hands on her hips and says , "For lands sakes wolfie ain't you gonna eat me?"
No fucking way
In the cartoons.
I fucking love that!
What's in the bag ?
Nothing.
what do you mean nothing, what's in there ?
I got some pie for Katie.
St least I am getting some.
Not going to cuff my carrot and go to bed.
It makes a man go to sleep.
That's not funny.
I love six graders.
Hi, smiley.
Where's your tooth where did it go ?
I lost it.
An other one is coming in ?
It's gonna be big huh?
What's your name ?
Betsy.
Betsy, that's a pretty name.
- Come on sweety, let's go.
- take care.
Betsy's Revenge.
Come on, 8 to 1.
Fred, give me a quarter.
Finish the day without betting
-Give me the money.
-Give him the quarter for Christ sake man.
Do it do it!
Doesn’t matter, He can't bet on horses on this system.
No shit.
Yeah it's ridiculous, what is worse the salt of the half gallon of Tabasco they put in there ?
You're an amazing chef.
Seymore, hey it's Harry.
What do you mean fuck me?
Yes, I know how much I owe Chicago.
Yes, listen to me, I want Betsy's Revenge, in the 4th at La Forth Paradise, ok?
No, I can't.
No, no more  Harvey, every time I place a bet with those guys I lose.
I'm telling you, this is a sure thing
No, not you and  your scientific system.
I'm betting on a little girl smile, Seymore.
All right, beautiful. I'll see you later.
What's up?
We got a call.
-You got a call?
-Yeah, then we gotta go.
What's going on ?
There's a woman in there, threatened to kill her husband.
She's got a gun to his head.
I gave you the last quarter.
Give me a quarter.
All right let me have your gun.
What is her name?
A Maria something.
Maria ?
Someone covered the back exists ? - There is no back exists
Maria, I am a police officer
Get the fuck away!
Just relax ok, relax?
One more step and I’ll kill him.
I’m gonna put my arm down, all right.
My name is Harry,
I just wanna find out what's going on.
-He's a pig.
- We're all pigs, Maria.
Do you mind if I have a cigarette?
I mean it, I’m gonna kill this asshole.
Guys, please.
Why don't you tell me, what's going on with the gun?
What's with the gun?
I'll tell you what's with the gun.
I come home from work, and this bastard is in bed with my daughter.
Told you, she...
Shut the fuck up!
- She's 12 years old.
Some stepfather huh!
You know what Maria,
shoot him!
Hey, are you crazy !
Shut the fuck up!
Ok, good. Let's start with your options.
if you shoot him, right away you're gonna have sympathy on your side
Media is gonna be all over this, like horseshit on a race track
Probably gonna get off.
- Really ?
I should kill this asshole.
You're right Maria, you should.
No question about it.
What about your daughter?
It seems to me she needs you.
So why don't you just give me your gun?
Let go of me!
Are you all right?
Did you ever see King Kong?
I've seen it a hundred times at least.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I haven't seen it since I was a kid, it was on last night
Let me ask you a question
Natives on this island. They build this huge fucking wall, designed to keep out King Kong
Wouldn't you?
The scene where King Kong attacks the village to get that screaming woman.
He attacks the village and he forces his way through these 2 giant doors.
That's the scene they use for the poster
Kong breaking through the giant doors.
They built a wall, to keep out this giant gorilla .
Why the fuck did they put two giant doors in it big enough for Kong to fit through ?
what the fuck were they thinking about?
Plus, King Kong can climb the Empire State Building
but he can't climb this wall
Did they coat it with KY jelly or something, it doesn’t make sense.
Doesn't make sense
Take him downtown!
Are you all right?
Come here.
What's your name, I’m a cop it's okay?
What's your name?
Veronica.
For how long are you, veronica?
I just came here to get some penicillin.
Are you sure you're gonna be ok?
You know you're the first person that asked me this question today.
Hey, Sid!
What did you do to your hand?
It's okay really.
What did you do, what happened?
I am a diabetic Harry...
And Ester, she got blood pressure.
You got no idea what my medication can do.
Sid, get to the point!
I needed money, Harry.
Who did you borrow from?
Louie.
Louie ?
Next time you need money, you come to see me.
Come on Harry, you're my tenant, I can't borrow money from you.
Get him to see a doctor.
He owes almost $2,000,
What am I gonna do?
You're going in there ?
I'll be right back.
Harry, Harry, Harry,
Is it business or pleasure?
Sid canned his tab.
Ok? don't lend him money anymore.
Sure, it’s recalcitrant anyway.
Deal.
Who broke his hand?
Well suppose I tell you it's your buddy.
Mike Henshaw
What mike does on his off time, I don't care about.
I also know that mike would never hurt Sid.
Look I don't wanna start anything.
you pick a girl.
Any girl. it's on me.
Don't worry about it.
I'd hate you to run me in
And then I would have to elaborate with phoenix police about
my relationship with detective Henshaw.
Who broke my landlords hand?
Jesus Christ, this is what you're getting all wind up about?
Yes.
-Who the fuck cares ?
-I care, Mike!
I didn't go after Louie just because of you.
Tell me, who broke Sid’s hand?
Look I’ll talk to Louie.
Mike, I wanna know this guy's name.
Tell me!
Harry I make really good money working for Louie.
Do you know what position you're putting me in?
Mike, I’m not gonna discuss the fact that you're a fucking cop.
We've known each other since 16 years, I am your fucking friend.
Don't fuck a friend.
Don't fuck a friend...
Don't fuck a friend?
what are you a parrot?
Don't fuck a friend.
Come on. who was it?
Chubby.
Chubby?
Good. Chubby...
You know what, wait!
Well you don't wanna fuck a friend,
give me that $50.
-For what?
-For the cactus.
-I wipe $50 on my ass.
-Whatever?
Give me my $50.
Don't ever welch on a bet.
Don't welch on a bet.
Don't welch.
You happy?
I'll be right back.
Chubby!
What the hell you want?
Don't ever bother to see Sid again.
Don't ever touch him!
Fuck you. wait till you own some money and see what happens.
It's this simple.
Enough with the paper work. You touch him again, I'm gonna kill you!
And don't you fucking sass me ever!
You understand me?
You're fucking with the wrong guy, Chubby!
Eat your fucking hotdog!
Hello!
Hey, Seymour, what's up?!
Yeah, yeah.
What are the stakes?
What? $100,000?
Definitely, I'm gonna be there in 20 minutes.
20 minutes, yes.
Lock it up, lock it up.
I got to go!
You got to be kidding me?
No, I got to go.
I'll be back in a few hours.
Harry, don't tell me that there's something you'd rather do
than make love to me right now.
Actually yes.
Actually , what ?
Poker.
You're gonna go play poker right now?
Yes.
What?
I'll be back in a few hours,
I can drop you off wherever you want me to drop you off
Wait a minute, maybe I can come with you,
maybe somebody there wanna have sex with me.
Enough of this, No!
No, you can't come.
You'd be a major distraction, these guys are there to play poker, they're not there to stare at
Take off your bra.
I don't get it Harry, how could you have possibly lost all that money?
Not one of those horndogs had their eyes on one thing but my boobs the whole entire night .
You almost had $3,000 at one point Harry...
shuh... $3,000
I thought that Murray,?
Wasn't he the one with the cigar?
yeah, Murray.
I thought that Murray was gonna lose it all over the cards.
How could you lose Harry?
I don't know.
Poker is a funny game.
Funny.
How old are you Veronica?
21.
On my next birthday.
Let's bet.
I win, you have to do whatever I want
I figure it should be fun, Harry.
And if I win?
Gee, Harry, If you win
then I have to do whatever you want
-Fine.
there's a nine, an ace, a pair of nines,
Jack and ace, three nines,
Four nines.
Four of a kind.
Do you know the odds of getting 4 of a kind are ? five studs? five hands ?
One in 4,000.
Do you know what beats four nines?
Royal flush.
Do you know the what the odds of getting a royal flush are ?
One in 700,000.
And the odds in dealing both in 5 studs, is one in over 2 billion.
I obviously cheated.
I obviously don't mind.
My dad once dealt that hand
he wasn't cheating.
It was in Lubbock, Texas, a nickel and dime game.
They shot him nine times and killed him.
You're very cute, Veronica
but you're bad luck.
I'm gonna take you home.
Don't touch me.
Veronica!
Harry, stay the fuck away from me, all right?
Damn it!
Double or nothing.
That was double or nothing.
Pay up!
Harry!
Chicago is outside.
How you doing Chicago?
Betsy's Revenge.
I know.
Say again, that you dumped $3,000 on the wrong one.
You got a flaw about you Harry, you know that.
Chicago, the point was of me playing the sure thing.
You don't know how it's gonna turn out.
There's one kind of gamblers, losers.
You know sometimes I can't figure out,
If you sound more like Duffy Duck or Sylvester the cat
What do you owe me Harry?
You owe me $16,000,
you got one week to come with the money.
You're despicable.
Seven days, Harry.
Seymour, don't hang up,
Seymour, don't hang up!
Listen to me!
Why the fuck didn't you tell me the fix was in?
All right, all right, fine!
Listen to me, I want $16,000 down on Astafy, ok?
$16,000... yes!
Astafy, it's a fucking character.
I don't give a fuck if they're messing with the calendar,
Just put that fucking bet down, you hear me?
Good morning Katie !
Mike.
$6,000 for a new roof!
I'm sorry honey,
That's the way it is.
Mrs. Shuster!
Good morning lieutenant!
Solar panels for the pool.
Yeah honey, but we have a pool, and a roof.
I got to go.
The tile guy is coming over, he's gonna strip my...tiles.
Yeah, gotta leave.
Goodbye Nutter!
Bye Harry.
Speaking about our conversation before.
Let me bring that cocksucker Chicago in.
Won't you forget about it?
What do you mean forget about it?
He's a fucking bookie, let the cops bring him in .
This has nothing to do with me being a cop, I gambled, I lost, I owe him.
I'm not gonna welch.
I didn't say welch.
Just give me 5 fucking minutes with this guy
I swear to god I’m...
We got a corpse at Salt River, let's move.
Now would be good.
I don't understand, why the fuck you don't break Chicago's legs?
I'm not gonna welch
Well give me a break with this bullshit code.
Just put a bullet behind his ear.
No.
Officer.
Do you know this guy ?
Who gives a shit ?
Somebody whipped off a heroin dealer.
Listen, I got a bet down that's gonna cover everything, ok?
All you gamblers are the same, what's next
Louie?
I could be a bit of a loan shark in my life.
You could do what you do and you will.
Freddie, this turned me on.
what about you ?
Hey guys, a little respect for the dead,
it could be someone’s father.
I fucked her.
Bullshit.
I did, ask her.
Give me one.
Got a light?
What am I, a fucking corpse?
Bad luck.
What bad luck?
Three on a match is bad luck.
Give me the lighter!
Match, lighter, it's the rule of threes, bad luck.
You superstitious fuck.
Give me a lighter.
I'm telling you, it's a proven scientific fact.
They did a study about this.
I think it was over at Cornell.
Two guys, one lit two,
one lit threes.
The guy who lit two, was fine.
The guy who lit threes, died of cancer
Second hand smoking.
Great, fucking great!
Listen why don't we shake down a couple of whorehouses ?
I'm not a pimp.
Pimps make money from whores.
I'm not a pimp, I’m gonna be fine, just back off.
Listen to what I’m telling you.
I hear you.
Hi!
What do you want?
How is Veronica?
I like your name,
Leila is a very pretty name.
Don't check up on me.
I didn't sleep with your daughter.
So you thought she was bad luck.
What kind of bullshit excuse is that?
You think making love with my daughter is bad luck?
And aren't you sweet for not sleeping with her.
You are a pig, you know that?
Veronica has never had a man in her life, that didn't end up being an asshole.
And you had every chance to be better than that.
You are a cop, for Christ sake.
She wound up in a strip joint, poker game, what’s wrong with you?
Shit!
Are you all right?
Would you get out of here.
Ok.
Hi, Leila!
Could we talk?
Are you hitting on me?
What is this, a penthouse letter mother and daughter combination bullshit ?
No.
I just wanted to tell you you're right.
And I am sorry.
It's all, I am sorry.
Wait up, I'll be back in five minutes.
Carl!
Carl, wakie wakie!
What are you doing?
Wait here.
You got a gun?
Please not here.
You got a gun, what do you need a gun for?
You know why I am here.
Right.
you got the money?
No.
Give me three more days.
Three days.
Three fucking days.
Get on your knees.
I'm gonna give you three minutes.
Please don't.
You got the money?
No, please don't.
Hi.
Who is this?
Your girlfriend?
My wife.
It's your wife
Do you know that you're husband owns Louie $13,000 ?
Why don't you tell your wife what you spent the money on?
Tell her.
Horses.
Horses
Whores.
Hookers, right?
Who was that little goose you paid a little extra to call you
...Uncle Carl.
You fucking scumbag.
What?
I’ll tell you what,
Maybe your wife can help you out.
...No
Yeah, I think so.
What was the name of that little hooker ?
What was her name?
How old was she?
14, 15?
Cute.
Blonde...so what do you say ?
Wanna help your husband?
You don't want me to hurt him do you?
Do you?
You do something for me, I’ll do something for you.
Good girl.
Your wife just bought you three more days.
Three days.
Good morning Harry, let's go,
Chicago's finest breakfast.
Let's go!
Astafey.
Astafy.
Dostoyevsky.
"The honest thief".
I never met an honest thief.
But once I knew an honest man.
Who happened to be a thief.
Did you read the book?
No.
I had to look that up
Cause I couldn't believe how stupid of you to drop $16,000
on that fucking horse.
Harry,
You're down $32,000 now
What were you thinking? Only a stupid gambler would
double his bet to get back to even.
But look,
I'm in a position to help you.
There's this guy who is in the custody of your police department
And this guy likes to talk
So maybe you shut this guy up
And maybe I forget the $32,000.
Chicago,
You're gonna get your money.
How?
You're tapped all over town.
Geez, I am only asking you to pop off one lousy crook
for $32,000.
I am sorry about the other night ok.
Really I am, Harry.
I am under a lot of pressure, Harry.
You know what I mean?
You got 48 hours to come with the scratch
or kill that guy Joey Schneider.
The police will take care of everything.
and that's it?
That's all I got to do?
That's all you got to do.
And until then,
You are cut off.
Not bets, nada.
You're not even laying down a fucking lottery ticket.
Until you kill this kid Harry, I own you.
Seymour, it's Harry,
Seymour, Seymour...
Don't hang up.
Harvey, Harvey, ...
Please wait ...
Marvin, it's Harry, Marvin
don't hang up...
Wait, they believe in some voodoo ritual.
Fuck.
You got a minute Joey?
Don't you see I am fucking busy here?
Who the fuck are you?
Just a cop.
Want a cigarette?
Yeah.
I heard you were caught running pickups for Chicago.
What, me?
Also heard you like to gamble.
No, you got it wrong pal.
You ever read Dostoyevsky?
No.
You should.
"Crime and Punishment", "Dream of Ridiculous Men", it's killer stuff.
Dostoyevsky was a degenerate gambler.
Look I don't know anything about anybody named Chicago, all right?
Chicago?
Forget that.
I just wanna play some cards.
Dostoyevsky once wrote a letter to his wife
In which he described his sensation of having an orgasm.
After he lost a considerable amount of money at the roulette table.
Wait, wait, this fucking Dostoi...
Dostiev...
Dostoyevsky.
He laid down a bet, he loses and he splat .
Yeah, he splooched right there at the roulette table.
Are you a good writer?
The fuck is that school system you grew up in?
I don't read too good.
You bet on anything, anywhere, anytime.
Let's play high card.
What do you got?
Got a king.
Don't even know what the bet was.
The bet was, I win I kill you
You win, I let you live.
Chicago likes you dead. I owe him 32 thousand dollars, what would you do in my place?
what would you do?
Please.
You're lucky I played aces low.
You keep your mouth shut.
You serve me every time you got to serve, you understand me ?
If I find out you kept your mouth shut,
you get along just fine
You rat out Chicago,
You know what do they do to rats in prison, Joey?
How old are you?
20.
Never rat out anyone.
You understand me, never,
It doesn’t pay in the long run.
And while you're in prison, Try to read a little,
not Dostoyevsky but some Mark Twain.
Thank you for coming forward.
It's very brave of you.
I'll have to set a meeting with your attorney's office.
Now you do realize it's gonna be difficult for you to testify.
You are aware of that.
I did what I did for my husband, lieutenant.
It won't be difficult to testify against that pig Henshaw.
Yeah.
-Louie.
-Mike.
Let them in, Norm.
Nice job!
Collecting that $13,000 from Carl.
yeah, well I’m very fucking sorry.
Here's your money.
Sit down.
You ever watch National Geographic
or any similar shit?
Do I look like the kind of guy who watches National Geographic or similar shit ?
Fascinating stuff.
I watched a story the other day about relationships.
About fish, Sharks, barnacles, crabs.
They achieve something.
Which I strive for.
It's called parasitic castration.
The barnacle lives and grows inside certain crabs.
A mass of fiber, extends through the crab and actually alters
the body of the crab, into a female,
regardless of what sex it was.
The barnacles reproduce.
But not the crab.
Fascinating shit!
Yeah!
Louie, check it out!
Thank you, Norm.
Want me to stick around?
I am good, Norm.
You sure?
Positive.
My basic intuition tells me you're the new girl
That's right.
Let's see what you got.
Mama mia!
Come over here.
Let's see what you got.
Nature is full of relationships, Mike.
Full of them.
Like leeches.
They crawl into the bluefish , for example
and suck the blood out of them.
The leeches have to keep the bluefish alive,
otherwise, the leech dies.
The barnacles have to keep the crabs alive,
otherwise the barnacles die.
Am I getting through to you?
Abso-fucking-lutely
You want to make an example
out of somebody who owes me money,
Make it someone who doesn't owe me a lot of money.
I need to keep my little bluefish and crabs alive.
Mike!
I got something for you.
Fucking come back later, I’m kinda busy right now.
I must...
I'm a little busy right now, come back.
You're not paying Dominic, are you!
Please, this is really important.
Just get in here.
Hi?
Harry... look, please don't tell Fred,
it would kill him.
Get the fuck out of here!
Please, Harry, I love  Fred.
Get the fuck out, Katie!
Turn around and leave!
The fuck is the matter with you?
How the fuck could you do that to Fred?
What do you want Harry?
what do you want?
You said you had something figured out.
What is it, what do you want?
I want Louie.
You heard me.
Listen, you know his setup, you know his timetable
How much money he's got and where he keeps it
Harry, why would I fucking heist Louie.
Jesus, you fuck your friend's wife, you make collections for this scumbag
but a heist for me is out of the question?
- This isn't easy for me, Harry.
- Fine. whatever.
You know Harry, you got to be an honest man to work for Louie.
I'll go hang myself .
You're gonna hang yourself !?
What about me?
You don't want me to wack Chicago because there's a bullshit code that
don't let you welch on a bet but you're gonna rob a loan shark to pay it off.
If I don't pay back Chicago,
he's gonna fucking own me.
I'm fucked.
It's a perfect crime, Mike.
We get masks, we're in, we're out, it's clean.
He can't call the fucking cops.
Right, and he's not gonna know what hit him.
Yeah, it's perfect.
You want a beer?
No.
Mike, what's this shit with Katie,
What the fuck are you doing?
What do you want me to say?
I want you to tell me you're not gonna pop her anymore that's for one.
she's nuts.
She doesn't cum unless I smack her,
Whip her, call her a whore.
You think Fred likes it?
Whips her, calls her a whore ?
I don't think so.
Are you gonna help me or what?
Sorry I had to be the one to show you these.
In case you want to hear the audio.
No.
Pretty nasty stuff.
Henshaw is in all kinds of shit,
we all know that.
I got to have something solid.
Just give me something to put him away.
Like clockwork at 2:30 every morning they open up the safe and count the receipts.
They keep the money in there from loan sharking operations and strip clubs.
I've seen it open with half a mill.
How many guys is gonna be around?
4, 5, 6 it doesn't matter,
They are not expecting us.
Who the fuck is that?
Calm down, it's all right.
What are you doing here?
What's up ?
Nothing.
What's he doing here ?
- I invited him.
- You invited him...
- You invited him !?
You wanna do it one more time, yes I invited him.
A, we are a team the four of us
B, we need someone to drive the car.
I can drive the car.
You're pissing your pants.
I don't have to take that shit from you, all right?
I need the money just like you do.
You're not cut out for this.
Guys...
Harry, I am not gonna trust this dildo to drive us around.
What are you saying, Mike ?
I am saying that you don't have the stomach for this.
Take it easy.
What the fuck you're getting so excited about, Freddie ?
I can drive a lousy car, James.
No one said you couldn't but it's not that simple.
For Christ sake,
You're giving me shit about it.
Guys, we don't need this,
Come on.
At least I can be trusted.
What the hell does that mean?
What the fuck does that mean?
What the fuck does that mean ?
Stop, stop, stop.
We don't need this.
Harry, talk to this prick, will you.
Prick ?
you're calling me a prick ?
You fucking freak!
Fuck you!
Stop!
Jesus!
Slow down, relax.
Listen to me Mike,
it's gonna take three of us to knock over Louie, right?
- Right.
- Ok!
We need someone to drive the car.
I would have felt more comfortable if Fred is driving the fucking car.
What's the big fucking deal?
- Will you pay him out of your money.
- Fine! whatever. Come on!
Fred, you're driving the car.
Sit down.
Robert Johnson, huh?
It's a very antique jukebox !?
How are you ?
What's the name of this song ?
Terraplane Blues.
My grandpa used to have this car.
Said he got it to 88 miles/h and that was in 1938.
The song isn't about a car.
Really?
You think there's a hidden meaning to the line: who's been
Driving my Terraplane Blues since I’ve been gone?
Maybe I’m wrong, but the line :
I’m gonna get down deep in this connection
Keep on tanglin' with your wires
Seems to me it's about a guy singing about a shortage in his wiring system.
I flash my lights, mama,
but this horn won't even blow.
Aha, little generator won't get the spark.
Am I getting through to you ?
No.
You're still a pig.
I know.
I bought you a present.
I don't want it.
Something to remember me by.
It's a little pink pig watch.
If you press this button right here
Go on.
See, so you're all right.
I am a pig.
Here you go.
you get your own pig watch.
Thanks a whole lot.
You're welcome.
Don't you want a drink or something.
No.
You know a place where we could get a good pie ?
Apple, it's really good.
I don't wanna get a pie with you.
I don't like it.
You like the watch don't you.
Oh I love it.
You sure you don't wanna get something to eat?
No, I ate, I have to get home.
Early. it's only...see
Here you go.
Fine.
Oh, man.
Wanna go to the movies or something?
I can't.
Why ?
Why you busy ?
I just can't.
If the drop on the left here,
beats the drop on the right,
you have to go to the movies with me.
They are off!
- Come on, come on, left, left...
- Oh...
I won.
We bet.
Can't welch.
- I told you, it's perfect.
- Let's hope they can find this shithole in the dark.
Maybe they're lost.
What's up with Fred ?
He's like a little edgy lately.
Then stop fucking his wife.
Maybe that will help.
It's a good point.
Here !
I got you a taco.
Where did you get that shit.
The only place that was open,
do you want it ?
The fuck did I just say, no.
- Fine.
- My ass will burn if I ate that.
Fine.
What time does the bartender leave ?
2:30, I don't know,
2:30, approximately more or less.
What kind of guns do Louie's guys carry ?
9mm, 12 gauge bore diameter.
There he is.
- I don't know
- Mike...
Are you sure about the money being there?
What the fuck is wrong with you tonight ?
Nothing, nothing.
I know a man that used to work for a loan shark.
So ?
He used to tell me the worst thing a gambler can do
Is borrow money from the loan shark.
Loan shops are okay, but not loan sharks.
Harry, borrowing money from a loan shark
and stealing money from a loan shark
are two different things.
It's still coming from a loan shark though, Mike.
It's better than cheating.
I'd never cheat, never.
Gamblers who cheat are more interested in money than gambling.
What's money ?
I don't gamble to make money.
No shit.
You think that's fucking funny ?
Hell yes, I think that's funny.
That's damn funny.
What's wrong with you anyway ?
Somebody a little testy today ?
Not in the mood for you funny shit that's all.
Oh, I see what it actually is.
It's a case of a little testy.
You want a fucking piece, motherfucker ?
- You can't take a hit ?
- Knock it off!
What the hell is going on right here, guys ?
Is the heat getting to you ?
I am talking on the goddamn phone.
Keep this shit out.
Detective Shuster.
Katie, no, we already told them once.
Listen to me, do what I say, just take care of it!
What are you looking at ?
Take it easy, Fred.
Has anybody seen my lighter ?
No.
God damn it!
Tell me about taking it easy.
Did you steal it ?
- Did you take it ?
- No, I didn't steal your fucking lighter.
Son of a bitch.
It's the only thing my dad gave me.
It's my lucky piece.
Why would I steal your father's lighter.
Because you are a sadistic fuck, that's why!
Fine.
This is not good.
Not good.
I need some air.
Where ?
it's fucking Phoenix, there is no air.
John, you got some matches ?
Here you go.
Thanks.
Hi.
So you came to collect on the rain drop ?
That's the first bet I have won in a long time.
Wanna take me to the movies ?
Yes.
Tonight is not a good night but...
So why did you come to see me ?
I've lost something of mine, that brought me
a lot of good luck in the past.
And I just wanted to have something of yours for luck.
I wouldn't know what good luck looks like.
It's really important to me.
what do you want it for, Harry ?
It doesn't matter.
why ask me, why not somebody else ?
Because I like you.
And I just wanted to come from you.
You're a gambler.
You wanna change your luck.
Get yourself sucked out of whatever this shit you got yourself into.
Just don't gamble with me.
I won't.
can I have those matches ?
I'll come by tomorrow for breakfast.
I'd like that
Harry!
Thanks.
Give me one will you.
Get over your scientific facts.
I believe it was Cornell University?
- Hey, Mr. Slik, how is it going ?
- Great.
- Listen.
- Hmm, it's all right.
No, no, it's all there.
Hi, baby!
Come over here
Let's go.
What's that ?
Lubricant.
You think you're Frank Sinatra or something?
Women just look at you and zang...
Instant wet.
It's all right boys?
Hey Norm, I'm next.
Knock yourself out dog.
What the fuck am I doing here ?
Oh yeah, oh god...
Oh god !
Get the fuck out!
Listen to me, I want you to get up, open the safe
and put the money in the bag.
Now!
Can we talk about it.
Shut up!
Open the motherfucking safe!
We can make a deal here.
Get up, open the safe, put the money in the bag.
Now!
Who the fuck do you think I am, a Swiss bank?
Fuck you!
God damn it,
What the fuck is the matter with you ?
Open the safe motherfucker.
Now.
Come on!
You guys are dead.
I hope you know that.
Just give us the fucking money, Louie.
Parasitic castration is gonna be a pic nic compared to what's gonna happen to you.
Fuck you and your barnacles.
No, Mike, no !!!
If only I had my dad's lucky lighter
What the fuck you doing bitch
It's a piece of gum, for Pete’s sake.
Don't do it, down !
Please don't kill me !
All right, all right.
Nobody is gonna shoot you.
Do you the combination to the safe ?
I don't know, only Louie does.
Only Louie.
Does anybody here knows how to crack a safe ?
Does anybody here have a borescope or a drill?
I left it by the motherfucking jacket.
Don't get testy, Mike.
You're the one who shot Louie, before he got to open the safe.
I had no choice.
Stop!
Can't you just take the whole safe ?
No, it's bolted down.
But I once knew a guy who opened a safe with an industrial vibrator.
What's your  name?
Bert.
Bert, shut the fuck up!
You can use a stethoscope.
You can listen for the tumbler.
Sh, sh.
Chew your gum, ok?
- You got the yellow pages?
- Yeah.
Where?
In the desk drawer.
What side ?
The right side.
The right from here or the right from there ?
This side over there.
Excuse me genius.
Don't trip on the body.
Monk locksmith, 24h dispatch, no lock we can't open
20% discount for first timers.
God damn it!
Get fucking moving,
don't turn around.
It's ok, we're first time customers,
if you do this in a hurry we'll forget about the 20%.
It's right over here.
I just had to drill to see where the tumbler fall.
See, I never met a safe I couldn't open.
Here you go, thanks a lot.
Here you go.
Hey let's not forget to keep our mouth shut.
Sup Fred!
Let's go Fred!
Fred!  Jesus Christ, come on
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Let's go.
I fucked up.
Don't worry about it.
You guys killed anybody up there ?
Yeah.
How much you think we got?
Minus $32,000 for Chicago, $40
for the masks, I say about $152,000.
How many did you guys kill ?
Fred, can we talk about something else ?
Step up, will you.
You don't think Harry will fuck us out of the money, will you ?
Harry, no, no way.
Drive a little faster, ok?
What the fuck is going on ?
Why you stopping?
- The fucking car is out of gas.
- We ran out of gas ?!
- You didn't put gas in the car ?
- I put the fucking gas in the car!
For fuck sake!
There it is.
We did it, Fred.
Harry, you didn't fuck Katie, did you ?
What ?
did you fuck Katie ?
No.
Did Mike fuck her ?
What are you talking about, Fred ?
He's talking about Henshaw fucking his wife.
You knew about it Harry, why didn't you tell him ?
Tell me you didn't do this, Fred.
It's over Harry, step away from the bag.
It' ok Fred, you did the right thing.
Good job.
Fred !
What the fuck you looking at ?
- Harry won't fuck us huh ?
- I told you he won't fuck us.
Shit.
Fuck !!!
I hate fucking gamblers.
So they were definitely three.
Yes, three, pig, monkey and bunny rabbit.
All right.
Put out an APB on Harry Collins.
and find Nutter and Henshaw,
and keep it off the radio.
Make them think we're just going after Harry.
Maybe they'll lead us to him.
All right, sir.
It's over Harry.
Us losers stick together.
Bet's a bet.
The police found out the plates.
Nutter is mine.
Mike, let's make this quick.
In and out.
He's been here.
Harry !
Come on you cocksucker !
Fuck this man.
Shit.
Harry !!!
Fuck!
James !
Mike !
Fuck him.
We're fucked, Mike?
Why ?
Coming out !
What the fuck are you doing ?
Coming out, don't shoot!
Put it down, James.
I'll do it, you know I’ll do it.
Cocksuckers !
Your name is Harry ?
No.
Mine's Dolores
Radio says you robbed and murdered a loan shark.
Does the radio also say I have a bullet hole?
You don't look like you're from Phoenix.
This city exists for god only knows why it exists.
Legend says that some guy sold his soul for exchange
of water supply.
It's not my soul I am worried about.
it's my luck, Dolores.
It's never too late to try to change it.
Can you turn this up, please ?
Robert Johnson.
Thanks.
Oh, daddy...
Katie, you're definitely a whore's whore.
How are you doing lieutenant?
Fuck you.
That cuff, Clyde, bet she made you do it.
Katie... you weren't gonna cuff him, were you ?
Is that what you're after, Harry. The money ?
Why don't you take it and get the hell out of here.
Are you crazy ?
Harry...
Did you ever see King Kong ?
What ?
Bunch of natives on this island.
They build this wall, to keep out this giant gorilla.
But they put two giant doors, big enough for the gorilla to fit through,
right in the walls.
Doesn't make sense
Please, stop burning the money.
Ok ?
I'll do anything.
No shit
Fred saw that movie a hundred times.
I bet you didn't know that, Katie.
What are you doing Harry ?
Harry, don't do it !
Don't fucking do it!!!
Gus, it's Harry...
I know Gus, I know
Just listen to me, okay ?
Send some guys over to Webber's house
I think you need to find the gun that killed  Fred.
And you'll find Fred's body in a shack 3 miles south of Providence.
It's on route 6.
I'm taking some envelopes and stamps.
- I'm borrowing your car.
- Just go, just get the fuck out of here!
Clyde.
Give me the fucking keys!
There you go buddy.
Jesus Christ, Harry!
You look like shit.
Never knew when the loan shark have left the building
and the cops came looking for you.
Excuse me, could I have a piece of apple pie ?
With some vanilla ice cream on top
It's OK Esmeralda, get him some pie.
$32,000.
Here you go.
Thank you Esmeralda.
That's the pie.
That kid Joey, I talked to him, and he's not gonna rat on you.
Do you know what he said ?
It's all there, Harry.
We're back in business.
No... I got myself a new hobby.
I am not gonna end up like my dad, Chicago.
Oh...
By the way Harry... that kid
Joey Schneider
He's dead anyway, ...
I slit his throat
Next time listen to me
It could have saved us whole lots of angst.
It's ok, I am a cop.
There you go, keep the change.