(WOMAN GROANS)
I can't...
Nanine!
Nanine,
get the doctor quickly!
(WEAKLY) Doctor?
If you can't make me live,
how can he?
No, no, don't say
such things, Marguerite.
You'll live.
You must live.
MARGUERITE:
Perhaps it's better
if I live in your heart...
(WOMAN SNIFFLING)
...where the world
can't see me.
(SOBS SOFTLY)
If I'm dead,
there'll be no stain
on our love.
Shh.
Don't think such things,
Marguerite.
Even if we've can't to go
to the country today,
think of how happy
we were once,
how happy
we shall be again.
Think of the day you found
the four-leaf clover,
of all the good luck
it's going to bring us.
Think of the vows we heard
Nisha and Gustav make,
and that we're going
to make to each other.
This is for life,
Marguerite.
Marguerite?
(WHIMPERING)
(SOBBING)
Marguerite.
Ah, don't leave me!
(CRYING)
Marguerite, come back!
Come back!
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(WOMAN SNIFFLING)
Jean?
JEAN: Wow!
SUSAN: It's just a movie.
JEAN: Don't say that!
When that last scene
was over,
Garbo got up,
marched off
and went out to eat.
JEAN: She died!
She died
a few years ago.
She died in
Robert Taylor's arms.
-Oh, dear!
-Oh!
If I'd known it was going
to affect you this way,
I would've signed up
for the series with Fred.
Of course,
he always falls asleep
before the end.
He's seen
Breakfast at Tiffany's
a dozen times,
he hasn't made it
to Moon River yet.
How are things
between you and Fred?
Wanna go for coffee?
If we make it fast.
I'm supposed
to be home by 11:00,
or Fred'll just have...
We'll make it fast.
-So tell me...
-Don't worry.
Fred has you
on a curfew?
He calls me at work
all hours of the day,
he checks
on everything I do.
(SOFTLY)
The affair was short,
the repercussions
seem to be lasting forever.
MAN: Can I get a latte?
Are you going
to a therapist?
SUSAN: When I tell Fred
where I've been
or what I've been doing,
he thinks I'm lying.
Now he's got this new thing,
when he gets home from work,
listen to this,
he hits the redial button
on the phone
to see who's the last person
I talked to.
-No.
-The affair was pure sex.
We didn't feel anything
for each other.
We were polite
to each other.
Well, I guess
sleeping with each other
is the highest form
of politeness.
(LAUGHS)
It's not as if Fred and I
are doing anything.
What are you staring at?
Uh, no...
Do you?
Do I what?
Do you and Roger
sleep together?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, I know you share
the same bed,
Fred and I share
the same bed.
I mean, do you and Roger
do anything in bed?
Mmm-hmm.
-After how many years?
-Fourteen.
Guinness Book of Records
know about this?
Not often, right?
Fairly often.
SUSAN: Well, often means
different things
to different people.
-You know that man?
-JEAN: No.
SUSAN: Youch!
Wasn't he
at the movies?
-(CUP CLATTERS)
-Uh-huh.
Did you see
how he looked at you?
Oh, stop it!
-We got to get you home.
-(GASPS) Fred.
(GIGGLING)
It'd be so much more fun
if we drove home together.
I wish,
but you know my hours,
the only way I can get
anywhere near on time
is if I leave
right from work.
Oh, well,
whoever said that
office management was easy
or highly paid...
Well, I'll talk
to you tomorrow
and I'll see you
next Monday.
Oh, that's just
what I need.
Vivien Leigh
in Anna Karenina,
something to remind me
what happens to married women
who have affairs.
Oh, no!
Thank God
there are no trains
out where I live.
(SUSAN LAUGHING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
JEAN: (SINGSONG) Morning!
ROGER: Hey!
-I cooked.
-Thank you.
Can I get you to do it
for me every day?
Yeah, if you play
your cards right.
Bess, could you please
turn off the sprinklers?
Why don't you
put them on a timer?
Well, I like to do it myself.
I feel like I'm part
of the earth.
Well, I don't care to be
part of the earth.
Just finish your breakfast,
please.
I'm finished.
Bess?
I'll untie it
when I get to school.
I think you should
untie it now.
Mom!
(MIMIC BESS) Mom!
Hey, who wants more, huh?
-No, thanks.
-What...
No compliments
for the chef?
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
(SHOUTS) Hey!
I've got two stops to make
so I'll see you
in a half hour.
I turn away for one minute.
BOTH: Mom!
JEAN: Bye!
(SIGHS CONTENTLY)
Ooh!
Hips.
(SOFTLY) Yeah.
Hips, hips, hips.
Excuse me?
Could you have
a look at this, please?
Ah, you need to see
my wife for this.
-Jean?
-JEAN: Yeah?
Have a problem.
Well, let's take a look at it.
My roses, they get
all set to open up,
then they collapse
and go brown.
Hmm. Thrips.
You need to use a systemic.
White lightning.
I never understood
why it didn't get the rating
it deserved.
Well, I'll just buy
a new one.
Oh, no, it's really easy
to get rid of this.
If you can save a child,
you should.
It's a rose.
To me, they're like children.
In some ways they are.
(PHONE RINGING)
ROGER: Hello?
Well, yeah. Just a second.
Jean, it's for you.
Susan!
Got it!
Hello.
(JEAN HUMMING SOFTLY)
You want to go
to the movies?
Oh, I got to do this.
Fred and Susan have
another emergency session
with their shrink.
They're still going
to that shrink?
Yeah, what does that mean?
What does it mean?
Well, neither Susan or Fred
ever saw a shrink
before they got married,
so what I think it means is
maybe Susan and Fred
don't bring out the best
in each other.
Hmm.
Ah, it happens.
-What's the movie?
-Anna Karenina.
Who?
Not for you.
Ask me again
when they're showing, uh...
BOTH: Clint Eastwood!
Okay. Bye-bye.
(BOTH LAUGH)
WOMAN: (ON SCREEN)
I was wondering
what he was doing...
This way.
-(WHISPERING) Right here.
-Thank you.
Mmm-hmm.
Excuse me.
(SOFTLY) Ah, sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Excuse me, excuse me.
WOMAN 2: Now, I never know
what my son may be doing.
(CHUCKLES)
Perhaps it's just as well.
WOMAN 1: Oh, why?
WOMAN 2: Have a look
at those eyes, my dear,
perhaps you'll understand
what I mean.
He's very handsome.
(CHUCKLES)
(TRAIN BELL TOLLS)
(TRAIN CHUGGING)
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
(STEAM HISSING)
(TRAIN CHUGGING)
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
(JEAN SNIFFLING)
It's wrinkled,
but it's clean.
Thank you.
Did you like Vivien Leigh
more than the Garbo version?
Oh, Garbo,
she had those eyes.
Yeah.
I liked this one better.
But you don't have to
ask me why.
ATTENDANT: Thank you, ma'am.
Good night.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Excuse me.
Uh, would you like
to have a cup of coffee?
I mean, it's early.
We can talk about the movie.
Thank you,
I don't think so.
Ah, look, um,
I'm sorry.
I'm not trying
to pick you up.
My name is Tom Doster,
I'm a 40-something,
I'm married, happily,
I might add and...
Well, I'm the father
of a terrific son.
I know all fathers say
that their sons are terrific,
but mine really is.
Well,
I'm a structural engineer.
I could go into great detail
about what that involves,
but to keep it simple,
I just tell people
I build things.
My wife was going to come
with me to this film series,
but Mondays aren't
a good night for her
because she volunteers
for project Helping Hand,
and they cook things
for people who can't
cook for themselves.
You sold me.
Good.
I'm sorry, I didn't even
tell you my name.
My name is Jean,
Jean Townsend.
-Jean.
-Hi.
Um, you were born here?
-Colorado.
-Ah, Colorado.
And you've lived here,
say, ten years.
See, I have these incredible
psychic powers.
Seven.
-Seven.
-Hmm.
Now, you're married
and no children?
Married and one daughter.
See, I used to be
a lot better at this.
(JEAN LAUGHS)
So, uh, you're a nurse?
Close.
I own a nursery.
Ah, lots of little
children running around?
No, it's not that kind
of a nursery.
Well, Climbing Rose nursery
in Topanga.
We got a lot of little
bushes running around.
-So, you own a nursery.
-Mmm-hmm.
My parents lent
Roger and I the money
and we wanted to
pay them back in five years,
we paid them back in three.
I'm very proud of that.
That's great!
So, um, why do you think
people go to see
these old movies?
Well, there's not much
romance and passion today.
I think people need it.
The old movies
are a way to get it.
Really?
Even the man of the '90s
needs romance?
Especially a man of the '90s.
Hmm.
Here I thought women
had the market cornered
on romance.
No way.
JEAN: Thank you.
I'm over there.
You don't have
to walk with me.
-See you next week.
-Yes.
My friend Susan
will be back by then.
Ah, what is the film
next week?
Betty Davis, Now Voyager.
Oh, my, double hanky.
Cloth hanky.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
-How was the movie?
-I cried my eyes out.
Hmm, must've been good.
Funniest thing
happened to me tonight.
Hmm.
Roger, are you awake?
The funniest thing happened
to you tonight.
Mmm-hmm.
This really nice man
that I was sitting next to
asked me out for coffee.
Roger?
Ah, this really nice man
asked you out for coffee.
I don't think that's unusual,
if I saw you alone,
I'd ask you for coffee, too.
Oh, I forgot to put
the coffee on for tomorrow.
I knew you'd be late.
I did it.
Ah, I'm so domestic
in my old age.
You're still looking
pretty good,
for an old man.
Hey, Dad!
(BARKS)
Hey! How was the water?
-It was great.
-Good!
And, I was
damn good today, too.
When did you start using
words like that?
Want to hear the words
I don't use around you?
No. Ask me again in ten years.
KEVIN: How come
you're turning here?
This isn't the right way home.
TOM: Well, I thought you might
enjoy the scenic route.
KEVIN: Come on, Dad,
I've got things to do.
TOM: This will be pretty,
trust me.
KEVIN: I'm twelve,
what choice do I have?
(INAUDIBLE)
(HONKS)
Dad?
Excuse me?
The Anniversary section.
-Oh, just around the corner.
-Thank you.
ATTENDANT: You want a basket
for all of that?
TOM: Well, I think I've got
everything I need.
Oh, I forgot candles,
that's the most
important thing, right?
ATTENDANT: Two aisles over.
TOM: Thank you.
Well, small world!
-What are you doing here?
-(CHUCKLES)
It's my parents'
50th wedding anniversary
this coming week,
and they're coming in
from Denver.
I thought I'd throw them
a little party at home.
I saw you the other day,
when you drove by?
Why didn't you come in?
Well, I didn't really
think about it.
I would have given you
the grand tour.
Oh, my son was with me.
Well! You could've
brought him in.
It's just a nursery.
Yeah.
My secretary's birthday,
surprising her.
Having lunch brought in,
you know.
Boss and his secretary.
Have you really
thought about that?
The boss and his secretary,
or you know,
boss and her secretary?
It's like they almost
have a marriage,
they spend the same
amount of time together
as a husband and wife.
Hmm, what color?
I don't know.
Margaret's a pink person.
How many of these in a box?
ATTENDANT: Uh, fifty.
Need another one,
Margaret's 63,
you know.
ATTENDANT:
So, is that everything? Good.
GIRL: Jennifer...
So?
Would you like
to get some lunch?
-Oh, well, I...
-I mean, what the hell!
Come on,
we both got to eat, right?
Yeah. Okay, all right.
And I wanted to give
my parents a big, fancy party
cause 50 years is 50 years.
My mother wouldn't have it.
Now, she said that
a golden wedding anniversary
only celebrates good luck,
luck that you didn't die
before you got there.
(LAUGHING)
My mom is very,
very practical.
Yeah.
How about a big,
gooey piece of cake?
-Oh, no way!
-Oh, come on, two forks?
No, no.
What are you working on?
What's the engineer
engineering?
Well, it's a new
bank building,
going to have it
framed soon.
You are accusing it
of something it didn't do?
Ah, no.
That's when you get the last
piece of steel set in place.
I know.
I know,
it was a terrible joke,
but I couldn't resist.
Still, it must be wonderful
when you look at a building
years from now
and you know you put it there.
Well, every engineer
would like to believe that.
-Yeah, I'll get this.
-Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, come on,
it's only 12 bucks.
No, please.
All right, you can get it.
I think we should split it.
I'm sorry,
it's the only way I'll do it.
It's very nice
to see you again.
Same here.
Will you be
at the movies tonight?
Sure as shootin'.
Haven't said that since
I was a little boy in Texas.
Maybe you're
still a little boy.
I meant that
in the very nicest way.
That's all right.
Well, uh, I guess I'll go,
I'm going to be late.
-See ya!
-Bye.
(PHONE RINGING)
I think maybe
the mashed potatoes
will be better.
Yeah.
-Oh, really?
-Think so.
-Depends on how they taste.
-Excuse me.
(BESS CHUCKLES)
(RINGING CONTINUES)
Yeah, just a second.
Hello?
SUSAN: Hello, honey.
Hi, what's up?
My fever, that's what.
I didn't even go in today.
I kept thinking this cold
would go away,
but it hasn't.
I'm not going out.
Sure, sure, don't worry.
Worry?
I've just got a cold.
Okay, all right, then.
Buh-bye.
(ROGER CHATTING WITH BESS)
ROGER: Who was that?
-Susan.
-Hmm.
Telling me not to be late.
(BESS SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
BESS: You can shop.
ROGER: Hmm, well, seems
like you've been doing
a lot of shopping lately.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Let me see.
Well, don't you look
like a million bucks!
Oh, stop. (LAUGHS)
Jerry, please help me.
Shall we just have
a cigarette on it?
Yes.
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
(WHISPERING) When I was young,
I didn't care to look
like Elizabeth Taylor,
or have Rita Hayworth's body,
or Marlene Dietrich's legs,
I wanted to smoke
like Betty Davis.
Yeah, but you don't.
No, it's bad for you.
We could talk
about your child.
Our child.
Thank you.
JERRY: And will you be happy,
Charlotte?
Oh, Jerry, don't let's ask
for the moment.
We have the stars.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(CAR HONKING)
You know, it's still early,
you sure you don't want
to change your mind
about having that
cup of coffee?
No, I have a busy day
tomorrow.
I really should go.
-All right.
-Okay.
So?
Anything I can do?
Yeah, you can take out
the potatoes and drain 'em
and mash 'em.
Oh, this looks heavy.
I'll do it.
Oh.
Uh, why don't I
set the table?
It's buffet.
I offered to split
half the cost,
I said, "Let's get a caterer,"
but you wouldn't.
I'm not good
at this sort of thing
and I don't pretend to be.
Why don't you
check on Dad's drink?
My rich sister,
my rich widowed sister.
It's hard to believe
you two are even related.
I do like the jewelry, though.
Mmm. It's all real, too,
of course.
Ugh, she must have
more money than God.
Some people have
all the luck.
Ah, I don't know.
Maybe Phillip had
all the luck, he died.
-(CHUCKLES)
-I heard that.
Daddy doesn't want
another drink,
he only wants a soda.
Coming right up!
You got the ones
in the cans?
Uh-huh.
With the lift-up tabs?
Yeah.
Susan?
Oh.
(LAUGHS)
Did Roger say anything
about last Monday night?
Huh?
Last Monday night,
did he ask you anything
about it?
What was Monday night?
Film series.
I had a cold.
I know you had a cold.
Did he ask you
anything about it?
What?
WOMAN: That's butter...
You can't eat that,
it's bad.
Have some of that.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Can I get you a plate?
I wish they would
all go home.
(CHUCKLES)
What's wrong?
I never told Roger
that you weren't at
the movies last Monday.
So when you came here today,
I thought he might
ask you something,
uh, whether
you liked it or not,
and you wouldn't know
any better than to answer.
Why didn't you tell Roger
I wasn't going?
Oh, I get it.
That guy was there last week.
You've been seeing
that guy at the movies.
There's no guy at the movies.
What am I supposed
to call him?
His name is Tom.
Don't worry.
I'll cover for you
if Roger asks anything.
There's nothing to cover!
Okay?
There's nothing to cover.
Then, why are you
so nervous?
Why didn't you tell Roger
I was sick last week?
I didn't go to the movies
last week?
MAN:
We're going to take off.
ROGER: Yeah, okay, Fred.
Good seeing you. Take care.
FRED: Yeah, you, too.
Oh, it is so peaceful here!
-Can I get you anything?
-No.
Oh, it's a lovely party, dear.
Oh, I'm glad you enjoyed it.
You know I appreciate it,
don't you?
Mmm-hmm.
Did Brooke help you out any?
She wrote a check,
Roger tore it up.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
He shouldn't have.
Oh, I love both my daughters.
Brooke is all on the surface
and you're the deep one.
How those things are decided,
I have no idea.
Mother, have you ever...
What, dear?
Have you ever been attracted
to another man besides Daddy?
(GASPS) What a question!
On my golden
wedding anniversary!
(LAUGHS) I'm sorry.
Honestly, Jean, your timing
somehow confounds me.
Have you?
Nope.
It was only your father
from the first day we met.
Didn't you ever
look at another man
in a mall or...
A movie...
And just for one moment,
wonder what it would be like?
Beverly Jean, I don't want to
ever hear you talk like that.
Oh, but you're only human.
It happens to everybody once.
Maybe you've forgotten.
What are you accusing me of?
Nothing. Nothing.
I haven't
forgotten a thing.
I still remember our old
telephone number, 43668.
We only had five digits then.
Well, I'm, going to go see
how everybody's doing.
-Honey?
-Hmm?
Uh, can I be honest with you
about something?
You won't be offended,
will you?
No, not at all, Mother, what?
I don't know
if it was your idea
or your friend Susan's,
but, dear,
nobody uses butter anymore.
You've been
to the market lately?
Everything is lite,
lite, lite.
I'll remember that.
Just a suggestion.
Thank you.
SUSAN: I always
do well with tomatoes.
Last year, they were
coming out my ears.
Well, now you have
two large red,
aroma and a yellow.
Don't let me forget peppers.
Oh, right here.
How did your affair start?
Did you see him
or did he see you?
We worked
in the same building.
We ran into each other
a couple of times.
He was flat out direct,
didn't mince any words.
He said if I wanted to get
to know him better,
I shouldn't stand on ceremony.
(SUSAN CHUCKLES)
As if I ever did.
I didn't even know
his last name
till the second time
we took the hotel room.
Didn't you notice
on his credit card?
I paid.
Oh.
He worked in maintenance.
When he wasn't at work,
he was at the gym.
Muscles for days. (SIGHS)
Oh, he may not have
invented sex,
but, phew,
he sure improved on it.
Okay, that's enough.
A person gets bored
after fifteen years.
I am not bored.
How about some stringed beans?
Excuse me, but you did
start the conversation, Jean.
While you're rushing off
to change the subject
like I was sub-human,
may I remind you,
you brought it up
in the first place?
I know.
I saw the way you and Tom
look at each other.
I know what that look means.
No, we have not done anything.
Well, why don't you?
You heard me.
Go to bed with Tom.
Get it out of your system.
They don't arrest you for it,
you know?
No.
But you pay for it
in other ways.
You should know that.
(SIGHS) Guess so.
Sure seemed worth it
at the time.
Senora Townsend.
(SIGHS) Where would you
like the citrus?
Uh, over by the fence, please.
Okay.
(PHONE RINGING)
No, wait a minute.
Uh, place it
right by the shed.
Okay, Jose?
Okay.
Jean, Tom's on the phone.
He wants to talk to you.
Jose, I'll count those
with you.
ROGER: Jean, it's Tom.
He needs to talk to you.
Maybe you shouldn't call here.
What?
Who is this?
Mr. Reynolds!
Hello, Tom!
Mildew on your roses, uh-huh.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
SUSAN:
I just loved this movie.
It's my all-time favorite.
Ah!
I mush every time I see it.
My wild, sweet Cathy.
Ugh, makes me
weak in the knees.
Merle Oberon
was so beautiful.
The clothes she wore.
The woman hardly had a waist.
And what a hunk
Olivier was.
He was a great actor,
I never thought of him
as a hunk.
(SCOFFS)
You wouldn't, we would.
A major superior hunk.
Trust us.
Well, I have to get up
very early tomorrow morning.
Good night, Tom.
Glad you could
make it this week.
Goodnight.
Goodnight,
dear Heathcliff.
-Ah!
-Lovely to meet you.
You, too.
See you next week.
He likes you, Jean.
No, he's just a nice guy
who likes romantic films.
I did think you were
a little formal, though,
"Goodnight,
glad you could make it."
I'm tired.
I'll see you tomorrow.
-Goodnight, honey.
-Bye.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
(CHUCKLES)
Oops. (SIGHS)
-Trouble losing her?
-None.
She made the light, I didn't.
She always says
I drive too slowly.
I've been looking forward
to this all week.
I think I know a place
we can go.
Where?
Let me surprise you.
I should take my car.
I should follow you.
Oh, dear.
I'm a bit of a klutz
when I'm nervous.
I didn't make it two weeks
in Madame Gregoire's
ballet school for girls.
Actually to
tell you the truth,
I'm a bit of a klutz
when I'm not nervous.
Excuse me. Yes.
Oops.
MAN: Here you go.
JEAN: I was a lousy dancer,
but Madame Gregoire
was from Atlanta
and although
I couldn't do a plie,
she could not speak
a word of French.
(CHUCKLES)
Would you like
something to eat?
No. Thank you.
Uh, you can.
No, I had a sandwich
before I left home.
Oh, what kind?
Oh, scintillating, Jean!
(LAUGHS)
What a wonderful
conversationalist!
I'm really so bad
at all of this,
all this chit chat
and small talk.
I'm nervous.
You're funny.
Funny nervous.
(SIGHS)
I don't know why I'm here.
I mean, I do, but I don't.
Look, can I say something
really dumb?
You are very pretty.
(CHUCKLES)
It's not dumb.
Why do you think it's dumb?
Well, I couldn't think
of a better way to say it.
Thank you.
I lied to Carol tonight.
I told her I was going
to the office to work
after the film.
I hate lying.
I know
I'm guilty of it myself,
but I've always taught Bess
to tell the truth,
even if it means
hurting somebody's feelings.
Sparing people's feelings
can become a lifelong job,
and you lose yourself.
I don't want her to spend
the rest of her life
pleasing others.
-Have you?
-No.
Yeah.
A little.
Roger's the nicest man I know.
He would move heaven
and earth for me.
He's strong, plays softball.
Well, he used to play
on the softball team,
team broke up.
Tell me about Carol.
Well, she's decent, caring.
She wanted to have
a lot of kids.
When Kevin was born,
there were some complications
so we couldn't have anymore,
which was a boon
for three-legged dogs.
I'll explain that.
See, there was a time
when we had two
three-legged dogs.
No one else would take them in
so Carol did,
separately,
several months apart.
Till they died,
they just jumped
and hobbled around,
happy as they could be.
She loves
what nobody else does.
She's not a saint,
but she's very kind.
So, that's why I really
don't know why I'm here.
But you're a bright woman...
I was hoping
you could tell me.
Not so bright, Tom.
If I were, I would've run
that yellow light
and followed Susan
as fast as I could.
But do you know,
to hell with it.
I don't think I care.
I just wanted to see
what that would be like.
Just curious?
Yes.
Still curious?
Mmm-hmm.
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
Still curious?
I got to go.
Well, we solved
your curiosity,
what about mine?
Tom, this has been
so much fun. Thank you!
-Jean?
-Thank you.
(DOOR OPENS)
What time is it?
-JEAN: Midnight.
-(GROANS)
How do you stay up so late,
then get up so early?
You're a better sleeper
than I am.
(CHUCKLES)
(DOOR OPENS)
-Hi, heard you come in.
-Hi.
I made a chocolate cake
from scratch.
I just wanted to see
if I still knew how.
How about a nice big piece?
Price is right.
No, thanks.
So, what did you
see tonight?
Wuthering Heights.
Ah, my Achilles heel.
They assigned that to us
in high school.
I could hardly
finish reading it.
I never did see
the movie.
Maybe I should
read the book again.
All I remember are a lot
of people running around.
Ah, what was it called?
The moors!
Running and crying,
and crying and running!
(CHUCKLES)
I'll just rent the video
sometime.
Come to bed.
-I'll be up in a minute.
-Okay.
(DIALING)
(RINGING)
WOMAN: (ON PHONE) Reservation!
May I help you?
Um, yes, I'd like to
reserve a room, please.
Uh, certainly.
A single or double?
A double.
Um, for me and my wife.
All right,
and your name, please.
Yeah, it's Doster.
Tom Doster.
Mr. and Mrs. Tom Doster.
Jose, could you
help Mrs. Winsinger
with her car, please?
-Por favor.
-Yeah.
-Gracias. (CHUCKLES)
-De nada.
Bye, Bess.
Hi, honey!
Your Spanish test?
How bad was it?
-Can we go to the mall?
-The mall?
Honey, we take you there
when you get an A
and your daddy and I
want to reward you.
Well, I'm getting to the age
where I need to go to the mall
to alleviate depression.
Tada!
You are 14 years old!
I'm almost 15.
Luther will love this,
it'll drive him crazy!
There's no way
Luther or anyone else
is going to see
your chest at age 14.
He already has, Mom.
Take it off.
I wouldn't buy that for you
if you were fluent in Spanish.
BESS: I know what
you're going to say.
What exactly have you
and Luther done together?
It's private, Mom.
Yes, it is.
It's private between
you and him and me.
We haven't done anything.
A little.
Mom, we've talked
about this before.
There's only reason
for a man and woman
to have sex
and that's because
they love each other.
Yeah, but sex
is not a sport, honey.
Sit down here for a second.
It's a pleasure,
I know that.
But it's not something
you do for recreation.
Honey, I'm not asking
you to wait forever.
Just wait for someone
that you really care about.
Did you?
-Well, honey, that's...
-Private.
Bess, listen to me.
Love and commitment
are the only reasons
that you have sex.
I know you're having
peer pressures.
-God...
-I know.
I don't care
about peer pressures!
What about my own pressures?
What about the fights
I have with myself?
I mean, sometimes I think
I never want to have sex
and then other times I think
why not just do it
and get it over with?
Not think about it.
But, Mom, the whole thing
scares me.
Don't you have
any feeling for that?
Of course I do.
I know there's considerations,
you've told me 100 times.
But, Mom, there's times
when I don't care about
those considerations,
when I just want to say
to hell with it!
Mom, don't you ever get tired
of thinking so much?
Sometimes.
Well, what do you do then?
(SIGHS) I don't know.
I haven't figured
that one out yet.
It'll be okay.
BESS: Okay, so, Mom,
about the birthday party.
Okay, I know that
my birthday is not
for another month, but...
Jean. I need to see you
in my office.
We'll talk about it later.
Close the door.
From the bank,
19 checks returned
for insufficient funds.
What?
Uh, no, no,
that can't be right.
I, um...
I, oh, God, I...
I wrote the checks
and I didn't make the deposit.
You've never done that before.
I'm sorry.
If the book keeping
is too much, just say so.
I'll help you. You don't have
to do it all yourself.
Honey, I'm perfectly
capable of doing it,
I just screwed up!
We've never bounced a check
since we opened this business.
Things like that are important
to me!
(LOUDLY)
They're important to me, too!
I'll take care of it.
I will call them and I will
explain everything.
Something's upsetting you.
I know you.
It's my parents. Um...
It takes me time to recover
from their visits.
Are you still worried about
what your folks think?
Jean, you're with me.
You don't have to worry
anymore about that.
I know.
You know,
I think you're the best.
(SIGHS) I wish that could
be enough for you.
It is.
MAN: "Darling..." That's me?
WOMAN: Mmm-hmm.
MAN: "You have a date,
my beloved,
July the 1st at 5:00."
But you don't say where.
WOMAN: Well, you name
the place and I'll obey.
I don't know,
I can't think.
How about the top of
the Empire State Building?
Oh, yes, that's perfect.
It's the nearest thing
to heaven we have in New York.
MAN: The 102nd floor,
and don't forget
to take the elevator.
WOMAN: (LAUGHING)
No, I won't.
WOMAN: Darling, if things
don't work out?
MAN: Don't talk like that.
I'm not listening.
WOMAN: But just in case.
Maybe he had something
else to do.
He would've told me.
Already started
to be considerate
of one another.
That's nice.
I need the ladies' room.
(COINS CLINKING)
(PHONE RINGING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
-ROGER: Hello?
-Hi!
Hey. Movie over?
No, I just called
to say I love you.
(CHUCKLES)
Someone...
Someone should make
a song like that.
(LAUGHS)
Ah, it's not every woman
who'd leave Cary Grant for me.
I would, Roger.
Bess just went to bed.
I helped her with her math.
Big help.
I would.
What?
Leave Cary Grant for you.
I would.
And I'd leave her, too.
What was her name? Um...
Deborah Kerr, Carr?
Jean?
Um...
I'll see you later.
I should go now.
Okay. Bye.
I was so afraid.
I was afraid something
had happened
and you weren't coming.
I'm here.
I got a bit of
a late start.
I, uh, they were working
on the freeway,
but I couldn't stay away,
Jean.
I don't care
about the movie,
I just knew
that you'd be here.
(SIGHS)
I was looking
for you all night.
Then my mind started
to play tricks on me,
I thought something happened,
I was so scared.
No, nothing happened.
Listen.
I've made some plans.
I reserved a room in Hamilton
for Friday night.
Now it's far enough away.
I don't think anyone
will see us there.
Don't you want to?
I've never done anything
like that before.
Well, I was just asking.
Hey, if you don't want to,
just say it.
Ah, it's just one night.
You can make an excuse.
Oh, God!
Of all of the dumb things
to say,
and the dumb ways
to say it, I...
Look, I want you, Jean.
I want you so bad.
I just want to make this real.
I wish I could say
that I didn't want you.
I wish I could even think it.
I wasn't going
to come tonight.
I didn't get a late start,
I wasn't going to come at all.
I wasn't going to phone.
I was going
to stop everything,
just disappear from movies,
from your life.
No.
I was going to
throw you away.
And then I realized
how stupid that was.
And then I was in the car
and then I was here.
I'm glad.
I'm so glad.
Maybe you don't
believe in destiny,
but I do.
I'll meet you,
anywhere, anytime.
Just tell me where and when,
I'll be there.
I wish it were now.
(SIGHS)
You almost finished homework?
Almost.
You got to tell your father,
Kevin.
He's going to have to know.
(OPERA MUSIC PLAYING)
You're gonna be mad
at me, Dad.
Is that right?
Well, why don't you
let me decide that?
I did something bad
at school today.
I stole a calculator
from somebody else's desk
and my teacher caught me.
Did you say you were sorry?
Yes.
Did you mean it?
I guess so.
(MUSIC STOPS)
You know, the same thing
happened to me once.
I was in about third
or fourth grade,
and I stole a book
from Ronnie Norman's desk.
It was a Hardy Boy book.
See, Ronnie was from
a rich family.
He had all of
the Hardy Boy books.
I could only borrow 'em
from the library.
And it wasn't that the book
was of great value,
just like I'm sure
the calculator wasn't.
It doesn't even cost
ten dollars.
Right.
But what I didn't know then
is that it doesn't matter
what the book cost
or what the calculator cost,
it's the act,
and the act was wrong.
And I was embarrassed,
just like I'm sure
you are embarrassed.
Well, I'm glad
you told me, kid.
And I'm glad you were honest.
I respect you for that.
I promise you, Dad,
I'll never do it again.
I know you won't, son.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Do we have any plans
this Friday?
I don't think so. Why?
Ah, I mean, arboretum
in Hamilton called,
they're doing those
lectures again.
They always have
these wonderful
English gardens.
-Hmm.
-You mind if I go?
Of course not.
What time is it?
I think 7:00, 7:30.
That means
it'll be over late.
I guess so.
I don't want you
driving back from Hamilton
late and alone.
That's fine, I could...
I could take a room
in a hotel, motel.
Yeah, sounds good.
Honey.
I have to run over
to Hamilton on Friday.
Mr. Blake is looking at
a new site over there
and he wants me
to have a look.
Well, you want
a hitch hiker?
You could drop me at a mall,
any mall.
Oh, I'm not sure what the day
will bring.
Oh, I hate for you to have
to drive all that way
by yourself.
It's only a couple of hours.
I have a new Tosca
to listen to.
Then you better go alone.
Why did you marry a low brow
like me anyway?
I hate opera, I don't read
any of the good books.
Guess I just married you
for the contrast.
There's plenty of that.
Going to meet Mark.
Bye, Mom, bye, Dad.
You be careful, Kev.
(DOOR CLOSING)
Kevin told me what you
said to him last night.
You know, that's one
of the things I love
most about you, Tom.
You always understand
the value of things.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
Now, one of the most
common questions
in buying a rose
is whether to buy
a bare root or in container.
Does anyone here know
the difference?
Well, let me tell you.
A bare root goes directly
into your soil.
Now you carefully separate
the roots,
place the rose correctly,
ah, that's something else
we'll talk about,
and fill in with your soil.
Now, does anyone know
what a bud union is?
Ah, yes, young lady,
can you tell us?
Yes, do you know
what a bud union is?
The bud union is the heart
of the rose bush,
it's from the bud union
that the major
new growth develops,
if the conditions are right.
Ah, there's one thing
you've left out.
Hmm.
If you live in
a temperate climate,
the bud union can be placed
just above ground level,
like so, but if you live
in a cold climate...
You have to place it beneath
the surface where it's hidden.
Now, why is that?
The rose won't grow
if it's not hidden.
That's right.
Bud union's very fragile.
Hiding it protects it against
anything that might hurt it.
(LAUGHS)
(OPERA MUSIC PLAYING)
-Checking in, sir?
-Yes, I am.
Do you need help
with your luggage?
Well, actually, I do have
some things in the trunk
I'd like you to bring in.
Thank you.
Coming in now.
Oh, Vern, put that between
two burners, okay?
It's not going to work.
Well, it's going to have to,
it's the largest one
we've got.
Roast.
-Green beans.
-Potatoes.
Hi, honey,
you want something to eat?
It's for sick people.
-Oh, excuse me.
-It's okay.
MAN: Roast.
WOMAN: Green beans.
(VIDEO GAME NOISES)
Turn that off, please.
(LOWERS VOLUME)
-All the way.
-(SIGHS)
When are they all going
to leave?
We lost our kitchen today.
It was an old church,
and it was sold.
They're probably
going to tear it down.
We found a new kitchen,
but we can't move into it
until next week.
That left us with no place
to work,
and if we don't work,
a lot of sick people
won't eat.
You don't want that
to happen, do you?
The food we make is healthy,
Kevin.
You're not going
to catch anything
by being around it
or around us,
or around the people
we make it for.
Where's Dad?
Daddy had to go to Hamilton
on a job,
he's going to be home
really late.
(INAUDIBLE)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Climbing Rose nursery.
Uh, Yes, Jean Townsend,
please.
She's not in today.
Could I take a...
Are you checking in?
-Checking in, ma'am?
-Yes.
MAN: Room 510.
I'll take...
(BEEPS)
WOMAN: Operator.
Could I have
an outside line, please?
Hello?
JEAN: Just checking in
on everybody.
Well, we've had, um,
a little emergency.
What happened, Roger?
I don't really know.
She only wants
to talk about it with you.
Here.
Hi, Mom.
What happened, honey?
Luther's parents
are out of town.
He wanted me
to come home with him.
(SNIFFLING)
Guess why?
I said no.
He said,
either I slept with him
or found a new boyfriend.
I'll come right home,
right now.
(SOBBING) I'm okay, Mom,
you don't have to.
No, I can.
I can and I'll be there
in a few hours.
Mom! You sound worse
than me. I'm okay.
You did the right thing,
Bess.
Mom, I cried all afternoon.
(SNIFFLING)
That felt really good.
And you know what I realized?
There's a lot of boys
and some of them
don't have stupid names.
Luther sounds like a dog,
which isn't far
from the truth.
I'm so proud of you, Bess.
I wish I was as smart as you
when I was your age.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Sleep tight, don't let
the bed bugs get ya.
(CHUCKLES)
There aren't any, Mom.
-Bess?
-(SNIFFLING) Yeah?
I love you.
I love you, too, Mom.
(SNIFFLES) Bye.
Bye.
(SOBBING)
(SIGHS)
(PHONE RINGING)
WOMAN: Operator.
Mr. Doster's room, please.
(PHONE RINGING)
TOM: Hello?
I'm here.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
It's like Christmas.
TOM: Well, I wanted it
to be beautiful for you.
You must have spent a fortune.
Well, I spent
a fortune on this.
I went and got the champagne,
the flowers, and everything,
and I forgot the glasses.
But found these
in the bathroom.
I'm not... I'm not ready yet.
Could we, maybe,
take that downstairs?
Just for a little while.
Sure.
We could talk.
Yeah.
You are the only thing
I have been able
to think about.
I've been walking
around the office,
and the house,
hoping that I was doing
a good job faking it.
I don't think anyone realized
how really far away I was.
Why me, Tom?
What do you mean?
You've met other women before,
younger, prettier.
You probably had
a lot of choices.
I don't know.
(CHUCKING) Oh, come on,
you have.
Come on.
You've never spent any time
with anybody other than Carol?
Quick hour in a hotel,
couple of drinks?
Oh, you probably have,
it's just slipped your mind.
You're the first.
(SIGHS)
Roger is the only man
I have ever been with.
Can you believe that?
In this day and age?
You probably think I'm weird.
No, I don't.
I'm... I'm probably
what they call an anachronism?
Is that right?
Anachronism, yeah.
Someone who doesn't fit
into their time
and their surroundings.
A '90s woman who has only
been with one man.
(JEAN CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
Roger would cross the earth
for me if I asked him to,
and he'd never ask why.
I love him for that,
the way he trusts me.
And sometimes
I resent him...
For trusting me so much.
See, I don't only cry
in movies.
No, thank you.
Maybe you'd like
to get some air, huh?
Mmm-hmm.
JEAN: You made the room
look like a garden.
TOM: Well, I wanted you
to feel at home.
Thought if I filled the room
with flowers,
think that you were outside,
somewhere off in a forest.
I always had a fantasy
about making love outside.
Have you ever done that?
I don't think so,
I don't remember.
On cool wet grass,
with nobody around
for miles and miles,
in a beautiful garden.
(CHUCKLES)
I always seem
to get emotional
in the dark.
The darkness of the theater
where nobody can see me and...
Here.
I've wondered how
you would feel...
So many times.
In my mind...
I've touched you.
Hold me, Tom.
(SIGHS)
Oh, I'm here.
I don't ever want you to go.
I don't ever want
to be away from you.
I don't ever want to be
not touching you.
Promise me, Tom.
I promise you.
I'm thinking maybe this is
what heaven's like.
Warm and safe.
I love you.
Ah, God, Jean,
you are so warm.
I've done this in my mind,
a hundred times.
Hundred times before now.
Let's go up.
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
I can't... I can't do this.
-(THUNDER RUMBLING)
-It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
It would be so easy
if I didn't love Roger.
You want to just come in?
No, see,
I've never been good
at keeping secrets,
I'd have to keep this one
for the rest of my life.
I'm sorry. I'm so scared,
I just can't.
I'm so sorry.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Jean, wait.
We could say
we couldn't help it.
Couldn't we, Tom?
Isn't that what other
people say?
That something happened,
they didn't know what?
You hear it all the time.
Oh, only if I could
stop thinking,
just stop thinking
for a few seconds.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GROANING)
Ow!
Oh.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(PANTING)
Oh!
(GASPS)
I don't have the ticket.
That's okay.
I never forget
a car or a face.
(PANTING)
(SOBBING)
(SNIFFLING)
(CAR HONKING)
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERING)
(SIGHS)
Oh, Jean, what a mess you are.
What a mess.
Look at her.
Look at me.
(DIALING)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Hello?
(SOBBING)
Wait a minute, it's okay.
It's all right.
(SIGHS)
(SOBBING)
I just came in
from the balcony.
The sky is so clear
after it rains.
(JEAN SIGHS)
Stars everywhere.
Don't see stars
very much here.
I'm sorry I ran away.
Sometimes when we can't find
words to explain, we run.
(SIGHS)
I can't live
like this anymore.
I'm doing things
I've never done,
I mean, lying.
I'm making up excuses.
I think people are seeing
how strange I'm acting.
(SIGHS)
I'm afraid to say anything
'cause I'm afraid
it's going to be wrong
and something will slip out.
Where are you?
(SIGHS) Some motel
off the freeway.
The Bates Motel.
(CHUCKLES)
(JEAN SNIFFLING)
You have a balcony?
Yeah.
Look up.
It's clear.
I see the stars.
Hold me, Tom.
Put your arms around me.
You feel them?
Mmm-hmm.
I'm holding you.
From the sea to the sea
I'm holding you
as close as I can.
What do we do now?
I wish I knew, Jean.
I wish I knew.
(SIGHS)
Hey, Kev, did you
get something to eat?
Mom made some chicken
before she left.
Good.
Hey, Dad.
Can a man and a woman
just be friends?
Yes.
Why do you ask that?
Hey.
Come on, you know
there's nothing off limits
between us.
I found this in your car.
Business cards
and a perfume bottle.
Well, Jean went to
the film series with me,
and I gave her a ride
in my car,
and as I recall,
she accidentally
spilled her bag.
So, you and her
are friends then?
Yeah. And I hope
we'll always be that.
That's all?
Yeah, just good friends.
Very good friends.
I think I understand now.
Can I have some
ice cream, Dad?
Sure.
BESS: Uh, Mom,
can you pass the vegetables?
-Mom?
-Yes, honey.
Um, can you please pass
the vegetables?
Oh, yeah.
I made dessert.
Oh, I'm too fat.
You are not too fat.
-Roger! You want dessert?
-ROGER: Later.
Are you going
to the movies tonight?
Yeah, have to. Last one.
All young people think
they're fat.
You're a six.
Do you know how many people
would love to be a six?
Well, what do you think?
Uh? (CHUCKLING)
Oh, jeez!
York Groove All Stars
are going to try again.
First practice
is this Saturday.
Danny Meyer
called all the guys,
everyone's over
their bruised egos.
We are ready
to bruise them again.
Uh, Dad, your pants are split.
Oh, yeah. I was hoping,
maybe, you could sew
it up for me.
Sure, when I get home.
Is, um, Susan
going tonight?
Or is she out on an emergency
session with her shrink?
Susan, yeah,
she'll be there.
WOMAN: When you were out
in the real country,
I think it was a few miles
beyond Greyfield,
we stopped the car
just outside a village
and got out.
There was a little bridge
and a stream,
and the sun was making
an effort to come out,
but really not succeeding
very well.
We leaned on the parapet
of the bridge
and looked down
into the water.
I shivered, and Alec
put his arm around me.
MAN: Cold?
WOMAN: No, not really.
MAN: Happy?
I knew exactly what you
were going to say.
That it isn't worth it.
That the furtiveness
and lying
outweigh the happiness
we might have together.
Isn't that it?
Something like that.
MAN:
I want to ask you something,
just to reassure myself.
WOMAN: What is it?
MAN: It is true for you,
isn't it?
This overwhelming feeling
we have for each other.
It's as true for you
as it is for me, isn't it?
WOMAN: Yes, it's true.
SUSAN: Was Brief Encounter
after Gone with the Wind?
-What?
-Which came first?
Brief Encounter or
Gone with the Wind?
Gone with the Wind,
I think.
Trevor Howard
doesn't look like he did
in Gone with the Wind.
Trevor Howard wasn't
Leslie Howard
was in Gone with the Wind.
Really?
I never knew they
were different people.
Leslie Howard, Trevor Howard.
Well, what do you know.
They're both English,
aren't they?
They were.
They're both dead now.
SUSAN: Well,
there you have it.
It's the way
the English talk...
(ENGLISH ACCENT)
...from the bottom
of their throats.
(NORMAL VOICE)
They all sound alike.
Excuse me, I'll be right back.
Of course,
you'll talk about me
while I'm gone.
Sticks and stones
can break my bones,
but words can never hurt me.
I'm not ignorant, you know.
Just because
I didn't know the difference
between Leslie Howard
and Trevor Howard,
doesn't mean I haven't
been well educated.
Actually, I was voted
most likely to succeed.
But I got married instead.
(CHUCKLES)
It was a lovely movie.
Yes, it was.
I'd never seen
that one before.
Yeah, I saw it a long ago,
but I remember
it being in color.
I don't remember it being
in black and white.
Oh, they didn't seem
to film much in color then,
but not much, yeah.
-Listen, I got a call...
-You know, I was thinking...
Oh, I'm sorry,
you go first.
-No, I'm sorry, go ahead.
-No, you.
I got a call a couple
of days ago
from a company...
SUSAN:
That's it for me, folks.
It was really nice
to meet you, Tom.
It was nice to meet you, too.
You two stay. I'm tired.
No, I... I have to go, too.
Goodbye.
I mean goodnight.
Don't let me break up
the party.
Oh, it's all right.
I think the evening's over.
Goodnight.
JOSE: Senora Townsend!
-Yeah?
-Telefono.
-Someone named Tom?
-Ah.
(CHUCKLES)
Still having
mildew problems, huh?
Well, I'm having
some problems,
but mildew
isn't one of them.
Oh, I...
Look, Jean,
I need to see you.
I have to see you, too.
When?
Now. Right now.
Um, city park,
by the rose garden.
(DIAL TONE)
Um, Roger?
I just got a call
and I have to run over
to Taylor's
to make a bid
for some landscaping.
Hope they don't need it soon,
we are up to our ears.
No, I don't think so.
I think they've still
got to put in their pool.
You mind going
and picking up Bess
after school, if I'm late?
Sure.
Thank you.
See you later.
(SIGHS)
You have one, too.
I don't quite know
how to say this.
(SOBBING) Oh, come on,
Beverly Jean, just say it.
I can't see you
after this anymore, Tom.
I just can't.
It's not true, I can,
but I won't.
I won't.
Seems to be the only thing
that's right.
(SNIFFLING)
And I don't mean just right,
I mean possible.
Are you angry with me?
No.
You are.
I'm moving, Jean.
I mean...
We're moving,
Carol, Kevin and I.
I wanted to tell you
the other night,
but I couldn't.
A few months ago
I got an offer
from a company
in Seattle.
I turned them down.
Last week,
I called them back
and said if they were
still interested,
I was.
You really have to do that?
Move away?
Jean, as long as I'm here,
I'll find you.
And then,
I'll drive by your house,
I'll go to the same places
you go,
I'll take all the risks.
You know how many times
I've driven by your house
just in the hope
of seeing you?
It's the only answer.
And after we've been away
from each other for a while,
our lives will go on.
Maybe not right away,
but in time.
I can't stay.
You're a much stronger person
than I am
and I just don't trust myself
that much.
Sometimes when you
don't know what else to do...
You run.
Your hair is turning
a little gray.
Mine, too.
Nobody will ever see mine,
I'm too vain.
I'll wonder what
you will look like
in years to come.
You'll probably
turn all silver.
Never felt for anyone
the way I feel
about you, Jean.
You have.
You've forgotten.
You felt it with Carol.
I felt it with Roger.
When we first met,
we were consumed with passion.
Every chance we got,
every place we could think of,
we couldn't get enough
of each other.
And then, as time passed...
Things got more familiar,
a little less exciting.
We're still physical,
but maybe not as much.
So, things change,
they turn to touching...
Little kisses.
The quiet things.
So maybe they are...
Different from
when we first met,
but in the beginning
it was passionate,
way beyond the movies.
Our problem
is our memory.
We forgot, didn't we, Tom?
We forgot what we really had.
When it's not
in front of us...
We forget that
it was really there,
but it was.
We just have to find a way
to get it back again.
You and I never made love...
But I really don't remember
if we did or not.
I wanted to give
you something,
a present,
so you wouldn't forget me.
I don't need
a present for that.
-When are you leaving?
-Next Saturday.
You'll like Seattle.
Things grow well in Seattle.
They have all that wonderful
rain there.
-I've got to go.
-Please.
I'm going to turn
and walk away,
and when I go,
I'm not gonna
look back at you.
Cause I can't look
at you one more time.
I love you, Jean.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(SNIFFLING)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSING)
Hello!
ROGER: I'm in here.
Hey. My baseball pants.
I told you I'd do it.
Yeah, well, I was
just sitting here,
and I thought
it's got to be pretty easy.
None of that phony
macho stuff for me,
so I tried to thread
the needle.
And I've been
trying to thread this needle
for the last ten minutes.
Oh.
(SCOFFS)
-You're staring at me.
-Mmm-hmm.
I missed you.
You missed me?
(LAUGHS)
How could you miss me?
We are together every day.
I was gone for a little while,
but now I'm back.
(SIGHS)
-Give me those pants.
-Yeah?
No, not those pants!
Give me those pants.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
ROGER: Got ya.