♪ ♪
Wake your lazy ass up, Eddie.
You know I never sleep, Mr. Cort.
You moving something
tonight?
Yeah, maybe.
See anybody in lab four?
All quiet.
I didn't let anybody in, just like you said.
Good man. Appreciate that.
No problem.
Hey, yo, Eddie.
Got something on your shirt.
- [ Groans ]
- I love it when they do that.
The bar is now open.
Come on. Move along.
Let's take the building.
Hey, you!
[ Sighs ]
It's you, Mr. Cort.
We thought we heard gunfire.
Oh, don't worry.
It's just a false alarm.
Thanks.
[ Gunfire ]
[ Gunfire continues ]
[ Screams, gasps ]
All right, let's go.
[ Commando ] Set the timers for five minutes.
[ Timer beeps ]
[ Alarm blaring ]
[ Blaring continues ]
Charges are in place.
Let's move!
[ Blaring continues ]
[ Beeps ]
[ Alarm blaring ]
Hey! Hey, you guys!
[ All firing ]
[ Gunfire continues ]
[ Firing gun ]
- [ Timer ticking ]
- [ Timer beeps ]
[ TV reporter ] A terrorist bombing attack
left eight dead in Florida last night,
including Stevens corporation
head of security, Jeff cort.
Federal officials investigating
the case promise swift...
And forceful reprisals
for the deadly incident.
In the meantime, buck Stevens
and NASA are determined...
To launch the world's first
antimissile laser satellite.
Dr. Kevin Thomas,
designer of the system,
believes it will end war
as we know it.
This weapon is not designed
to kill human beings.
It's designed to kill other weapons.
It's designed to kill wars.
[ Ringing ]
[ Sighs, turns off TV ]
Horseshit.
Mack, Stevens corp.
Two.
[ Sighs ]
- This is agent Taylor.
- Agent Taylor, good morning.
Frank Ewing, Stevens corp.
What can I do for you?
I'm been trying to get through to your
office for the last day and a half.
I'm a busy man. Thunderstrike
launch is in 24 hours.
I'm up to my ass in federal investigators, and
I lost a lot of good men in that explosion.
I mean no disrespect, doctor, but our agency's
been assigned to security on this project,
and I don't appreciate being
shut out on the investigation.
According to Washington, your
agency's involvement doesn't begin...
Until we fly to the pacific
for further testing.
So until that time,
I trust you will inform us...
Of any possible overseas leads
regarding this terrible attack.
[ Line disconnects ]
Kiss my ass.
[ Slams down receiver ]
Hey.
You break it, you buy it.
Sorry, Sam.
We're just spinning
our wheels here.
Owen Cantrell has surfaced;
Late last week, in Moscow.
Cantrell?
Yeah, ex-marine colonel turned arms dealer.
Haven't heard from him
in a while.
You think
he's the connection?
The most powerful weapon in history
is about to be launched into space.
A lot of unsavory characters might
pay a great deal of money for that.
- If I was in the market, I'd go to Cantrell.
- Somebody needs to tell Stevens.
Do either of you guys
own a good suit?
Two scotches, straight up.
Mine's a fruit juice, thank you.
I'm in no mood to celebrate.
[ Mack ]
You need to get a new suit.
[ Laughs ]
Look who's talking.
We need new bank accounts.
Women appreciate a good look.
Think about that.
- I think I'm not interested.
- Men appreciate a good look too.
What?
You've got to get on
with your life.
It's been three years
since you lost them.
As it happens, partner,
it's been three years
to the day.
If you want to talk
about my wife and son,
why don't you do it on your
own time and without me?
Cheers.
I was just trying
to get him laid.
I don't want to argue, Kevin.
I want to get drunk.
Double vodka rocks, please.
I'll set everything up
with buck. Big office
right here in L.A.
All you have to do
is say yes.
I like my job. I like
traveling with daddy.
I don't like L.A., and I
don't like married men.
Why don't you ever
give me a chance to explain?
I love you, Tiffany.
You want to know what I love?
I love this drink.
No word from the feds
on the terrorists.
What about the c.I.A.?
They're riding shotgun on this deal.
I think they may want us
to postpone the launch.
They don't take over security till we leave
the country, but they're getting pushy.
What's Kevin think?
Kevin's having some personal problems.
I don't know.
What do you think?
You know as much about
thunderstrike as he does.
I say we light that candle.
Mr. Stevens,
my name's mack Taylor.
Taylor. I understand you've been
trying to snoop around my barn.
We haven't been able to get through
to your office until today.
The f.B.I. Is handling the investigation
and security at this time.
Mr. Taylor's group
takes over from the feds...
Once we're en route
to Guam for the test phase.
What the hell have you got
your ass in a knot for, boy?
They got the barn.
They didn't get the cattle.
Look, partner, we think Owen
Cantrell might be gunning for you,
so why don't you just think
of us as the cavalry?
Sir, we have reason to believe
they may have taken something...
From your lab
prior to the explosion.
The f.B.I. Retrieved black box video
from one of the security cams.
Even if that's true, all they got
was a thunderstrike control unit.
That piece of hardware
is useless without the software.
Without the brains,
you can't control
the thunderstrike satellite.
That software is safe here in L.A.
till we are on that plane.
Maybe they have a plan
to get the software.
If I was Wyatt Earp here,
I'd be real concerned.
Hey, I've got plenty of enemies,
always have, but hear this:
Thunderstrike goes up at dawn.
Now, I got a speech to make,
if you'll excuse me.
Nice suit.
Making friends wherever you go, Taylor.
C.I.A. Is on that plane...
Or the operation is shut down, and
that is straight from Washington.
You got that?
That will be fine...
As long as it isn't you.
And you're planning
on leaving her?
Leave her?
I was gonna tell you.
I'd never respect you
if you did.
You want to know
what sucks about my life?
After learning
what a shit you really are,
I still love you.
Well, this is the big moment, doctor.
Are you excited?
I suppose.
Buck wants you to join him.
You do it.
You always wanted the credit.
You go ahead.
Kevin, pick yourself up off the floor...
And go help daddy.
I'll be right back.
Sorry I had to break up
the party. Work, you know.
And, by the way...
I'm not married.
I'm not surprised.
[ Sighs ]
Wendy Robbins.
Alcohol, tobacco and firearms.
You've come
to the right place.
Trying to bust buck for making moonshine
or are you drinking all the evidence?
That's very cute, Taylor.
We're tracking a group of illegal
arms buyers; Russian mafia, I think.
Maybe Balkan.
What's that got to do with your man, buck?
We think they're in the market
for thunderstrike.
[ Scoffs ]
Hell, they can't afford it.
No one can except
for that old bastard up there.
Nice talking to you.
I'd like to dedicate
this little gathering...
To the fine men and women that
died in the attack on our lab.
[ Crowd applauding ]
Now, together with the f.B.I.
And the c.I.A.,
we're gonna find out who blew up our
lab, and we're gonna kill them.
[ Man ]
Right.
But tomorrow morning, thunderstrike flies
into the sky on that shuttle on schedule.
[ Crowd applauding ]
Y'all want to hear
something funny?
Back in the '80s, they canceled the
star wars missile defense program.
You know why?
Well, they said it was because
they didn't have enough money.
Hell, it was
a lot simpler than that.
They didn't have buck Stevens.
[ Chuckling ]
Now Dr. Kevin Thomas,
the man who built this weapon.
Dr. Thomas.
Thank you, buck.
Thank you, everyone.
Ladies and gentlemen...
The guardian of our children's
future: Thunderstrike.
[ Crowd applauding ]
[ News reporter ]
Thunderstrike began its
journey into space today...
Blasting off
on board shuttle Atlantis.
A series of tests are scheduled in
the pacific. Space-based laser...
Bikini atoll.
[ Turns off TV ]
What?
It's just like those h-bomb tests
at bikini atoll in the '50s.
They sank over a hundred Navy ships
in that exercise... and an island.
"And an island."
God bless America.
- That will be something to see.
- I'm glad you're interested.
Langley says they want you to escort
Stevens and his people to Hawaii.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What the hell is going on?
This is mack's gig, sir. I'm just
supposed to monitor security from here.
Buck Stevens doesn't want
mack on that flight.
I don't give a rat's ass
what he wants.
This is a joint military civilian project.
Very touchy.
Stevens corporation has requested
a more diplomatic escort.
Jim's all we got.
This is bullshit.
This is Langley.
I do what they tell me
to do and so do you.
Fine, Sam. You want me
to be more diplomatic,
you just tell me which one of his ass
cheeks to kiss, and I'll get down to it.
You're too late.
Jim's already set.
What are we carrying?
Strike software.
A handful of computer disks.
A milk run.
Yeah, it's nothing.
[ Water running ]
David, would you
come in here, honey?
How about a hot bath
with me?
I'm flying Mr. Stevens to Hawaii.
He's gonna call any minute.
Oh... this suite
must have cost you a fortune.
This is a special occasion.
Tell me more.
Karen, I know we've only known
each other a few weeks,
and...
I said I can't afford to get serious.
Do you have something to say?
A friend got me an offer
from a major airline:
A regular schedule,
big money, big things.
For us.
[ Laughs ]
Oh, my god.
Will you marry me?
Mrs. David Rogers.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
[ Knocking ]
Who the hell is that?
Who is it?
[ Indistinct ]
Rich.
Sneaky, rotten...
I believe the gentleman
ordered these.
Karen...
Rich Layton, my backup pilot.
We've met.
[ David gasping ]
- How long does this take?
- He's dying now.
He'll know in ten seconds.
He'll be dead in less than 30.
[ Gasps ]
[ Groans ]
You'll get the rest
when you land the plane.
That's if I land the plane.
This isn't gonna be
enough money.
This is a very dangerous sort of
landing you folks want me to pull off.
Take it as a down payment.
We'll double it at the other end.
No, that's not good enough.
I want triple
the money.
All right.
It's only money.
[ Door opens, closes ]
Hey.
Damn fine job, cort.
Now all we need is the software.
You'll get it.
You paid for it.
Better than Stevens?
I wouldn't be here otherwise.
Now where's my money?
I'm very impressed with your efficiency.
I hope you'll think about joining our crusade.
"Crusade"? What the hell
are you crusading about, Owen?
Have you met my god?
I'm thinking you boys must be pretty worried
about someone stealing thunderstrike.
What makes you think we're worried?
That's your fifth cup of coffee,
and you're risking congressional
inquiry by operating on U.S. soil.
We don't officially take control
of project security...
Until the Stevens team's
en route to Hawaii and Guam.
Agent Taylor, you look a little worried,
got a few more lines on your face today.
That's old age and hypertension,
the silent killer.
I think that lab explosion is tied into a
possible theft of thunderstrike technology.
I can place buyers in the U.S.
who have a motive.
You have no hard evidence.
- So you're confirming that line of investigation?
- I'm not confirming anything.
You want something from me, you
give me something in return.
We have an informant
inside Stevens corp.
The informant has mentioned
a possible connection...
Between someone in the company
and our group of foreign buyers.
- Give me the name of the informant.
- What do I get?
Dinner, my house.
Strictly business.
I don't have time for sex.
[ Laughs ]
Mmm, that is unbelievable.
The secret's in the sauce.
Did you study gourmet cooking?
Yeah, right.
Actually, I studied mechanical engineering.
Wanted to build airplanes.
That was my nanny's recipe.
Ooh, a little rich boy.
Rich and spoiled.
That's probably why I flunked out of
engineering school and joined the army.
Then the agency grabbed me.
Quite a career track.
You should be so lucky.
I think that's the whole
point of this dinner.
I want to move up.
I tie up this investigation,
I get to jump a few rungs.
- What do you want from me?
- I've got buyers. Who's the seller?
- We think it's Owen Cantrell.
- Son of a bitch.
So it is thunderstrike
they're after.
- Is he inside the country?
- Give Sam a call tomorrow.
He'll give you limited access
to the files on thunderstrike.
Now you give me what I want.
Who's the informant?
- He's a pilot.
- Let's go meet him.
Can't do that.
He's flying buck Stevens to Hawaii tonight.
Who's the c.I.A. Sending?
It's a guy named carpenter.
He's a widower.
Wife and kid ate it
in a car accident.
That's nice.
That's very nice.
They send
a grief-stricken widower.
It was three years ago.
Now he's got no life.
He lives for his job, which
means he would die for you.
Of course,
we'd all die for you, sir.
Makes me feel
real warm and cuddly.
Your itinerary, buck.
Thank you.
Judy...
You're about ready to pop.
I'm just seven months, Dr. Ewing, but
I guess I have been eating for two.
Word to the wise: After that
baby, I'd get the weight off quick.
See you on the plane, buck.
Yeah, you bet.
Judy, you're just
pretty as a picture.
Here, have a seat.
One minute.
I want to beat traffic.
I need you to go with me.
No, no, no. I can't do that.
I've got too much to do at home.
Judy, you got two months before that
youngin comes knocking to get out.
I need my best personal
assistant with me, in Hawaii.
Buck, I-I haven't packed.
I can't.
Oh, hell, Judy.
The company will buy you a whole
new wardrobe in Honolulu.
Maternity size, but cute.
- I have commitments.
- You got a date?
You mind telling me
what the real problem is?
Buck, I have another job.
I need the money.
In your condition?
Do you think I set out
to be a single mom?
Uh-uh.
I just got lucky.
Your h.M.O. Doesn't cover a preexisting condition.
I haven't been here long enough.
Judy, you have become the best that I got.
You can quit that other job.
You understand?
Consider your salary doubled.
I'll take care of the insurance.
So get your butt
down on that plane.
There's a nice Sandy beach waiting for you...
And your passenger.
Thank you, buck.
I don't know what to say.
Say aloha.
Aloha.
[ Radar, computer equipment
beeping ]
[ Beeping continues ]
- Coffee's on the table.
- Thanks.
- Tastes like money.
- [ Laughs ]
[ Judy ]
It's like a flying sports bar.
[ Laughing ]
Yes. And you must be Judy Campbell.
How in the hell
would you know that?
Jim carpenter.
I'm the c.I.A. Liaison on this flight.
I've read
everyone's files.
- Except his.
- Or hers.
I better make sure
everything's ready for buck.
From what I hear, he doesn't
need anything but the bar.
Oh, man,
what a character.
You have no idea.
[ Laughs ]
Looks like
they oversold the flight...
In which case I may have
to sit next to you...
At least until we take off.
Well, all right then.
Buck wants the bar open
when he gets here.
I'd do it myself,
but... all tied up.
Would you mind?
I know it's not part
of the job description.
- Unless you want to carry this damn thing around.
- I could use a drink.
Double-check that landing light, huh?
Hey, guys.
- You must be miss kenner.
- Yeah. Where's Dave Rogers?
I'm rich Layton.
I'm Dave's backup.
Dave's got a flu bug today.
I've never known Dave
to be sick a day in his life.
Last time I saw him, he was flat on his back.
Oh.
We go way back. I was just
looking forward to seeing him.
Yeah, maybe next time.
Call me Cindy.
Okay, Cindy.
I better go check
on the passengers.
Where the hell's my whiskey?
Hey, Cindy Lou!
Buck.
Damn glad to see you back.
Just like old times.
Thanks for hiring me back.
[ Scoffs ]
I'm sorry
about your divorce.
I'm not.
Catch you later.
You just can't seem to keep
your hands off him, can you?
I never meant to cause your
family any pain, Tiffany.
Really?
Then what are you doing on our plane?
I'm working...
For Mr. Stevens.
Really?
I heard that pays really well
if you're limber enough.
Tell me,
do married men tip better?
I don't know. I hear your married
man's coming on board. Let's ask him.
This must be the secret agent.
Have you met Judy?
She's unattached.
Well, sort of.
Don't hardly look pregnant.
Y'all are most kind and full of horse manure.
[ Buck laughing ]
Oh, she's a feisty one.
Best assistant I ever had.
- Name your poison.
- Straight bourbon.
And give Judy anything she wants
here as long as it's virgin.
And a shot of Tequila
for the secret agent.
Oh, no, sir.
I'm working.
According to Langley you're
working for me, so drink.
Buck, come on.
If he doesn't want to drink,
he doesn't want to drink.
Shut up and give it to him.
- Well, here's to it.
- Cheers.
All right.
That will do it.
Hey, man, they got a fresh pot
of coffee if you want some.
No, man.
I like my coffee cold.
You know that.
Hey, where's
that Stevens jet going?
- 747's heading to Honolulu.
- Nice night for it.
- It's clear as a friggin' bell.
- [ Chuckles ]
All right, I'm starting to get sweaty palms.
Have them roll the tractor.
All right, unhook us, boys.
[ Sighs ]
She dump you yet?
Excuse me?
She ought to,
you son of a bitch.
You don't diddle with my daughter, boy.
You got a wife back east.
Dad, I can diddle
with whoever I want.
- And it's not gonna be you.
- [ Buck chuckling ]
Boy,
she sure takes after her mama.
- Whoo!
- Look, buck, I'm sorry.
I know it looks like I'm taking
advantage of your daughter.
Hey, she's a grown woman.
She makes her own way.
You want to fool around
with her, that's okay with me.
I just pity the son of a bitch
that wants to marry her.
Well, that would be me.
Stevens 747,
this is L.A. tower.
You are clear for taxi,
runway 6.
Roger, tower.
[ Revving engines ]
On your own natural breath.
[ Exhales ]
In... out.
[ Inhales, exhales ]
You're good at this.
I didn't take the classes.
I have some experience.
Again, breathe in.
And out.
[ Inhales, exhales ]
You have a kid?
Uh... no.
No kids.
Not anymore.
[ Exhales deeply ]
Oh, my god.
Are you in labor?
Hell, no.
I'm practicing.
Okay.
Stevens 747,
this is L.A. tower.
You are clear for takeoff.
You have the ball.
Roger, tower.
Next stop: Waikiki.
Rev 'em up.
[ Rich ]
Okay, everyone, please buckle yourselves in.
We are preparing for takeoff.
- [ Buckles seat belt ]
- [ Sighs ]
[ Light beeps ]
Did you dust
for fingerprints?
[ Ringing ]
Taylor.
Mack, the informant's dead.
Someone else is flying that plane.
[ Hangs up receiver ]
[ Ringing ]
Cantrell.
[ Karen ]
Unscramble.
Their pilot's dead.
Our pilot wanted more money,
so I had to make sure that he got some.
We'll get it back from him.
What about the buyers?
They've arrived in country
and gone underground.
We'll dig them up
after the rendezvous.
Perfect.
Next transmission: 0200 hours.
Get some rest.
You've had a busy day.
Just leaving a trail
of broken hearts.
- Who is she?
- My corporate raider.
You trust her?
-I trust her to do the wrong
thing for the right price.
-Like we all do about that time.
We're at our cruising altitude
of 29,000 feet.
Should get us into Honolulu
in time for sunrise.
Please feel free to wander
the cabin at your leisure.
[ Unbuckles seat belt ]
Join me for a drink, doc?
No, thanks, buck.
[ Sighs ]
Look, sooner or later
we'll have to talk.
Would you like to discuss
the itinerary? Ask Judy.
She has all the paperwork.
I want to discuss this relationship.
Which relationship
would that be, Kevin?
The one with your wife?
We've been separated for three years.
"Separated"? What?
Why wouldn't you tell me?
I've been trying.
My wife left me a long time ago.
She's in another relationship.
We're divorcing next month.
Okay?
[ Sighs ]
I think I will have
that drink with buck now.
Excuse me.
[ Sighs ]
Set me up, dad.
[ Clears throat ]
Yes, ma'am.
Oh...
We'll be down soon.
- Don't you tell anybody.
- Never.
- Having fun, frank?
- Always. You?
Help yourself.
Okay, let's go ahead and put her on autopilot.
Roger.
Switching to autopilot.
[ Rich sighs ]
I'm gonna stretch my legs.
What's that level
on number four there?
[ Groaning ]
[ Falls to floor ]
[ Inhales ]
Okay. All right.
Bye-bye gas.
Back on manual.
[ Sighing ]
[ Alarm beeping ]
Shit.
That's not supposed to happen.
[ Alarm continues beeping ]
Cindy, could you come
to the flight deck, please?
Oh, my god.
The engine's on fire.
[ Beeping continues ]
What's happening?
We have major fuel loss,
and number four is on fire.
- What's wrong with Jack?
- [ Rich ] I don't know. He keeled over. Check him out.
He's dead.
My auxiliary fuel's gone.
I'm on fumes.
Get the passengers ready
for an emergency landing.
I'm gonna have to ditch.
[ Beeping continues ]
Move it!
[ Sighs ]
Okay.
[ Phone buzzes ]
Cargo bay.
[ Rich ] We're going to have to ditch.
Make sure everything's secure in the hold.
Ditch?
Shit.
Ah, fuck.
What the hell is going on?
There's an engine on fire.
Take your seat, buck.
We have to land.
Take your seat!
Get below radar.
[ Alarm continues beeping ]
The fire's out.
Yeah, but we're losing altitude,
so stay calm.
We're going to have to make
an emergency landing.
Please take your seats
as quickly as possible.
All right, listen up.
We don't leave
without the cargo.
without the passenger.
[ Ringing ]
Cort.
This is the bridge. She should
drop off radar any second.
Okay, boys.
It's time to take a boat ride.
[ Beeping ]
Stevens 747,
this is L.A. control.
We have lost you on radar,
over.
Bill.
Bill, come here.
What's the matter?
The Honolulu flight just dropped off radar.
What?
Log the time,
the last known position vector.
Folks, we have a code 99!
Keep shouting.
Stevens 747,
this is L.A. control.
This is L.A. control,
over.
This is 747 to carpathia.
The approximate point of impact
is longitude 150, latitude 30.
Affirmative.
We're on our way.
Steady on, sweet thing.
Come on.
I'm too young to die like this.
It's gonna be okay.
[ Judy screams ]
[ Screams, groans ]
[ Glass clinking ]
[ Panting ]
[ Fuselage groaning ]
Don't panic.
Emergency lights come on automatically.
Unbuckle and move
to the exits quickly.
Floatation devices will automatically
expand at all main exits.
Let's get out of here!
Give me a hand!
Now.
Wait! Hold up!
We're sinking!
[ Plane groaning ]
- Oh, my god. We're sinking.
- [ Judy ] Are we under?
[ Radar beeping ]
- The water's at the door.
- [ Tiffany ] Is there another way out?
The cockpit.
Let's go upstairs.
[ All screaming ]
[ Screaming continues ]
- [ Screaming continues ]
- Hang on!
We've stopped.
We're on the bottom.
Oh, my god, no.
[ Door opens ]
What are we gonna do?
I can't deploy
the emergency beacon.
- I think the mechanism jammed on impact.
- What about the radio?
It's dead.
Can they find us?
I don't know.
Maybe with radar traces.
But let's not give the passengers
any more to worry about, all right?
The plane was lost on radar
about 20 minutes ago.
That gives us
a 230-square-mile grid to cover.
The Navy has a battle group
in the region.
They're moving in
to support rescue op.
They aren't gonna find much in the dark.
[ Phone rings ]
Yeah.
Who? A.T.F.?
Mack, an a.T.F. Agent
named Robbins?
This is mack.
- It's down, isn't it?
- [ Mack ] No comment.
You didn't get much for your trade so
I thought I'd try and make it up to you.
The pilot mentioned something
about a girlfriend.
He gave me her name and an address
up on Mulholland near Benedict.
- Meet me there in half an hour.
- Why?
There is no girlfriend.
The house belongs to something
called marsh ocean industries.
We can tie that to Owen cantrell. Maybe
he knows where that plane went down.
Okay.
Give me the address.
Sir.
At ease, lieutenant.
Any signals from the plane?
No, not yet.
I'm sending up search planes
to monitor this grid.
I want you to keep in touch with them.
Give me any and all updates.
Once they narrow it down, I want a
night vision search by 0600 hours.
Is anybody alive?
Do you think they have a chance, sir?
If they are,
it's because they're trapped in a
747 at the bottom of the ocean.
What do you think,
lieutenant?
Hello?
Get me L.A. control.
Some U.S. Navy captain,
line one.
How can I help you, sir?
All I can give you
is their last known position.
They just dropped off
the radar screen.
At this point, the most important
thing for us to do is to stay calm.
- I'll stay calm when you get us the hell out of here.
- Easy, buck. Easy.
We're only down about 100 feet. That's not
enough water pressure to crack the fuselage.
Our air purifier is working.
As long as we have battery power we can breathe.
So Cindy's going
to pass out life vests.
I would ask that each of you
put them on right away.
What makes you so sure that
somebody is coming to help us?
All flights are tracked by radar
and satellite every 12 seconds.
We've already released
an emergency beacon.
What happens when they find us?
They send divers to get us.
All we have to do is wait.
We'll be rescued before we're
even missed. I promise.
Pretty pickle, huh?
[ Laughs ]
[ Gasping ]
What is it?
I don't know.
Come on, help me.
[ Sighs ]
Come on, don't be shy.
You've done this before,
right?
Yeah,
but it was another lifetime.
Okay.
What do you think?
The good thing is you're not too
tense and it's not too tight.
I don't know.
Maybe a tiny bruise.
- You're not feeling contractions?
- I don't know.
[ Gasps ]
Look! They're here!
They're here!
Hot damn!
In here!
Hold on a second.
They got here fast!
[ Whispers ]
Can I have a word with you?
That was quick.
Too quick.
This isn't a rescue party.
They were waiting for us.
Did you bring a gun?
You?
Keep your ears open.
Okay, gentlemen, let's go.
Are they bringing
the rest of my money?
[ Frank ]
You are going with us to the exchange.
After we demo thunderstrike
for the buyers, they pay us.
Then we pay you.
No, that was not my agreement.
Do you want to stay here?
Stay down.
Don't move, captain.
All right, ewing, I don't want money.
I want answers.
Who the hell
are those guys out there?
Hello, gentlemen.
- Am I glad to see you.
- Likewise.
What the hell is going on?
Howdy, buck!
Welcome to my hostile corporate takeover.
Cort?
Why, you worthless son of a bitch.
- Easy. He'll kill us all.
- Eventually.
Yeah, but you want ewing and his
black box, and I've already got him.
Why don't you swim back out?
What are you gonna do, shoot him on
a plane at the bottom of the ocean?
There's a lot of soft tissue.
I'm gonna cut it close.
- [ Groans ]
- So am I.
Why, you miserable
piece of horseshit.
Buck, please,
there are ladies present.
Kev, I bet you wish
you would have traded me.
[ Scoffs ]
You'll never live to spend
what they're paying you.
Let me worry about that.
They'll kill you just like
the pilot, you idiot.
You bastards!
Come on.
That's enough small talk, okay?
Get ewing into his dive gear.
We gotta get out of here.
You ladies and gentlemen
have a nice evening.
And by the way,
I wouldn't try to follow me...
'Cause a small hole in this big
plane would let a lot of water in.
See ya.
[ Sighs ]
I'm the dumbest son of a bitch in Texas.
You got company, buck.
[ Laughs ]
[ Jim groaning ]
Over here.
[ Cindy ]
Put him down.
[ Continues groaning ]
[ Grunts, groaning ]
Oh, god. Thanks, buck.
I'm having trouble
breathing.
I think it missed any vital organs.
How would you know?
- I was a triage nurse in desert storm.
- [ Jim ] That's good.
You're losing blood, but not
as much as you should be.
[ Groaning ]
I'm not feeling too great.
Tiffany, can you get me
the first-aid kit?
It's the second locker
near the cockpit door.
I don't have the time or gear to get the bullet
out. I think we're gonna have to leave it in.
Hey, what do you know,
maybe it's plugging me up.
- I think so.
- [ Jim ] Fine.
The pain's not too bad.
We'll see if we can't
find you some good drugs.
I want to stay alert,
all right?
Okay.
Thanks.
[ Exhaling deeply ]
[ Groaning ]
Anything yet?
They picked up some shadows,
nothing they could pinpoint.
They're loading the sonar
gear into my chopper now.
If we find something, we send a team in.
How long will that take?
Two hours, maybe more.
That's sunup.
Damn.
We need to narrow the search area.
Otherwise, we just wait for daylight.
I don't think
they've got that much time.
[ Phone ringing ]
Cantrell.
Has it been a productive morning?
Very productive.
Tell the buyers we're on our way.
They're very anxious
to get down to business.
- [ Alarm sounding ]
- Goddamn it.
- [ Alarm continues ]
- What's the problem?
- We're blown.
- [ Alarm continues ]
[ Alarm continues ]
"Iverson mountain village."
God!
Shut up and drive!
What the hell's going on?
Go! Move!
We're east of Benedict canyon.
Bring in the helicopters.
"Helicopters"?
[ Horns honking ]
[ Yells ]
[ Helicopters whirring
overhead ]
- Damn it.
- She was our only hope.
Now what are we gonna do?
What's that?
It's her cell phone.
I think she was talking to
cantrell aboard a salvage ship.
If we follow the satellite downlink,
we might be able to pinpoint...
The location
of that plane.
I need a schematic and diagram
for a boeing 747.
You think you can do that?
What for?
I'm going swimming.
- Everything okay?
- Okay.
For a while back there, I thought
you were gonna kill me too, cort.
No, we need you to push the
buttons to impress the buyers.
Yeah, we'll kill you later
after the check clears.
- Want to get the door?
- Not a problem.
[ Judy gasping ]
We're almost there.
Hold on.
Here we go.
I got her.
I want to be near Jim.
Here you go.
[ Tiffany ]
Try and relax.
[ Panting ]
[ Exhales deeply ]
Where's miss Campbell?
How's Judy?
You can ask her yourself.
She's right there.
Hey, Jim.
I don't know about you,
but I feel great.
It's just a matter of time until
they spot that signal beacon.
Then we'll get
your cute butt out of here.
We didn't fire the beacon.
I think Layton did something to it.
It wasn't working.
- He asked me not to tell anybody.
- [ Buck ] You lied?
- Hell, we're dead.
- He told me not to worry the passengers.
- "Worry"?
- [ Kevin ] Wait.
- Does the cockpit still have power?
- I think so.
Can you show me?
I'll be back.
All right. Good.
[ Groans ]
This way, Kevin.
Watch your step.
This wasn't on the itinerary, boss.
How come?
Well, if I let you
know everything,
it makes me a pretty dull boy.
[ Laughs ]
You hanging in there?
Yeah. You?
Yeah.
Thanks.
That helps.
[ Rotors whirring ]
Give me an update, Nick.
Tell me you got a fix
on that plane.
No, I do not, sir.
Damn it.
[ Sighs ]
Take it around again.
It's not that one.
[ Cindy ]
I think they're contractions.
No, it's too early.
I'm only seven months.
It can't be.
[ Gasps, groans ]
Oh. Oh.
[ Sighs ]
Okay.
- Now tell me the truth.
- I-I need to check on Kevin.
Can you hang on
just a little bit?
I'll come back, and I'll do a quick exam.
Cindy...
You're a bad liar.
Is she
in premature labor?
[ Softly ]
I think so.
God help us, I think so.
[ Sighs ]
- Did you fix it?
- Yeah. He just disabled a switch.
- What was that?
- It could be the beacon. Maybe they fixed it.
- That's it.
- [ Kevin ] There it goes.
It's on its way.
Let's go.
- We released it.
- All right!
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah.
But we don't know
if it's going to work.
I put good money into that.
It damn well better work.
Anything you say, buck.
[ Helicopter rotors whirring ]
Come on.
Where the hell are you?
Sir, I'm picking up
an emergency beacon.
Hallelujah.
Where the hell you been?
Take her down
for a closer look!
- Let's go!
- [ Pilot ] Roger that, sir.
Captain masters,
we've located the aircraft.
Good work, Nick. Roger that, sir.
Thank you.
How much oxygen
have we got left?
The residual power in the main
cells gives us maybe two hours.
Is that enough time
for a rescue?
I sure hope so, buck.
[ Wendy ]
I'll be damned.
Owen cantrell.
And how the hell
is she still alive?
[ Indistinct ]
[ Sighs ]
Son of a bitch.
[ Scoffs ]
Welcome aboard, Mr. Taylor.
Did you get any sleep on that plane?
You look like you could use a good cup of coffee.
No, thank you.
I spent the flight
going over those 747 specs.
I've been up for 24 hours; About the same
amount of time as those people in that plane.
This is lieutenant Nick Stuart with the seals.
He'll lead the dive team.
Let's get started.
We've located the plane on a ledge
about three nautical miles from here.
Depth:
About 100 feet.
How do we get them out?
We were going to use a d.S.V.
Mini sub to pull them out,
but our engineers tell us a 747's outer
skin is too soft to give us a good seal.
We're going to have
to swim them out.
"Swim them out"?
- We're at the drop point.
- All right! Let's go!
Jump!
[ Pilot ]
Taylor, Stuart and winslow
are in the water, sir.
Mission is underway and all systems
are go for underwater retrieval.
This is rescue one terminating
recon and returning to base.
Very well.
We'll wait
till we hear from them.
[ Hangs up receiver, sighs ]
This is where
it's coming from.
It's very cold.
What?
What's this come from?
- What the hell does that mean?
- It means the compartment's completely flooded.
[ Kevin ]
What's inside?
The air purifier.
Can you get it?
A shark?
There are sharks out there!
That's all we need.
How long
do you think?
Maybe 30, 40 minutes
before the air's toxic.
[ Sighs ]
Divers. Hey! Hey!
[ Knocking ]
Hey!
[ Pounding ]
- Oh!
- That's Judy.
Oh, god!
It hurts!
[ Crying ]
- What is it?
- Her water's broken.
[ Sighs ]
Peel your tanks.
Take them off.
Lieutenant Stuart,
U.S. Navy seals.
Welcome aboard.
You sure are a sight for sore eyes.
- Any injuries or casualties?
- Are you a doctor?
- Yeah.
- We need you up front.
I should have listened to you.
I didn't.
Yeah, I know.
I gotta talk to Jim.
[ Mack ]
What happened?
[ Winslow ]
He's got a bullet in him, but it's not deep.
Someone's dressed this already.
I think he's in shock.
I'm not in shock.
I'm dead.
Go check
on Mrs. Campbell, please.
Hi.
Miss Campbell?
Yeah.
I'm doctor winslow.
How you doing?
I feel like shit, doc.
You're doing great.
How far apart are the contractions?
I don't know.
Five minutes?
About a minute each?
Hey, mack... give me a hand.
[ Groaning ]
Easy.
You all right?
Yeah.
Jim...
What's the situation?
They did it.
Crashed the plane
on purpose.
Got the damn software.
The pilot was in on it.
So was ewing and cort.
Cort?
I thought cort was dead.
Yeah, so did I.
That's what I was told.
- Where are they?
- They left during the night.
They got at least
two hours on you, pal.
Did they say
where they were going?
I guess they're meeting
some buyers, taking some bids.
- They're gonna sell thunderstrike.
- You know it.
You're short on oxygen?
We're open to sea in both cargo bays...
And the main power cells
are flooded.
I'll be back, okay?
Keep breathing.
- Doc.
- Jim's lost some blood.
The crash kicked miss Campbell into early
labor. That baby needs to come out soon.
- Get to it.
- I can't do it here.
We're not far from the first stage
of carbon monoxide poisoning.
- Leave them behind?
- Of course not. But they aren't going to swim out.
Maybe they don't have to swim.
What if we bring the plane up?
We don't have cranes and chains
for this kind of salvage.
You have floatation pontoons,
right? Right?
We just attach them
to key points on the plane,
inflate them,
and the plane goes right up.
And the plane breaks apart
underwater if the balance is off.
Make damn sure
the balance ain't off.
- This is seal team three.
- Go ahead, Nick.
We found
six passengers alive,
- two with serious medical conditions, over.
- [ Masters ] I copy, Nick.
Captain, we have a
problem and a solution.
I don't think you're gonna like either one.
Try me.
All right, agent Robbins.
What's the deal?
My team controls the op.
Simple.
I can't sign off on that
without higher authority.
In this case, I am the higher authority.
I have the address.
Okay.
Okay, you win.
What's your location?
Iverson mountain village.
Okay, let's move the pontoons
on the boats!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
All right, let's
reel it out slow!
Why don't you take your seats?
I'll be right with you.
Okay.
Here, hook it up.
[ Gasping ]
Easy, easy, easy.
- Oh, god!
- [ Whimpering ] You're doing great.
[ Panting ]
You're doing great.
Glad to see
you're dating again.
Yeah, and she's throwing
the kid in for free.
[ Leader ]
Barker, you're on number one.
Thompson, grab number two.
Okay, take it on down!
[ Crying out ]
Breathe, Judy.
Breathe.
I'm right here, Judy.
Jim.
[ Straining ]
You're not breathing.
[ Gasping ]
I love you too.
[ Crewman ]
Pontoons in position to elevate, sir!
Very well.
Let's bring her up!
[ Air hissing ]
[ Continues hissing ]
This will get very rocky.
We'll start to move up fast.
Anybody who can,
get to your seats.
- Push, girl! Push!
- [ Straining ]
[ Gasping ]
- [ Judy panting ]
- [ Pontoon strap groaning ]
[ Stuart ]
Come on, let's get out of here.
[ Crewman ]
She's at 75 feet, sir.
Push now, this is it!
Target sighted.
[ Panting ]
Come on, Judy.
Keep pushing.
[ Yelling ]
Come on. Come on.
[ Screams ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Cindy screaming ]
Everybody hang onto something!
Hang on!
Goddamn it, Taylor, I hope
you know what you're doing.
Target locked!
[ Screaming ]
It's a hit!
[ Crying, gasping ]
[ Winslow ] Great job.
It's a boy.
Great job, Judy.
[ Panting ]
Just get them out
of the water, now!
All right, all right.
Oh, hi.
[ Helicopter rotors whirring ]
Send in the boats!
Damn.
Let me help you.
In.
[ Groans ]
[ Stuart ]
All right, everybody, let's get out of here!
Okay. Shh.
- Hold it together.
- Bring it around!
[ Baby crying ]
Let's go.
Watch the extension.
Next.
Go.
Let's go.
- [ Tiffany screams ]
- [ Stuart ] What are you doing?
[ Tiffany continues screaming ]
Get in the boat.
Get her. Help her.
[ Baby crying ]
You got it, you got it. There you go.
You first, buck.
Get in the boat!
That's an order!
Buck!
Buck! Buck!
Sir.
My regrets for your father.
Welcome aboard.
It's good to be here, sir.
[ Baby fussing ]
Agent carpenter, we need to see
you in the debriefing room.
Right away, sir.
[ Fussing continues ]
[ Carpenter ]
You can only do your best, right?
And you two...
You two are wonderful.
Show him
the way, doc.
Captain, thank you so much
for saving us. Thank you, sir.
My pleasure.
Good work,
Taylor.
Thank you, sir.
- Mother and son are doing just fine.
- How's Jim?
- He'll make it, but another few hours in that plane...
- Yeah... I know.
Hell of a job
you did down there, Taylor.
The lieutenant tells me you did
our seal rescue team credit.
Thank you, captain...
But my job's a long way from being over.
Tiffany...
I'm so sorry.
Why?
I mean, you saved us.
Not everybody.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
You're gonna need this.
It's all the computer codes
to shut thunderstrike down.
Just follow it step-by-step.
Will I need anything else?
Just a lot of luck.
I wonder if you're as good in
bed as you are at the wheel?
Mr. Drago?
Mm-hmm?
Bite me.
[ Cantrell ]
The ultimate weapon
designed by man and god.
It's as if god himself has
provided us with the lenses...
To make thunderstrike
the ultimate weapon.
The beam can vaporize an
entire city within seconds.
This way, gentlemen,
please.
We go around this way.
All right, Taylor,
I control the op.
In your dreams.
Of course you do, Wendy.
We're just here to provide backup.
Let's go.
All right, guys, follow me.
Don't say a word.
[ Equipment beeping ]
The owner of this weapon will control
the world, whether he likes it or not.
And for the right price,
gentlemen, that could be you.
We will expect a demonstration.
Of course. And we expect
to see your credentials.
Now that I would fuck.
Welcome to the wide
world of capitalism.
Let's go.
All clear.
On my way.
[ Gasps, groaning ]
[ Equipment beeping ]
What's the target?
- Does it really matter?
- Trying to pick something close
so you can see the fireball.
It's always the fun part.
[ Continues beeping ]
[ Both grunting ]
[ Groaning ]
Have you ever been
to San reseda?
- No.
- Ooh, pity.
[ Gasps ]
- What's this?
- Owen.
Let's go.
[ Yells ]
Freeze!
You're under arrest.
Owen...
Go get the Van started.
I said don't move.
[ Women grunting ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Continues beeping ]
In there.
What's the status?
[ Continues typing ]
The firing codes are locked
in the hard drive.
But they took the software,
and the satellite will still fire.
Can you shut it down?
I think so.
All I need is time.
[ Continues typing ]
[ Sighs, continues typing ]
[ Mack ]
That's it.
[ Sighs ]
[ Pats shoulder ]
Come on, come on!
[ Starts engine ]
Oh, shit.
What is it?
Why did you stop?
That's it then.
Without a control system, thunderstrike
is just another useless satellite.
Yeah, until somebody
builds another one.
Quite a mess you made here.
Mess I've made?
I think
I had a little help.
This was an a.T.F. Operation.
Remember? Officially, we're
not even supposed to be here.
- You're such a bastard.
- I'm not the bastard.
Mack's the bastard.
I'm just his enabler.
I'll let you two work that out.
That's Mr. Bastard to you.
[ Scoffs ]
Rich and spoiled.
I've been meaning to talk to you about that.
Oh, yeah?
My nanny's got some recipes...