[bright music]
[light orchestral music]
[children giggling]
[brakes screeching]
[glass shattering]
[people screaming]
[sirens wailing]
[car horns honking]
- Could you spare some
money for the tooth fairy?
Well thank you, thank you
so much, you're so sweet.
Hello there, I know
what you're thinking.
You think I'm gonna
ask you for money
and well I am,
but it's not for what you think.
You see, I am the tooth fairy
and I need your spare change
to give to the deserving
children of the neighborhood.
- Sh.
- No?
Well, hello, do you
have any spare change
for the tooth fairy?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Oh jeez.
- Yo, Briefcase.
Spare some change for Santa's
hippest helper? [laughing]
Gotta give back to the North
Pole before the big day.
- You still going
with the elf bit?
- Well Christmas is
only a few months away.
Any brother or sister
with holiday cheer
be giving their change to me.
Check out my new elf dance.
- Oh yeah.
Whoa, whoa big fella.
Originality is what
made this country great.
Remember I said that.
- [Muskat] I'll write it down.
- You better.
Could you spare some change
for the tooth fairy fund?
[air whooshing]
Oh excuse me.
Home sweet home, yes sir.
[groans] Oh, that's
getting pretty ripe.
Where's my girls?
Hey, girls where you gone?
Ah, here's my girls.
Yeah, here's my girls.
Hi girls.
Me?
I had a pretty good day.
Yeah, everybody at the
office says hi. [chuckles]
[gentle music]
[girl laughing]
[Briefcase sobbing]
There's my love.
[upbeat music]
Oh hey little girl, hello, hi,
I'd like to introduce myself.
My name is Briefcase
and I am a tooth fairy.
- So, why do they
call you Briefcase?
- Well 'cause when
I first moved here
I used to carry a briefcase.
What's your name?
- Mary Elizabeth, but
no one calls me that
except my mother.
Everybody calls me Lizbeth.
- Well, it's nice to
meet you, Lizbeth.
- Well, bye.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey,
Lizbeth, Lizbeth,
did you happen to lose a tooth?
- Sure, lots of times.
- [Briefcase] And didn't the
tooth fairy give you money?
- No.
- No?
Oh well that must have been
before I was the tooth fairy
in this territory.
I guarantee that the next
time that you lose a tooth,
the tooth fairy is
gonna give you money,
how's that sound?
- Well I won't hold my breath.
- Hey, hey, you know,
you're about the oldest
little girl I ever met.
Who told you not believe
in the tooth fairy?
- Too old to believe
in stuff like that.
- No, you ain't never too old
to believe in stuff like that.
- My mum said you people who ask
for change in streets are
winos and no-account drunks.
- Oh, well your mum is right,
but you know, sometimes people
can be two things at once.
Take me for example,
I am a wino, but I'm
also the tooth fairy.
Hey, look at this.
Last night I had to visit a
little girl just like you.
I went into her house
and I found that
and I put some money
under her pillow.
See, see, that's how it works.
- You could have
gotten that anywhere.
- Well of course I could.
You kids lose your teeth
everywhere you know,
but I gotta find
'em just the same.
You know, sometimes it takes
me a couple of extra days
but I always get there.
You just have to have faith.
You know what faith is?
- Yeah, it's what you
need to believe in stuff,
like God, even though
you never see Him.
Bad things always happen.
- Well yeah, I mean I guess
that's one way to define it,
but I mean it's
a bad way for you
because, you know,
you're so young and all.
- Ho, ho, ho.
- Give it a rest
will ya, Muskat?
See, faith is like that Lizbeth,
but if you lose your
faith in everything,
like God and the
tooth fairy, well,
then you're gonna
be sad all the time.
You don't wanna be sad
all the time do ya?
- No.
My mommy said it's not nice
for little girls to cry.
- Well your mom is
certainly right about that.
Especially on airplanes.
Never, ever cry on airplanes.
- Mary Elizabeth, get
over here right now!
What are you doing?
- [Lizbeth] I have
to go now, bye.
- Bye.
Boy, that is one
mixed up little girl.
Could you imagine her not
having faith in God or anything?
- You don't.
- We are talking about
the little girl, Muskat.
- Two, I thought it was four.
Oh man.
[door thuds]
Mary Elizabeth, is that you?
I have a surprise.
- It's just me, baby. [laughs]
What are you up to?
- What are you up to?
- Nothing, just calm down, baby.
- Don't you baby me.
I don't want that in the house.
Mary Elizabeth is
gonna be home soon.
She could find it.
- Will you be cool,
I'm gonna hide it in a place
where she'll never find it.
- I want you and that
thing out of my house.
[dramatic music]
- [sighs] Home sweet...
[somber music]
Oh no.
Oh no, no.
Baby, baby [sobbing].
No, no, please, no!
I got you, I got you.
[Briefcase sobbing]
- Ho, ho, ho.
Ho, ho, ho.
- Briefcase, Briefcase.
My friend Resa said she got
visited by the tooth fairy.
- Yeah, well look kid, you know,
now is not a really good time.
- Did you really give her
that 10 bucks for her tooth?
- [snickers] 10 bucks, $10,
yeah, sure, I mean
yeah, you know I mean,
she's a good kid you know
and she went through
a lot of pain,
so she gets the big bucks.
- Resa thinks it was her father
who put the $10
under her pillow.
- Well, you know, usually I
let the daddy do the leg work.
See, that way the
dad and the kid,
they get some quality
time together.
Any more questions
before you go?
- What if you
don't have a daddy?
- Oh.
Well, well, then I guess I
have to do that by myself.
You know, with my tooth
fairy magic. [laughs]
- [Lizbeth] Really?
- Yeah.
[Muskat laughing]
What?
- Yeah B, why don't you show us
a little of your
tooth fairy magic?
- Well you know I'm still
trying to recharge myself
from last night,
but I'm sure I can
muster up a little power,
you know what I'm saying?
- Can you?
- Give me a quarter.
- What?
[bright music]
There's your magic trick.
Ready?
Watching, ready, watch closely.
[breath blowing]
[Briefcase laughing]
- You really must
be the tooth fairy.
- See now you're getting it.
- Oh yeah, now I'm
Santa's helper.
- There is no Santa Claus.
- [Briefcase] Sure there is.
Well did your mom tell you that?
- No, it's just he
didn't come last year
or the year before that.
So what good is he?
- Well you know, Santa's
had a couple of problems
over the last couple
of Christmases,
you know I mean, last year,
last year he had that
reindeer, broke a hoof,
you know and then
they had to shoot him
in the head over Greenland.
- Santa shoots his reindeer?
- Oh no, no, no,
not Santa, no, no,
it was this mean dwarf.
- Elf.
- Elf, yeah, it was a mean elf.
Yeah.
- Stinky.
- Yeah, Stinky,
Stinky the Elf, yeah.
- I don't like Stinky the Elf.
- So, Lizbeth, come sit down.
You know being a tooth
fairy in this area,
you know I was
looking in my records
and well I noticed that well,
that you haven't put any money
into the tooth fairy fund.
- The tooth fairy fund?
- Well yeah you see,
well Santa Claus,
he works pro bono,
that means for free,
but the tooth fairy you see,
they can only operate
if you put money
into the tooth fairy fund.
- Oh man.
- Hey hey, those
aren't my rules.
Right, it's the head
tooth fairy's rules
and you know, I'm
telling you, Lizbeth,
he is a hard case.
- Is he part wino too?
- No, no, no, no.
To be head tooth fairy you
gotta be all tooth fairy.
I mean and some day I might
become head tooth fairy,
but now I gotta follow the rules
and what, what was
your friend's name?
- Resa.
- Resa, well see Resa
looking at my records,
I saw that Resa had
already put money in.
See, being a member of
the tooth fairy fund,
well it's like being
in social security.
You gotta put money in before
you can take money out.
- Hatcha matcha.
- Put in?
- Put that money in.
Before you can get any out.
You understand?
[Muskat laughing]
- And then Briefcase,
he tells her
that the tooth fairy operates
the same way as social security.
You gotta put money
in to take some out.
- I had the heebie jeebies,
you know, you guys
know, I'm sweating it.
I'm itching and stuff.
- And then this little girl,
I mean the sweetest little
girl you ever wanted to see,
she looks up at
him and she says,
"I wanna put in to
the tooth fairy fund.
"Will you take these
cans?" [laughing]
- All right, all right, that's
enough I say, enough, enough!
- [Muskat] You're
the king, Briefcase.
You are the freakin' tooth
fairy king. [guffaws]
See, he knows how to deal with
them kids, 'cause he had one.
- Hey, hey, hey you would
have done the same thing.
The same [gasping]
- [Man] Briefcase you all right?
- Jimmy, Jimmy, help me.
- Briefcase, Briefcase.
[somber music]
[monitor beeping]
[Briefcase snores]
[Briefcase gasping]
- Hey, hey, take it easy now.
- I'm not dead?
- Take it easy, go slow.
- Oh, Preacher. [sighs]
Oh, don't tell me I'm in
that lousy clinic of yours.
- The very same.
- [sighs] Any port
in a storm I guess.
- You're lucky to be alive.
- Yeah, maybe I should
buy a lottery ticket.
Couldn't hurt, right.
- I'm gonna read this to you.
Myocardial infarction,
that's a heart attack.
Based on your echo cardiogram,
your heart's in
pretty dismal shape
and your liver enzymes are high.
So on the verge of failure.
- What are you a doctor now?
- It doesn't take a doctor
to see what a mess you're in.
- I did see a white light.
No, no, that was Sinatra
singing at the Sands.
No, no, maybe that
was just a paramedic
shocking me back to
life, huh? [laughs]
- You know the lack of
oxygen to your brain
has not affected your sarcasm.
What it is with you Briefcase,
how can you be so smart
and not see how bad
your situation is?
- I guess it's the same way
you call shrimp jumbo. [laughs]
- I don't know how
to tell you this.
But in Dr. Thompson's opinion,
you only have a year to live,
two at the most if you're lucky.
- Is that a joke?
'Cause if you're joking,
you better work on your
bedside manner, Preacher.
Are you joking or are you
just trying to trick me?
- We're not the Mayo
Clinic, we could be wrong.
Maybe you'll live 10 years
if you just take
care of yourself.
- Or I could die next week,
is that what you're sayin'?
That I'm gonna die,
I'm gonna die alone
in a filthy gutter?
- I mean how could
you expect to live
the way you were living,
and not have a bad--
- I don't need you
preaching at me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but
what I meant was, this is a
lot to take in in five minutes.
I just wanna be alone.
[gentle music]
- Stay as long as you like.
[monitor beeping]
[traffic whooshing]
[chips crunching]
- [Clerk] Rummie,
how you doing today?
- Can't believe it, it's
like I'm on autopilot.
- You know I was just reading
about you in the newspaper.
Did you know that 10%
of the boozers out there
account for 99% of
all the alcohol sales.
- You're full of all sorts of
fun facts today, aren't ya?
- [Clerk] Hey, if it wasn't for
you, I'd be out of business.
What'll it be today?
- Is this stuff supposed
to be good for ya?
- Well it's the healthiest
of the jerky family.
99% fat free.
But Olympians don't train on it.
- Well, I'll take one.
- And?
- And, hey two years
is a long time,
wouldn't you say?
- [laughs] Yeah, especially
if somebody is poking ya
in the butt with a sharp stick.
[both laughing]
- Yeah, ah heck, give
me a pint of penicillin.
- Huh?
- Vodka.
- Oh, okay, yeah.
- Hey, how much is this?
- Not enough, you don't
have enough money.
- Make it a half pint then.
- There is nothing
in there to drink.
- Yeah, I know.
- [Clerk] It's a pinwheel.
- I know, I want it anyway.
- You can't drink this.
- Hey, look what is this?
Can't a guy buy a pinwheel?
- I'm willing to go along
with you on the jerky thing,
'cause a man's gotta eat.
But the rest of the
10% of the boozers
are gonna be very
disappointed in you, Rummie.
You're not maximizing your
alcohol purchase here.
- Look, just ring me up.
- Okay.
Change.
- Thanks a lot.
- Briefcase, I'm
telling you, [laughs]
you really scared me there.
- Who needs extreme sports
when we got extreme living.
- Yeah, [chuckles] so, you
gonna do anything different?
- I don't think so,
I don't know, maybe.
- Well that was quick.
[bright music]
Hey, here comes your little
ray of sunshine. [chuckles]
You know, she looks kinda irate,
I'll see you back in a bit.
- Yeah.
- Resa said she didn't put money
into the tooth fairy fund.
And neither did her father.
- Well, I never
tell the daddies.
You know, daddies have to sign
a confidentiality agreement.
Hey, come on up here and
sit with me, come on.
Now, I was looking
in my records,
and well I noticed that
you're owed some back gifts
from both Santa and
the tooth fairy.
So, here we go,
nothing up my sleeves.
A little tooth fairy magic.
Then, surprise.
[Briefcase laughs]
It's a pinwheel.
- Well, what does it do?
- Well you know, you
run along with it
and the wind blows through
it and it spins around.
- It looks kinda lame to me.
- Oh.
Well, well, you know
Santa always gives
the lamest back presents first,
but you know, they get better.
Here, why don't
you give it a try.
[bright music]
Well, get up and
move around with it.
Yeah.
Back and forth.
Here, you know, let me
show you, let me show you.
- Like that.
- Yeah, hold it out like that
and let it catch
the wind, there.
Try running with it, see
what what happens, yeah.
Run, run, run.
Run, run with it, yeah.
Look at it spinning,
huh? [chuckles]
Lizbeth?
Lizbeth, Lizbeth?
[Lizbeth sobbing]
You're not supposed
to fall with it,
you're supposed to run with it.
Don't cry, don't cry.
Remember little girls
who cry aren't pretty.
Think of happy things
like puppy dogs
and dollies and stuff like that.
What?
- Look at this.
- Well, that's great.
Now the tooth fairy's
gonna give ya--
- And Resa only got $10 dollars
and I went through more
pain than her, huh?
- Well.
- Good thing I just to put money
into the tooth fairy fund, huh?
- Well, that's
always a good thing.
- What was that thing,
you know that thing
that I have to do before I
get my tooth fairy money?
- Be fully vested.
- Fully vested, well I am.
[Briefcase chuckles]
Are you still the tooth fairy
or are you gonna
change your story now?
- Lizbeth, I am the tooth fairy.
- Okay then, this will
be waiting for you
under my pillow.
Bye, Briefcase.
- [groans] $10.
[bright upbeat music]
- Yeah, here you go.
- No, sorry.
- [Man] Here.
- [Woman] Get away.
- [Man] I don't have anything.
- [Man] No, no.
- No, no, stop,
sorry, sorry, don't.
- [Clerk] Get outta here.
- Hey, hey, hey.
$11.
I need 11 one dollar bills.
- That's some real money there.
Special occasion, birthday?
- [Briefcase] $11, please.
- Yeah, I heard you the first
time, now what do you want?
Man could have himself a
real party on $11, Rummie.
- No, I didn't come in for that,
you know, I gotta
do something else.
I just want 11
bills for my change.
- Look, this ain't
Bank of America,
you gotta buy something.
- Look, I just need the
money, okay, please.
- How about this bottle of rum?
Ronrico, huh.
$15 marked down to 9.95.
I drink this stuff.
- [Briefcase] No, no.
Here, I'll take this gum.
- I can tell you really
got something going there.
Sure that's $11.
- Yeah, man, I'm sure, I'm sure.
- All right, one, two, three.
[horns honking]
- Oh, Lizbeth, Lizbeth.
[gasps] There you are. [laughs]
And here you are, from
the tooth fairy to you.
It's yours and then we're done.
- That's not the way
the tooth fairy does it.
- Look kid I gotta get a,
I got bigger things
to worry about.
- The tooth fairy puts
money under the pillow.
- Well, that's the way the
tooth fairy used to do it,
but now we do all sorts
of different things,
like sometimes we wire the money
right into your bank account,
but since you don't
have a bank account,
you don't have a
bank account do ya?
- No.
- No, well then we
do it like this.
Go on, take it.
- Yeah, but I didn't
even give you my tooth.
- Well, you can owe it to me.
- If you're the tooth fairy,
you put money under my
pillow where my tooth is.
- [groans] Nothing's
gonna be easy is it?
I suppose it's all my fault.
Another big joke at my expense.
Okay, okay, fine, we'll
do it the old way.
The old out of date,
the old I'll put it under
the pillow way, okay.
Fine, all right,
then you'll have
to believe in the tooth
fairy and Santa, and God
and you'll have to have a
little faith then, right?
Okay then, just a little
bit of faith, okay?
Okay.
- Okay.
- It's settled,
where do you live?
- What?
- Where do you live?
- You don't know?
- Well I, I, you live here.
- [Lizbeth] Which apartment?
- Which apartment?
Well I, I've got
that written down
in my tooth fairy records.
You know, Lizbeth,
I can't be expected
to remember everything. [laughs]
- [Cyril] Is there
a problem here?
- Hey just buzz off..
Oh, no, no, no, no, no problem.
No problem at all.
[somber music]
[wagon rattling]
[cans clunking]
[gentle music]
[Muskat snoring]
[Muskat groaning]
- What happened?
- A flash flood,
now wake up,
I told you what I wanted
to do, do you remember?
I told you this afternoon.
- Yeah, yeah I remember.
You said,
oh no, no, no, are you crazy?
Briefcase!
Do you know what will happen
if the police catch you sneaking
into some little girl's window
to put money under her pillow?
- You make it sound sick.
- Oh boy, just go on and
give the girl the money.
It's a good thing
you're doing, Briefcase,
what does it matter if she
believes your hatchy matchy,
you hate it when the
preacher does that.
- Yeah, when he does it
that's totally different.
I mean, when he's
doing, he's trying,
you see what I'm
trying to do is...
Nevermind the freakin'
logic of the situation,
that little girl needs
to believe in stuff
like the tooth fairies
actually exist.
- Oh boy, you better
get home, let me sleep.
- [Briefcase] Don't make
me fill up this bottle.
- Okay, I'm up.
- [Briefcase] All right come on.
- I'm up.
- [Muskat] Get up.
- Shoes on.
- Come on!
- All right,
all right, all right.
- [Briefcase] Got it?
- [Muskat] Oh man you have
really let yourself go.
- Okay.
- I'm just saying,
maybe light beer from now on.
- [Briefcase] You're
buying the beer.
You wait for me here.
Wait.
- All right.
I'll wait, I'll wait.
[dogs distant barking]
[crickets chirping]
[window clicking]
[window scraping]
[suspenseful music]
[toe thuds]
- Sh.
[distant TV chattering]
[door creaking]
[envelope rustling]
[clock ticking]
[door creaking]
[distant TV chattering]
- He said wait, I'm gonna wait.
He's my buddy so I'm gonna wait.
Wish I had a watch.
Okay, okay, okay.
[TV chattering]
[door clicking]
[toy squeaks]
[upbeat music]
[door creaking]
[Briefcase groaning]
We gotta go, we gotta go.
- [Briefcase] You
got me, catch me.
[body thudding]
- [Muskat] No wait,
let's go, come on.
- [Briefcase] I thought
you were gonna catch me.
- [Muskat] I thought
you was gonna wait.
- Wow.
[both panting]
$11, I got more than Resa, yes.
[both laughing]
- Oh man, I would
have peed my pants
if I'd seen Cyril
standing there.
Ooh very scary. [laughs]
[wagon rattling]
- [Lizbeth] It's true, what
you said is really true.
- [laughs] Oh course it is.
- I can't wait to tell
all my friends and mommy.
- Well no, that's
not the best idea.
You know a better idea
would be to keep it
a secret, all right.
Especially from mommy and well,
whoever else she talks to.
- Why?
- Well, see we tooth fairies
we act like a secret club,
you know, and
without our secrets,
well, we couldn't do
our job half as well.
Because, you know, and
then all the people
would know are
aforementioned secrets.
So, you think you can
keep all this a secret?
- Well yeah, I think so,
but I have to tell Resa,
'cause she only got $10.
- [Briefcase] Well,
okay you can tell Resa,
but that's it, all right.
Now, look I wanna talk to you
about something
really important.
- I can't right now, I
gotta go home for dinner.
Mom gets mad if I'm late.
- [Briefcase] Yeah, but
it'll just take two seconds.
- [Lizbeth] Later, then I'll
show you my secret hideout.
- Ah yeah [sighs].
[sirens wailing]
Oh jeez, couldn't
your secret place
be a little easier to get to?
- Well, then everyone
would be here.
- Yeah, well, yeah
I guess overcrowding
could ruin a place
like this. [groaning]
Hey, isn't kind of
late for you to be out,
especially on a school night.
- Yeah, but my
homework's all done.
- What about your mom,
won't she be worried?
- She's gonna be
at Cyril's tonight.
- Oh, you know,
speaking of Cyril.
I saw you yesterday doing,
doing what you might
call an errand for him.
- [Lizbeth] He gives me
money to run errands.
- You know, Lizbeth, those
errands aren't really good.
- I know but mommy
and I need the money.
- Mommy and you need the money.
- [Lizbeth] Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, there it is. [laughs]
- Briefcase.
- Lizbeth, slow down.
I told you you shouldn't
be running like that.
- [laughing]
Especially in airports.
Ever.
- I have to tell my mommy about
you being the tooth fairy.
- Oh, no, no, no, no,
remember what we talked about?
Remember what I said?
It's best that mommy--
- And her boyfriends.
- That's right, they
don't know our...
- Yes, yes.
- My true identity, right?
We talked about this.
- I know but today
I was telling Gina,
that's Resa's friend,
about you being the
tooth fairy and a wino
and they didn't believe me.
- Oh he's gonna find out.
He can't find out, you
know who I'm talking about.
He cannot find out.
- Then what happened?
- And then I told them about
how I got into the system
by putting money into
the tooth fairy fund,
but they didn't
believe that either.
- Well you know, Lizbeth,
some kids are like that,
you know I mean, well in
the tooth fairy business
we call those kids--
- Idiots.
- We call those
kids idiots, yeah.
You know, so what's
the problem, huh?
- Then when she said that
you were a dirty old wino,
and not the tooth fairy I hit
her, pow, right in the nose.
[Briefcase laughs]
- You did that for me?
- Yeah, but then she told
our teacher, Mr. Rady,
who told our
Principal Miss Blake,
and now I have to get my
mom to come to school.
- Oh, this is not good.
This isn't even related to good.
- Never been in
trouble before, never.
- I got it, I got it.
Just don't tell
your mom anything.
- Now Principal Blake
says I have to get my mom
to come tomorrow
at school at noon,
otherwise I'll be suspended.
- Well there you go, being
suspended is like, well,
it's like being on vacation.
- No.
- No?
- Hey, hey, hey, how
about if your granddaddy
goes to school
instead of your mommy?
- My granddaddy?
- Yeah, your Granddaddy yeah.
- Oh.
- Oh, yes.
- Oh no way, no way.
No, you can't be serious.
No, I can't be a granddaddy.
- [Principal] This
is your first time
at our school, isn't it?
- Yes, my work keeps me from
doing this sort of stuff.
- What type of work is that?
- I was an, I am an accountant.
- I looked into Mary
Elizabeth's records
and your name's not listed
as a member of the family.
Is it our mistake?
- Oh no, no, she's my
step granddaughter.
My first wife and child died.
- I'm terribly sorry.
But now to the matter at hand.
You see this type of
behavior is inappropriate.
Mary Elizabeth just can't
be punching her classmates.
- Oh, I promise, it'll
never happen again.
You can count on
Elizabeth and me.
- Excuse me, I'm so
sorry that I'm late.
- I'm in the middle of
a meeting, who are you?
- Well I'm Mary Elizabeth's
mother, Shari Jackson.
- Welcome, sit down.
I was just talking
with your father.
Or is it your husband's father?
- My who?
[door thudding]
I don't ever wanna see you
around my daughter
again, you got that?
- Look, Lizbeth
asked me to do this
'cause she thought
you'd overreact
to her getting in trouble
and I'm afraid I
gotta side with her.
- Overreact?
You are a dirty, stinky wino
and if you ever come
near my daughter again,
I'll call the cops.
[somber music]
You are a dirty, stinky wino.
♪ Sweet as honey on the band
You know, you have
very nice hair.
Very manageable.
I wish I had hair like this.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah,
are you sure you know
what you're doing?
- I told you my daddy
was a barber. [laughs]
- Well, you--
- Quit fidgeting.
I'll cut off your ear
and feed it to Mugsey.
- [Briefcase] What?
- [Muskat] My daddy
used to say that
to kids when they fidgeted.
Mugsey was our bulldog.
- Oh, thanks for that lovely
trip down memory lane.
[broom whooshing]
Excuse me.
- [Clerk] I don't give handouts.
- I wasn't looking
for one today,
I notice you have a help
wanted sign in your window.
- I've had to ask you to
leave this area before,
do you remember?
- No, sir, I sure don't.
- [Clerk] You
accosted my customers
as they entered and
exited my store.
Drunk out of your mind you were.
- I am, I'm sorry about that.
- And now you're
looking for work?
- Yes, sir, yes, I am.
- [Clerk] And you've
decided to stop drinking?
- Well, during work
hours at least.
- I won't use
anyone who's drunk.
I won't abide it.
- I understand.
- I pay minimum
wage off the books.
I don't need you full
time, only part time.
You get paid for
hours you work only.
You get paid on Fridays only.
No advances, ever.
How's that sound?
- That sounds great.
- When you're finished here
I have some boxes
that need throwing out
and some crates that
need throwing away.
- Yes sir, I'll get
right on it, sir.
Thank you, sir, I
won't let you down.
[bright music]
[traffic whooshing]
- Man, this junk is heavy.
- This is not junk, Muskat,
this is the shattered
remnants of my life
and I'll ask you to
show some respect.
- Exactly why are we doing this?
- 'Cause I don't wanna
die in the gutter.
- What's wrong with the gutter.
- [scoffs] All right if you
look at it a different way,
it's a surprise.
- Yeah you better be
surprising me with a beer soon.
Cold too.
- [Briefcase] Oh just
come on, come on.
- I'm coming I'm
just telling ya.
You know.
- [Briefcase] Oh you're
worse than an old woman.
- Well this old
woman wants a beer.
[upbeat music]
[both coughing]
Man, what is that smell?
- Disinfectant. [sniffs]
[Briefcase coughs]
What, that's working.
[Muskat laughing]
- You pay extra for the view?
- It was either that or some
fat guy aerobicizing all day.
[Muskat chuckles]
- Man, oh man. [laughs]
So, this is your place.
- Yeah.
[both laughing]
What?
- You gotta place!
- I got a place.
[both laughing]
[gentle music]
Hey girls, I got ya a new frame.
Yeah.
Got my own place now.
Clean everything up, got a
job too, did you know that?
Yeah.
Working at a grocery store.
That looks great.
Put you right here.
Right there, huh.
What do you think?
Pretty nice place, huh?
I'll fix it up, I'll fix up.
There's my girls.
Yep, job,
new place.
Sure miss ya though.
How's school going?
You haven't punched anybody
in the nose again have ya?
- Whatever.
- Oh okay, how about this?
If you bring home a
straight A report card.
- [Lizbeth] What's a straight A?
- It's a grade.
It's the highest
grade you can get.
- It's not our highest grade.
- Well what's your
highest grade?
- An exceeds expectations.
- Exceeds expectations?
That's the silliest
thing I ever heard of.
Okay, okay fine.
If you bring home an all
exceeds expectations,
I will take you camping.
- Really, cross your
heart and hope to die?
- Yeah, cross my
heart and, yeah.
So, you sure your
mom's not gonna
come looking for you tonight?
- No.
- [Briefcase] What, is she
staying over at Cyril's?
- No, she's using the
word processor at work.
'Cause the IRS sent us a
letter wanting money from us
and she thinks they're
all full of crap.
- You know, you
shouldn't talk like that.
- To who?
- To me.
'Cause it's not nice.
So your mom has
tax problems huh?
- Yeah.
- [Briefcase] I can fix that.
[doorbell buzzing]
- [Shari] Yes.
- Hi, Briefcase.
- Hey.
- You.
What are you doing here?
- Charles Herschler,
ma'am, accountant.
- For what, the
trees in the park?
- Well, before I came
to your attention
as a bum, I was a
CPA for 13 years.
- Look, I told--
- Elizabeth tells me
that you're being asked
to pay money that you
don't think you owe.
- Elizabeth.
- [Briefcase] What, no,
no, no, it's not her fault.
- I know it's not her fault.
And why are you still here?
- I'm just trying to help.
- Who asked you?
I'm gonna call the police.
- Look, lady.
You're being stubborn.
You have a tax problem and I'm
telling you, I can solve it.
All right, or, or perhaps
I'm just blocking your door
from all the tax accountants
that are rushing to help you.
Ha, no, no, don't
see anybody, just me.
- [Shari] I'm gonna
call the police.
- Look, I can help ya, so
what do you got to lose?
- Please, Mommy, he can do it.
[gentle music]
Please, Mommy.
Please, please, Mom.
- Okay.
- Yes.
You guys hold hands on
your way to school okay.
- Bye.
- I'll be by to
pick you up after.
- Bye Briefcase.
- Bye, bye, Michael.
- [Shari] Would you
like something to drink?
I mean, coffee.
- Yeah, sure, I'd love some.
When did they come
to you with this?
- I don't know,
like six months ago.
- What have you been
doing since then?
What I meant was, usually
people like to get
this stuff over with.
- I work full time and
I kept putting it off
because the people there made
me feel stupid when I called.
- Well, they are a bunch
of self important jerks.
At least I know
I was. [chuckles]
- So why did you
quit accounting?
- I need to look at this.
You know, it seems
they sent you a bill
based on the interest income
and yeah, then they
charged you double for it.
But you know, that's okay,
as long as you paid the
original interest income,
we can just get a
statement from the bank.
- I mean I paid
it, it's just that
that savings and loan
has gone out of business.
- Okay, well then
we'll just file a 604B
and a 5204 addendum
and I'll type up
a piece of paper
explaining all that.
- And you know how
to do all of that?
- Sure, there's a guy in my
building with a typewriter,
so I'll work on it this weekend
and then on Monday I'll go
with you to the IRS office.
You know, it's best to take
care of these things in person
before they snowball.
- Why would you do that?
- Because Elizabeth's my friend.
- [Cyril] How you
doin' today, Briefcase?
- I'm sorry, young man.
Do I know you?
- I think you know
who I am, old man.
Shari just called me
and was all excited
about her new fairy
godfather, Briefcase the wino.
Lizbeth was real excited too.
- You don't say.
- You disrespecting me?
Book I read on leadership says
I gotta come down on that, hard.
Or the disrespect might
spread to my other employees.
- Hey, Cyril, Sebastian.
How are you both doing?
- Preacher, isn't it
a little dangerous
to be walking in
this neighborhood?
- Nah, there's a couple
of narkies down there
on the corner sniffling around
trying to bust somebody
so things are pretty
safe right now.
- [Briefcase] Bye, Sebastian.
- Hey you know--
- No, no, no talking,
no preaching, thanks.
I gotta go, I gotta go.
- That was so easy.
- Well the trick is to
speak their language
and to go in before lunch.
If they think they're
gonna miss lunch,
they become very helpful.
- I'm almost embarrassed
to mention this
but I promised Mary Elizabeth.
- Oh did Elizabeth
get her report card?
And did she get all
exceeds expectations?
- Yeah.
She told me that you
wanted to take us camping.
- Yeah, I'd like that.
- Why?
- Well it'd be nice to get out
of the city for a few days,
don't you think?
And there's something
about Elizabeth.
The way she asks me
questions all the time
and the way she makes me
smile, kinda reminds me of...
I know, I know it sounds kind
of weird if you look at it
the wrong way, but it's
nothing like that, I swear.
- I wasn't thinking that.
- Yes, you were.
- Okay well I
wasn't thinking that
for the last couple of days.
I mean, since I've gotten to
know you a little bit better.
- That's a start.
So let me take you
camping, it'll be fun.
I know this really nice place.
I haven't been there in
a long, long time, but,
so what do you say?
[doorbell buzzing]
Hey it's camping day.
Wait 'til you see what
I've put together.
We can spend forever
underneath those stars.
- I can't go.
- What do you mean you can't go?
- She means she
can't go, old man.
She has more important
things to do tomorrow,
don't you, Lizbeth?
- But I've been planning this.
- You've been planning what?
- [Briefcase] Well, Lizbeth,
I mean, she wanted I, I--
- She's just a kid.
She doesn't know what she
wants or what's good for her.
- I guess you're right.
- Cyril, your dinner's ready.
- Dinner, okay.
- I'm so sorry, Briefcase.
Mary Elizabeth really wants to--
- You're letting her
run an errand for him?
- I have to.
Okay, he'll, nevermind.
- Do you wanna go camping today?
Because if you really wanna
go, you can tell that,
you can tell him that you
have to run an errand.
Right, both you and Lizbeth
and I'll meet you on the corner,
but Shari only if
you really wanna go,
'cause I don't wanna
cause anymore trouble
for you and Elizabeth.
- [Cyril] Shari,
will you get up here.
- Okay.
Okay, I'll meet you
around the corner okay?
Okay.
[upbeat music]
[engine puttering]
- Come on.
- [Shari] Hurry up, go, go, go!
- Inside, here we go.
Up you go, up you go.
Go, go, go!
[truck engine revving]
[upbeat music]
♪ Da, da, da, da, duh, da, da
♪ Duh, da, da, da,
da, da, duh, da ♪
♪ Da, da, da, da, da, duh, da
♪ Duh, duh, da, da,
da, da, da, da ♪
♪ Da, da, da, da
[man scatting]
- [Lizbeth] We're
here, we're here.
- Told you we were
going camping.
Now you guys sit down,
sit down, sit down,
I'm gonna fix everything up,
just sit down and
watch, here we go.
Oh yeah, look at this
we got warm blankets,
warm blankets,
pillows and lemonade.
Look at this, this is just food.
Look at all that food,
and I'm gonna put
the tent right here.
And then I'm gonna,
well I forgot the rope.
I can't, I can't put the
tent up without the rope.
I've forgotten it.
I've forgotten it all.
- [Shari] Why don't we
help while you rest?
- Yeah we wanna
try, let us, please.
- Oh I should have
got a better tent.
Maybe we should just go back.
- No, we don't need a tent.
We could sleep outside,
it won't hurt us.
- Sure, why not, I
mean it's a nice night.
We can just put the
tent out on the ground,
and sleep on it that way
we don't have to worry
about the snakes and the bugs.
- Yeah.
- You really wanna stay?
- Mm-hmm.
- Like you said, it
would be nice to get out
of the city for a few days.
- Okay, then.
Let's set up camp, we'll stay.
- [Girls] Yes.
- I need some help.
- Help up.
- Oh, gosh.
[girls groaning]
♪ Da, da, da, da
- [Briefcase]
Having a good time?
- [Shari] Yeah this is so nice.
- [laughs] You seem surprised.
- [sighs] Maybe I'm
just not used to nice.
- Yeah, you can say that again.
I'm sorry, I'm not
talking about Cyril.
- Cyril is a big baby, okay.
Unless you owe him money,
you have nothing to worry about.
- How can you allow him
to be in the same
house as Elizabeth?
- When I was young
I did some things
that I'm not proud of.
But then I had Mary Elizabeth
and I turned myself around.
I mean, I went back to junior
college and I got a job.
Cyril helped me out then.
I owe him.
But he knows about my past
and he threatens to
tell Mary Elizabeth
every single time that
he gets mad at me.
But only when he's mad.
- He uses Lizbeth
to make drug runs.
- Look, I try my best.
Do you want me to say it?
I'm a bad person, okay.
I'm a bad mom.
- I'm not saying that.
Honest, I mean no
one has a right
to tell somebody how
to run their life,
it's me, I mean, what
am I, I'm a drunk
who pretends to be the
tooth fairy. [laughs]
I'm not trying to make
you feel bad, Shari.
Heck, I'm just thankful
to know you and Lizbeth.
- [Lizbeth] Mommy, Briefcase,
come help me find some crickets.
- [chuckles] Should, you wanna
go get some crickets with us?
- No, nah, I'm exhausted.
I'm gonna have
another marshmallow.
[both laughing]
You go.
[gentle music]
[skateboard whirring]
- That is one
shifty looking kid.
- He was all I could find.
By the way do--
- No one has seen him,
or Shari or Lizbeth.
This isn't gonna turn out well.
- Positive attitude,
positive result, so shut up.
Be cool, be cool.
Jeez, who just ratted on me?
Who?
- Oh, come on now.
- There's a million
kids out on the streets,
why are the cops picking on me?
[dramatic music]
[gentle music]
- Well, looks like
we made it. [laughs]
- [Shari] Home sweet home.
- Yeah.
- I was wrong
about you, Charles.
I'm sorry.
- That's okay.
- So, what are you
doing after this?
- Well, I gotta get the
truck back like I promised.
You know, do the
responsible thing.
And then I guess
I'll just go home.
Hm, home, haven't said that
to anybody in a long time.
Sounds pretty good.
- I meant what are
you doing after this.
- I'm just taking it
one day at a time.
That's all I can do.
- If anybody deserves a second
chance, Charles, it's you.
- Jeez, here.
- Hey kiddo. [groans]
So, would you like to
come in for some coffee?
- No, you know, I better
get going, ya know.
Matter of fact it's
probably a good idea
if I don't show up around
here for a couple of weeks.
- How was camping?
- Listen, Cyril. [groans]
- Don't speak out
of turn, Briefcase.
It's rude.
You are a piece of work.
There are drunks out there
but you're the whole package.
And the name, that's great too.
- I'm glad you approve.
- It all stopped when you
started costing me money.
- [Shari] Cyril, stop it.
- Will you shut up,
you wanna wake up
your little girl?
This is gonna be a
lesson, Briefcase,
that you will never forget.
- I can make it so the cops
never bust you guys again.
- [Cyril] What are
you talking about?
- All those winos out there,
they're not all winos.
Some of them are
undercover cops.
And they've been watching you.
I mean, you probably can't
tell the difference, but I can.
- And I suppose
you don't want me
to use Lizbeth to
make deliveries?
- I can take her place.
So I have a weak spot, shoot me.
[Cyril chuckles]
[both laughing]
[police sirens blaring]
- On a scale of one to 10,
this is the stupidest--
- Sh, watch.
- Are you gonna trust that fool?
- Of course not, but I'm
gonna use him though.
Perfect.
- What's the matter with you,
thought you said
you wanted a drink?
- Taken all the fun
out of it for me.
- You know Briefcase,
you were kinda impressing
me for a while, you know.
Cleaning yourself up,
getting that place and all.
What happened to your
job at the grocery store?
- Fired.
It was idiot work anyway.
- Yeah, but you was doing it.
- I was throwing rotten
produce in the garbage.
Big bucks, look
out Donald Trump.
- Talked to Lizbeth yesterday.
- She didn't lose
another tooth, did she?
Boy, that come back and
bite me in the butt.
- She misses you, Briefcase.
- She'll get over it.
Kids they bounce back.
- Briefcase, what the
is the matter with you?
You were almost there.
I mean, yeah you still
drank, but not like before.
Not like now.
Why you wanna throw it all away?
- I decided I was
too old for change.
Maybe I didn't wanna change,
you ever think about that?
You, you just remember,
no more tips to the cops.
Or Cyril and his goons are
gonna pound on me again.
- You gonna end up
in jail or dead.
Is that what you want?
- Who cares?
- [Muskat] Cyril ain't
worth this man, he ain't.
Yeah.
[door thudding]
[Briefcase yelling]
- Is that any way to
greet your guests?
- What do you want?
- What a dump.
- With a capital D.
- [Cyril] You been
crying, Briefcase?
- No.
- I can be real sympathetic
when I need to be.
Makes people work harder for me.
That's what it says in
the books I read anyway.
- Get to the point, Cyril.
Just tell me when and where.
- You see, all business.
All right, tomorrow
you pick up from me
but you drop off to
707 Placer Street,
entrance in the alley.
- That's not the usual way.
[body thudding]
[Briefcase groaning]
- Don't you worry about
what's usual and what isn't.
[chuckles] I just want to
spice things up for you.
Wouldn't want you
to get in a rut.
- You're too good to me.
[blow thuds]
[Briefcase groaning]
- [Cyril] And after the
delivery you come back
to my place with the package,
and I'll give you a
$100 bonus, old man.
[suspenseful music]
[mysterious music]
[brakes screeching]
[Briefcase gasping]
[door squeaking]
[door thudding]
- Oh.
Hi.
You know even the stuff
they use on television
wouldn't work on this.
You would think that
cleanliness is easier
than godliness, but not when
you're dealing with this junk.
- I couldn't think of
anyplace else to go.
So I came here.
- Oh well listen, I'll leave
and let you pray in peace.
- Oh no, no, actually, actually
I was hoping to talk to you.
You being the only
clergy I know.
- Whoa now this is beginning
to sound like a lost sheep.
Here, sit down, take a load off.
- I've been blaming God
for the bad things that
have happened in my life
and I've hated Him.
And now--
- And now you need His help?
- I was hoping He
could do me a favor.
Maybe help me do something
that I don't have the
strength to do it by myself.
- You know what I've
discovered, Briefcase?
God is not a slot machine.
You don't just put a quarter in
and hope for lucky
sevens to come out.
- I know that Preacher, I,
[gentle music]
I guess what I'm asking is,
do you think maybe,
maybe a guy like me could
get a second chance?
- I was a doctor once,
Briefcase, believe it or not.
- So that's why the clinic.
- Yep.
I performed miracles, I
brought people back to life.
These people for
any reason, science,
they should have been dead.
But I didn't think that
I was God's vessel.
I thought I was God.
What a prideful I was.
Anyway, my ego made me think
that I was not addicted to
these drugs that I prescribed.
It would be a problem
for a lessor person,
but not for me, not for God.
Anyway that attitude
killed somebody.
They made me stop
doing what I loved
more than anything else forever.
I was out on the
streets too, Briefcase.
But then one day,
I heard Him call.
He forgave me.
What do you say, Charles?
Do you wanna be forgiven?
- You haven't lost your
touch there, Preacher.
[gentle music]
Hey you, you know there's no
loitering round these parts.
- Hey, hey, hey, look who
it is, hey, Briefcase.
- You drinking water?
- Oh well you know, thought
I'd, time for a little change.
Enjoy the day for a while.
- [Briefcase] But paying
for bottled water?
- Oh get real, I found
this bottle a week ago,
been refilling it ever since.
[both chuckling]
- So how you been doing?
- Saved up $48,
thought I might get me a
place when I get enough.
- Slow going though, huh?
- You know it is.
Tough keeping money saved.
- Unless you have a
whole bunch of it.
- Well that would be
a different story.
But the lottery, that
like a tax for the stupid.
- No, no, no, you'd
have a sure thing.
- Oh, a sure thing
sure would be nice.
What exactly are we talking
about here, Briefcase?
- Oh, just talking about
getting out of this city,
you know, both of us.
- Me and you?
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm, by ripping off Cyril?
No, no, no, no, my momma didn't
raise no fool, he'd kill us.
- Don't you think I know that?
Look, I gotta make a
pick up this evening
and well all the signs
are pointing to it being,
being really big.
- What's so big about both of us
getting a bullet in our head?
- Well there are risks involved,
there always is Muskat.
Look, all right if you don't
wanna help me with this,
that's fine, you know, I
mean I'll respect that.
Can you honestly tell me
that anything is gonna change
with $48 in your pocket?
And if everything goes
the way I think it should,
Cyril won't even know what
we did until we're all gone.
You, me, Elizabeth
and her mother.
- You got them helping?
- No, no, no, no.
I don't want them
involved at all.
I don't want them to
know anything about it
unless it all goes right.
We're talking about
40 or $50,000 here.
- How do you know that?
- I just do.
I'll call it all off
if it goes wrong,
but I can't do this alone.
I need you on that phone.
I need you watching Cyril
and I need you to get
Elizabeth and her mom away
if everything goes smooth.
- What if it don't go right?
- I don't know.
Muskat, it's like
someone just told me.
You just gotta have faith.
[gentle music]
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay, I'm in.
- You're in?
Yeah, yeah.
[both laughing]
- Yeah.
[both grunting]
- [Salesman] It's almost new.
- Hi, how much is this?
- That ones, well I can let you
have that one for about $15.
- $10.
- You've gotta be joking, $10.
- Come on, $10.
- Like 12, 12, 12.
- 10 bucks, 10 bucks.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- What are you doing, leave
the phone alone, go, go, go.
Jeez.
[basketball thudding]
- [Player] Where are
you going old man?
[fist banging]
- The man of the hour is here.
You ready?
- Ready as I'll ever be.
- This will be waiting for you
when you come back.
- I'll be back in a jiffy.
Sebastian.
- [Cyril] You like Briefcase?
- Sure don't.
- When he comes
back, he's all yours.
[Sebastian chuckles]
[phone ringing]
- Muskat here.
- Stay loose Muskat, breathe.
- I'm breathing, I'm breathing.
- All right look, there's a
phone by the exchange place,
I'll call you when
I get the cash.
- All right I'll be there,
no, I'll be here, I'll be here.
[upbeat rap music]
[people chattering]
- Oh, is there a problem?
- No, no, delivery,
C Bone Enterprises.
- Let's have it.
♪ If you start to, I
will love it here ♪
♪ The way to play rough
♪ Blaize is here
♪ It's a big attack
♪ I make the Mardi Gras
- [whistling] Hey yo, hey.
♪ Splash, he always
wants a partner ♪
♪ Let go
♪ Friends cuttin, half bro
♪ Kick him down properly
♪ It ain' my property
- Yo, slip him the
chip it's straight.
♪ Like that
♪ When I get
♪ I'll fit my hand glove
♪ I'll
- Whoa, heavy.
- 270 large today, don't
throw your back out.
- Man, he's a mule,
you never tell a mule
what he's carrying man.
- [Adrian] Sorry man,
- Oh you seem to be
interested in numbers.
- Makes no difference to me.
- Hey, phone Cyril, homie.
[phone beeping]
- It's ringing player.
- It's ringing?
- [Adrian] It's ringing.
- [Jerry] It's ringing.
- [Adrian] It's ringing, player.
♪ Combined with the
state of California ♪
- Man, so what,
why you always got
your answering machine on man,
anyway your man's got the
cash and he's headed home,
he knows how much is in
it, thanks to Adrian.
- Oh man.
- Thanks.
Anyway, holler at me,
player, with quickness.
[gentle music]
[Briefcase laughing]
- 270,000.
[hook clicking]
- [Jerry] Anyway your
man's got the cash
and he's headed home,
he knows how much is
in it thanks to Adrian.
Anyway holler at me,
player, with quickness.
- Ah.
- What?
- Just Jerry being a fool.
But, smart leaders don't
let events control them.
They control the events.
I wonder, send Dwayne and
Eddie over to Shari's place
and make sure they stay put.
You and me, let's go deal
with Briefcase right now.
- [Sebastian] It's about time.
[phone beeping]
[phone ringing]
- Muskat.
- Briefcase.
- I got it, I got the money.
270,000, yeah get
Shari and Elizabeth
to the bus station.
- Briefcase, it's no good now.
Cyril's on to you.
He's got two guys
at Shari's door.
He's coming for you I know it.
Now you gotta get out of there.
- Where, where at Shari's?
- [Muskat] What do you
mean, what do you mean?
- Where, where
are they standing?
- They're at the front
door, I told you,
what difference does that make?
- Where's Elizabeth,
where's Shari?
- They got them
there too, Briefcase,
now just call it
off, call it off now.
- No.
No, no, no, we're never
gonna get another chance.
You call the cops right now.
- No, no, Briefcase
I'm not doing it.
- I am counting on you.
[Muskat groaning]
[phone thudding]
[dramatic music]
- [Operator] 911 emergency.
- Yes, yes there's
gonna be a shooting.
I mean, I heard shots.
I heard shots.
Oh man, oh man.
[dramatic music]
[tense music]
[gun firing]
[people screaming]
No!
[brakes screeching]
Help me.
[sirens blaring]
- [Officer] Turn around.
- [Officer] Newspaper.
[radio chattering]
[mysterious music]
[soft music]
- It's okay, Daddy.
[gentle music]
- No, you can't go there now.
- Briefcase.
- You can't go there.
You can't go there.
Ssh it's all right,
it's all right.
- [Lizbeth] Briefcase. [sobbing]
- I told him it wouldn't work.
- [Lizbeth] Briefcase.
[police sirens blaring]
- [Muskat] It's all right baby.
It's all right.
[gentle music]
- Briefcase?
Wow.
Thank you, Briefcase,
I love you too.
[air whooshing]
[triumphant music]
- [Briefcase] Hold
it out like that
and let it catch the wind.
There now try running with it.
- [Lizbeth] Thank
you, Briefcase.
[gentle music]
- You guys have
a safe trip, huh.
- You stay out of trouble, okay?
- I will, come on.
Let's go.
Yeah. [chuckles]
- Tell Santa hi from me, okay.
- I will.
- Okay, bye.
- [Muskat] Bye.
- Bye.
- Bye!
- [Lizbeth] Bye, Muskat.
- Bye now.
[gentle music]
Thanks, pal.
[triumphant music]
[bright upbeat music]
[bright music]