[panting]
[birds chirping]
[heroic music]
[man] It was the summer
of 1875
and McKennna was
a long way from home.
He was married
to an Indian girl,
daughter
of the tribal elder.
She was waiting for him
in a cabin on the mountain.
She had a fever
and he'd ridden his horse
to death,
to get back
with medicine for her.
[panting]
There were dangers
in the forest that night,
not just the wind
and the rain, and lightning.
A gang of cutthroats,
hired by timber agents
from the Northern Pacific
were waiting for him.
They wanted his trees
for railroad ties,
but he wouldn't sell
and he wouldn't deal.
It was Indian land,
given to him
by his wife's father.
He could sense the danger
but by then it was too late.
They caught up with him
on the trail about the river.
[grunting]
McKenna fought them
in the way of the Indians.
Launching and spinning,
grappling and swirling.
[grunting]
They had their guns,
but every part
of Jedidiah McKenna,
a man hardened by rain
and fire on the mountain,
every part of him
was a weapon.
He was alone
and there were six of them.
[grunting]
[man] Look out!
Then there were five.
[laughs]
[yelling]
McKenna had run 40 miles,
from a trading post
on the Columbia,
but he was winning,
he was billing them.
[yelling]
[grunt]
They shot him though.
Cowards that they were.
And he fell tumbling
and rolling
down into the white water.
[girl] He never made it
back to her?
He just drowned
in the river?
Come on, you guys.
I mean, the guy was shot.
He didn't have to drown,
he was already on his way
to the boneyard.
He maybe is the river
in our mountain.
This is the Bigfoot story?
Sasquatch,
is that was this is?
No.
Is not about Sasquatch
or the river or the gun.
And you were right, Austene.
He never saw his wife again.
But he never left
the mountain either.
[peaceful music]
[man] He was cold,
lost in the eternal darkness,
lying on the river bank
in the wilderness.
[snorting]
But this time
he was not alone.
The forest spirit found him.
This one had taken the form
of a great bear.
[growl]
This is how the legend began.
The Legend of the Spirit
of the Mountain.
I'm sure about this legend.
We've all heard little bits
and pieces of it.
But he was shot,
wasn't he?
And he was drowned,
[Brian] Guys,
legends aren't true.
They're just things
that people want to be true.
I don't know what better
than to believe on it, Brian.
-It has to be some good in it.
-Justin is right, Brian.
Must legends and folklore
are based in facts.
That's right.
McKenna was shot.
He was in the river
all night.
[growling]
[screech]
[roaring]
[twinkling]
In the magic glade
deep entangled
all those years ago,
the power of the forest,
the power
that could restore life
to any human
or beast harmed by another,
that power was called down
by the bear
and it touched McKenna.
And the spirits
of the mountain joined in him.
Then, the bear,
the wolf,
the eagle
became one in McKenna.
He could become all of them.
In the Indian legend,
a shape-shifter.
And he would stay forever
to protect the mountain
and everything
that lived there,
and everyone who loved it.
You mean he's a spirit now?
A spirit of the mountain?
Like a ghost?
No, no, not a ghost.
McKenna's spirit embodies
the strenght of the balance
of nature.
[man laughs]
Well, that's enough for now.
We better go now
or we'll late
for the big shindy.
[man] I'll tell you some
more another time.
-Wait. Mr. Madison?
-Yeah?
What's a shape-shifter?
You know, like the one
in the Indian legend?
Well, Justin, a shape-shifter
can appear a human,
who has the ability
to take the shape
of those creatures
he loved in life.
He can even see through
your eyes into your soul.
No kidding?
[chuckles]
No kidding, Logan.
Let's go!
Ready to go, Justin.
We won't be late.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
[woman] Make sure
to put the fire out, honey!
Yeah, yeah.
-[Madison] Stacy.
-What are you've been up
to out there?
-You're looking very pretty.
-Thank you.
What do you think about
this big "get together."
Everybody knows
what I think.
Do you think Mr. Madison
makes it all up,
you know,
about the legend
of Tanglewood?
[Brian] Come on! He knows
we hang around
the old tree house.
He just wants to give Logan
the creeps. That's all.
That is so sad.
What's sad?
He never got to see
his wife again.
Yeah, that's sad.
[man] All we're talking about
is cutting down
a few old trees, alright?
I understand,
and to all of your concerns
I'm still one of you,
and like one of you,
I only want what is best
for this community.
But remember,
the unharvested riches
that we have on our mountain
can only bring
prosperity and hope
for our future,
here in Tanglewood.
Excuse me, Mr. Thorne,
sounds like
Thorne Lumber Company
stands to benefit a whole lot.
What about our alternatives?
What about the wildlife?
What about
our nature conservacy?
My staff and I are fully aware
of the alternatives.
But folks,
let's be reasonable.
I mean,
the nature conservacy?
There's no money on that.
And I think it's obvious
to you all hardworking people.
But my harvesting proposal
is gonna change
this town around.
And that's
what we all want, isn't?
-[woman] No!
-[cheering]
[whistling]
My lawyers,
my colleagues here,
will be glad
to answer any questions
that you may still have.
And I want to thank
all of you for coming.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
Very good.
-I think they'll come around.
-It's lovely.
You two don't know
what the hell
are you talking about.
[playing country music]
-Can I offer you some punch?
-Thank you, Austene.
-Having fun?
-Yeah.
No.
It's hard to believe that boy
comes from this parts.
He's driven by nothing
but grieve.
I don't get it.
What are they willing to do
to our mountain?
You know, Logan,
how can we be related?
They're just gonna
pick it clean, bonehead.
Hey! Don't call me
"bonehead", bonehead!
-Don't touch me.
-[Grunts]
I guess we're just let
the Town Council decide
if that Thorne guy
can log them out.
Well, my dad is
a logger, too,
and he's never, ever,
cut down those old trees.
Yeah, you know,
Mr. Madison says
those trees are 600,
800 years old.
No kidding?
No kidding, Logan.
Brian, what are you...?
[scoffs]
Oh, that's attractive.
Oh, come on, you guys.
Oh, Lord, help me survive
my older son's appetite.
Let's go.
We got a big day tomorrow.
Yeah. Logan becomes
an official Lord of Tanglewood.
Tomorrow.
Where's your jacket, honey?
-Daddy, where you've been?
-I got delayed.
I didn't mean to be late.
I'm sorry, honey.
I... I'm sorry,
but you know...
Yes, Daddy.
I know.
They're talking about
the mountain and...
it could mean
"new job."
It could mean everything
for us.
I... I should just stay.
They can decide it
without us.
Come on, Daddy,
let's go home.
You need some sleep.
Yeah... I'm pretty tired.
Daddy, we'll walk.
[Shirley] Come on.
Good night, Daddy.
[Austene] Please help my daddy
to be strong and healthy.
Bless our mountain
with a gift of melting snow,
a heart that give life
to our forest.
Please try to find a way
to save it.
Bless Mommy,
wherever she is.
And give her a thought of me
and Daddy once in a while.
We need your help so much.
So much.
Amen.
[growl]
[growling]
[birds chirping]
Remember, Logan,
this is your first trip
to the mountain.
I want you to listen
to your brother.
Give me candy, Brian.
Listen to your brother,
and do everything
he tells you to do.
-Everything?
-No!
Brian, give me the candy.
You had a good breakfast
this morning.
-[Brian] No.
-[Shirley] No? Yeah.
OK, you guys,
have a good time.
[Justin] What's up, dudes!
-[Justin] Let's go! Let's go!
-[Austene] Hi, guys!
[hubbub]
Listen to what
your brother says,
you understand?
[kids yelling]
I want all you kids
to watch out for Logan!
And chat with Clovis
before you leave town!
-[Logan] Thank you, Mom!
-Uh-huh.
He'll call me if you don't!
[ominous music]
Thorne, this nature
conservacy thing is
nothing more than a threat.
They'll yield.
The bottom line is greed.
-There's nothing like it.
-Well, you should know.
Williams!
You handled that impeccably.
The prosperity and progress
are always the best bait.
I couldn't care less about
the progress of anyone
except Travis Thorne, boys.
And so should you, too,
because I'm your meal ticket.
Williams, I want you
to get survey teams
on top of the mountain,
first thing in the morning.
Set up grids
for clear cutting.
30 million board-feet
of lumber are up there
and I want it all.
-You wanna use local labor?
-What for?
They don't want to cooperate.
Scruples.
-What?
-Scruples, boys! Scruples!
Like they sizzle
in their own grease.
[laughing]
We'll get a temporary permit,
we'll scrap the place,
we'll have our money
in the bank before
they can file on us.
And then you two geniuses,
you'll just bury them
in paperwork
until hell is
a ski resort.
Holly, come in.
Nevermind.
Come on, let's go.
I know what he meant.
Got enough food,
snacks, power bars?
[all] Yes, sir. We got'em.
[Madison] Toothpaste,
extra brushes?
[Austene] I got'em,
Mr. Madison.
So...
You can't think of anything
you might've forgotten, huh?
[all] No, sir. Nothing.
We got it alright this time,
Mr. Madison. Right, guys?
-[all] Yeah.
-I see.
Well now...
this could be important,
you know?
Especially since
your alternative is
pine cone or tree barks.
Oh...
Oh, toilet paper.
-There you go, Justin.
-Thanks.
-Put this in my bag.
-Cool.
Now, my young Lords
of Tanglewood, go on.
-And tell the mountain
hello for me.
-[Justin] Alright!
[all] Bye, Mr. Madison!
[kids yelling]
[Austene] Bye, Mr. Madison!
[Justin] See you later,
Mr. Madison!
[kids yelling]
Hmm.
Fill up that for me,
will you?
-You mean now?
-Yeah, that'd be good.
What happened
to the conversation?
Hey, Blaine.
-How about a cup of coffee?
-No, thanks.
How about a cup
of world-class chili?
No, no. I had some
of that last summer.
And?
When it gets hot
I still taste it.
[Shirley laughs]
[grunts]
Lately, he's been coming in
whenever he feels like it,
and that means less and less.
Yes.
Arlen...
-How's everything going?
-[Arlen] Couldn't be better.
[exhales]
Sorry, only got
to one cup.
Arlen, two years is
enough time for all this.
Why, Blaine, whatever
are you talking about?
Forget it, Arlen.
She was my wife,
you know?
[sighs]
Why not I just run
my wife off, too?
Then we can get drunk
and sniffle about
our bad luck together.
I didn't run her off!
If you could've just have
a little more patience...
-If you just understood...
-I did understand!
I understood you were
the best deputy I've ever had
till people started
tripping over you.
-Is there a point to all this?
-Yeah! You got a daughter!
Who's doing a pretty good job
at taking care of you so far,
-but it can't go on forever.
-What are you talking about?
You're on the slide, Arlen.
And if you don't hoist up
your pantyhose
and get your life
back together again,
you're gonna lose Austene.
Sooner or later,
one way or the other,
that's what's gonna happen.
Put the gas on my tab,
will you, Barney?
[soft rock song plays]
♪ Where the bees are buzzing
And the skies are blue ♪
♪ No more troubles
For me and you♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ Where it ain't no crime
To love the sunshine ♪
-♪ In the summertime
-[hoot]
♪ Down by the river
Where the breeze is cool ♪
♪ We'll all get together
And act like fools ♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ Yeah, in the summertime
♪ Where it ain't no crime
To love the sunshine ♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ That's right!
♪ Yeah! In the summertime
♪ Oh! In the summertime
♪ Where it ain't no crime
To love the sunshine ♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ Yeah, in the summertime
♪ Yeah! In the summertime
♪ Where it ain't no crime
To love the sunshine ♪
♪ In the summertime
[song ends]
Hey, guys?
Where did everybody go?
Hey, guys!
Hello?
[branch cracks]
Don't mess with me.
I know karate.
[ominous music]
[chirps]
Come on, guys!
Come out!
Austene?
Come on, guys!
Come out, please!
Lewis!
We're not doing chores,
so come out!
Please, come out!
Hey, guys?
Hey, guys... I'm getting
a little scare here.
Wow!
[kids shouting]
[Brian] Yeah! Oh, yeah!
Logan! Come on,
man, this place is sick!
[Austene] Come on, Logan
Welcome to Tanglewood manor.
[kids] Come on, Logan!
[kids shouting]
[Brian] We're here!
Yes! Check out the hub!
Logan, come on, man!
Let's go!
-[roaring]
-[kids screaming]
What? Yeah, right.
I'm not falling for that.
I'm no fool, you know.
[Lewis] Come on, Justin,
let's go!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
-Did you see what it was?
-[Brian] It was a big gorilla.
I swear!
[Lewis] I don't know
what it was doing, gorillas are
only around here in the zoo.
Well, one of them
must've got out then.
This is cool.
[Austene] No, it was
a mountain lion.
I saw its eye.
No, you're both crazy.
I saw it.
It was a bear.
A giant bear.
-[roaring]
-A monster! Giant monster!
Logan!
-[Logan] Help me!
-[Austene] Logan!
It grabbed me!
Please, help me!
[all shouting]
[cans rattling]
[screaming]
[kids giggling]
Guys, it's a baby bear.
[all laughing]
[huffing]
Let me get that rag off you,
little guy.
Rags, that's a good name.
[Justin] Hey!
You know, guys,
I wasn't scared.
-[Lewis] Yeah?
-[Justin] Yeah, right, Brian.
Come on, you guys,
I wasn't scared!
[Justin] Come on!
Rags is so cute.
I know what
you're thinking, Austene.
Bear cubs
do not make good pets.
[bear cub snorting]
Goodbye, Rags.
[huffing]
[croaking]
[moaning]
Oof!
[Austene] That's a smelly job
it gifted here, guys.
Mr. Rags left us two piles
of current cards.
I'll get the water.
My Logan,
I'll show you around.
This place is awesome.
Come on, let's go.
Mark it.
[echoing]
What was that?
What?
-Phill.
-What?
I don't know.
It's... something. It's...
This doesn't feel right.
So...
Just finish the job,
will you?
Yeah.
[huffing]
Holly, grab your gun.
We got a bear over here.
-Did he say bear?
-[both] Bear!
[cub whining]
[Williams] Guys, hurry up,
we're gonna lose him!
[crack]
[thumping]
The danger signal.
The danger signal!
Come on, Logan.
Let's go, guys!
Come on!
[huffing]
[Williams] There it is!
Now we got him.
[screeching]
[cub whining]
Either of you want
the shot?
[Holly] Come on,
if it's a fish, you got
to throw it back.
[Williams] That's not a fish.
And it's worth something,
no matter how big it is.
Yeah? It'd worth a lot more
if it was bigger.
Huh. You wanna wait
for it to grow up?
They're gonna shoot Rags.
[whining]
No! No, you can't shoot him!
Stop!
Well, well, well.
Where did you come from?
Don't you know better
than to run at a man
with a rifle?
You can't shoot
that bear cub.
You're right. Holly.
I should just skin it alive.
[laughs]
No! Please!
Come here, you little
oogie boogie bear.
[screeching]
[screams]
[grunting]
Halt!
Move one more muscle,
and I'm gonna blow
your head off.
Oh...
Oh!
[moans]
[screams]
Wow!
-Oh!
-Gotta hurt!
[Holly yelling]
[all] Oh!
Uh-oh.
[cheering]
Yeah!
I don't know
who you are, mister,
but you're in big trouble.
Get off the mountain.
All of you.
We have the right to be here.
You can't tell us what to do.
[growling]
[hooting]
[howling]
[several animal noises]
[Holly] Let's do
what he says.
What's the matter, Holly?
You're getting superstitious
on me?
Yeah, that's exactly
what I'm doing.
Let's get out of here.
[whining]
[whispering]
Rags, come here.
Oh, Rags.
I'm so glad you're back.
I missed you.
You were very brave, Austene.
You saved his life.
Where is his mother?
His mother was old and sick.
She died giving him life.
Do you think
it will be alright
if I can take him home?
Just for a little while?
He wouldn't be happy
off the mountain.
His home is here,
in the forest.
-Can I be his friend?
-You are his friend.
[kids chattering]
Where did he go?
Did you guys see?
I was just talking with him.
Did you look at their faces?
That was awesome.
[guys agreeing]
Are you guys blind?
I was just talking to him.
Where did he go?
He just walk out
after the fight, Austene.
No, I was talking
with him.
Austene, you were talking
to the bear.
He said he was my friend.
What do you mean
he said he was your friend?
-He's a bear, Austene.
-Bears don't talk.
Hey, Justin, Brian,
one of those guys drop
his walkie-talkie.
You may as well toss it.
One walkie-talkie isn't good
for anything.
-Let's go.
-[Logan] I guess you're right.
[Brian] Yes, man.
-[Logan] Shut up.
-You.
[cub whining]
Mr. Thorne.
Give good news, Williams.
All I want
to hear is good news.
Well, we nearly finish it.
What the hell
does "nearly" mean?
There's some kids up there.
School's out.
I should've figured
on that.
Well, you let me do
the figure, alright?
And there's somebody else
up there, too.
Who?
-I don't know.
-What did he look like?
A trapper.
Some kind of hippie
out of the '70s.
You know,
leather and stuff.
Is that what happened
to your face?
Holly and two
of my surveyors quit
when we got back.
They say you don't pay'em
enough money
to get busted up.
Is that right?
Then just find a few men
who aren't squeamish
about fighting, alright?
You know,
I don't know
about that trapper guy
but there's no mystery
why those kids
are up there.
It's a tree house.
[chuckles]
I used to play up there
when I was a kid. It was...
magical.
A wonderful place.
[chuckles]
I have some of my fondest
memories when I...
Just get rid
of the damned thing.
OK.
[all yelling]
[Logan moaning]
[Brian] Yeah, just go...
[Brian laughing]
[Brian] You're ready?
You're ready?
Here we go!
[Lewis] One more.
Let's go, buddy.
Logan, you made it!
You're one of us now.
You're Lord.
[Logan moaning]
[Austene] The initiation
is over.
[Justin] Come on.
[Austene] He ate 15 sardines
and he drank a chocolate milk.
That's enough.
He doesn't need to toss
his cookies, too.
-[Justin] Brian did.
-I had the flu.
OK, we need to do this
as the sun sets.
Why do we have to do it
as the sun sets?
We have to do this
at sunset
because that's how
the generations before us
did it.
This is our vow.
You know your part?
We, the Lords of Tanglewood...
Where the forest
as for centuries did...
[Brian] Cherish our mountain
and all the earth...
[Lewis] Love all its creatures
and boundless worth.
As did the ones
who came before...
And those will teach
our wood and lore.
[bonfire spreads]
We ask you to leave it
pure as found.
We are to it forever bound.
We ask you to leave it
pure as found.
We are to it forever bound.
[all] We are to it
forever bound.
[hooting]
[huffing]
[hissing]
[screams]
Oh, it's you, Fred.
Austene, Fred's back.
I'll be right there.
-Where is he?
-In my sleeping bag.
Wow... a snake.
I think Fred is OK,
but I don't want him
in my sleeping bag.
Especially when I'm
in there.
He's cold
and you're warm.
What did you expect?
He's my Freddy,
Freddy, Freddy.
Ew...
-Are we going fishing?
-Yeah!
Hey, Austene,
maybe we could use
old Freddy for bait.
No way.
[boys laughing]
Hey, you guys just watch.
I'm gonna catch
some fish today.
[soft music]
-[Logan] Hey, Rags.
-[Lewis] Rags, what are you
smelling at?
Hey, guys,
I caught another fish!
Another one!
We're zip and she's got
seven already.
[laughing]
Yes!
She's just showing off.
I hate when this happens.
I hate it.
Hey, Austene!
Get your puppy out
of the water!
He's scaring
all the fish!
He's not scaring mine.
Well, that's because
you're over there
and he's over here.
Yeah!
[whining]
[kids laughing]
[Brian] Alright!
-[Justin] I got it!
-[Brian] Guys, my face!
-[Lewis] We caught a whale!
Yeah!
[trill]
[all yelling]
They'll be playing there
all day.
Let's go set the charge.
[laughing, yelling]
[ominous music]
[laughing]
[beeping]
[Logan screams]
-[Justin] What happened?
-[Logan] I fell on a rock.
-[Austene] Let me look at it.
-[Logan] It was like a knife.
[moaning]
[screams]
No!
[Lewis] A minor laceration.
Thought it was
far more worse than this.
We gotta get back.
The first aid kit
is in the tree house.
-I'm sorry, you guys.
-It's your first time up here,
Mom told me
to take care of you
and look what you do, Logan.
You crash and burn.
[cub wining]
[kids yelling, arguing]
I don't care!
Get that away from me!
No!
Logan.
You know, it didn't
really hurt at all.
[Logan] Thanks, Austene.
[Justin] Told you
it wouldn't hurt.
[Lewis] Listen to her
more often, man.
[Justin] You OK?
Does anybody want
to help me clean the fish?
I gotta go find
some firewood.
I'm gonna go help him.
I gotta go find a tree
and take care
of my business.
I gotta go make a fire
with the... firewood.
Wimps.
Come on, Rags.
[beeping]
Well, well, well.
The miracles never cease
to happen.
I'm glad you realize that.
Huh.
I was hopping for this.
I told you to get off
the mountain.
Yeah, you did.
[yelling]
[grunting]
[whining]
[yelling]
Uh-oh!
[hiss]
Oh...
[Williams] You're really
slippery, aren't you?
Well, fight this!
-[Brian] A gunshot!
-[Justin] Austene!
Come on! They're the same guys.
We'll call the rangers.
I can't right now.
Austene, what are you
waiting for? Come on!
I have to put the fish away
or Rags will eat them.
OK, well just catch up
with the thing, alright?
[Lewis] And hurry!
[mystical sounds]
[man screaming]
[screech]
Stay here, Rags.
[beeping]
[panting]
-Sounds like an explosion.
-Where did it come from?
Sounds like
the tree house.
[Lewis and Justin] Austene!
[cub whining]
Austene! She must
be in there!
[Justin and Lewis] No!
[Brian] No!
Austene!
Austene! Austene!
Protective spirit, huh?
Protective spirit?
[Brian] What good does it do
to believe in anything?
Justin, we gotta get
some help.
Somebody's gotta help us.
Somebody's gotta help us!
Listen to me!
Where was he
when we really need him, huh?
Where was he?
[Lewis] Calm down
and listen to me!
[Justin] OK! Guys, shut up!
Everybody just shut up!
-[sobbing]
-[Justin] Alright.
Listen to me, guys.
We gotta get
some help, OK?
Let's go! Let's go!
[Lewis] Let's go. We'll go
get some help. Come on!
[Brian] No!
We need to find her!
[guys shouting]
[Lewis] Go! Go! Go!
Clovis.
[panting]
[Justin] Hey, Mr. Madison!
[Brian] Mr. Madison!
[kids shouting
at the same time]
[Madison] Calm down!
Calm down!
[kids shouting]
-[Arlen] Austen what?
-[kids shouting]
[Arlen] Come on,
get on the Bronco.
Let's go!
We'll find Austene.
Clovis, call sheriff Ramsey.
And the fire sergeant.
Tell him it might be a fire.
Give me the sheriff.
[roaring]
[twinkling]
[bear huffing]
How are you feeling,
Austene?
Where am I?
Was I sleeping?
Yes, you were sleeping.
Rags, where is he?
Over there.
What happened?
Where are all the others?
Your friends are fine.
This is your home?
Is this where you live?
The forest is my home.
Are you the...?
Have you lived here
a long, long time?
A long, long time.
I'm really sorry
you never saw
your wife again.
Sleep.
Everything will be fine.
[Blaine] Arlen, calm down.
[Arlen grunting]
Arlen, come here.
Come here.
You gotta calm down.
She's not here, Blaine!
She wasn't here!
If she... was here,
we would've found her.
-Alright, alright!
-We'd found her, wouldn't we?
[Arlen sobbing]
Why don't you just beat
the hell out of me?
[crying]
It wouldn't do any good.
Nothing would feel
like it.
Come on.
[Blaine] Clovis,
come over here.
Oh, God!
God, help me!
What would I give...
Oh, Austene...
Daddy?
My baby!
Guys, it's Austene!
-[Lewis] Oh, gosh!
-[Justin] She's OK!
[Arlen] Oh, thanks!
[sobbing]
My baby! My baby!
I love you so much.
I love you, Austene.
Austene, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry for everything.
Please, forgive me.
Daddy, it's fine.
I love you, baby!
[eagle screeches]
Still on the job, huh?
-What was that?
-I was just saying thank you.
[screech]
To the spirit
of the mountain?
[chuckles]
You don't still believe
on those old stories,
do you?
[Arlen] What happened
on the mountain, Blaine?
You saw it.
How could anything
would've live through that?
I told you, Daddy.
My friend helped me.
You know, odd things have been
happening on that mountain
for a long time.
It's not haunted,
I know that.
[pouring coffee]
Enchanted, maybe.
Enchanted?
What happened to you
up there today
it reminds me of something
that happened...
30 years ago.
I took my wife out canoing
in the moonlight.
And it got breezy
and it got chilly.
And I wanted to move
to the front and put
my jacket around her.
And I took a wrong step,
I shifted my weight
and the canoe turned upside.
I thought I could
hear her screaming,
but before I could get
to her, she went under.
So I dove.
And I dove and I dove,
but I couldn't find her.
I didn't know what else
to do so I ran for help.
When I got back,
she was there.
Cold and wet,
and waiting for me.
Something had lifted
her up, she said.
Something embraced her
and carried her
to the surface.
And she wasn't afraid,
and she knew
I was coming back.
How do you explain that?
Some things
you can't explain.
I know what I believe,
and you might not agree.
But I'm thankful
for the way things worked out.
And you should be, too.
[rumbling]
What the heck?
[ominous music]
Thorne is on the move.
He managed to get
a temporary permit.
He can start cutting
the trees at noon tomorrow.
[Arlen] What?
We were supposed
to vote on this.
We gotta get a court order.
This might help.
I gotta call this morning
from someone who saw
one of Thorne's crew
loading explosives.
You mean... Thorne could be
responsible for blowing up
the tree house?
Everything points
at Thorne.
Whoa, whoa.
Justin, hey.
Austene, what are you
doing here?
We have some emergency
planning to do.
I know the sheriff
and the grown ups
are gonna do all they can,
but we can't just
wait around.
Right, after what they did
to our tree house, guys.
If we're gonna put
our plan into action,
we gotta move fast.
Hold on.
We got a little problem
with our plan.
What?
Communications.
They have CBs
and walkie-talkies.
I might have something.
[cheering]
[whirring]
-[Thorne] Everyone of
the crew teams have a radio?
-[Williams] Yes, sir.
And they're all
in the same frequency?
I checked them
all myself.
You'll make absolutely clear
that nothing and no one
makes a move without
a direct order from me.
Yes, Mr. Thorne, I guarantee
nothing's gonna go wrong.
I'll remember you said that.
Buster, get that truck
loaded up and follow us.
We're taking
the back road.
Travis, why is it necessary
for us to go?
We don't belong up there.
He's right, Travis.
We're big city attorneys.
We're not backwoods lawyers.
I'm sorry, gentleman.
I really am.
Are you two certain
that those permits
are in order?
Well, yeah, sure.
But this is...
Then get your petty
butts on board!
We got 72 hours to cut
everything we can
and get the heck out!
So get in!
Go! Move out!
Get in.
Move out.
This is it.
Let's do it.
-Alright. You got the tapes
and the walkie?
-Yes.
Alright. Then walk to the top
of the hill and you'll be
between Thorne and his men.
-You ready?
-Yeah, I'm ready.
Go.
Alright, guys.
One, two,
three! Push!
Right there.
[whispering]
Guys, they're coming!
Let's go.
-You guys ready?
-[both] Yeah.
[Thorne] Alright, every out!
Look alive!
[Williams] Come on, ladies,
just move it!
Hustle! Hustle Hustle!
We gotta move this log.
Get this chunk of kindling
off the road.
And you two,
come on, out of the car.
You know what, gentleman?
I think somebody's trying
to pull my chain.
[man yelling]
[chuckles]
We got thumb tacks
in the log there, Mr. Thorne.
[shushes]
-It's the green weenies.
-Weenies?
Environmentalists.
Get it.
[Thorne] They're out there.
I know they are.
Continue,
Mr. Williams.
Do it again.
Come on, you can take care
of your boo-boo
when we get back.
Let's go! Lift it up.
Come on, girls.
Yes!
[Thorne] I know
you're out there. Huh?
You little green weenies.
Environmentalists?
Are you afraid
to show your face,
is that what it is? Huh?
Well, it's not gonna work.
I don't need
to see your face.
Because I know
you're out there.
[Williams] Put your backs
into it, girls! Come on!
[Thorne] I know your game.
Nothing new to me.
You're afraid, right?
Hiding in the woods
like the cowardly
little fairies you are.
-Mr. Thorne!
-Not now, Buster. Huh?
And I'm tired
of your nonsenses.
Now, you might try
to slow me down, dear,
but you will never stop me.
Mr. Thorne, the antennae.
You understand? Never!
Mr. Williams.
You will never stop
Travis Thorne!
And no...! Never sneak up
on me like that.
Alright, everybody,
load up!
-Mr. Thorne.
-I said now.
Right? Not tomorrow.
Not next week.
-Now!
-Yes, sure, Mr. Thorne.
[Williams] Come on, Buster.
What, am I surrounded
by morons or something?
Just get in the car!
Hey, Austene.
I finally caught
one bigger than you.
[engine cranking]
Won't start.
It's a brilliant observation,
Mr. Williams.
It's probably just
flooded out.
I'll get it.
[engines cranking]
Potato...
Two potatoes.
Mr. Thorne!
Oh, no.
Time for plan 2.
Just look what they put
into the tailpipes.
A potato!
-A potato?
-Yeah.
I got two of them.
One potato,
two potatoes.
[chuckles]
You want one?
What? Do I want one?
He wants to know
if I want a potato.
[chuckles]
Come here, man.
Near, Buster.
You are one of them,
aren't you?
You're a green weenie!
They have penetrated.
Mr. Thorne,
it's not his fault!
No, he watch for you,
Mr. Thorne.
-Hurting him won't do...
-I don't want to hurt him.
I don't wanna hurt him!
I just wanna strangle him!
-It'll make me
feel better. Alright?
-Alright.
-OK.
-[Thorne] Alright. Alright.
Alright. I'm OK.
They just wanna stop me.
I think we can go now,
Mr. Williams.
-OK.
-[engine starts]
[officer] And another
Thorne crew here.
Do any of you believe
that Thorne's gonna wait
for a twelve o'clock deadline
once he gets set up?
Thorne? No.
We gotta get
that court order.
Yes!
You gutless
environmental punks!
If there's trouble you want,
there's trouble you'll get!
That's right, trouble!
And its name is Thorne!
[kids] Pull it! Go! Go!
Travis... Whoa!
[screaming]
[grunting, screaming]
[all] "Travis Thorne!"
Hush, guys.
We gotta go!
[screaming]
Oh...
I stop. I stop...
That's good.
[grunting]
Damn you...!
[screaming]
[phone ringing]
Ramsey.
OK.
Great. You tell the judge
I say thank you.
We got him.
We got the court order.
And we got a bonus.
An arrest warrant
for Thorne and Williams.
-Great!
-Let's go.
[man 1] I'm gonna get
that truck down to warm up.
[man 2] We gotta wait
for Thorne on the radio
before we start cutting
the trees.
[man 1] I wish we could just
cut down damned trees.
[man 2] Yeah, me too.
[rock music plays]
♪ Rayleen
♪ Why do you
Chasing down to me? ♪
♪ Rayleen, Rayleen
Is on me, it's all clear ♪
♪ Rayleen
♪ I took you out to dinner
♪ I took you to a show
♪ I took you on the Mondays
All you did was saying no ♪
I need a first aid kit.
Now.
[Buster] Oh, I know.
I know you need one, sir.
Them brambles are full
of poison oak and sumac, too.
Looks like you got
a good dose of both.
Don't touch me!
Don't ever touch me.
Get on the CB
and get me a first aid kit.
I'd like to help out,
but somebody busted
the antennae. All of them.
[Williams] The tire's fixed.
Alright, alright. OK.
Next plan.
I wanna cut
the trees down now.
OK? Right now
Does anybody have
a problem with that?
It's not twelve o'clock yet.
[mimicking]
Our permit is not good
before twelve.
I pay you 400 dollars at hour.
You know what time it is?
Buster!
Give me that walkie-talkie.
-Now!
-But, sir...
-I'm worried about him.
-Me too.
-[loud rock music playing]
-[screams]
What the hell is that?
What was that? Huh?
OK. Williams,
give me yours.
I... lost mine.
Well, obviously somebody
must have found it, huh?
[Thorne] OK!
I want you to hustle
your buns over that hill.
Go get there before us.
Just tell them that I said
to cut the trees down now.
Alright?
-Buster!
-[song continues]
Get in here
and drive this thing.
-But, sir...
-Shush, shush! Drive it!
They're gonna cut down
the forest!
We can't let them
do that!
What are we
gonna do now?
[song continues]
We gotta stop them!
♪ Why do you chasing down
To me ♪
♪ Rayleen, Rayleen
Some things aren't clear♪
♪ Rayleen
♪ I gave you all my money ♪
♪ I bought you diamond rings
You tell me no and no ♪
♪ And that's your one
And final stand ♪
♪ Rayleen, why do you
Chasing down to me? Yeah ♪
♪ Rayleen, Rayleen
Is on me, it's all clear ♪
♪ Rayleen
♪ Come on!
[music stops]
So you're the little punk
messing with the radios, huh?
[yells]
So...
You'd be one of those
karate guys, huh?
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
Who you think you are?
Bruce Lee?
No, see,
you'd be Bruce Flea.
I tell you what.
I'll let you have a free shot.
Come on here.
Give me one right here.
It's all yours.
Give me your best shot.
Come on.
Come on, right there.
Don't be afraid.
[yelps]
[grunting]
Where did you come from?
We got some
unfinished business
you and me.
You're gonna
stick around this time
and fight like a man? Huh?
Do you wanna fight him,
Logan?
Uh-uh.
He's too big.
Yeah, you're right.
Fight like a man, huh?
-Yeah.
-You mean like an Englishman?
[grunting]
None of that
Englishman garbage!
Just... Just... Fight!
You know, just...
-Like a mountain man?
-Yeah.
[banjo music]
[grunting]
Why don't you just...
fight...
fair?
Over here.
It's not fair...
[moaning]
Now he's your size.
[karate shout]
[grunts]
Yeah!
Those environmentalists.
They sent kids to do
their dirty work.
Well, I'm just scare
the pants off them.
Watch this.
Give me the rifle.
[lawyer] Here.
[screams]
Don't ever point a gun
at me like that.
Sorry.
Nobody.
Nobody is gonna stop me
from cutting down my trees!
You see this?
It's a rifle.
It has five bullets in it,
and there's four of you.
Somebody's gonna
get shot twice.
[giggles]
[panting]
[growling]
Wolf...
[police siren]
Where did it go?
-Mr. Thorne! The cops!
-Where?
Take this.
-It's your gun, Mr. Thorne.
-Take the gun!
-It's your gun!
-Take it!
Oh, no...
Buster!
Why is this happening
to me? Why?
-Here. Here.
-I don't want it.
I want you two
to deal with this.
Just deal with it!
Alright, drop the gun!
You're under arrest
for illegal use of explosives.
And now for assaulting
a police officer.
Drop the gun!
But what am I gonna do
with it? Here, you take it.
-I don't want it!
-Take it!
-Take the gun!
-I don't want it!
Thorne is getting away!
Come on!
Go after the lawyers!
Mr. Thorne!
We don't want
a criminal case!
Take it!
[shouting]
[man1] Thorne's never
gonna radio us.
[man 2] Yeah,
you're probably right.
[man 1] Let's start
cutting down some trees.
What do you think?
[man 3] We sat in these trucks
all day. We gotta do something.
[chainsaw snarl echoing]
[heroic music]
[grunting]
[yelps]
[screams]
[moaning]
[man] Let's get out of here!
[panting]
I heard someone.
[chuckles]
Need a hand?
Oh, that's nice.
Bad day?
You can't imagine
what kind of day I've had.
Wait a minute.
Aren't you that hippie?
I mean, the guy that gave
my boys a whip it, right?
Hey, no hard feelings,
alright?
[nervous laugh]
Look.
I gotta get over
this mountain over here.
I'll give you ten
thousand bucks
if you help me out.
-Why?
-What you mean why?
'Cause I guys chasing me,
that's guy.
Why are they chasing you?
Because I wanted to cut down
a few trees, OK?
Well, you almost
burn them down
when you were a kid...
Travis Thorne.
How did you know that?
I never told nobody that.
I know.
[chuckles]
It's true.
When I was a little tiny guy
I built this fire,
one as big as I could.
I mean, big fire.
And then it started spreading.
I didn't know what to do,
so I just took off,
running for home.
[laughs]
You know, to this day,
I never figured out
how I never burned down
this whole mountain.
I saved the forest
from your carelessness.
Now I'll save it
from your greed.
You kill me,
you know that?
[chuckles]
You just kill me.
Whoa!
You believed in the magic
of the mountain
when you were a kid.
That's... That's because
I was a kid.
I'm a grown up now, OK?
You wanna know the...
-[bone cracks]
-Oh...
...only magic I believe in?
It's the magic
of the almighty dollar.
How very sad.
Well, sad this!
[grunts]
[moaning]
[sighs]
Yes, very sad.
That the only dreams
you believe in
are the ones
that you can buy.
That's the only kind
there are.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Well, there's nothing
I can do to change your mind.
[deep voice]
But maybe I can.
[growling]
Oh...!
Wow...!
[muffled laugh]
Oh...
-[roaring]
-[screaming]
Help!
[screaming, grunting]
Hi. I just had a vision.
I feel reborn.
You know, I love everything.
I love the forest, the trees,
the eagles, the bears,
especially the bears.
I love bears.
I know I'm gonna have
to spend some time,
but it really doesn't matter.
[giggles]
I'm so happy I could sing.
I love this land!
From the rainwood forest
I feel love just
flowing through me.
Hi. I've been reborn.
You never seen a bear
that talks, did you? Ever?
[chuckles]
I don't know,
I love these trees.
Don't put me
in the cell with the rest.
They're crazy. Please!
[chattering overlapping]
-[Madison] You saw a wolf?
-[guys] Yes! Yes!
I'd like you to wear
this again, Arlen.
If you feel
you're ready for it.
[Madison] Yeah, alright.
I'd like that, Blaine.
[Madison] Tell me what?
Tell me what?
Thanks.
It looks good
on you, Daddy.
-I love you.
-I love you, too.
Come to me.
[huffing]
[chattering overlapping]
Stretch your hands
right up.
[Madison] Down!
Easy.
-No, I can't...
-[Logan] Get in here.
-You know, it's kinda cool.
-Yeah!
[Lewis] Hey,
how's it going?
-[kids laughing]
-[Barney] No, boys!
[whining]
[man] Come on, Brian!
[cheering]
He did find her!
He did find his wife!
What are you
talking about?
Never mind.
♪ Where the bees are buzzing
And the skies are blue ♪
♪ No more troubles
For me and you♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ Where it ain't no crime
To love the sunshine ♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ Down by the river
Where the breeze is cool ♪
♪ We'll all get together
And act like fools ♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ Yeah, in the summertime
♪ Where it ain't no crime
To love the sunshine ♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ That's right!
♪ Well, look at little Esther
She's all grown up ♪
♪ Now here comes, my boys,
She ain't giving it up ♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ Where it ain't no crime
To love the sunshine ♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ That's right!
♪ Where sunsets are seeing
But it's not one in mind ♪
♪ 'Cause the good Lord said
Come on and drink the wine ♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ Yeah, in the summertime
♪ Where it ain't no crime
To love the sunshine ♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ One more time!
♪ Yeah! In the summertime
♪ Ooh! In the summertime
♪ Where it ain't no crime
To love the sunshine ♪
♪ In the summertime
♪ Yeah, in the summertime
♪ Yeah! In the summertime
♪ When it ain't no crime
To love the sunshine ♪
♪ In the summertime