And now it's time for Political Jeopardy!.
From Washington DC we have Frank. Frank is
the manager of a spy shop and a conspiracy
buff. Next to him is Natalie from Seattle.
She is an elementary school drama teacher
and aspiring playwright. And from Philadelphia,
Pennsylvania our returning champion Jerry.
Jerry is a veterinarian and a producer of
his very own cable access show. And now it's
time to meet our host. Here's Sid.
Hey! How you doing! All right ladies and gentlemen,
we've got one hell of a show tonight. The
object of the game is to collect as many Prozac
tablets as you possibly can by giving the
correct responses to the questions on the
board. Please remember to phrase your responses
in question form. Are you ready? Fantastic!
Okay! Tonight's categories are: censored words,
communicable diseases, crooked politicians,
conspiracies, constitutional calamities, and
corporate cons. Let's get started. Jerry as
a returning champion you make the first selection.
Can I have censored words for one tablet please.
You sure can. A word placed on the tombstones
of 16th century prostitutes.
What is fuck.
That is correct! All right, please make another
selection.
Communicable diseases for one tablet please.
This device can give you over 90% protection
from STDs and unwanted pregnancies.
What is a vibrator.
IÕm sorry that's incorrect. Frank.
What is it was a condom.
That is correct. Please make another selection.
I would like to take five tablets of conspiracy,
Sid.
Oh wow looky here, Frank, you lucky dog. You
have found today's daily dosage. That enables
you to take any or all of your Prozac tablets.
Since you only have one, you can wager up
to five.
I want to take them all.
Frank I like your style. For five tablets,
they have implanted a recording device in
your filling to monitor your every move.
Who are the space aliens.
You need to be more specific.
Who is the federal government.
That is correct, Frank. You have earned todayÕs
daily dosage. Katie go on over there and medicate
him. Oh this is fantastic. This has been such
an exciting show. Congratulations Frank. Ladies
and gentlemen, that's all the show we have
for you tonight, but please tune in next time
for celebrity political jeopardy where our
guests will be Don Knotts, Malachi from children
of the corn, and Molly Ringwald. Be there!.
Okay you guys we are live in three. Three,
two É.
We're back.
We'd like to get serious for a moment and
remember our dear friend and political activist
Abbey Archer who passed away this week.
You are like clairvoyant and it's freaking
me outÉ.
Tell me why you're opposing the prayer in
schools initiative.
Well uh first of all you have to understand
that there's a great many people who actually
believe that the world was created in seven
days because it says so in the bible. Now
my aunt Sadie on the other hand, bless her
soul, she was a devout Christian É she told
me that Jesus had apparently come to her in
a dream and Jesus clued her in that it was
actually Satan the great deceiver who had
written the bible in order to dupe people
into leading a life of sin all the while thinking
they were serving the lord.
That's brilliant.
Hey everyone's entitled to their opinion right
which is one of the great things about this
country. And the reason we're fighting the
initiative is a big part of keeping our freedom
of thought comes from separating church and
state.
Brilliant. Abbey Archer.
And finally we take you out to the grassy
knoll for our conspiracy of the week.
An ultra right-wing paramilitary group is
believed to be secretly assassinating political
activists with a microwave assassination device.
IÕll see you burn in hell for that.
No Frank no they did not move the furniture.
Yes they did. Komodo dragons.
Nobody moved the furniture. Guys that was
a great show. Abbey wouldÕve been proud.
How awesome was political jeopardy.
Oh man was that funny and with the Prozac
É Katie that was a great idea.
Hey Frank what's up with that conspiracy man.
Oh yeah I think that was a little over the
top.
A little over the top? Did the Indians get
blankets infected with smallpox? No, no it's
just the beginning. It's a postage stamp in
the bigger picture. The truth is that the
US government was blackmailed into giving
them the formula for the weapons version of
the device because they were threatening to
bring David Koresh out of hiding. He's alive.
Really?.
No shit.
There's a fine line between conspiracy and
insanity.
I saw that.
Can you explain the two Darrens on bewitched.
Guys, Natalie and I are going to nudestock
this weekend. Anybody want to go?.
Me É I want to go.
Going to be a nude dude. Frank?.
Um when is it going to be?.
Saturday É Saturday I have to work É I
have to work.
Katie?.
Um oh look you guys Eat MeÕs on. No seriously
these kids are outrageous.
Caller, you there. Do you have a topic for
us.
Yeah. Why isn't the smart ass little kid in
school.
It's night time. School's over dumb shit.
So why don't you take your phone and stick
it up your ass.
Yeah eat me. Caller let's hear it.
I want to know how old you two are.
Listen Moses, you can take your age and stick
it up your ass!.
I love public access.
Wildlife is important for healthy forests
and wetlands which in turn provide us with
clean air and water.
Then why isn't the government doing more to
protect the environment?
Greed. The blind search for profit. And if
we don't do something about it now one day
soon we might be an endangered species. First
the corporate machine will build over our
forests, and then they'll pollute our food
and water, then we will all experience a slow
and agonizing death.
Hello Mrs Dickman.
Hello children. Ms. Wright I'd like to speak
with you.
Keep rehearsing guys.
People tell me that this play you're putting
on is heavy-handed.
Who who?.
That's not important. Also, parents are complaining
about your television show.
Who who?.
That's confidential. Just remember Ms. Wright,
we're watching you.
Why are we subjecting ourselves to this?.
It's only once a year. I mean even Hitler
had a birthday.
Actually Hitler did not have a birthday. He
was genetically engineered.
Who told you that?.
Frank.
Figures. Now you be good.
Door's open. Welcome to the house of the lord.
Mary, Mary, Mary, it is so nice to see you
my darling.
It's Natalie dad. You know that.
I believe on my birthday, in my house, I should
be allowed to call my daughter by her Christian
name.
Don't start with me dad.
What's new Mr. Wright?.
The lord's work is never done. There's always
something new young man. Come to my study
I'll tell you all about it. Dinner will be
served soon. Gerald wipe your feet.
My name is Jerry sir.
How nice for you. Oh you shouldn't have gotten
me É something so small. No that's very
charming. Thank you. Yes, yes, yes. Well,
wel,l well. Praise the lord. Gerald you know
I was once a young man like you.
That is hard to believe sir.
Gerald let me get right to the point. You've
been dating Mary for some two years now, I
thought it was time that we talked about her
future and whatever plans you might have together.
Well we're very interested in the future and
that's why we're working to make a difference.
Running an animal shelter and making home
videos with your pals doesn't exactly provide
the kind of security and wealth that my daughter
will require to raise a family.
Daddy I'm not a child.
I've been talking to my people and we thought
this would be an appropriate time to offer
you a position at my network.
Can we change the subject dad?.
Distilled water?.
Please.
Gerald?.
Sure.
So what have you two kids been up to lately?.
The funniest thing happened. Last weekend
we decided to do a piece for the show on this
festival É.
What?.
It wasn't that funny.
What are you hiding?.
I'm not hiding anything.
Then tell me what you did last weekend.
All right fine. We went to nude stock, the
all-nude festival, but it was so cold that
everyone had to wear clothes.
A school teacher cannot be seen at a nudie
carnival. This is a horrible example for children.
Does Mrs. Dickman know about this.
To hell with Mrs. Dickman, Natalie can do
what she wants on her own time.
Profanity is the language of Satan and Satan
does not dine in my house.
Well that's good because I heard Satan has
lousy tables.
Oh you make light of Satan. SatanÕs wine
is the poison of dragons and the cruel venom
of asps.
You forced me to tell you the goddamn story.
Oh Mary that language will not be tolerated.
My name is not Mary. ItÕs Natalie for ChristÕs
sakes after mom - not after some mythological
virgin. I lost my virginity at that bible
camp you sent me to when I was 12.
No! I won't listen to these lies. Leave now!.
Come on Jer.
It's been real,.
God help you, you will both surely rue this day.
Hello there. I'm Anita Deal and I am incredibly
excited to bring you this revolutionary tool
in perception. V-vision! Right now we're going
to meet the inventor of V-vision, Dr Veil.
Dr Veil if everybody already has a V chip
to filter out filthy programming in their
TVs why do they need these incredibly attractive
designer glasses.
Well Ms. Deal that's a very good question.
After years of extensive research at the Baktali
Institute of Technology of Research, we have
ascertained that most Americans don't watch
television 24 hours a day. Now we've created
V-vision and the way it works is that it blocks
out what's happening in everyday life É the
ghettos, the crime, and the criminals. And
what it does is instead of that you would
see a beautiful, peaceful and surreal images
that lull the viewer into a trance-like euphoric
state. You are a beautiful woman.
Oh! Now we're going to hear from some of our
incredibly satisfied customers.
Make love to me in the weirdest way.
Last week on my way to the market a dozen
bums asked me for change. This week with V-vision
I can't see or hear any of them.
My neighbor is a homicidal maniac who used
to keep me up at night killing his victims.
But not anymore because I have V-vision and
it is helping me to block things out so I
can get the rest that I need.
It's like É this is bad É these are boss
specs.
Without V-vision you are faced with the poverty,
violence, and pornography of the world around
you. But put on a pair of V-vision designer
glasses and everything becomes clean and pure.
V-vision É using yesterday's ignorance to
shape tomorrow's world. Oh sheeba shabba looba
doo bah doo wah É.
Katie, what's going on?.
I didn't do that. I don't I don't know.
Jerry, they're shutting us down.
What's going on.
You must leave immediately.
You can't get away with this you son of a
bitch.
How can you do this to your own daughter?.
You think you can silence us like this? You
think you can stop us?.
I am silencing you heathen. Thou shalt no
longer infect the minds of children against
everything this country stands for.
We are everything this country stands for
you jackass like freedom of speech, equality
before the law, the right to be who you want
to be.
If you do this dad I won't ever talk to you
again.
You are no longer my daughter Natalie. I disown
you. Disownership papers. You can leave now
or face arrest, and please take this band
of sinners with you.
Move out.
Everyone go limp.
Bobby, there's got to be something we can
do.
I'm telling you guys it's vile, disgusting,
horrible, and violates all norms of civilized
society, but it is completely legal. Cable
companies are permitted to direct public access
stations to other uses if they are quote not
well utilized.
Capitalism run amok.
This is no coincidence. This guy wrote the
playbook for the new world order.
What about getting a new public access station.
Until the city finds another contractor we're
screwed.
When's that gonna be?.
Who knows? It's a bureaucracy. They specialize
in getting nothing done especially if there's
no public outcry. Anger is the only thing
they respond to. I remember standing at the
barricades, facing down the man. We were united.
It had an impact. We made a difference.
That's it! WeÕve got to get everybody from
the station to band together and we're going
to go down there and we're going to voice
our anger as one.
Oh Jerry this protest sucks! it's a joke!
We got no grassroots organization, no financial
backing, no direction, no nothing.
Do you have any idea what the chlorine gas
released from that tub does to the ozone layer?.
Listen up granola head. This is a free country.
Hey lady, why don't you stick a green thumb
up your ass.
There will be no freedom in this country as
long as we have bimbos like you perpetuating
female stereotypes that reek of sexual servitude
to a patriarchal society.
Go fuck yourself you feminazi.
You get out of the water!.
How long are you people on public access going
to allow yourselves to be the uncle toms of
the corporate media elite?.
Right now! Right now! You want some of this?.
Katie stop it.
Hey everybody itÕs the press! Shut up!.
This party blows. I'm outta here.
Stick this protest up your ass.
Yeah eat me. Nice kick, Eddie.
Jer, you okay?.
I used to like that kid.
LetÕs go, Jer. We're just torturing ourselves.
WeÕll get our message out.
The lord giveth and the lord taketh away.
Blessed be the powers of the lord.].
You're right, Natalie. We haven't gotten our
message out. WeÕre going to fight this thing.
We're gonna be heard if we have to take it
down the city hall.
Well, well, well. If it isnÕt the freak
show! Well you'll be happy to hear that I'm
filing the ReverendÕs plans to upgrade Christian
Unity Network Television's newest station.
What a stupid bunch of losers. Why donÕt
you do something with your lives. I am sick
of paying taxes so you lazy bums can sit around
all day playing counter culture. Get a job!
Have a family! Produce anything! Just get
out of my way. Maybe theyÕll beat some sense
into you!.
This is just one day out of our lives.
Please just keep your voices down. They're
watching us. WeÕre under surveillance.
Jer, how the hell are we gonna get out of
here?.
Honey, Bobby will do something.
What if they've gotten to Bobby? What if Bobby's
been bought off? What if no one knows we're
in here? What if we never get out of here?.
This is the price that we pay for challenging
the tyranny of illegitimate authority.
Frank, we're gonna get out of here.
How do you know that?.
Cause we have to get out of here.
Frank mellow out. You're paranoid and you're
bumming everybody out.
Jerry you think I'm paranoid.
Frank you thought that Jerry Garcia was with
the DEA.
Yeah so?.
Frank you thought they were aiming a ray gun
into your bedroom window to make you weak
when you just had the flu.
I never get the flu. How do you explain that?.
Stop.
Hey I know you! YouÕre the TV guys. YouÕre
on that cable show..whaddaya call it? YouÕre
on right before those Ôstick it up your
assÕ kids, right?.
ÒEat Me.Ó.
Fuck you. ThatÕs not it. Your show is...
Anarchy TV.
That's it! I love your show. That special
report you did on the rubber gloves has definitely
saved me a disease or two. Oh and you have
that crazy guy with all the paranoid conspiracy
theories.
IÕm not paranoid.
ItÕs him! ItÕs him! I love you. You are
the greatest.
First time in huh?.
Hey why donÕt you take your hands off him.
Hey what's your fuckinÕ problem, Joe!.
Guard!.
Buzz off Tiffany! I don't need your mouth.
Listen fat ass boy. I'm not scared of you.
Now let the nut go.
Stop, stop, stop, stop. The machine has us
fighting against each other. They love it
when we fight each other because when we fight
each other we're not fighting them. Can't
you see? They're watching us right now. They're
laughing at us. We're caged down here like
a bunch of animals. Look we don't even have
a toilet. Do you guys have toilet paper? The
ladies don't even have toilet paper. You know
what that is? That is cruel and unusual punishment.
Cruel and unusual punishment. You know what
cruel and unusual punishment means? Our eighth
amendment rights as American citizens are
being violated. Your eighth amendment rights
as an American citizen are being violated.
But rights are not just established by words.
No. They are won and they are sustained by
struggle, and right now we have got to struggle
together to get our freedom. We want our freedom
now. We want our freedom now! We want our
freedom now! We want our freedom now! We want
our freedom now! We want our freedom now!
We want our freedom now! .
You guys are going to be here a long time.
How do you know that? .
Enough Frank.
Do you have any idea how bad it smells in
there?.
I have the play at school.
Bobby, you couldn't dig the money up anywhere?.
I'll see what I can do, but Jerry all your
friends are broke including me. And Natalie's
father doesn't want to have anything to do
with her.
We're prepared to do whatever it takes, Bobby.
Have you tried the vet?.
Your bailÕs been posted.
What?.
I posted your bail. You're free to go.
Really?.
Yes! You guys inspired me so much. Anyone
who can make that animal Joe stand up for
anything deserve my support. Besides I just
want to be on your show. I think you guys
are the greatest.
As soon as we get our show back you got it.
We get it back. Let's get out of here!.
All right!.
Here's to Tiffany.
Be careful with that, please.
What is this Frank?.
Oh um this is a uh miniature uh Spy Con É let
go I'll show you É Spy Con high fidelity
bug and tap detector with this super multiplexing
mil-spec cable descrambler.
Can you get cable?.
Sure, sure I can. I'll show you. Look out,
Jerry. Channels galore.
Wait, wait. Go back.
We can not sit back my friends while SatanÕs
message devours É.
Turn it up!.
Change it!.
Honey I want to see what MussoliniÕs broadcasting
from our station.
And we must not glamorize, no, we must not
celebrate the notion of pornography. I said
pornography, and I whisper pornography like
the dirty little shameful secret it is. Though
some would shout sodomy, some would shout
fornication, some shout pornography from the
little devil's box that we must eradicate
one channel at a time going click hallelujah,
click praise the lord, until the devil's message
is gone from our lives.
Just when he was getting to the good part.
I've had a lifetime of that crap, I can't
take any more.
What's going on?.
That's her father.
I'm sorry baby he's such an asshole.
Yeah he is.
You know in my day we wouldn't take this sitting
down.
Oh no, no, wait, wait. I just got out of jail.
I can't hear this.
No, no, no. We would organize. We would build
momentum. We would be deaf to their lies and
blind to their illusions. We would cut ourselves
free from the strings that jerk us like puppets
and we would create our own destiny. We would
achieve justice by all means necessary. By
all means necessary.
Right on man!.
I've got it. I got it.
Time to see what the good word is tonight.
You are watching God's station. Praise the
Lord. Hallelujah! And now for the Countdown
to Armageddon!.
This is the kind of television people want
to see.
Count your blessings and say your prayers,
because the times are changing, the signs
are there. It's plain as day I'm sure you'll
agree, that the world will soon be history.
What are you doing? We all agreed no guns.
Katie IÕm so sorry. I fell.
What were you thinking?.
What if they shoot at us?
These are very dangerous people.
Then you get to die for the cause, Frank.
ItÕs just a scratch, Katie.
You guys still want to do this?.
LetÕs do this.
Bingo.
Hey listen I don't know you, and I don't have
any gripe with you man, but I have been censored,
abused and imprisoned all because of your
boss and at this point I'm ready to blow this
place sky high so I suggest you leave right
now.
Jedi mind trick you will let us pass.
Buying that station was the best investment
I ever made.
Coming up next is the personal tale of revelation
that will forever change the way that you
look at your television set. For God's sakes
stay tuned.
Okay world you are watching Anarchy TV. We
are reclaiming this station to assert our
constitutional right to free speech. We start
broadcasting now. Power of the people!.
Harry what is this? Is this a joke? .
No this is no joke. Everybody just stay calm.
If you cooperate you will not be hurt. I want
everyone to make their way out to the lobby
right now. Come on preacher man.
I'm not going anywhere. I refuse to be intimidated
by every young person that straps some dynamite
to their chest.
Fine. Let's take them into the control room and tie him up.
Everybody else make your way out to the lobby.
Sweetheart you're in charge.
Let's redecorate.
Don't worry about it Reverend. We've got it
covered.
This must be kept quiet Chief Cochon. You
keep the police away.
You got it Reverend Wright.
And if anybody from the press calls stonewall
them. I don't want those little punks, those
delinquents to get one bit of attention.
Whatever you say Reverend.
All right. I'm glad I can count on a good
God-fearing man like yourself Chief.
Of course Reverend. And I look forward to
seeing you at the charity bake and bowl next
week.
Oh thank you goddess.
You are watching Anarchy TV. We have seized
control of this station to protest the sale
of our public access channel to a private
company. Without access to the means of communication
our constitutional right to free speech is
just an empty promise. We are going to hold
on to this station until public access TV
is rightfully restored to the people. We'll
be right back.
Sound volume's high and I'm losing the signal
on the remote feeds here.
I'm working on it Katie.
The people that control organized religions
don't want it known that the divine power
and the ultimate wisdom is not in a church
but inside each human being.
They bought it.
I told you they would. Suicide bomber costumeÕs
our biggest seller.
Is everything secure?
Jerry nothing's ever really secure.
That's good. You just put your paranoia to
good use.
I'm not paranoid.
I knew it!
Hi! I'm Reverend profit and I'm unbelievably
happy to see you. I've successfully started
over 25 religions and with my new home video
so can you. By the time you finish my course
you're going to think you're the big guy himself.
Should we get that mother?.
Harold, what would we do with our own religion?.
I'm going to show you how you can both write
and interpret scripture to suit your own needs,
and if you order right now I'm going to throw
in my own patented demonic adversary to explain
away any flaws in your belief system. It's
the best deal in the universe. Order now.
What's the situation Greed?.
Jerry you there?.
What's up, Frank?.
The Reverend has arrived.
They have implemented the emergency defense
system sir. That place is pretty much impregnable.
They're also broadcasting live. Oh yeah and
they're holding Mr. Arnold as a hostage.
All I know is God's station is not on the
air right now.
Probably, but they can't hear us. We didn't
get the mics operational yet.
What about the safe?.
100% secure. That is the same safe the desert
storm plans were held in at the NSA.
The men are in position to shut off the power
whenever you're ready sir.
Emergency power?
Doesn't matter. If the power goes off even
for a second the computer goes down and they
won't be able to transmit any signal.
Jerry they're going to cut the power. YouÕve
got to meet me in the basement.
Any second now sir.
Frank where are you?
Back here.
Ready sir.
Whenever you're ready, Reverend.
Okay you have to turn on the emergency power
at the exact same time that i turn off the
main power. You got it?
I got it.
On three.
Three two one .
Frank! You okay. Oh man I'm sorry buddy. Talk
to me Frank.
I know who had the Kennedys killed .
We'll get them another way, Reverend.
How can you work for that guy Clarence? Do
you know anything about him? There has been
article after article written about how rotten
he is. He thinks that women are second-class
citizens. He thinks that homosexuals should
be executed. And he's a racist.
Doesn't that bother you? I mean you're an
African American.
What does the color of my skin have to do
with anything? If the Reverend was a racist,
he never would have hired me.
Oh, Clarence you cannot be that na•ve.
Oh lord.
Hi I'm Natalie. Here's your safe sex tip.
It is important to remember that when using
a dildo, one must treat it exactly like a
penis and put a condom on it. Especially when
it's used by multiple partners.
Turn that execration off. Take out the dish,
Greed.
We canÕt sir. You had it fortified in case
the feds ever pulled a Waco on us. But their
power will run out in less than 24 hours so
all we have to do is wait.
Don't tell me to wait. Ollie told me you were
the best. I want them off my station now.
Yes sir.
All right love birds we are live in three.
Three, twoÉ
Hi guys I figured I could be the most help
here with you two.
I'm sure you could be É
We are live you guys.
We already worked something out.
That's okay I'm great at improvising. Watch
this. Hi I'm Tiffany. I'm here with the cast
of Anarchy TV. We all met in jail. It was
my 18th bust for solicitation. Can you believe
prostitution is illegal? I thought this was
a capitalist country. If some horny bastard
wants to pay me a hundred bucks so he can
jerk off all over my face who the hell is
government to interfere in my business?
Right on! Absolutely right. Who are they to
interfere in her business? That's very É thank
you for the vivid introduction Tiffany. It's
true we didn't meet in jail. We were arrested
for protesting the elimination of our public
access to television. Right now we are looking
for your support. We want to know what you
are thinking about the importance of free
speech. Please give us a call at 555 oh one
69 and talk to us. Tell us what you think
of free speech. Call us.
We have a call.
Great go ahead. Caller hello.
Uh yeah I tried calling that number to order
the instructional video you advertised, but
I kept getting the suicide hotline.
Oh, uh that was a parody.
They're taking a call sir.
They have callers. Turn it on.
The commercial was not real. We were making
fun of religious hucksters like Reverend Wright.
People who prey on poor unsuspecting folks.
Cut them off.
My wife and I both want to say that we think
Tiffany's doing a great job filling in for
Clarence.
Hello caller. Hello.
The phones are dead.
Frank where are you man. Frank, Frank, you
there? The phone's dead man.
Yeah Jerry. Give me a minute and I'll patch
in my cell phone.
Okay cool.
Boy that Frank is good. He could steal the
cherry from a 90 year old nun.
Let's go to tape.
I'm Sorely Reefer and sitting across from
me is the Unabonger, a man who has been terrorizing
DEA agents by sending them filthy bongs resulting
in a mandatory five-year prison sentence for
receiving drug paraphernalia in the mail.
Unabonger, tell me, when all the smoke clears,
what do you want to have happen.
Well Regis, I want people to realize that
the war on drugs is not a war on drugs, it's
a war on people. That's what I want.
But aren't you in the process violating and
victimizing innocent people?
Why yes I am Regis, but desperate times they
call for desperate measures. Did you know
that over 1,000 people a day are arrested
on marijuana charges, 80 percent of those
are for possession alone. There are people
serving life sentences. There are over a hundred
people on death row for pot. For pot. Pot.
It's insane Regis.
My name is Sorely.
Mr. Unabonger, what would make you consider
ending your campaign.
I would I would have to É I don't remember.
I don't remember. Would you like the best
cookie you have ever had?
No I would not like a cookie and I cannot
accept anything from a known felon. I am a
professional reporter.
They are scrumptious. My wife is Amish. Oh
yes. Oh yes. I am the cookie man people of
earth.
Hello I'm Candy Looney and I think that we
should take the idiot who invented the child
proof lighter, tie him to a stake, and then
let him starve to death while we try to light
him on fire with his goddamn contraption.
I mean these child-proof lighters they make
me so angry. I can light the American flag
on fire. I mean this makes me so angry IÕll
light my bra on fire.
Jerry you look really pretty in a dress.
Bobby, hi. Where is everybody? There's nobody
here. Where are the cops? Where's the press?
Nobody even wants to bust us?
I don't understand it, Jer. I've called everybody.
Maybe Frank was right. Maybe there is a big
media conspiracy. Maybe nobody gives a damn.
What are the ratings?
What are the ratings man?
Well if that was an EKG we'd be dead.
Maybe you better call Dr Kevorkian.
And let him know we got less than 20 hours
of power left.
I heard that. Look IÕll work on it and get
back to you. Try to think of something to
get some attention.
Later man.
Later.
What'd Bobby say?
He's got no idea.
I do. Clearly this is coming down from central
command Jerry.
Frank please not now. Please.
Okay. I'm sorry. The Reverend was really worried
about that safe, Jerry. There's something
in there. I know it.
Can you get it open.
Yes. It's going to take a few hours. It's
very heavy duty stuff. Used by all the big
boys. I mean it's incredible Jerry. They've
got everything. They're ready for Armageddon
in here.
You're doing a great job, man, a great job.
Thanks.
Can you give me a little volume on this?
Our operators are standing by we won't start
the revolution without you. Come on guys we
need your help. We need you to become involved.
We have a new number. Frank's loaned us his
cellular it is 917-555-0101.
Did you hear that, Tiff.
Yes.
SheÕs got it. Call us. Even if you don't
want to call us, call us and tell us why you
don't want to call us.
We have a call.
Ah. Hello caller are you there?
WhoÕs this?
This is Anarchy TV who's this?
This is your mother Frank stop it with the
impersonations already. I'm not the FBI. Come
on Frankie I need your help. I'm hearing those
voices in my head again. I need you to come
over and sleep with me tonight.
Boy heÕs kinky too.
She's doing it to me again. Just like the
fifth grade.
Mrs Corder, I'm not Frank. I'm Frank's friend.
He loaned us his phone for the show. We're
live on the air.
Well then put Frank on.
Things are really kind of crazy right now.
Missy, I am not crazy. I want to speak to
my Frankie.
Mrs. Corder you wait right there. Frank's
gonna call you okay.
At least their ratings are no better than
ours, Reverend. Let's just hope they keep
this guy's mother on the line all night.
What about tomorrow, Greed? What about tomorrow?
Well now it's nine minutes after the hour,
and I'm wondering where you are America. What
happened to the spirit of revolution? You
know give me liberty or give me death. Having
the right to speak your mind freely that's
the very foundation of democracy. I need you
to call me. I need to know that you care.
You guys we have a call.
We have a call.
Is it Frank's mom again?
Go ahead, caller.
Jerry it's me Bobby.
Bobby. Katie can we go to tape.
Go ahead Bobby.
No complaint has been filed with the police.
As far as the press goes the Reverend has
apparently told him that you're an experimental
program to promote the Christian Unity Network's
new youth missionary movement.
You're kidding right.
No fucking way.
He's putting us in the missionary position.
Welcome to cross burning. Today we debate
the allocation of penal resources. More people
are behind bars in America than in any other
country in the world. Is it a new growth industry
or just another huge welfare program? Joining
us today are on the left Duke David, and on
the right Lenny Speer. Duke you're first.
Thank you, maÕam. Let me tell you a little
story. Prisons are like another big brother.
An expensive government handout to the scum
of America. Now when I think of America, I
think of the cream of the crop the cream that
rises to the top and that cream is white.
Let me tell you something else. It's time
those people started paying their way. We
could have an army of worker slaves that make
them goddamn Chinese green with envy. I'm
talking about making them make everything.
Think of the profits. Pie in the sky-high
profits.
Duke, Duke, Duke. YouÕre such a bleeding
heart liberal. Haven't we learned our lesson.
Concentration camps never work. To engineer
the perfect society, the solution is always
extermination.
Let's go to commercial.
Fucking machine ripped me off again. Sid,
change please. Anybody have any change.
Sorry Katie.
I'm starving.
I could use some food.
Yeah I'm starving too. Open it Frank. You
could steal a turd outta my ass and I wouldn't
even know it.
Property is theft.
Christ we're off the air.
Who's on tape control?
Shit, that's me. Sorry.
What's the point? Nobody's watching.
Why don't you lighten up Katie.
You know I'm not gonna listen to you and nobody
else is.
Stop it. Stop it. WeÕve dealt with bad ratings
before. Come on guys. Why did we take over
the station? ItÕs something that we all
agreed on. You know we wanted to question
authority, we wanted to challenge injustice,
we wanted to take a stand, we wanted to expose
the naked truth.
Yeah! If we all went to naked we'd get some
serious ratings.
Uh Tiffany, hi. Thank you. It's about liberation
not exploitation.
Katie, nudity doesn't necessarily involve
exploitation. There's nothing shameful about
the naked body.
Yeah, it's a first amendment issue. It's like
our safe sex tips.
All rights guys. Let's do it.
You can't be serious.
We can't go naked. Nobody gets to see me naked.
I've never seen me naked. No naked.
I bet you look great, Frank.
How could you advocate selling out to the
methods of mainstream media manipulation?
Whoa nude anarchists. Stop the presses. I
wonder what they have to say? Who cares? They're
naked.
Right.
Katie, we have no time. Nobody's watching.
It's not what we planned, but it is a revolutionary
statement. What would you do to get people
to watch?
Yeah Tiffany's right. We have got to do something
to just get people's attention.
Fuck it.
She's got balls.
Jerry do something.
It's totally voluntary. Sid fire up the cameras.
WeÕre going live.
Oh my God. Are they gone?
Yeah they're gone.
Oh my God.
Sir, sir, sir. Sir, I think you need to see
this.
As you can see weÕve decided to give you
the naked truth. Uncensored. I think it was
Mark Twain who said ÒNature knows no indecency.
Man invents them.Ó
Let this be just another nightmare.
Mother, these people are naked.
No they're not.
Their headlights are on high beam.
Women in those cultures are forced to wear
veils. In America nudity is considered obscene
which is just as selective of behavior.
The Reverend sure has taken this station in
a new direction.
Hey, get out of the way.
We were all born naked into the world, and
it's only a warped, puritan ideology that
tells people that their natural form is in
some way obscene. Shame is just another tool
that is used to control who you think.
Hey guys Tiffany's on television. Holy shit,
theyÕre naked!
Ultimately it's about freedom and it's about
liberty.
Yes it is Jer.
Great.
Right.
We are really tense our energy is low we need
to exercise, and I just happen to be a certified
aerobics instructor.
What is she doing?
I don't know.
Come on guys I'm telling you. You will feel
great. Sid crank up the music!
All right Tiffany.
No. Go back. Go back.
Come on guys. Come on get over here.
What is she doing?
It's called aerobics and yeah do it to get
fit. I need to get that switched.
Come on guys!
Come on, letÕs go out there. Seriously,
letÕs do it.
Are you high?
Please feel free to join us home. You will
feel great. Go ahead. Just take all your clothes
off and start moving. You will feel great.
Finally entertainment for the entire family.
Would you look how quickly the revolution
is co-opted. Now we're being led by a naked
aerobics instructor.
Katie, if a revolution falls in the forest
and no one hears it, is it still a revolution?
Yes it is Sid. It is a pure revolution. It
is a revolution with meaning and values. Not
this.
Let's give it some meaning. Let's use a blue
screen and we'll key in some political images
and whatever we have. Let's just find something
crazy.
I cannot believe IÕm doing this.
You see how much better that is. Clarence,
you like that don't you?
What are you doing mother?
OhÉ
Look out! YouÕll poke your eye out.
ItÕs wonderful. Wonderful. Freedom. Freedom.
You sure can cut a rug mother.
Yes Milton I had one of my famous chats with
her. That's right. Sometimes teachers just
need to be made aware of the influence that
they have on children. That's right. Okay
well don't worry about it we won't be having
any more problems with her. All right now.
Bye-bye. Christ!
The last flight of the nut bird. Hey.
Officer Sweitzer, how can I help you? Uh-huh.
Naked people on your TV. Why didn't you just
turn
the channel? Uh-huh. All right. Yeah. We're
on it.
What?
Some wacko says his daughter got possessed
by satanic messages from naked people on TV.
What channel?
Channel 169.
This footage reminds me of how fragile our
freedoms really are in this society. I mean
if this can happen to you at any time or at
any place how can you say that you're truly
free.
What the fuck is this?
This is Anarchy TV. Are you guys dancing out
there?
Hi I'm Susannah smart and I'm coming to you
live from outside the studios of channel 96
where a naked religious cult has seized control
of the station in protest of poor cable service.
Jerry it's show time.
Look at that.
This is great.
Okay.
You should never underestimate the power of
nudity, Katie.
Excuse me officer, I'd like to drive through.
I'm the attorney for the group that's taken
over the station.
Out of the car slowjam. Do it!
What are you talking about? IÕm the lawyer
for the guys inside the station.
Out of the car midnight. Don't make me use
this. Do it!
You're interfering with the most important
act of civil disobedience since the levitating
of the pentagon.
Lord, why hast thou forsaken me.
Reverend is it true that a revolutionary group
called Anarchy TV has taken control of your
station and taken hostages?
Yes unfortunately that is true. These heathens
have stolen my station in order to spread
their doctrine of pornographic filth.
Let's see what the coverage is like.
Ébroadcasting an experimental program to
promote the Christian Unity Network's new
youth missionary movement. What about that
Reverend?
No, that's ridiculous.
Well maybe this tape will jog your memory.
Reverend, Is it true that your daughter is
one of the people in there?
I don't have a daughter.
This just in. We have obtained exclusive footage
of the naked protesters who have taken over
channel 69.
Why isn't she naked?
Be advised, some of this footage might not
be suitable for children and sensitive viewers.
And now for the real news.
The government is stealing from you the corporations
are poisoning you and the media are lying
to you.
And now for the weather.
What is going on Cochon?
There was nothing I could do Reverend.
Well do something now. Look at those animals
parading naked on God's station.
We think it's a serious commentary on the
state of the media when you realize that we
took over this station last night and nobody
noticed until we took our clothes off and
now the whole world is tuning in.
We have a call from someone who claims to
be the police chief Jerry.
The police chief. Cool. Okay. I'm sure he's
his own man speaks his own mind. Put him through.
Hello.
Who am I speaking with?
This is police Chief Cochon, and I'm calling
to ascertain exactly what your demands are.
Well chief my name is Jerry, this is Natalie,
this is Tiffany. You're live on Anarchy TV,
and our demands are that a public access station
be made available to all the people, and we
want that in writing.
We want some pizza.
And we want to talk to our lawyer.
This type of fascist behavior will not intimidate
me. Nor will it weaken my resolve to confront.
And expose the abuse of power.
Things aren't going your way. I mean sometimes
the world can appear to be a really cruel
and unfair place.
Stop pandering to those little punks. They're
terrorists. Can't you see that? They're like
plagues of locusts. Listen to me you godless
heathens. You cannot steal God's station.
You will not spew forth venomous, vile, lewd,
licentious smut and get away with it.
Jerry we're gonna take the TV news signal
and go split screen with you and the Reverend.
Cool. Do it.
I'll get the camera.
Listen world. This guy is a greedy hate monger
who uses a religious veil to hide a multi-million
dollar business and propaganda machine designed
to enrich him at our expense. He disseminates
messages of hate. He shows a rampant disregard
for the poor in the downtrodden, and he was
an abusive father to the woman that I love,
Natalie.
You represent a failed counter culture society,
an ideology that has been responsible for
sexual disease, drug addiction, the decay
of the American family, the callous disregard
for the aged, for the unborn, and ultimately
it is you who will be responsible for the
moral decay of this great nation, the promotion
and the glorification of Satan.
There is no failed counter-culture ideology.
What there is is a group of greedy and selfish
individuals who have no regard for their fellow
human beings or the planet that we all live
on. People like you who promote a view of
the world in which we are all pitted against
each other in some kind of pathetic race for
profit and power. You know you're the one
who's immoral you are the one who glorifies
evil. With people like you taking over the
airwaves we might as well all just destroy
our TV sets. What's the point of having one?
You profit by painting a picture of the world
in which danger lurks behind every corner
and we are all powerless to make the world
a better place.
Poppa, what is he saying?
He has a good point, Mother.
The fact is that you think that freedom and
democracy are threats to be avoided and not
values to be preserved. That's the saddest
part.
Jerry!
What?
It's all true. It's all true. Everything.
Exactly like I said.
Frank I'm live. Please.
No Jerry! The microwave assassination device.
Exactly like I said. The victims, the operatives
for the Christian Supremacy Movement.
This is not the time for a conspiracy theory,
Frank.
This is not a theory. I got it out of the
safe. The Reverend's safe. Look AbbeyÕs
name is on the top of the list.
You can't be serious.
Jerry?
What?
YouÕve got to let me take this out there.
This is big. This is the summit of the mountain
I've been climbing my whole life. You gotta.
Okay. Go ahead. Frank is going to give evidence
that implicates Reverend right with this unbelievable
weapon.
Jeez.
It's lies. It's all lies.
This has gone too far shut him down now.
Relax Reverend they're gonna run out of power
soon enough.
DonÕt talk back to me. What do you think
I pay you for?
We can't go in there. The place is barricaded,
and they have a hostage.
Oh I don't give a soggy shit about that little
fuckhead, faggot, jungle bunny.
Oh my God.
See, I told you that guy was an evil son of
a bitch.
Katie, now is not the time. Clarence, weÕre
going to untie you.
Hey Reverend take a pass! Stick this station
up your ass! Hey Reverend take a pass! Stick
this station up your ass! Hey Reverend take
a pass! Stick this station up your ass! Hey
Reverend take a pass! Stick this station up
your ass!
Ébecause of their political beliefs. Because
they disagree with you. People who are trying
to make the world a better place.
Here's your happy juice, sir.
No. I don't want my medicine now. I want justice.
I want a pox on their homes.
Don't worry Reverend, you're gonna feel better
in a minute.
I hope so.
Stop him. Somebody stop him!
By violating my rights, you're participating
in your own oppression. Every time you silence
another voice, your own freedom of expression
is diminished.
Shut up! I don't need a lecture from you Mr.
Moon Cricket. Society pays me to rid the scum
like you off this planet. Okay. All right.
Hey that guy's throwing money. TheyÕre throwing
money.
Good morning world!
Atta boy, Frank. Way to go!
We kicked their ass! We got proof!
IÕll shoot your ass!
HeÕs got a gun!
Heathen!
I missed his dick.
What happened?
You got shot. You got shot. You're going to
be all right. Just hang in there. Just hang
in there. You're going to be alright. Don't
touch it. Don't touch it.
What the hell. He got me.
Call an ambulance!
Where's the ambulance!
This proves it. This proves everything.
Rotten machine.
CÕmon. Give me a hand. Put your shoulder
to it.
Hey where's the paramedic!
WhereÕs the medic?
No! No medic!
Why not?
No medic. Don't you leave me alone with them.
That's when they implant the chip.
Jerry this is not a real ambulance and those
are not real medics.