- We need to know what you know.
- It wasn't my op.
I have no intel.
- It wasn't authorized.
- No.
Why'd you call me here?
- Jeremy and Caleb
have disappeared.
As you can see,
they delivered an asset into
the hands of the Russians.
CIA contracted Anthony Greene
and his team to stop them.
- Reads like an ambush.
- Yeah, there was a shootout.
The asset got away.
We need to know everything
that they might have shared.
- What happened to
my father and Caleb?
- Caleb, he fled.
He went underground.
- My father?
- Greene reported that
your father went down,
but he had to remove
any dead and wounded
before anyone else arrived.
- Where's his body?
- I'm assuming the
Russians got him.
Perhaps Caleb came
back. I don't know.
The site was clean
once we arrived back.
As of 1800 hours last night,
their status has been
changed internally.
The CIA has deemed
them as traitors,
and they now have a
bounty on their head.
Their position with
this organization
has been forfeited
And anyone working with
them is now in question.
- Are you suggesting
that I'm a traitor?
- Within time, I'm sure you can
repair the damage
that's been done by...
Banshee, don't do this.
You're not an
enemy of the state.
- We both know that
Caleb and my father
were loyal to this organization.
- Well, in light of
this current situation,
I'm not really sure right now.
Don't do this!
- Take my name off your books.
I'm out.
And when I find out
what really happened,
I'll return for all of you
that left them out
there to fucking die.
- I got control of the cameras.
You're good to go.
In and out, just
like we planned.
There'll be two in the lobby.
- Any others?
- None visible.
Second set of elevators.
And your chariot is on its way.
- There's no way
those guys are Feds.
- Obviously, he knows
there's a price on his head.
- What the hell did
this guy do anyway?
- I'm the executioner,
not the judge.
- Damn it!
- Kronos?
- One second.
I'm having some
technical difficulty.
- Are they taking it back?
- No, no, no. Don't worry.
- I need to know. Am
I walking into a trap?
- No, it's just an
elevator. I wouldn't worry.
- Talk to me.
- All right, there's
one small thing.
- There's no such
thing as a small thing.
- I couldn't access the
camera on this floor.
- And?
- Ugh, someone's overriding
my control in the elevator.
- Do something.
- I can't!
- Well, well, well.
There she is.
Banshee...
You still going with that?
- Anthony Greene.
It's been a minute.
You took my kill.
You just cost me
a million dollars.
- No.
I didn't cost you a
penny, sweetheart.
In fact, I'm going to give
you the credit and the money.
And all you have to do is
hand over your boy Caleb.
Oh, man, you're still on that?
Really?
It's kind of sad,
don't you think?
- No, uh, I fucking don't.
'Cause every second
that I get closer
to that piece of shit
is a second well spent.
- Five years is kind of a
long time to track someone,
but a revenge killing is a
revenge killing, I guess.
- Uh-huh.
For what he did, I'm
going to take his life.
- Hmm.
We both know he's off the grid.
He's a fucking ghost.
- Yeah, he's a fucking ghost.
That's why you're the perfect
person to track him down.
- If I didn't know any better,
I would think that
you're too big of a pussy
to take me on one-on-one.
- Oh.
Shut the fuck up.
I ain't come here to play.
Banshee, do some thinking.
'Cause end of the day,
we both know how this
shit's going to end.
Don't we?
- I do.
Kronos, open the door!
- Opening elevator doors.
- Go!
- Kronos!
- I'm trying!
Got it.
- Walkie. She's
on her way down.
Do you hear me? She's
Move, move, move.
- I take it we're not
getting that 1 million.
- Not now.
- I really needed that money.
Door's about to
open. Are you ready?
- Fucking bring it.
How many?
- Two in the lobby.
Anthony's on the move.
I'm trying to stop him.
- Kronos, start the car now!
- Done.
What?
So one person did
all of this to us.
Who was she talking to?
- She called him Kronos.
- Go on this.
I wanna know who
he is, where he is.
I want my hands on him.
Clean this shite up.
- Well, that was fun, Banshee.
- Dude, I've told
you ten million times
do not call me that.
- How do you know
Anthony Greene?
- He's former Special Forces
who's made it his goal in life
to hunt down people for the CIA.
- So he's part of the Collective
and you want him dead?
- He killed someone
who's close to me.
- If he's an assassin, why
does he have so many guys?
- Because he's a fucking pussy,
and he knows I would kill him.
I need you to find
someone for me.
- That's what I'm here for.
- Find Caleb Navvaro.
- Are you serious?
Caleb Navvaro?
That's our target?
- Yes.
- We're talking about
the same Caleb Navvaro?
The one that trained
you and ran black ops?
- That's the one.
- D, there's a thousand
people named Caleb Navvaro.
If Greene couldn't find
him, there's no way I will.
He's been underground
for five years.
And we just lost out on
a whole lot of money.
Can we please just move
on to the next contract?
- We will not have
another shot at Anthony.
- Are you serious? It's
you versus a small army.
Please.
- I'm not letting him win again.
- You've seen the photographs.
Told you he's dead.
Listen, I want our money in my
account by the end of the week.
- Sir?
- No, as usual, it's a million.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, always a pleasure.
What?
- I've a lead on Kronos.
- And?
- Top-rate hacker.
Acts as a middle
man for Banshee.
Apparently, he's been her
eyes and ears for a few years.
- So where is he?
- I don't know yet.
- So find him,
and before sun up.
- All right, let's see
what the CIA has to say.
- If they knew
anything, he'd be dead,
and we would not be
having this conversation.
- Is this about
the traitor thing?
- Amongst other things, yes.
- The price on this
guy's head is 10 million.
- I know.
- And you didn't
kill him. Why?
- You don't understand.
Greene and Caleb are worth
so much fucking more
to me than 10 mil.
- All right.
Would you say you knew
him better than anyone?
- Yes.
Definitely.
- He had to slip
up at some point,
shared some kind of
info that could help us.
If you were Caleb,
where would you go?
He's from Chicago.
Would he go back?
- Nah, nah, nah, nah.
No, no, definitely not.
He'd gain too much
attention there.
- Favorite vacation
spots, friends, family,
something, let's... let's
work with something here.
- Wellburg. Check Wellburg.
- Where the hell is Wellburg?
- Jersey.
- All right, there's a few homes
that were purchased
five years ago.
Some businesses opened up too.
Barb's Hardware. We
have an Italian place.
And there's a bar
named Old Well Tavern.
That's it, that's it!
Old Well Tavern, that's it.
- Old Well Tavern, It's
owned by Walter Herrero.
Looks like Mr. Herrero
bought the house and bar
about three years ago.
- Mm.
Lay low for two years,
start a new life.
That's fucking
him. Take me there.
- Update the GPS.
This is what I call a game.
Players who can actually play.
- It's a rerun, Rick.
- Still.
You know what I'm saying, right?
Our team can't stay healthy,
and our bullpen sucks.
- Ugh.
I can't see that
changing any time soon.
Imagine if we got some decent
pitching like those guys.
- Hmm.
- We'd be a ball club
worth playing against.
Ah! Another shot.
What was the, uh, home team
where you come from again?
Laredo, right?
- Nuevo Laredo,
across the river.
- Mm.
Do you run a tavern there too?
- You always drink this
much at 10:00 a.m.?
- Kronos?
I'm here.
- How are you this morning?
- Probably better than you
are. Did you drive all night?
- No, I stopped at some dumpy...
Some dumpy...
Gee, Kronos, come on, man.
- All right, I'm here.
I'm here.
- Anyway, so I stopped
at some dumpy place,
and I had a shower and
a little bit of sleep.
- Little vacation.
- Shut up.
- You're almost there.
- I know.
There's something I
wanna talk to you about.
This is kind of a
personal matter,
so I'm gonna go offline until
I sort things out with Caleb.
- No complaints with me.
I finally get a day off.
- Good to know.
I'll see you on the
other side, my friend.
- Godspeed, Banshee.
- Don't fucking call me that.
- Mmm!
You're a real asshole,
you know that?
The only reason I
keep coming back here
is because my wife's a
bitch and you open early.
- Well, at least you come back.
- Yes.
- Sorry.
No, it was my fault.
I'm the one who should be sorry.
And between me and you,
get your drinks and leave.
The owner is a real crank.
- He's always been that way.
Yeah.
- Anybody else here?
- Mornings are quiet.
There is a latch
right behind you.
You know what to do.
- I assume you want these down?
- Sure.
- Caleb, don't.
- I have to.
And you too.
Just slowly.
That's good.
- It's great to see you too.
Yeah.
- How did you find me?
- You said you were going
to buy this place someday.
- Hmm.
- You were drunk, but...
- What?
- Sincere.
- You remember that?
- I'm not here to kill you.
- Okay.
So what is my price anyway?
4 mil, 5 mil?
- Ten.
- Well, that feels pretty good.
- And it's, uh...
it's gonna get collected
if you don't listen to me.
Anthony Greene is
gunning for you.
He, uh, beat me to a
job and ambushed me...
and offered me a
mil to give you up.
- So you gave me up.
- Who do you think I am?
- I haven't seen you in
years, so I don't know.
- And whose fault is that?
I am not gonna let him
get away this time.
And I can't handle
his army alone.
- It looks like I...
I trained you well.
So...
Hey, Suit, don't move!
- Who's the girl
with the black hair?
- She's my daughter.
- Your what?
- Yeah. Hailey, she's fine.
- Who is she?
- Uh, she's an old
friend from work.
- Are you a hostage?
- No! No.
Just stop pointing your
gun at our guest, right?
- You have a lot of
explaining to do.
- Yeah.
Well, you know, Hailey,
this is, uh, Delilah.
Delilah, Hailey.
Come on, give me that.
- Get ready to lose
everything you own, Dogmom93.
- ♪ Don't talk to me ♪
♪ Don't talk to me ♪
- ♪ I have nothing left ♪
Ah, damn it!
She's good.
- ♪ I told you no ♪
♪ Your chance is... ♪
Hmm.
Hello?
- Kronos, are there any
guns hidden in here?
We're gonna find them
if there are, so...
make things easier for
yourself and tell us.
- I always keep a
revolver in the pizza box.
- Hmm.
- Kronos.
What a shithole.
So you're a gambler, huh?
That's expensive.
You ever won?
- Not my lucky day.
- Eh.
I wouldn't say that.
Yet.
So this is how you live, huh?
Computers and fucking plants.
- Plants don't talk back.
- Kronos, perhaps over here
would be more comfortable.
- Okay.
- So you know the man I've
been looking for, don't ya?
No.
Well, I got a hunch
that you know exactly
where the fuck he is.
No.
Well, if you don't know where
he is, maybe Banshee does.
And I know for sure
you know where she is.
I'm here to offer you something.
That there...
is a million dollars.
Now, what's your usual cut?
20% maybe?
Look at the balls on this guy.
Tell him.
- Your real name's
Michael Shea Thomson.
You graduated from MIT with
a degree in computer science
before joining the Department
of Homeland Security,
where you spent
every waking moment
preventing Russian cyberattacks.
That is, until you
realized there's more money
in contracting and
made the switch.
- He knows me.
- Yeah, we know you.
Your mom and dad are dead.
And I can't find
anyone who loves you
that I can terrify and hurt.
So...
do I just kill you and then
find Banshee on my own?
No?
Well, that's kinda handy 'cause
I'm not much of a computer guy.
But these four
people in this room
are very, very good
at hurting people.
And they will hurt
you for hours.
Now, do I have to
keep you alive?
Not at all.
Is it convenient for me?
Maybe.
- I wanna run your contracts.
I wanna be your
eyes and your ears.
I wanna be your new cyber guy.
- Why would I do that?
- 'Cause I can give you Banshee.
Let's make this deal.
- You give me Banshee,
you give me Caleb.
But if you try and fuck
me, son, I'll find ya.
- Is your mom a painter?
- Was.
She's dead.
- Nancy got diagnosed with
cancer four years ago.
She... she died a few
months before we moved here.
- I'm sorry.
Yeah.
- If she's your friend,
then how does she
not know about Mom?
- Well, we... we... we
weren't that close, actually.
- Are you kidding?
- What are you
guys talking about?
- Your dad and my
dad were very close,
so we grew up together.
- Was your dad in construction?
- We worked into... In
construction together.
- Yep, well, there was a time...
we'd be in some kind
of danger spots and...
- Yeah, like when we
had to build skyscrapers
and had to have
each other's backs.
- What does any of that have to
do with not knowing about Mom?
- Well... it's been a
long time, Hailey, really.
Yeah.
- Well, she knows where we are.
Does she know about the mob?
- Hailey, enough.
Don't you have
some homework to do
or a show to watch
on television?
- Fine.
- Good.
- I'll go upstairs.
- Thank you.
Hey, I'm sorry. I'm...
okay. All right.
- Good night.
Construction worker?
Really?
Out of all the
options that you had,
you went with
construction worker?
- Yeah.
Construction sites in big cities
can get tangled
with dirty people,
giving me a reason to
move to a small town.
So construction.
- Ah, so you're
hiding from the mob?
Makes sense, why she
said hello at gunpoint.
Oh, and you're training
her to fight the mob.
Well, it's interesting
because it's very similar
to how you trained me.
Yeah.
So you wanted to
talk about Anthony.
- Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
- Was he there that night
with you and my father?
- No, no, no, no. We're
done with my past, eh?
We're talking about Anthony.
- This isn't about your past.
You are...
You were such an
amazing mentor for me.
And I need you.
I really do.
I need your help.
- You know, all your
questions are for Anthony.
Yeah, he was there.
- Was he alone?
Did he bring anyone?
- Does it matter?
- No.
- So you're gonna
fight Stalin Jr.?
- No.
- Oh.
- We are going to
fight him together.
Don't you wanna stop hiding?
- Can't change the past.
I am fine.
I'm fine right here.
- What happened to you?
- You know, I...
I wish your father was here
as much as you do.
I know what it feels
like to be alone.
There is more to life than
just contract killing.
I'm happy now.
Right here, right now, yes.
- Well, I'm happy
for your happiness.
- Thank you.
But, um...
I am not gonna be your bait.
- Hey, it was a good move.
- Well, you taught me well.
Hold on.
The files on your
dad are two in back.
- Good night, Banshee.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Malia, this is Mr. Navvaro.
He's a friend of myself
and our organization.
- Uh...
Miss Malia, I... I understand,
uh, your father is,
uh, is a powerful man.
- You know who he is.
- I do.
I would like to
know who you are.
And I also would like to know
what do you get out
of this whole thing?
- Protection. All I
want is protection.
- But, yeah.
But you don't get protection
just because your
father is a billionaire.
You know I can't grant it.
- On that drive is just a taste.
Customers, transactions,
but most important,
blueprints to weapons
most governments
don't even know about.
The government, with all
the secrets he's stolen,
takes a leap forward
by ten years.
- Right.
- It's all there.
- I'm sure it is.
Or it's all fake
and you're just,
uh, setting us up.
- I don't care what
you suits think.
I get you the names
of all his buyers
and the locations
of all his weapons,
and I get protection.
He's a monster,
and I need you to hide me as
far away from him as you can.
- Right.
I'll make some calls, yeah.
Good morning.
Hmm.
- So that's what happened.
I knew it.
I knew it, I knew it, I knew it.
I fucking knew it.
Where's my dad?
- Move on. You know
nothing has changed.
Nothing.
- They didn't recover his body.
He could still be out there.
- Banshee, I saw him go down.
- But they didn't find him.
He could still be out there.
- You know, I-I-I told you
yesterday, that's, uh...
- That's a question for Anthony.
- Good morning.
- Am I interrupting something?
- Uh, no.
Just, uh, having
a cup of coffee.
Speaking of which,
uh, I should be going.
Ugh.
D, call the tavern
if anything comes up.
- The pub has a
front and a back door
that leads to a parking lot.
It's pretty straightforward.
- There's nothing
straightforward about Caleb.
What about the house?
- Dead-end streets
surrounded by woods.
- Banshee's probably there.
That means Caleb knows
that you're coming.
- We're coming?
Are you not going?
- Oh, Jesus Christ,
you know what?
You want to question me again?
Please.
Do I need to find
another assistant?
How long?
- Um, six hours or so.
Call the Philly team.
- What are you thinking?
- Two teams.
One takes the house,
one takes the tavern.
They can be there
within the hour.
And tell the team that
goes to the Old Well,
you know, be subtle, be quiet.
Caleb is smart. It
may all be for not.
Tell them to text me
when they're in position.
- Got it.
- And remind them
I want him alive.
Alive and kicking
'cause he's mine.
You got it?
- Got it.
- So make the damn call.
You, find me a
take-away. I'm starving.
- All right, so we
head out at 1500.
No sooner, no later.
Stay off the main
road at all cost.
We wouldn't want any uninvited
guest during the party.
Now, when we reach the
outskirts of town, we hit dirt.
Now, all off-road until we
find an old packing house
about seven clicks out.
There, the handoff
to the CIA happens.
Male and female agents,
they will take Malia and her
drives into protective custody.
Good? Happiness?
All right, so get some coffee,
take a nap, and be ready.
- Jeremy, wait.
- What is it?
- This all sounds
great, Mr. Navvaro.
But?
- But there's no Plan B.
- This is a routine op.
We have done it
hundreds of times,
and I trust my men, believe me.
- Seems as though you've
taken every precaution
against my father's men,
who are definitely out there
hunting for me right now.
But you've taken no precautions
against your own men.
- Malia, if I may,
it is normal to be
a little nervous
or even paranoid as we
get closer to the handoff.
- Is it..
- But...
- More rational to be
paranoid or careless?
I am risking
everything being here.
You have no idea what he'll
do to me if he catches me.
I've held up my
end of the bargain,
and I expect you to do the same.
- We are.
Have you met the agents
I'm being handed off to?
- Of course.
They are CIA agents
with top clearance.
- The CIA's always been the
most trustworthy organization.
- Let us do our job, Malia.
In six months, you will be
living wherever you want
and doing whatever
the fuck you want.
Trust me, okay?
Okay.
- Hey, it's okay.
- Used to be one
of my favorites.
- Used to?
- Memories suck when
you know how they end.
So what's your deal?
- My deal?
- You came here to
get my dad's help,
but you haven't done anything
but eat and stare at
photos of my family.
Were you lovers or something?
No.
I've known him
since I was seven.
- Is he in danger?
Look, I know he's in
danger with the mob.
I looked at your
file on the table.
Are you with the
government or something?
- You shouldn't have done that.
- I'm sorry. I
couldn't help it.
I feel like he's in danger,
and he is all I have left.
Hey, if he's in
danger, I need to know,
because I will not
let anything...
- Stop!
I'm here to help you.
Now, tell me everything
that you know.
Sit.
- Tough, but quiet bar owner.
Love it.
Let's start with,
uh, three beers.
- Sure.
All right.
- And some menus.
- Oh, I'm sorry, but,
uh, the cook is sick.
- That's fine then.
We're celebrating, actually.
- All right.
- Yep, my son's getting married.
- Oh, wow.
Well, nothing says wedding
destination like Wellburg.
Ah!
- He grew up here.
- Yeah.
- It's like one last
bit of nostalgia
before he takes that
next big step in life.
- Hey, you know, you seem
happier about it than he is.
- Ah, what can I say?
Guess he knows what he's
getting himself into.
Yeah, it's true.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
- They're in position.
- Good.
Give them the go.
And tell the other
team to hit the house.
And make sure they find
anything they may have on me,
and to keep him alive
until I get there.
- I didn't read much of it.
I just saw pictures of bodies
and buzz words
like nuclear codes.
Are people coming here?
- Yes.
- What are we gonna do?
It's my dad.
- Hey, Baby.
You see, I forgot to tell you
that the repairman is coming by.
- They're here.
- Yeah, I'll be there
as soon as I can, yeah.
Uh, yeah, give a kiss
to the baby for me.
- I will.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Get your gun.
Now!
- Honestly...
I have seen worse.
I mean, you were
very good, very good.
But these two?
They preform like wet towels.
- Three entrances. Any others?
- Basement entrance
comes out down the hall.
- Hailey, I want
you to go upstairs,
lock yourself in your room.
And do not come out
until I say it's clear.
- I'm not leaving you alone.
- Hailey, go!
- Let me go!
- Get off! Get up!
- Don't worry.
I'll take care of your
girl when you're gone.
- Hey.
Baby.
Hey, baby.
Um... hey...
she needs to know the truth...
before she hears lies.
- Yes.
- I'm so sorry I didn't
tell you this before.
I'm sorry.
- It's okay, it's
okay, it's okay.
- Hmm, yeah?
I, you know, I have trained you.
And you have to listen
to... To D now, all right?
You understand me?
- I understand.
- You understand what
I'm trying... good, good.
Hide her.
- I will.
- You know they want her, right?
- Yes.
- Hey, Baby, you're...
you're the best thing
that ever happened to me.
- What's the word on the
team that had the house?
- Not a thing.
- Okay, they're dead.
- I mean, maybe
they're just waiting...
- Nah, they're dead.
What about the spotters?
- They're in position now.
Caleb's car's there, but
no sign of him or Banshee.
- So they're holed up in
the house waiting for us.
What're you hearing?
- Our three are dead
inside the tavern.
- And is there anything
to link them back to us?
- Cops think it was
a robbery gone wrong.
They're trying to
find the owner.
- How long before
we get some backup?
- There's another team
coming from the city now.
They'll be here in three hours.
- Ugh, make sure they hustle.
I want these assholes.
- What if they run?
- Where?
There's only one
way out of town.
The spotters will see them.
So now, we just sit back and
we play the waiting game.
- What was it he
wanted me to know?
- The truth about who he was.
The CIA sent a man named
Anthony to kill them.
They said that
they were traitors
selling witnesses'
intel to the Russians.
- Why would the CIA do that?
- They were getting old.
They were too powerful,
and they knew too much.
- Fuck!
- Caleb went into hiding.
My father had been shot.
And Anthony's brother
had been killed.
- So Anthony will come here?
- I fucking hope so.
- Good.
Do you have a plan?
- I'm working on one.
- Come with me.
Will this help?
- He kept all these?
- He had trust issues.
Lucky me.
We should take the upstairs.
It'll be to our advantage.
- My dad said if you
aren't mobile, you're dead.
- Normally, that's true.
But if we go anywhere,
they'll find us.
This house is our territory.
It's advantageous to us.
- Won't they just burn us out?
- No way.
They need Caleb's
body as proof of kill.
I have a price on my head,
so they'll wanna
collect that too.
- How many you got?
- Enough.
- Send them in.
- What was he really like?
- What?
- My dad. What was
he really like?
- I think you probably
knew him best.
You just knew a
different version of him.
- Which version did you know?
I knew the big, strong,
I'm-a-bad-ass Caleb.
He had a hard shell, but...
he had a soft spot
for a few people.
- What was it like when
you lost your parents?
- It was hard.
I was angry.
But I just kept my head
down, focused on the work,
and eye on the prize.
- So he really
never mentioned us?
- No.
Which means he loved
you more than anything.
He was protecting your safety
even from the ones that
he trusted the most.
- So you guess it's just us now?
- Yes.
- That's fine.
Kinda like you.
- Kinda like you too.
- Why are they not getting out?
- Come here.
- What are you doing?
- They're using thermal.
We need to register as one.
- Looks like the front
door is boarded up.
- Walkie.
Go around the back.
Make sure it's the same.
- Roger that.
- Two guys across the yard.
- Back door's boarded up too.
- Did they just board
it up and leave?
- All I'm seeing is
one thermal image,
so what the fuck are
you talking about?
- Is there any sign
of life downstairs?
- Negative. I'll
go around back.
- Sir, what if it's a trap?
- Of course it's a trap.
But I need to know who
the second person is.
Use this to find out
before Caleb's on.
It's time.
- Hey, Banshee!
Little bitch! Little bitch!
Time to play!
Come on, Banshee.
I know you're in there.
- D, don't worry about me!
Kill this bastard!
- Banshee...
are you really going
to let your boy die?
- Do something.
- I can't.
Anthony's the only one
who knows about my father.
- Oh!
Three more in the back.
Go.
- Three going around
back! They're coming in!
- Oh, fucking Christ!
Rush the house!
- How's it going?
- Not great!
Fucking useless.
They keep kicking them
before they go off!
- Cook 'em.
- What?
- Cook 'the grenades.
- I don't know what that means!
- Hold them for a few seconds
before you throw them.
- One, two, three...
- You got a gun?
You do now.
Come on.
- Five or six coming in!
- Eyes on Anthony?
- I don't know!
They're all wearing masks!
- Fucker's trying
to wear us down.
Go upstairs now.
Fuck!
- Go. Go, go, go, go!
- Finally.
- Fuck off.
Do you got any men left alive?
- I don't know. I
think they're all dead.
- No, I can't do this.
- Of course you can.
Listen to me.
Who we find in that
building, I want them alive.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah, I'm serious.
Until I put them in body
bags, I'm very serious.
Go.
Fuck.
- Whoa!
Wow.
Look at you, girl.
Good job.
Where's Caleb?
Go, go, go!
- I have an idea.
How about you get your
fucking dudes off the girl?
I'll tell you where Caleb is,
you tell me where my father is,
everybody's fucking happy.
- I don't recall
where your father is.
- You're a liar.
You know what? You're right.
I do recall.
The last time I seen him,
there was a couple of guys
beating the shit out of him.
And he was lying
in a pool of blood.
Silly me.
- Get the fuck in here!
- Feels like a little
much for a teenage girl!
- They never found a body.
- Or because your father's
a traitor, and he ran away.
- Wrong. Get them
off the fucking girl!
- Where's Caleb?
- Buried in the back yard.
- Now you're upsetting me
because I know you're lying!
'Cause after Caleb shot my men,
I know he came back here.
Where the fuck is he?
- Oh, you're feeling tough?
Okay.
Let's do this old school.
- Shoot her!
Shoot her!
- Yeah. Hey, hey, hey.
Where...
the fuck...
is... Caleb?
Huh?
- You punch like a
little fucking bitch.
- Hey, asshole.
Fuck you.
- Fuck.
- Are there more?
- I hope not.
- I got shot today.
- I got shot too.
- No. I got shot.
In the shoulder.
- It's a flesh wound.
You'll be okay.
- What's next?
Are more people
gonna shoot at us?
- Probably.
It just depends on where
we go and who we go after.
But for now, let's
just get a cocktail
and a steak in a hotel room.
- There's nothing I'd rather do.
- ♪ I have no home ♪
♪ I have nowhere to be ♪
♪ I'm a wanderer ♪
♪ That's me ♪
♪ And I don't care
how you judge me ♪
♪ I don't care what
you think of me ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ There is darkness ♪
♪ And the rain
is pouring down ♪
♪ There is violence
all around ♪
♪ And I don't need
you to hold me ♪
♪ I don't need you
to take care of me ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ So what do you want? ♪
♪ What do you want
from me now? ♪
♪ You can't hurt me, no ♪
♪ And you can't help me out ♪
♪ And I will scream
like a banshee ♪
♪ I will scream
♪ So what do you want? ♪
♪ What do you want
from me now? ♪
♪ You can't change me, no ♪
♪ And you can't
chain me down ♪
♪ I will scream
like a banshee ♪
♪ I will fight, you
can't block me ♪
♪ I have no fear,
you won't stop me ♪
♪ I will win, you
can't beat me ♪