-[people screaming]
-[alarms ringing]
[sirens blaring]
[screaming continues]
[indistinct chanting]
[glass shatters]
-[punches landing]
-[camera static]
["O Come, All Ye Faithful"
by Teresa Tudury playing]
♪ O come
All ye faithful ♪
♪ Joyful and triumphant ♪
♪ O come ye ♪
♪ To Bethlehem ♪
♪ Come ♪
♪ And behold Him ♪
♪ Born the King of Angels ♪
♪ O come let us ♪
♪ Adore Him ♪
♪ O come ♪
♪ Let us adore Him ♪
♪ Christ the Lord ♪
♪ Hallelujah, hallelujah,
Hallelujah♪
-[people shouting]
-[glass breaking]
[clamoring]
[fire truck honks]
[siren blaring]
[indistinct clamoring]
♪ Sing choirs ♪
♪ Of angels ♪
♪ Sing in exultation ♪
♪ Sing all ye citizens ♪
♪ Of heaven above ♪
♪ Glory to God ♪
♪ Glory in the highest ♪
♪ O come ♪
♪ Let us adore Him ♪
♪ O come...♪
Let's take a walk
down Main Street.
This is Main and 4th.
A few hours ago,
the street team was live.
Kids on bicycles,
lunch-time crowds,
people hurrying around,
looking for that
last perfect Christmas present.
And then shots rang out.
When the smoke cleared,
three teenagers were lying
dead on the ground.
Innocent victims,
that the police,
had mistaken for gang members.
-[siren blaring]
-Within moments
the outrage turned to violence.
And... this is the result.
I'm Harry Johansen,
reporting from the war zone...
-[helicopter whirring]
-...and this is ground zero.
That wreath and the candles
behind me on the ground,
are not Christmas decorations.
Those are memorials on the site
where these children died,
sparking off,
what is quickly becoming known,
as the "Christmas Eve Riot."
Off in the distance, you can
see the yellow glow from...
-[sirens blaring]
-...fires that are spreading
all over the city.
[Harry] The police are so busy, trying to take care of the fire fight--
-[sirens blaring]
-[cars honking]
-[sighs]
-[Harry] ... called in,
the governor's declared
-an immediate state
of emergency...
-I'm scared, Anna.
[Harry] ... and the hospitals
are just being...
Everything will be fine.
[Harry] ...they don't know
what to do with
all of the injured.
-So far, 70...
-[sighs] Everyone's gone mad.
[Harry] ...hundreds more have been hurt...
We're not far from home.
Well go back.
-[Harry]
...the mayor's imposed a...
-After we get to this turn,
can you find
a shorter way home, John?
[John] I'll do my best, ma'am,
but the riots are making things
-really crazy.
-Okay.
[Harry] ...compliance
has been spotty at best.
-[cars honking]
-[sirens blaring]
-[glass shatters]
-[both scream]
[gunshots fired]
You bitches better mind
your business.
-Get off!
-I don't want to kill you.
-What do you want from us?
-Shut up! Don't ask questions.
I ask the questions. Shut up!
[mailbox unlocks]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[children talking]
-I wanna watch basketball.
-I wanna watch
The Simpsons,now!
But, I wanna watch
basketball now.
You can watch it afterwards.
It's on at the same time,
stupid.
I'm not stupid. You're stupid.
I'm not making you
any sandwiches.
Good. I'm making pizza.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
See, this is so easy.
Mom said never to cook
anything when she's not home.
I've seen mom do this,
a billion, zillion,
trillion times.
Please, I'll make you
a ham sandwich.
I'm doing it.
Fine, I'm going to my room.
Fine, I'm gonna have pizza
and watch the game.
["Deck The Halls"
playing over radio]
[grunts]
[fire alarm beeping]
[beeping continues]
Oh, God.
[Sue coughs] Turn it off!
-Okay, ouch!
-[oven hissing]
I told you
not to cook the pizza.
[beeping continues]
Johnny, Sue, you in there?
-[oven hissing]
-Ow.
Help us.
-Shane, help us.
-Shane, are you there?
-[Sue] Please, help us.
-You guys okay?
-[both] Help us!
-Open the door!
-[Johnny] It's locked. Mom
didn't leave the keys.
-Come on!
-[Sue] Help us, please!
-Okay, stand back.
I'm gonna break the door in,
so stand back.
[both cough]
-[Shane grunts]
-[both cough]
-Come out, let's go.
-[Sue] Let's go Johnny.
-[coughs]
-[beeping continues]
-[oven hissing]
-Ah!
[Shane coughs]
[cheerful Christmas
music playing]
Here you go, guys.
Now tell me,
which one of you guys
decided to play mum, tonight?
-He did.
-[sirens blaring in distance]
You know, you're supposed
to take the pizza
out of the box,
-before you put it in the oven.
-[Sue giggles]
Don't worry.
I think, this will taste better
than the burnt pizza, anyway.
Told you so.
[sighs]
So guys,
where is your mum tonight?
She didn't come home yet.
She was supposed
to be home two hours ago.
I don't know, where she is.
Well, there
was a lot of traffic, tonight.
So, I'm sure
she'll be home soon.
You eat with these?
Yeah, it's simple.
Look, just put it in one hand,
like this, between your fingers
and use this one for leverage.
-[sirens continue]
-I got it.
[Shane chuckles]
All right, Johnny.
You were in the army, Shane?
-Yeah, but not in this country.
-Cool. Did you kill people?
I don't think that's
a very nice thing to ask him.
He's so rude.
[chuckles]
Why are you
in this country, then?
-And he's not even polite.
-That's okay.
I'm here to help train
American soldiers
so they can protect
their families.
All right guys,
less talk, more eat, okay?
-[telephone ringing]
-[firetruck horn blaring]
Okay, I wanna see you
eat it all, okay?
[ringing continues]
-Hello?
-Shane, this is Williams.
Hello, mate. What's up?
Wanna come out
and play some pool?
Maybe, grab a cup of beers?
Oh, yeah.
It'll have to be in a while,
I'm in the middle of some
babysitting right now.
[chuckles] Babysitting?
Yeah, my neighbor's kids
got a little fired up early
this evening.
[on TV] This is Harry Johansen,
reporting from the war zone.
And these scenes
are just going on...
-[siren blaring]
-[Harry] ...all over the city.
The streets are awfully quiet, right now,
but let me give you a picture of what it looked like, just a little bit earlier in the day.
This is an electronic store,
where I bought my VCR
and my television set.
Within minutes,
looters pilfered
for the inventory.
They used Molotov cocktails to
-burn the building
to the ground...
-[Williams] Hey, man.
-Your shot.
-[Harry] ...here's a food
market
-where people in this...
-You take it for me, will you?
I wanna watch this.
[Harry] ...buildings, folks,
going up and smoke.
It's about
the abandoned employees
who need their jobs.
It's about the people
in the community
who depended on this market
to feed their families.
And this is madness folks,
festering in the hearts
of the human-- of humanity
in this city.
Stay home, and make sure you know where your kids are,
but whatever you do, stay calm. Stay calm and do not panic.
A store owner, a woman,
told me a story
about her 19 year-old son,
-who was almost
beaten to death...
-This is disgusting.
What the hell
do these people think
they're going to resolve
back to him like this?
Come on, let's shoot some
pool.
Hell of a way
to spend Christmas.
-[Harry] ...we can stop this,
we must stop this...
-Come on, man. Come on.
-[Williams] Oh.
-[man] Ah, Jesus, man.
-Hey man, I'm really sorry.
-Why don't you watch
where the fuck you're going?
[chuckles]
I'm sorry, man. Listen,
-um, drinks on me, okay?
-We don't want your drinks.
Why aren't you out there
burning down the city
with the rest of the brothers?
What's your problem, man?
Tuesday night,
six o'clock,
me and my friends,
we like to go and play
a little softball.
It's a ritual that's lasted
13 years and three marriages.
And tonight,
they tell us,
we can't play softball.
-Because the spits
and the niggers are out there...
-Watch it!
...burning down
the goddamn city.
Listen mate,
why don't you just calm down?
We're not looking
for any trouble.
I know the riots have gotten
everyone a little bit edgy.
Why don't we just have a drink
and forget about it, huh?
You talk funny.
Where are you from?
England. Why?
That's a great country.
[chuckles]
I did the last half of my tour
in the Marines in England.
Hey, you gotta tell me
something, really.
Do Englishmen know how to fuck?
[chuckles]
Because the Englishwomen
couldn't get enough of this.
So either,
Englishmen don't know
how to do it...
[chuckles]
...or they're all faggots.
Which is it?
[all laugh]
Yeah.
Come on, Williams.
Let's get out of here.
Hey! Hey where are you going?
[man] Oh, you gonna go home
and do it together?
[all laughing]
That's it, man. That's it.
-That's it.
-Hey, Williams.
-[indistinct chatter]
-Let's close this place first.
[balls racking]
[funky Christmas music playing]
[all grunt]
[grunting continues]
[glass breaks]
[Williams] Come on!
-[bone cracks]
-Ah!
Look man, if you're done
playing with these guys
I suggest we get
the hell out of here.
Who told you I was playing?
You did that yourself.
[men grunting]
All right.
[man] Please.
This must be the place.
Major Alcott, Major Williams,
I've got orders to bring you
back to the British Embassy.
ASAP.
Let's hit it.
There goes our night off.
You guys have been kicking
some ass, huh?
Make yourself comfortable, sir.
[man] Can you help us here?
-[man] Please sir.
-Let's hit it.
[indistinct chatter]
[sirens blaring]
[indistinct clamoring]
[crickets chirping]
[brakes squeaking]
[doorbell rings]
Mr. Alcott.
So happy to see you, sir.
Hello, Arthur.
It's good to see you again.
-This is Major Williams.
-Very pleased to meet you.
So, what's the urgency?
They're waiting for you
in the library, sir.
Thank you.
Shane. Thank you
so much for coming.
Ambassador, how are you?
I'm all right.
You're looking well.
I want you to meet somebody.
Come on, in.
[Ambassador]
Special Agent Devaney,
Major Shane Alcott.
Major Alcott.
And of course, you know,
Major Williams.
-Sir.
-Major.
Please. Take a seat.
The reason I asked you here is,
because of Anna Lisa.
Anna Lisa?
-Why? What's happened?
-I'm afraid she's...
She was on her way
to a photoshoot
with her friend, Amy.
And the bloody riots came about.
I didn't hear from her
for hours.
Police found her driver
shot through the head.
I-- I feared she was dead.
Unti-- until...
The Ambassador received
this ransom demand.
-You mean, she's been kidnapped?
-I'm afraid so.
[VCR clicks]
[Shyboy] Mr. Ambassador,
I'm sure you're probably
real worried, right about now.
But, I want you
to be confident to know,
that I got the bitches.
That's right.
Now this is what I want
you to do for me.
Have one motherfucker...
that's one man.
Bring two million dollars
to the church
on 8th and Central.
No guns, no cops.
No Feds, no bullshit.
And don't be
one fucking second late.
Or I will personally
hand-deliver you
one dead bitch.
Do I make my
goddamn self clear?
[Devaney]
We only have three hours
and 42 minutes left.
Kidnapper's Leon Hues,
known to the police as Shyboy.
He's a leader
of a street gang,
known as the "3rd Street Crips."
And, uh, from what we can tell
the kidnapping was random.
Inside this circle,
is a no-man's land.
Nobody gets in
and nobody gets out.
The exchange point,
the smack-dab in the middle.
And about the only company
you're gonna find here
are gun crazy looters, uh,
gang bangers and...
scared shitless store owners.
Shane, I know
your reputation and, uh...
And I have no doubt that you
are one of the best operatives
in the world,
but in this situation...
you're outnumbered, 30 to one.
There's still have time
to send in a team.
[Arthur] No,
I can't risk her life.
They asked for one man.
They'll get one man.
[Williams] It's a suicide.
No way, Shane.
No way.
Two million, embassy tab.
Don't lose it,
Garrison will drive
you to the airstrip.
Major Williams will fly you in,
drop you off, six blocks
from the rendezvous point
so they don't get spooked.
You know what to do.
Now, you got two hours
to get this girl
and get back to the drop sight
for extraction.
Good luck.
Shane, take a look
down here, man.
I don't know about this one.
You sure, you wanna do this?
So how come you never
talk about this
Ana Lisa anyway?
Hey, man. You listening to me?
[dance music playing]
[cameras flashing]
Come on, come on,
come on, ladies.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Ah, Anna Lisa, yes.
Okay, what's--
-What is this?
-What?
[speaking French]
You have this fluff--
fluff all over your dress.
I didn't dress myself.
Ah, what did you just
roll around in this fluff, hmm?
-Am I okay?
-No, you're not okay.
And these shoes,
where did you get these shoes?
-Marco gave these shoes to me.
I couldn't...
-Marco gave these shoes?
Well, come on,
you must get out.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Marco, Marco!
Shane.
You shouldn't be back here.
-You looked great, out there.
-Well, I'm glad
you're enjoying the show.
-Gotta go.
-Wait a minute.
[Shane sighs]
What's wrong?
I've gotten orders.
I'm gonna leave
on an assignment.
Where?
You know I can't tell you that.
Well, can you call me
or is that forbidden too?
Of course, I will.
First chance, I get.
-[crowd applauding]
-Come on, Anna Lisa,
you're next. Please.
-I gotta go.
-Anna Lisa, wait a minute.
What?
I wanna marry you.
Look, I know
this is hard for you,
but, I want you to wait for me.
Can you wait around?
I get off in an hour.
I can't.
My flight leaves
in half an hour.
Goodbye, Shane.
I love you.
Love you too.
[footsteps retreating]
-Goodbye, Lisa.
-[Williams] Here,
take this.
No way.
He said, no guns.
It's an ankle gun, man.
They won't see it.
No way.
What are you
talking about, Shane?
Take the gun. Take it.
-Look, I can't risk it.
-You'll need it.
-What are you, a psychic?
-Just trust me, man.
What am I gonna do with this?
I might as well
been carrying a peashooter.
I'd have to hit
the guy six times with this
before it even does anything.
[exhales]
Okay.
[Williams] This is Red Leader
to Army Two.
[man] Army Two.
Go ahead Red Leader.
[Williams] I'm closing in
on the drop sight.
From what I can see,
our approach is clear.
Can you confirm?
[man] Affirmative.
Your airspace is clear.
Watch for ground fire.
[Williams] Roger
that, Army Two.
Red Leader out.
This is the place.
I'm not too sure
about this, man.
I'll be fine. Just put it down.
I wish I was going
with you, man.
Like good, old times.
-Yeah, I know.
-She must be pretty special.
Yeah, she is.
Don't forget
to pick me up, huh?
I'll be right here, man.
Good luck, buddy. Be careful.
[indistinct chatter]
-[sirens blaring]
-[man 1] Cracker!
-[glass breaking]
[man 1] You gotta raise up,
Mr. Rogers!
[man 2] Look at that white boy
walking over there, man!
[man 3] Hey, cracker!
-[man 4] Hey!
-[man 3] Hey.
You!
Fuck you doing
in this neighborhood, man?
Don't you know,
you get fucked up in here?
Hey man, you got some of my 40?
Me and my boys?
I know you got some--
-Hey, what the fuck--
-[indistinct shouting]
That's right.
-Get the fuck out
of here, bitch.
-[indistinct shouting]
Punk ass, motherfucker.
-[sirens blaring]
-[fire crackling]
[footsteps approaching]
-[glass shatters]
-[car alarm blaring]
[footsteps running]
[man] Hey.
What you got in the case,
motherfucker?
I'm talking to you, man.
What's in the case, man?
Give it up.
You got something valuable
in there, man?
Come here,
or I'm fuck you up.
-[bones crack]
-[grunts]
Kick his ass, man!
-Hey!
Got us a white honky, huh now.
[indistinct clamoring]
[man] Yeah. Come on.
[indistinct clamoring continues]
[Shane grunts]
[indistinct taunting]
[indistinct taunting continues]
[men grunt]
[man] Get him, get him.
Come on!
[grunts]
[Shane grunts]
[man] He ain't giving up, huh?
[man laughing]
-[electricity crackles]
-[men screaming]
[briefcase clicks shut]
[indistinct chatter]
[helicopter blades whirring]
Oh, you better have
a goddamn good reason
for being here.
And start praying
to whatever God you want.
'Cause your little sad
ass about to meet Him.
Just call me Santa Claus.
Well, ho, ho, ho, motherfucker.
[footsteps echoing]
[gun cocks]
Ain't it funny?
Life.
[Shyboy scoffs]
See, mama wanted me
to be a preacher.
She always said: "God
will always watch
over you, Leon."
Problem is...
preachers don't make shit.
And God...
[scoffs] He give you salvation.
But he don't give you
no Mercedes.
You got my fucking money?
I got half of it, here.
You'll get the rest when I leave
with the girls.
Smart.
I bet you figured...
we was gonna pop a cap
in your ass, the second
you walked up in here.
-The thought crossed my mind.
-Yeah.
Well, I figured, they may have
wanna go send me no dummy
I said to Blaze,
our boy won't be coming
into hell without no game plan.
Nah... [chuckles]
I said, you'll find some way
to save your white ass.
Where are the girls?
-[Shyboy] Let's get
this shit done. [grunts]
-[briefcase slams down]
When I see the girls.
You don't trust me?
Oh...
Bring!
-[whimpers]
-[grunts]
Come here.
Bitch! Sit down!
Shane?
[Shyboy] Shit...
The man sent us
a straight up lover boy.
[chuckles]
Ain't that something?
And all along, I thought
you was a little bitch.
[men laugh]
[stutters] Ah, wha-- what.
What about her?
You know her too?
[Shyboy] Huh?
-I don't know.
-Oh.
So, you don't give a shit
about her, huh?
-No! Amy!
-[man grunts]
No! Shane!
No!
Be still.
[Shyboy] Now tell me where
the rest is before I splat
your motherfucking brains
all over the floor
next to that bitch over there.
You'll get your money,
when I leave with the girl.
Hand him his shit.
Hand him his shit!
[grunts]
[Anna grunts]
[Anna screams]
[men screaming]
[Anna] Shane!
[Anna screams]
-What are you doing?
-Just go!
[Shane grunts]
Yo, move.
[Anna screams]
[Anna and Shane grunt]
[Anna grunts]
-Help me, Shane.
-Come on baby, let's go.
Let's get that motherfucker.
[Anna panting]
I'm Kathy Austin,
with KKGL News,
coming to you live, in front of the British Embassy,
where we have just
been informed
that Anna Lisa Gray, daughter of British Ambassador, Alexander Gray,
has been kidnapped at gunpoint.
FBI agents are here
at the embassy now,
and are currently
inside in closed meetings.
[Harry] Federal troops have thrown a barricade around the violent areas
and they've been able to keep it from spreading so far.
I think that
ourAction 9 news team
is the only crew that's working behind the army periphery.
I've heard that another helicopter from one of the other channels,
came down while they were trying to get over this territory here. I--
I don't know whether there are any survivors right now or not.
We'll keep trying to transmit to you as long as we can...
-[door opens]
-...but I'll tell you folks,
it looks like this
Christmas Eve
-is gonna be a long, long
night.
-[door closes]
[Harry] Fortunately, we were able to find safety with a platoon of National Guardsmen,
who're doing the best to keep order downtown.
I'm telling you, I've never seen anything like this before.
And I wouldn't wanna be two blocks west of where I am, right now 'cause there's a...
-What's up, Major?
-[Harry] ...major outbreak of looting...
-Want a drink?
-Where's my chopper?
Every thing's grounded.
They just shot down
the TV helicopter.
So, what does that mean?
What about Shane?
-I'm sorry.
-You're sorry?
Does the Ambassador
know about this?
I haven't told him, yet.
You son of a bitch.
You're gonna let
him die, out there.
Hey listen, let me tell you
something, I don't like this
any more than you do.
There's nothing more I can do.
My hands are tied.
You make me sick.
Sick!
-Major?
-What?
Come here.
Major, if someone were to
accidentally find the keys
to helicopter 124DA,
then, I would have
no knowledge of that person.
But,
if that person were caught,
disobeying a command order,
then of course...
-[keys jingle]
-...that person
would not know me.
Good luck, Major.
Thank you, sir.
-[Anna breathing heavily]
-[sirens blaring]
[indistinct clamoring]
[Shane] Okay, in here.
[Anna] Oh, thank god.
[Shane grunts]
[sobs]
I'm sorry about your friend.
[indistinct chatter]
Ain't no motherfuckers
can't just disappear.
They gotta be here, somewhere!
We're gonna find their ass.
[indistinct chatter in distance]
I want you to know Shane,
the reason I broke
our engagement.
No, please.
The past is the past.
I couldn't stand the idea
about being separated.
You were always gone
for so long.
Everything's so secret.
I thought I could,
but I'm sorry.
I would've given it
up for you, Anna Lisa.
I would've done
anything for you.
I loved you.
I loved you so much.
All you had to do,
was say the word.
I was young...
but I felt I had no choice.
You had a choice, Anna Lisa.
-We all had choices.
-[helicopter blades whirring]
I had a choice.
And I chose to come
here for you.
I love you, Shane.
We got ten minutes
to get to the chopper.
[siren blaring]
Where are you going, Major?
I'm headed to the airfield
to take the chopper for a ride.
Is it okay with you, soldier?
I need to see
your authorization papers, sir.
All air crafts have
been grounded, sir.
-Commander Louis said, sir--
-Commander Louis said?
Tell me, Cooper,
how long have you
been in the army?
One year, sir.
I've been here for 15 years.
Now, what do you
think that means?
You're a career-man, sir.
And do you think
I'll risk my neck
for an unauthorized
flight release?
Well, do you, Cooper?
Or maybe, I should refer to you
as Private Cooper.
No, sir.
Have a nice flight, sir.
[Harry] Death toll,
right now, is estimated at 65
while the number
of injured is just...
Thanks.
As if I didn't have
enough to worry about.
God help you, Alcott.
God help you.
That's our ride.
All we gotta do is,
get to the roof
and we're outta here.
You ready for this?
Ready.
Okay, let's go.
Does that motherfucker
think we're stupid? Yo.
He's right up
on that goddamn roof.
You, you go to the front.
You take the back.
Boys, come with me.
Let's do this shit.
[Anna breathing heavily]
-Right in here.
-Okay.
Damn it.
[footsteps approaching]
[grunts]
Come on, hurry up.
-[bone cracks]
-[screams]
[man] Come on. Come on.
[man] There he is.
[Shane] Let's go.
Bitch.
[grunts]
[Shane grunts]
You wanna go toe to toe
with me, motherfucker?
[yelps]
[choking]
[neck snaps]
[Shane] Come on.
Let's get to the roof.
[helicopter blades whirring]
Come on, come on. Hurry, hurry.
Come on! Get in, get in!
Okay Williams.
Get us out of here, man.
-Let's go.
-We're out of here.
You okay, hon?
Yes.
Yo, baby.
Time to meet the devil,
motherfucker.
-What was that?
-Jesus Christ. We've been hit.
[Anna screams]
-Come on, Williams, control--
-I'm losing it.
-Take us down!
-I'm losing control, Shane.
Come on Williams, get us down.
-I'm trying, I'm trying!
-[Shane] Come on.
-Hold on, Anna Lisa.
-Take over Shane.
We're going down hard!
[Anna screams]
[metal screeches]
-[Anna screams]
-[Shane] Hang on!
[Anna grunts]
-Help her.
-[Williams] Got it.
I got her.
It's okay, Anna Lisa. Let go!
-[Williams] I got you!
-[Shane] Hold on to her, man.
[Williams] I got you. Come on.
[Shane] Hang on to her,
Williams. Get her out of here.
Get on the roof.
[Williams grunts]
[Williams] Hold me.
[Williams] Pull me up, Shane.
Don't let me fall, Shane.
[Shyboy] Yeah.
[Williams] Shane.
-[Shane] Hold on!
-[Williams] Hold-- hold me.
[Williams] I'm-- I'm slipping.
-Hang in there buddy.
-Don't let me drop man
Hold me.
Come on, baby, come on, come on.
[Williams] I'm losing my grip.
Come on, come--
Come to fucking daddy.
[Williams grunts]
Pull us up!
Give up, motherfucker!
[Williams] Help me.
-Help me.
-Pull us up!
Pull me up, Shane.
Come on. Here it is.
-Yeah!
-No!
No, Williams!
Got that son of a bitch!
[both scream]
[screams] No!
No!
[door opens]
[footsteps approaching]
Well, well, the money is mine.
You said it was easier
than getting laid
in a whorehouse with a fist
full of hundreds.
Yeah, that's what I said.
But, you didn't fucking tell me
he was sending G.I. Joe to
goddamn rescue, either.
[grunts]
Here's what we'll do.
We separate into teams
and cover this grid
from end to end.
Use channel six
in your scanners.
Find Shane Alcott.
Get the money and the girl...
-and kill him.
-Oh, shit.
What?
They don't look
like gang members.
They're not.
Now, what do you mean?
That Rambo motherfucker took
out five of my best men.
That's what the fuck, I mean.
You shady, man.
You paint this
perfect fucking picture
while this shit's supposed to
go down, but yet somehow,
you failed to warn us
what the fuck we up against.
Half of my fucking men, dead!
The way I see it,
you owe me every fucking
red cent of this goddamn money.
Now, I didn't ask
for your opinion, did I?
I asked you to do a simple job.
To get the man's money
and return with the woman.
And you come back empty handed.
I told you,
we couldn't trust his kind.
-What the fuck you say?
-No, no, no, no, no.
We mustn't let color come
in between us.
A man is a man.
Isn't that right, Shy...
boy?
Even if he has
just made a mistake.
Oh, I didn't make no mistake.
Other than dealing
with your sorry,
peckerwood, white ass.
[chuckles]
That's Bryan O'Flaherty.
Green Eagle Provo.
IRA?
Yeah, this whole thing
is beginning
to make sense now.
Your kidnapping wasn't random.
He knew I'd come after you.
Come on, let's get out of here.
They'll be all over this roof
in minutes.
Why the fuck, do you wanna keep
playing games, man, huh?
-[sirens approaching]
-The deal was,
half the money
for that stupid bitch.
Do you see a girl here?
Patrick? Do you see a female,
anywhere around here?
I don't see a thing, Bryan.
I didn't come this far
and not to get paid.
I don't have the girl,
I lost half of my fucking men.
So, what I'm telling you is...
you break me off
half of what you owe me.
And I swear to Almighty God,
-I will have that bitch
back, like that.
-[snaps fingers]
We mustn't let inconvenience
come between us.
You and I are much more alike
than we know.
You're a man whose people
have been put upon
by an outside force
for centuries.
I'm a man who knows
how that feels.
You have
your American oppressors.
And I have the British.
So let's be fonder
of each other that we are.
I just ask that you be mindful
of me political situation.
'Cause I don't give a shit
about yours.
[grunts]
Pathetic pillocks.
Gentlemen, we've got work to do.
Do you see something?
[IRA soldier]
He's a dangerous one.
Come on, come on.
I thought I saw him
around here somewhere.
Look, about seven blocks
of west is Waverly Avenue.
There's a police outpost there
that marks the ends
of the perimeter.
That's the end of the riot zone.
If you can make it there
you'll be safe.
Me? I'm not going without you.
-Anna Lisa, you've gotta go.
-No.
-[sirens blaring]
-You two over there.
-You're wasting time,
all right--
-I'm not going.
No!
-Come on. Come on.
-Anna Lisa, you gotta go.
Come with me.
I gotta stay here
and take care of them. Go.
Go!
[bike engine revving]
[IRA soldier] Check in between
that area. Go over there. Move.
[IRA soldier] All right,
wait, wait, wait.
[motorbike approaching]
[man grunts]
[neck snaps]
[grunts]
[Anna gasps]
[man grunts]
-[gunshots fire]
-[gun clicks empty]
[man grunts]
[gunshots fire]
[man screams]
She went this way.
[Anna grunts]
Oh!
[Anna] Shane.
You okay?
-I'm sorry, Shane.
-No.
But we can still make it.
No.
We gotta get to
seen to first.
Come on.
Let's go.
-[mumbles]
-Where did he go?
-I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
Where is everybody?
-I don't know.
-What the fuck
is just going on here?
Jesus fucking Christ!
What are you, stupid?
-Huh?
-[man grunts]
Man, I don't know,
what the fuck's going on.
Useless.
Fuck!
[glass shattering]
[Shane] Stay close, baby.
-Oh, Christ.
-[Anna grunts]
[Shane] That looks bad.
Come on.
-[man on TV] It's Bigfoot!
-[Bigfoot pants]
He's not a legend.
-[banging on door]
-He's real.
-Daddy, the door!
-Faster.
-[banging continues]
I was watching that.
-[Shane] Please open the door.
-[sirens blaring]
-Yeah, what can I do for you?
-Let us in, please?
She needs help.
I'm sorry,
we can't help you here.
Come on, man.
Can't you see she's bleeding?
That's not my problem, man.
Now, move on.
Look, if she doesn't get
treatment, she's gonna die.
Get away from my door
and I don't want no trouble.
-Go ahead, move on.
-[helicopter blades whirring]
Daddy, maybe we should
help them.
They'll figure
something out, all right?
-Honey, what's going on?
-Oh, nothing. Just...
[chuckles] Wait a minute.
I heard voices out there,
what do you mean
nothing's going on?
It's just some guy
with a girl and she's hurt,
something like that.
I don't know, I sent them
on down the road, all right?
She's hurt? Was she shot?
Look, I don't know
if she was shot or not.
But what they need
is a hospital.
I know we ain't no hospital,
-all right?
-Honey...
There's a girl,
hurt out there. I'm gonna go
out there and look, okay?
Look. We don't need
their problems.
All right? That's their problem.
Let 'em handle it.
-All right?
-Look...
-I just wanna see
what's going on, that's all.
-[man sighs]
-That's all.
-All right.
-I'm just gonna look.
-Go ahead.
[door opens]
[indistinct chatter]
[banging on door]
Please help. Let us in.
-[man] Go away. Leave us alone
-[woman] Yeah, get the hell
out of here.
Complying with the kidnappers' demands,
Ambassador Gray has
dispatched an SAS officer
with two million dollars
to secure the safety
of his daughter.
The information we have is that a military helicopter...
[Shane] I need a first aid kit
quickly, please.
But we don't have
a first aid kit.
Okay, get me a towel,
some hot water and some gauze.
-Right away.
-Quickly.
-Where am I?
-It's okay, baby. You're safe.
Just relax.
[groans]
Can you get me
a blanket, please?
Yeah.
[groans]
[smooth jazz Christmas
music playing]
Is she your wife?
[Shane] No.
She almost was.
Oh.
I didn't see a field dressing
like this since Nam.
You know, two white people,
this part of the town,
I'd almost bet
it wasn't a wrong turn
off the freeway.
She was kidnapped.
I was sent in to get her out.
You're in army?
Special Air Service.
SAS.
Damn.
I don't wanna know no more.
You obviously know
how to handle a weapon.
-You really plan on shooting us?
-[man scoffs]
Nah, you don't
keep live ammunition
around the house
when you got kids.
It's empty.
You know, I had almost forgotten
it was Christmas Eve.
[man] Yeah.
The kids were expecting
a good Christmas.
I had to tell them...
Santa Claus wasn't coming
on account he don't carry
an automatic rifle.
So, what do you do for work now?
Anything I can get.
Been kinda slow the past
couple of years.
Spent 16 years,
street maintenance.
Got laid off.
[siren blaring]
[Patrick] The bloke's got
to be here.
I want you to check
all the residences.
If anyone resists,
shoot them on the spot.
You, there. You, there.
Let's go.
-[thud]
-[glass shattering]
[Kathy on TV] The information we have, is that a military helicopter
was dispatched
into the riot zone.
Landing on the rooftop
of a building to pick
up the hostages.
However, immediately
after takeoff,
a malfunction
caused the helicopter
to lose control and crash,
igniting a fire
on a nearby building.
All those on the helicopter
are presumed to be dead.
[news anchor] Thanks for that
latest update, Kathy...
Listen, there's something
that I gotta do.
You mind, if I leave her here
for a few hours?
Well, I didn't figure
you was waiting on a taxi.
Sure, go ahead.
[choir singing "God Rest Ye,
Merry Gentlemen" on TV]
♪ ...Remember Christ our Savior Was born on Christmas Day ♪
♪ To save us all from Satan's
Pow'r when we were gone astray
♪
♪ Oh tidings of comfort and joy Comfort and joy... ♪
Please don't leave me.
It's okay, baby.
I'll be back.
Don't go.
♪ ...And unto certain shepherds Brought tidings of the same ♪
♪ How that in Bethlehem was
born The Son of God by name ♪
♪ Oh tidings of comfort
And joy... ♪
-[footsteps retreating]
-[door closes]
Hey!
[Bryan] Patrick?
Come in, Patrick?
Bryan?
He's back in the riot zone.
He's already killed
a few of our men.
I'm gonna kill this fucker.
I'm gonna kill this fucker!
Watch your back. He's tricky.
[man grunts]
[Shane] Hi-yah!
[neck breaks]
[glass shattering]
[helicopter blades whirring]
[gunshot fired]
Bryan,
we got Alcott surrounded.
We're on McClintock
and Avenue A.
Come quick.
I'm about to fry him.
Well done, little brother.
Make him scream,
while you're doing it.
It's time you went back
to the promised land, Alcott.
You didn't think you'd see
us again, did you?
I can't say it's something
I've been dreaming about.
So, where's that wanker
of brother of yours?
Uh, he's around somewhere,
watching.
To see how I fry you.
He never was man enough,
to do the job himself, huh?
Careful what you say
about my brother.
Last time,
where is the girl?
And where is our money?
And all this time
I thought, it was politics,
you were interested in.
If it's an idea
to believe in you're after,
believe in the idea
that I'll be cooking you
in two seconds flat. [chuckles]
I know you're out of bullets,
Alcott.
So why don't you just
-come out like a man?
-Oh, yeah?
So, why don't you come
and get me?
-[thud]
-[Patrick grunts]
[gunshots fired]
Mommy, is she gonna die
like grandma?
[woman] No honey.
She's gonna be just fine.
-Okay.
-[glass breaks in distance]
And now young lady...
I think it's just about time
you turned into bed.
But I wanna wait
for Santa Claus.
Oh, well...
I don't think Santa comes
while you're awake.
Santa doesn't come
unless you're asleep.
-Okay.
-[chuckles] Okay.
That's a good girl.
-[girl whispers] Goodnight.
-Goodnight. [kisses]
Oh, Patty.
Patty, oh, Christ.
No!
I can't believe you're gone.
Shane?
Alcott?
You son of a bitch,
you murdered my brother.
I'll kill you, you English fuck.
I swear, I will.
Bryan O'Flaherty...
big shot terrorist.
Since when is the IRA
been operating
on American shores?
What? Even Ireland is not safe
of your sick ideology?
Betrayed all your friends, huh?
Oh, the only person you need
to be worrying about
is yourself.
Let me guess...
The IRA uses the cover
of a street gang
during the riots,
to kidnap the daughter
of a prominent
British Ambassador.
Promises the ransom money
to the gang.
But no doubt, takes it
back after killing them.
Takes the girl,
and uses her a second time, to ransom political prisoners.
Tell me, Bryan...
-am I getting warm?
-Yes, but we're not in Dublin
now, are we?
And bygones be bygones
be damned.
You will die.
[chuckles]
Well, let me make it
easy for you, Bryan.
Let'’s meet half way.
So, why don't you come
and get me?
That I will, Shane.
I'll kill him for you, Patty.
And I'll make it slow.
[neck snaps]
[IRA soldier] There he goes!
[coughs]
[car engine starts]
[Shane screams]
You can run but you can't hide!
When I get done with you,
Fergie won't even want you.
[Shane grunts]
Well hello, Shane.
This one's for Patty.
[car engine starts]
[screams]
[Shane screams]
[grunts]
Every minute is bringing us
a new story of courage
and determination
in the face of this violence.
Finally the good citizens
of this community are getting
the upper hand on the looting,
and the streets
are quieting down again.
People are crowding
into the churches.
They're asking:
"Why? How did something
like this happen?"
The answer that they're getting
is that the lessons
of that first Christmas
are as relevant now
as they ever were before.
That the sword
must give way to the plowshare.
The child must lead the man.
That each one of us, is in fact,
our brother's keeper.
And that violence like this,
must never, never occur again.
As dawn breaks
over this healing city,
the words from that manger
2,000 years ago,
still echo in our ear.
Peace on earth,
goodwill toward men.
Merry Christmas, everyone.
["O, Come, All Ye Faithful" by
Teresa Tudury playing]
♪ Oh come ye♪
♪ To Bethlehem♪
♪ Come and behold him...♪
Mommy, Daddy! Look what I found.
[Shane sighs]
[Anna] Thank God, you're alive.
[Shane] I can't imagine
what your father's gonna say
when he learns
I've had you out all night.
He's never gonna forgive me.
[Anna] We mustn't tell him then.
[Shane] By the way,
Merry Christmas, Anna Lisa.
[Anna] Merry Christmas, Shane.
♪ Come let us♪
♪ Adore him...♪
[tense exciting music playing]
[tense exciting music fades]