[dramatic music]
♪♪♪
[intense music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪♪♪
[engine humming]
[engine winding down]
[tense music]
♪♪♪
MAN: The prototype
has been located.
♪♪♪
[whooshing]
[digital beeping]
[muffled coughing]
[rumbling]
Water.
I don't feel so good.
Considering you've been buried
for over 300 years,
you look pretty good to me.
What? What the hell
are you talking about?
Do I know you?
You look kind of familiar.
You can call me Tony.
I'm a human clone of one of your
dead colleagues at the agency.
You can't remember
a thing, can you?
No, am I supposed to?
Don't worry,
we're on the same team.
We're the good guys.
Your name is Garrett Brown.
Your the last human survivor
of the nuclear war.
Everything, everybody
you knew, is gone.
What the hell are you
talking about, man?
I don't believe anything
you're saying. What the...
- Where the hell am I?
- TONY: Calm down.
Look around.
The world you knew is gone.
Your life has been preserved
until just the right moment.
And this is it.
But you have less
than one day of life in you.
You have survived all this time
because you drank one of these.
I've just given you an
additional injection.
It'll help you remember.
Trust me, we can't move forward
if you don't remember
what happened.
Why in the hell should
I trust you?
You're dying.
You better believe that.
I'm dying?
What the hell did you
inject me with?
It's an alien supplement.
I understand you had it before.
Now concentrate.
We do not have much time.
Hopefully, it will
help you remember.
Hopefully.
Hope.
Reverend Hope.
The case.
♪♪♪
We've become skeptical
evangelists
full of fire and brimstone.
Who come on television
to ask us for money.
I am not going to do that.
We've been criticized for using
our followers' donations
to fund many successful
businesses.
I felt we should use
the money responsibly,
support ourselves.
We have followers who are poor
and it is difficult
for them to give.
I am happy to announce today
that the Jeremiah
C. Hope Ministries,
will no longer
be accepting donations.
We'll be the first of our kind
to operate
without taking another penny
from anyone.
GARRETT: The United States
government pegged him
as another false messiah.
They feared he would become the
most dangerous man in the world.
Worse than Jim Jones,
David Koresh,
even worse
than Mercury Mason,
the deadliest of all
the false prophets.
He was responsible for the
suicide deaths of 5,000 men,
women and children
in August 2003.
Jeremiah Hope, a simple country
boy from Georgia,
who's pledged his life
to God's service.
They weren't about to
let it happen again.
Sci-Tech,
a special investigation agency,
was created.
The best of the FBI, CIA
and other special agencies
throughout the free world.
This time it was a different
case, a new enigma.
It was about one man
and one man alone.
Reverend Jeremiah C. Hope.
Good, you're starting
to recover.
Maybe, but I still
feel like crap.
That's normal after
all this time,
you'll be yourself
in no time, okay?
What do you mean, "No time?"
One day, two days? What?
Unfortunately, yes.
[rumbling]
[blasting]
Shit. We got company.
Stay down.
[vehicles whirring]
[lasers blasting]
That'll buy us some time.
Come on, we got to go.
- Where to?
- That was our ride.
We've got to find a place
to hide. Let's go.
[intense music]
- TONY: Cigarette?
- No thanks.
Last smoke on Earth.
[sighs]
So, where are you taking me?
Home.
Home?
TONY: To what's left
of the agency.
Years ago, we built a
subterranean secret facility
to protect us from
the radiation.
Although the humans died
we got our hands on
some alien technology
and we managed
to clone ourselves.
Only the fittest
and the strongest made it.
What else do you remember?
I don't know, man.
I'm too tired.
Listen to me.
This is extremely important.
Look, come on man.
I don't know if you're real
or not.
Seriously, tell me what
is going on here.
Look, I have nothing to hide,
okay? I'm here to help you.
Help me? Okay. Who buried me?
Virgil Conway did.
He wanted to preserve your life.
He's also my creator.
Do you remember him?
Can't say I do.
He's already dead.
So why did you come for me?
You'll find out later,
I promise.
Great.
Who was that that
just attacked us?
Alien terrorists from
the planet Nobus.
Nobus?
You're very creative, Tony.
As I told you,
I'm here to help you.
Now, what else do you
remember about this?
[dramatic music]
GARRETT:
SciTech agency log.
Monday, 17 April, 1998.
Investigate the rising
of Reverend Jeremiah C. Hope.
Mysterious disappearances at
Hope's discovery camps.
Money ties with Future Corp
and CEO Stew Horn.
That was brutal.
I love getting yelled at for an
hour straight, don't you?
Yeah. Well, what do you expect?
I mean, they've been trying
to keep this thing
out of the media forever.
Well, with the shit
that went down
with Mercury Mason,
I can't say that I blame them.
Shit man.
Reverend Hope is going
to be on the cover
of every major magazine and
every television show tomorrow.
If the stress is too much,
maybe you should consider
other work.
The weak don't survive
in this business.
Who you calling weak?
It was just
a general statement.
It was not directed
at anyone in particular.
Come on. Let it go.
He's just pushing your buttons.
Good idea.
Considering I'm the lead agent
in this investigation.
You don't have to constantly
remind us.
[brakes squeaking]
With this, we have plenty
to start turning up the heat
on Reverend Hope.
Why the delays?
Our execution
has to be flawless.
Our plan, perfect.
Come on. The whole world
knows this guy.
We've got to start pressuring
him now.
We will not be reckless just
because we under scrutiny.
[engine starting]
More bullshit.
I had a meeting with the contact
that gave me the pictures.
Virgil Conway.
All right. You finally found
out his name, huh?
I had to go to Italy
to find the guy.
Pictures, too.
Who's the woman?
His girlfriend.
Her name is Rosa.
She's an exchange student
at a local university.
Her family's in Italy.
What, you only have
two pictures of her?
It was windy.
I kept waiting for her dress to
fly up so I could take more.
- Never happened.
- The voice of a real pro.
- She's not involved.
- Alright.
This afternoon, I'm meeting
with a programmer
from Future Corp that
got fired last week.
Virgil's to contact
me tomorrow.
Good.
Well, I'll be with the fun
and exciting boys
from electronic reconnaissance
all day tomorrow.
Why don't you meet me at my
place in, uh, 42 hours.
- All right?
- All right.
- Hey.
- What?
I've been investigating
something else lately.
What's that?
You're sleeping with Jenna.
[giggling]
All right,
I'll catch you later.
[city din]
Goddamn,
can you say, "Obsessed?"
Helps keep me focused.
Well, at least you don't
have a picture
- of him in a bathing suit.
- Oh, but I do.
Keep it hidden
under my mattress.
- Come on, show me what you got.
- All right.
Virgil gave me this.
This links Future Corp
to the Hope Ministries
and number one to both of them.
It's not enough.
We need to catch
him in the act.
I thought you might say that.
He told me someone from Future
Corp is going to deliver
a package to Number One
tomorrow night.
Well, that package better
be damn important.
We've got to convince Hines
to let us go
after his number one agent.
How about two million in cash?
That's it.
Stew Herns from Future Corp.
He's been transferring funds
to offshore accounts for,
what, six months now?
And I'll bet you it's close
to two million bucks.
And it's a match.
Why don't we just take the
money and go to Aruba?
- I'd spend it in six months.
- Yeah, I believe that.
Sure you wanna do this?
Yeah.
All right. We'll take this
to Hines in the morning.
Go home and get some sleep.
You've got balls.
Are you sure that you
can prove this?
- Absolutely.
- Enough to risk your own career?
Yes, sir.
I'm giving you the green light.
Don't mess this up.
No turning back now.
Wouldn't have it any other way.
[tense music]
[car door latching]
♪♪♪
- [cat meowing]
- [thump]
♪♪♪
[grunts]
You're a traitor
to the agency.
Don't make this any
more difficult.
[grunting]
♪♪♪
[thumping]
[knife slicing]
[high-pitched blast]
♪♪♪
[metal grinding of gate]
[car door latching]
♪♪♪
[low whoosh]
[engine starting]
[dramatic music]
[breathing heavily]
[objects thumping]
Jesus.
♪♪♪
Jenna. Jenna, wake up.
Come on, wake up.
What happened?
Number One was here.
He killed everybody.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's impossible.
I just killed him.
I don't want to die.
Hey, hey, shh. Hey, hey.
It's all right. It's all right.
It's going to be okay.
I promise.
Do you still love me?
Hey. Of course I do.
[soft moaning]
[woman gasping]
[Garrett clicking tongue]
[tense music]
MAN: That belongs to me.
What the hell?
- Who are you?
- A good friend.
- Now give me back the case.
- No.
This belongs to the agency.
Get back.
I said step back!
[gunshot]
- JENNA: He's back!
- Who the fuck are you?
What the fuck do you want?
[gunshots]
This is what it's all about,
isn't it?
This is what gives
you your power.
Don't be a fool.
That won't work.
Maybe not.
But I'll take that risk.
NUMBER ONE: I thought you were
our best agent.
I am, and I always
finish the job.
[slurping]
[exhaling]
[choking]
[tense music]
[yells]
This is what it's all about.
Information.
That's the key to real power.
Please!
[sobbing]
No, no, no!
[lock clicking]
[cat purring]
[intense music]
Mission accomplished.
Proceed.
NUMBER ONE: Who's my next brain?
A very important leader.
You'll be surprised.
Why am I being interrogated?
I've got five dead bodies
to account for.
One of them being
the agency director.
The secretary of Defense
is breathing down my back
and you're... the only survivor.
- You think I did it?
- I ask the questions here.
You answer them.
That's how it works.
Understood.
Now, someone dropped
the package off
in the trunk of your
car last night.
Who and what?
He's a contact I have
in the Hope Ministries.
It was blueprints
for his next camp.
You went to see Stew Hern
last night.
- Why?
- I never heard of him.
What were you doing
in the parking garage?
- My garage?
- The one in
the apartment building
on Martel Street.
- An agent saw you there.
- I've never been there.
So you think the agent's lying?
Maybe he thought he saw me,
but he was mistaken.
How did you know
Number Three was dead?
I wasn't aware of his death.
Is that right?
For your information,
his body was found
on a park bench this morning
by the police in West Hollywood.
How unfortunate.
But you're sure Number Two
is dead.
I saw his body!
Who's Virgil Conway?
The name doesn't
sound familiar.
You know him. You reacted when
I mentioned his name,
you weren't expecting it.
I don't know a Virgil.
You just don't know anything.
Do you?
No.
I have something
I think is going to help
jar your memory.
[door latching]
Apparently, I was wrong.
Apparently so, now sit down.
Wake up Number Two.
I said, wake up Number Two.
I think there's somebody here
you're really going
to be surprised to see.
Stop!
Now why is it you two have
completely different versions
about what went on last night?
All I know is he killed
them all.
Funny, he seems to
think you did.
No way. Guy's a fricking freak.
I shot him over and over again
and he didn't die.
He killed them all.
Number three and Jenna were
having an affair,
you killed him in
a jealous rage.
- No!
- I know people that would kill
their own mother for $2 million.
There was never any money
in the briefcase
when I picked it up.
- Money wasn't there.
- Bullshit!
You have a clear motive.
We have you on camera
entering the building.
Now listen to me.
He killed them all.
He killed Clay,
and he went to the agency and
he killed the rest of them.
I wasn't in the building.
I couldn't have done it.
I can prove he's been
sabotaging our investigation
- of Reverend Hope.
- You're desperate.
All that money and
nowhere to go.
Who are those two men
you met with yesterday
from Future Corp?
I don't know anyone from that
company.
What about the pictures and
the documents I gave you?
Number One has given me an
acceptable explanation
for all of it.
I have more, Hines. I have
enough to put this guy away.
Produce the evidence.
It was at my safe house.
And I'm sure you took it after
you thought I was dead.
But you have nothing to
back you up, Number Two.
Christ. Can't you see
he set me up, Hines?
Well, if he did, he did a pretty
goddamn good job of it.
You were dead when we found
you, and now you're alive.
- How?
- I don't know.
HINES: "I don't know..."
Excuse me, gentlemen.
You're absolutely certain it
was Number One you saw driving
into the apartment
on Martel?
Positive.
Take him out.
[gunshot]
What are you?
The liquid you drank should
have killed you.
- How did you survive?
- I don't... I don't know.
- You feel different? Stronger?
- Yeah.
Just like King fucking Kong!
This presents an interesting
problem.
You must come with me.
I won't hurt you.
Yeah, right. Are you kidding me?
[thud]
Is that your best shot?
The solution worked on you,
but not on the others.
What others?
I'm the only person
that can help you.
Help me?
You wanted to kill me.
The liquid you drank
may kill you.
I may be able to
save your life.
Why save me? Last night
you wanted me dead.
Come with me
and I will tell you.
You can't kill me.
You were so sure of yourself
last night.
The way you toyed with me.
But now you're afraid of me.
I'm not afraid of you.
I want you alive.
Yeah? Then come and get me.
I will. Not now, but I will.
[whoosh]
That's it. After that,
my mind draws a blank.
You will get it back. Patience.
Now we got to keep going.
An old friend awaits us.
Hold on to this.
Cover your eyes.
[whooshing]
Hines.
His clone actually.
Sorry to have ordered
your execution,
it was in the interest of
national security.
Yeah, well, it looks like we
all screwed that one up
real good, didn't we?
As long as you are still alive,
there is half a chance.
How is his memory now?
Much better,
but he's not ready yet.
Ready for what?
You must recover
as much information
as possible in order to
activate Virgil's message.
- What message?
- We don't know.
We were programmed
to bring you in
once the radiation levels
had dropped.
[digital beeping]
Computer is ready, sir.
Take a seat, Garrett.
[low humming]
So why me, Hines?
You were exposed to chemical
warfare in the Persian Gulf.
Your DNA mutated with the
alien supplement,
providing you superior
strength.
But as you found out,
plenty of side effects
and certain death.
- I see.
- You were just lucky to last
a little bit longer
than the rest of the humans.
TONY: I have
computer sync up, sir.
Take us back into
your memories, Garett.
The more you can remember,
the more accurate Virgil's
message will be.
Tell us about Virgil Conway.
[birds tweeting]
WOMAN: You're one unique man.
You'd think I'd come out
here to paint the lake,
or the hills?
What are you going to call it?
"Nobus At Peace."
WOMAN: Nobus?
Just a place I made up.
A place in that wild
imagination of yours.
I love it, Virgil.
You've been criticized
for using
charitable donations to build
a corporate empire.
Why do you need all that money?
I have never benefited
personally from the money.
Money was going to various
charities.
Also, my discovery camps.
INTERVIEWER: Discovery camps?
Cities you will build, places
free from crime and hate.
We will invite people
of all races,
rich and poor alike as
brothers and sisters.
We hope those
that do not follow God
will come to our camps
and discover him.
Those that have the faith will
be able to learn more.
Situations like these always
end in tragedy.
Jim Jones, Mercury Mason.
I understand the criticism.
These camps will not be
isolated like Mercury Mason's.
The people will be free to come
and go as they please.
I believe in trusting
the people on this Earth.
I believe in their good nature.
The people will govern
themselves.
What are your ties with
Future Corp?
I have none.
I have no need for computers.
I was told you
have an announcement
you would like to make.
Unfortunately,
I have grave news.
Five days from now,
Southern California is going to
be devastated by an earthquake.
I believe it will be at
least an eight on the Ric...
[click]
[tense music]
[low humming]
♪♪♪
You knew
you couldn't hide forever.
How did you find me?
Persistence.
Along with your sloppiness.
Actually, we stopped looking
until you became an informant
for the United States
government.
Hey!
[gunshots]
- [thud]
- [grunt]
♪♪♪
The miracle will burn!
VIRGIL: Who are you?
You're welcome.
Why did you save me?
- Did you set us up?
- Who?
You're Clay's contact, right?
Ah, your Clay's partner.
I was. He's dead.
I'm sorry. Stay there.
♪♪♪
[buzzing]
I drank one of these puppies,
it nearly killed me.
- Are you sure you drank this?
- Yeah.
How did you get a hold of it?
Came across it while
investigating another agent.
I see. Help me here.
♪♪♪
- [gunshot]
- [thud]
- [deep breath]
- [guttural coughing]
[panting]
[dramatic music]
Sorry about that.
What the hell did
you do that for?
I had to see if
you were telling the truth.
The blue liquid you drank
is a diet supplement.
It's supposed to help humans
improve their skills.
So you shoot me in the chest?
It hurts less than a gut shot.
Yeah, well, don't ever
do anything like that again.
So, how's this supplement
supposed to improve my skills?
And by the way, where
the hell do you come from?
I come from the planet Nobus.
Great, another fucking alien.
So which one are you?
E.T. or The Terminator?
Neither. Morrucan.
All right, moving on.
You don't sound too surprised.
With all the shit
I've seen in the last 48 hours,
I believe just about anything.
Well, there's more.
The supplement will increase
your strength tenfold.
Unfortunately,
I don't know its side effects.
They've been testing it
on humans.
No survivors.
We need it in order to adapt
to this planet's atmosphere.
A sip and we feel rejuvenated.
So why test it on a human?
I can't explain it all now.
Piak, Number One to you,
is going to start wondering
why they haven't
reported back yet.
Time to explore.
This is amazing.
Is there any information
here we can use?
We?
I'll have to look at this later.
All right, fine.
So what is Reverend Hope's
part in all of this?
He's a human puppet
controlled by the alien boss.
Alien boss?
Yes. Allatarek.
He's been their leader ever
since he arrived on my planet.
Wait a minute.
You're telling me that
he's an alien to you also?
He tried to control our planet
just like he's trying
to take over yours.
What? He's trying
to conquer Earth?
Not completely.
He just wants to use you.
He wants Earth's raw materials
and its manufacturing
infrastructure to build
ships and weapons.
He wants your
population as soldiers.
He plans on going back to
Nobus and continuing his war.
Number One, Piak,
works for him.
He was the most dangerous
terrorist on Nobus.
His group had killed
thousands of people.
One day this
Allatarek appeared
and Piak allied with him.
It's pretty bizarre
you'd have terrorism on a planet
that's so advanced like yours.
Just because technology
improves,
doesn't mean people
improve along with it.
True. So, does this
Allatarek control Piak?
He, convinced Piak
he was sent to him
from there, God, Allalak.
He gained his trust.
[typing on keyboard]
Help me get these guys
to the truck.
Is it over yet?
Are they dead?
In order to kill them, you
must first erase their brains,
then cremate them.
So how did you stop Allatarek?
I infiltrated their group
and given away their position.
We bombed them and destroyed
most of their facilities.
He realized he couldn't win,
but he still wanted
a piece of Nobus.
An island the size
of your Africa
the long part of the planet.
He would use it to rebuild.
He planned on attacking
our Temple of Thoughts.
He wanted the community
of minds.
Thoughts we've saved
of our great scientists,
creative geniuses.
Great minds that guide us.
So how in the hell
did you get here?
Oh, yeah, the good stuff.
I informed my people
of their location.
They bombed again, this time
with more powerful weapons.
They destroyed everything.
The terrorists also
discovered me,
but didn't kill me.
They took me with them to
the spaceship for ransom.
Our navy was patrolling the area
and was on them
the minute they took off.
Cruisers pounded them.
Damaged and desperate,
they headed out to space.
The Navy was closing in.
There was a dark matter
fold into space.
Every probe we send through
there was destroyed.
No one would even try
to take a ship through.
Piak and this
Allatarek had no choice.
We went through then
suddenly we're shot out
at incredible speed.
I was in restraints.
We were thrown about the ship
and knocked unconscious.
The computer system managed
to crash land the ship on Earth
in a secure place
south of your continent.
They put me in a gas chamber
and ejected me into the ocean.
The machine didn't work.
I was lucky.
I survived.
♪♪♪
[fire crackling]
Will you help me?
I protected my world, it's
not my job to protect yours.
I lost everything
I had fighting them,
not this time.
Why not? You can't go back
to the other aliens.
You can't live amongst us
because we'll all be slaves.
You have no place to go.
They cannot control every piece
of land on this planet.
I know of safe spots
that'll be left alone.
It'll be a simple life.
But we'll be free.
Who's we?
You and Rosa?
How do you know about her?
I have my sources.
After I fled the agency,
I tracked you down, did my
homework and saved your life.
- You think I owe you.
- Yeah.
I didn't ask you to save me.
I don't owe you anything.
I'll give you
what I have on them.
You'll have to save
your world. Not me.
Great. So, you're just
going to let us rot in slavery.
Your people are going to
have to defend
themselves like we did.
GARRETT: But someone like you
could give us the chance
we need to survive.
- You can't stop him.
- But you did.
There's nothing I can do now.
Nothing you can do or will do?
All right, then there's
nothing I will do.
You can waste your time with me,
or you can spend it
trying to stop them.
That's bullshit.
Once they're done with us here,
they'll return to Nobus
and finish what they started.
You'd be best off
going to a safe area.
Take your family with you.
It's your only chance.
Give me the keys to your car.
I'll give you a ride in the
city. That's all you're getting.
[gunshots]
[tense music]
[car door opening]
[car door closing]
♪♪♪
So is it official?
The rumors are expected
to become official in minutes.
If it is confirmed,
we are witnessing
the first major assassination
of the new millennium.
It is a great loss for mankind.
It is a terrible moment.
Is there any word yet
on who is responsible?
They say it's the work
of one man,
someone unknown to
the Vatican's inner circle
or to the Pope's group
of advisers.
Apparently he disappeared
mysteriously.
[birds tweeting]
[car door closing]
Virgil?
[speaking foreign language]
[water splashing]
Virgil?
Virgil's fine but he won't be
back for a while.
Who are you?
It's all right,
I'm not here to hurt you.
- I'm a government agent.
- Get out of my house, okay?
I have something very important
to show you, please!
Please, it's very important.
Wait.
It's about Virgil.
- What do you want from Virgil?
- He's in serious trouble.
We're all in serious trouble.
You need to watch this.
Please.
Not completely.
He just wants to use you.
He wants Earth's raw materials
and its manufacturing
infrastructure to
build ships and weapons.
He wants your population
as soldiers.
This is fake, okay?
I couldn't fake this.
If so, why is this truck here?
Where's Virgil?
This is my ID card.
Contact SciTech, they'll
confirm everything with you.
I don't trust you. Okay?
This is fake.
Get off my property. Now!
You didn't need to involve her!
GARRETT:
You gave me no choice!
I should erase your thoughts
and replace them
with those of a cockroach.
GARRETT:
Virgil, listen,
if they can find you,
they can find her.
- You're not an alien!
- Come on, Virgil, it can't be!
- VIRGIL: I'm sorry, I love you.
- You are sorry?
You are sorry?
You love me?
VIRGIL: Please, Rosa.
I can explain. I love you.
ROSA: Virgil, get away from me!
Rosa. Rosa,
you could be in danger!
Shit!
You don't understand.
She's all I have in this world.
Give me back my car keys.
I can't do that.
[grunts]
She'll be fine as long
as we work together,
and the sooner we act,
the better it is for everybody.
I should kill you.
In order for you to help Rosa,
you have to help me.
I can find Rosa on my own.
True. What if Piak finds
her first somehow?
You wouldn't give them
that kind of advantage.
But that's exactly what
you're doing by not helping me.
Mind your temper,
remember, we're equals.
All I have to do
is get away from you.
Filthy earthling.
I hope you're the first slave.
Maybe Rosa will be.
Sorry, I didn't want to have
to do things this way,
but you left me no choice.
I'll help you for now,
but I'm telling you will fail.
What? Did they teach you
that in the Morrucan Army?
Okay, let's check
the computer one more time.
[keys clacking]
- What is it?
- It's a message.
For us.
From Piak.
- He has Rosa.
- No way.
He also assassinated the Pope.
PIAK: Hello, gentlemen.
You can't kill me, remember?
I wouldn't bet on
that if I were you.
PIAK: Save it for later.
I need a favor from you.
- Where's Rosa?
- Relax, Morrucan.
She's fine.
I think she's enjoying
her connection to the computer.
You bastard.
Wait a minute. Let him finish.
Good. Now, listen carefully.
Two days from now, Reverend
Hope will be in New York.
He'll be staying
at the Plaza Hotel.
He'll be in his room
between five and six o'clock,
accompanied by only
five human bodyguards.
At exactly 5:37,
you will shoot him in the chest.
You'll make sure he dies. 5:37.
Not a minute before,
not a minute after.
You fail,
Rosa becomes my personal slave.
Sooner or later, Piak.
I can't wait.
Goodbye for now, gentlemen.
Why in the hell is
he betraying Allatarek?
I believe it's because of you.
[tense music]
♪♪♪
- Garrett.
- God bless you.
Now, that wasn't that hard,
was it?
Remembering the past
is the easy part.
Accepting the fact
that everyone's gone?
I don't think
I'm prepared for this.
Don't blame yourself.
Nobody saw it coming.
Reverend Hope and Piak
worked hard to find
a human that would survive
the DNA experiments.
They made a big mistake
letting you go.
They never saw your potential.
All these centuries,
Piak has been heavily patrolling
this planet, looking for you or
waiting for us to bring you in.
We have been protecting
you for all this time.
Earth was heavily contaminated,
so we had to wait.
How in the hell
did we let this happen?
There's no time for regrets.
If Piak captures you,
he will clone you
and create an invincible army.
So what now?
Over here, your palm
will activate the message.
[whirring]
[digital whirring]
VIRGIL: Welcome back, Garrett.
I'm glad you're still
in one piece.
These have been some
tough years.
You were right.
I should have cared much
earlier about your planet.
I am sorry I couldn't stop
the war on time.
You have suffered
a great memory loss
due to the alien
supplement you drank.
When your body couldn't
resist it much longer
and your death was inevitable,
I decided to preserve your life
and await your resurrection.
The community of
[indistinct] agreed
that we should give
humanity a second chance,
and they have planned
something special for you.
Not far from here,
there is a hidden city.
Inside the city,
there is a palace.
Your destiny awaits you there.
Good luck to you, old friend.
I am transmitting
the location now.
- [yelling]
- [digital whirring]
[mechanical winding]
[booming]
- [grunts]
- I got it. I know the way.
Excellent.
We must be on the way then.
Well, well, well.
Just like a class reunion.
SciTech Agents united.
Piak. I should have
killed you myself.
No, sir,
I'm going to kill you this time.
I got him, sir.
[blasting]
I killed you once,
and I'll kill you again,
and I'll kill your clones
and the clones of
your clones as I please.
This is my planet now,
and I will rule it
without any interference.
I'm your interference now.
What the hell
were you thinking
when you destroyed
the entire planet?
Come here and I'll kill you
with my bare hands.
Don't get emotional on me now.
Just make it easy for everybody.
Just surrender.
- Not likely.
- Look at you now, old man.
I've waited a long
time to find you.
Well, I'm not going
anywhere without a fight.
Get out of here, boys. I'll
handle these puppets myself.
[rumbling]
[yelling]
[explosion]
[intense music]
[exhaling]
Are you okay?
I think so, but I'm feeling
kind of weird again.
This is the last supplement
we have left.
Blue liquid.
Gotta love this stuff.
You're welcome.
[exhaling]
[panting]
You think Piak's dead?
He's getting stronger
every minute.
We can't take any chances.
Well, in that case, follow me.
I know where the hidden
palace is.
♪♪♪
- There.
- There's nothing there.
Can't you see it?
It's right there. Come on.
- You see it now?
- No.
You got a gun?
- [gunshot]
- [zapping]
[low buzzing]
Un-fucking-believable.
- Let's go.
♪♪♪
[whooshing]
[high-pitched whirring]
[whirring]
♪♪♪
[low buzzing]
Welcome.
We've been expecting you.
And you are?
I am Queen Ilona.
And you are my guest.
Queen of who exactly?
My planet was devastated like
yours by Piak and his army.
The community of mines
have brought us here
to rebuild our society.
So why am I here?
You are the reason
this palace exists.
You are the one
who will save mankind.
I don't recall applying
for that job.
A gift was given to you.
Your survival will give the
human race a second chance.
I don't quite understand.
You will.
We're running out of time.
Ladies, please escort
our guest to his room.
Make sure he gets ready
for the ceremony.
Ceremony?
This might sound strange,
but a ceremony must take place
in order for the community of
mines to send you back in time.
Back in time?
Yes, you will be travelling
soon.
[dramatic music]
♪♪♪
Now, let's get
the ceremony started.
When the light comes,
you must plunge this
dagger into your heart.
[chuckling]
Yeah, right.
That sounds like a great plan.
Your sacrifice
will save your world.
Look, Queen. I'm sorry,
I don't mean to rain
on your parade,
but I've been buried
a few hundred years,
I haven't got
my memory back yet.
And you expect me
to commit suicide,
travel back through time
so I can save the human race?
- Exactly.
- And if I don't?
There is not much life
left in you.
It is the only way
to save your planet
and change this dark future.
My queen, the army
has surrounded the temple.
The shield won't resist
much longer.
- [blasting]
- [booming]
Let's do something!
We are not warriors,
we have no weapons.
Great,
you're going to get slaughtered.
Why don't I just
turn myself over?
No, you can't do that.
You must fulfill your destiny.
We must get the ceremony
started.
I'd rather just fight them.
[tense music]
[women panting]
♪♪♪
- [blasting]
- [screaming]
♪♪♪
[cracking]
Stay down. Get down.
[blasting]
[screams]
♪♪♪
Glad you could join the party.
Who's the lady?
Queen Ilona,
meet your savior, Tony.
Thank you for your help.
Once this is over,
you will be rewarded.
- Thanks.
- Not bad for a clone.
- Is there another way out?
- No.
Yes, there is.
Let's give 'em some hell.
- Stay here.
- Ready?
- [blasting]
- [grunting]
♪♪♪
Piak!
- [screaming]
- [blasting]
No.
Ilona?
The light...
it's coming for us all.
♪♪♪
Erase his thoughts.
[pounding]
- [panting]
- Interesting.
You're next.
Did you have a nice nap?
Get enough rest?
Oh, and by the way,
sorry about your planet.
Just taking care of business.
Terrorism business?
Slaughtering millions of people?
Destroying an entire planet?
You're going to pay
big time for it, Piak.
You're the last survivor
of a weak race,
you have nowhere to run now.
Who's running?
Your time's up.
And what makes you
think you can beat me?
You're one small alien
on the wrong planet
at the wrong time.
I'll make you a deal.
You give me your DNA sequence
and I'll let you live.
I'll even spare
a few of these women.
You can start a family.
Nice offer.
But I've got a better plan.
How about we travel
back through time
and you die in the process?
So many years and you haven't
lost that sense of humor.
Remember, you can't kill me.
I am what you humans call
"immortal."
And you... you were the prototype
of a new breed,
a new race that
will make my army stronger.
You humans,
the missing link in my quest.
Well, keep dreaming, Piak.
[intense music]
♪♪♪
I gave you a chance.
[panting]
[grunts]
[blasting]
[zapping]
[yelling]
[rattling]
[thud]
[grunts]
[panting]
[tense music]
Show time.
♪♪♪
[grunts]
[crying out]
♪♪♪
[whoosh]
[fly buzzing]
[exhaling]
[moaning]
[small grunt]
Good morning.
Where are we?
I found you outside
the house last night naked
and you had a wound
to your chest.
Don't you remember?
And who are you and what are
you doing on my claim?
I'm sorry, I can't remember.
Um...
I'm a little confused.
Where are we exactly?
Tombstone, Arizona Territory.
Seriously?
Of all the places,
I get stuck in a tourist trap.
We don't get many
tourists around here.
Just prospectors...
like my late husband,
and thirsty cowboys.
- What year is it?
- 1880.
Look, um...
I want to thank you
for your hospitality,
but I got to get out of here.
I got to go.
Go where?
I got to go to the authorities
to figure all this out.
Perhaps Sheriff Clark
can help you?
If you're going to do that,
you'll need better clothing.
Yes, please.
I think you're about the same
size as my late husband.
Here, take these.
All right.
Thank you for your hospitality.
What... What's your name?
- Carol.
- Carol. I'm Garrett.
Nice to meet you.
Pleasure to meet you
and thank you very much,
but I got to get going. [grunts]
[bluesy music]
♪♪♪
Sheriff.
[birds tweeting]
You ain't from around here.
Funny you should say that,
because I'm definitely
not from around here.
Well, where are you coming from?
I can't really say,
but I need to confirm that
you are who you say you are
and that we are where
you believe we are.
I don't follow you there.
You better start talking,
who are you?
Okay. I am from the future.
Your future.
But something happened and I
wasn't supposed to end up here.
SHERIFF: But where
are you supposed to be?
That's not important.
My name is Garrett Brown.
I'm a special agent
for the U.S. government,
and I need to speak to the
president as soon as possible.
We don't go for that
crazy talk around here.
I think you're
going to need to stay here
until we figure out who you are.
Lock him up, boys.
♪♪♪
[gunshot]
El diablo!
Don't know how the hell
that happened.
Haul him back to the jail,
lock him up.
[metal clanging]
You boys clear out. I need
to talk to this man alone.
It's just me and you in here.
You tell me your story
and I'll listen.
Sure you're ready?
It's a hell of a ride.
That is one hell of a story.
- I believe you.
- You do. I do, Garrett.
I got a telegram.
Sky man, like you, showed up
in Las Cruces, New Mexico
a couple of days ago
and killed a few men.
According to this,
he's heading this way.
Can't be him, can it?
SHERIFF:
You mean that Pee-yak?
- Piak.
The alien conqueror
from your story?
If your story's true,
and I assume it is,
we better be ready for him.
I agree.
[horse hooves clopping]
[tense music]
♪♪♪
[ragtime music]
[tapping] Whiskey.
[doors squeaking]
- You look good.
- So do you. I think.
Didn't I just kill you?
Gentlemen, my friend here
thinks I can be killed.
A mistake he made
more than once.
You will find this
information amusing.
There was a glitch
in the system.
A virus was unleashed
into your population,
followed by a deadly pandemic,
and as you can imagine,
the community of minds
wanted to preserve your life
once again,
but gave you no warning.
So here we are.
Both of us stuck in
the past with no army,
no purpose and no blue liquid.
What a shame.
Well, maybe my DNA
could be a cure.
Too many maybes.
Sheriff?
You have exactly one minute
to go outside
and release your prisoner to me.
If you fail to comply,
I will have every gun
for hire in this dust bowl
shoot anyone who opposes.
That includes
women and children.
Ask him, I'm good for that.
Listen up, cowboys,
I will pay $1,000 dollars
to whoever brings me Diablo.
Dead or alive.
- Who wants to play?
- I do! I do!
[various men agreeing]
Whatever happens,
he cannot capture me.
Burn my body if necessary.
- He wants your DNA?
- Correct.
What the hell's DNA?
Let him out.
[lock rattles]
It's been a pleasure
to know you.
Let's give them some hell.
[tense music]
♪♪♪
[gun cocks]
[gunshots]
♪♪♪
[somber music]
[rattlesnake rattling]
This is my army?
[gunshot]
♪♪♪
You're not going to capture me.
I've got something
better than the blue liquid
if you want to stick around
a little longer.
This is your ticket home.
Reload,
I'll give you a chance.
[clicking]
♪♪♪
- You know bullets can't kill...
- [gunshots]
[static buzz]
You want to go
back to the future
and I'll risk everything
to kill you.
[thud then gasp]
You want my DNA, asshole?
[flesh squelching]
♪♪♪
[music intensifies]
[dramatic music]
[traffic din]
[slow percussive
dramatic music]
[honking]
♪♪♪
[car engine humming]
[music tempo lightens]
[intense dramatic music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull