Just when you think it's all over,
something unspeakable
comes after you and your family,
murders your sister Jenny in cold blood,
and disappears into thin air.
But a clue left behind leads us here,
to this club in Bangkok.
And that's why
we still need the Wu Assassin.
What's a Wu Assassin?
All right. So about a year ago,
my friends and I
were living it up in San Francisco.
Uh, my sister, Jenny, and I,
we ran this restaurant,
and, um, my boy Lu Xin, he ran cars,
until she showed up.
A 10,000-year-old warrior spirit
brought back to Earth.
And then she gave her powers to Kai,
my best friend.
And then he became
the last Wu Assassin. Whatever.
What, like The Avengers?
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
- But Asian.
Actually, no. More like
that show from the '70s.
Kai and Lu Xin are the Angels.
I'm like Charlie.
So what kind of mission?
Um, it's a supernatural one.
Sounds dangerous.
It's what we do.
- You seeing this?
- You know why we're here.
So your friend Kai…
- What about him?
- This Wu Assassin.
He's got to have
some kind of powers, right?
He's empowered
by this thing called the Dao.
He's faster and stronger than any man.
He calls himself Death's Instrument.
And your other friend?
Oh no, he's just
really good at kicking ass.
So why aren't you with them?
This seems more dangerous.
Do you want to continue your story
somewhere else?
Hell, yeah.
What about your friends?
They'll be fine.
I think.
Ah!
I fucking love Thailand.
Why Bangkok? I mean, what's here?
Answers.
I, uh,
traced this material back to Thailand.
It's from an ancient, old piece of stone.
Kai! Up there! He's turning them.
Jiangshi.
Chi vampire.
What's so special about this?
I found it in my dead sister's hand.
Kai, Lu Xin, and I
came back to my family restaurant,
and she was just there,
dead on the ground.
Well, here's to your sister.
You want to know a secret?
Sure.
Come here.
I don't drink anymore.
This will turn you into
a Jiangshi, won't it?
I just want to talk.
Your powers don't work on me.
Who killed Jenny?
Who killed my sister?
Kai!
- He's not talking!
- Ah!
Ah!
Assassin's strike.
That's not what I was thinking at all.
Yo. Hey, hey! What is this?
Yo! Press the start button, man.
This isn't me.
It's me. I need your help.
You? Who are you?
No,
I'm speaking through them.
I can't hold it for long.
It's not safe
to put myself out here like this.
What do you want?
Not here.
8:00 a.m.
Silom Temple archaeological dig site.
We have much to discuss, Wu Assassin.
I am never coming
to a club with you ever again.
- Who was that?
- We should call Tommy.
Stop the van!
Yeah.
She didn't know anything.
What about your Jiangshi?
I guess we finally have a lead.
The archaeological site
is owned by this biotech billionaire.
Not much else on him,
but he owns that building.
So, uh, we're just
going to roll onto his turf?
If it gets us closer to Jenny's killer,
that's all that matters.
Looks shady as fuck.
It should be up on the right.
Guessing he's not the valet.
Since founding his firm
in 1999,
William Pan has formed
collaboration agreements
with the world's largest companies.
Providing scientists
the opportunity and resources
to tackle humankind's
most perplexing problems.
All in service of William's unique vision.
One people,
one world,
one planet.
We're not just looking to the future…
We're looking to shape it.
Thank you for coming.
I know my message was unorthodox.
I apologize for not meeting you in person.
Communicating like that was difficult.
Dr. William Pan.
Do you know the story of Pan Gu?
Yeah, we do.
The first man to shape the universe
from the great nothingness
and made the heavens,
the Earth, and the seas.
We all went to Chinese school.
Chinese school didn't teach you
what happened to Pan Gu
after he became a god.
He went mad with power.
Threatened to remake the world
in his own image.
But the Dao,
in its infinite celestial wisdom,
called upon the first Wu Assassin
to strike down that first man.
Yin and yang. Chaos and order.
These spirits have clashed for millennia.
I'm not the first vessel.
But thanks to you,
I am the last.
And with the world left unbalanced,
chaos and I can finally complete
our unending war.
I was attacked.
Barely made it out alive.
And that's why
I've retreated here for safety,
while my twin continues to spread chaos.
Who is he?
She.
Yin and yang.
You might have heard of her. Ku An Qi.
Queen of the Bangkok underworld.
She's going global.
Taking out any threats to her.
Consuming Chi to build her power.
The Shaolin in China.
The Druids in Ireland.
And last month, she went to San Francisco.
Ku An Qi was looking for you,
but your friend intervened.
Jenny.
She fought valiantly.
But Ku cannot be stopped.
She will continue her rampage
if left unchecked.
How do you know all this?
Because Ku and I are connected.
That is why I must be careful.
If I open myself up to her,
she will come.
Follow me.
This whole thing could be bullshit.
In the fight,
your sister took something of Ku's,
a talisman.
I have the other half.
I assume you have hers.
What's it matter to you?
It's a piece of our Essence.
- She'll try to get it back.
- Good. Send her my way.
In two days' time, my worse half
is meeting the heads of the Five Triads
at the Vie Hotel,
solidifying her power base.
Cameras everywhere, no weapons allowed.
- There's no honor in guns.
- And won't she know what you're up to?
I'm doing my best
to shield my thoughts from her.
My powers extend to the mind,
while hers are focused on the body.
Ah…
A kidnapping mission in broad daylight.
Hotel security,
the five bosses of the Triads,
their whole crews.
You know what?
I got a better idea.
Why don't you do the mind control thing
and send an army after them?
I can't control an army.
I can reach out, communicate,
hold a thought for a minute.
But that is the extent of my powers now.
Well, it seems like you got
all the answers, but the answers.
We're in.
When you subdue Ku,
you bring her to me with the talisman,
and I'll take care of the rest.
No.
You said the Dao is broken.
Yes.
But you and I together,
maybe we can restore it.
Or we let it be broken.
And I kill her.
The hotel, it's a death trap.
Yeah, but it's the person, demigod,
whatever, who murdered Jenny.
Yes, I understand that,
which is why we need to be smart about it.
- Look at the pieces in front of us.
- This isn't a game.
Actually, it is a game.
Everything is a game, Tommy.
We have the perfect opportunity right now.
We should take advantage of it.
If you have a death wish
because of your sister, don't drag me...
You act like
you don't care about Jenny at all!
- That's the game. No one's safe.
- Ah, fuck you, man.
- Yeah, fuck you too.
- Guys! Calm down.
I'm calm!
Ku An Qi wants the Wu Assassin.
I'll give her the Wu Assassin. Myself.
We're going together.
- No.
- It might not be the smartest choice,
but, look,
this is the only opportunity we have.
Fuck that. No way. I'll do this one alone.
You know what your problem is, Kai?
You think because you have powers,
you're better than us.
Like we're just
some kind of fucking burden.
Lu Xin is calling his contact.
Can he get a rocket launcher
to take Ku down?
You never know, with magic.
But I guess this worked.
Let me show you something.
Keep this finger loose.
It'll make it easier.
Try that.
I'm coming. I don't care what you say.
I have to go. Okay?
Look, Tommy.
You go angry, you get yourself killed.
That's… that's not how you fight.
You got to understand, though, man.
It's the only thing I have.
Anger.
Sorry to break up
the tanning session, boys.
Bad news.
The dude who outfitted us
for the Jiangshi mission blocked me.
Too much heat at the club.
Anyone else?
I mean, as soon as they hear
we're going after Ku An Qi,
they lose my number fast.
I might know someone crazy enough to help.
What? Since when
did you get a Bangkok hookup?
I said "might."
I'll hit her up.
Something just
doesn't feel right about this.
Something smells good.
- Whoa.
- Thank you so much.
What's Preeya look like anyway?
Like that.
Hey! How are you?
- Hey!
- It's been a long time. What's happen...
Now we've got that over with.
What's up, Thomas?
Thomas.
Uh, first, why are we meeting here?
Oh, you know, support the local economy.
Plus, it's out in the open. Can't be
too careful these days.
You, I know.
Them…
…don't know.
Wow.
Oh shit.
Where are we going?
Ah, too many questions.
You know who I work for?
Interpol, police of the world.
We know your Triad is meeting
with Ku An Qi, a known terrorist.
When?
And where?
Good luck.
Agent Zulu, bonjour.
That means, fuck off.
Both of you.
You wanna have fun?
The Vie Hotel, tomorrow.
You might wanna call in the cleaners.
I thought he gave you the information.
The actual cleaners.
He soiled himself.
Uh, Preeya, meet the boys.
Boys, this is, uh, Preeya.
'Sup. Lu Xin.
- Lu, is that a "Sin" or a "Xin"?
- Is that supposed to be a funny joke?
- What's his problem?
- Don't worry. He's cool.
Uh, this is my man, Kai.
- Hello.
See? Someone's got manners.
- Where's your sister?
- Oh, she's not here.
That's too bad. I love Jen.
Anywho.
Hear you boys are on a suicide mission.
What the fuck, Thomas. You told her?
It's the only way she'd help.
I have to tell her everything.
Yeah, I like to know
what I'm getting into.
Due diligence.
If you know, then why are you helping?
I don't mind a little action.
It's part of the territory.
This woman you're dealing with,
serious shit. Lots of people dying.
She needs to be stopped.
Can you get this?
Let me make some calls.
Enjoy your shopping, boys.
Keep your mouth shut.
Shopping?
Mmm.
The fuck?
Thank you.
- Tommy?
- Yeah.
How do you know her again?
Oh, um…
So I was actually here five years ago,
and someone stole my Louis V backpack.
They took my wallet,
passport, phone, everything.
So I went to the cops to report it,
and, uh, the cops didn't do anything.
- So, someone told me to go talk to...
- Uh.
I'm just gonna make
this story short and sweet,
in case we ever have
to hear it again, okay?
He got his shit jacked,
and he doesn't know anything about her.
Okay, guys. Look, she's our only hookup.
- We need this.
- And beggars can't be choosers.
- Did you get it?
- Yes, every goddamn thing.
See?
Thank you!
Listen. I know it's none of my business.
But, you know, I'm fond of this one.
So I got to tell you guys that your plan...
Is none of your business.
Relax, big guy.
We're on the same team.
There is no way you're getting
that hardware into the Vie Hotel.
It's locked down tight,
and the only way in is through the front.
I don't like this. We need to rethink it.
All right. I'll take care of it.
No. Tomorrow, we're all going.
We're gonna get Jenny's killer together.
Hey! Yo!
Jen's dead?
Uh, yeah. Our target took her out.
Now it's our turn.
Shit.
I'm so sorry.
I can help you get in.
It's dangerous.
I know.
Security there is tight.
We can use that to our advantage.
We?
Morning, boys.
Hey. Thanks.
Is this your idea of a joke?
Trust me.
This is 007 shit.
We're good.
Okay. Be careful with these.
Wow.
What's so special about them?
- Magic.
- Come on. Let's go.
Hey.
We're gonna get justice for her.
What do you think?
You don't want to know, Lu.
Then we're thinking the same thing.
Come on.
Hey!
Okay. Whoa, whoa! What did we do?
We didn't do anything!
Goddamn!
A bit much, isn't it?
Are you guys seeing this?
Looks like a dipshit nobody.
Ah.
Get up.
- All right. Easy. Easy.
- Can I talk to your manager?
Hey, we're just on holiday.
We're valued customers.
One-star Yelp review on the way!
Agent Zulu.
Let the hotel security handle that.
You just focus on…
Why are you here?
You're wasting your time.
It's for Songkran,
the Thai water festival.
That's not until April.
Yeah. Well, we like to be prepared.
Now you're gonna
have to reorganize her bag.
You for real?
Yes, I'm for real.
- Bullshit!
- Look at all this mess.
Stay here.
What's going on?
Where is our fucking visual?
- I'm working on it.
- Our gear is still working.
Whatever is happening
is only affecting the hotel.
Something is going down.
This is not good.
Zulu! Zulu!
Your card. ID card.
You are my men now.
Come on. Fix it.
- Close your eyes.
- What?
Just close your eyes.
- Trust me.
- Come on!
Hey!
Come on. Let's get out of here.
See you in a second.
Stop!
Hyah!
- Good timing.
- Yeah. Of course it is.
Ah, fuck. Who the fuck did this?
Hands where I can see 'em.
Zama?
Lu.
What are you doing here?
- You know her?
- Yeah, we met in London.
I was pushing some Aston Martins,
and my broker turned out
to be Interpol's finest.
- Look, hey, these bodies...
- Get down on your knees!
This wasn't us.
So you just tripped
and fell into a massacre?
Zama, you know me.
You think I would do this?
There's a lot I don't know about you, Lu.
This is bigger and more complicated
than you can imagine.
Try me.
The fate of the world.
- I didn't come to fuck around.
- Don't!
Agent Boucher.
I have two suspects. I need backup.
Boucher?
Whoever got them probably got your team.
Interlace your fingers behind your head,
and get down on the floor.
- I don't want to hurt you.
- Kai. Don't.
Listen to your friend.
He seems to be the reasonable one.
First time I've heard that.
Lower your gun.
- What the fuck happened here?
- We're working on it.
Let her go. She's not the threat. Please.
Look, it's clear that none of us
are the bad guys.
But they are coming.
Who's coming?
The entire hotel.
On your six!
- I got it.
- I'm just looking out for you.
- Because that's always been your MO.
- Here we go again.
You could just say sorry.
- What?
- Sorry works just fine.
Did you guys,
like, used to date or...
- No!
Zan.
Assassin.
Why are you here?
They offered me a deal.
The Wu Assassin in exchange for power.
Where we going?
-Fuck. Come with me
-Go!
Hyah!
Shit!
Fuck! Get in the car!
Looks like you're not
the only special one.
Look out!
Hey. Hey, hey, take it easy.
Fuck.
It's locked!
Go!
Door says push, not pull.
What?
Hold up. Where's Kai?
Don't worry about Kai, all right?
Oh shit. You okay?
Yo, you good?
Zan?
- Yo, we gotta go. Come on.
- My van's still here. Come on!
Get in.
- What happened back there?
- What happened in here?
This is chaotic.
You know what to do.
If only you would've listened to me
when I told you something's sketchy.
We didn't have another lead.
Take them down.
Get me out of here now.
- Shit.
- What?
In case you thought we lost 'em,
we didn't.
Hold tight.
Can you get to Khaosan Road?
- We have another safe house there.
- Yeah.
Shit.
It's the end of the road.
Get out of the car!
- She's locking down the city.
- What are we gonna do?
Sail away.
I'm really starting
to strongly dislike you.
We get to the canal.
Take a boat up the Chao Phraya.
That plan is just...
Stop firing.
Get them out of the car.
Bring them to me.
I changed my mind.
I like the plan.
Yeah. River, boat.
- If you wanna join me, guns are up top.
- Come on.
Shoot it! Let's get these fuckers!
Ah, fuck. I'm all out.
Shh. Shh. Shh.
They're trying
to burn us alive. We gotta go!
Okay. Everybody, follow me.
Hey!
Hey. Hey.
Yo, what's up?
Never seen that before.
I picked up a few things
since you ghosted me.
Yeah. Well, if I'd have stayed,
it would've been behind bars, wouldn't it?
This way. The river.
Get out the way!
Get to the boat!
Get off my boat!
Kai! Look out!
Go, go!
- Get us out of here!
- Come on!
Hurry, they're catching up!
Faster, faster, faster! Come on!
Get out of the way!
We're almost there.
It's just up ahead.
Ah, Preeya!
You are back.
I didn't know if we'd ever see you.
Everyone's excited to see you.
So this is your home.
- It's been a while since I was last here.
- What about your family?
They were long gone before that.
Um…
What's this?
Magical protection.
If they don't want you, you can't pass.
I guess they want us in.
This is the home of a shaman.
He knows everything
about the supernatural.
If anyone might know what's going on,
it's Chatree.
You used to call me
a charlatan, didn't you?
Uncle!
It's nice to meet everyone.
You all must be starving.
- 100%
-How'd you know?
Usually,
I am the one showing hospitality.
You are.
It is my honor
to have such an esteemed guest.
What do you know about Pan Gu?
In Thailand, we don't talk business
on an empty stomach.
Is that a saying?
One that I just made up.
There are people after us.
There will always be people after you.
Here we are well-protected.
We have weapons.
Is this a prank?
No.
But it is funny
that this bracelet is yours.
But it is not for you.
You speak like Yoda, old man.
Baby Yoda.
I am only 50.
Pan Gu.
Uncle.
William Pan, he wasn't, uh,
completely honest with you.
Yeah? No shit.
Pan and Ku An Qi are opposite forces.
Yin
and yang.
But they are not
in opposition to each other.
They are two halves of a whole.
They have been working in harmony
through all their births,
lives, deaths, rebirths
towards one goal,
reforming back to Pan Gu,
the first man.
And using their power,
they will remake the world in their image.
And now that the Dao is broken,
they have the opportunity.
How will they do that?
By harnessing the Chi
of the one who split them.
The Wu Assassin.
The two of them
each have a piece of their old Essence.
The only constant they have,
forged from the stone
of the temple where they were split.
If they can infuse the pieces
with Kai's Chi,
they will be able to connect the halves.
Does it look something like this?
Where did you get that from?
I mean, it doesn't matter.
If it's part of Ku,
we'll just destroy it...
It can't be destroyed!
I've had quite enough, thank you.
This…
This whole thing is just crazy.
You okay?
I'm just trying to wrap my head around
this supernatural shit
and the world ending.
Yeah.
What did you do when you first found out?
I had just shot
a Russian gangster in the face.
So you could say
it was a little bit weird.
Honestly?
I poured myself a big fucking drink.
Ugh. This is terrible.
Can't be worse than that Chinese
whiskey we had in Brick Lane.
Yeah. Well, that was…
that was part of a job, so…
Is that what I was to you?
Just part of the job.
I can taste when you're lying.
Training?
Meditation.
My meditation is meditation.
- You're not worried about us losing?
- No, I'm not.
Because if that should happen,
Pan Gu would remake the world,
and we would simply be
the forgotten dreams of a butterfly.
Sounds peaceful.
But that is the one thing
that the Wu Assassin can never have.
He may have friends
that he's shutting out.
It's my responsibility to protect them.
You have lost one.
And now you're trying everything
to avoid that pain again.
They're all I have left.
But Pan Gu seeks to control all.
What do you want, Wu Assassin?
We'll stop him.
We'll stop him. We'll make plans.
There's a Jeep there.
There is the path
that leads to the main road.
From there, it's an easy ride to wherever.
You did not come here to train
or reflect.
You came here to leave
after everyone went to bed.
Last time I was here was, um…
Ten years ago.
Family had a farm by the river.
There was a bad flood.
Water came suddenly, and just like that…
My mum, my dad,
and my sister were gone.
No magical attack.
No clash for the world.
It was, uh,
just an accident.
There's nothing I can do
to bring my family back,
but I thought I could bring you
some peace for Jen.
And that is why I'm helping.
At least there's something you can do.
You have Kai,
Lu Xin.
Me…
I'm all alone.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
Well, you never asked.
This can't be real.
It isn't.
It's the version
of the village in your mind
from when you were a child.
But we can make it like this again.
We can make it into whatever we want.
Pan Gu is all.
Mum, Dad, Ratana!
I miss you.
You can be together again…
…forever.
All we need is one small thing.
The Wu Assassin's Chi.
It'll be easy.
- What are you doing?
- I had no choice.
What did they promise you?
Get up.
What's going on?
What do you think?
I fuck with these.
- There's more down there. Let's go.
- Yo! Tommy, hold up!
I'll get Preeya.
- What?
- Be careful, okay?
I am getting really,
really sick of this shit.
Tommy, get the Jeep.
We'll hold them off
while Zama and Preeya get here.
Preeya betrayed us.
- No. She wouldn't.
- What?
She took Ku An Qi's necklace.
- Fuck.
- Lu, get Zama. Tommy, the car!
- Hold on. We're stronger together.
- Just do as I say!
Shit.
Oh shit.
Zama.
Preeya betrayed us. We gotta go now.
I know. I saw her leave
with Pan's men. Let's go.
Calm down, boys.
Hyah!
Ah!
All right. Let's go, guys!
Come on, let's go.
Come on, everybody in.
Hey!
You can no longer be stopped.
It's in your hands now. Go!
Don't let Pan Gu reform!
- No! Chatree!
- Get in the car!
- We need to go!
- Drive, Tommy!
We shouldn't have left Chatree.
- Should have listened to me.
- There wasn't anything to listen to.
- I made a decision.
- Yeah. Nothing new there, Kai.
- I'm leading us.
- No, you're not. You're shutting us out.
Guys, let's focus on
what the fuck we're gonna do now.
I'm sorry. You have no right to say shit.
- What the fuck you talking about?
- What do you mean?
Your little girlfriend that you brought
into our inner circle betrayed us.
You gonna put that on me?
Sure, you weren't on the lookout either.
You were occupied fucking Zama.
And, Kai, like, what the fuck?
What were you doing? What was your plan?
My plan was to kill Pan and Ku myself.
- Like I should have done.
- Yeah? Great, 'cause you're always right.
We don't need you.
I don't need any of you.
True! I'm going myself.
- Get the fuck out of here!
- Just stop it!
All of you.
You're acting like little children.
Do I need to remind you
that we need to stop a god
from destroying reality?
You say you're a family.
You're not acting like a family,
not one that's about to save the world.
Because you cannot
even take care of each other.
If you can…
Just get over your anger…
Your guilt…
Your ego.
We might actually have a chance.
We really might.
So, let's remind ourselves.
Why are we here?
For Jenny.
She's right.
We're all fucking idiots.
No, no, no, no.
No.
I'm the idiot.
I'm a fucking idiot.
For Jenny.
- For Jenny.
Now we're getting somewhere.
When we were at Pan's temple,
I saw that splitting symbol in a photo
of a factory at another dig site.
That's where the stone came from,
so we gotta go to that dig site.
But they only have
half of the symbol completed, so, like,
they're gonna need your power.
No. We shouldn't risk it.
No, no. We should. We should.
Because they'll come after all of us
if we don't stop them.
This ends tonight.
If you all agree.
As long as we're smart about it.
You can count me in.
We are all the Wu Assassins.
Shit.
- Let's go kill a god.
- Let's do it.
There are a lot of guards here.
They'll know we're coming.
They already know I'm here.
In that case…
Boom.
This is where
the first Wu Assassin tore us apart.
They'll be here soon.
This Wu Assassin
is particularly hard to kill.
I got this.
This thing killed my uncle.
How many more people have to die
before I get my family back?
Your problem, child,
is that you see death as the end.
You'll be with them soon enough.
Along with all living things.
That's where the stone is melted.
Those are the sleeping quarters.
- Those are the main pressing machines.
- How do you know?
Wikipedia.
We gotta be careful.
They still need you for the ritual, so…
Get down! Move!
Zan.
- What do you want to do?
- We're splitting up.
Yeah. We're not divided.
We're dividing them.
I got Zan. Lu, the Beast.
You guys find Pan and Ku.
Fuck!
Try this. It's got good range.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
Zan!
Let's finish this.
I promised myself
I'd erase anything related
to when I was a pawn of your father's.
We started with Jenny.
And it ends when I kill you, Assassin.
You're not the one I'm looking for.
Well, we are who you've got, bitch.
The necklace isn't here.
None of this matters if we can't find it.
They're not fools, Tommy.
Let's go find the others.
You fucking piece of shit.
- The fuck were you thinking?
- Wait. No. Stop.
Hey.
Tell me they mind-controlled you.
They told me I could see my family again,
and I made a mistake,
and I'm so sorry. So sorry!
I messed up.
Hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
Mastery over the body has its perks.
Fucking magic.
- Give up.
- Never.
Get up!
This isn't for me.
This is for all of us.
Welcome.
- Lu Xin!
- He'll be fine.
Your friends took out Ku.
But you
will not be so lucky.
I am Pan Gu,
the first man.
Control of mind, body, and soul.
Lu. Lu, wait. Hey.
Brother. It's not you!
- Pan Gu!
- Kai.
What the fuck?
The trouble is, you are but one man,
while I am all.
Brother, I don't want to do this.
Thank you
for your sacrifice.
No. No!
Lu! Lu! Lu!
Fight it.
We can't do this without you.
Fight it, brother! Wake up!
Come on, Lu! Get up!
We need you, brother!
Tommy.
- Come on. You can do it.
- Fucking bitch.
I think we've got bigger problems.
Let's go.
What the fuck happened?
Is that you? Hey.
Of course, it's fucking me.
Who else would it be?
Nice.
Let's kill this motherfucker.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Lu!
- Kai!
- Lu, what's going on?
- Ah, Lu! Ah!
- It's sinking!
Grab that.
Kai! Heads up!
- I can't hold.
- Hold on. Hold on, Kai!
Lu!
No!
Stay there. Zama!
- Yeah?
- Follow me.
Tie that!
Gotcha.
- This is serious, man.
- No shit!
- You guys know knots?
- We're about to find out.
Girl Scout those ropes together.
We'll bring 'em up with up this.
Let me know when there's enough rope.
Kai, this isn't working.
Come up with something.
You're the Wu Assassin.
Come on! Grab it! Grab it!
- Zama?
- Almost there.
Let me know when you guys are good.
Start pulling!
Ah! It's about time.
All right, guys. I need help.
Come on! Come on!
Come on, Zama.
Keep going!
Keep going! Keep going!
It's over.
I know a really nice,
safe passage out. Come on.
Food's ready, guys.
Looks good.
Hold it, man. First, a toast.
To family. New and old.
To family. Cheers!
To Jenny.
So, Kai, what's next?
- I'm off to fight a necromancer.
- Ooh!
I guess we're going on vacation then.
- We? I thought you could handle yourself.
- What do you mean?
Oh wow. Here we go with the talk.
Look, look, look,
just 'cause I kicked your ass,
all of us saw it,
but we don't have to talk about it.
- You wanna spar? You wanna try me?
- Do I want to spar?
I don't got to prove anything to you!
You're the Wu Assassin.
I'm just the Lu Assassin.
- You gonna let him say that?
- Oh!
Okay. Okay.
- Oh my God. That's crazy.
- Guys, guys, guys.
- Let's get him!
- Ah!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- He's going in.
Get him in the water.