[THUNDER]
[KIDS SINGING JOHN JACOB
JINGLEHEIMER SCHMIDT]
[THUNDER]
[KIDS SINGING]
-Thank god.
OK, kids.
We're almost there.
[KIDS SINGING]
[TRAIN HORN]
-It's not working.
-The crossing guard,
it's not working.
[KIDS SINGING]
[TRAIN HORN]
[SHOUTING]
[KIDS SINGING]
[SCREAMING]
[KIDS SINGING AND
PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[TRAIN HORN]
[SCREAMING AND CRASHING]
-The bus was torn to pieces.
None of the kids
survived the accident.
-Crystal, you are
so full of shit.
All of the kids died?
-It's totally true.
Melanie, bodies were everywhere.
And body parts.
-That's terrible, especially
for such a small town.
-They say if you park your car
at the spot where it happened
and put it in neutral,
it moves by itself.
-Ohh.
-Pushed over the
tracks to safety
by the ghosts of
the dead children.
-Can you say urban legend?
-I swear, it's true.
I hate to say it,
but that accident
is the only thing this
town has going for it.
-Well, anything's
better than rehab.
-Yeah, except for
moving back in with mom
and dad in some lame ghost town.
Let me know if you want me to
take you back to the airport.
-No.
I mean, it's time I
get back to reality.
-Melanie, can I
ask you something?
-Of course.
-What was it like?
-Rehab?
You know, it wasn't the typical
melodrama you would think.
You just spend a lot of time
in the mountains, hiking,
learning how to survive.
Someday I want to go, just
you and me in the mountains.
-That sounds like a plan.
Here we are.
-Where?
-This is where it happened.
-These are the train tracks?
-Yep.
-Yeah.
-Now, we're going to
try a little experiment.
-OK.
-Let's see if it really works.
-Hmmm.
Wow, we're really moving.
-Patience, little sister.
[TRUCK HONKING]
[SCREAMING]
-Come on.
Move it!
-OK, asshole!
-Damn kids.
-There you go.
[GRUNTS]
-Hey, there she is.
Look at this.
Oh, you look great.
-Hi.
-Oh.
What do you think of this house?
Nice, huh?
-It's huge.
-That's one benefit of
moving out of the city.
Really good to see you, Mel.
We missed you.
-Me, too, daddy.
-Hello, Melanie.
You're looking well.
-Hi, mom.
It's good to see you.
-How are you doing?
-I'm fine.
-I know this is probably
a big change for you.
-It's OK.
I'm glad I wasn't here
while you guys were moving.
I hate moving.
-Well, it's been a big
change for all of us.
But I think we
can be happy here.
Do you think you
could be happy here?
-I don't know.
I've only been
here three minutes.
-You know what I mean.
-Hey, let me-- let
me take you inside.
Come on.
You're gonna love it.
Home sweet home.
-Wow.
It's nice.
-Your room's right
up here, honey.
Here we are.
Where-- where's my computer?
-We didn't think it
was a good idea for you
to have one right now.
-How am I supposed
to do my homework?
On an abacus?
-Use your sister's
computer for now.
-Dinner will be ready
in about 30 minutes.
-You know, the guy
at the store said
you can only use so
many minutes a month.
So I guess use it wisely.
Gotta built-in camera.
-Thanks, dad.
-Oh, it's good to see you.
Oh.
And, uh, don't tell mom
about the cell phone.
-Don't worry about it.
[SIGHS]
[CHUCKLE]
-You wanna get high?
-Yeah.
What is that?
-It's chiva.
It's incredible.
-Heroin?
Are you kidding me?
I'm not shooting up.
-You don't have to.
Trust me.
You won't-- you won't be sorry.
-Shawn.
Shawn.
Shawn!
-It took about three years
for total construction.
Now, normally it
would take longer.
But we're laying
the turnpike right
over the existing
train track route.
So we don't expect to relocate
any of the properties.
-Well, that sounds wonderful.
Congratulations, dad.
-Yeah.
Well, it's not
like I designed it.
I mean, this job
was supposed to have
been done in the late '50s.
But they put it back until now.
That's more than 40 years later.
-Bureaucracy at its finest.
Maybe the haunted train
track scared everyone away.
-Melanie, please don't start
trashing the place so soon.
-I was kidding.
-So, now that you're
back, have you
given any thought
to your future?
-Mom, she just got here.
-Thank you, Crystal.
I'm well aware of that.
Well, Melanie?
-I hear the, uh, state school
has an excellent dance program.
-Dad.
-You made a beautiful ballerina.
-That was five years ago.
-Which is all the more
reason to get back into it.
-Ballet is for kids, mom.
-Well, don't tell
the Russians that.
I mean, they love ballet.
-Melanie, all I'm saying is that
idle hands do the devil's work.
You should know that
better than anyone.
Don't go after her, Edward.
She knows I'm right.
-(WHISPERING)Mel.
Mel.
Come on.
-Where are we going?
-Out.
-I don't think that's
such a good idea.
[SHUSHING]
-Come on.
-See you later.
-Hey, Crystal.
PARTY-GOERS (OFFSCREEN): Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
-What's up?
-Three.
Two.
One.
[CHEERING]
-You're up.
-Ohhh!!!
-Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
[CHEERING]
-Oh, fuck.
-You OK with this?
-Yeah.
Just say no.
Right?
-Go fist yourself.
[LAUGHING]
-That's Mitch.
[JEERING]
-Thirteen.
Twelve.
Eleven.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-There he is.
Penn!
Hey, Penn.
Come here.
Hey.
-What's up, ladies?
-Penn, this is my little sister.
-How's it going?
-Hi.
I'm Melanie.
-You know, uh, our dads are
working on the highway project
together.
-Oh.
-I guess that means
we'll be hanging out.
Right, Crystal?
-Hell yeah.
-Can I get you ladies a drink?
-Sure.
-Melanie, you thirsty?
-Um, maybe something
nonalcoholic.
-OK.
Cool.
Chucky!
Two beers, s'il vous
plait, and a club soda.
-Two brews coming up.
[CHEERING AND CLAPPING]
-There you go.
There you go.
Crazy bastard.
[LAUGHING]
-(SIGHING) Thank you.
-Appreciate it, man.
-All right.
-Hey, where's the bathroom?
-Through the
kitchen, to the left.
-OK.
Thank you.
Hold my purse.
-Cute.
-Ah-ha.
You kinda like her.
-All right!
-So I don't know
if you knew this.
[VOMITING]
[KNOCKING]
-Go away!
-You want some of this?
-Aww, prude!
Come on.
Hey!
-Don't talk like
that, shit breath.
Come on, man.
-Great.
[SIGHS]
-Club soda?
-Thank you.
-Of course.
So how does your
sister like Emerald?
-I took Melanie by
the railroad crossing,
but she didn't believe in the
story about the dead children.
I mean, we went to
the train tracks.
And we tried it,
but it didn't work.
I don't know.
I still believe it.
-I don't know.
-Sorry.
-Melanie, right?
-Yeah.
-Can I ask you something?
-Sure.
-Is it true you OD'd?
You like died and
came back to life?
-Who told you that?
-(LAUGHS) So it is true.
Freak.
[LAUGHING]
-What's up, baby?
-Can I talk to you?
-Sure.
-Are you fucking telling people?
-Telling people what?
-About rehab.
-No!
Yes.
Just Penn and maybe Mitch.
-Well, now barf butt knows, too.
So apparently everyone
in town knows.
-I'm sorry.
I only told because--
-I don't care.
-Don't worry.
Rehab's the in thing.
-Yeah, and next year
it'll be bulimia.
-I'm really sorry.
Do you want me to take you home?
-No.
I don't want to ruin your night.
-I just want you to have fun.
-Anybody want to go for a ride?
-Let's do it.
[LOUD MUSIC]
-Why are we letting the
drunkest one of us drive?
-Actually, he's the only
one who won't get busted.
His uncle's chief of police.
-Right.
-Yow!
Woo-hoo!
[SCREECHING TIRES]
-Uh, I think you have to stop
before the actual tracks,
Mitch.
-Mmmm.
Baby powder is a necessity.
-How many times
have you done this?
-First time.
-Seriously?
-Seriously.
Melanie, we're not as
backward as you might think.
-Hmm.
-Bastard.
-Well, uh, most of us.
Mitch has done this before.
I don't believe in ghosts.
-Neither do I. What is he doing?
-The legend says if you
put powder on the bumper,
you'll see the fingerprints
of the dead children,
but only if you truly believe.
-I'll believe it when I see it.
-I guess we're
about to find out.
[WHISTLING]
[SIGHING]
-This will be fucking awesome!
They're coming for you, Melanie.
Ooooo!
-Leave her alone.
-Relax.
Just playing.
Here we go.
Come on, you little fuckers.
-Nothing's happening, Mitch.
-What a surprise.
-All right.
Give it a minute.
[TRAIN HORN]
-Ah, OK.
The ghosts are sleeping.
Let's go.
[TRAIN HORN]
[CROSSING BELL]
-Come on.
I'm serious.
-They will push us when
the train gets closer.
-That's bullshit.
-Come on, Mitch.
-Let's go.
[TRAIN HORN]
-This isn't funny.
-Don't be a dickhead, Mitch.
Move the car!
-What the hell are you doing?
Come on!
-Screw this.
-What the hell are
you doing, Mitch?
Move the car!
-Unlock the fucking
doors, Mitch.
-Non-believers!
-This isn't funny, Mitch!
-They'll push us when
the train gets closer!
-Come on!
[SCREAMING]
-They're gonna push us!
-Mitch, let me out of the car!
[SCREAMING]
-This isn't funny!
Let's go!
-Let me out of the car!
Let me out of the car!
[SCREAMING]
-Noooo!
[SCREECHING TIRES]
-That's what I'm talking about.
-You asshole!
-Woo-hoo!
-Fucking ass.
Man, what's your problem?
-Hey, man.
Fucking relax.
Jesus.
Fucking chill out.
-Where is she?
Did you guys see her?
Shit.
-She is nuts.
-What the fuck?
-Little girl!
Little girl!
-Melanie, where are you going?
-Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid.
Hello?
Little girl!
-Hey.
You OK?
-What are you doing over here?
This place is creepy.
-Didn't you see the little girl?
-Hello?
Mr. Pearl!
-Dude.
Enough.
-Who's Mr. Pearl?
-Oh, he used to be the train
conductor that ran this depot.
-Now, his ghost haunts it.
-After the bus crashed Mr.
Pearl hung himself right here
in the depot.
They say he felt the
accident was his fault.
-Well, maybe we
should go inside.
-Hell no.
[GASPS]
-It's him!
-Hey!
You kids shouldn't be here.
This place is condemned.
[LAUGHING]
-What's so funny?
He's an old man.
-That's Fuzzy Keeler,
the town drunk.
-Of course.
-Our parents said if
we drank and did drugs,
we'd end up like
Old Fuzzy Keeler.
-Ahhh.
-You don't scare us, bum.
I gotta take a leak.
-Let's get out of here.
[SIGHS AND WHISTLES]
-You know what?
I'm driving.
-Is he waiting for another girl?
-I guess so.
-Hey.
I ran out before I
finished the H. Heh.
[ZIPPER___CLOSING]
[SIRENS]
-No.
No.
Shawn.
-Please, miss.
Lie down.
-Shawn.
No.
Shawn, Shawn, Shawn.
-We're losing her.
We're losing her!
[BEEP]
[ALARM BUZZING]
-School.
Ahh.
Fuck.
[KIDS TALKING]
-Hey, check it out.
-Fresh meat.
-I hate football.
-Shut up.
-Screw her.
[BELL RINGING]
-Mr. Perrywine?
-Yes.
-Um, I'm Melanie Wood.
The office told me
to report to you.
-Well, yes.
Melanie.
Been expecting you.
Please, have a seat.
-Haven't been here five
minutes, and they already
have me on the couch.
-(LAUGHING) It's not like that.
-Who's your friend?
-My CPR dummy.
I teach first response.
-Jack of all trades.
Your family looks
nice, Mr. Perrywine.
-Call me Doug.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I love my kids.
-And your wife?
-Well, before we
get into me, uh, I
want you to know that
your parents filled me
in on everything that happened.
The loss of a close
friend is really tough.
Melanie, it's OK.
I'm not here to judge or preach.
I mean, we do have a
zero-tolerance policy
on substance use.
But I know that's not
going to be a problem.
This may be a little
ambitious, but I
think we could be friends.
-That's exactly what
my last counselor said.
-And?
-He tried to fuck me, so
I kicked him in the balls.
-Yeah.
Your mother told me about your
penchant for telling lies.
-Well, you just know
everything, don't you?
-No.
But I do know one thing.
If you trust me, I'll
never betray you.
It's the least I can do.
[SIGHS]
-My wife and I
have been separated
since the day I found her
in bed with the neighbor.
-Doug, that's a little
more than I needed to know.
-Sorry.
I just want you to trust me.
-Sure.
-Dig it.
So what's your first class?
-English Lit.
-Hmm.
Great.
I'll walk you there.
-It's really not necessary.
-Oh, I know.
It's my first class, too.
-Oh.
-All right, scholars.
We have a new inmate today.
Everyone please welcome
Ms. Melanie Wood.
Melanie, would you
like to tell us
a little something
about yourself?
-Well, my name is Melanie Wood.
You probably already
know my sister, Crystal.
-Hottie.
[LAUGHING]
-That's enough, Mitch.
Melanie, please.
Continue.
-I am, well, starting
school here late
because my dad's work relocated.
And he wanted to take
me to the Himalayas
to hike in the mountains.
We had an amazing time, and I
would recommend it to anyone.
-Rehab.
[LAUGHING]
-Get out of my classroom.
-What?
-I'm serious.
Now.
-(WHISPERING) You're mine.
-Anyone else?
All right then.
What I'd like to
discuss today is
the relationship
between the children
and their caregiver in
"The Turn of the Screw."
So, please, everybody,
take out your books.
Turn to page 53.
-[INAUDIBLE]
-Woo!
-Fuck!
-Hi.
We all wanted you to know that
we're keeping an eye on you.
After last night you're
all Mitch talks about.
So you've been warned, freak.
Come on.
-Tough first day?
-It's amazing.
New town, same bitches.
[LAUGHS]
-When are we
getting out of here?
-I'm gonna hang for a bit.
But why don't you take
my car if you want?
My keys are in my locker.
-OK.
-All right.
I'll see you later.
-I can't believe I'm doing this.
[GASP]
-Oh my god.
Hi.
Can I help you?
Um, are you lost?
No?
Um, do you need a ride home?
Here, you can get in back.
Wow.
You're quick.
OK.
So which way do I go?
All right.
You got it.
I've seen you playing
around here before.
So what's your name?
Julie?
That's a pretty name.
I'm Melanie.
You don't talk
much, do you, Julie?
Is that where you live?
Are you OK?
God, you're really shivering.
Here.
Put on my jacket.
Here you go.
Are your parents home?
Well, do you want
me to wait with you?
Hey, Julie.
Julie, where you going?
Julie?
[CROSSING BELL]
-Mind if I join you?
-I'm kind of having
some alone time.
-What is it?
Like a moment of
silence or something?
-More like an hour.
-Fuck.
Who died?
-You know, you don't have
to feel sorry for me.
-I don't know what
you're talking about.
-Oh, you don't, do you?
-I know why you have
this aura about you.
-Really?
You don't strike me as
the aura-reading type.
-Crystal told you that
she told me, didn't she?
-Can you say that
three times fast?
Yes.
I know that you know.
-About your boyfriend,
about what happened?
-See.
This is why I need alone time.
How many people have you told?
-I just want to let you know
that you're not the only one.
-What do you mean?
-I lost my older brother
a little over a year ago.
They found him in his dorm room.
He OD'd.
-I'm sorry.
That's terrible.
-That's just between you and me.
-You haven't told anybody?
-I told you.
-Hey, Penn.
Thanks.
-Any time.
-Hello?
So much for hidden treasure.
Andrew Pearl must vacate?
[TAP]
-Hello?
Mr. Keeler?
Julie?
Do I know you?
[SCREAMS]
-God.
That's not funny, asshole.
-You know, I thought I
saw you slip in here.
What's this?
-Give it back.
[TAUNTING LAUGH]
-What would you do for it?
-Give it back.
-Get it.
-What would you do for it?
-I am not in the
mood for your games.
Could you please give it back?
-Come and get it.
-That's bullshit.
-Hey.
Hey.
Come here.
-No, Mitch.
-Come here.
-Stop it.
-Come on.
I want to talk to you.
-Mitch, let me go!
-I want to show you something.
Come here.
-Let go of me, Mitch!
-Shh.
Stop it!
-Let go of me!
-Shh.
-Mitch, stop it!
Stop it!
Someone help me!
Help me!
Get off of me!
Stop!
-Shh.
-Stop it!
-Ow, fuck!
-Hey!
-Shh.
Shh.
What the fuck you
looking at, huh?
-God.
-Fuck!
I gotta go back to
the same old pussy.
-Glad I could help.
-Fuck off.
-Hey, save some for me.
What?
Hey, I got an idea.
[ZIPPER OPENS]
-Smoke that.
What the fuck is this?
-That's, um, something
that didn't pan out.
Back to work.
Who the fuck is that?
-Huh?
-Keeler.
-What?
-That motherfucking bum.
[GASP]
-I'm gonna kick his ass.
Come on, bitch.
-MITCH(OFFSCREEN): Woo!
Come on, motherfucker!
Come on!
-Mitch?
Mitch!
[THUMP]
[GASPS]
Mitch!
[THUMPING]
[SCREAMING]
-No!
-FEMALE SPEAKER(OFFSCREEN):
All right.
Hands up.
All the way up.
-There is no way I
can climb this rope.
-Oh, don't worry about it.
We used to do this stuff
all the time in rehab.
-Have you seen my tan
jacket, by the way?
I thought it was in my car.
-Oh, I lent it to a little girl.
Don't worry about it.
I'll get it back.
Watch and learn.
See, the trick is everyone
says it's in the arms.
But it's all in the legs.
-Whatever you say.
[GRUNTING]
-Mel, you're doing great.
[GASPS]
[SCREAM]
FEMALE SPEAKER(OFFSCREEN):
Oh my god.
Give her some room.
-Mel, are you OK?
FEMALE SPEAKER(OFFSCREEN):
Back up.
Don't move her.
-Melanie, can you hear me?
Somebody go get a nurse.
-FEMALE SPEAKER(OFFSCREEN):
Don't touch her.
OK.
Melanie, are you with me?
Melanie, are you OK?
DOUG(OFFSCREEN):Took
quite a fall.
-Doug, can I tell you something?
-Yeah.
What's up?
-I, um-- I didn't just fall.
There was something written
on the ceiling in blood.
-What was it?
-Andrew Pearl.
-Melanie, you took a bad fall.
Something like that
can cause your brain--
-No, Doug.
Listen.
Have you ever been down
to the train tracks?
-I've driven by them
a million times.
-Have you ever, you know,
put your car in neutral and--
-No.
I haven't.
But I know that spot
has become popular
with teenagers
and ghost seekers.
-It works.
I've done it.
My sister's car was pushed
across the tracks by something.
The children.
Or maybe it was the
ghost of Andrew Pearl.
-Well, I see you've
been brought up
to speed on our local folklore.
-I know how this sounds.
-Melanie, listen to me.
It's sad that the
Pearl's tragedy
has become gossip and rumor.
If you have any respect
for the dead, please,
don't help spread
this nonsense around.
-But my car moved by
itself across the tracks.
-A terrible accident
happened many years ago,
and I think this town
needs to move on.
Heck, I'd even vote
to change the street
names if it would
help us forget.
-Wait.
Street names?
-Every child that
died in that accident
had a street named
after him or her.
Once the new turnpike
comes in, the entire tracks
and that story will be
a thing of the past.
They will finally rip those
godforsaken tracks up for good.
-My dad said the
track was supposed
to be torn up in the '50s.
Something made it postpone.
I was down at the depot.
I got some old
permits and papers.
-Melanie, stay away from there.
OK?
It's dangerous.
To be continued?
-Sure.
But remember, trust.
-OK.
Come on in.
-Hi, Mr. Perrywine.
I'm going to drive her
over to the doctor's now.
-Thanks, Crystal.
See you later, Melanie.
-Yeah.
Right over here.
Pull over.
-Who lives here?
-A little girl I
lent your jacket to.
Don't you want it back?
-Yes.
-Well, then give me a second.
-All right.
[DOORBELL]
-Can I help you?
-Um, hi.
Um, yeah.
I was looking for
a girl named Julie.
-Julie?
-Yeah.
-I think you have
the wrong house.
-No.
I'm-- that's strange, because I
dropped a little girl off here.
And she accidentally ran
away with my sister's jacket.
Are you sure there are no
Julies around the neighborhood?
-No.
So if you don't mind, I'm going
to get back to my business.
-I'm so sorry for bothering you.
Yes.
Of course.
-How I wish this would all stop.
-Excuse me?
-I had a sister named Julie.
She died many years ago.
If I had a penny
for every teenager
that came to disrespect me
and my family-- aren't there
better things to
do in the world?
-I am so sorry.
I-- I honestly had no idea.
-He put you up to
this, didn't he?
Well, you can tell him
he should be ashamed!
-What happened to my sister?
-Well, I-- I was passing by,
saw the situation, thought
I'd give Crystal the night
off, take you home myself.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
-Oh.
Sorry.
-That's all right.
-Huh.
Oh boy.
-Hop in, cowgirl.
PENN(OFFSCREEN): So what are you
going to do after graduation?
-I haven't a clue.
Probably go up to the mountains,
though, at least for awhile.
You?
-Well, uh, I wanted to
head out West for school.
But what happened to my brother,
my dad was like, no way.
-That sucks.
-Yeah.
He's a little overprotective.
-Ha.
Tell me about it.
Where out West did
you want to go?
-California.
San Diego, actually.
Yeah.
Back in the day, I could
have hopped a train
and been there in no time.
-I'm from California, you know.
-I know.
What?
-Um, can I ask you a question?
-Sure.
-I told you that Mr.
Pearl killed himself.
-Oh, jeez.
Come on.
Is that why you were
at Mary Pearl's house?
-Mary Pearl?
-Yeah.
The conductor's daughter,
that was her house.
-I had no idea.
Well, who told you
about the suicide?
-I-- I-- I guess my
grandfather, but everyone knows.
Can we please talk
about something else?
-In a second.
In a second.
Is your grandfather still alive?
I'd like to talk to him.
-No.
Melanie, he's dead.
All right?
Just like Mr. Pearl, just like
the kids on the school bus,
just like we'll all be someday.
They're all having one hell
of a time at the cemetery--
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
-Shit.
Shit.
I have to go.
-Great.
[SIGHS]
-Thank you.
-Of course.
-I'll see you tomorrow.
-All right.
MRS. WOOD(OFFSCREEN): Melanie,
would mind coming here, please?
-Hello, Melanie.
-Blood on the ceiling, Melanie?
Good god.
-Sorry, Melanie.
But it's best.
I promise.
-No wonder your wife
fucking left you, Doug.
-MRS. WOOD(OFFSCREEN): Melanie!
-I'm so sorry, Mr. Perrywine.
I want to thank you
for stopping by.
-It's no problem.
Um, should I wait for
your husband to get home?
That way we could all sit
down with Melanie together.
-No.
My husband has been
too soft on her.
I'll take care of it from here.
-Of course.
Well, good evening.
[BRANCH SNAPPING]
-I can't believe I'm doing this.
[SIGHS]
-(LAUGHING) This is ridiculous.
[CREAKING]
-Oh shit.
[EXHALES]
-Oh my god.
[KIDS SINGING JOHN JACOB
JINGLEHEIMER SCHMIDT]
[KIDS LAUGHING]
-Melanie.
(VOICE MAIL): Hi.
You've reached
Melanie's cell phone.
I can't get to my phone.
You know what to
do after the beep.
-Melanie, it's Doug.
I know you're pretty
pissed at me right now,
and you have every right to be.
Listen, I'm at the train tracks
and-- and-- and you're right.
My car was pushed
across, and there-- there
are all these tiny
fingerprints everywhere.
I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
I'm going back to my office.
OK?
Call me as soon as you get this.
Bye.
-Melanie, stop that.
-It hurts.
-I hate to be the
one to say it, but I
think that she should
be taken out of school.
-What?
-I'm only going to
ask you this once,
so you'd better be honest.
Are you on drugs again?
-How can you even ask me that?
-Blood on the ceiling?
Falling in gym class?
Ghosts at the train track?
Should I go on?
-She's not on drugs, mother.
-Shut up, Crystal.
-We're just worried
about you, honey.
-I know that you snuck out,
and that won't happen again.
-What are you doing?
You're crazy!
-We have to be sure.
-No!
I'm not on drugs!
OK?
-Leave her alone, mom.
I was with her, and I swear
we didn't touch anything.
-Sit down, young lady!
I will deal with you later.
MELANIE(OFFSCREEN):
Daddy, you're hurting me.
-I'm sorry, hon.
Just hold still.
-(SOBBING) Stop!
[SNIP]
[SOBBING]
-A hair test is the only way to
be sure that you're drug free.
[SOBBING]
-You guys are fucking crazy.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[SCREAMING]
[KIDS SINGING JOHN JACOB
JINGLEHEIMER SCHMIDT]
[SCREAMING]
-She wants attention.
We simply cannot indulge her.
[SCREAMING]
[KNIFE SLICING]
-Melanie!
Melanie!
Open this door.
Melanie, open this door!
[SCREAMING]
-Melanie!
Open this door!
[SCREAM]
-Melanie!
-Oh my god.
[SOBBING]
-What did you do?
Melanie.
Melanie, you're bleeding.
We have to get you
to the hospital.
Who-- who wrote that?
-Julie.
-You're scaring
the shit out of me.
-You're scared?
What about me?
-I have to get this
off before mom sees it.
Oh god.
-Crystal, the ghost
children, they're real.
I can see them.
-What are you talking about?
-Ever since my overdose,
I can see things.
People.
I think this little
girl needs my help.
-Oh my god.
[SOBBING]
[SIGHS]
[CELL_PHONE__VIBRATING]
[SNORTS]
-Yeah.
Right.
[GLASS BREAKING]
-Hello?
Hello?
Bonnie, you cleaning up?
What the--
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
[GASP]
-Shit.
Yeah, Jason.
What is it?
JASON(ON PHONE): Hey, dad.
I was wondering if you could
take me to my soccer practice
tomorrow.
Mom says she can't
take me because she
has to go to that counselor.
-Yeah.
[SCREAMS]
JASON(ON PHONE): Dad.
Dad.
Why are you yelling?
-Ahh!
[GRUNTING]
JASON(ON PHONE): Dad.
Dad.
[SCREAMING]
-No!
No!
Help!
JASON(ON PHONE) Dad?
-Come on.
Where are you hiding?
No Pulitzer for
investigative reporting here.
Julie.
Mary Pearl.
Keeler.
Fuzzy Keeler.
-Scare ya?
-No.
Yes.
-Sorry.
I've been looking
all over for you.
What are you reading?
-Oh.
It's, um-- it's just
for a history report.
-Shit.
We have a history report?
-Yeah.
It's due tomorrow.
[LAUGHS]
-What?
-I was kidding.
-How about we go out tonight?
-Meet me at the tracks at 10:00.
-Uh, sure, if that's
where you want to meet.
MELANIE(OFFSCREEN):
Is this your father?
-Yeah.
There never was a kinder
man than my daddy.
You know what?
Everything he did
was for this town.
You know, he was given
the, uh, key to this city.
I think I've got it
around here somewhere.
I don't know.
I mean, it doesn't really
open no real doors.
-Mary, I do-- I do
want to apologize
for the misunderstanding
we had yesterday.
And I appreciate
you-- you seeing me.
-It's all right.
-Do you have any,
um, pictures of Julie
from when she was young?
-Well, my sister never really
got beyond being a little girl.
I've got a few.
Ah.
-I know it's painful.
I lost someone I
loved very much.
-I'm sorry.
-Anyway.
MARY(OFFSCREEN):
That's me and my daddy.
-I think she's trying
to tell me something
about the accident
or your father.
-Darling, I'm not sure I follow.
-I know this sounds
strange, but I've
seen Julie several times
since I've moved here.
Something is not right.
She's trying to
tell me something.
-Well, that's
enough, sweetheart.
I can't play host to this.
I accepted your apologies.
I invited you into my
house with good intentions,
and now I'm going to
have to ask you to leave.
-This is not a prank.
I swear.
-You know, sometimes I wish
there had been a bus crash.
Show yourself out.
-Mr. Pearl.
Julie.
What are you trying to tell me?
[GASPING]
-Ahh!
Nice job, Mel.
[SCREAMING]
[KIDS SINGING JOHN JACOB
JINGLEHEIMER SCHMIDT]
[SCREAMING]
-Help me!
Help me!
Someone help me!
-There you go.
Miss Wood?
-Yes.
-I'm Sheriff Kowalski.
This is Deputy Reynolds.
You mind coming with
us back to the station
so we can ask you
a few questions?
-About what?
-About the disappearance
of Mitch Keller Berenbaum
and Carolyn Jessup Murphy.
Come with us, please.
This your jacket?
-Why am I here?
-Why do you think
you're here, Melanie?
-I don't know.
Something to do with
Mitch and Carolyn.
-And how did you know that?
-Because you told
me at the cemetery.
-Right.
You know, I remember
when my nephew
helped our baseball
team beat Tom's River.
Advanced to the Little
League World Series.
-Who's your nephew?
-Mitch.
He's a good kid
with a good future.
Only a special kind of girl,
a different kind of girl,
could turn him into
pervert like this.
Girl like you.
-I can't look at this.
This is disgusting.
-We have a couple
of witnesses who
saw you lead him into the
old depot two days ago.
We know you're the
last person to see him.
-I was not.
Mr. Keeler was the
last person to see him.
-Fuzzy Keeler?
[LAUGHS]
-Old Keeler's been here detoxing
on a drunk and disorderly.
Anyone else you want
to try to pin this on?
-Maybe the two of them ran away.
-I know my nephew.
He ain't the kinda kid
who would run away.
You ever give him drugs?
We know you have a past
history of illegal activity.
-Who told you that?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-Ma'am, thank you for coming.
We're just asking your
daughter a few questions.
The information you gave
us on the phone earlier
was very helpful.
-Mom, what did you tell them?
They're accusing me
hurting kids at school.
-Nobody's accusing you
of anything, honey.
We're just trying to get
you the help you need.
-Mind if I have a word
with you two in private?
-Of course not.
-I need a refill.
-Get it yourself.
-(CHUCKLING) I was
planning on it.
Have a seat.
-Sorry.
-Can I get you some?
-No.
Thanks.
MR. KEELER(OFFSCREEN
SINGING): Whenever I go out,
people always shout John
Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt.
Dah dah dah dah dah dah.
John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt.
That's my name, too.
Whenever I go out,
the people always
shout John Jacob
Jingleheimer Schmidt.
Dah dah dah dah dah dah dah.
John Jacob.
-Mr. Keeler.
-Do I know you?
-No.
But I know who you were.
You were the mayor of this town.
[LAUGHS]
-What happened to the kids?
-What kids?
There's kids all over the place.
There's too many goddamn
kids, if you ask me.
-The bus crash.
You were mayor when
the train hit the bus.
-Those kids.
-Why are there no bodies of
the children at the cemetery?
-Who told you that?
-It's true, isn't it?
There are no bodies because
the bus crash never happened.
-Say, didn't I see
you at the depot?
-Mr. Keeler, what really
happened to the kids?
I know you're hiding something.
Please.
Kids are missing again.
-You see that bag there?
Hand me that bag.
Oh boy.
Boy, I knew this day was coming.
[EXHALES]
-You were right.
There was no bus crash.
The whole thing was a cover-up,
and I was responsible.
I knew that if the truth
came out about the children
disappearing, that whole highway
project would be in jeopardy.
And it was.
It never got made.
Everything went sour.
Mr. Pearl got his wish.
When the town council
voted to destroy the depot,
something snapped
in Pearl's head.
And the children went
missing, and every finger
pointed to him.
-Did you do anything
to stop him?
-The police had no evidence.
We had no proof.
His little daughter,
Julie, went missing.
So we took matters
into our own hands.
-Did you kill him?
-It was an accident.
We just tried to lean on
him a little bit, tried
to get him to tell us
where the kids were.
But he never talked.
He died.
-And that's why the parents
allowed the cover-up.
-Yeah.
-Were the children ever found?
-No.
-Mr. Keeler, what
happened to the bodies?
-I wish I knew.
[KIDS SINGING JOHN JACOB
JINGLEHEIMER SCHMIDT]
-Julie?
Are you in here?
-What a fucking day
I've been having.
We have to go.
Something happened.
I think Crystal's in trouble.
-Don't use your sister as an
excuse for your own problems.
-She's right, Mel.
Just tell the police the truth.
-Shit.
-Keeler just told me the
bus wreck was bullshit.
Andrew Pearl killed
those children,
and I think it's
happening again.
And if you don't
believe me, ask Keeler.
-Chief, they just found
Doug Perrywine in a dumpster
behind the school.
He's dead.
[GASP]
-Melanie!
-Find out what Keeler told her.
-Keeler!
What the hell did
you say to that girl?
Oh my god.
[SCREAMING]
-Oh no.
Oh god.
Crystal!
Crys--
-You are going to your room
for the rest of your life!
-Mom, please stop!
Mom, look!
Look!
It's on the photo.
I am not crazy.
It's right there.
-Where did you get this phone?
-Mom, it's the hard copy!
No!
-I'm sick of your shit!
-(SOBBING) No.
Fuck.
Come on, Julie.
Where are you?
Please, where are you?
Please.
[WHISPERING]
[KIDS SINGING JOHN JACOB
JINGLEHEIMER SCHMIDT]
[CROSSING BELL]
[KIDS SINGING]
-Shh.
Shh.
I think there's a train.
Just sit tight.
I'll be right back.
[CROSSING BELL]
[GASP]
[CHOKING]
-Daddy?
-Shh.
[SCREAMING]
[TRAIN HORN]
[DOOR CREAKING]
-Mel?
-Crystal?
Crystal.
[GASPING]
-Crystal, I'm here.
It's OK.
It's all right.
We're gonna get you out of here.
Oh god.
It's gonna be OK.
Yes.
It's gonna be just fine.
Here you go.
Come on.
This way.
Here you go.
Crystal?
-No.
Crystal, who did this to you?
[SCREAMING]
-It's OK.
It's all right.
[SOBBING]
-OK.
Here.
[SOBBING]
-Get in.
Get in.
OK.
OK now.
Um, all right.
Let me just get these
stitches out of you.
It's OK.
Hold still.
[SOBBING]
-Shh.
Shh.
Just one more.
[SOBBING]
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Shh.
Crystal, I think he's coming.
[SCREAM]
-Jesus Christ.
[CRYING]
-Oh fuck.
Fuck!
Crystal, you have to be quiet.
[CRYING]
-Shh.
Shh.
-Oh my god!
-Crystal, be quiet.
[SCREAMING]
-Melanie?
-Penn?
Penn, help us.
-Come here.
Can you walk?
-Uh-huh.
Crystal, where is she?
-I don't know.
I didn't-- I didn't see her.
-You have to find them.
He's been trying to kill us.
-Who?
Who did this?
[SNAP]
-No!
No.
[GASP]
-No!
No.
No!
Mary.
-You will never
take our station.
This is my daddy's station.
-Mary, why are you doing this?
Why?
-You will pay for trying to take
my home, for taking my father,
for taking his life.
-It was an accident.
-Liar!
Liar!
I was there!
I saw it!
[SMACK]
-They killed him,
but we made damn sure
that they did not
build that highway.
They won't build
it now, because I
am gonna shut you up just
like I shut up my sister.
-Remember, you have
to pinch the skin
before you put the needle in.
Now go ahead and give it a try.
-Daddy says you don't
know how to be quiet.
So now you have to be punished.
[MUFFLED SCREAMS]
-You sick bitch!
She was your sister!
-She would never just
keep her mouth shut.
Nobody will destroy our home.
Not them and not you.
-Ahh!
[SCREAMING]
-You're a murderer!
-Crystal?
Crystal!
-I'm down here.
-Crystal, are you OK?
-No.
-OK.
I'm on my way down right now.
-Hurry.
-OK.
OK.
All right.
We're almost home.
Keys.
I think I left
them in the jacket.
[SCREAMING]
-I'll teach you just
what my daddy taught me!
[SCREAMING]
[CROSSING BELL]
[TRAIN HORN]
-We're all gonna die together!
[SCREAMING]
-Ahh!
[TRAIN HORN]
-Let me go!
Let me go!
[TRAIN HORN]
-Let me go!
[SCREAM]
-Oh my god.
[SCREAMING]
-Crystal, it's OK.
[CRYING]
-It's OK.
-It's all over.
It's OK.
[SIRENS]
-You ladies OK?
Tell me what happened.
-I swear it's totally true.
-What happened to
Melanie and her sister?
-I don't know.
They say that they left
town with their parents.
Melanie's mother went
insane or something,
and they had to
put her in a home.
-Shit.
-I know.
And you know what else?
They say that those
ghost children
are still out there
on the tracks.
-I don't know if
this is a good idea.
-Just don't piss your pants.
OK.
Here we go.
-Oh my god.
We're actually moving.
[GIGGLE]
-Oh my god.
That was so freaky.
-That was so cool.
-Well--
[SCREAMING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]