AND WHAT A DAY FOR THE 3RD
GAME OF THE WORLD SERIES.
CLEAR SKIES, MID 70'S,
58,000 EXPECTED
AT THE STADIUM.
SO TELL YOUR BOSS
TO LET YOU GET OFF EARLY.
TELL HIM I SAID SO.
NAN CALLAHAN,
K.J.M.C. F.M., 102.6.
SPEAKING OF TRAFFIC,
THAT BAY BRIDGE CONGESTION
HAS CLEARED UP.
SO WE'RE GOING OVER
TO OAKLAND TO CHECK OUT
A FENDER-BENDER
ON INTERSTATE 880.
HOLD ON!
HE HAS THE BALL!
CATHY, SPEED IT UP.
DADDY SAYS I CAN GO
TO THE TOP TODAY.
PASTOR, IT'S SO DANGEROUS
UP THERE WITH THE WIND.
WHY DON'T YOU WAIT UNTIL
THE BUILDING'S FINISHED.
PETRA,
IT'S ONLY CONCRETE.
HE'LL HAVE
A HARD HAT ON.
COME ON.
IT'LL ONLY BE
A COUPLE OF MINUTES
ON THE WAY TO THE DENTIST.
MAMA, I'M BIG.
OK.
JULIO, DON'T GO
NEAR THE EDGE, OK?
STAY 10 FEET BACK.
PRINCESS!
LOOK AT YOU!
YOU'RE THE PRETTIEST.
THANK YOU,
DADDY.
WHAT TIME IS
CATHY'S APPOINTMENT?
3:30.
YOU GUYS COME STRAIGHT
HOME FROM SCHOOL.
OK.
I GOT TO GO.
THEY'RE GONNA PAINT
THAT CONCRETE PURPLE
IF I'M NOT WATCHING.
PASTOR, NO!
THOSE ARE FOR CATHY
FOR SCHOOL.
I'LL MAKE YOU SOME MORE
FOR THE GAME.
BYE, KIDS.
HI, PETRA.
HELLO, DONNA.
PASTOR.
YES, PETRA?
NO, NO,
THIS IS SERIOUS.
I MEAN,
IT'S NO BIG DEAL,
BUT I GOT
A SATURDAY JOB.
NOT CLEANING HOUSES?
IT'S JUST ONE HOUSE.
AND IT'S
A VERY SMALL HOUSE.
IT ONLY TAKES
4 HOURS.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO THAT.
I MAKE ENOUGH MONEY.
I KNOW.
BUT YOU SAID YOURSELF
WE COULD USE SOME SAVINGS.
NO, DON'T SAY
ANYTHING.
JUST PROMISE ME YOU'LL
BE THERE FOR THE KIDS,
OK?
WE'LL BE THERE AT 3:30, OK?
THAT EARLIER ACCIDENT
HAS NOW BEEN CLEARED.
MINOR DAMAGE,
NO INJURIES REPORTED
AND TRAFFIC IS ONCE AGAIN
FLOWING FAIRLY EASILY
THROUGH THIS SECTION.
THERE ARE THE USUAL
DELAYS, HOWEVER,
GETTING ONTO
THE BAY BRIDGE.
RIGHT NOW WE'RE GOING TO HEAD
OVER DOWNTOWN OAKLAND,
AND WE'LL CHECK BACK
WITH YOU SHORTLY.
IN THE MEANTIME, RELAX AND
ENJOY THE MORNING COMMUTE
WITH K.J.M.C. F.M., 102.6.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE
A CONTAMINATED VEHICLE.
SMELLS LIKE BENZENE
TO ME.
TELL THAT FOOL
OF A DRIVER
HE ISN'T BUDGING
TILL WE AIR OUT
THAT BENZENE BUILDUP.
AND CALL SECURITY
AND HAVE THEM OPEN THIS UP.
NO, TO HELL WITH IT.
I'LL DO IT MYSELF.
BUCK, THAT
COULD BLOW YOU
TO KINGDOM COME.
MARK.
WHY AREN'T YOU
IN SCHOOL?
WELL, I'M NOT EVEN GOING
TO SAY HELLO
IF YOU'RE SKIPPING.
DAD, WAIT A SEC.
NAM ET IPSA SCIENTIA
POTESTAS EST.
YEAH, I KNOW.
"KNOWLEDGE IS POWER."
LOOK, DAD, I CAME DOWN HERE
BECAUSE I NEED YOUR HELP.
I WANT YOU TO GET ME INTO
THE LONGSHOREMEN.
HOLD UP.
YOU'RE GETTING EDUCATED
SO THAT YOU WON'T HAVE TO
DO THIS KIND OF WORK.
LOOK, WHAT DO YOU GOT?
2 DEGREES?
YOU'RE STILL WORKING DOWN
ON THE DOCKS.
THIS HAPPENS TO BE
THE ONLY PLACE I CAN MAKE
ENOUGH MONEY
TO KEEP
5 PEOPLE AFLOAT.
SO WHY DENY YOUR SON
ALL THAT MONEY-MAKING
POTENTIAL?
COME ON. WHAT KIND OF LIFE
IS THIS? LIVING IN A JUNK VAN
AND COMMUTING HOME
ON WEEKENDS?
I'M GONNA BE SMARTER
THAN THAT.
I'M NOT GONNA PARK
MY FAMILY 6 HOURS AWAY
IN THE BOONDOCKS.
BESIDES, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH WANTING TO BE
LIKE YOUR OLD MAN?
SO HOW COME YOU NEED
MONEY ALL OF A SUDDEN?
DAD, I'M ENGAGED.
OH, MARK...
JUST WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE HER.
SHE'S GORGEOUS
AND REAL SWEET.
I'LL FINISH SCHOOL
AND I'LL GRADUATE,
I PROMISE.
GOING TO HELP ME?
I'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
THINK FAST, ALL RIGHT?
HEY, IF YOU'VE BEEN
WALKING IN BENZENE,
I'M TAKING
MY OLD BOOTS BACK.
HEY, IF YOU'D
STUDIED CHEMISTRY,
YOU'D KNOW THAT
BENZENE EVAPORATES.
YOLANDA,
YOU ARE NOT DRESSED YET?
IT'S ALMOST 3:00.
COME ON. LOOK ALIVE.
QUIT WORRYING.
I'M OK.
POR FAVOR, GET YOUR PURSE.
YOU'LL BE BETTER
IF YOU COME WITH ME.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
A BLAST.
A BLAST?
YES.
FIRST WE'RE GOING TO
PASTOR'S CONSTRUCTION SITE
AND THEN WE'RE GOING
TO THE DENTIST.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
THE TICKETS ARE FREE.
JULIO, STOP!
JULIO! CATHY!
JUAN'S BEEN GONE
3 MONTHS.
YOU HAVE TO
GET OUT OF THE HOUSE.
YOU'VE GOT
3 MINUTES.
WE'LL WAIT FOR YOU
IN THE CAR.
HELLO?
HI, DESIREE.
I JUST WANTED
TO SAY HELLO.
OH, DADDY.
GOOD.
MY FRIENDS ARE GOING
CAMPING ON SATURDAY.
I TOLD THEM
YOU'RE AN EXPERT AT IT.
SO WILL YOU TAKE US?
YOUR MOTHER DIDN'T TELL YOU
I'M NOT COMING HOME
NEXT WEEKEND?
YOU ALWAYS COME.
WELL, MOM WANTED
SOME TIME ALONE.
SHE SAID SHE NEEDED
TIME TO THINK.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
SHE'S ALWAYS--
NOW, HONEY,
DON'T CRITICIZE HER.
SHE'S GOT TO DO WHAT
SHE'S GOT TO DO,
JUST LIKE ALL OF US.
WHY DID YOU LET HER
THROW YOU OUT
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
TELL YOU WHAT
I'M GONNA DO.
I'LL WRITE YOU A
LONG LETTER TONIGHT,
TRY AND MAKE SOME SENSE
OUT OF THIS CRAZY
SITUATION FOR YOU.
I LOVE YOU, DADDY.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
IT'S WHAT
KEEPS ME GOIN'.
GIVE MY LOVE TO JEFF.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, DES?
DAD'S NOT COMING
HOME NEXT WEEKEND.
GOOD. WE'LL GET
GRILLED ON HISTORY.
YOU'RE SO STUPID!
DES.
DESIREE.
CAN'T YOU
TAKE A JOKE?
DAD'S COOL, OK?
SLOW DOWN! YOU GOT
WORLD SERIES FEVER?
PASTOR.
LOOK WHAT I FOUND.
HEY!
LISTEN, PETRA SAYS
TO TELL YOU TO MAKE IT QUICK
OR SHE'LL BE LATE,
AND DON'T FORGET
10 FEET.
DADDY MADE THIS
WHOLE BUILDING,
UNCLE TONY.
ONLY THE CEMENT PARTS,
AND I NEEDED A LOT OF HELP.
DON'T LISTEN TO HIM.
HE'S THE BRAINS
BEHIND THE OPERATION.
IF YOUR BOSS HASN'T
LET YOU OFF EARLY,
IT'S TIME TO GIVE HIM
SOME SERIOUS GRIEF.
RIGHT NOW
WE ARE JUST OVER...
YOU RIG THAT?
FINISH THAT SECTION
AND YOU CAN ALL TAKE OFF.
JULIO AND I WILL TOP OFF
THE BUILDING BY OURSELVES.
HERE YOU GO, CHICO!
THANKS, UNCLE TONY.
THAT EARLIER SIG ALERT
HAS NOW BEEN CANCELLED.
I CAN REPORT THAT THE TRAFFIC
ON THE BAY BRIDGE
IS SURPRISINGLY LIGHT FOR
A WORLD SERIES RUSH HOUR.
I GUESS ALL YOU FANS
ARE ALREADY AT
CANDLESTICK PARK, HUH?
FOR THOSE OF YOU
JUST LEAVING WORK,
PLEASE REMEMBER
TO KEEP IT COOL, OK?
SO ALL OF US BASEBALL FANS
CAN GET TO THE GAME SAFELY.
I THOUGHT I WAS DOING
THE RIGHT THING,
MOVING THE FAMILY
OUT OF THIS CRIME-INFESTED
CITY TO THE COUNTRY.
LAURIE KEPT WANTING
TO HAVE MORE SPACE,
SO I GAVE HER MORE SPACE.
NOW SHE WANTS MORE SPACE.
IF YOU DON'T GIVE IT TO HER,
SHE'LL JUST TAKE IT.
SHE ALREADY HAS.
WE'RE LEGALLY SEPARATED.
WELL, LOOK, LIKE THEY SAY,
IT ISN'T OVER TILL IT'S OVER.
COME WATCH THE GAME.
WE'LL THROW SOME
BEER AND LASAGNA
AT THAT MOOD OF YOURS.
OH. THANKS, ANYWAY,
BUT I HAVE TO GO
TO THE LIBRARY.
I'VE GOT
A VERY IMPORTANT
LETTER TO WRITE.
NO-FATHER GREG.
SAY HELLO, DAD.
THE ONLY TIME YOU SAY HELLO
IS WHEN YOU WANT SOMETHING.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
NOT TO FIGHT.
JUST...
LOOK, I KNOW
YOU DON'T BELIEVE
I'M GOING
TO PAY YOU BACK.
WHY WOULD I BELIEVE YOU
THIS TIME?
LOOK, IT'S JUST
FOR A WEEK OR SO.
JUST TIDE ME OVER
TILL I GET A NEW JOB.
WILL 100 BUCKS
KILL YOU?
GREG,
THE WELL IS DRY.
50?
50 BUCKS.
MAMA, WHEN'S
MY TURN?
AN HOUR AGO.
EXCUSE ME, COULD I CALL
MY HUSBAND, PLEASE?
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
I'M HAVING A BLAST.
HELLO? HELLO?
THEY'RE CALLING THIS
BAY'S BALL HERE.
YOU'RE GOING TO
KILL THEM, CANSECO.
GAME 3 OF
THE 1989 WORLD SERIES.
BASEBALL HASN'T BEEN
A SUBWAY SERIES
SINCE THE NEW YORK YANKEES
PLAYED THE BROOKLYN
DODGERS IN 1956.
WELL, THE GIANTS ARE DOWN
TWO GAMES TO NONE.
YOU'RE GONNA
KILL 'EM, CANSECO.
I'LL EVEN DRIVE YOU BACK
AFTER THE GAME.
THIS FIRST.
THE AMERICAN LEAGUE
CHAMPION OAKLAND ATHLETICS'
LEAD-OFF BATTER
IS NUMBER 24,
LEFT FIELDER
RICKEY HENDERSON.
I'M GONNA MISS
THE OPENING PITCH.
WE'LL BE HOME SOON.
NUMBER ONE!
HOLD ON!
THIS IS DEFINITELY
AN EARTHQUAKE.
WE'RE DEFINITELY
IN THE MIDST OF...
THERE'S PANIC IN THE STADIUM.
IT'S OK.
GET OUT OF HERE!
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
OUTSIDE! COME ON,
COME ON, GUYS!
CALVIN, GET THE GUYS OVER
TO THE LUMBER YARD.
BRING BACK FORK LIFTS,
LADDERS, WHATEVER
GETS US UP THERE.
FRANK, IT'S LIKE 40 FEET.
WE GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
IT'S IN OUR LAP!
FRANK!
LET'S GET GOING, GUYS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
QUICK, QUICK,
GET THE LADDER.
FRANK, YOU HAVE
A WIFE AND BABY!
CALL HER AND TELL HER
I'M OK!
FRANK, DON'T BE
A DAMN FOOL!
WE'RE GETTING A SIGNAL--
LET'S GO.
SHELLY COULDN'T
MAKE IT ACROSS TOWN.
YOU'RE DOING
ON-CAMERA.
I'M RADIO!
YOU'RE NOT
FINISHED YET.
TIME TO SHOW
YOUR PRETTY FACE,
NANAHAN.
NAN CALLAHAN!
I HATE WHEN YOU
CALL ME NANAHAN.
THERE'S A GREAT DEAL
OF CONFUSION HERE
WITH SOME DAMAGE
TO THE STATION. TO REPEAT,
A MAJOR EARTHQUAKE STRUCK
THE BAY AREA MINUTES AGO,
LASTING APPROXIMATELY
8 TO 10 SECONDS.
NAN CALLAHAN OF K.J.M.C.
AIRBORNE OVER OAKLAND,
WHERE IT APPEARS
THERE'S BEEN DAMAGE
TO INTERSTATE 880.
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
IS EVERYBODY FINE?
OH, GOOD.
LISTEN, ROSA, DID THAT
SISTER OF YOURS STOP BY?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I'M SURE PETRA'S FINE.
I'LL HAVE HER CALL YOU
WHEN SHE GETS IN.
OK.
THIS IS MAJOR, MAJOR DAMAGE,
JUST AN INCREDIBLE SIGHT.
IT LOOKS AS IF
THE FREEWAY'S UPPER LEVEL JUST
SHOOK LOOSE
AND SLAMMED DOWN
ONTO THE LOWER DECK,
SECTION BY SECTION.
YOLANDA.
THIS IS INTERSTATE 880
IN OAKLAND,
JUST SOUTH OF THE BAY BRIDGE.
THERE ARE UNDOUBTEDLY
PEOPLE HURT
AND POSSIBLY DEAD
DOWN THERE.
HEY! HEY, OVER HERE!
I CAN'T GET DOWN!
HANG ON!
JUST HANG ON!
IT'LL BE OK!
CALVIN, HURRY UP!
DON'T MOVE, BUDDY!
THAT COPTER'S COMING
TO SAVE YOU!
THERE ARE PEOPLE DOWN HERE.
SOMEBODY HELP ME!
IT'S T.V. NEWS.
YOU CAN SEE THE ENTIRE LENGTH
OF THE DOUBLE-DECK STRUCTURE
APPEARS TO BE LITERALLY
SANDWICHED TOGETHER.
ANYBODY HEAR ME?
IS ANYBODY-- ANYBODY
IN THERE? HUH? ANY...
HELLO?
HELLO.
IS ANYBODY IN THERE?
OH, MY GOD.
HELLO?
HANG ON!
DON'T DO
NOTHING STUPID!
HOLD ON.
I'M LOSING MY GRIP!
MY FINGERS ARE SLIPPING!
HANG ON, MAN.
HELP'S ON THE WAY.
I CAN'T HANG ON.
HELP!
I'M GOING TO FALL!
GOD, I HOPE
NOBODY'S IN THERE!
HELLO? IS ANYBODY IN THERE?
IS ANYBODY--ANYBODY...
ANYBODY?
ANYBODY--ANYBODY
IN THERE? ANY...
ARE YOU THERE?
ARE YOU--ARE YOU THERE?
OH, GOD.
NOW WE'RE OVER SAN FRANCISCO'S
MARINA DISTRICT
WHERE A MASSIVE FIRE
HAS BROKEN OUT.
FLAMES APPEAR TO BE
SHOOTING AT LEAST
200 FEET IN THE AIR,
AND I'M TOLD THE WATER MAINS
DOWN HERE ARE BROKEN.
DID MY SISTER CALL?
NO, ROSA, BUT SHE WILL.
APPARENTLY, OFFICIALS ARE
TRYING TO PUMP SEA WATER
FROM THE BAY UP HERE.
WELL, WE'RE NOT GOING TO
LET IT WORRY US.
NO WAY.
SHE'LL BE HERE
ANY MINUTE.
THESE WERE 3 AND 4 STORY
APARTMENT BUILDINGS.
SHE LEFT THAT
CASSEROLE OUT.
WELL, THEY'RE GOING
TO BE HUNGRY.
LET'S WARM IT UP, OK?
THAT SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
THE QUAKE LITERALLY
SHOOK IT OFF ITS FOUNDATION.
IT SLUMPED RIGHT
INTO THE STREET.
SHE HAD TO COME HOME
ON THE 880.
PASTOR,
I TRIED TO PRAY,
BUT I COULDN'T.
THE WORDS WOULDN'T COME.
I CAN SEE A FEW PEOPLE
ACTUALLY CLIMBING BACK
INTO BUILDINGS
NOT ON FIRE,
OBVIOUSLY LOOKING FOR
FRIENDS AND RELATIVES INSIDE.
IT'S STILL VERY DANGEROUS
IN THIS AREA.
HURRY UP.
YEAH.
YOU SEE ANYTHING
UP HERE?
SEE ANYTHING?
SARGE, THE FIRE DEPARTMENT
IS TAKING COMMAND.
NOW, LOOK,
I'M GONNA MOVE A LOT OF
HEAVY EQUIPMENT IN HERE.
MOVE ALL CIVILIANS
WHO ARE NOT DIRECTLY ASSISTING
IN THE RESCUE
AND SECURE
THE PERIMETER NOW.
CHIEF NAVARRO,
DID YOU ORDER THE UNIT
FROM HIGHLAND HOSPITAL?
YOU CAPTAIN SCHAFFER?
I'M DR. SCOTT,
THIS IS DR. GREEN.
YOU NEEDED
A TRIAGE UNIT?
YEAH. I'LL SET
YOU UP OVER THERE.
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF WOUNDED
FROM THE UPPER LEVEL
AS WELL AS FROM THE GROUND.
RON?
JIM.
GOOD TO HAVE YOU.
I GOT TO GET UP THERE
TO BEGIN A PRIMARY SEARCH.
I'M NOT LETTING YOU UP
UNTIL I'VE MET WITH
THE CALTRANS ENGINEERS.
YOU KNOW FULLY WELL
THERE'S GOING TO BE
AFTER-SHOCKS.
YEAH,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THE TREMOR REGISTERED
AT LEAST 7.
YOU THINK ANYBODY'S
COMING OUT OF THERE ALIVE?
ONE WOULD BE A MIRACLE.
HELLO.
ANYBODY?
ANYBODY HERE?
IS ANYBODY HERE?
OH, MY GOD.
HOW YOU DOING,
SWEETHEART?
NOT SO GOOD, HUH?
WELL, YOU'RE GOING
TO BE FINE.
MY NAME'S FRANK,
AND I'M GOING TO GO
AND GET SOME HELP
FOR YOU RIGHT NOW,
SO YOU JUST KEEP THOSE
PRETTY EYES OPEN, OK?
IT'S OK. I'LL BE
RIGHT BACK, HONEY.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OK?
JUST KEEP THEM OPEN.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
THE FREEWAY SECTIONS ARE
NUMBERED IN ASCENDING ORDER.
PAINT THE NUMBERS
ON THE COLUMNS
SO YOU CAN ID THEM MORE EASILY
AS YOU SEARCH FOR SURVIVERS.
IF NOONE'S ALIVE,
GET A DESCRIPTION OF
EACH CAR'S POSITION
RELATIVE TO THE MAP.
GET LICENSE NUMBERS,
LOCATIONS OF BODIES,
IDENTIFIABLE CLOTHING,
ANY DESCRIPTIONS
THAT CAN HELP US.
HEY!
OVER HERE!
QUIET!
EVERYBODY QUIET!
YOU STRANDED?
YEAH.
FOUND A CHILD.
SHE'S STUCK
IN A CAR.
ALIVE?
YEAH.
LOOKS LIKE
HER PARENTS ARE DEAD.
SCHAFFER, BETWEEN 76 AND 77.
GET HIM A PRYING BAR
AND A FIRST AID KIT.
STAND BY FOR
A RESOURCES ORDER.
WE'LL BE RIGHT UP.
HERE, CATCH THIS.
NICE CATCH.
THANK GOD FOR FOOLS.
HEY, SWEETHEART?
FRANK'S BACK.
HEY, IT'S FRANK.
IT'S FRANK, HONEY.
THAT'S A GIRL.
CAN YOU OPEN
YOUR EYES?
COME ON.
COME ON,
OPEN YOUR EYES.
COME ON, HONEY.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S GOOD.
NOW WE'RE JUST GOING
TO SIT HERE AND--AND TALK
UNTIL THE RESCUE TEAM
GETS HERE,
OK?
CAN YOU TELL ME
YOUR NAME?
THAT'S--THAT'S OK.
YOU JUST KEEP BREATHING.
THAT'S IT.
RESCUE GROUP NICOLA
TO CYPRESS COMMAND.
TELL CHIEF NAVARRO
I'M ALMOST CERTAIN
NO ONE'S SURVIVED
AT THIS END.
UPPER LEVEL'S TOTALLY
PANCAKED ON THE LOWER.
I'M TAKING THE SQUAD
UP TOP.
ARE YOU OK?
I WAS LISTENING
TO THIS ON THE RADIO.
...THIS PRECARIOUS STRUCTURE,
IT COULD GO AT ANY TIME.
A POLICE LIEUTENANT
IS TELLING US
CARS ON THE LOWER DECK
APPEAR TO HAVE BEEN
BUMPER-TO-BUMPER.
GUYS.
GUYS, I THINK
YOU COULD USE
A BREAK FROM THIS.
WHAT?
YOU DON'T THINK
MARK'S IN THERE OR DAD?
THEY COULD BE, MOTHER.
THEY'D HAVE CALLED.
TURN IT ON.
I'M SURE THERE ARE A LOT OF
PHONE LINES DOWN.
LET'S NOT MAKE
OURSELVES CRAZY, OK?
THINK. MARK'S CAMPUS
IS NOWHERE NEAR THE 880.
AND I'M SURE
YOUR DAD'S SITTING
ON THAT OLD VAN WRITING.
WHY'D YOU HAVE TO
THROW DADDY OUT?
HE MIGHT BE HERE SAFE.
DESIREE,
YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S OK.
DAD'S NEVER HOME
TUESDAYS ANYWAY.
AND WE BOTH KNOW HE'S
TOO CRANKY TO GO YOUNG.
IT'S A JOKE, DESIREE.
YOU'RE BOTH BEING SILLY.
CAN WE TURN IT ON NOW?
SURE.
...CLIMBING IN BETWEEN
THE SECTIONS SEARCHING
FOR ANYONE
WHO MIGHT BE TRAPPED
IN THERE.
BUT THE POLICE OFFICER
TELLS ME
THERE ARE DEFINITELY--
THAT'S A QUOTE--
DEFINITELY DEAD PEOPLE
IN THE MIDDLE.
OK, CAPTAIN, I'VE SENT
THE GUYS OVER TO 101.
NEW CREW'S GOING TO 100.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO NOW?
TAKE A COUPLE OF GUYS
AND CHECK OUT
THAT UPPER LEVEL.
OK, YOU GOT IT.
HEY, CAN ANYBODY HEAR ME?
IS ANYBODY IN THERE?
IS ANYBODY THERE?
HELP.
BOB. BOB, IF YOU WANT US
TO GET TO THE GROUND,
WE'LL DO IT.
BUT WE'RE GETTING
GREAT STUFF OUT HERE.
YOU GUYS ARE DOING GREAT,
BUT WE HAVE TO CONSOLIDATE
OUR FORCES AND WORK FASTER
IF WE'RE GOING TO
FIND ANY SURVIVORS.
EVERYBODY'S PITCHING IN,
AND THANK GOD
THE CASUALTIES SO FAR
ARE FEW.
BOTH FROM THE FREEWAY
AND SURROUNDING AREAS.
WITH THE BRIDGE DOWN,
WE'RE NOT GOING TO GET
ANY HELP FROM ACROSS THE BAY,
SO IT'S ALL UP TO US.
SCHAFFER. SCHAFFER!
STOP! THERE'S GAS!
OK, OK.
I'M GONNA TRY
THE CROWBAR.
ALL RIGHT.
HOW MUCH LONGER?
YOU GETTING CLOSE?
COME ON,
COME ON.
OK. WE'RE GOING IN.
WE'RE IN!
OK, OK. WE'LL HAVE HER
OUT IN NO TIME.
UH, ANYTHING I CAN DO?
SCRAM.
YOU'RE A GUTSY GUY,
BUT YOU'RE IN THE WAY HERE.
GOT TO GO NOW,
HONEY.
YOU'RE DOING
JUST GREAT.
THAT'S A GIRL.
WE'LL BE WAITING
FOR YOU DOWNSTAIRS.
IT'S OK. WE'LL TAKE OVER
FROM HERE.
WAIT. THERE'S
ANOTHER KID IN HERE.
IT'S A BOY.
HE'S ALIVE.
JIM?
I'M NEEDED
AT THE 880 COLLAPSE.
THEY TOLD ME THE CHIEF
OF SURGERY--
KEVIN SCOTT
ASKED FOR ME.
A CHILD IS PINNED
BETWEEN LAYERS.
YOU'RE NOT GOD,
YOU KNOW.
I LIVE WITH YOU.
I'M THE ONE WHO
KNOWS THAT FOR SURE.
I'M MORTAL AS HELL.
I GOTTA GO.
THIS IS DON DELGADO,
K.N.K.I. E.
AT THE 14TH STREET EXIT
OF INTERSTATE 880,
WHERE A RESCUE WORKER
IS DESCENDING
FROM THE CRUSHED
LOWER LEVEL OF THE FREEWAY.
WE'VE JUST RECEIVED WORD
FROM GROUND WORKERS
THAT AT LEAST ONE CHILD
HAS BEEN DISCOVERED ALIVE,
THOUGH APPARENTLY,
BOTH PARENTS ARE DEAD.
THE CHILD IS SAID TO BE
A GIRL OF ASIAN DESCENT.
ONCE AGAIN,
A CHILD FOUND ALIVE IN 880.
EVERYONE, STAY BACK.
PLEASE, LET'S KEEP
THIS AREA CLEAR.
SORRY, MA'AM, WE HAVE
NO INFORMATION
AT THIS TIME.
THIS THE RIGHT
PLACE?
TWO KIDS TRAPPED
IN A CAR?
YEAH, ONE OF THEM
IS ABOUT TO COME DOWN.
I WAS JUST UP THERE
WITH THEM.
WHAT'S IT LIKE?
THE MOTHER'S DEAD
AND THE DRIVER'S CRUSHED
BEYOND RECOGNITION.
I WORKED WITH DR. SCOTT
ON THE RUNWAY CRASH.
HE'S, UH-- IF ANYONE CAN
HELP THEM, IT'S HIM.
DR. BETZ.
JIM MENDONSA.
I CAN SEND YOU UP
AS SOON AS THE GIRL
COMES DOWN.
NO, NO, IT'S OK.
I NEED THE EXERCISE.
OK.
TELL 'EM FRANK SAID
TO HANG IN THERE.
LET ME KNOW
WHEN HE'S UP TOP.
OK. GOOD.
ALL RIGHT,
TAKE IT EASY. EASY.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE WANT TO BE REAL CAREFUL.
ALL RIGHT,
HERE SHE COMES.
KEEP IT STEADY.
ALL RIGHT,
WE GOT HER.
GOT HER.
WE'LL TAKE IT
FROM HERE. THAT'S OK.
JIM. THANK GOD.
MAMA!
I THINK WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TO AMPUTATE
HIS RIGHT LEG.
MUST BE 100 TONS
PUSHING DOWN,
JAMMING
THE WOMAN'S BODY
ON TOP OF HIS LEG.
WHAT ABOUT THE LEFT?
YOU DECIDE.
3 OF THE
CONCRETE CAPLETS
STUCK UNDER
THE DRIVER'S SEAT.
WE'RE TRYING
TO JACK IT UP.
DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
I'LL HAVE
THAT OXYGEN NOW.
THE SEDATIVE SHOULD
CALM HIM DOWN.
MAMA! MAMA!
MAMA.
...SAYING THAT 53 ARE DEAD,
400 ARE INJURED...
DES, I'M GONNA HAVE TO
TURN IT OFF
IF YOU'RE GOING TO
GET THIS UPSET.
DON DELGADO
IS AT THE SITE.
DON, WHAT CAN YOU SEE?
HELLO.
CHICAGO?
WHAT IS IT, DES?
DADDY'S INSULIN IS
PROBABLY IN THE VAN.
EVEN IF
THEY FIND HIM--
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU
SO MUCH.
YOUR BROTHER
COULDN'T GET THROUGH
TO US,
SO HE CALLED A FRIEND
IN CHICAGO TO LET US
KNOW THAT HE'S OK.
MARK OR GREG?
MARK.
GREG'S STILL IN NEVADA
AS FAR AS I KNOW.
LET'S HOPE
HE STAYS THERE.
JEFF.
HE JUST
CAUSES TROUBLE
WHEN HE'S HOME.
HE'S STILL YOUR BROTHER.
THE FIRE IS STILL
RAGING OUT OF CONTROL.
THAT'S A BUILDING
THAT THE FIRE FIGHTERS
HAVE ESTIMATED...
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
ALL RIGHT.
TAKE IT EASY.
YOU WANT TO BE
REAL CAREFUL.
HERE'S WHAT WE DO
WHEN WE GET DOWN.
YOU PASS THE CASE,
I'LL TAKE THE I.V.
HERE WE GO.
OK, 1, 2, 3,
UP WE GO.
ALL RIGHT, CAREFUL.
EASY.
HOW IS SHE?
SHE HAD TO BE
INTUBATED,
BUT WE'RE HOPIN'.
WHAT ABOUT THE BOY?
THEY'RE DOING
EVERYTHING THEY CAN.
WE'LL LOOK AFTER HER, PAL.
DON'T WORRY.
LET'S GO.
HOW'S THE GIRL?
IS THE BOY ALIVE?
CAN YOU NAME
ALL THE DOCTORS?
THE YOUNG WOMAN
YOU SAW...
I'M REPORTING
LIVE...
FROM THE MILE AND HALF OF
A CONCRETE TUBE
IS SAID TO BE ALIVE.
EARLIER REPORTS INDICATED
THAT THE GIRL
APPREARED TO BE ASIAN.
ALSO, WORD OF A BOY,
ALSO ASIAN.
LATINO!
I WAS THERE.
AND THEY'RE
BOTH LATINO.
WE HAVE JUST HAD
AN UNCONFIRMED REPORT
FROM AN EYEWITNESS
THAT BOTH CHILDREN
ARE LATINO.
IT DOESN'T MEAN--
I CAN'T STAY.
WE'VE GOT TO HAVE FAITH,
PASTOR. I HAVE FAITH.
OK, YOU STAY
IN CASE THEY CALL.
I'LL CALL YOU FROM...
I'LL CALL YOU FROM EVERYWHERE.
THAT'S WHERE THE YOUNG GIRL
WAS BEING WHEELED FIRST.
WE'LL TRY AND GET A REPORT
FROM THERE SOON.
IT'S TAKING SO LONG
TO EXTRICATE THESE VICTIMS
BECAUSE RESCUERS
HAVE VERY LITTLE ROOM
TO MANEUVER...
MAMA.
I CAN'T GET
THE BOY'S LEG OUT
WITHOUT MOVING THE BODY.
SHAFFER, WHAT'S THE CHANCE
OF MOVING THIS BODY
OUT OF THE WAY?
SNOWBALL IN HELL.
OR WORSE.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT
ABOUT DIVIDING THE BODY?
I'VE TRIED NOT TO.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
EASY WITH IT.
ALL RIGHT.
WHO GETS THIS?
YOU'RE THE CHILD
SPECIALIST.
ALL RIGHT.
TAKE OFF!
GET YOUR TAIL DOWN!
THE WHOLE THING'S
COMING DOWN!
ALL RESCUE WORKERS ARE
TO CLEAR THE AREA NOW!
CLEAR THE AREA!
RESCUE WORKERS
ARE TO CLEAR THE AREA!
CONDITIONS ARE UNSAFE!
PLEASE! CLEAR THE AREA!
WORKERS FROM SECTION 75
TO 102 MUST CLEAR THE AREA!
HELP.
RELAY AND REPEAT:
CLEAR THE AREA!
HELP!
101'S CLEAR.
HOW'S 100?
HELP! DOWN HERE!
100'S CLEAR!
CLEAR THE AREA!
96 CLEAR!
WORKERS WITH 77!
CLEAR THE AREA!
ALL WORKERS,
CLEAR THE AREA.
CONDITIONS ARE UNSAFE.
RELAY AND REPEAT!
63 CLEAR!
64, CLEAR THE AREA.
ALL WORKERS.
PLEASE, LADY,
MOVE OUT OF THE WAY.
HEY, YOU.
WAIT. MY DAUGHTER,
MAYBE SHE WAS UP THERE.
WAS SHE THE LITTLE
GIRL ON T.V.?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M PRETTY BUSY HERE.
WAS THERE A BOY
WITH HER?
I'M SORRY, THERE'S MANY PEOPLE
IN YOUR PREDICAMENT.
TRY THE HOSPITAL.
HER HUSBAND'S UP THERE.
CAN YOU PLEASE TELL US WHERE
WE ARE SUPPOSED TO GO?
HEY, BUDDY, TRY HIGHLAND.
IT'S THE CLOSEST.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE
TO GET HELP,
TO FIND OUT--
WE'RE OUT OF TIME.
THE BOY'S DYING.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
WE'RE OUT OF TIME.
THE BOY'S DIEING.
WE CAN'T LIFT UP.
WE HAVE TO AMPUTATE RIGHT AWAY
IF WE'RE GOING TO SAVE HIM.
MAYBE I CAN MOVE
THE DRIVER'S SEAT
FORWARD.
GIVE ME THE PRY BAR.
I'LL TAKE THIS END.
YOU GO AHEAD.
THIS CAN'T WORK, JIM.
I KNOW.
WE'RE LOSING HIM.
WHAT'S WRONG?
SOMETHING MOVED.
HOLD ON.
COME ON, COME ON.
OK, I CAN MOVE IT.
HIS LEFT LEG'S FREE.
GO!
HEY, LOOK, I'M GOING TO
DISARTICULATE THE JOINT,
SO THERE'S NO BONE TO CUT.
THIS IS NOT EXACTLY
AN IDEAL MEDICAL FACILITY
FOR AN AMPUTATION.
GIVE ME THAT SCALPEL.
COME ON. LET'S GO.
COME ON, COME ON.
COME ON.
HIS PULSE IS DROPPING.
DEAR DESIREE,
I DON'T KNOW
IF THE WORLD HAS ENDED,
IF THERE'S BEEN
A NUCLEAR HOLOCAUST,
IF I'M STUCK
IN A BAD DREAM
WITH ALL MY SENSES
CRUELLY AT WORK,
HEARING SIRENS,
SMELLING SMOKE
AND BURNING RUBBER,
TASTING BLOOD AND SWEAT,
AND FEELING...
FEELING DISSIPATED
PHYSICALLY, MENTALLY.
ALL I REMEMBER, SWEETHEART,
IS I OWE YOU A LETTER.
I WAS GOING TO WRITE TO YOU
IN THE LIBRARY TONIGHT.
WELL, I SEEM
TO HAVE STUMBLED
ON THE LIBRARY IN HELL.
THAT'S A JOKE, ISN'T IT?
I DON'T BELIEVE IN HELL
OR HEAVEN.
THIS LETTER'S ABOUT YOU, DES,
AND HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT YOUR MOTHER AND ME.
I KNOW YOU BLAME HER A LOT,
BUT, YOU KNOW, I CAN BE
A REAL HOTHEAD.
YOU'VE SEEN ME ORDER
YOUR MOTHER AROUND
LIKE A DRILL SERGEANT.
DESIREE, COME AND HAVE
SOMETHING TO EAT.
DINNER'S READY.
I'M NOT HUNGRY.
LISTEN TO ME.
YOUR FATHER IS NOT DEAD.
AND I WANT YOU TO STOP ACTING
LIKE HE IS, ALL RIGHT?
NO, NO.
HE COULDN'T HAVE
GOTTEN HERE THAT QUICKLY.
THANKS A LOT.
OH, DES.
HEY, JEFF,
DID DAD CALL?
NO.
MARK, OH.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
IN TIME FOR DINNER.
SHE THINKS HE'S DEAD.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE EATING
LIKE NORMAL PEOPLE.
ALL RIGHT, DESIREE,
KNOCK IT OFF.
SHE'S BLAMING ME.
WHAT AM I
SUPPOSED TO DO?
TAKE IT EASY, MOM.
STOP TAKING EVERYTHING
SO PERSONALLY.
DESIREE, WHY DON'T YOU JUST
STOP YOUR CHILDISH BEHAVIOR
AND HELP YOUR MOTHER
PUT FOOD ON THE TABLE.
WHY SHOULD I?
BECAUSE I SAID SO.
HEY.
WHO MADE YOU BOSS?
YOU'RE NOT DAD.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M NOT,
BUT I SAW HIM
ON THE DOCKS
THIS MORNING.
THERE WAS THIS CONTAINER
THAT COULD HAVE EXPLODED.
YOU KNOW WHAT
THAT HEROIC NUT DID?
TELL US.
MAYBE I WILL
OVER DINNER.
BUT, DES,
DESPITE MY TEMPER,
AND MY IRON HAND,
YOU'VE GOT TO BELIEVE
MY FAMILY
ALWAYS CAME FIRST,
LAST,
AND ALWAYS.
FIRST...
LAST...
AND ALWAYS.
BULLSHIT, YOU'RE NOT HURT.
PLEASE, GET OUT OF THE WAY
SO WE CAN HELP THOSE
WHO ARE.
MOVE BACK.
LET THIS VEHICLE THROUGH!
STEP ASIDE!
WE DON'T HAVE ANY NAMES YET.
YOU'LL HAVE TO WAIT.
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
THEY DIDN'T KNOW
WHERE MY LITTLE GIRL WAS
AT THE FREEWAY,
THEY SENT ME HERE.
SHE'S 8 YEARS OLD.
I'VE GOT A PICTURE.
TRY CHILDRENS.
IT'S A LOGICAL PLACE.
PLEASE, CLEAR THE DRIVE
SO THE AMBULANCE
CAN LEAVE!
COME ON, COME ON.
LET'S GO.
HEMOSTAT.
OH, I CAN'T...
I CAN'T GET THIS ON
TO KEEP THE MAIN
ARTERY SHUT.
DAMN.
YOU WORKING ONE-HANDED?
AH, I GOT TO.
AS SOON AS YOU'RE FREE,
I'LL CLAMP THE ARTERY.
YOU READY
TO WRAP THE LEG?
YEAH.
WIRE BASKET?
SET. EVERYTHING'S SET.
HOW MUCH LONGER?
HANG ON.
WE'RE HANGIN'.
10 SECONDS.
YOU READY TO LIFT?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT. LET'S GO.
GO. GO.
DOCTOR, HOW'S THE BOY?
CRITICAL.
LOOK. PLEASE,
NO QUESTIONS.
WE DON'T KNOW
THE NEXT OF KIN.
UNDERSTAND.
THE MEDIA IS ALL OVER ME.
WHAT CAN I TELL THEM?
WE'RE GOING
INTO SURGERY.
WE'LL HAVE WORD IN AN HOUR.
GOD BLESS HIM.
HE ALREADY HAS,
BELIEVE ME.
EXCUSE ME, PLEASE.
LET ME THROUGH.
EXCUSE ME.
I'M A DOCTOR.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
YOU WORK FOR DELGADO.
GIVE ME A BREAK, SIR.
HE'S LEANING ON ME
HARD FOR INFORMATION.
HERE'S SOME
HOT INFORMATION.
YOU TRY A STUNT LIKE THIS
AGAIN,
I'LL MAKE
A FORMAL COMPLAINT
TO YOUR NETWORK.
HEY, COME ON NOW.
COME ON.
THAT'S ALL I CAN TELL YOU
FOR THE TIME BEING.
AS WE GET INFORMATION,
WE'LL PASS IT ON TO YOU.
CAN YOU
HELP ME, PLEASE?
CAN--CAN SOMEBODY
HELP ME?
I'M LOOKING FOR 2 KIDS.
ONE IS A GIRL, 8,
AND A BOY, 6.
SIR, SIR.
THEY JUST TOOK
A BOY INSIDE.
WAS HE ALIVE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK SO.
CAN YOU TELL ME
WHAT HE LOOKED LIKE?
OH, MY GOD.
WAIT A SECOND.
STEVE, STEVE,
TAKE THIS MAN INSIDE.
I THINK HE MAY BE
THE FATHER.
CALLAHAN,
WHAT'S THE GUY'S NAME?
UM, I DIDN'T ASK.
YOU WHAT?
YOU HAD TO
BE THERE, OK?
MR. BARUMAN?
MY KIDS?
YOUR DAUGHTER'S
IN ANOTHER FACILITY.
NOTHING
LIFE-THREATENING.
WE'RE ARRANGING
TO HAVE HER
BROUGHT OVER SOON.
OK.
AND JULIO?
HE'S STILL IN SURGERY.
HE MAY BE ALL NIGHT.
I'M AFRAID
HIS CONDITION IS CRITICAL.
HIS RIGHT LEG WAS
AMPUTATED AT THE KNEE,
MR. BARUMAN.
IT--IT WAS THE ONLY WAY
TO FREE HIM FROM THE CAR.
THEY'RE FIGHTING
TO SAVE THE OTHER LEG.
DR. BETZ
IS OUR TOP SURGEON.
PASTOR!
OUR KIDS ARE ALIVE.
OH, GRACIAS, DIOS.
JULIO'S IN SURGERY,
SO I'M GOING TO STAY HERE.
WOULD YOU PLEASE
GO TO SEE CATHY?
COULD YOU SHOW HER
WHERE CATHY IS?
YOU BE STRONG FOR CATHY.
OK.
YOU HAVE MY WORD.
IN A TRAGIC CONCLUSION
TO LAST NIGHT'S RESCUES,
SURGEONS REVEALED
THEY HAD TO CUT THROUGH
THE BODY OF HIS MOTHER
TO SAVE YOUNG
JULIO BARUMAN'S LIFE.
DR. JAMES BETZ,
CHIEF OF SURGERY...
AMPUTATION BELOW THE KNEE.
IN HORRIFIC CIRCUMSTANCES,
PETRA BARUMAN...
A TEAM OF SURGEONS
WORKS TIRELESSLY
TO SAVE YOUNG
JULIO BARUMAN'S LEFT LEG.
HIS RIGHT LEG
WAS AMPUTATED LAST NIGHT
IN GRISLY CIRCUMSTANCES
AS, REPORTEDLY,
HIS MOTHER'S BODY
HAD TO BE DISMEMBERED
FOR SURGEONS
TO SAVE HIS LIFE.
WE WILL KEEP YOU POSTED
AS THE STORY DEVELOPS.
MR. BARUMAN?
MY BOY?
YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO SEE HIM PRETTY SOON.
HE'S...
HIS CONDITION
REMAINS CRITICAL.
HIS LEG
HAS A GOOD CHANCE,
BUT WE WON'T KNOW
FOR A COUPLE DAYS.
WHAT WAS
YOUR WIFE WEARING?
BLUE.
THIS MORNING
SHE WAS WEARING BLUE.
SHE WAS DRIVING?
YES.
THE PRESS IS
MISTAKENLY REPORTING
WE HAD TO CUT HER BODY
IN ORDER TO REACH JULIO.
WELL, IT WAS THE OTHER WOMAN,
SHE WAS WEARING
A YELLOW BLOUSE.
YOLANDA.
IF WE WERE GOING TO
SAVE JULIO'S LIFE,
WE HAD TO DO IT.
AND PETRA?
I WANT TO ASSURE YOU
THAT THEY DIDN'T SUFFER.
THEY BOTH DIED INSTANTLY.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO NOW?
HOW ARE MY KIDS GOING TO DO
WITHOUT A MOTHER?
CAN YOU TELL ME?
YEAH, I'M SURE PEOPLE ARE
SLOW COMING IN TODAY,
BUT BUCK DOESN'T HAVE
THAT MUCH OF A COMMUTE
FROM HIS VAN.
DO YOU THINK
IT WOULD BE POSSIBLE
TO SEND SOMEBODY OVER
JUST TO CHECK TO SEE
IF HE'S OVERSLEPT?
UM, I'LL CALL YOU BACK.
POLICE HAVE CORDONED OFF
SEVERAL NEIGHBORHOODS...
YOU'RE UP EARLY.
IS DADDY AT WORK?
THEY'RE CLOSED TODAY.
WOULDN'T YOU KNOW IT?
AUTHORITIES ARE ASKING
THAT IF YOU DON'T LIVE
IN THESE AFFECTED AREAS
DO NOT VENTURE DOWN THERE.
EVEN AT THIS EARLY HOUR
WE'RE GETTING REPORTS
OF SOME PEOPLE HEADING
INTO THESE NEIGHBORHOODS
JUST TO SEE THE DAMAGE.
AND, PETE, THIS IS BECOMING
THE SYMBOL OF THE QUAKE,
A BROKEN, USELESS
BAY BRIDGE.
OBVIOUSLY, NO CARS ARE
BEING ALLOWED TO CROSS IT.
OTHER AFFECTED ARTERIES,
THE CENTRAL FREEWAY IS CLOSED,
THE EMBARCADERO FREEWAY
SHUT DOWN,
THE DOUBLE-DECK PORTION
OF THE I-280
IN SAN FRANCISCO SHUT DOWN.
ALL FOR INSPECTION
AND REPAIR.
NURSE'S AIDE TO STATION 6,
PLEASE.
NURSE'S AIDE
TO STATION 6, PLEASE.
MR. JAMES PRICE,
PLEASE REPORT TO ADMITTING.
THEY'RE PRAYING FOR HIM
ALL OVER THE WORLD,
I'M SURE.
HOW IS YOUR FAITH
HOLDING UP?
GOD SHOULD HAVE
TAKEN ME, SISTER.
MAYBE THIS WILL
HELP ME UNDERSTAND
WHY HE MADE
SUCH A HORRIBLE MISTAKE.
I KNOW IT DOESN'T SEEM
LIKE IT NOW, MR. BARUMAN,
BUT YOU'LL FIND
THE STRENGTH TO HANDLE IT.
ALL OF IT.
I KNOW
THAT YOU ARE DEEPLY GRIEVED
OVER YOUR WIFE'S DEATH.
EXCUSE ME, SISTER.
I'LL JUST READ IT
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
OF COURSE.
JIM, YOU GOT A BONE TO
THROW THE MEDIA OUTSIDE,
BEFORE THEY CLAW
MY SHIRT OFF?
YOU KNOW THE DRILL.
THE BARUMAN'S
ARE AN INTENSELY
PRIVATE FAMILY,
AND THEY RESPECTFULLY REQUEST
THEY BE SPARED--
MEDIA INTRUSION
IN THIS DIFFICULT TIME.
GOOD.
OK,
BUT THEY'LL HATE IT.
NOT MUCH LEFT OF YOU,
IS THERE?
OH, GAIL.
I WANT THAT BOY
TO MAKE IT.
HE CAN'T HAVE COME THIS FAR
AND NOT MAKE IT.
SURE WISH
IT WORKED THAT WAY.
SOMETIMES IT DOES.
HOLD ON TO THAT.
OK, LISTEN UP!
QUIET!
THE INCIDENT COMMANDER
HAS ORDERED ALL CIVILIANS
OUT OF THIS AREA
FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY.
O.P.D., CALTRANS,
AUTHORIZED CONTRACTORS,
AND THE OAKLAND
FIRE DEPARTMENT
WILL BE WORKING HERE
UNTIL THE LAST VICTIM
HAS BEEN LOCATED
AND REMOVED.
YOU'VE ALL WORKED
LONG AND HARD
THESE LAST 3 DAYS.
AND WE WANT TO...
I WANT TO PERSONALLY
THANK YOU.
ALL OF YOU.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S BREAK IT UP.
CLEAR THIS AREA.
CLEAR THE AREA!
CIVILIANS AND VOLUNTEERS,
CLEAR THE AREA.
THE SEARCH FOR THE SURVIVORS
IS OVER.
CLEAR THE FREEWAY
AND SURROUNDING AREA.
THE SEARCH FOR SURVIVORS
IS OVER.
CIVILIANS AND VOLUNTEERS,
CLEAR THE AREA.
WELL,
WITH EACH SUCCEEDING HOUR,
HOPE IS FADING HERE
THAT ANYONE WILL BE
EXTRICATED ALIVE
FROM THIS WRECKAGE
THAT WAS ONCE
THE I-880 FREEWAY.
THIS MORNING,
THE ONLY PEOPLE WE'VE SEEN
LOWERED FROM THAT CONCRETE
HAVE BEEN COVERED IN
THE SHROUD OF DEATH.
IN FACT,
MOST OF THE ACTIVITY HERE
IS CENTERED AROUND
MOVING VEHICLES.
...SLIM HOPE ANYBODY'S...
THAT'S GREG.
BE NICE.
HI.
ARE YOU GONNA
OPEN THE DOOR?
NOT UNLESS
YOU'RE CLEAN AND SOBER.
I'M HIS SON, TOO.
NO.
THERE ARE STILL RULES.
I'M CLEAN, OK?
I GUESS I HAVE TO
TAKE YOUR WORD FOR THAT.
...FOR NOW, FEARING THAT COULD
CAUSE FURTHER COLLAPSE
AND BURY THE SURVIVOR
FOR GOOD.
IN ADDITION,
COUNTY AUTHORITIES ARE SAYING
THAT SOME 2 DOZEN PEOPLE
STILL REMAIN
HI.
OFFICIALLY MISSING.
...THE DECEASED VICTIMS
WILL ALREADY
HAVE BEEN REMOVED...
BUT NOT YET
POSITIVELY IDENTIFIED.
IN SOME CASES, FRANKLY,
THE REMAINS ARE
SO BADLY MANGLED,
IT IS DIFFICULT FOR
THE CORONER TO DETERMINE...
BUCK DOESN'T HAVE
MUCH OF A CHANCE
IF HE'S IN THERE,
DOES HE?
GREG.
WELL, DIABETES AND ALL.
HE'S NOT DEAD!
WELL, NO,
NOT NECESSARILY.
WE JUST HOPE NOT,
OK, KIDDO?
BUT NOW RESCUERS
ARE FINDING ONLY BODIES.
THIS IS BECOMING
A GRIM TASK TO PEOPLE
WHO HAVE BEEN WORKING
BLEARY-EYED, NONSTOP,
SINCE THE QUAKE HIT.
GOOD NEWS.
CATHY'S ON HER WAY OVER.
MY BEAUTIFUL PRINCESS.
MR. BARUMAN,
THERE'S A, UH...
THERE'S A LOT OF SWELLING
THAT ACCOMPANIES
FACIAL SURGERY,
AND HER JAW
HAS BEEN WIRED SHUT,
BUT WE'RE 100% SURE
SHE'LL BE BEAUTIFUL AGAIN.
YOU REMEMBER THAT
WHEN YOU SEE HER.
100%?
MAYBE 200.
MR. BARUMAN,
UH, PLEASE,
CALL ME PASTOR.
PASTOR.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT HOW
YOU'RE GOING TO TELL
CATHY AND, UH, AND JULIO
ABOUT THEIR MOTHER?
NOT NOW.
WHEN THEY GET WELL.
SOONER IS ALWAYS BETTER.
IT'S WORTH PRAYING OVER.
MR. BARUMAN,
THE AMBULANCE IS HERE.
IS IT TRUE THAT SHE'S GOT
57 BROKEN FACIAL BONES?
PLEASE! WE'LL HAVE
A STATEMENT LATER.
HOW'S THE BOY?
HOW'S CATHY'S FACE?
WILL SHE BE DISFIGURED?
ESCORT THIS MAN
FROM THE PREMISES.
HEY, BUDDY,
ARE YOU A BARUMAN?
WHO EVER TOLD YOU
THIS WAS JOURNALISM?
PRINCESS.
SHE'LL BE
BEAUTIFUL AGAIN.
PASTOR. PASTOR.
YOU LOOK AT CATHY
LIKE SHE'S STILL BEAUTIFUL,
AND SHE WILL BE.
MMM-HMM.
ALL RIGHT?
200%
I'VE GOT TO REMEMBER THAT.
WHERE'S JULIO?
DOCTOR BETZ IS OPERATING
ON HIS LEG AGAIN.
HIS CONDITION
IS DETERIORATING.
I KNEW I SHOULDN'T
HAVE LEFT HIM.
I GOT TO GO TO HIM.
NO, NO, PASTOR. COME ON.
THE DOCTORS WILL DO
WHAT THEY CAN.
WE WILL DO WHAT WE CAN.
SISTER, WILL YOU LEAD US
IN THE ROSARY?
IN THE NAME OF THE FATHER
AND THE SON
AND THE HOLY GHOST.
AMEN.
I BELIEVE IN GOD
THE FATHER ALMIGHTY,
MAKER OF
HEAVEN AND EARTH.
I BELIEVE IN JESUS CHRIST,
HIS ONLY SON, OUR LORD.
OUR FATHER
WHICH ART IN HEAVEN,
HALLOWED BE THY NAME.
THY KINGDOM COME.
THY WILL BE DONE
ON EARTH
AS IT IS IN HEAVEN.
HAIL MARY, FULL OF GRACE,
THE LORD IS WITH THEE.
BLESSED ART THOU
AMONG WOMEN,
AND BLESSED IS
THE FRUIT OF THY WOMB, JESUS.
HOLY MARY, MOTHER OF GOD,
PRAY FOR US SINNERS,
FROM NOW UNTIL
THE HOUR OF OUR DEATH. AMEN.
HAIL MARY, FULL OF GRACE,
THE LORD IS WITH THEE.
BLESSED ART THOU
AMONG WOMEN...
I CAN'T REMEMBER
WHAT I'VE TOLD YOU, DES.
MY FLAWS FADE.
DON'T SEEM TO MATTER NOW.
I'M COLD. HUNGRY.
BUT THE TERRIBLE LONELINESS
MAY BE THE LAST THING I KNOW.
NO ONE TO CRY OUT TO
THAT WOULD HEAR.
HELP ME.
SOMEONE HELP ME.
FROM NOW UNTIL
THE HOUR OF OUR DEATH. AMEN.
MY BABY.
I'M BIG.
OH, YES, YOU ARE.
YOU'RE SO BIG.
WHERE AM I?
YOU'RE IN A HOSPITAL.
YOU GOT HURT.
IT WAS AN EARTHQUAKE,
REMEMBER?
WAS IT FUN?
NO.
I WANT MY MAMA.
SHE'S NOT HERE.
GET HER.
PASTOR, GO HOME.
LEAVE THEM WITH US
FOR A FEW HOURS.
AS THE DEATH TOLL
IS ADDED UP,
IT APPEARS THERE ARE
FAR FEWER FATALITIES...
MOM, ARE YOU CRYING?
DID GREG DO SOMETHING?
NO, HONEY,
HE'S BEEN FINE.
IT'S THESE ONIONS.
THAT'S WHAT
THEY ALL SAY, MOM.
MAYBE, UH, I DON'T KNOW,
YOU STILL CARE ABOUT DAD.
JEFF, NO.
NOT--NOT--NOT THAT WAY.
HONEY, I WILL ALWAYS
CARE ABOUT HIM.
HE GAVE ME ALL OF YOU.
YOUR DAD WAS
A HELL OF A GUY.
COMPLETE SECTION 87
WITH A TOTAL OF
41 FATALITIES SO FAR.
BODY COUNT'S COMING IN
WAY LOWER THAN EXPECTED.
GUESS EVERYBODY
WAS AT THE GAME
OR AT HOME WATCHING.
DON TO THE CYPRESS COMMAND.
I'M STILL AT 100.
BLUE PICKUP,
NO SURVIVORS.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I CAN SEE A HAND HERE.
THIS IS IT, THIS IS IT.
THERE WE GO.
GOT IT?
ALL RIGHT, NICOLA,
YOU CAN I.D. THE BODY.
GET THE MEDICS!
WE HAVE A LIVE MALE.
MOM! SOMEONE'S STILL ALIVE.
A MAN.
HERE AT THE NORTHERN END
OF THE COLLAPSED FREEWAY,
WORKERS ARE ATTEMPTING
TO RESCUE A MAN
WHO HAS APPARENTLY
BEEN TRAPPED INSIDE
THE CONCRETE STRUCTURE
FOR 4 DAYS.
SURVIVAL IN A SITUATION
LIKE THIS
COULD ONLY BE CALLED
MIRACULOUS.
NOTHING IS KNOWN ABOUT
THE LONE SURVIVOR,
JUST FOUND NEAR THE NORTH END
OF THE COLLAPSED FREEWAY.
I KNOW IT'S DAD.
DES, LET'S JUST NOT
GET OUR HOPES UP, OK?
MY HOPES ARE UP.
GET YOURS UP, MAMA.
MAYBE HE CAN FEEL IT.
MAYBE HE CAN.
JEFF, CALL MARK.
...AUTHORITIES HAVE SAID,
FREEING THE MAN FROM
THE METAL AND CONCRETE
COULD TAKE SEVERAL HOURS.
AGAIN TO REITERATE,
A SURVIVOR
HAS BEEN FOUND
AFTER 4 DAYS
TRAPPED IN THE RUBBLE.
A DOCTOR TOLD ME...
DEAR GOD,
LET IT BE BUCK.
...SEVERELY DEHYDRATED
AFTER 90 HOURS
IF ONLY I HADN'T LEANED ON HIM
A LITTLE HARDER.
DAVE,
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
I SHOULD HAVE INSISTED
HE COME WITH ME.
EASY NOW.
CAREFUL WITH HIS HEAD.
BE DADDY.
YES. YES.
IF THERE'S ANYONE
IN THE UNIVERSE
WHO CAN PULL THROUGH THIS,
IT'S OUR OLD MAN.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
COME ON, GET OUT OF THE WAY!
GET OUT OF THERE.
COME ON. OH, COME ON.
MOVE IT, DAMN IT!
THOSE ARE MY BOOTS.
HE WAS WEARIN' 'EM.
HE WORE MY BOOTS!
THAT'S HIM!
HE'S ALIVE.
YEAH, THAT'S IT!
OH, JEFF.
YES, I'M SURE.
BUCK HELM, H-E-L-M.
TELL THEM HE'S A DIABETIC.
I'M HIS WIFE.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE
THEY'RE TAKING HIM?
GREG, YOU WANT TO
RIDE WITH ME?
WOULDN'T THAT THRILL DAD
TO SEE ME?
TELL HIM I SAID HI.
GREG,
BUCK NEEDS ALL HIS KIDS.
"AND EVERYONE HOPES
YOU GET WELL SOON.
THIS IS MARY BYRNE
FROM THIRD GRADE."
THIS ONE'S
FROM MEXICO.
"DEAR CATHY AND JULIO,
"WE HAVE EARTHQUAKES
IN OUR COUNTRY, TOO,
"AND BAD THINGS HAPPEN.
WE'RE SORRY ABOUT..."
SORRY ABOUT WHAT?
WHAT?
IT'S ABOUT
THE EARTHQUAKE,
AND ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR MOTHER.
DO YOU REMEMBER?
SHE DROVE YOU
TO THE DENTIST.
WHEN--WHEN--WHEN MOMMY
DROVE TO,
TO THE FREEWAY,
THE EARTHQUAKE HIT,
AND YOU BOTH WERE SAVED,
BUT MOMMY...
THE ANGELS TOOK MOMMY.
WHY?
THEY DON'T SAY.
BUT SHE'S IN HEAVEN NOW,
AND SHE'S VERY, VERY HAPPY.
THEY SHOULD
BRING HER BACK.
THEY CAN'T, SON.
THEY'RE ONE-WAY ANGELS
SENT BY GOD,
AND WE GOT TO LET HER GO.
I WANT MY MAMA.
IT'S OK, BABY.
IT'LL BE ANOTHER
12 TO 24 HOURS
BEFORE HIS CONDITION
DEFINES ITSELF.
DOCTOR SCOTT,
I'M A CERTIFIED NURSE'S AIDE.
I WANT THE TRUTH.
OK.
HIS KIDNEYS SHUT DOWN,
SO WE'VE GOT TO GET HIM
ONTO DIALYSIS RIGHT AWAY.
SOME BROKEN BONES,
SEVERE DEHYDRATION.
THE DIABETES
COMPLICATES THINGS.
HE'S CRITICAL.
YOU WANT TO KEEP HIM ALIVE,
TELL THE GUARD DOWNSTAIRS
TO LET HIS KIDS THROUGH.
I PROMISE YOU
THAT'S WHAT'S KEPT HIM GOING
ALL THIS TIME.
THIS IS A TRAUMA UNIT.
YOU GOT TO HELP ME.
SLOW DOWN, DES.
YOU'RE IN A HOSPITAL.
TRY AND BE REALLY UP
AND CHEERFUL FOR DAD.
HE LOOKS A LITTLE THINNER.
DADDY?
YOU'RE GETTING LETTERS
FROM ALL OVER THE WORLD.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
AND THIS IS FROM JAPAN.
"ITO TANAKA."
NICE BOX?
CARD.
IN ENGLISH.
SAYS, "DEAR CATHY AND JULIO,
"THIS ORIGAMI
COMES FROM THOUSANDS
OF SCHOOL CHILDREN IN TOKYO."
YOU LOOK SO PRETTY
WHEN YOU SMILE.
OH, EVEN THOSE WIRES
ARE PRETTY.
YOU'RE GETTING
PRETTIER AND PRETTIER
EVERY SINGLE DAY,
JUST LIKE
DR. BETZ SAID YOU WOULD.
BUT YOU DON'T REMEMBER
THAT HE ALSO SAID
THAT YOU HAD TO EXERCISE
AFTER 2 WEEKS.
NOW IT'S TIME.
CATHY WOULD RATHER NOT
WALK TODAY.
AT LEAST ANGELS
DIDN'T TAKE YOUR LEG.
HEY, CATHY.
YOU REMEMBER ME?
YOU REMEMBER THAT?
YEAH.
JULIO, THE ANGELS
DID NOT TAKE YOUR LEG.
THEY TOOK MAMA,
DIDN'T THEY?
THAT IS NOT
HOW ANGELS OPERATE.
WELL, WHO'S TO BLAME THEN?
NOBODY.
JUST THE EARTHQUAKE.
WELL, WHO MADE
THE EARTHQUAKE?
GOD!
THEN GOD TOOK MY LEG.
YOU CAN'T BE ANGRY AT GOD.
WHO EVER HEARD
OF SUCH A THING?
OK, THE ANGELS THEN.
MR. BARUMAN?
FRANK STEWART.
HI.
JULIO, THIS IS THE MAN
WHO FOUND YOU.
HI, JULIO.
YOU'RE LOOKIN' PRETTY GOOD.
THE ANGELS TOOK MY LEG.
WELL, LOOKS LIKE
THEY MADE A CLEAN GETAWAY.
BUT I BET
THEY'LL BRING YOU ANOTHER ONE,
ONE
THAT'S SUPERSONIC TOUGH
THAT NOT EVEN EARTHQUAKES
CAN MESS WITH.
HERE.
I THINK YOU LOST THIS.
OPEN IT.
THANK YOU, MR. STEWART.
YOU KNOW,
I'M A BIG A'S FAN MYSELF.
I GOT SEASON TICKETS,
AND MAYBE
WE CAN GO SOMETIME.
DAD, THIS IS AUDRA,
MY FIANCEE.
WE SET A DATE
FOR CHRISTMAS.
I WANT YOU TO BE
MY BEST MAN.
HEY, BUCK.
SEE YOU LATER.
SEE YOU, MARK.
WE MISS YOU, GUY.
NOBODY TO QUOTE
ALL THOSE DEAD GREEKS.
WHEN CAN I TELL THEM
YOU'LL BE BACK?
6 MONTHS? A YEAR?
BUCK, UH, WHAT IS IT?
HE'S A GREAT KID.
YOU KNOW,
IN A THOUSAND YEARS,
I COULD NOT REPAY YOU
FOR SAVING MY CHILDREN,
RISKING YOUR LIFE.
MAYBE IT WAS A CASE
OF TEMPORARY INSANITY.
BUT YOU KNOW,
MR. BARUMAN,
FOR A WHILE THERE,
IT FELT LIKE
IT WAS MY KIDS.
MAYBE EVEN MY RIGHT ARM.
I COULDN'T HAVE LEFT,
EVEN IF I TRIED.
THERE WAS NOTHING
HEROIC ABOUT IT, BELIEVE ME.
ANYBODY WOULD HAVE
DONE IT.
BUT THEY DIDN'T.
YOU DID.
SO, UH, JULIO'S HAVING
A TOUGH ADJUSTMENT?
HE'S VERY ANGRY,
MR. STEWART.
BOY, I WOULD BE, TOO.
I DON'T FEEL ANGRY,
I JUST FEEL EMPTY.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
BECAUSE THAT PICTURE
IS PRIVATE PROPERTY.
YOU BET I'LL HOLD.
WE WOULD LIKE TO MAKE
THE 6:00 NEWSCAST.
SO, HOW MUCH
DID YOU GET FOR IT?
UH, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
THIS. MY PICTURE OF BUCK.
HOW MUCH DID YOU GET?
COOL IT, LAURIE.
I'LL SPLIT IT WITH YOU.
DON'T YOU TELL ME
THIS IS ABOUT MONEY.
IS THAT ALL
YOU EVER THINK ABOUT? MONEY?
THEY'D HAVE GOTTEN
THE PICTURE ANYWAY.
SO WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO NOW?
WALK IN THERE, TAPE BUCK,
AND SELL IT TO T.V.?
I'M NO MILLIONAIRE.
I GOT TO LIVE.
GREG,
WHEN ARE YOU GOING
TO GET IT TOGETHER?
WHO PUT YOU IN CHARGE?
YOU'RE JUST
HIS DAMN EX-WIFE.
THIS IS NOT ABOUT
BEING IN CHARGE.
THIS IS ABOUT CARING
FOR SOMEONE WHO LOVES YOU
NO MATTER WHAT
YOU PUT HIM THROUGH.
LOOK, JUST TAKE IT ALL.
I'M NOT GONNA TELL BUCK
ABOUT THIS,
WHETHER HE PULLS THROUGH
OR NOT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN WHETHER?
I THOUGHT--
DON'T THINK, GREG. ASK.
HEY, I THOUGHT
WE HAD A DEAL!
BUCK, LOOK WHO'S HERE.
I'LL COME AGAIN SOON.
SEE YOU.
HEY, BUCK.
YOU'RE LOOKIN' PRETTY GOOD
FOR A DIRTY OLD MAN.
NURSES TREATIN' YOU ALL RIGHT?
HEY, YOU WANT ME
TO GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE?
YEAH, I FIGURED.
IT'S MORE OF
THE SAME OLD STUFF.
I KNOW YOU THINK
THIS IS GONNA BE
ANOTHER ONE
OF MY COME-ONS.
LOOK, I KNOW
I'M A DISAPPOINTMENT TO YOU,
RIGHT?
THIS WHOLE THING'S GOT ME
THINKING DIFFERENTLY, OK?
I'M REALLY SORRY, DAD.
I LOVE YOU.
HELLO, WELL,
MY 2 FAVORITE LADIES.
LOOK AT YOU.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE READY
FOR THE 100-YARD DASH.
OH, DON'T LOOK AT ME.
I CAN'T EVEN CATCH HIM.
HEY, ARE YOU GOING
TO ANSWER ALL THAT MAIL?
WE GOT A LOT
TO BE GRATEFUL FOR.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, JULIO?
JULIO, SISTER MARY SAYS
YOU'RE BLAMING THE ANGELS
FOR TAKING YOUR LEG.
WELL, I CAN'T LET THEM
TAKE THE RAP.
I HAD TO AMPUTATE YOUR LEG.
BUT JULIO, I HAD TO DO IT.
YOUR LEG WAS BADLY HURT.
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO WALK ON IT ANYWAY.
IT WOULD HAVE HURT YOU
TERRIBLY ALL THE TIME.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
ALL RIGHT.
THEN, FROM NOW ON,
IF YOU GET MAD AT ME,
OR YOU GET MAD AT YOUR LEG,
I WANT YOU
TO BEAT ON YOUR BED.
LIKE THIS.
ALL RIGHT? YOU DO IT.
OH, I'D BE WAY MADDER
THAN THAT.
NO, NO, NO, NO. LIKE THIS.
ALL RIGHT? YOU DO IT.
HARD. HIT IT.
MAD. GET MAD.
MAD, MAD, MAD!
YEAH, MAD.
MAD, MAD, MAD, MAD, MAD,
MAD, MAD, MAD, MAD, MAD.
"BUT YOUR COURAGE
UNDER ALL THAT RUBBLE
"MADE ME REALIZE
"I SHOULD STOP COMPLAINING
ABOUT MY OWN DIABETES
AND REALIZE
HOW LUCKY I AM."
YOU HELPED SO MANY PEOPLE
JUST BY NOT GIVING UP.
I'M GOING TO SHOW THESE
TO MOM
SO SHE'LL SEE
HOW GREAT YOU ARE.
EVERYBODY SAYS SO.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE OK?
DES, HONEY,
VISITING HOURS ARE OVER.
LOVE YOU, DADDY.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
BUCK, YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
THAT CAN CRY, YOU KNOW.
GOD, IT KILLS ME
WHEN YOU DO THIS.
EVERY TIME I THINK
I'M FED UP WITH YOU,
YOU PULL SOMETHING
LIKE THIS.
BUCK,
DON'T YOU DIE ON ME.
YOU HANG ON,
AND WE'LL JUST FORGET ABOUT
THIS SEPARATION THING.
WE'LL WALK OUT
OF THIS HOSPITAL
AND TRY AGAIN.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, BUCK?
WE GOT A DEAL?
I STILL CAN'T
FIGURE YOU OUT,
BUT YOU SURE GO
TO A LOT OF TROUBLE
TO GET YOUR WAY.
PLEASE, BUCK, COME ON.
FIGHT.
THIS LEG ISN'T SUPERSONIC.
IT JUST STANDS THERE.
YOU HAVE TO PUT
THE MOTOR IN IT.
COME ON.
IT'S TOO HARD.
NOT FOR A FIGHTER.
IT WAS HARD
THE FIRST TIME
WHEN YOU KICKED THE BALL,
REMEMBER?
SO, YOU DID IT.
COME ON.
THIS IS DIFFERENT.
YOU HAVE TO TRY.
I CAN'T.
LOOK, IMAGINE THERE'S A BALL
IN FRONT OF YOU. NOW KICK IT.
I CAN'T MOVE
THIS STUPID LEG.
KICK THE BALL.
NO. I CAN'T!
KICK IT!
THIS BALL IS STUPID!
THIS LEG IS STUPID!
STUPID, STUPID, STUPID!
HEY, HEY.
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAVE MAMA?
I WANTED TO.
I WANTED TO, SON.
I WANTED IT SO BAD.
I WANT MY MAMA.
SO DO I, SON. SO DO I.
AT HIGHLAND HOSPITAL,
WHERE BUCK HELM,
WHO SO HEROICALLY
FOUGHT FOR HIS LIFE LAST MONTH
UNDER
THE INTERSTATE RUBBLE,
IS FIGHTING
FOR HIS LIFE AGAIN.
THIS DRAMATIC TURN
CAME JUST MOMENTS AGO...
MARK, I NEED
TO TALK TO YOU.
I GOT TO GET UP THERE.
OH, WAIT,
THIS IS BUCK'S ORDERS,
SOMETHING HE WANTS
YOU TO HAVE.
THIS IS DAD'S UNION BOOK.
HE NEEDS IT FOR WORK.
OH, GOD.
HEY, COME HERE.
MR. BARUMAN?
WHERE ARE YOUR KIDS?
IT'S JUST ME TODAY.
I--I--I--I STILL WANT
TO KEEP THEM SAFE,
YOU KNOW,
AWAY FROM THE PUBLIC EYE.
UM, THE--THE REASON
THAT I, UH, UM,
WANT TO SPEAK TO YOU
IS BECAUSE
THE--THE FEELINGS THAT I HAVE
FOR SO MANY ARE TOO LARGE
FOR A SIMPLE THANK YOU.
THESE LAST MONTHS,
I'VE BEEN WONDERING
WHAT MAKES A FATHER
CLIMB INTO A BURNING HELL
TO SAVE THE CHILDREN
OF A MAN THAT HE'S NEVER MET.
WHAT--WHAT KIND OF LOVE
SENDS DOCTORS
AND HUNDREDS OF RESCUE WORKERS
INTO SITUATIONS
OF EXTREME DANGER,
WITH NO THOUGHT
FOR THEIR OWN SAFETY?
WHAT KIND OF LOVE MAKES
ORDINARY MEN AND WOMEN
BECOME SO MUCH LARGER
THAN THEMSELVES?
SO MANY THOUSANDS
HAVE WRITTEN TO ME
TO SHARE WITH ME
THEIR OWN PERSONAL TRAGEDIES,
SO THAT I CAN LEARN
FROM THEIRS
AND LEARN HOW TO COPE
WITH MY OWN.
I WISH YOU COULD HAVE ALL
KNOWN MY WIFE PETRA.
SHE WAS A BEAUTIFUL PERSON,
YOU KNOW,
REAL THROUGH TO HER SOUL.
I--I--I CAN'T UNDERSTAND
AND I GUESS
I NEVER WILL UNDERSTAND
WHY GOD CLAIMED HER.
SHE WAS ALWAYS DOING
GOOD THINGS FOR EVERYBODY.
BUT I FEEL THAT, UM...
ALL THE GOOD THINGS
THAT SHE DID
ARE COMING BACK TO ME
AND TO--TO CATHY AND TO JULIO
THROUGH YOU.
YOU HAVE RESTORED
MY CHILDREN TO ME
THROUGH YOUR COURAGE
AND YOUR PRAYERS.
I, UH...
I--I CAN'T
THANK YOU INDIVIDUALLY,
AND I CERTAINLY
WON'T BE ABLE
TO ANSWER ALL THE MAIL,
BUT I WANT YOU
TO KNOW THAT, UM,
I'LL BE TALKING TO YOU
IN MY HEART WHENEVER I, UH...
I FEEL
THAT I NEED THE STRENGTH
TO GO ON WITHOUT MY WIFE.
AND WHAT A BEAUTIFUL DAY
IT IS HERE IN OAKLAND.
AS WE APPROACH
THE RUSH HOUR,
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE HEAD ACROSS
THE NEWLY OPENED
BAY BRIDGE,
WHERE TRAFFIC IS FLOWING WELL,
OUTBOUND AND IN?
MIRACLE OF MIRACLES.