Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Joining us
for the toss of the coin,
the President
of the United States...
Mr. President,
will you please toss the coin?
It is tails.
San Francisco
has won the toss.
You can elect to kick...
You want the ball?
Which goal will you defend?
Will you put your backs
to the goal, please?
Joe Montana joins
his teammates on the field.
Super Bowl 19.
The Miami Dolphins.
And the San Francisco 49ers.
The best combined records of any two
teams to ever meet in a Super Bowl.
And Joe Montana.
They talk of the cool of Dan Marino.
Super Bowl 19.
Second quarter.
Joe Montana steps
to the line of scrimmage,
drops back to throw,
and then...
Montana in
trouble and Doug Betters
covers him quickly
at the 42-yard line.
You feel pretty
good, then all of a sudden,
the pocket starts to cave in.
Now this might seem
like a failure. A mistake.
But of all the characteristics
needed to be an all-pro quarterback,
this one is
rarely talked about.
The ability to stay
in the pocket.
To stay calm and collected as a wall
of humanity collapses around you.
The courage to stand your
ground and take the hit.
And then have the will to get back
up, and do it all over again.
Drop back, settle,
deliver the perfect throw.
And another record has fallen.
Another one to Joe Montana.
Falling all over the place.
They've really put on a terrific
show, particularly offensively...
They roll to the right.
Montana fires a shot...
How much longer?
I want to play some Atari.
Kurt?
Ever since I saw Joe Montana
become the MVP of that Super Bowl
and break his
all-time pass record,
I knew I wanted
to be that guy.
Over a million athletes play high
school football every year in America.
Each with a dream
of their own.
Only about 5% of them
make it to college ball.
And only 1% of those
get drafted to the NFL.
Most don't stay in the league
for more than three years.
Most are not quarterbacks.
Only a select few will ever
play in the Super Bowl...
And each year,
there is only one MVP of that game.
So, by all accounts,
my dream, my story
is impossible.
That's just
the kind of story this is.
Huddle up.
All right, boys.
Let's do this.
Ah...
Trips right, 70-watt special.
On one, ready.
And that
will bring on Kurt Warner,
the 5th year senior,
making his first start.
Remember, folks, he's sat
on the bench for four years
even though he was highly
recruited out of high school.
Blue, 60, hut!
Warner takes the snap.
A strong interior rush...
...and he's levelled by middle
linebacker Cole Banks...
Go home, Kurt!
Go home. Go home.
Come on!
Let's go, baby.
Whoo!
Get set, get set, get set.
Blue, 60, hut!
He's flushed
out of the pocket...
No, no, no, no.
Stay in the pocket.
He's running
out of real estate
and throws the ball
across his body
towards the corner
of the end zone.
Touchdown!
How you like that, Coach?
- You still didn't stay in the damn pocket.
- Yeah, you're welcome.
Kicking game!
Move it!
Ineligible, down field.
Okay.
I'm gonna wear this one.
You take this one.
No. I'm staying here.
I got work to do.
Work? Man, you can
hardly call that work.
How you gonna make a highlight
reel with no highlights, huh?
You only started two games.
Just sayin'.
I have
highlights.
- And who you gonna send that to?
- Scouts. Agents.
You really are
delusional, huh?
The NFL's not gonna draft some dude
who's been sitting on the bench
for four years at a
1-AA school in Iowa.
It's madness.
Come on.
We're going out.
I'm never gonna
wear this.
Hudnutt, how do you listen
to this music? It is garbage.
We're gonna have
a good old time. Let's go.
Can we get
two Buds?
Thank you.
I'm gonna
make a lap.
You do that.
Have fun.
Blue 80, hut!
Hey!
No, no, no, no.
Stay in the pocket.
What did I say?
To stay in
the pocket, Coach.
Bingo, hotshot.
Hello,
and welcome everybody
to Sports Center,
I'm Karl Ravech.
And a very special welcome
to the newest member
of our Sports Center family,
that's Steve Levy.
The MO Morris
Lewis show of the New York Jets
opened up well off-Broadway in
Pittsburgh against the Steelers
who already had
a preseason...
Hud? I'm gonna need
to ask you a favor
and I'm gonna appreciate you
not laughing at me too much.
Can't wait
to hear this.
I need you to teach
me how to dance.
Well, like, dance,
like, line dance?
Like line dancing,
barn dancing,
all the dancing...
Oh, man, this is gonna be great.
This about that girl, isn't it?
That's none of
your business.
You have no idea how
happy this makes me.
Yeah, I do.
You look good.
Oh, wow.
- Hey, uh, bartender.
- Yeah.
Hey, uh,
can you play a line...
Uh, not a line dance.
A barn dance for me?
All right,
it's a barn dance!
Barn dance!
Grab your partner,
do-si-do.
Excuse me, cowboy. I'm gonna take this one.
Thank you very much.
Oh, about time.
You don't look
like a cowboy.
That's 'cause I'm not.
What are you, then?
I'm a football player.
My name is Kurt Warner.
What's yours?
Nope. Not yet.
That hardly
seems fair.
I mean, I just
gave you my name.
You're not gonna
give me yours?
No.
What am I supposed to do?
Just guess?
Go for it.
Okay, all right. Um...
Abby? Abigail.
Gail. Uh, Helen, Isabelle,
Jacqueline, Beatrice.
You're supposed to
be the other way.
Yeah, I know.
I just like this view a lot more.
She won't
tell me her name, so...
You move real good
on that dance floor.
Well, that makes one of us.
Thank you. Actually, it's...
Yeah, okay.
What? I like what I like.
So, football?
Tell me about that.
How do you mean?
What do you want to know?
You defined yourself as a sport.
So it must be pretty
important to you.
Hell, I don't know.
I just love it.
Well, I like a man who knows
why he loves something, so...
Okay. Okay,
how about this?
I'll answer
your question,
but first,
you gotta answer one of mine.
Uh, what exactly is
Miss August over there?
That is, um...
That's a tight-fitting
jeans contest.
Oh, is it really?
First Thursday
of every month.
It's the first time
I won.
Congratulations.
- It's so embarrassing.
- Yeah.
Um, so football?
Seriously.
You give me an honest answer
and I'll give you my name.
Okay. Um...
So, football was
the most important thing
my pops taught me
before he...
uh, left.
I mean, he's back
in my life now
but, you know,
back then it was tough...
and we always,
you know, struggled.
Me and my mom,
my brother.
Never had enough.
And I wanted more.
I wanted to make something
of my life.
And football, um,
is just like the only thing
I've ever really been good at.
So, just feels like
more than a game to me.
As long as I have
a ball in my hands,
then I feel like everything's
gonna be all right.
Is that honest enough
for you?
You know, I normally
hate country music
but I kinda like
this song.
Well, I hate sports,
so guess it'll never work between us.
- I suppose so. What a shame.
- Mmm.
What do you like
about it?
I don't know.
I guess that it's different.
Kinda like you.
I'm Brenda.
Well, it's a pleasure
to meet you, Brenda.
Last call.
And I gotta go.
Gotta go?
You gotta "go" go?
Hey. Hey, come on,
wait a second.
I mean,
is this something that I said?
Is it something
that I did?
Can I at least get
your phone number?
Trust me. You don't want it.
What?
Wait, wait, wait. Why wouldn't I?
Why wouldn't I?
Why wouldn't I want your number?
Look, there's a few things
you need to know about me.
I'm divorced
and I got two kids.
So, if I never see you
again, I totally understand.
- But I don't want to.
- Okay, just one bite for Mama.
One bite. Come on.
Okay, sweetheart.
Well,
I'm making the jam one...
The jelly one
first, honey.
I need you to eat just
a tiny little bit more.
- Mama?
- Oh! Over here, baby.
Over here.
Oh, is it broken?
Broken, Mama.
Okay. Mama will fix that
in just a minute.
No, Jesse,
not for you.
But can you just have
a few more bites
of your applesauce,
please, sweetheart?
I just...
Mom, can you get that?
Hello?
I didn't mean to scare you.
It's Kurt from the bar last night.
I knocked on the front door but...
This was
a bad idea.
Okay.
Okay, okay,
okay...
Mom?
Mom? Mom, help!
Hey. What's going on,
little...
- Come on.
- Oh.
Yeah, hey.
Am I coming in?
It's broken.
Oh, it's broken?
Uh...
What's broken?
Oh, the radio is broken. Okay.
- Oh, we're going to the bathroom? Okay.
- Broken radio.
Oh, well.
You're missing a battery.
That's why we're in the bathroom.
Look at that.
All right.
There we go.
Oh. Country?
They got you too, huh?
Lay down.
Okay.
There you go.
♪ You and
me go fishing in the dark
♪ Lying on our backs
and counting the stars
♪ Where the cool
grass grows
♪ Down by the river
in the full moon light
♪ We'll be fallin'
in love
♪ In the middle of the
night Just movin' slow ♪
You know? Maybe country
ain't so bad after all.
What's your name,
little man?
Zack.
Mmm. That's a good name.
My name's Kurt.
You like trucks?
Black trucks. Driver.
Oh, you want to be
a truck driver, huh?
A black truck driver.
Oh, what he means is he
wants to drive a black truck.
Right. Uh...
Hey, I'm... I'm Kurt.
I'm here for Brenda.
I figured.
Otherwise I'd be, you
know, calling the police.
Yeah.
I'm Jenny Jo.
The mom.
Nice to meet you.
Kind of you
to fix the radio.
It was my pleasure.
Brenda? Is that the guy?
He's cute.
Mom, can you
please just...
And he's so nice.
- I know. Okay, now you can go. Thank you.
- Yes. Okay.
Uh, radio's fixed.
Thanks. Um...
We keep one in every room in the house.
It helps Zack.
Look, can I just be blunt?
Is there another option?
How do you know
where I live?
The bartender
at the bar.
And why are you here?
Well, I wanted to
meet your kids.
You seemed so passionate
about them last night.
And I also wanted
to give you this.
Oh.
Look, I have to get Zack
to physical therapy so...
Physical therapy?
He's legally blind,
and...
He's on his own journey.
Hmm.
I hadn't really
noticed that.
It was really nice
to meet you, Zack.
Yeah.
I'll see you around.
Hey.
My number.
So, maybe call
next time?
Where's your car?
I walked.
From UNI?
That's like three miles.
Oh, yeah.
Totally worth it.
Come on, Tanner.
Doubles, doubles, go.
Hut!
No!
Punt!
Tanner, come here. What are you doing?
First down's 25.
Your job is to
move the chains.
Come on, boys,
we've done this a thousand times before.
Hey, Coach.
Put me in and
I can win for you.
Come on.
Coach, come on.
- "UNI" on three. One, two, three.
- UNI!
You're
back on the bench
for the same reason you sat
on the bench for four years.
What is your
problem with me, Coach?
You want me to
sum it up for ya,
why you are
such a tragedy?
- You don't stay in the pocket.
- What?
You got the talent,
loads of it.
But when things
get hard, you bail.
You run from
adversity.
You don't trust your
team or my playbook.
You don't deserve
to play in the game.
Coach, 10 more games
and my dream is gone.
I've been working my whole
life for this. Please.
You need to start thinking
about life after football, son.
Respectfully,
you are wrong, Coach.
I'm not gonna quit,
because that's not what leaders do.
I just need to know
how to get on that field.
Blue 80, hut!
Again.
Hut!
You could throw.
But you cannot leave the pocket.
You want your shot?
You take the pain.
Hurry up!
Blue 80, hut!
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't you fumble my football.
You hold onto my football.
Again!
Again.
I said, "Again".
How many more times
we gonna do this, Coach?
As many times as I say.
Who else wants to kill Kurt?
I do.
Hudnutt,
you're on offense.
I'll switch for
this, though, baby.
Somebody give me a purple jersey.
Come on.
Hello?
Hey, there.
I'm startin' next week.
It's Kurt,
by the way. Warner.
You get my messages?
Yeah. All of them.
See? I called first.
That's good, right?
What do you say?
Monday night,
let's go on a date.
What are we
gonna do? Walk?
Is that a yes?
'Cause it sounds
like a yes.
I think you're trying
to say yes.
What are you doing?
Got us a ride.
Kurt, I have kids.
You should've called first.
I did call. You hung up on
me, don't you remember?
God, you're insane.
I saw that smile!
Yep.
Hey, kids...
You ever been
out here before?
- No, it's real pretty.
- Yeah.
Real peaceful, too.
It's one of my favorite
places to come.
- I dig your tattoo.
- Yeah?
Semper fidelis.
It's the motto of...
For the Marines,
yeah. Yeah.
I saw the pictures
on your mantle.
When...
When I was maybe
12, after church...
this woman comes up
to me and says...
"There's something special about
you, Brenda."
"God is gonna do
something great with you."
And...
I had the audacity
to believe her.
So, I had this dream of being
a Marine and marrying a Marine,
and having little
Marine children
and God, country,
and Corps all the way.
So, I signed up
right outta high school.
Wow.
Then, I met Brad.
My perfect Marine.
Whirlwind romance,
marriage...
and Zack was born
a year later.
And what happened
to Brad?
He cheated on me when I was
eight months pregnant with Jesse.
Oh... What?
So, um...
Yeah. I have
some trust issues.
Was Zack born blind?
No.
He wasn't.
I got this call
from Brad
when Zack was
four months old.
He said,
"He's breathing funny."
And I still remember
the panic in his voice.
And I rushed
to the hospital...
where we were told
his brain was swelling
and that he'd be lucky to
make it through the night.
And they had no idea
what was wrong 'cause...
'Cause Brad didn't tell us,
not for 24 hours...
that he accidentally
dropped Zack.
On his head.
In the tub.
Oh...
Could've been different, you
know, if he'd just told the truth.
I remember
praying and praying
and begging God
to just save my baby boy.
So, the doctor told me he'd never
walk, and yet...
That he'd never talk,
and now,
I can't get him to stop.
That he'd never be
a black truck driver.
He keeps finding a way
to prove everyone wrong.
He's...
He's my miracle.
That all seems pretty, uh,
important to you in your life.
Religion and God.
Yeah, it's more like
a relationship for me...
and, yes, it defines me.
And that lady who came up
and talked to you at church
all those years ago,
you still believe her?
I'm trying.
I'm a work
in progress.
This is where you
bring all your girls?
Oh,
are you my girl now?
No.
- Hey, there.
- Hey.
You just come
with me.
Hi. Good to
see you again.
- Yes, good to see you.
- Kurt, this is my dad.
- Hey, there.
- Hello, sir, pleasure to meet you.
- I want Grandma.
- Yeah?
He's cute.
- Oh, will you stop?
- Please, I'm married.
- That's my sister.
- Nice to meet ya.
Uh, hey, Dad,
could you give us a minute?
It's my garage.
I wasn't finished yet.
All right.
Okay, I'm trying to imagine a
scenario where any of this works.
- What, exactly?
- You know, us.
Oh, we're an "us" now.
That's good news.
This is crazy.
This isn't gonna work.
You keep saying that.
I just can't, I mean...
So, tomorrow night?
- Yep.
- All right.
Get set! Get set! Get set!
Three-sixty!
One-sixty! Hut, hut!
Hey, hey.
How does it feel to make out with
a future professional athlete?
It was better
before you said that.
Sixty, hut.
Hut!
Again. Let's go again.
Come on, right now, let's go.
Kurt Warner has
been absolutely on fire today.
There's been
a growing buzz
that this kid may be a dark
horse in this year's NFL draft.
I was voted
Gateway Player of the Year
and our team was
first in conference.
Look,
it's rare that a 1-AA player gets drafted.
But let's see
what we can do.
Thank you!
Yes! I promise...
Okay, gotta grab this.
Look forward to it, buddy.
- Yes!
- I got an agent!
- Let's go!
Hey.
Hey. Draft day.
How do you feel?
Are you nervous?
Yeah, no, I feel good.
I just want my chance, you know.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Who's this?
Oh, yeah, Mom,
so, this is Brenda.
- And this is her son, Zack.
- Hi.
Hi, it's nice to meet you.
The Bengals have selected Dan
Wilkinson, defensive tackle,
- Ohio State University.
- Pick Kurt. Pick Kurt.
Okay, shh,
sweetheart.
No, no, hey,
it's okay.
It's okay.
I probably won't get picked
until tomorrow, though.
Tomorrow?
Yeah, there's seven
rounds of picks
that are spread out
over two days,
so, if I get picked, when I get
picked, it'll be in the later rounds.
Kurt, it's Zack's birthday
tomorrow, remember?
We're havin' a party
at the house?
Birthday.
It's my birthday.
No, no, no,
it'll be fine, Brenda.
You guys can
start the party,
and then I'll just join
as soon as this is over.
And then, we can all celebrate
together, you know?
Right.
That was something
that had been debated for weeks.
If Seattle would've said, "Hey,
Cortez Kennedy, 27 other teams,
"he's out there
for a trade."
What kind of offers would
they have gotten in return?
Bye, Kurt.
Bye, Z-Man.
Bye, Brenda.
Drive safe.
You sure you're good
driving me back?
Ain't
a problem.
You sure
that's a good idea?
What?
Single mom, two kids.
That's no joke.
I would know.
Is that really
the life you want?
Yay.
Who wants cake?
- I do.
- Yes!
- Got a fork? Okay, good.
- He's got a fork.
Okay, here you
go, honey.
Another piece of cake
comin' right up for you.
Great.
Uh-huh.
Happy birthday,
Zack.
Want cake?
Come on, well,
you're just in time for the cake.
- Yeah.
- You made it just in time.
I'm sorry.
Mama,
I can't wait to eat mine.
How's it taste?
- Good.
- I bet real sugary, huh?
How do you feel?
Older?
I was wondering
where you were.
Hey.
You wanna
talk to me?
I'm just wondering why
God would give me a dream
that's probably never
gonna come true.
'Cause I just feel like
that's cruel, you know?
Babe, you know what, I just want...
I just want my shot.
I... I just...
I want one chance,
so I can prove...
Prove what?
Prove that I'm good
enough, that's what.
I don't think a football
game is ever gonna do that.
It doesn't have
to define you.
If this is
your dream,
you have to go
fight for it.
So, how do you think the Bears
are gonna do this year, son?
Well, they just
fired Ditka,
so things are probably gonna
get worse before they...
- Did they call?
- Hmm?
Are you kidding me?
Did somebody from the
Bears call here today?
No, the Bears didn't call,
buddy, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No.
The Packers called.
- They wanna sign you.
- Come on.
- No, they do.
- Come on!
Oh, wow.
Congratulations.
A $5,000 signing bonus, baby!
Pretty great, huh?
Thank you so much.
It is green.
The Packers. Green Bay. Get it?
Yeah, we get it.
Packers for life.
- That's why she's green.
- Yeah, we get it, man.
Hey.
I don't wanna
leave you.
- I don't wanna leave you.
- Oh.
You ever feel like your whole
life was just leadin' up to one moment?
Then go make
the most of it.
Hey.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah.
I'm happy for you,
but I know that this
is gonna change things.
Your life is gonna
get busier, and...
Hey, Brenda, Brenda,
Brenda, it's okay.
We'll figure it out.
Yeah. We'll figure it out.
- I miss you already.
- Me, too.
- I'll call you when I get...
- You drive safe.
I will. I'll call you
when I get there.
- Packers for life!
- You better.
Wow.
Step and throw.
Move! Move!
Yeah, good ball.
Nice ball.
Thataway, Brett.
Thataway to zip it
in there.
Hey, Pop.
Pop Warner.
Let's see
what you got.
Did you hear what I said?
You're in.
Uh, yeah, Coach,
I just got here.
I don't know
the playbook yet.
- You don't wanna go in?
- I do wanna go in.
I just don't wanna
blow it out there.
- Give me till tomorrow, I'll know it.
- Detner, you're in.
Hey, you wanted
to see me, Coach?
Yeah, thanks for
comin' in, Warner.
Hey...
wish you well.
Wait, what?
We're letting you go.
No, no, you're letting me go?
No. I just got here.
You haven't even
seen me play yet.
Well, we tried.
No, I'm sorry, sir,
but I'm not gonna leave.
Not yet.
You can't cut me.
- You cut yourself, okay?
- Coach, please.
I have been working
for this my entire life.
Stop it. Come on.
Don't do that.
If it were true, you would've
been ready to go on the field.
You're not.
I'm gonna need
that playbook.
I just don't know
what to do, Brenda.
I've called every team in the
NFL, and no one's interested.
I wanna go on, I do.
But, I mean,
look at me.
I'm unemployed.
I'm homeless.
Oh. Right,
I forgot to tell you that
Hudnutt's movin' to Des Moines.
Then move in.
What?
With us.
My family.
With nursing school starting,
I could use a live-in nanny.
We're both gonna
be struggling, so...
Why don't we
struggle together?
Yeah, together.
What is your mom
gonna think?
It's your mom
I'm worried about.
That woman
hates me.
I mean, she...
I mean...
Oh, come on, man.
Just throw the dang ball.
Football.
That's right, Z-Man.
You like it?
You play.
Yeah, I'd really like to,
bud, but they didn't pick me.
I pick you.
I pick you too, bud.
$27.12.
Yeah.
Uh, you take
food stamps?
Mmm-hmm. Anything else for ya?
No. That's...
Uh, actually, yeah.
Um, can I get, uh...
Can I get one of
your applications?
Yeah.
Hey, Mama.
- I got a job today.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Stockin' shelves at the Hy-Vee.
Graveyard shift.
It's just for
a little while.
Until next season's tryouts.
You know
what they say.
"Sometimes you gotta do
what you gotta do,
"until you can do what
you want to do," you know?
Don't give up.
It's Kurt Warner.
Go Panthers.
- I gotta get to class.
- Hey.
Pray for me.
We're learning how to insert an IV.
I'll be home by 7:00.
Date night?
No, my shift starts
at 6:30.
Oh. Sorry.
Okay.
Think you'd be
that guy?
Yeah, I do.
What are you doin' here?
Get it done.
Yeah, 'cause
it's that easy.
Oh, nice hands.
Oh.
Go long.
Set! Hut!
Ow.
Come on, man.
Yeah, yeah,
I got it.
Kurt Warner.
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Jim Foster. It is my absolute
pleasure to meet you.
And you are?
- Brenda.
- Pleasure to meet you.
Can I sit?
Look, elephant in the room,
I am sorry
about the draft...
and the Packers.
But you got it all, kid.
The whole package.
The world just needs
more time to see it.
Well, thank you.
See, this guy gets it.
Yes, I get it.
And what if I told you,
starting tomorrow,
you have a job playing the game you love?
- What are you, a scout or something?
- No.
I'm the proud owner and head
coach of the Iowa Barnstormers.
The newest members of
the Arena Football League.
Right. You're the guy who came
up with this whole arena concept.
Last year,
I was commissioner of the league.
This year, I came home to
Iowa to start my own team
and I wanna
build it around you.
So, it's arena football?
No, it is not football, babe.
It's like a circus.
Yes, that's right. You get it.
People love the circus.
- I like the circus.
- Hey, hey.
I am gonna play football,
and I'm gonna play it in the NFL.
And I can't do that if I'm playing
arena football in the spring.
This is for guys that are,
you know, circling the drain.
I'll tell you what,
just think about it.
Get him to
think about it.
Here's my card. Oops.
Dropped a little
money there.
Brenda, it's all the way
in Des Moines.
And it's not football.
Hell, I don't know!
You're the agent.
What happened
to Tampa Bay?
San Diego?
There were other offers.
Can't you just
make some calls?
Kurt,
that was last year.
Look, the teams
have moved on.
I just don't see
a path forward here.
I'm sorry.
I gotta grab this.
- Take care of yourself.
- No, no...
- Hey, Kurt, can I borrow you a second?
- Yeah.
Yeah,
one minute.
All right, Z-Man.
We bought
our dream home, son.
Down in Arkansas.
It's closer to Jenny's family.
And, uh,
oh, it's great.
It's a brand-new ranch home.
Two-car garage.
And it's right down the
road from the White River.
And there's some good fishin' in
there, buddy...
So...
Well, we'll be
leavin' soon.
And, um,
the thing is...
We need to find
a new place to live.
Well, I'm glad to
hear you say "we."
Look, uh, Jenny Jo would
want me to ask you this.
I mean, a good Christian
family, after all, and, uh...
- Do you love her?
- Yes, sir.
I do.
I knew you did.
Do you mind me asking
what's holding you up?
That's okay.
No, no, no.
That's fine. Um...
I guess I just felt like I
needed to prove myself first.
Show her I was capable of
doing what I set out to do.
Be worthy of her.
Well, hell, Kurt.
Accomplishing one thing
or the other
is not what's gonna
make you worthy of her.
Life is not about
what you can achieve,
it's about what
you can become.
It's a journey, son.
It's not an event.
Just promise me this.
You won't take off
when things get hard.
And they will get hard.
Yes, sir.
Take care of
these kids for me.
Well, that's a guarantee.
I know.
A major blizzard caused
accidents across the Midwest, Monday,
and the dangerous
blast of arctic air
is expected to spread across
the region overnight.
Record-breaking low temperatures
will make the next few days
the coldest the region has
seen in at least 25 years.
Hey. How's the fever?
The same.
What happened to the heat?
Did we pay the bill?
I don't know, Kurt. You told me not
to put it in the mail, remember?
Damn it.
Maybe we should just go to my
mom's till the storm passes.
Hey.
I decided, I'm droppin' out of
school, gettin' a job.
What? No. No, no, no. No way.
Kurt, it's not working.
Nothing here is working.
Stop. Stop it.
Listen, if this is what you really
wanna do, I'm not gonna let you quit.
Because that's what
you did for me,
and that's what we do
for each other.
We are not quitting.
Do you understand?
Okay?
- Yeah.
It's bad out here.
Maybe we should
head back home.
- Oh, Kurtis?
- Uh...
Baby, we just
ran outta gas.
Okay, all right, there's a...
There's a gas station
a couple miles back.
That was...
That was more than a couple of miles.
It's okay, it's okay,
it's okay.
I can make it there.
No problem. No problem.
- Just grab the change outta the door.
- Yep.
And check the
glove compartment, too.
Yep. Here's some.
I got a couple
dollars in my wallet here.
- Here's another quarter.
- All right, here.
- Stay inside.
- Uh-huh.
- Stay warm. Keep the doors shut.
- Yeah, be fast.
Excuse me, hi.
Uh, $4.86 on pump three,
and do you have any gas cans?
- Uh, yeah, 5 bucks.
- Oh, no, no, no.
I... I don't need to buy one,
I just need to borrow one.
I'll bring it right back.
Please, please.
- All right.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Hey. Hey.
- Kurt...
I'm so sorry,
are you okay?
Let's get you
all warmed up.
Brenda,
I'm so sorry.
You all could have
died out there.
It's not
your fault, Kurt.
Yeah, it is
my fault.
I promised your father that I would
take care of you and the kids.
So that is exactly
what I'm gonna do.
Fifty yards long.
Eight-yard end zones.
Eight men each side.
This is not
a football field.
This is an arena.
For gladiators.
For true believers
and lovers of the game.
And right over here
is our sideline.
In our version of the game,
the sideline is a wall.
And it will pound you
and punish you.
Trust me.
Kurt Warner.
So, did hell freeze over or are you
just tired of waiting on the NFL?
Uh, bit of both, sir.
Forget everything you think
you know about football.
No punts, no turning back.
It's all pressure.
It's football at
the speed of NASCAR.
We call it
"the 50-yard indoor war."
You think you can
handle that, Warner?
I think it's time I tried.
All right, Red.
Well, well, well,
look who's still circling the drain.
What's up, boy?
All right,
all right, all right.
Well, Kurt, if we gonna go down,
might as well
go down together.
Set!
Faster, faster.
Pull the trigger.
Come on, Warner.
Ooh, that'll wake you up
in the morning, boy.
- Get out of here.
- You gotta watch it.
Get outta here.
You gotta get rid
of the ball, Warner.
You look like you're
movin' in slow motion.
Set!
One, two, three, throw.
One, two, three, throw. Come on!
Pain feels good, don't it?
Pain feels good, baby!
Oh, you can't
touch me, boy.
You can't
Whatever.
Man, it's fast.
Yeah, you'll get
used to it.
Uh, if this is
where we practice,
where on earth
do we play?
Hey. Hey, Hud.
What is that?
Oh, that's
the Rodeo Arena.
Rare cattle, cuttin' horse
shows, pony shows.
Them pony shows
is fresh.
We this way.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome...
That's us right here, right now!
Come and take,
come and take!
The Iowa Barnstormers!
They call it
the Barn.
Let's go, 1-3!
The crazies are out
in force tonight in Des Moines.
Don't touch the dial, folks.
The mayhem starts right now.
Oh, my God!
Taylor fires to Hogan
and he is ragdolled over
the wall into his own bench.
And we got our first fight of the night!
That's a good end.
That was a good end.
A quick slant to Corn
Willis in the middle of the field.
And he goes in
for the touchdown.
God help me.
On one, ready!
And that will bring out
a new face.
Kurt Warner from the
University of Northern Iowa.
He had quite a reputation for being
a gunslinger with the Panthers.
Let's see if he's got any
of that cowboy still in him.
Oh, boy,
that moves fast.
- Snap it, snap it, snap it!
- Stewart in motion
and Warner won't get
the snap off in time.
Unbelievable.
Get him outta here!
Trips left. No.
Uh, trips right.
50 double,
post on one, right!
Warner definitely
out of rhythm right now.
- Set, hut!
- There's the snap. Drops back.
In trouble, takes off...
Buried by defensive end,
Travis Leigh.
Hey, Red, they got a
lemon law on quarterbacks?
What are you doing?
Warner, that way.
Not that way.
Ball there.
Set, hut!
Three steps, drop, throw.
Three step,
drop, and throw.
Late!
Set, hut!
Late.
What are you doin' in that extra beat?
Balancing your checkbook? Come on, man.
You don't have time enough to
drop back and settle like that.
It's faster than that.
You just gotta pick it up.
Push and throw.
He gettin' it, Coach.
He gettin' it.
Set!
Left 33, wing out.
Z-go. On one. Ready?
First in 10
for Jim Foster's 0-1 team.
There is growing concern
in Des Moines
in their old coach's
taste in quarterbacks.
One game in and the
seat is already red hot.
His line buys him
some time.
All right, all right.
There we go.
Kurt! You got
your completion!
- Come on! Let's go!
- Come on!
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
Let's go!
Iowa's ball
at the 25-yard line.
Get back!
Crowd is making noise
for the first time tonight.
And there's a little hope
sneaking into the building.
Stands tall in the pocket.
And it's Smallbone,
who holds on to the catch.
All right. Now we're
playin' football.
See Mike!
Warner under center...
- Set, hut!
- ...surveys the defense.
Drops to throw,
going long.
Touchdown!
Yeah, now we're talking.
Thank you.
And for the
first time this season,
there's actual excitement
in this arena.
- There he is.
- Come on, let's keep it going.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, here.
What is this?
That's a touchdown
bonus.
You pay me
per touchdown?
I also pay you to win.
Did you even read your contract?
Teach him
to read, man.
Wait, really, $100
every single touchdown?
Every touchdown.
Happy to pay it.
Oh, this is gonna be fun.
The Barnyard
comin' to life. It is loud.
Touchdown. Drop for Warner.
He lets it fly.
And he drops it in
perfectly over the receiver.
Touchdown!
Oh, my word.
What a play.
Welcome to Arena Football,
Mr. Warner.
Seven touchdowns.
Seven, baby.
It was epic.
Hey, you gettin' my salary checks, right?
I told 'em to send 'em
straight to you.
Yep,
I got them. Thanks.
Sounds party-ish
over there.
Yeah, well, you
know, right out of...
Kurt!
I wanna talk to him.
Hey! Z-Man! Hey, pal.
I miss you so much.
I can't
hear him, Mama.
It's loud.
Kurt, listen, I gotta get the kids down.
Are you coming home this weekend?
Zack's been asking.
Um, I'm sorry, hon, no, I can't.
We have practice.
But, hey, why don't you come
up on Saturday, and, uh...
You can... you can
bring the kids.
I have to study this weekend.
Look, I'm tired.
Going to bed. Love you.
I need my partner.
Come on.
- I'm comin'.
- Undefeated, baby.
I'm comin', I'm comin'.
Come on, now.
Come on, Stormers.
What a show Kurt
Warner's put on all season.
18 touchdown passes.
And he's rushed
for 12 more...
What a hidden gem
out of Northern Iowa.
Right. Z-cross, S flare.
On one, ready.
Tell you what,
you give Kurt Warner
time to throw a football,
he is a dangerous man.
Set, hut!
This was a strike,
to Hudnutt with a catch.
And a run down
the 20-yard line.
Come on, Coach!
What next?
Come on!
Okay.
Set, hut!
Warner,
quarterback draw.
And he's in!
Another Barnstormer touchdown!
That's my boy!
You all enjoy
the game tonight?
Yeah, that was great.
You were amazing out there.
Good. Got a long
drive home.
I'm sorry.
We need to get by through here.
We're here
to see Kurt.
You need a wristband, ma'am.
For the meet and greet.
Oh, no, no, no.
We're with Kurt.
Yeah, you
and everyone else.
No, we're
his family. Um...
Look, I've got our tickets right
here, and I just need to...
You still need
a wristband.
Zack?
Zack!
Sir, excuse me.
Zack? Zack?
Excuse me.
Oh, my God!
Brenda, I didn't even know
you guys were gonna be here.
I thought
you had to study.
Well, that's why it's
called a "surprise", Kurt.
Okay, then why
are you upset?
Because...
I couldn't get to you,
and it felt like everyone else could.
And then I lost Zack...
Because I didn't know you were
coming, but, hey, babe, we won.
We're going to
the semi-finals.
I know. It was just
supposed to be different.
Yo, Kurt, party at
our place tonight.
- Hey, Bren.
- Hud.
I don't have to
go to that.
We've got
a long drive home.
How's my baby girl?
Just fine.
How are you?
Just waiting on tonight.
Sunday night movie night.
Miss watching with you.
So, what does
"just fine" mean?
You know...
Just...
fine.
And how's Kurt?
Far away.
Hey.
Uh, no kids?
No kids.
Do you wanna go
grab some lunch?
Could we sit and talk
for a few minutes?
Yeah, sure.
Come on in.
What's on
your mind?
I have a question
and I'm just...
gonna say it
and get it out.
I want you to know
that I'm not angry.
I just need
an honest answer.
Uh, okay.
Do you see yourself
in my life, long-term?
I mean, watching
Zack grow up,
walking Jesse
down the aisle.
Standing by my side at my
parents' 50th anniversary.
Do you honestly
see yourself there?
Okay. 'Cause I've had
a lot of time to think...
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me answer your question.
Kurt, you already did.
I'm happy for you.
For everything that's
going on in your life.
But it's not working
for my life.
- Brenda, you...
- Can you please just let me finish?
I've been through this
before, you know that.
And I can't do it again.
So...
why don't we just
skip to that part,
and save ourself a
lot of time and tears?
So... So...
Help me understand this.
What, exactly?
We're just supposed
to end it now,
so we don't have
to end it later?
- Yes.
- Why?
Because you can't decide.
You won't...
Oh, oh, oh... Oh, no, no,
you don't get to pin that on me.
No, sorry.
You're the one who's afraid.
Yes, I'm afraid.
Yes, you're afraid. Of what?
Of me bailin' on you?
Of me hurtin' you?
Me being some version
of your ex?
I'm afraid that we are
gonna hurt each other.
That is the only way
that this ends.
You don't know that!
Kurt, I want you to chase your
dreams, just not with me.
Okay.
- What is that?
- That's my touchdown money.
Are you paying me
to break up?
I'm pretty sure you're the one
breaking up with me right now.
It was a discussion.
It was a discussion and now it's
a decision, and you know what?
I get it.
I get it. You're right, Brenda.
You're always right.
We should just
end it now,
and just be done
with it, yeah.
I gotta get to the game,
because apparently,
that's the only thing
I'm any good at.
Anyway, drive safe.
Tell the kids I said hi.
Left,
50 Pogo, wide cross.
Warner!
Left, 50
Pogo, wide cross. Come on, man.
Left, 50 Pogo,
wide cross. Ready?
C-44, C-44!
Set, hut!
That'll do it.
With time running out,
that touchdown will seal
the win for Coach Foster.
The Iowa Barnstormers are heading
to the Arena Bowl to face Tampa Bay.
Shouldn't you
be celebrating?
I mean,
what do you think this is? Come on.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
What?
That is not the face of somebody
that just made the Finals.
Where's Brenda?
We, uh...
We broke up.
Winning doesn't always
feel like winning, no?
It never has.
Why is that?
Guess it doesn't
mean anything
when you don't have
someone to share it with.
She should
be here, Kurt.
It's wrong
that she isn't.
I thought you
didn't like her.
No... No, I just...
I just saw too much
of myself in her.
I didn't want you to struggle
the way that I struggled.
But my story doesn't
have to be her story.
You love her.
You stuck with her.
With those kids.
You have grown up
to be a good man.
She makes you
happy, Kurt.
I've seen it.
She makes you better.
Hi, again.
Sports Center hippin' you to what's up.
Alongside Steve Levy,
I'm Stuart Scott.
Coming up, in addition
to the items already mentioned,
Mark will narrate this. I'm sure
he'll put it in proper perspective.
Raiders head coach
Jon Gruden says...
Hello?
Kurt.
Brenda, what's wrong?
Kurt,
oh, my God, my parents...
After the massive
amount of damage,
large trees are down
all over the area
and the street I'm looking at,
the entire block has been leveled
to the concrete foundations.
Category 4 tornado
that hit at about 7:45
last night...
Brenda!
Kurt!
Hey, hey.
I got you.
I'm right here,
okay?
How can this
be real?
I don't understand.
It's not fair.
I'm so
angry with you.
I'm so angry.
They're gone.
Really gone.
I'm just gonna
check on the kids.
No, no, hey,
I'll take care of that.
You stay.
I sure did
miss you, buddy.
God, help.
I need you.
Hey, hey...
Hey, Z-Man.
Sorry, I didn't mean to wake you up.
I just miss 'em.
I miss them.
Yeah, we all
miss 'em.
- Wait just a second.
- Okay.
Okay, look.
The way
I see it,
I'm gonna remember this moment
for the rest of my life,
so if you're not...
Hey, Brenda.
I'm gonna be here.
I'm gonna be
right here.
I love you.
I love you, too.
- See you in a couple days, okay?
- Okay.
Bye,
sweetheart.
Thanks for
taking them.
I just... I need
a couple days.
Hey. Whenever you're ready,
we'll see you at home.
Okay?
Hey, guys.
Mama missed you so much.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
Okay.
Come here.
All my life,
I've defined myself through sports.
What I could accomplish,
how many games I could win.
And I've always
come up empty.
It's never
been enough.
Like I was meant
for somethin' else.
Somethin' more.
What if it's this?
What if it's us?
Together?
Everything I could ever
want or need is right here.
It doesn't matter if I play football,
or if I don't play football,
or if I do play football,
where I play football.
None of that matters.
'Cause winning
isn't winning
if I don't have you
by my side.
I've made
my choice.
I love you.
And I want
what you have.
I want your faith, I want your
strength, I want it all. I need it.
I need it in my life.
It makes me a better man.
Yes.
You gotta wait till
I say the words first.
Well, then,
hurry up. God!
- Brenda Carney...
- Yes!
- You're not gonna let me finish?
- No!
Ladies and gentlemen,
on the first day
of the rest of their lives,
Mr. and Mrs. Kurt
and Brenda Warner.
Come on! Come on!
Hey, Warner.
We got Arena Bowl this weekend.
Arena Bowl. Are you all in?
Let's do it.
Wow.
This right here,
this is my "all in."
I love you.
Daddy, will you
dance with me?
Aw...
Yeah.
♪ It was no accident
♪ Me finding you, Daddy
♪ Someone had a hand in it ♪
It's okay.
After 4 months and
16 games, it has come down to this.
A barn dance in Des Moines.
And they are rockin' and rollin' here
at the Veterans Auditorium
in Des Moines.
The defending champions
Tampa Bay Storm
against the Iowa Barnstormers.
Hello, everyone.
Along with Kirk Herbstreit,
I am Todd Christensen.
Hey, Todd, Kirk.
Cleveland Stadium
has a Dawg Pound.
Veteran Memorial Stadium
has the Barnyard...
Let's keep this area
for the "different" people.
Whoo!
Hurry up, hurry up!
The outcome.
Hear the momentum switching to Iowa here
as they drive
for a go-ahead score...
Twenty-sixth completion by Kurt Warner,
that too is an Arena Bowl record.
Warner, the ball is tipped.
The keeper is out of the length of catch.
Yes!
Come on, come on!
Hurry up. Let's go.
If you don't
keep contain on this guy,
he's gonna hurt ya.
If they want a championship,
this is where they have to earn it.
Don't hold it.
- He cocks and motions left...
- Throw. Throw.
Pump fakes, is able to
buy some time. He gets rid of it.
And it appears... No!
A little pressure right
in the face of Kurt Warner
and who would've thought, that on the
one-yard line that they couldn't get it in?
And they're gonna
look back at that,
you can see the pressure
applied there...
It's okay,
we'll be fine.
The Tampa Bay
Storm are the champions.
- Thanks.
- There you go. Oh, my pleasure.
Thanks for coming out.
Sorry we didn't win.
Kurt?
Hey, Kurt?
Excuse us, Brenda.
There's a gentleman here to see you.
- Hey, do you want me to go?
- No, stay here, that's fine.
Heck of a game
for you, Kurt.
Well, thank you,
but it didn't help us win.
I hate to lose, sir.
I hate it for the team.
I'm David Gillis.
We've been trying
to reach you.
We want you to come
and try out for us.
Try out?
I've been putting off
his calls for a while.
Can you blame me?
I'm sorry,
who are you?
I'm with the Rams.
Dick, come on.
Dick, I mean...
I don't get it.
I like him.
- It's a hunch.
- It's arena football.
You think
that'll translate?
Character translates
anywhere, Mike.
GM sure likes
his price.
Our groundskeeper's gonna make
more than him this season.
John, this guy is old.
Slow as molasses.
And frankly, he's beneath the
standards of this franchise.
That's what people said
about me when I came here.
He got a howitzer
for a right arm, though.
There is no way this
guy makes the team.
No way.
I like him.
Split!
Through one.
All right, next group, let's go.
Set, hut!
Great way to sling it, Trent.
Good boy.
The Packers
called you up once.
Yes, sir.
A long time ago.
Ah. How long
did you last?
Not long enough.
Two days.
You lasted
two days.
Don't get too
comfortable.
All we're lookin' for,
gentlemen, is perfection.
Let's see how we did with
Trent Green on the C map.
One, two, three,
four, five.
Step and throw.
Very nice. Stop.
Now, Is, you know why he put
that ball right there, right?
That's to keep you
from gettin' hit.
That's to protect you. Very good.
Excellent ball placement.
Stop, stop. Torry, no.
You know that dig
is 15 in cut.
Not 14. Right? 15.
Don't mind
Coach Martz.
Let me know if you need anything.
I'm Isaac.
Yeah. Yeah, man,
I know who you are.
I'm Kurt.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, Mike.
Have you put in
1-3 yet?
You wanna waste everybody's time?
All right, second
group, let's go.
Pop Warner, that's
you, let's go.
All right, let's see
some happy feet.
Okay, let's watch
Kurt Warner.
How close to perfection
could we get this time?
Step, throw, stop.
It's a wrong read.
It's a wrong damn read!
You're ahead of 'em.
You gotta hit 'em
in stride, Kurt.
Yes, sir.
"Yes, sir," with a grin.
Why the grin?
I don't know, Coach.
I was just...
I was curious as to why everybody
here in the NFL moves so slow.
Gentlemen,
I believe arena boy just
called every one of you slow.
So, we gonna end on that.
And on this, which is for Warner,
when he learns
to throw a spiral.
Mr. Trent Green.
You can break 'em
down and take 'em out.
Good night, gentlemen.
Ride it out, rook.
It's all part of the plan.
Ready?
C-57! C-57!
Blue 80! Blue 80.
Give me that ball.
Give me the ball.
What are you thinking?
How do you drop that?
That ain't on
the QB, Coach.
That man is risking his
life for you every snap!
And you don't have the dignity
to hold on to the damn ball?
You hold on
to this ball.
Yes, sir. That's my mistake.
It won't happen again.
All right,
let's run it again.
We good.
I don't know, Brenda, I don't
think I'm gonna be here much longer.
How do you
know that?
The offensive coordinator hates me.
I can't prove myself.
He won't let me.
I'm not gettin' any snaps.
- Hates you?
- Yeah, no, he hates me.
I mean, this is Trent Green's
team, anyway.
They built it around him
and he's incredible.
Babe, hang in there.
Hey, Warner,
Coach wants to see you upstairs.
- I gotta go.
- I love you.
I love you, too.
- You wanted to see me, sir?
- Oh.
Yes.
How long for you in the
wilderness, son?
How long
out of college?
Right. Well, yeah, I mean, it's, uh...
it's been a few years.
Wow.
But, sir, that doesn't mean
that I don't know how...
Fourteen.
For me.
Fourteen years
outta coaching.
I burnt out.
I'm not embarrassed to say it.
Took a year off,
turned out to be a decade and a half.
And when I did
come back,
they said I was a retread,
has-been, too old.
Game had passed me
by, all that stuff.
All that same stuff
that they're gonna
say about you.
What they didn't know...
was all that experience
that I had in those years
made me who I am.
Made me ready
for this moment.
Gave me something
others didn't have.
And I see that
in you, Kurt.
Destiny.
It belongs
to the underdogs.
You wanna prove that?
Together?
There's somethin' special
about you, son.
And I'm really gonna enjoy
finding out what that is.
Welcome to the Rams.
Come on. Come on!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, Coach, thank you.
Thank you for trusting me.
I gotta tell my wife.
This is the best decision
you've ever made in your life.
I promise you.
I gotta go tell my wife.
Guys, I'm home.
Zack?
Zack, honey, no!
No, no, no!
Hey, baby, baby,
Brenda, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, come here.
Sit with me.
Sit down.
Why would you
let him do that?
He said
he was ready.
And I believed him.
Mom, I'm driving!
Yeah, you are, bud!
Come on, Charles!
Trent Green,
ninth-rated passer
with 81.8% quarterback
rating in 1998,
the real hope
for this offense.
We've been talking about him all
game and all through season long...
Hey, check it out.
That's my boy.
This might be the only
screen time he gets, though.
Boy, shut up.
...to number 18,
Tony Small, the rookie's...
- Whoa!
- We have a scorer.
Freddie Miller is a bad man.
Freddie Miller's a bad man.
Now, we got Trent Green down.
We've got Trent Green down
in the middle of the field.
This is not
the way I saw this.
And Green went
down hard and is not getting up.
And that looks bad.
...writhing in
pain, you do not wanna see this.
If you're the Rams,
or anybody, for that matter.
He was in a lot of
pain and you hate to see that
after a player gets you
by the knees from behind.
Son of a...
And Isaac Bruce is obviously
upset about it as well.
He should
have been penalized.
Kurt Warner, now warming up
on the sideline for the Rams.
Kurt Warner,
a capable back-up.
Oh, my God.
Certainly not where
Trent Green is.
To an exciting night
for us here at ESPN,
an exciting night
for the NFL.
So obviously,
lots of buzz coming out
this morning here
from Rams' camp
and the question today is
"Why not Kurt Warner?"
Why not Kurt
Warner? Really? You just said that?
Kurt Warner replaced
Trent Green as the starting quarterback.
This ain't the guy.
The Rams are gonna trade
for a quality starting quarterback.
They can't wait.
They've gotta do it right now.
If Dick
Vermeil stays with this guy,
he's gonna be a joke.
Their program is a joke.
The season's over.
Come in.
- Sit down.
- Thank you, Coach, I prefer to stand.
All right. Go ahead, then.
Tell me.
Tell you what?
Why a team
worth $800 million
with one of the most complex
offenses ever built, by me,
should put you
in the driver's seat.
Because you threw some touchdowns
on a little football arena?
Hmm?
You're too old
to be a rookie.
You're too green to be a
pro, you don't belong here.
Well, with all due respect,
sir, you're wrong.
And if you give me a chance,
I will prove that to you.
Make us a laughingstock
of the league?
Embarrass every member
of this team,
- every fan of the city?
- That's not true.
You don't have
what it takes.
That's what
I believe.
So, why in the world would
I give you this shot?
Because this is
my time, sir.
Because I know who I am,
and I know why I'm here.
Because I've earned it.
I've waited for it,
I've bled for it. And...
I'm finally ready for it.
I wasn't before.
God knows I wasn't,
but I am now.
And I will not
let you down.
You put the ball
in my hands,
and we will win.
That's all, Kurt.
- Hello?
- Hey, Coach.
He's ready.
People asked me
last night
how I felt in that
press conference.
It hurts. I get emotional.
But that's what this
business is all about.
We will rally around
Kurt Warner.
And we will play
good football.
CBS is proud to present
the National Football League.
Today, we come to you
from St. Louis, Missouri,
Gateway to the West.
The Trans World Dome
where the Ravens
and St. Louis Rams
are set
to go at it.
It's kick-off 1999.
Opening Day in
the National Football League.
I do like
a man in uniform.
Jeez...
What are you...
How did you get in here?
I, uh...
I needed you to hear this before
you went out on that field.
I was talking with our son,
and I helped him write it.
"To my daddy, Kurt.
"You fix all my radios.
"You walk to the gas
station in the snow.
"You never give up
on me.
"You never give up.
"You play your football game.
I drive my truck.
"Love, Zack."
That little boy
has defied all odds.
Every time.
He's proven
everyone wrong.
And so will you.
You helped me
believe again.
That anything
can happen.
That maybe God does have
something amazing in store for us.
Maybe that
moment's now.
Are you nervous?
Yeah, I'm terrified.
Well, you go out there,
and you show the world
what I've known all along.
Sell-out crowd.
Over 66,000 expected here
at the TWA Dome.
This is the
opportunity of a lifetime
for this young man.
A lot of pressure on
the shoulders of Number 13.
If he doesn't
perform well today,
the Cinderella story
could be over
before it even gets started.
The 1999 season underway...
It is on the end-zone...
Ready for this, son?
Yes, sir.
And the Rams with
their new quarterback, Kurt Warner,
replaced Trent Green
as the starting quarterback.
Good, good.
Take a look at the Ravens'
defensive lead, Ray Lewis is the All-Pro...
All mine now, rook.
All mine.
All right, boys.
Launch left, 36 alpha.
On one. Ready!
Z-4-2!
Easy. I'm here, rook.
Hey, I'm here.
You get nothing.
This is my house.
My house!
Now,
we're ready to get goin'.
First down and 10
for the Rams
- from the 42 yard line.
- Blue 80! Hut!
Let's go!
Faulk taken down
at the 40.
Ray Lewis got there...
Let's go, let's go!
All right,
I'm ready.
I see you.
I see you, rook.
Blue 80.
Blue 80, hut!
And Warner ripped down
by, guess who? Ray Lewis.
It didn't take much of a guess for
those people who know Ray Lewis...
This is just another game
of "Kill Kurt." Let's go.
Let's go! Let's go!
They talked about
blitzing this young quarterback early.
Ray Lewis coming in
untouched.
The Rams need to give
Kurt Warner some time today
- for him to be able...
- Ten for two!
- ...those weapons down field.
- Black nine!
Black nine, hut!
Warner
steps up in the pocket.
Caught! Isaac Bruce.
Yes!
At the front
and you love to see that...
Hey! Yeah!
I taught him
that, now.
One-eighty!
One-eighty, hut!
Warner...
Let's go, huddle.
Hey, let's go, huddle.
Let's huddle.
Let's huddle right now.
Mike, what have
we got?
Right slot, fake 28,
power double seam.
- On one. Ready?
- Four-twenty-one. Ready?
Come on! Let's go, guys.
Let's go.
And Kurt Warner, so far,
very nice job, stayin' within himself...
52's the Mike.
52!
Green, 60, hut!
Warner.
Intercepted by Ray Lewis.
And he's gotta beat the
quarterback down the sideline.
Cuts it in.
Lewis still running.
Ray Lewis all the way
down inside the 35.
Warner finally
makes a mistake.
All day long, rook.
Eatin' you for lunch
all day long.
Shake that off.
You got this.
Hey, Warner,
Coach Martz wants to talk to you.
Yeah, Coach?
Kurt, listen to me.
You know why I was so hard on you?
Why I put all that
pressure on you?
I had to know
that you were ready.
Had to be sure.
And guess what?
You are.
I never would've
put you on that field
if I didn't fully believe
you were a champion.
Now, you get back out there
and you get this job done.
Let's go.
Let's get after it.
Yes, sir.
And, Coach?
Thank you.
And the
Rams are in business.
A 34-yard return.
Huddle.
Look at me.
You can do this.
I know you can.
Yeah. We got your back,
no matter what happens. Let's go to work.
Let's go to work.
All right.
That last one was on me.
But we got this.
Let's get to work.
Right doubles, grip, 50 sail.
On one, ready!
C-4 Rams!
You got this.
And this young
man, Kurt Warner,
he played in the
Arena League in Iowa.
Green, 60, hut!
That's it!
Let's give 'em a confidence play.
What do you say?
- Get him settled in.
- All right. Let's throw this at him.
Black, nine, hut!
Throws to 10...
And it's Isaac Bruce.
Here's the back. Right there, Kurt.
Good call,
good call!
Warner, under
pressure, dances out of the pocket,
and...
That's my boy!
Look at that
composure from Kurt Warner.
- Come on, Kurt!
- He's hot.
Watch it, watch it, watch it,
watch it, watch it, watch it.
Wide 20.
Wide 20, hut!
Warner.
Corner of the end zone!
Roland Williams!
Touchdown!
Yes!
And Kurt Warner six
of ten 74 yards,
throws his first
NFL touchdown.
See that?
I taught him that.
Come on, 1-3, show me some...
Have some faith.
...their own 30-yard line.
Play-action,
Warner sets up tee...
Fires at the sidelines,
Isaac Bruce makes the catch...
Oh, yeah!
Come on,
come on, come on.
Three, hut!
Look at Ray
Lewis chasing his tail.
Switch it! No.
Abort, abort, abort!
Oh, you're gonna love this.
Blue, 20, hut!
Shovel pass.
Hakim.
Dodged.
When was the last time you saw shovel
pass to a wide receiver like that?
This kid can play!
Three-fifty!
Three-fifty, hut!
Warner again,
in the end zone...
Touchdown!
Well, Bruce!
Twenty yards.
What a show!
I have never been so
happy to have been proven so wrong.
I mean, you're watching
a star being born.
This is a day
that we will not forget.
Ravens falling
apart offensively right now.
- Wow.
- Mitchell.
Come on. Pump fake. All right.
Intercepted!
Huge. Running down the clock,
there's only four and a half
minutes left in this game.
- Four more minutes, baby.
- I don't want this game to end, gentlemen.
Hey, left, cross, split,
50-F, follow on one, ready!
Kurt Warner.
And he throws.
Marshall Faulk
out of the back field.
And there he goes.
Look at this.
Making people miss
inside the 21-yard line.
We got 'em
on the ropes!
We're gonna punch
this in, right now.
Left, close,
red, X, laser.
On one, ready.
And Kurt
Warner, he's confident.
Because he certainly
has something to prove.
Blue 80, hut!
Perfect.
Great catch!
Touchdown! The rookie!
Yeah!
And what a job
by that young man there.
Kurt Warner is like
Magic Johnson today.
Look at all the assists.
You got it done.
He's partying right now.
That's because the Rams gave complete
control of this football game...
Warner! Warner! Warner!
Dick Vermeil.
The old coach has to smile after this
one because they're happy in St. Louis.
And that should do it.
One more kneel-down by the Rams.
And the first win
is in the books.
My gosh.
Blue, 80, hut!
Thank you.
Look at him!
That's what I'm talkin' 'bout,
that's my guy!
We did it!
We did it.
Man, you keep that game ball.
You earned it.
I will.
Kurt!
Kurt! Kurt!
Hey, good game, bro.
Hey, that means a heck
of a lot comin' from you.
- No problem.
- It really does.
Brenda!
Great game, boys.
Well done.
It was a beautiful thing to watch.
- Thank you for believing in me, Coach.
- Well done.
Thank you.
Brenda!
Hey! Baby. Hey.
Hey, I don't know
where we go from here,
I don't know what comes next.
But this?
We did this.
We did this together.
I love you.
I love you, too.
We did it!
One-eighty!
Kurt Warner has brought hope
back to St. Louis.
The first quarterback
in the history of the NFL
to throw three touchdown passes
in each of his first three starts.
Here they come again.
Forget Ringling Brothers.
The Rams are the
greatest show on Earth.
Kurt Warner,
out of the Arena League
and as a back-up when the season
began, became the league's MVP.
A phenomenal
and unbelievable story.
Just
remember, this guy here,
he was bagging groceries
at the Hy-Vee five years ago.
So, he goes from
the Hy-Vee to the MVP.
The best human-interest story
in sports in years.
All aboard St.
Louis, this train is now...
You couldn't ask
for a better script.
Let's go win this
thing right now.
Let's win it right now. Come on!
The MVP
of the league, Kurt Warner,
comes into a situation
that every kid dreams of, Al.
Two minutes to go in the Super
Bowl, your team is tied.
I can't tell you how many
times I relived this as a kid.
Going deep downfield,
adjusting for it
is Isaac Bruce.
And Isaac Bruce threads
his way for a touchdown!
Seventy-three yards.
You couldn't have written a better
script for the MVP of the league.
He throws a beautiful pass
in the face of pressure.
And the Rams have won
the Super Bowl.
Go on, the game is over.
The game is over.
Kurt Warner.
First things first.
Five years ago,
you were stocking
supermarket shelves in Iowa.
Now, you're
a Super Bowl champion,
an NFL MVP,
a Super Bowl MVP.
What message does it
send to people?
I thank all the players,
all the coaches,
my family, everybody,
for believin' in me
and I gotta give
the praise and glory
to my Lord and savior
up above.
Now we're world champions,
how about that, Rams?
Zachary.
Brenda.
Kurt Warner
has a little boy.
It's not a complete circle,
because this is open.
- So it's a big hook.
- Yeah.
It starts here.
And then it comes around
so that is a heart.
Heart.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull