MAN: Hey, Jed.
♪ I fell in love with a woman
♪ She don't know right from wrong
♪ She's got me so confused
♪ She'll have made me leave my happy home
♪ I bought her some great long hair
♪ And I bought her some fancy clothes
♪ She woke me up this morning
♪ Said that I got to put your clothes outdoors
♪ I fell in love with this woman
♪ She don't know right from wrong
♪ She got me so confused
♪ She made me leave my happy home
♪ I come home every evening
♪ Two or three men around
♪ She said, "Daddy, them is my French cousins"
♪ "And don't you be no clown" All right
♪ I don't believe she know right from wrong
♪ She's got me so confused
♪ She made me leave my happy home
♪ All right
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
Hey, Jed.
Hey, Emily. Hey, J.D.
Bonnie?
Bonnie.
Look at all this crap.
Hi, Jed. Hi, honey. Do you know what time it is?
It's 7:15. They paying you overtime?
Should be resting up this time of month. Remember that cycle we're on.
Maybe we should give it a rest.
Well, I tell you, I'm doing my part. You just gotta do your part.
We're on a cycle now, honey,
we both agreed to what we gotta do to get what we wanted, right?
I know, Jed. It's just that I'm...
Tired? Worn out? Planning another headache.
'Cause I get them too, hon, you know.
You don't plan headaches!
You get them because you're sick and tired or someone gives them to you!
All right, now, listen, I didn't mean, you know, plan, like, to plan.
You ready for dinner?
Thought you'd never ask.
Hang on, I'll have it ready in a few minutes.
(SIGHS)
There's no beer in the refrigerator, honey.
(THUNDER RUMBLING) Yes, there is.
It's going to rain tonight.
Here's your beer.
What's the matter with you?
Nothing.
It's just that you're always telling me what to do.
Yeah? Well, then stop screwing up.
We're trying to put some life into this house besides these damn plants, you know?
(SIGHS)
Plant one, all right?
Please.
Mmm. Good.
Oh. That was the best.
What?
That was stupendous. That was just great.
I'm gonna do the dishes.
You will? Yup! Here.
All right. All right.
(EXCLAIMS) Shit!
Honey!
(HUMMING)
I got some fine wine here, honey, let's have us a good time.
Oh? We going out tonight?
I am. Just to the pharmacy, I need some more pills.
Some pills?
Well, I'll go out and get the pills, honey, it's pouring outside.
I don't want you to catch another cold.
That'll throw us off our cycle again.
I said I would get the pills.
(DOOR OPENING)
Take a raincoat.
Jeez! It's storming out here!
Hold on a second. Hang on, hang on, hang on. My goodness.
Jesus! Can you believe this!
(EXCLAIMS) These late summer showers.
(SHUDDERING) Showers? You must be kidding.
I'll tell you something, you better get home to them five kids.
That's what you gotta do.
You gotta come out and see them. I tell you, you got to come out to see them.
Are you serious? Yeah!
All right. Drive carefully.
Bonnie!
Bonnie Jackson, what are you doing out here?
C. Ray, I didn't know if you'd be here. I need a refill.
All right, come in, quickly!
I'm glad I caught you!
My goodness gracious, I ain't seen it like this here in years.
(MAN CHATTERING ON TV)
ANCHOR ON TV: On tonight's Close-up segment,
Chrissy Lee begins the first of a five-part series,
on an issue that seems to be on everyone's mind these days.
Now, this abortion thing is really starting to heat up, isn't it, Chrissy?
CHRISSY ON TV: It certainly is, Bill.
Today in Washington, the Supreme Court issued a ruling,
called Webster v. Reproductive Health Services,
which allows states new latitude to restrict abortion.
While not overturning the landmark decision which legalized abortion in 1973,
the court's decision set off a chaotic scramble to interpret the ruling
and to predict where and when new test cases might emerge.
Experts are divided on the effect the Webster ruling might have
on the status of abortion in this state and across the nation.
LAUREN: "Furthermore, we will be compelled to take legal action
"if we don't get a response from you in 15 days."
Blah, blah, blah. You know how to end it.
Got it.
LAUREN: You know what? No, make it seven days, it sounds scarier.
(LAUGHS) Yes, it does, Ms. McKinley.
So, we'll take care of everything else when I get back from Georgia.
God, can you believe it? Ten-year reunion. Ten years.
Hi!
(SQUEALING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hi!
I can't believe you're here!
Look at you, you're so skinny.
You look great!
(LAUGHS)
Oh, I missed you so much.
I'm sorry about you and David.
No, you're sorry about me and Chad.
David was last Christmas.
But my career is doing great!
I just made partner in a very important New York City firm.
I have an obscene expense account. I live in Manhattan like a rich tourist.
But it's not important what I'm doing.
And that's important to you.
Yeah, because...
You've always been such a great listener. Tell me about you.
I like hearing about your life.
We sure are different.
And yet.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
♪ We're cousins identical cousins
♪ Da da-da
♪ We walk alike we talk alike ♪
How does it go after that?
So tell me what's going on.
(DOOR OPENING)
Jed, look who's here!
Hi, Lauren.
Hi, Jed!
Where's dinner? Is it ready?
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Well, you know, Carla, you were my favorite student.
Oh, you're just saying that.
It's been so long since I've seen you.
God, you just look great!
Hi, how are you? Hi.
Nice to see you.
Hi, Bonnie. So good to see you.
I'm afraid she's getting wired.
She's just having a good time.
I guess.
Well, we're both nervous, you know, we've been working so hard to have a baby.
I know.
You still live in Union? Yeah, sure do.
And if we had a child, things would be different, I'm sure about that.
Be patient, things are going to change.
Hope so.
♪ Your cheatin' heart
♪ Will make you weep
♪ You'll cry and cry
♪ And try to sleep
♪ But sleep won't come
Andy!
♪ The whole night through
♪ Your cheatin' heart
♪ Will tell on you
Hey! Hey!
LAUREN: This place sure holds some memories.
Sissy? Sissy Cunningham!
Lauren! Oh, you look so great!
I don't believe it. New York must agree with you.
I know that you're a hotshot lawyer.
You must meet my husband, he's with the DA.
This is Leonard. This is Lauren McKinley.
Lauren McKinley, how do you do? Hi.
Bonnie Jackson! How are you? Hi.
This is my husband, Leonard.
Hi. Hi. This is my husband, Jed.
Yeah, Jed and I know each other.
Jed, it's so nice to meet you.
JED: The pleasure is mine. My, what a beautiful dress.
Oh, thank you!
Isn't that Carter Evans?
Yes, I believe it is.
You know, he's our DA now. The youngest Georgia has ever had.
The guy breaking laws is now making them.
Didn't you two have an affair?
Mmm. Just one night. He was my first one.
(GASPS) That was your first time!
It was my birthday.
Oh, that's funny. I did it with him when I was 16.
It was my birthday, too.
Must be his little birthday present to us all.
(CHUCKLES)
Must be.
Carter! Carter Evans.
Lauren McKinley!
Whoa! Hold on, there. Hold on. Jed.
Not with the fertility medicine you're taking now.
You know what the doctor said about drinking alcohol now.
Jed, I'm having a good time.
No! (GROANING) Oh!
Sorry! Honey, are you bleeding?
Oh, my God! Bonnie!
I'm sorry. LAUREN: What happened?
Where are you going?
I'm going to go home. I'll see you back at the house.
Let me see. Let me see that.
It was an accident, hon. It was an accident.
I'll go take care of her right now.
Carter Evans.
♪ Well, it's so loud in here
♪ I can't hear myself think
(LAUGHING)
♪ And it's so damn hot
♪ Can't get another drink
Come on, Lauren, for $1,000 a week,
you, too, can be a slave of the people. Come on, what's it about?
You were always such an inspiration to me.
The last of the campus radicals.
(LAUGHS)
Yup.
I think it's 'cause of you that I went on to law school.
Really?
God, I always wanted to find a way to pay you back.
Well, my birthday present is getting a little harder and longer.
(LAUGHING)
You must be kidding, we just met!
No, uh, we met over 10 years ago.
You haven't changed.
No, neither have you. Come on, come on. Come on.
(GIGGLING)
Same bells.
Nothing has changed.
Nothing, nothing. You were 16 when we, uh...
Seventeen. Seventeen.
That's right, I was 18 when we visited this bell tower last.
(BELLS TOLLING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Sanctuary! Sanctuary.
Hey, Quasimodo.
What?
How's the marriage? How's the wife?
Well, she's my ex-wife now. Divorced three years.
What went wrong?
She didn't share my passion for public service.
The wife of an ambitious man.
With your own ambition.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, whoa!
It's great to be home again. Seventeen again.
It was a full moon that night, too, wasn't it?
I think I was in love with you then.
And now?
It's been a long time. It's like we just met.
Kind of.
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MOANING)
Oh!
(SIGHS)
(CAR DOOR CLOSING)
(DOOR OPENING)
(GIGGLING)
Good morning!
Good morning.
Oh, Bonnie, I feel so...
I had a great time last night.
I'm sorry, should I have called?
Are you okay?
Does your lip hurt?
No. No, I'm all right.
I just, um, don't feel well. I think I'm getting my period.
Or maybe you're pregnant.
You don't want to be pregnant?
Why not, Bon? You're not happy.
I'm just sorry to see you leave.
I'll be lonely. Can't you stay a few days?
Why don't you just come up to New York for a while.
Maybe you and Jed just need some time apart.
No. No, I couldn't do that, Lauren. I'd be lost without Jed.
That's bullshit.
You don't understand. When I married, I married for life.
I married for better or for worse, and it's getting better.
I mean...
It's hit rock bottom.
Oh, Bon.
And I don't know what to do. You know, and so, um...
It's like I'm panicking. Because I don't know what to do.
Well, we could look at this seriously,
or we could just go to the islands next month.
(LAUGHING)
You and me, we could check into a swanky hotel,
wear red dresses. Lie about our age.
(LAUGHS)
Drive the guys apeshit.
I'd like that. Yeah, I'd really like that.
I'm sorry I can't stay for a couple days. I got this stupid deposition.
That's good, thank you very much.
But now I want to hear what you all be thinking,
because, after all, my candidacy will be your candidacy.
Man has a point. That's right!
One thing that I would hope for would be
a right attitude towards new construction projects.
Jed Jackson, I'll tell you right now that what this community needs
is more responsible and civic-minded builders like yourself,
who will continue to provide good homes for our families,
schools for our children.
ALL: Yes, yeah.
Carter. You are right on the money.
Family orientation runs deep here, and voters will be looking for that.
And how!
Particularly from a good-looking single fellow like yourself,
who has a better chance.
Look at the Kennedys.
(CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
I couldn't leave without saying goodbye.
Lauren! So soon. Yeah.
Gentlemen! Whoa!
First photo with your first lady, Carter.
Is that so?
Well, let's make the best of it.
PHOTOGRAPHER: Great, nice, nice.
(DOOR CLOSING)
Bonnie?
You okay, honey?
I'm fine, go back to bed.
(CLEARS THROAT) All right.
(GROANING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(COUGHING)
(TOILET FLUSHING)
Look, Ms. Jackson, you're on fertility pills,
so I'm going to have to take you off the Prozac,
the antidepressant and the sleeping medication.
But I don't sleep.
Look, Bonnie, if you're trying to get pregnant, we must stop all this.
Is there something else you want to tell me?
No, no, it's just that
everywhere I see these women protesting about abortion,
and I saw something on TV about the Supreme Court.
Abortion is still legal isn't it?
It's up to the states now. It's still legal here,
but I'm sure that Louisiana and Alabama and here in Georgia
are going to restrict abortion.
It's the climate of our times.
Why do you ask? You aren't pregnant, are you?
No, of course not.
(TEARING OFF PAPER)
I'm going to give you a non-narcotic medication that will help you sleep.
Don't take more than two a night.
Oh, and, Bonnie,
can you give me some urine, just to make sure you aren't?
I'm going to leave this here.
Yeah, mmm-hmm.
Customer profile, current medication.
I guess you know everything about me, C. Ray.
Doc already told you that these are going to make you kind of sluggish, right?
He took me off Prozac and all those other tranquilizers.
But those also are a little bit, well, you know, right?
Depends upon how many you take.
Just remember, no alcohol and...
And no operating heavy farm equipment. I know. I heard it before.
How much do I owe you?
$14.
To the penny.
Uh, just two a night.
I promise.
I gather everything at home is going okay?
Yes, thank you.
(WHISPERING) Hey, you awake?
Where have you been?
Just been out with the boys, just had a couple of beers.
(SIGHS)
Jed.
Come on, damn it! What's the matter, honey?
Nothing, Jed, I just want to go back to sleep, it's late.
Jed, come on!
(SHOUTING) Come on, what do you want!
You don't care what I want!
You just want me to be here like a thing, adoring you, making babies.
What babies, huh? What babies? Do you see any babies around here, honey? 'Cause I don't!
You can't even give me one!
You think having a baby is going to make everything good between us?
Yeah, yeah, maybe I do.
You know what, you have been all screwed up since that reunion.
No! I want to change! I want us to change!
You want to change, honey? Okay. Well, we'll change.
We'll go to New York City
and you can become a corporate lawyer like your friend Lauren!
Nothing is going change, honey. You're dreaming, you know that?
Look around here! This here is your life!
Let go of me!
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST)
Don't you walk away from me!
Honey! Honey, come back here, I'm talking to you.
Don't you walk away from me! I am sick of all of this shit!
Jed, stop! Stop talking!
What about me? Bullshit! Bullshit!
Don't tear my plants up! Here's your plants!
Here's your fucking plants!
Stop it!
What about me, Bonnie! What about me!
Stop! Stop it! Bullshit, Bonnie! Bullshit!
Stop it! I'm sick of these fucking plants!
I want a son! Let go!
(GRUNTS) Jed, don't, don't! Stop!
(CLOTHES TEARING) Stop it!
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
No!
Stop it! Stop it!
You son of a bitch, I hate you!
You screwed up my life!
(SHRIEKING) Go to hell! I hate you!
(CRYING)
I hate you!
I hate you! Go to hell! I hate you!
You and your plants! I'm through with it.
Go home to mama! Go on!
I hate you!
Go to hell! I hate you!
(SOBBING)
(CAR DRIVING AWAY)
♪ There's a hole in my heart
♪ From loving you
♪ And all the dreams I had inside
♪ Have fallen through
♪ I'm all alone
♪ That this love
♪ Is over for you and me
♪ I can't believe that it's true
♪ There's a hole in my heart from loving you ♪
It was my fault. I will never do that again.
'Cause a man should not hit a woman, especially not his wife.
I'll never do it again, honey, as long as I live.
Bonnie?
Bonnie? Bonnie!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Bonnie!
What have you done, honey?
Bonnie, what have you done?
Bonnie? Honey?
It's gonna be all right, honey.
It's gonna be all right, hon.
Hold on, honey. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
We'll get in the car. Hold on now.
Hold on tight. Everything is gonna be all right. Here you go.
Here, here you go. I'll get you there in time, honey. Don't you worry.
Okay, honey, it's gonna be all right.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
Shit!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Son of a bitch!
(CAR HORN HONKING)
(SIREN WAILING)
All right, here we go, honey. We're almost there.
Hold on now, honey.
It's gonna be all right, all right? It's gonna be okay. Help!
Jed, what happened?
We had a fight and she took some pills.
Stretcher!
Come on, here we go. Here we go, honey.
It's gonna be all right. I'm right here with you.
Right here with you, honey.
NURSE: Watch your back, now, come on.
I'm sorry. Stay here. What happened?
She took these... She took all of these pills.
I don't know... Oh, my God! Dr. Young!
Overdose! I didn't mean to...
Get the stomach pump ready. Wait here.
I hit her and I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean to hit her. It's the first time!
Watch your turn. Come on, let's go.
She's losing blood.
Let's hurry up with the suction.
NURSE: Incubate.
Airways cleared, pressure's down.
Bolus 500 CCs normal saline.
Stomach pump's ready.
NURSE: Losing vital signs.
Suction.
NURSE 1: Should I page Dr. Block?
NURSE 2: Yeah, yeah, yeah!
She's not responding.
NURSE: Doctor, look.
Oh, my God.
(SNIFFLING)
(CRYING) Please, God. Let her be all right.
Punish me. But don't take her.
Don't take Bonnie.
(DR. YOUNG CLEARING THROAT)
Doctor. Doctor.
Bonnie Jackson.
Mr. Jackson? Yeah.
She's gonna be all right.
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
Oh, God! Merciful God.
I'm so sorry, Jed, we weren't able to save the baby.
What baby?
Okay, it was a boy.
I mean the fetus was about three and a half months.
It's what you wanted to know, wasn't it?
And...
What?
Never mind.
(INTERCOM BUZZING)
SECRETARY: Ms. McKinley? Ms. McKinley?
I said no calls.
I think you want to take this one.
It's from Newnan, Georgia. Bonnie?
Hello?
BONNIE: Lauren? This whole thing was a mistake.
A mistake?
I don't know, I guess I just got kind of confused.
Confused about what? What do you mean, Bonnie?
Yeah, hey, Lauren, this is Jed.
Yeah, well the fact is that those damn doctors
didn't know what the hell they were giving her.
Really? Yeah.
Do you think we got a lawsuit? I don't know, Jed, maybe.
Well, you know.
It's all right, everything is okay. She just got confused.
Everything's going to be okay. Can I speak to her?
Uh-huh.
Say goodbye to your friend Lauren.
Take care of yourself, honey.
Bye-bye, Lauren. Should I come down?
Yeah, I'd love to see you.
Bonnie...
Lauren? Yeah?
Jed. No, it's just not going to work out.
But, Jed... Yeah, it's just a little bit...
You know, too much excitement around here.
Well, you keep me posted, all right?
Oh, I promise. You got it. Okay.
I'll talk to you later, then. Uh-huh.
Problems?
It's Bonnie. She's in trouble.
She needs my help, but her husband doesn't want me there.
Here, take it.
Don't worry, Bonnie, I'm not going to poison you.
Thank you.
We got to fatten you up.
So you can get your health back.
You want that, don't you?
Yeah, yeah.
And we can try again.
You want that, don't you, Bonnie?
Yeah. Yeah.
So we can...
You didn't know.
How could you not know?
(SHOUTING) How could you not know?
I don't know how I didn't know.
I can't be the first woman to have this happen.
But you missed your period! I missed two!
I was on medication.
What do you want from me?
(EXCLAIMS)
A child would have saved our marriage.
There is no marriage.
(DOOR CLOSING)
(CAR DRIVING AWAY)
(CRYING)
We don't have business like we used to.
It's like them Depression days all over again.
Yeah, but we'll set you up in our best room down here.
Yeah. You gonna stay long? I don't know.
What room are you gonna put him in?
I'm gonna put him in number 5, there.
No, put him in number 6, why put him in number 5?
Five's got the new television set.
Number 6 has the air conditioner in it, and you can move that television.
That's a beautiful cradle. Did you make it yourself?
JED: I made this cradle, yes, ma'am.
MAN: Come on back here, honey.
Yeah. We just sold this place.
Yeah, next week we'll be in Miami Beach, Florida.
Oh, won't it be nice and warm and sunny down there.
We will miss this old motel.
Well, Jed, we've been running this place for 30 years.
Newnan's been just like family to us.
There we are.
Go on in and make yourself at home. We got the air conditioning in here
and I'll have Jason bring in the color television for you.
Come on in.
Why don't you take off your things and come and join me?
You lesbian freak! I'd rather die.
WOMAN ON TV: Die? I think I can arrange that.
(PEOPLE ARGUING)
(VOLUME INCREASES)
(LOUD ARGUING CONTINUES)
Shut up!
Bonnie.
Bonnie, Bonnie, Bonnie, Bonnie, Bonnie.
(MAN GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Shit.
Jed. You're playing like you want to kill somebody.
Are you angry, Jed?
(SIGHS)
Of course I'm angry, man.
I had a dream. I had a family business.
You know, that's why I named the company Jackson and Son.
So that when he grew up, he'd be my partner.
Then after I'd retired, he'd take everything over.
Let it go.
I can't let it go, Leonard.
You still love her, don't you?
Loving your woman doesn't make it any easier, Leonard.
You know, it's like there ought to be a law against what she did.
What she took from me.
A son.
You know, Bonnie was hurt pretty bad by this, too.
You know, she knew she was pregnant. You know, she didn't tell me.
It's like she's a murderer.
LEONARD: Oh, come on, Jed, let it go.
You let it go, Leonard! Huh?
You have a baby murdered recently? Huh? She killed my son, man.
What does he know? What do you know?
Jed! Sit down, it's all right. Come on.
What does he know?
Sit down.
Hey, man, I know some people that feel the same way you do.
Maybe you want to talk to them.
You ready, sweetie? You know what to do.
Just wait here.
Jed, I want you to meet Tom Corey. He's from Atlanta.
Pleased to meet you, Jed. Tom.
And meet little Julie.
Pleased to meet you, sir.
Honey, go get yourself a cold drink. Okay.
Can I have a milkshake?
About six years ago, I was seeing this woman.
No big deal. On and off.
I really didn't even know much about her.
We did a lot of drugs together.
(LAUGHING) We had fun!
One day she came to me and told me she was pregnant.
Wanted me to give her money for an abortion.
And I thought, why not?
And then, I had a vision of this child.
This child. I know it sounds crazy.
I asked her to have the kid.
I told her I'd pay her to keep it, not destroy it.
She started crying, talking about taking drugs and damage.
Well, sir, that only made me more determined.
She wasn't a bad girl. I wasn't bad, either.
She moved in with me and I cleaned up my act.
For the first time in my life, I took care of somebody.
After little Julie was born, that old gal took off, I never knew where or why.
But I got Julie.
And she ain't damaged.
No.
She's a beautiful girl.
(LAUGHS)
Ever since that day, we travel all over the country,
trying to help people see the light.
So, uh, what do I do?
You sue her.
I'm sorry, but I'm going to do it!
Oh, God, Jed. Please don't.
Everybody in town is going to be looking at me in court,
and the newspaper and the television...
Jed, why are you doing this to me? I have to do it!
Why do you have to do it? So that...
So that what happened to me can never happen again. You got that?
(SIGHS)
(BELL TOLLING)
JED: It was in August. It was a hot night.
And we went to bed and I was nervous,
I don't remember why.
And we got in a fight and I lost control.
And, uh...
When I came back, she had tried to commit suicide.
Hi, Carter. Hi, Chrissy.
Anything doing? No, we don't have anything on today.
What's this about?
Nothing special. Husband fights his wife.
She said that she didn't know that she was pregnant.
I guess she didn't, but I guess she should have.
God entrusted her with this, and she let us both down.
She had no right to go off and try and commit suicide.
She had my son inside of her.
And she killed him.
It's as simple as that.
Oh, my God! Abortion by suicide?
What?
What are you talking about, nothing special?
This is great stuff.
Don't you know realize what's happening with abortion in this country?
Mr. Jackson, the court notes your grief, but what law has been broken?
I don't know, Judge.
But there ought to be one.
Maybe, son. Maybe there should be one.
I'll research the law.
I'm taking this under advisement for 20 days.
(GAVEL BANGS)
Chrissy, what are you doing?
What, are you kidding? This is national news.
You know, this is the kind of case that could take someone like Carter Evans,
Georgia's youngest prosecutor,
and most active bachelor, I might add, to the Supreme Court.
Get me a crew down to the courthouse. I need it fast.
Whether the inadvertent abortion of a local woman during a suicide attempt
can constitute criminal action under the law...
I see our County Prosecutor, Carter Evans. Mr. Evans? Chrissy.
I know you've been following this matter,
I wonder if we could solicit your legal opinion.
Well, Chrissy, as you know, our office is not involved in this action.
This is solely a matter between husband and wife.
However, I will say that, as an issue,
abortion is one that will not just go away.
I calls into question our most fundamental beliefs.
Our values and our emotions. And I have come to believe that abortion is
abhorrent to a large sector of our public.
However, Mr. Evans,
there is a public committed to protecting the integrity of a woman's control over her body.
Indeed, and let me say that until the great state of Georgia
enacts new legislation, and the nation's highest court upholds it,
then, in this land, Roe v. Wade is still the law,
which does means that abortions are legal.
Thank you, Chrissy. Thank you.
This has been Chrissy Lee, WGBN TV 33, evening news.
CARTER ON TV: However, I will say that, as an issue,
abortion is one that will not just go away.
I calls into question our most fundamental beliefs.
Our values and our emotions. And I have come to believe that abortion is
abhorrent to a large sector of our public.
This has been Chrissy Lee, WGBN TV 33, evening news.
Oh, come on! They cut me short. They slandered what I said.
Did they? I thought you looked great.
Oh, you know, I tried to be more even-handed than that.
(PHONE RINGING)
District Attorney's Office, Forest speaking.
Yes. Yes, I'll tell him!
(CHUCKLES) Well, you got one vote.
I don't even know if I'm running yet, do I?
(PHONE RINGING) You soon will be.
DA's Office, Forest speaking.
Yes. Yes, sir. I told you, they love you.
Your name and address, please. We'll contact you.
Our polls show that 48% of the public would approve of
the state filing charges against Bonnie Jackson.
It's a good issue. It's family-oriented and all,
but where did you take your poll, Newnan?
Where else?
Everyone around here wants to nail the Jackson woman,
but what about the rest of the state?
Doesn't matter.
What is really important is that people are starting to talk about Carter Evans.
This abortion thing gives you visibility.
We got us a real hot potato.
Look, I want to do what folks want.
You could ride all the way to the Governor's Mansion with this one.
You need to step into the Bonnie Jackson case, Carter.
I need to?
I know what you mean, Forest. It's a great idea.
So it is no more Jackson v. Jackson.
It's The State v. Bonnie Jackson. That's exciting.
I'd have to get our friends in the statehouse to let me run with it.
That's easy. So it's decided?
Yes.
♪ My Bonnie lies over the ocean
♪ My Bonnie lies over the sea
♪ Oh, bring back my Bonnie to me
♪ Bring back, bring back
♪ Bring back my Bonnie to me
Now as many of you may know, in 1989,
the Supreme Court saw the wisdom of returning to each state some rights in regard to
the regulation of abortion, and in view of this solemn responsibility,
the state of Georgia will now be intervening in the matter of Jackson v. Jackson.
(ALL CLAMORING)
This has been Chrissy Lee reporting for TV 33 in Newnan, Georgia.
Good Evening. Remarkable developments in the Bonnie Jackson case.
County Prosecutor Carter Evans has intervened in the case,
charging Bonnie Jackson on four counts:
the unlicensed practice of medicine,
the attempt to commit suicide, which ended in feticide,
the interference with her husband's property rights,
and the failure to inform her husband of her intent to abort her pregnancy.
And it looks like the prosecutors of the case
are hoping to find a backdoor mechanism for recriminalizing abortion.
Five, four, three, two.
We have on our show tonight Mr. James Forest, the Assistant DA.
Mr. Forest, is it true that the District Attorney, Carter Evans,
is thinking of running for Governor?
Well, that's what people are asking him to do, Chrissy.
His popularity is soaring at the moment.
But I can assure you that Carter Evans himself hasn't decided yet.
Excellent. Well said, Forest, well said.
The polls show that Carter Evans is not yet a viable contender,
but people's opinions change, and so does the popularity of the candidates.
Will he make it?
FOREST ON TV: We shall see.
Oh, yeah. CHRISSY ON TV: Well, that's our show for tonight.
WEATHERMAN ON TV: Air moving down from central Canada,
and as that occurs, that means the old cold front is going to move down on New England.
And that means an increase in clouds and showers.
So, it looks like it's going to be a wet weekend
in New York City and the tri-state area.
Better wear your raincoat, Joe.
(LAUGHS) Thanks for the warning, Al.
Let me remind you that tonight on this channel at 10:00,
there will be a special report on abortion, 1991: The Uncivil War,
focusing on the case of The State of Georgia v. Bonnie Jackson.
Carter, you son of a bitch!
I understand that my leaving is problematic,
but she's my best friend and they're nailing her to a cross.
I'll just have to take that chance.
Excuse me. Stewardess, I have been buzzing you since Des Moines.
Either get me another vodka, or get me a parachute.
Hilda Pollack.
Ned. Harris. You guys covering the Jackson trial?
Yeah, for a couple of weeks, anyway.
We wanted to go to Utah to cover the anti-nuke rally.
HARRIS: But abortion is a hotter topic right now.
It is. It is.
NED: But now that you're here, I have that feeling it is going to be newsworthy.
(LAUGHS) Ms. Pollack.
I'm Lauren McKinley. I've always admired your work.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
You know, I understand that Bonnie Jackson,
she may not be able to stand trial.
Nonsense, of course she will. I'm her attorney.
Lauren McKinley?
Come, Lauren, tell me about Bonnie Jackson.
I can't believe you're here. You're my idol in the women's movement.
(LAUGHS) And idols have clay feet.
Tell me, how are Bonnie Jackson's feet?
You know, the pro-lifers running the Georgia Legislature
want this case to go all the way to the Supreme Court.
Can she handle it?
Guess she'll have to.
Hmm.
Nice suit.
Oh, thank you.
Designer, huh? Mmm-hmm.
Don't wear designer suits in Newnan, doll.
You want to buy your clothes around the corner from the courthouse.
You want to dress down.
Go on.
Well, you might want to go out and rent Invasion of the Body Snatchers,
because that's what's going to happen.
You're going to have press, pro-life, pro-choice.
You're going to have idealists, opportunists and nuts.
And for the next two weeks, America is going to be watching you on television.
Can you take it?
I guess I'll have to.
Lauren, doll, trust me. I'm telling you this for your own good.
We are not in New York.
You are in Georgia. Small towns, small minds.
MAN: Hey, Hilda! What?
Where can we get a decent meal around here?
Canada! Come on, doll.
(LAUGHING)
So, do you have any more cars at this abortion circus?
There's my people, they got me a limo.
A limo? Can you believe it?
Well, there's a lot of old money in New England. Take it when you can get it.
Can I give you a lift?
No, I think I see my client right now.
Lauren! I'll see you later.
So that's Bonnie Jackson? Yes, the town is in an uproar.
Am I glad to see you!
(SIGHS) Nice to see you.
Here you go. Thank you. You're welcome.
Hi, how are you? Hi.
I'm so glad you're here.
I don't know what I'd do without you.
You know, Bon, the next couple of weeks are going to be tough.
There's going to be a lot of people asking a lot of questions.
But you're right, I'm not going to put you on the stand.
Oh, no, I couldn't. Oh, Lauren, you know, I couldn't.
I couldn't have all those people watching me.
Bonnie, why did you do it?
Why did you try to kill yourself?
I felt trapped. Like I couldn't see a way out, where to go.
I thought Jed would kill me if he found out.
Found out what?
I don't know.
I just, I felt so alone. You know, without any friends.
And in spite of everything, I still love him, and I don't want to hurt him.
It's going to be all right.
CARTER: Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
these are unusual charges. These are unusual times.
We believe that by undertaking this prosecution,
we represent more here than just the citizens of Georgia,
we believe that we are here on behalf of a husband.
And, by proxy, on behalf of his unborn child, the silent victim.
And after hearing all the evidence against Bonnie Jackson,
including what I am sure will be a most spirited defense,
I am confident that you will find that she is guilty of criminal abortion.
We will show that she was not merely attempting to take her own life,
but willingly overdosed with the intent to abort her unborn child.
And we believe that after hearing the laws of the state of Georgia,
in respect to the performance of abortion,
and direct evidence in regard to Bonnie Jackson's actions and state of mind,
that you will find that she is guilty of some very serious criminal charges.
Charges that, in this state, carry with them a mandatory prison term.
Members of the jury, we will prove to you
that Bonnie Jackson took medicine given to her in good faith by a family doctor,
hoarded it, and medicated herself.
Not enough to die, just enough to abort.
She illegally prescribed herself medicine, and in so doing,
she committed a criminal abortion.
In addition, she violated her husband's property rights,
and broke a long-standing Georgia statute
that simply requires that a person be notified
of a spouse's intent to end a pregnancy.
Now, ladies and gentlemen, I know that some of you might be tempted at first glance
to view this as a victimless crime,
but I assure you that there is a victim, in fact there is more than one.
Look at this man sitting at this table here.
This is Jed Jackson. He's a builder.
He works hard, he loved his wife, he wants a family.
He urged his wife to take fertility medication,
he dreams of the day that a child could be born.
And the one day he is suddenly confronted
by a so-called suicide attempt, and his dream of a family is destroyed.
A shattered ruin.
You see, this is a very important case.
It asks a question that our courts have ignored for years,
does a man have no rights when it comes to the creation of a life.
Is there no redress for a man
when his wife, without his consent,
chooses to destroy a child?
A child who was cruelly aborted,
unable to breathe life outside his mother's womb.
You see, it is only by prosecuting Bonnie Jackson
that the state, with your help, as responsible jurors,
can even begin to defend these two victims, this parent and his unborn child.
Thank you.
(CHEERING)
JUDGE: Order in the court.
Order! Order in this courtroom. Order!
(GAVEL BANGING)
Order in this court!
What are you doing?
Lady! You sit down!
JUDGE: Order in this courtroom, please.
I see that there are cameras in the courtroom.
People taking notes, writing books.
But I will not tolerate these outbursts!
All right?
Now, we've heard some eloquent words by our District Attorney.
Now I'm sure we will hear more eloquent words from our counsel for the defense.
Counselor.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury.
To say these are unusual charges
is an understatement of the worst order.
These are impossible charges.
I assure you that our defense will rest on the fact
that this case is not about abortion.
This case is about a simple attempted suicide.
Let me tell you the real story of what happened one hot summer night in August.
Jed Jackson staggered home drunk and woke his wife from a sound sleep.
He picked a fight and lost control.
I assure you that Jed Jackson
will not deny the fact that he beat his wife until her face was black and blue!
My client, physically and emotionally abused,
susceptible to depression and impulsive behavior, chose suicide.
How can the state charge Bonnie Jackson with criminal abortion
when she did not know she was pregnant?
Where is the intent?
How could she notify her spouse of something she had no knowledge of?
How could she have interfered with her husband's so-called property rights?
I ask you, is any one person the property of another?
These are innocent babies! Young woman, you need to settle down.
(ALL SHOUTING)
Stop this.
You sit down, lady.
Finally, to the question regarding a husband's right
in the decision of when to end a pregnancy,
I can only reply that this issue has no place here.
This is all bullshit! Why don't you go back to New York.
(GAVEL BANGING)
The reason that Bonnie Jackson stands here accused today is because she is a woman.
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
And on that count, we plead for freedom!
JUDGE: Order! Please be seated!
Bravo! Bravo!
(PEOPLE WHISTLING)
Stop this applause! Stop this!
This is not a rock concert!
The decision for a woman to have a child
may be one of the most important decisions she ever makes.
(ALL ARGUING)
Your Honor, will you do something?
Stop it!
You take away that decision, and you take away her dignity.
MAN: Get her out of this courtroom.
I saved this child's life!
This could have been an unborn child, but I saved her.
Stop this!
Court will resume at 10:00 in the morning.
This court is adjourned.
CROWD: (CHANTING) We're pro-life, that's why we're here.
Life is precious, life is dear. We're pro-life, that's why we're here.
Come on.
(ALL CHANTING)
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
Go get 'em, Lauren! You tell them New York lawyers don't take shit.
A woman can be irregular, yes. And miss one period, yes.
But I have to conclude that a woman who missed two menstrual cycles
must have known she was carrying a child. I have no doubt.
Dr. Reed, it says right here in here in your notes,
one week before the attempted suicide,
you took Bonnie Jackson off the Prozac and the tranquilizers
that you had prescribed to her for two years.
Now, why did you do that? Objection!
JUDGE: Overruled.
Isn't it true that she was pregnant, and you both knew it?
Objection, Your Honor, the District Attorney is leading the witness.
Well, I guess he is, but let's just see where he's leading him to.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
(GAVEL BANGS)
Order in the court. Stop this laughing. I am not that funny.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
Order in the court.
Please continue, Mr. Evans.
Isn't it true that she was pregnant, and you both knew it?
I took her urine to make sure that she was not pregnant.
Weren't you aware that Bonnie Jackson was ambivalent about having a child?
What, are you in the habit of prescribing different pills to a known pill abuser?
Weren't you aware that Bonnie Jackson might abuse those pills
in an effort to abort her unborn child?
Objection!
No further questions.
CROWD: (CHANTING) Mother youths and microwaves.
We won't be your fucking slaves.
Screw the court, screw the state, women must control their fate.
I'm the mother of six children and I can honestly tell you
that from the moment of conception, there is a life growing inside a woman.
(CROWD AGREEING)
And from very early on, you can feel that life attaching itself
to the wall of the uterus, attaching itself to you.
Depending on you! Now, on whom can that innocent being depend on if not the woman?
HILDA: How can you say that the life of an unborn child is at stake?
It's a fetus!
What about the life of a fully grown woman?
What about the life of a welfare mother with six children already?
Like you.
A woman is meant to nurture and protect this life,
as a man is meant to take care of material needs and protect her in this task.
And every one of us must acknowledge the rights,
the civil rights, of this unborn child.
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
That's right. Come to Jesus. Come to God.
(CHANTING) Mother youths and microwaves. We won't be your fucking slaves.
What about the young child?
The young girl raped by her own father and pregnant with his child?
What about the woman in law school with a dream, a dream to be somebody,
before she decides whether or not to have a child?
Are her rights nothing in the face of an embryo?
A being that cannot breathe, cannot exist outside of her body.
A potential person.
We cannot say why the good Lord has chosen
our community, our home, for this great and trying ordeal.
We can only pray that in this central clinic,
and all other clinics of America,
they will stop this sinful act,
they will stop the murder of God's little children.
Yes, life is beautiful.
Yes, motherhood is sacred.
But only when the woman has the chance to choose!
ALL: Yeah!
Freedom of choice! Protect the women of America!
Freedom of choice!
(ALL CHANTING) Freedom of choice! Freedom of choice!
Save the lives of our pre-born babies!
All of you can save the lives of our pre-born babies.
These people are not pro-choice, they are pro-murder!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(CHANTING) ...life is dear.
We're pro-life, that's why we're here.
Freedom of choice! Freedom of choice!
GUARD: All rise.
Good morning. GUARD: Be seated.
BAILIFF: Mr. Charles Ray Thompson to the stand, please.
(CROWD MURMURING)
Put your left hand on the Bible. State your name for the court, please.
Charles Ray Thompson. Raise your right hand.
Do you swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth, and nothing but the truth, so help you God?
I do. Have a seat, please.
Mr. Thompson, do you work as a pharmacist?
Yes, ma'am, I'm a licensed pharmacist.
And you work in Newnan?
Yes, ma'am, I run the pharmacy in the center of town.
Do you know Mrs. Jackson?
Yes, ma'am, Mrs. Jackson is a good client of the pharmacy.
Do you know her well?
Yes, ma'am, I know Bonnie Jackson pretty well.
Did Mrs. Jackson ever tell you that she was pregnant?
No, ma'am.
But you knew she was trying to get pregnant
because you filled her prescriptions for fertility pills.
Yes, ma'am, I did.
Did you know she was pregnant? No.
Did she tell you she was pregnant?
No, no, she didn't.
Did she know she was pregnant?
I don't know.
Objection, Your Honor, Ms. McKinley is asking the witness to speculate.
Sustained.
No further questions, Your Honor.
Mr. Evans, your witness.
Thank you, Ms. McKinley.
Now, did you wonder why all of a sudden
she stopped buying these tranquilizers, these anti-depressants?
No, I didn't wonder. It's not my job to wonder.
(CHUCKLING)
(GAVEL BANGING)
Are you close enough to Mrs. Jackson for her to tell you she was pregnant?
Sometimes my clients share their good news with me,
and sometimes they don't. Mrs. Jackson never did.
It's a possibility that she intentionally kept her pregnancy
a secret from you, isn't it?
Objection, Your Honor. Mr. Evans is leading the witness to speculate.
Sustained.
Now look me in the eye, Mr. Charles Ray Thompson.
Did Bonnie Jackson know she was pregnant or didn't she?
I don't know!
The fertility pills, you knew she had stopped taking them. No.
Did you know she was pregnant? No.
Do you know if she knew she was pregnant?
I don't know. No! Objection.
Let me tell you right now that she knew she was pregnant.
Objection, Your Honor!
Your Honor, I have no further questions.
I do my best. I try to help.
You may step down now.
REPORTER 1: Mrs. Jackson, Mrs. Jackson!
Did you or did you not know you were pregnant?
REPORTER 2: Are you on medication now, Mrs. Jackson?
Leave her alone!
We can't leave her alone, she's a public figure now.
And speaking of public figures, I hear you have
a little thing going with the DA. You want to tell us about that?
Out of my way.
There you are, Mrs. Jackson.
Thank you, C. Ray. $14.
To the penny.
Hey, you made it through the first week of your trial.
Thanks, C. Ray.
Bonnie, does your husband have any funny little habits that get on your nerves?
Was he ever violent with you? Did he ever abuse you, or mistreat you in any way?
Mrs. Jackson, could you answer at least one question today?
Go ahead.
Do you have intimate relations with other men?
Did you get that? Good.
Yeah, it is her, hurry.
Do you see her? CAMERAMAN: Yeah, I got her.
CHRISSY: What is she doing?
CAMERAMAN: I don't know. It looks like she's planting something.
CHRISSY: Well, make sure you get it, I need a good tight close-up.
CAMERAMAN: I got it, I got it.
Gloria, I got a doctor's appointment.
I hope Abe doesn't get too pissed off.
Yeah, okay, don't worry about it.
She's corning! Get ready!
Bonnie, how are you feeling?
Mrs. Jackson, do you ever talk to your husband anymore?
Mrs. Jackson, what are your religious beliefs?
♪ My Bonnie lies over the ocean
♪ My bonnie lies over the sea ♪
MALE REPORTER: Mrs. Jackson, do think you have any chance at all of winning in court?
(CHANTING) Not the church, not the state, women should decide their fate.
Not the church, not the state, women should decide their fate.
I want you all to look at this place.
This place, this medical center, is a house of murder!
Even now, in this very building, babies are being butchered.
We must stop them!
Block the entrance, everybody!
Lock hands, lock hands!
What you are doing, Father, is illegal. You know that.
If we can save one life, it's worth a penalty!
HILDA: Abortion is still legal in this country, Father.
Don't you listen to this woman!
Please don't listen to this woman!
Look, look right here!
Here is a woman coming in here for an illegal abortion!
You leave her alone!
Are you crazy? I'm not here for an abortion.
I'm five months pregnant and I'm here for a checkup.
Now get out of my way!
She's lying. You are lying! Look at that face.
Now, now, you listen to me, young girl,
for I am speaking to you in the name of the Lord Jesus!
I don't want you to come in here to kill your child.
People of Newnan. People of Newnan, look at this.
These are coat hangers.
Do you realize that before abortion became legal in 1973,
many women died using these bloody instruments to abort their child.
(ALL AGREEING)
These bloody coat hangers killed women, young and old,
and desperate girls are still using them today.
Look at this. This is what they call a fetus.
(ALL SHOUTING)
Thirteen weeks old.
It looks like a baby. Doesn't it?
And it would have been a baby, and it would have been alive.
But her mother had it ripped from her womb!
She murdered this baby!
That's bullshit!
That is a 5-month-old baby.
A 13-week-old fetus is no larger than a quarter.
I am warning you!
The women of America will boycott...
What do they make in this state?
Peaches, cotton and peanuts.
Peanuts! We will boycott the peanuts of Georgia!
(CROWD LAUGHING)
That woman is an outside agitator.
♪ We shall overcome
♪ Someday
(SIREN WAILING)
Everybody, let's get going.
Let's get going.
♪ Oh, deep in my heart
Come on, people, let's break this up.
(CROWD SHOUTING)
Lock arms, lock arms, lock arms.
POLICEMAN ON BULLHORN: Attention! Attention, everybody!
You are in violation of the law here.
Illegal assembly, people.
Attention! Attention!
You all are trespassing on private property.
(CROWD SHOUTING)
I'm going to ask you all to vacate the premises,
or I'm going to place everybody under arrest.
(LAUGHS)
Oh, Officer, you have enough jail cells in Newnan for all of us?
Lady, I will place you under arrest
and I will place every single one of you under arrest.
Go ahead!
(CHANTING) Choice! Choice! Choice!
Life is precious, life is dear. We're pro-life, that's why we're here.
Choice! Choice! Choice! Choice!
Daddy!
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
Oh, my God!
Daddy!
(NEIGHING)
Let go of me!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
Oh, my God! Somebody help that woman.
Oh, my God, she's bleeding!
Help her, get a doctor!
Get a doctor! Help her!
Oh, Doctor, come and help her!
Hi, Jed. Hey.
This must be really hard on you.
We're all behind you, though.
Thanks.
Sometimes I wonder if I'm doing the right thing.
Right. So, why don't you drop the case?
It's out of my hands now.
But didn't Bonnie try the same thing with the pills last year?
Didn't you encourage her to see Dr. Reed and take all those pills?
What's that? What are you doing?
(STAMMERING) What am I doing?
You're recording me!
I'm trying to help your wife and the community.
What are you trying to do?
Why are you doing this to me?
Carter!
Carter Evans. I need to talk to him right now, please.
Buzz him. Thank you.
CARTER: What you going on about, Jed?
I want the whole thing dropped, man. It's gone way too far.
Tell me about it. You can read about my love life on page 2.
All right, well, good enough. I'll just withdraw my complaint.
Jed! This isn't your complaint anymore.
The entire state of Georgia is prosecuting Bonnie Jackson now.
Now listen here. I happen to know
that a husband can't be forced to testify against his wife.
Fine! You can sit on that stand and claim your spousal immunity,
but before you do, I want you to remember one thing, that's your boy that she killed.
Jed, this case has a life of its own.
You can't abort it now.
Sure, we had our good days and our bad days.
What marriage is perfect? You show me one.
Anyway, I have a bad temper sometimes.
The point is, we were working at it.
We wanted to have a kid.
Now, Mr. Jackson, I realize that this is very difficult for you,
but did you both want to have children?
Yeah, yeah, both of us.
Bonnie wanted to have one too, I'm sure of that.
Thank you, Mr. Jackson. Your Honor, I have no further questions.
It's your witness, ma'am.
Jed, do you now regret
your involvement in bringing this action?
Objection, Your Honor.
This action.
Sustained.
No further questions.
JUDGE: We shall resume at 10:00 in the morning.
Court is adjourned.
(CROWD MURMURING)
Let's stop it. Let's go, Bonnie.
Newnan, Georgia, is where militant anti-abortion activists
were arrested today and then released on bail.
All this went on the last few days.
I'll raise you five!
(SCOFFS)
And I'll see you.
Ta-da!
(LAUGHING)
Next time.
...his property as much as it was hers, she did not consult him.
She broke the law...
Remember her?
Lauren McKinley, New York attorney for the defense, is claiming...
Oh yeah, that rainy day in May.
She came a few times. She'd come in the afternoon and leave before nightfall.
She was always alone.
Well, I wouldn't count on her winning that case.
Unless, of course... What?
There was a man... Yeah?
Yeah. What's she doing on TV?
(CROWD CHANTING SOFTLY) Life is precious, life is dear.
We're pro-life, that's why we're here.
Life is precious, life is dear.
MAN: Say goodnight to your baby, Bonnie!
(SCREAMS)
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh!
That's disgusting!
Go away!
Leave me alone! Get out of here! I'll call the police!
Go away! Get out of here!
Oh, my God!
I can't take it anymore.
LAUREN: Bonnie, what's going on?
I can't take this anymore. Bonnie!
I can't take it anymore. End it!
End it! I'll say anything they want me to say.
I can't allow that, I'm your attorney.
No, you're my friend.
(CRYING)
I'm your friend.
What do these polls say about how the public feels about abortion?
It's not clear.
No, it's not clear at all.
The polls are quite clear.
Gentlemen, you should know Chrissy Lee very well by now,
but in case you don't, she's formerly from WGBN and she's now...
Well, she's come aboard to head the PR for our campaign.
Welcome aboard, Ms. Lee. Congratulations.
Thank you.
Our polls are clear, gentlemen. It's the public that's not clear.
You see where sympathy for the Jackson woman has remained constant but rather low?
Yeah, 22%, 23%, 24.5%.
And it's not just abortion. People don't like suicide very much.
Well, however, if you rephrase the question in terms of
women's rights in general, including Bonnie Jackson,
almost 41% approve of the right for a woman to have an abortion.
Perhaps we should delay formally announcing our candidacy.
The most constant number up here is
the 68% that disapprove of the way the media has handled this issue.
(LAUGHS) Coming from there, I can tell you that
no matter what the issue, people are going to disapprove of how the media handles it.
All I'm doing is trying to find out is if the people of this state
approve of the action we're trying to take here.
There's no longer a consensus, Carter.
But, now that we have Miss Chrissy Lee with us,
I would expect that we can produce whatever results you want to appear in the media.
CHRISSY: (LAUGHS) That is not so simple!
I mean, the media is very powerful and it can't be bought.
Not in America.
I disagree with that, Chrissy. There is nothing in America that can't be bought.
We bought you.
Go to hell.
Come on, Chrissy, he didn't mean that. Come on. Chrissy.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean it.
Come on, Chrissy, I need you on this team.
It's been a long day. I'm sure all our nerves are on edge.
I'm sure there's a thing or two that you could teach these gentlemen
about how to reverse public opinion.
Hmm?
You're the boss.
That's a girl.
Janice, do me a favor and call over to the country club for me.
I just don't think... LAUREN: Hello, Carter.
Lauren? Well, well. What brings you here?
My client has authorized me to explore a settlement.
I see.
I must say, I didn't expect that.
We plead guilty to one count, the unlicensed practice of medicine.
Not the criminal abortion. So, you would get a conviction in the books.
You would get what you want.
What I want? You know, I wanted to fight for what the public wants,
but now I find myself fighting all the time, tilting at windmills.
Tell me, what is it you want?
I thought I wanted to help a friend. But now I want more.
So think about it.
You want power. And you want me to exonerate you.
We're both the same people. We're both ambitious.
Oh, and, Lauren, I'll tell you this much,
I'll take your offer of settlement under advisement.
What the hell is going on? I hear you're going to quit!
I represent Bonnie Jackson, Hilda.
No shit! You represent every woman in America.
She can't stand it anymore.
She wants to settle.
And what do you want?
Did you settle?
Bonnie? I brought you a plant.
Thank you. Did you settle?
(SIGHS)
No, not yet.
I beg you, Bonnie, let's just keep on fighting.
No! It's not just for you.
This case could help hundreds of women,
women who are desperate, who can't communicate with their husbands.
Who think that the only way to fix it is to end it. Just like you did, Bonnie.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello. Yeah, it's Bonnie Jackson's house.
She's right here. It's for you.
Lauren McKinley.
Yes, I'm Bonnie Jackson's attorney.
What?
I don't understand. Who is this?
Miami Beach Retirement Home. What's your number, sir?
I see.
I'll be in touch with you. Thank you.
What?
We're going to win this case. Come on.
Where to?
Recognize this place?
Bonnie, talk to me.
No.
I'm you're attorney, for Christ's sake. You have to talk to me!
Tell me the truth.
No.
You had an affair.
Who was he?
Bonnie. Who was he?
It's nobody's business. Oh, yes, it is.
You don't have any idea how important this is.
If it's not Jed's baby, then they don't have a case.
No, you don't understand.
Lauren, I understand, just don't come crying to me later.
I tell you, you're asking for it.
Okay, so the trial will resume on Monday.
And you're absolutely sure?
Yeah.
Okay.
It's a circus!
It's a goddamn three-ring circus.
(BAND PLAYING YOUR CHEATIN' HEART)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
♪ But sleep won't come
♪ The whole night through
I got pro-life extra-large T-shirts, I got pro-choice extra-large T-shirts.
I got them all, folks. Tell me what you want.
I can sell you anything.
(CHANTING) Life is precious, life is dear.
We're pro-life, that's why we're here.
Not the church, not the state, women should decide their fate.
Mother youths and microwaves.
We won't be your fucking slaves.
Do you want an abortion? I'll give you one.
(SCREAMING)
Abortion! Abortion!
The defense calls Mr. Herbert Gordon to the stand.
(CROWD MURMURING)
Carter. What's this shit about?
What's going on here?
Look, I'm as puzzled about this as you are. God knows what she's up to.
Be careful.
Lauren, no. Don't do this to me.
It's going to be okay.
Raise your right hand. Put your left hand on the Bible.
State your name for the court, please.
Herbert T. Gordon.
Mr. Gordon, do you swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth, and nothing but the truth, so help you God?
I do. Thank you.
Mr. Gordon, where do you live?
Miami Beach, Florida, since last September.
And where did you reside before that date?
Why, we resided right here.
Mrs. Gordon and I lived just outside this town,
where we ran the Oaks Inn Motel, ran it for some 30-odd years.
What kind of people patronized that hotel?
Well...
In the early years, we had all kinds of people.
Traveling salesmen and the like.
Then, in later years,
more and more folks that just wanted to get away for a few hours.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
(GAVEL BANGING)
JUDGE: Proceed, Mr. Gordon.
Mrs. Gordon didn't like that. No, she didn't!
Then, last week,
we saw this Ms. Bonnie Jackson on the television,
and we knew that we must come back to Newnan to perform our duties
and testify for the sake of truth and justice.
(MURMURING)
Mr. Gordon. Can you identify the man who...
Stop it! ...who you saw at the motel with Mrs. Jackson?
That man. Objection!
In the third row, there, that black man.
(GAVEL BANGING) JUDGE: Order. Order in the court.
Return to your seats, please.
It's a trick.
Quiet, please.
Quiet!
Please continue, Mr. Gordon.
He and the accused, Mrs. Bonnie Jackson,
used to come to the motel in the afternoons.
It was the month of May, if I'm not mistaken.
No more! Your Honor, I want to testify!
Young lady, sit down!
Sit down! Sit down! No! You have ruined my life!
Your Honor, please let me testify!
Your Honor, my objection?
Your Honor, I also object.
Maybe we're onto something. Young lady, you may take the stand.
Raise your right hand. Place your left hand on the Bible.
State your name for the court.
I'm Mrs. Jed Jackson.
I'm Bonnie Jackson.
Do you swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth, and nothing but the truth, so help you God?
I do. Thank you.
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
I'm Bonnie Jackson.
And I knew that I was pregnant.
MAN 1: Murderer! She's a liar!
(CHATTERING)
MAN 2: Let her speak!
WOMAN: Go to hell!
MAN 3: You killed your child.
I couldn't tell you, Lauren.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
JED: Bonnie.
Jed, don't scream at me.
Bonnie! You, sir, sit down and be quiet...
Bonnie!
He never understood what I needed. He just screamed all the time.
The only thing he wanted was a baby.
If you scream... Bonnie!
Bonnie! All he wanted was a baby.
(GAVEL BANGING) Bonnie!
JUDGE: That is enough! ...what I needed. And I needed something else.
And there was someone else,
who was gentle with me.
And so I went to that person.
(LAUGHING)
So I went to that person
'cause I was so lonely.
But I knew I couldn't have this child.
I knew that Jed would kill me
if he found out about this child.
And so I tried to kill myself
and my baby.
Come on, Jed. Let's sit down.
Come on, sit down.
Now, Bonnie, are you aware of the Georgia statute regarding criminal abortion?
No, sir.
Do you mind if I read it to you now?
"A person commits the offense of criminal abortion when he administers
"any medication, drugs, or other substance, whatever, to any woman,
"or when he uses any instrument or other means upon any woman,
"with intent to produce a miscarriage or abortion."
Section B.
"A person convicted of the offense of criminal abortion
"shall be punished by imprisonment of no less than one, nor more than 10, years."
Bonnie, in your own words, and for the record of this trial,
I must ask you to say whether anyone had any knowledge...
No. No, no one knew. It was my decision, mine alone.
So, the decision to end your life...
That was mine.
Your decision.
My decision. It's my life. It was my body.
And the life inside your body...
That was mine!
No woman could give that up easily.
But no one else should be able to make that decision for me.
No one.
Continue, Bonnie.
Do you think I could have given up my child that easily?
I was not ready to have a child.
I was not ready for Jed's child.
And I certainly could not have handled C. Ray's.
Maybe in another time or another place.
How could I have protected that child from my husband?
Or from the harshness of this town.
I didn't want to be pregnant then. It was an accident.
And I want children. I love children.
And I thought about having an abortion.
But I didn't want to do that, either.
It was the hardest decision I had to make in all my life.
So I decided to end it all because I didn't know what else to do.
Free Bonnie Jackson!
(CHANTING) Free Bonnie Jackson. Free Bonnie Jackson.
Free Bonnie Jackson. Free Bonnie Jackson.
(ALL SHOUTING)
(GAVEL BANGING) Free Bonnie Jackson.
You look at that face. You look at it!
Quiet! Quiet in the gallery.
Free Bonnie Jackson. Free Bonnie Jackson.
Let us have some respect in this court of law.
Silence! Quiet!
I will not tolerate this behavior in a court of law.
Will you control yourselves! Quiet. Silence!
Bailiff! I order this court cleared for the afternoon session,
at which time the jury will begin deliberation.
And I sincerely hope we will be able to conclude this case at the end of the day.
Court is adjourned!
REPORTER: Mr. Forest, Mr. Forest, do you think you will win this case?
(ALL SHOUTING)
Mr. Montgomery.
Mr. Montgomery, has the jury reached a verdict?
Yes, we have, Your Honor.
Will the defendant please rise.
Mr. Foreman, will you publish the verdict.
Count 1, as to criminal attempt to commit suicide,
we, the jury, find the defendant
not guilty.
Count 2, interference with husband's property rights,
we, the jury, find the defendant not guilty.
She's not her husband's property, she's community property now.
Count 3, failure to obtain spousal notification,
we, the jury, find the defendant not guilty.
(EXCLAIMS)
Count 4, unlicensed practice of medicine
to produce a criminal abortion, we, the jury, find the defendant
guilty.
Your Honor. Your Honor, I would like to be heard, please.
Sit down, Ms. McKinley. But something is wrong here.
Something is clearly wrong. I said, sit down, Ms. McKinley.
Does this mean that she goes off to jail?
Mrs. Jackson, you have been tried by a jury of your peers,
and they have made their judgment.
Before I pronounce sentencing, I want to say for the record
that I have lived uneasily with this case for some time.
Our country is so involved with this heated debate about abortion.
Ostensibly, the issue is about the question of when life begins and who should choose.
But the pro-lifers and the pro-choicers have been hurling every imaginable argument
at each other in an effort to gain new ground in their pitched battle.
They have thrown in morality issues, women's lib,
religion, family tradition and even racism.
And yet neither side has ever really listened to the other.
Tactics are escalating. The hatred intensifying.
We are steadily building toward another civil war.
Never has an issue so complicated and so sensitive
been so quickly politicized.
And never has the humanity behind such an issue
been so quickly forgotten, as though it were an unexploded landmine.
Now, as to the case before us, The State v. Bonnie Jackson,
Mrs. Jackson, I'm sure that you have come to see
that your misuse of prescribed medicine,
and of the confidence your doctor had in you,
caused a considerable amount of your turmoil.
Be that as it may, I want to give the both of you
an opportunity to rebuild your lives.
And with that in mind, I suspend sentence and fine you $1,000.
Yes! Judge, I got $1,000 right here. Jed, Jed.
Now, I can write you a check, and...
Sit down, young man, or I'll hold you in contempt of court.
Okay, okay.
I'll pay it later, then.
I just want to pay. Sit down.
Now, as to the performance of all other persons involved in this lawsuit,
and to the use of taxpayers' money herein, we can offer no opinion,
except that I can personally say that I have found these proceedings
to have been exploitive and outrageous.
Bonnie Jackson, you are free to leave.
This court is adjourned.
(GAVEL BANGS)
Thank you. Thank you.
Bonnie, I'll be outside. Maybe we can talk?
Our claim is that it was a great moral victory.
Yeah, that's our only chance to change the polls.
Are you listening to us?
Not anymore, I'm not.
Congratulations, Counselor.
Oh, come on, Lauren, be a sport.
See you around.
CROWD: (CHANTING DISTANTLY) Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie!
They're calling for us, Bonnie.
I'm finally doing something important for my life.
You have great plans.
I sure do, doll. I feel great. We won!
We didn't win anything. You won.
You loved it, didn't you?
All these bright lights, all this attention, all those people watching you.
You used me to get people to watch you!
Okay, maybe I did want some recognition.
Sure.
But I risked everything, my job, my future,
for you.
And we won!
Did we?
We sure did! We won a victory for women everywhere.
Lauren, do you really give a shit about women everywhere, or women anywhere?
You ungrateful bitch.
Ungrateful? For what? For becoming a goddamn sideshow?
I begged you to settle, but no, you wanted me parading around there.
Hold, hold, hold! I didn't know what would come out in this trial!
You didn't share with me the fact that you were balling C. Ray Thompson, thank you.
You're always the lawyer, you always know how to defend yourself.
Damn right, I'm a lawyer.
Next time you're on trial, why don't you get your dentist to help you!
Unless, of course, you're fucking him, too! Go to hell!
You ruined my life! Ruined your life?
Your life is what you make of it! Bonnie, you are a symbol.
I'm a symbol? I'm a symbol of what?
I wish... I wish I were dead!
Then take them. Take them! Take these pills.
Take them. After all you've been through, after all you could have been.
You had the courage for a moment.
But now you're looking for a new place to hide.
Shit. You're dead already.
If you don't grow, you die.
So get it over with!
Take the goddamn pills! We've got a prize outside, and I'm going to take it.
(DISTANT CHANTING)
You were worthless. Absolutely worthless.
How do you feel? I'm absolutely glad it's over with, that's how I feel.
Chrissy.
What are you doing here? I'm back with the media. My resignation is on your desk.
Well, I see. I hope you understand.
I hope I see you around, that's all. Sure.
CROWD: (CHANTING) Not the church, not the state, women should decide their fate.
REPORTER: Lauren, Lauren! Can we get some comments from you?
Congratulations, Lauren, we won. It's a great day for women.
Ms. McKinley, do you feel the women's rights movement has been vindicated?
REPORTER: Ms. McKinley, would you step up to our microphone?
Have all women been vindicated?
Yes. But at what cost to one woman? We stand here so deeply...
MAN 1: Here she is! Here she is!
MAN 2: You murdered, lady!
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
Lauren, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Mrs. Jackson, Mrs. Jackson. Now that it's all over, how do you feel?
Are you going back to your husband?
Do you have any plans for the future?
Why don't you just leave her alone?
No, it's all right, it's all right.
You all can ask me any questions you want, I'm not afraid anymore.
(ALL CLAMORING)
Bonnie, I had a dream last night
and I dreamed that we were together.
I want to go home now.
I don't know, Jed. I need time.
Well, I think we can make it work out. I think I learned my lesson.
I need time, Jed.