(Multicom Jingle)
(somber orchestral music)
(ominous orchestral music)
- Stop!
You doing?
Get off of me.
(Adrianne cries out)
Stop it, stop!
(David grunts)
(hand weight thuds)
(Adrianne cries out)
(disjointed ominous music)
(gun firing)
- Diane's beautiful eyes have always
played the strings of
my heart effortlessly.
I couldn't imagine life without her.
Not for a second did I wanna lose her.
I was totally in love with
her and always will be.
(bell rings)
- Guys, most really suck.
You are so lucky to have David
even though he does go to Manning.
- Oh, I know.
- Ooh, although Billy's
pretty cute, don't you think?
- I haven't noticed.
- Oh, come on.
- No, I mean, it's just you know,
David and me are really special.
- Yeah, but I mean just
hypothetically speaking.
Let's suppose David never knew.
- There is no suppose.
I mean, David and me,
it's not just because
we're getting married and we're
gonna be together forever.
It's like we're the same person in a way
and always have been.
It's kind of hard to put
into words. (chuckles)
- Yeah, but I at least
wish I had a relationship
I could put into words.
- Oh, you will.
If you want something bad
enough, things just come to you.
I mean, that's been my experience.
- I want Billy.
- I think you should aim higher.
- (chuckles) It's easy for you to say.
You have David.
- Yeah, David's special, it's true.
He'd do anything in the world for me.
(Susie chuckles)
(drumsticks tapping rhythmically)
- At close interval.
Dress right, dress!
- [Announcer] And now if y'all would rise
for the presentation of
the colors by the members
of the Manning High ROTC.
- Ready!
Front!
Color Guard, fall in!
Quickstep, halt.
Present arms.
("The Star-Spangled Banner")
(crowd cheering)
- [Coach] Left!
Aw, come on.
- [David] Even though we
went to different schools,
Diane and I created and lived in our own
separate, wonderful world.
(crowd chattering)
- That was embarrassing.
- How'd we look?
- You looked magnificent.
Greenish brown female sheep.
- Greenish brown female sheep.
That was our secret code
(sultry music)
so we could say any time, anywhere
how much we loved each other
and no one else would ever know.
- David, wait.
I don't wanna do anything
until, you know, David.
Don't be mad.
- I'm not mad, I just don't understand
what we're waiting for here.
Do you doubt me?
- I don't doubt you.
- So what are you (mumbles)?
- David.
- What?
What, do you think if we make love
this is gonna change things or something?
That only makes me think
you don't believe in us.
- No, I do.
- Okay.
- It's just that,
David, my virginity's something
I can only give you once.
- I know.
Well that's important to me, too,
but you think waiting four years
is gonna make a difference?
♪ Just the way I need to ♪
♪ I'm distracted ♪
- You're right.
♪ By this power I'm pouring down ♪
♪ I begin to count the hours ♪
♪ Until I can feel you ♪
♪ Feel you ♪
♪ You can feel me ♪
♪ Feel me ♪
♪ We'll be so happy together ♪
♪ I can feel you ♪
♪ Feel you ♪
♪ You can feel me ♪
♪ Feel me ♪
♪ We'll be so happy
together in the night ♪
- We are bound together forever.
- Forever and ever.
Diane had always held her virginity
as one of her highest virtues.
When we agreed to be married,
I love you,
she finally let her guard down long enough
for our teenage hormones to kick in.
- [Salesman] Nice ring, young lady.
60 days to redeem those guns, young man.
- Oh, it's so beautiful I
wanna wear it right now.
- Isn't that bad luck?
- We make our own luck.
I'm so hungry I could eat my boots.
Pull in at the Texas Roaster, okay?
- We can't, we're gonna be late.
- David.
- All right, we'll do drive-through.
- Thanks.
Hi, Texas Roasters, may I take your order?
- Can I get a couple of crispy
chicken sandwiches, please?
Fries?
A couple of fries, a
couple of shakes, yes?
Anything else?
- Nope.
- And that's all.
- Okay, two crispy chickens,
two larges fries, and two shakes.
Okay, just pull up to the
99th window and get your food.
(girls giggle)
Welcome to Texas Roasters,
may I take your order?
- [Customer] Two roasters
and fries, please.
- Okay, two roasters and two fries.
Okay, pull up to the window.
Thank you.
Hey, y'all.
- Hey, A.J.
That was you, huh?
- [Adrianne] Yep.
How y'all doin'?
You all set for regionals?
- Oh yeah.
- A.J.,
he's here again.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll see ya around, David.
- All right.
- Hey.
- Is she all right?
- Yeah,
just some boy keeps stoppin' by.
Drive careful, y'all.
- [David] All right.
- [Boy] I'm serious.
- [Girl] Marcy, come here.
- [Marcy] I said I was
gonna come, didn't I?
- [Boy] Gimme 50 cents.
- [Boy] What, you don't have a wallet?
- Hey, Bryan.
Can I get ya somethin' to eat?
- Is A.J. around?
- Not right now.
Bryan, I think she's
dating somebody, ya know?
- I just wanted to talk to her.
Well, tell her I said hey.
- Okay.
Bye-bye.
- [Employee] You gotta
get some out of the fryer.
- I feel so bad hidin' like this.
- It's a kindness, A.J.
- Well, I could at least talk to him.
- You did, and now he follows
you around like a puppy.
Don't worry about him.
- He just seems so sad
all the time, ya know?
Welcome to Texas Roasters,
may I take your order?
- Who was she, the little blonde?
- Her name's A.J.
She's on the cross country team.
- She's cute, can she run?
- I don't know.
She's just a sophomore.
(crowd cheering)
(crowd applauding)
- [Announcer] Got Manning at 15:41.
Euclid, 15:43.
15:44.
Euclid, 15:45, 15:46.
15:48.
15:51.
15:54.
15:55, six.
15:58.
16 even.
Euclid, 16:01.
Manning, 16:03.
(students chattering)
- [Coach] Everybody,
let's get back on the bus.
Let's get back--
(students chattering)
- [Coach] Good job, ladies.
- [Boy] Thanks.
- Let's get going, girls.
- Excuse me.
- [Coach] I'm real proud of you.
- Hey.
- Hey, A.J., nice race.
- [Adrianne] Thanks.
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm all right.
- [David] You sure?
- Yeah, it's nothin', it's
just my durned old knee.
- [Coach] Come on, girls, let's go.
We're all ready.
- I should probably get you
some ice for that.
(girls chattering)
- You don't have to get
me any ice, it's okay.
- [Coach] Jimmy, tell your
sister to hurry up, will ya?
- Oh, I'll get you some ice.
- Go ahead.
- Everybody make sure
you get all your gear.
We're gonna be leavin' in 10 minutes.
(soft rock music)
(students chattering)
- Hi.
Yeah, it's all right.
I don't mind.
I'm just fine with it.
♪ I don't wanna talk about it ♪
♪ Do enough I think ♪
♪ Don't wanna spend more money ♪
♪ I don't want another drink ♪
- [Adrianne] David.
♪ I would scratch out ♪
♪ All the images ♪
- I like the way
you say my name.
♪ If I had a chance ♪
♪ Don't ask me what I'm thinking ♪
♪ Can't you see I only want
to dance without sleeping ♪
♪ I'll dance without fear ♪
♪ Dance without senses ♪
♪ No message I hear ♪
♪ Dance without sleeping ♪
♪ I'll dance 'til I'm numb ♪
♪ Dance 'til I think I can ♪
- Mama, I told you already, okay.
- No, you said you thought she was stupid
to let herself get pregnant.
- And she was.
- You're not stupid, though.
- I'm not pregnant either.
♪ Walking on the edge ♪
- David.
♪ Rage and understanding ♪
♪ Between black and white ♪
- Diane.
Tell me the truth.
- Mama.
♪ This child is so angry ♪
- When did it happen?
♪ Alone here tonight ♪
- It's all right, we're getting married.
- Oh, well I hope so,
but Diane, baby.
- Mama, we are, I know, okay?
We are.
- That's a long time from now.
- Mama, I'm either gonna
die Mrs. David Graham,
or I'm gonna die Miss Diane
Zamora, one or the other.
♪ I perceive ♪
♪ Dance without sleeping ♪
(horn honks)
- [Man] I'm doin' well. (chuckles)
- [Woman] Yeah, looks good.
- [Boy] Aw man, he is so funny.
♪ Without senses, no message I hear ♪
♪ Dance without sleeping,
I'll dance 'til I'm numb ♪
♪ Dance 'til I think I can oh oh ♪
- Take a left up at the corner.
- Shortcut?
When are your folks expecting you?
- No particular time.
- The event was meaningless and painful.
Painful, that is, because
I was letting down
the one person I had
swore to be faithful to.
Come on.
(rain pattering)
(soft suspenseful music)
(couple breathing heavily)
- [Man] False.
- Ya got the guilts,
'cause you haven't said two words to me.
- I'm just tired from
the track meet, ya know.
- You're not goin' steady
with somebody are you?
'Cause I've never seen you
with anybody at school at all.
- No, it's not that, I'm
just thinkin' about stuff.
- Okay, 'cause you can
get hurt around here
goin' out with the wrong boy.
Remember what happened to Lucy Collier?
- No, what?
- She got the tar beat out of
her by that girl Marguerite.
I testified in court, did you know that?
She had to have her face
rebuilt all on account
of messin' with Marguerite's
steady boyfriend.
- Is that a fact?
- So, I don't mess around
with other girls' guys,
just so we're clear on that.
- Crystal.
(somber music)
- [Girl] Actually, these
fries are really, really good.
(mumbles) if you think
I'm gonna share 'em.
- [Girl] What?
- Hey, Val.
- How ya doin'?
- Hey!
- I'm fine, how are you?
- It's good to see ya.
- Who's that?
- [Boy] How's it goin', man?
- So, what's goin' on, kids?
- Hi, how ya doin', yeah.
- It's fry time.
- Hey.
(girl laughs)
- Hey Tracy.
- Actually, you know what?
We have to go.
Are you ready, Tracy?
Yeah, I forgot it.
I'll get some later.
- Good to see ya again.
- Take it easy.
- All right.
- [Boy] See later, A.J.
- Bye.
- See ya around, A.J.
- [Val] Well that was quick.
I wonder what they're off to do.
- David.
David, did you hear me?
That's the third time today.
What's going on with you?
- Nothing.
Come on, Diane, the movie
starts in 20 minutes.
- David, wait a minute.
David, we're not going to the movies.
- We're not goin' now?
- Why don't you just come over
and sit down for a minute.
I need to talk to you.
- What's up?
- You've been troubled lately.
Something's going on.
- I don't know what you mean.
- I know you.
You can't lie to me, don't you know that?
So, come on and just get it over with.
Out with it, David, what is it?
Another woman?
(David sighs)
Who?
- It was
A.J. from the track team.
You don't know her.
- The girl from the fried chicken place.
So, how did it happen?
I mean, don't make me drag it out of you.
- It just happened.
I mean, I was at the track
meat and we were talking,
and then,
I don't know, we sat on the bus together.
I was talkin' to her and then
she kissed me and...
- Go on.
- I don't know.
She needed a ride home so
I said I'd give her a ride,
and
we didn't go straight there,
we stopped at the school first.
- What did you do?
- I had
carnal knowledge of her.
(somber music)
(Diane grunts)
- Oh God. (sobbing)
- [David] Oh God.
- No. (sobbing)
- [David] Diane.
- [Diane] Oh my God.
- Oh God, Diane.
- No.
No.
- I'll do anything.
Just tell me what
you want me to do.
- No. Oh my God.
(sobbing) Why?
Oh, go away!
I gave up my virginity for you.
- I love you.
- For us!
Oh my God. (sobbing)
Why?
- I'm sorry.
- This isn't
supposed to happen.
This wasn't supposed to happen.
- I am so sorry.
- This can't be allowed
to happen. (sobbing)
Why? (sobbing)
- [David] For at least
an hour she screamed sobs
I wouldn't have thought possible.
(Diane sobbing)
It wasn't just jealousy.
For Diane
- Why?
- she'd been betrayed,
deceived, and forgotten.
(Diane sobbing)
- I don't think it was your fault.
Women have ways of makin'
a man forget himself.
She knew what she was doin'.
So therefore she must
suffer the consequences.
- Whatever you say.
- It's the only way.
And when she's gone,
we can go on as before,
but not until.
You understand?
- Yeah.
- She'll have to suffer the consequences.
She will have to die.
(upbeat music)
- [Adrianne] Come here to bug me instead
while I'm trying to work.
- [Val] Come on, he's really nice.
- [Boy] That's why I didn't tell you.
- [Girl] I'm coming.
- Guys, I have to clean up.
Larry, out, out.
- [David] I didn't have any
harsh feelings for Adrianne,
but no one could stand
between me and Diane.
♪ You can see them, they've been sent to ♪
- [David] When this
precious relationship we had
was damaged by my thoughtless actions,
the only thing that could
satisfy her womanly vengeance
was the life of the one
that had, for an instant,
taken her place.
- Okay.
♪ Alone makes two, let's start ♪
- A.J., come on, why don't you go with us?
- Hey come on, A.J.
- I'll buy the popcorn.
- I can't, I wanna work out.
- [Larry] Wait a minute, Tracy's back
in town tonight, isn't he?
- Yes.
- Uh-huh, yeah.
- But that's not eat, smarty.
- Oh, I didn't say nothin'.
- Is that gettin' serious, you and Tracy?
- Well no, Tracy's a sweet boy,
but I'm still young ya know?
- Yeah, uh-huh.
(girls giggle)
- A.J., see ya tomorrow.
- All right.
- You have fun workin' out.
- I will.
- Yuck.
How do you work out at night?
- Night's about the only time
I got left for workin' out.
- [Val] See ya.
- [Adrianne] Oh man.
- What is it?
- Oh, nothin'.
I thought it might've
been this guy, never mind.
- You all right?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah?
- [Val] Don't work too hard.
- I won't.
- Goodnight.
- Bye.
See y'all tomorrow.
- All right.
(soft suspenseful music)
- Hey, you.
- Hey.
Pew, that smell.
- You're tellin' me.
Been paintin' this room all day.
- Hey, it looks good.
- Thanks.
- Come on, I need a workout buddy.
- Oh, get real.
- It's time to get out
of this odorifousness.
Get out.
(Linda laughs)
Come on, it'll make you feel better.
- Okay.
Boy, I raised a pushy little girl.
- Like mother, like daughter.
Come on.
- [Linda] Okay.
(soft suspenseful music)
♪ There she goes ♪
♪ It don't matter ♪
- Do some squats.
(weights clang)
- (exhales) Okay, I'm
on the stationary bike
and then we're outta here.
- Okay, all I have left is butt crunchers.
- Oh yeah, don't forget
those, Miss Bubble Butt.
- Mama.
- It's true, jiggle just like
a pair of bubbles when you walk.
- It does not.
- It does, too.
Mm-hm.
- Oh.
(ominous music)
Hey, what do you call
someone who figures out
why people they do?
Is that a psychologist?
- Mm, psychologist or
behavioral analyst, somethin'.
- Yeah, I think I'm interested
in doing that for a living.
- Okay.
You can start with me.
- What?
- I'm serious, I have no idea
why I do the things I do.
(Adrianne chuckles)
(ominous music)
(phone rings)
- [Linda] Adrianne.
- Is it Tracy?
- [Linda] Please tell him
not to call this late here.
- I will.
Daddy, just one second, please?
- A second, okay?
- Okay.
- A.J.'s in love.
- Hello?
- Yeah, no, it's okay.
- A.J.'s in love.
- Get off the phone.
- So when'd ya get back?
- A.J.'s in love.
- Get out of here.
- No, after work Mama and
me worked out, that's it.
So, oh shoot, hang on a second.
Let me see who this is.
Hello?
Yeah, hello.
What, what's the matter?
- [Linda] Adrianne.
Adrianne?
- Well I don't know what to say.
It's David from cross country
and I'm still on with Tracy.
- I don't care, get off the phone.
- Okay.
My mom.
When?
Well I don't know, it's late.
Oh don't.
Yeah, sure I can just,
yeah okay.
Yes, I will.
- A.J., I gotta go.
- Okay.
- Get out.
- Bye.
- [A.J.'s Brother] I gotta go now.
- I'm sorry.
- I can't hold it!
- My mom was talkin' to me, too.
Just somebody from cross country.
His name's Bryan.
He was real upset so I
didn't wanna cut him off.
No, he just wanted to
talk, ya know. (chuckles)
So, what about us, where were we?
Yeah.
- Time.
- [Linda] You know how you get
when you don't get enough sleep.
- Mom, don't worry.
I'll see you tomorrow.
- 'Night, baby.
- Goodnight.
(somber music)
Well hi there.
(engine rumbling)
(train whistle blows)
(soft ominous music)
- [Linda] Hon, will you get them?
- [Bill] Okay, guys, let's go.
Come on, come on.
- Come on!
- [Bill] Hup, hup, let's go.
- Whoa, we're gonna be late.
Oh get over--
- Good morning, baby.
- Hi, baby.
Sit down here.
Who cares?
I want you to eat now
because we're late, again.
Hey, not with your fingers.
Adrianne?
Adrianne!
Adrianne, you up?
- Another late night?
- Too late for him to drive home anyway.
I've got a test.
- [Carlos] Hey, David.
- Where's my lunch?
- Didn't see your car.
- It's just down the block.
- [Gloria] You two are up early.
- I have a test, I told you.
We're leaving early.
- [Carlos] Let's go, come on.
(detectives chattering)
- [Officer] Okay, I'll check.
- [Officer] By the way,
you left it up there.
- [Dispatcher] Full connect, 45, roger.
- [Officer] I'm gonna
make some molds here also.
Yeah, I've got some
(mumbles), I'll get it.
- [Officer] Charlie, give me
a hand over here, will ya?
- [Officer] All the way down
to the edge of the water.
- [Officer] Yeah, what do you got?
I'll have the forensics
boys take a look at this.
- Not there.
- Okay, I'll check.
I'll be waiting--
- She was shot twice in the head and hit
very hard with some sort of
blunt object, skull's crushed.
That's the puzzle.
Take a look.
All four fingers on her
left hand were crushed.
- [Officer] Guys, give me
a hand over here, will ya?
- She was probably trying
to protect herself.
- [Officer] What do you got?
- I'm thinking that she
was either dead or dying
before she was shot.
We're finished here.
- [Officer] Down here.
- [Man With Stretcher] Watch it.
- Adrianne?
Hurry up.
Have you seen your sister?
Adrianne.
(bell rings)
- [Girl] Oh, I'll tell Mom later.
- Okay.
- That means practice.
(students chattering)
- Sorry, man.
- That's okay.
- Move back now.
- You see what happened?
- [Carl] How ya doin'?
- Hey, Tom Green, Manning PD.
- Carl Baker, Tanner County.
You got anything?
- Yeah, there's a missing persons out
for an Adrianne Jones,
age 16, from Manning.
If that's not her, it's her twin sister.
- You saw the body?
- Okay let's put this through.
- Yeah.
This is where you found her?
- Right over here.
- I don't think she was raped.
- Right.
I wonder what she was doing
out here with no shoes.
Hey.
Hey, you.
Here, son, step back
behind this tape, come on.
- Is that blood?
Is that her blood?
- Yeah.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, watch
where you're walkin'.
What's your name, son?
- Larry.
I'm a friend of A.J.'s,
I mean, if it is A.J.
- [Tom] A.J.?
- Adrianne Jones, everybody
calls her A.J. at school.
Is it her?
- Come on, son, we need to ask you some,
right this way, come on.
Ask you some questions, over here.
- Hi, this is Linda Jones,
Adrianne Jones' mother.
I called before.
Yeah, hi.
Yes, I called missing persons
and I've called all around
and I can't find her anywhere.
Well when?
I'm getting a, okay, I'll hold.
Did you find her?
- Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry, Ms. Jones,
your daughter's dead.
(Linda breathing raggedly)
Ma'am, the reason we have
to do this now is that,
actually this is a homicide investigation.
- What does that mean?
- Your daughter's death
wasn't an accident, Ms. Jones.
She was shot.
- Not an accident, you mean--
- We need to find out who
did this so we have to--
- You mean my Adrianne was shot?
- Yes, ma'am.
And in a case like this it's important
that we act quickly, so.
- You mean deliberately murdered?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Oh God, (sobbing) oh my God.
Oh my God! (sobbing)
- Do you know where your
daughter was last night,
who she was with?
- Um, she was, um...
No one, she went to her job and
then she and I
went to work out together. (sobbing)
Oh God, are you sure? (sobbing)
- What time was that, ma'am?
- She was ironing her school clothes
at around 11,
I saw her.
- And you didn't see her go out again?
- Where was she? (crying)
- Did she talk to anybody?
Were there any phone calls?
- Phone calls.
Um, yeah, yeah.
Her boyfriend, Tracy Smith, he called her.
And we let her talk to him
even though it was after 10.
There was somebody else,
David, or,
I don't know, I don't remember.
The track team or
soemthin', I don't remember.
- But she didn't go out?
- It was a school night.
But this morning,
sometimes she gets up
and goes running in the morning,
and so when she didn't
come to breakfast I thought
maybe she went to school
early, but her books were here,
and her shoes.
She has two pair of tennis shoes
and one of 'em was missing.
And so I thought she was out running.
Then I found 'em in the dryer.
I used to always worry about her
gettin' hit by a car runnin'
in the dark like she did.
Oh God, somebody killed
my little girl. (sobbing)
Somebody killed my little girl. (sobbing)
- [Jason] Is Adrianne dead?
- You're Jason, aren't ya?
Your mother's gonna need you
to help her through this, Jason.
- I will.
I saw a pickup truck in the night.
- You did?
When was this?
- Last night about midnight.
- [Tom] Uh-huh.
- I couldn't sleep so then
I looked out my window
and I saw a white pickup
truck pullin' away.
- You sure?
- I think so.
- [Principal] I'd like
to have your attention
for a moment, please.
I have an announcement.
We have lost a student.
It is my sad task to inform you
that 10th grader Adrianne Jones is dead.
- [Student] Whoa.
- [Principal] This is a tragedy
we will all have to deal
with in our own way,
but she was one of Manning's own,
and we are all saddened by her loss.
I know how all of you would like--
- [Boy] Hey, Tommy.
- [Principal] There
will be a police inquiry
into her movements up
to the time of her death
and anyone who can offer any help
is encouraged to come forward.
Again, this is a shock for all of us
and a time of sadness and reflection.
(students chattering)
- I'm sorry, David.
Look, did you talk to A.J. last night?
- Did I talk to Adrianne?
No, why would I?
- Because someone said
she talked to a David
from the track team and
you were the only one
Coach Barr could think of.
- Wasn't me.
- Yeah, okay, I'm sorry to bother you.
It's just, this is so terrible
and they're gonna be talking
to everyone who knew her.
- That's okay, no problem.
That first day at school was the hardest,
to make it seem as though
nothing had happened
when we were really both scared as hell.
- [Woman On Loudspeaker]
5th period biology students
may now report
- Well, you are
- to the school cafeteria.
- on the track team
and your name is David.
- Yes, sir.
- 5th period biology students
- But you were
- can report
- dating her, right?
- to the school cafeteria.
- We weren't going
steady or anything, but.
- Okay, now, you called
her on Sunday night
and while you were talking to
her somebody called in, right?
- [Tracy] Mm-hm.
- You drive a pickup?
- No, sir.
Did the killer drive a pickup?
- [Carl] You know anyone
who drives a white pickup?
- No, sir.
- [Tom] Any idea who that was?
- She said it was some guy named Bryan.
- You sure it was Bryan?
- Bryan's what she told me.
- And you say you never dated Adrianne?
- No, sir, I'm engaged to be married.
- Little young to get married, aren't ya?
- No, sir, we already set the date.
Right after I graduate
from the Air Force Academy.
- [Tracy] Bryan's what she told me.
- Hopefully.
- [Tom] Not David?
- [Tracy] No, sir.
A friend of hers who was really upset.
That's all I know.
- Well, good luck.
You think of anything that
might help us, give us a call.
- Yes, sir.
- She told me I didn't know him,
so I didn't really pay it much mind.
She put me on hold
while she talked to him.
I didn't think she'd sneak out
to meet that guy or anything.
- [Tom] Mm-hm.
- But she wouldn't have
told me that exactly,
would she have?
- Tom, there's a Bryan
McMillen in her address book.
- Thank you.
(frenetic heavy metal music)
♪ This is again ♪
(engine rumbling)
- Bryan McMillen?
I'm Detective Baker from Tanner Police.
This is Detective Green from Manning.
We're workin' on a case.
We were hopin' you might
be able to help us out.
- Me?
Is this about Adrianne Jones?
- You don't mind answering
some questions, do you, Bryan?
- No, why not?
- Of course we could check
with the phone company,
but it would help us out if you remember.
- Well, see the only
thing is I don't remember.
- Bryan, you either called her
Sunday night or you didn't.
- Well, see I was drinkin' some,
and when you mix that with the
other pills I take sometimes
the next day it's like I
wasn't even there, ya know?
- What kind of pills
are you takin', Bryan?
- Well, a couple of things,
for depression and all.
- Did you go over there, Bryan?
Is it possible that you called her
and then maybe drove by there?
Even though you were
drinking, is that possible?
- It's possible.
I mean, I don't remember much.
- He don't remember much.
It's all on tape and I
offered him a lawyer.
- We don't even know if he's tracking.
The kid's on medication for God's sake.
- Now why were ya drinkin', then?
- I was just, ya know.
- I know, I know.
It's the end of the weekend,
you've got school tomorrow.
- Might as well get drunk,
bash some girl's head in with a hammer.
- [Bryan] I'd never hurt A.J.
- Nah, you wouldn't do that.
You're not that kind of a guy.
But if he is, he doesn't remember.
- It's not my fault I
don't remember, is it?
Look, ask anybody.
- Who?
Make us a list, Bryan.
You write the names of
everybody who called Adrianne
on Sunday night because they
were really, really upset
and depressed and had to see her.
- [Officer] Bryan, you're the
only one on that list there.
- But even if I went there
I wouldn't have killed her.
- But you don't remember, right?
So how do ya know?
- All right, Bryan, had you done it,
just supposing, all right, Bryan?
Where would ya leave the body?
What kind of place?
- I don't know.
Away from people,
somewhere remote, a field.
Away from houses.
(singing in foreign language)
- I feel so strange.
- Shock is what it is.
It's gonna be all right.
- I don't know.
- Come on, Diane, we're in the clear.
They got that Bryan McMillen kid.
- But he didn't do it.
- Don't worry about that.
If they can't prove he did
it, they gotta let him go.
- That's what I mean.
They're gonna know the real
killer's still out there
and they're never ever
gonna stop looking, never.
- Look, I know on TV they
always get the guy in the end,
but in real life there's a lot of cases
where they never figure out what happened.
- (sighs) Maybe.
Just need for some time to pass.
- I know, I know.
- God, David.
- You just gotta hang in there, okay?
- We've been very lucky so far,
but right now we need to tow the line.
- You're right and we will.
- Beautiful service.
- We have to become models
of good conduct from here on out.
- Hi.
And we were.
We both applied to military academies.
- [Military Officer] From
the United States Congress.
- [David] I got my letters first.
- [Military Officer] Dear David,
congratulations on your appointment
to the United States Air Force Academy.
You have demonstrated
excellence in academics,
athletics, civics, and community service.
You are the shining example
that we in government look to
when we envision the future
of this great country of ours.
The United States Military
is lucky to have you, David.
Good luck and God speed.
- [Woman] Jennifer, you
sit where I can see you.
- See what ends up happening?
(group chattering)
(upbeat Latin music)
(party goers chattering)
- Well, I can't stand it anymore.
Go in the house and get the letter.
- Okay.
- Go.
Carlos?
- (speaking in foreign
language), listen up.
We have an announcement to make.
- [Gloria] Listen, everyone.
- Pressed on the envelope
is United States Navy.
(guests applaud)
(guests cheer)
- Let her read it.
- Mama, I don't wanna read it out loud.
It's from Annapolis.
I got in!
(guests cheer)
(guests applaud)
I can't believe it, I'm
accepted at Annapolis.
I'm in the class of the year 2000.
Can you stand it?
- We're all so proud of you.
- Oh.
- And David, too.
- Oh, David, David, by the way,
David got into West Point
and the Air Force Academy.
(guests cheer)
(guests applaud)
- [Carl] Okay, Bryan, you
can see how this is going.
We need to find out
everything there is to know
about you and Adrianne.
- We were just friends.
I never hit anybody in
my life, not on purpose,
never mind bashin' their
head in with a hammer.
- How did you know her
head was bashed in, Bryan?
- What?
- You said her head was
bashed in with a hammer.
How'd you know that?
- Somebody said it.
- Nope, try again.
- It was on the news then.
- No, that was never
released to the media.
That little detail is something
very few people know about.
- But you knew.
Where's the hammer, Bryan.
- I didn't, somebody musta said it then,
because I didn't kill her!
- All right, that's enough
of this. Let's go, Bryan.
- Oh, hey, hey!
- Hey, wait.
- You gonna charge him?
Don't tell me what I can
do when it comes to my son.
- [Carl] Now, Mr. McMillen, I really think
we oughta talk about this.
- Now, I already told
your boss I may not be rich or a big shot,
but you mess with my son
and I'll come after you
or anybody else with everything I got,
cop or no cop, you hear me?
(crickets chirping)
- Clear.
(whistle blowing)
(upbeat marching band music)
- [Officer] Clear.
Police Department, we
have a search warrant.
Police Department!
Put your hands in the air.
(woman screams)
Do it now.
- [Officer] Put your hands in the air.
- [Officer] Police Department.
Bryan McMillen, you're under arrest.
- [Officer] Get out of
bed, get out of bed.
- Can I put on my pants?
- Get up, come on.
- This is a very rare
and distinctive honor
which brings credit not only to himself,
(Jimmy cries out)
but to his family
- Let go of me!
- and to Manning High as well.
And so, I present to you
our very own David Graham.
- Thank you.
(crowd cheers)
- Hands up.
- What's goin' on?
- [Officer] Get on the
ground, get on the ground.
(crowd cheering)
- [Officer] Handcuff him.
(crowd applauding)
- I'll never stop loving you, Diane.
- You better not, not
with what I've got on you.
- [Officer] You're under arrest
for the murder of Adrianne Jones.
(crowd cheering)
(crowd applauding)
(upbeat marching band music)
- [Officer] Get him up, come on.
(crowd cheering)
(camera clicks)
- What happened that night, A.J.?
- [Val] I hear they're
gonna hook Bryan McMillen
up to a lie detector.
- Yeah, like Forrest Gump
mighta been the killer.
- Now that's not kind, Larry.
- Well it's true.
Bryan's not exactly
arch criminal material.
- Yeah, everybody but
the police knows that.
- Yeah, they know it, too,
only now they're gonna have
to do somethin' about it
after they let old Bryan go.
- Yeah, it'll be real again, ya know?
- Yeah, she was a real girl
and now she's really gone.
- I still can't believe it.
I mean, she's dead.
She died right here.
- [Interviewer] Are you a
student at Manning High School?
- [Bryan] Yeah.
- [Interviewer] Do you know anyone
that owns a white pickup truck?
- Yeah, no.
- Were you born in 1972?
- [Bryan] No.
- Bryan.
- Let's get this straight.
Bryan is not a suspect
in this case
- Do you have any comments
- any longer.
- about your recent situation?
- [Man] Move over here, please.
- Bryan, Bryan!
- He was not released
for lack of evidence.
- What was your relationship
with Adrianne, Bryan?
- He was set free because he
- Mr. McMillen, what have--
- was arrested in error.
- Bryan look this way, please.
- Sir.
- Can we find out, Bryan.
- [Reporter] Can we get
a statement, please?
- His lawyer'll have
somethin' for ya later on,
but just give the kid a break, all right?
- [Reporter] Mr. McMillen,
one more question, please?
- Mr. McMillen.
- Sir, please.
(somber music)
- What can one say about
a life ended so soon?
She was here with us
and then she was gone.
It must be enough that
we celebrate her life,
accepting her in memory,
and trusting in our Lord Jesus Christ
to keep her in the hollow of his hand.
Larry.
(ominous music)
- [Carl] Tom, where are those files?
- Back here.
- [Carl] Good.
- Finnegan begin again.
- Well she knew him, so the killer's
gotta be in one of these folders here.
- We'll find him eventually.
Probably.
- Yeah. (chuckles)
There's one, Grady, first name Pete.
Let's see, he was in County General
that night with bad tonsils.
- Now that's an alibi.
- Un-huh.
Graham, first name David.
- Yeah, I remember him.
He was on the high school track team.
- Yeah, that's him,
interviewed him myself.
- [Tom] Graham, yeah he
was going to Annapolis or--
- No, that was his girlfriend.
This young man is goin'
to Colorado Springs.
- Air Force Academy?
Outstanding.
- Yeah, outstanding is
right, he's a good kid.
Read this.
National Merit Finalist, athlete,
ROTC battalion commander.
That young man is a recruiting poster.
- [Tom] Doesn't drive a pickup.
- No pick 'em up truck.
Ralph Buyers.
- I'm going home because
I actually have a life.
- [Carl] Hey Tom, we got
about 50 or 60 more here.
- [Tom] They'll all be
there Monday morning, Carl.
- Thanks for your help, Tom.
(romantic rock music)
(students chattering)
♪ Let's think about the good times, baby ♪
♪ Should let this moment last ♪
- [Val] Hey, David.
- Hey.
- You look very handsome.
- Y'all look nice.
- You look very pretty.
- Thank you.
- I'm taking her away from
you for a minute, David.
- I'll be right back.
- I'll be right here.
Something else.
- Enjoy your evening.
- Yeah, have a nice time.
- Okay, so here are the two latest.
Adrianne snuck out of the house
and went to this rave
party where she wound up
with some gang members.
Oh, and Jenny Taylor?
She heard that it was Colombians.
She knew too much.
But this is the one that
you're gonna die over.
You killed her with a baseball bat.
- Really?
- I mean, I couldn't believe Morgan Manlee
would actually say something like that,
but you were the one who told
me she didn't like you, so.
- Morgan Manlee said that?
Who was she talking to?
- I don't know, she was
talking to some girl,
but what she said was that
David was unfaithful to you.
You know, with her.
- She's so full of it.
Like David would ever be unfaithful to me.
- Yeah, but I mean, to go
and kill somebody over it?
- On top of which she was shot,
or did Morgan forget that little detail?
- Well yeah, but I mean her head was,
anyway, you have to be
some kind of lunatic
to do something like that.
- Well she wasn't saying
that she saw anything.
I mean, she wasn't talking about somebody
eyewitnessing anything, was she?
- No, it wasn't like that.
- All right then, she should
keep her stupid mouth shut.
- Okay.
(girls chattering)
- I'm tellin' ya.
- Yeah, it's party time.
So there's the famous Diane.
Well David may think she hung the moon,
but I'm not seein' it.
- Why, what's the matter with her?
- I don't know, she just strikes me
as a stuck up, you know what.
- You guys are not gonna
believe what I just heard.
There is a rumor goin' around
that David Graham's girlfriend killed A.J.
- What?
- You heard this
in the girl's room?
- I overheard her talking to someone,
her name is Diane something.
- Zamora, we know.
So give.
What'd she say?
- Well, they said that
David slept with A.J.
and Diane found out about it
and killed her with a baseball bat.
- What?
- Yeah, good, right.
I think that was right after they both
got abducted by space aliens.
(Val laughs)
- I still think it was Marguerite
if it was another girl.
After what she did to Lucy,
A.J. testifying against her and all.
- Yeah, but the police have already
been down that road, haven't they?
- [Perry] Who knows?
♪ Say goodbye ♪
- What?
- It's okay, it'll go away.
- She said you did it with a baseball bat?
Oh.
- David, look at me,
look at me, listen to
me. Listen to me now.
You were the one that told me this.
There is nothing we can do about the past.
What's done is done, isn't that right?
- [Student] Okay.
- Yes, that's right.
- Okay, all right then.
No matter what we do or say,
nothing can bring her back,
so the only thing left for us is we have
to live up to our potential.
- You're right.
We have to have the character to make it
through the bad to get
to the good in life.
- [Student] Is king!
(girl laughs)
- Okay.
- Come dance with me.
(students chattering)
♪ Here we are ♪
(Val laughs)
- [Student] Yeah, that's what she said.
- You're funny.
(slow romantic music)
- [Deejay] And now a special
song for Manning Memories 1996.
♪ No doubt for all time ♪
♪ The world will keep turning ♪
♪ The moon will shine ♪
- [Diane] We have such wonderful
opportunities, you and I.
- That would be the real crime,
for us to throw away our lives, too.
You're right.
- Of course I am.
What good would that do?
- I love you so much, Diane.
- David, I love you more
than I can ever tell you.
♪ Their babies to sleep ♪
♪ And I, darlin' I ♪
♪ I will ♪
♪ Still ♪
♪ Be fallin' ♪
- [David] I was totally in love with her
and I always will be.
♪ With you ♪
- I regret it now, for never did I imagine
the heartache it would cause my school,
my friends, Adrianne's
family, or even my community.
I guess I just shut it all out of my mind
in the instant when I convinced myself
that Diane was even worth murder.
♪ Your lovin' man ♪
♪ Is a man of his word ♪
♪ I'll be faithful ♪
- [Carl] So Logan hits this three-pointer
right at the buzzer
and the Golden Eagles win.
- Of course they do.
- [Carl] They always do.
- Mr. Baker?
- Wanna check
with the watch commander on that.
- [Officer] Hey, you know, you have to--
- Oh hey.
Hello, Ms. Jones.
- Hi.
- Didn't see you. (chuckles)
What can I do for you?
- I just came by to talk to somebody,
to see what was happenin'.
- Well I'm sorry, Ms. Jones.
We're still working on
it, but the truth is
it's a very difficult kind of case.
- You mean 'cause it's been so long?
- What I mean is when an adult is killed
it's easier to trace their
movements and contacts
and so on, but with a high school girl,
she literally came in contact
with hundreds of people,
so it's a huge investigative
job and we're doin' the best--
- So are you makin' any headway?
- Ma'am, I'd like to be more optimistic,
but the truth is we're
not much further along.
- Don't stop tryin', okay?
- We'll keep trying.
We will.
- Ya know, I've taken to
wearin' somethin' of hers,
every day somethin' belonged to her.
This was hers.
- It's very pretty.
- Oh, I still,
when the door slams I look up.
I know she's not comin'
home, but I still...
- Yes, ma'am.
- Don't stop trying.
- Bye, thanks for comin'.
- I'll be home in July.
- Take care.
- Take care of yourself.
- All right.
You be good now, okay?
- I will. I'm gonna miss you so much.
- I'll miss you, too.
- Greenish brown female sheep.
- Me, too.
- [Man] Say hi to Nancy for me.
- Oh God, please just go, I'm dyin'.
- [Woman] Bye.
Call when you get there.
- Are you okay?
- Oh Mama, I just have
this terrible feelin'.
- It will get better.
A few days and then you'll
be off on your own adventure.
- No, I mean I just have this awful sense
that everything is ending.
- Nothing is ending.
It's all beginning for you, and for David.
- I'm so afraid.
- It's going to be good
for you, you'll see.
Even this separation.
I know you don't believe me,
it's going to do you good
to spend a little time
apart from each other.
- You don't know what
you're talkin' about.
- Is the world coming to an end again?
- No, she's sad to say goodbye
but something else, too.
- Eh, don't worry. Give her
a couple of days in Annapolis
and everything will be fine, you watch.
(dramatic drum music)
- I know you've shown promise
or you wouldn't be here,
but if any one of you
thinks that the honor code
does not apply to him or her,
then let me save you some heartache.
Leave now.
Get up and walk away.
You won't like it here.
And frankly, we don't want you here.
- [Officer] Hey, that's roughing.
Move, move.
- [Commander] That's right, we
take the honor code seriously
and I tell you this
from my own experience.
If you have no honor,
- [Officer] Let's go, let's go!
- [Commander] you have nothing.
You will abide by the code
while you are at Annapolis.
You will abide by the code as
long as you wear the uniform.
It takes a very special individual
to wear the uniform of a naval officer.
And if you are such a
person, we welcome you.
If not, you will surely come to ruin.
You can be declared
officers by act of Congress,
but honor can only come from within.
(somber trumpet music)
(button clattering)
(Diane breathing raggedly)
- I just had to tell somebody.
If David were here--
- I understand, I guess.
- I couldn't live with such
a terrible secret anymore,
I'm so sorry.
- Look, don't worry, Diane.
I won't tell anyone.
Your secret's safe with me.
- [David] Diane's
beautiful eyes have always
played the strings of
my heart effortlessly.
I couldn't imagine life without her.
Not for a second did I wanna lose her.
- Yeah, well, my boyfriend's
goin' to Boston University.
- [Gail] That's a good school.
- Yeah, yeah.
He swore he wouldn't date anybody else,
but I kinda think he will.
Oh, he may feel guilty about
it, but he'll go out, I'm sure.
- Why do men find it so
difficult to be faithful?
- [Diane] David won't be cheatin' on me.
- Oh sure, why not?
Because he said so?
- No, because we have a secret
that we have to take to the grave.
- Come on.
I can't think of anything
that's bad enough
to make a man keep his hands to himself
once he's had a couple of beers.
There was this once--
- So what is it?
What happened?
- [Gail] Yeah, what did he do?
- [Annette] Yeah, what'd
ya do, kill for each other?
- Yes.
- Get outta here.
- He was unfaithful
with this girl back home
and I wanted her dead so he did it.
I saw him do it.
- And she died?
- [Diane] Oh yeah.
He shot her twice, I was there.
(somber music)
- [Officer] Roll in.
Right, left.
(soft ominous music)
- [Carl] State your name, please.
- Diane Zamora.
- Okay, Diane, you have been advised
of your legal rights, is that correct?
Your rights to an attorney and so on?
- Yes, sir.
- Now, what can you tell us
about the murder of Adrianne Jones?
- (grunts) Nothing, sir.
- [Officer] Right, left, right.
- Diane, we came a long way.
We know what you told you
roommates, your fellow cadets.
- Oh, I'm sorry about that, sir,
but see, that was just girl talk.
I was trying to impress my classmates
and I just, I made some stuff up just,
well I don't know why.
- So your statement now is
that what you told them isn't true.
- Yes, sir.
- Diane, according to your roommates,
your boyfriend David shot Adrianne twice.
- That's not true.
- [Carl] And you have no idea who did.
- No, sir.
- Diane, if you're hiding
something, anything,
the only way you can help
yourself out is to talk to us.
- Sir, I was very foolish
to say the things I did,
but it wasn't true, none of it.
I knew about the Jones girl getting killed
and everything so naturally
that's what came into my mind,
but it was just talk, honest.
- It's just for a few
days until this business
gets cleared up.
- He on the field right now?
- Yes, sir.
- I believe so, yes.
- Here are your orders.
You go home to Texas and you
rest up after plebe summer.
Think of it as a furlough.
- Yes, sir.
- Very well.
The duty van'll give you
a lift to the airport.
That's all, Zamora, dismissed.
- Aye aye, sir.
- [Officer] You've got
about another 18 minutes.
(somber music)
- What is the first name that
Adrianne's mother gave us?
David from cross country.
- Yeah, but he's not the type.
We both said so.
- What is the type?
- (sighs) We dropped the ball on this.
- He's a recruiting poster,
so I don't put him on a polygraph.
- Let's go do that.
- No, first we go back to Manning.
There's gotta be somebody
that knows somethin'
about those two.
- [Announcer] At this time, we'd like to
Flight 151 to Birmingham non-stop.
Please advise our
- Hi.
- first class passengers,
- What can I do for you
- platinum circle members,
- Midshipman Zamora?
- and passengers--
- Well, I have
these travel orders.
- All right.
Looks like that's gonna take
you into Dallas-Fort Worth
and the next flight is--
- Yeah, I know, I need
to make a stop first
in Colorado Springs.
- [Clerk] Colorado Springs?
- [Diane] Mm-hm.
- That's Air Force country, isn't it?
- Yeah, my fiance's at the academy.
- Thought the Air Force and
the Navy were big rivals.
- Well, I plan to transfer my
commission after I graduate.
We're both gonna be fliers.
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
- Well, in that case,
let's see if we can't find you a plane.
- Great.
Could you just tell him
that Diane will be there
as planned, the plane's leavin' on time?
And one more thing,
just put greenish brown female sheep.
That's right.
Now he'll know what it means.
Okay, thank you very much.
- Yeah, but did they believe you?
- I don't know, that's not the point.
I was very firm about it.
- You know what, they're just gonna
keep comin' at us from now on.
(Diane sighs)
- Well, if they had any hard evidence,
they would've brought it with them, right?
- I don't know, that's what they do.
They just keep comin' on and on.
(soft ominous music)
- [Diane] Look, the important thing
is for us to stick together.
- Yeah, you're right.
- United we stand,
that's what you told me.
- God, I missed you so much.
(camera clicks)
- [Photographer] One
minute, I'll be right back.
- Okay.
- The thing that bothers
me is that I never thought
they'd run out and tell on me
without talking to me first.
I mean, what kind of honor code is that?
- They should have as fellow officers--
- As fellow officers,
they had the obligation
to confront me with
their suspicions first.
- That's right, they did.
- They're the ones that
broke the code, not me.
- You're right, they
shoulda come to you first.
- Just put this behind you.
- I didn't know what to do.
Nobody's ever asked me
about this until now.
- What time was it?
- I don't even know, I was asleep.
- Okay, so you were asleep.
What made you wake up?
- Well,
(knuckles tapping)
he knocked on my window.
- I need to come in for a minute,
all right?
- Okay.
(Diane gasps)
- [Ben] I thought they must've been
in a car wreck or something.
- Listen to me, you're my
best friend, all right?
This never happened.
We were never here tonight.
We never came in that window, understand?
- Okay.
- Okay, good.
- You guys all right?
- Listen,
don't ask any questions.
You are my friend, this never happened.
Okay, okay?
- I'm not gonna question ya.
If you need a place to stay,
you got one right here,
you know that.
(Diane crying)
- What happened next?
- Well, I let 'em in.
David wanted some clothes.
- On the left!
- If you need a place to stay,
you know you got one right
here, man, you know that.
- We need to borrow some clothes, okay?
Oh, I'm gonna be sick. (coughing)
Oh God.
(camera clicks)
- [Photographer] Hang on, one second.
- They're gonna come at you
with everything they have now.
- Don't worry about me.
- I'm not worried.
You're the most disciplined
man I've ever met.
God, I love you.
- I love you so much.
- And I always will no matter what.
- [Tom] What happened
to the other clothes,
the ones they took off?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
They took 'em with 'em I guess.
I looked in on 'em at one point
because I heard 'em, like, crying.
I left 'em alone and then
when I went back later
they were gone.
And I did talk to David
a couple days later
and he said that I shouldn't say anything
to anybody ever and he wouldn't tell me
what happened, so.
I don't know.
(camera clicks)
- We'll get through this, won't we?
- Of course we will and
we'll be together forever.
- Forever and ever.
- That's nice.
(camera clicks)
(ominous music)
- You said that before,
but you were the only David
on the cross country team, weren't ya?
- Sir, I never said I didn't know A.J.,
but I didn't kill her.
- Says he didn't kill her.
- Mm-hm.
Personally, I believe you, David.
Why don't you let us give you a polygraph,
we can wrap this whole thing up.
- Polygraph?
- You don't have to, but
it would help us out.
We can eliminate you
as a suspect, move on,
focus on the next name
on the list, ya know?
- I don't know.
- Does the Air Force have
any objection to a polygraph?
- No, no objections.
Graham?
- Sir, I have no objections.
- Good, that's good.
- [Interviewer] Were you
having a relationship
with Adrianna Jones?
- [David] No.
- [Interviewer] Did you
kill Adrianna Jones?
- No.
- David, I want you to listen to me.
We know you did it, the
machine told us that.
- What?
What do you mean?
What did it say?
- We know you killed Adrianne.
- It's not just the polygraph.
We talked to your friend
Ben about that night.
He gave you up.
- He told us about the
knock on the window,
the bloody clothes, you getting sick,
you and Diane lying down
together and crying.
He told us everything, David.
- [Tom] We know it was you.
- It's your duty to tell the truth, David.
It's a matter of honor.
- I,
I did it.
- That's better.
Just start with that.
Make a chronology.
Tell us what happened when, in what order.
You're gonna feel a lot better
when this is over, believe me.
- If ya have a typewriter
it'll make things
move faster for both of us.
- Okay, I'll get ya what you need.
(computer keys clicking)
- Diane's beautiful eyes have always
played the strings of
my heart effortlessly.
I couldn't imagine life without her.
Not for a second did I wanna lose her.
I thought long and hard about
how to carry out the crime.
I was stupid, but I was in love.
Some of the plan worked, some did not.
The plan was to call
Adrianne and convince her
to come out to my car.
That worked.
A.J. it's me, David Graham.
Hey, look, I have to talk to you.
Can I see you?
Can you get outta your house
for a few minutes later on tonight?
Please, A.J., this is
real important, all right?
Who was that?
So look, can you come tonight?
Midnight.
Please, A.J., this is real
important to me, all right?
I'm all twisted up inside
and I don't know what to do
and you're the only one
who can help me, all right.
So you'll be there?
Great.
Okay.
(soft suspenseful music)
The plan was to drive her
out near Joe Pool Lake.
That worked.
- [Adrianne] So where are we goin'?
- Just up the road a piece.
I figured we should be alone.
- I can't go far, though.
- No, no.
- My folks caught me
sneakin' out one time before
and they fixed the screen
so I couldn't get back in.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, my daddy nailed
my bedroom window shut
so I couldn't sneak out.
So what's goin' on with you?
- The plan was to,
(computer keys clicking)
this is not easy for me to confess,
break her young neck and sink
her to the bottom of the lake
with the weights that ended
up being hit into her head.
That didn't work.
(soft ominous music)
- So what is it?
- Come here.
- What?
- Just come here.
(Adrianne cries out)
Come here.
- [Adrianne] What are you doing?
- Stop!
- Let go of me.
- Stop.
- What are you doing?
Let go!
What is wrong with you?
Let go of me.
- Diane, help me hold her.
- Oh my God.
- Diane, help me.
(Adrianne cries out)
You hold her.
- [Adrianne] What are you doing?
- [David] Get her!
(Adrianne screaming)
- [Adrianne] Get away now!
- [David] Come on.
I can't get her neck.
We realized that it was either her or us.
Diane struck her in the back of the head
with one of the weights while I held her.
- Remember.
(skull crunching)
(David grunts)
(Adrianne whimpers)
- [Adrianne] Get off me. (crying)
Oh my God. (whimpering)
- [David] Come on, hold her.
- Come on.
- Let me go.
Help me.
Let me go.
Let me go. (whimpering)
- (grunting) You didn't die.
Never mind.
(Adrianne whimpering)
(David grunting)
Adrianne somehow crawled
through the window,
and to our horror, ran off.
She ran into a nearby field and collapsed.
I wanted to just jump in and drive off.
We were both shaking and even surprised
by the nature of our actions.
Neither Diane or myself
were ever violent people.
(Adrianne grunting)
I was panicky and just grabbed
the nine miller Makarov to follow.
In that short instant I knew
I wouldn't leave the key
witness to our crime alive.
It was either her or us.
So I just pointed and shot.
(gun fires)
I fired again
and ran to the car.
(gun fires)
I was very confused and scared.
- [Diane] I love you.
- I love you.
- Oh David, we shouldn't have done that.
- [David] I thought, nice
time to tell me. (chuckles)
I just wanted it to be a dream.
I wanted to be able to
drive Adrianne back home,
go to sleep, and wake
up back on December 3rd,
free to make my decisions all over again.
Diane was constantly
depressed from the guilt.
She was also scared I'd be arrested.
Really didn't matter, however,
what any police or detectives found.
What happened was over.
Adrianne was gone and I was responsible.
And it wasn't going away.
(computer beeps)
(printer clacking)
- Where's the gun, David?
- My house.
I wrapped it in a shirt
and I hid it there.
- Need you to sign this.
I'll get moving on a warrant.
- [Carl] Okay, David, we're goin' nextdoor
so let's put these on.
- Those are for me?
- Yes, they are.
(handcuffs clicking)
Ya did kill a girl, ya know.
- They're bringing your
boyfriend down from Colorado.
He'll be on a different
floor, but I could probably
get a message to him.
Anything you want me to tell him?
- Just tell him greenish
brown female sheep.
- What's that all about?
- It's our code.
Greenish brown is olive
and female sheep is a ewe.
Olive ewe.
- [Guard] Olive ewe?
- I love you.
(reporters shouting)
(siren beeping)
- [Officer] Come on, ma'am.
(officers chattering)
- [Officer] Stay back.
- [Officer] Back it up, back it up.
(reporters and officers chattering)
- No questions, please, there'll be
official statement later day.
- Yes, sir.
- David, David!
- Later.
- David!
- [Reporter] Hey, David.
David, is there anything
you'd like to say to Diane?
- I love you.
- Back up.
Back it up.
Sir, back up.
- Made you crack?
(camera clicks)
(ominous music)
(Linda sobbing)
(somber orchestral music)
(Multicom Jingle)