Now a certain man was sick,
named Lazarus of Bethany.
The town of Mary and her
sister Martha.
It was that Mary which anointed
the Lord with ointment
and wiped his feet
with her hair.
who's brother Lazarus was sick.
Therefore his sister sent unto
Him saying, Lord, behold!
He whom Thou loveth is sick,
for he hath been dead four days.
Jesus sayeth unto her, Said I
not unto thee,
that if thou wouldst believe,
thou should see
the glory of God?
But, I think we all have an
understanding that the Bible is
a book of miracles.
It revolves around them.
In a way, miracles are what make
us follow this Book,
and dedicate our lives to
its teachings.
You look like a man who enjoys
a good story.
You ever hear the one about
Lazarus?
They say Jesus Christ performed
quite a few miracles
when He walked the earth.
People in my congregation
always took to debate about
the greatest miracle.
Everybody always had a
different answer.
For me though?
The greatest miracle?
The power of life over death.
Resurrection.
It's beautiful.
Turn it over.
Isn't there a rule against
carving into something holy?
You know, I was going to
mention that on Sunday.
Do believe I'll feel a might
bit conflicted standing in
front of all those people.
Taking James into town
next time I head in.
Saw something at the general
store he might like.
Papa! There's horses outside!
What's your business
in these parts, Isaiah?
Jakob and I are just
lookingfor a place
to rest for the evening,
Preacher.
Nothing more.
Evening ma'am.
You like it boy?
Tell ya, your pa let's us
have a place to stay for
the night, I might just let
you have a go with her tomo--
Isabelle. James.
Go inside now.
If it's money you want
that's fine. But my fam
Relax.
We don't want your money.
And we ain't gonna do nothing
to that pretty wife of yours.
Unless your name is
Reynolds we ain't got--
What's that about Reynolds?
There are some things in life
that are better left unanswered.
The answer to that question
is one of those things.
Now we sitting here too much
longer, we might be needing
something more than
a place to rest.
You can shack up in the barn
for the evening.
Should be able to find some wood
in there for a fire.
l be in there in the morning to
tend to the cows.
We'll leave everything
just like we found it.
Least we can do for the
hospitality, Preacher.
Would you like to start us off?
Let's let James do it tonight.
I think he's old enough. How
bout you?
Of course he is.
Well partner? What do you say?
We thank you Lord for the meal
you've laid out before us.
For the food you give us
everyday.
Thank you for the family
you've given us.
Thank you for my mama and
my papa.
Now what the hell do
you think?!
What in the name of Jesus
Goddamn Christ
was going through that piss
ant ol' mind
of the great philospher
Jakob Bannon?!
No guesses?
Shit. I ain't got one neither.
WHAT DO I PAY YOU FOR, JAKOB?!
To gossip with the local
town converter?
Isa, I don't think--
YOU'RE GODDAMNED RIGHT
YOU DON'T THINK!
I don't think it'll lead
to nothing.
What's that about Reynolds?
That's what he said before
God and all of us.
But ... you don't think
it'll lead to nothing.
Well, hell! Just consider
me assuaged,
if you don't think it'll
lead to nothing!
Isa, you're just about to push
me to a place you don't want
to see me go to.
You ain't never had the sand
to do nothing Jakob.
You never did!
You know that ain't
the truth.
Like hell it ain't.
If you hadn't let that
son of a bitch Reynolds
take a chunk out of you,
we'd be clear out of town
by now!
C'mon you yellow
son of a bitch!
Isaiah, you say one
more word and I will
put you in the dirt!
No sign of 'em?
Last we saw of them was
after church on Sunday.
Ain't hardly nobody's
been up this way anymore.
Not even traders.
Hey Marshal. Anyone checked
with ol' Doc Morris?
He might've sent them up
to Burnham's Hope to see
that big doctor up there.
Mornng Marshal. Happen to
have seen Isaiah Bannon around?
Problems with your flock?
There's always a few
wolves in the mix.
I don't know any wolves who
steal from the collection plate.
ll, Marshal, the Lord will judge
the saints and sinners alike.
I'll leave that up to him.
Fair enough.
You got a moment?
Sure.
That's a fine looking
horse you got there.
What's his name?
Jack.
That's a good strong name.
Now you think Jack might
like some candy?
When was the last time you saw
Marcus or Talbicia Reynolds?
Guess that'd be Sunday. Saw
Talb and the little girl
at church.
Everything okay?
Well nobody's seen 'em since.
Which wouldn't be unusual
for most folks, but this is
Talbicia we're talking about.
You can set your clock by her
trips to town.
Especially since Marcus
has been gone.
I can go down to the
house and chec-
Already been there.
It's covered in blood.
Like a goddamn-
Like someone gutted a
pig in there.
Only no bodies.
Alive or otherwise.
When was this?
Well I was over there
this morning. Why?
Last night Jakob and Isaiah
came to our home.
Needed a place to stay.
I can't say I was happy
about it to begin with
but had I known-
No, I understand.
In any case, Jakob said
something about Reynolds.
Isaiah wanted to keep it
quiet.
Any guesses where they
might be heading?
Not a clue.
Maybe low country.
Maybe. Or on the
dodge in the outskirts.
They couldn't get very far with
Jakob being the way he was.
His arm was in bad way.
You really think they
could have done something
like this to the Reynolds?
What about the-
Well. Thanks for your
help, Preacher.
Now you take good care
of Jack, young man.
Break him in good!
Isabelle: What's the word
in town?
There's plenty of words.
None of them any good.
Edwards said Marcus and Talbicia
hadn't been seen in days.
What about the girl?
folding laundry.
No sign of her.
No sign of anyone.
Just the aftermath.
James asked about
her at all?
Not so far. I don't think he
knows anythings happened yet.
Good.
You had no idea what they'd
done. Couldn't have.
You were just doing what
you thought was right.
Yeah.
But I know what sort of men
they are.
You turning them men away?
As injured as Jackob was?
Would have made you no different
than those who walked before
the Samaritan.
I'm sure glad you're better at
orating verses than you are at
folding laundry.
Otherwise we'd be in trouble.
Yeah, well, I sure am glad
you're better at
folding laundry than you are
at milking cows. Otherwise...
we'd be out of milk and wearing
wrinkly pants.
Keep pressure here. I'll
go get the doctor!
You have to take him
otherwise--
If I take him with me the ride
will kill him worse than
if he stays!
I swear I'll be back.
I swear he's going to be
alright.
You said he was attacked?
Woman: Yes Doctor Morris.
Liked to have taken
his hand clean
off if I hadn't been there.
Doctor Morris! It's James!
He's injured.
Where is he?
What happened?
Back at the house.
Please Doctor Morris ...
He was attacked! There's
blood all over him!
Please, you've got to help
him--you've got to help him!
I want you to keep this wrapped
up tight. Come back tomorrow.
If you notice anything different
about this--odor, discoloration
anything--you make sure you
come back--
Isaiah!
Tend to my boy.
Yes sir.
Isaiah!
I've got
this under control!
Bannon!
I've got this under control!
BANNON!
Lower your rifle!
You don't want
to be doing this!
Look at me you
son of a bitch!
Edwards:Nooooo!
I was seventeen, in
Virginia. Waiting to enlist.
I was young and
the pay was good.
Day comes that I'm
going to do it. I'm going
to sign that paper,
and I get crippled ill.
But I'll be damned if I don't
drag myself down there anyway.
And I see this little wisp of
a lady, taking two goats
to market, just being
dragged all over creation.
Walked over to give her a
hand, and she spoke to me...
Suddenly the army didn't
seem all that appealing anymore.
Isabelle taught me my way.
Said I was too sick to
enlist, and ...
Anyway, my place wasn't
fighting men on the frontier.
It was guiding spirits through
the wilderness.
Never saw any of that coming.
Always been a fault of mine.
Not to see things coming.
You saw what he did!
You were standing right there!
Yes, I saw that.
There were children who
saw him gun a man down
right there on the street.
I understsand that.
Well then you also understand
that we've got rights!
Rights?
That's right, Marshal
Edwards. Rights!
And that man you have locked
up in there committed
an act of violence! An act that
goes against the entire
foundation of his life!
And we know he let let
them stay on his land,
not but a day ago,
right after they slaughtered
the Reynoldses,
and then he guns one of
them down in the street
right out in front of God
and all the rest of us watching!
And if we don't do something
about it, God in Heaven will!
That's right Marshal! And
I think given the circumstances
his town is owed some justice!
And we owe it to God
in Heaven above to--
We owe it to God?
Let me make this clear.
If so much as one man steps in
that building without me
granting it, the only person
you're gonna be owing
is the doctor for pulling
lead out of your gut.
Now I'm going to go out
and check on this man's wife.
And I'm going to find out
more about what happened.
And when I get back,
there better be a prisoner
in that cell.
Do I make myself clear?
Isabelle?
Oh God. What happened?
What's going on? Where's
James? Where's Isabelle?
Sorry, Preacher.
HELP!
Preacher!
Goddamnit if you're not
going to use that thing
then give it to me!
What about the town?
What about these people?
These people are
already dead.
All we could do
was run.
We rode all night and all day.
Highland Mills was Hell
reaching out for us.
Never really sat right with me,
what happened to
all those people.
Something on your
mind, Preacher?
Hell of a night.
I can't remember the last time
I sat down and enjoyed it.
The sounds. The stars.
Hell, now I'm in bed by
sundown and up before sunrise.
Ain't I supposed to be getting
something out of that?
Are you healthy,
wealthy or wise?
Still wearing this
badge, ain't I?
Probably no.
On all counts.
You know there was a lynching
one night back in town when
I was deputy?
Night like this, I guess.
Negro boy. Fifteen. Sixteen.
People said he'd been caught
stealing.
Chicken here. Some lumber there.
Shit, he'd probably take a pie
off a window sill if you left
it there.
I believed there was no
reasoning with these people.
Nothing could be said.
I was too wrapped up in holding
a job. Too green.
Too weak to push my gut into
doing anything.
Highland Mills was already
dead, Preacher.
They were ready to be
your judge and jury without
a moment's hesitation.
Thought that would fix the
situation.
Nothing you or I could have done
short of killing them ourselves.
Puts a mighty hurt on the
brain when you realize what a
person will do when they
believe in something.
Get some rest.
We got a ways to go tomorrow.
I don't recall when it's been so
cool this time of year, do you?
My boy, James-my son.
This was always one of our
favorite times.
We'd go walking out in those
woods and just kinda...
marvel at everything.
I was always struck when I saw
a herd of deer grazing. Such...
graceful animals.
Always put a hurt in my head
when it came time to kill one,
but I guess God put animals in
Eden for a reason.
Don't supposed Adam could
eat dirt all day.
James was funny out in those
woods.
Wintertime, he always liked...
watching his breath
on the cold air.
He'd take these...
big breaths, and just keep
blowing out 'til he was blue
in the face, just so he could
see it rising.
Kids'll fascinate you like
that, you know?
Absolutely amazed by the
smallest little things.
That was his purpose.
Maybe God made kids that way
so we'd appreciate the
simple things.
We grow old.
We lose faith.
Not James.
How 'bout you?
Got any kids?
That's a nasty hurt
you got there.
Got a long way to
Burnham's Hope, but...
we could probably pack
you along,
might be a doc down there
who can patch you up.
What's your name?
Yeah...
I thought you might say that.
Preacher!
Jesus himself would
have been proud of that last
shot, Preacher.
Hell of a miracle right there.
They teach that kinda thing-
You planting something?
These men deserved
to be buried.
Now I have seen and heard
some crazy shit in my time,
up to and including a man of God
sliding across the ground,
grabbing a rifle and killing
two people with one shot.
But I'll be goddamned if
I am going to bury four of
those cocksuckers who
tried to rip my face off.
Five.
Five?
There's another one just
up over the hill.
I delivered him a
while ago.
Oh, so that's what-
You mean while I was
here struggling with
this bastard here, you
were delivering a sermon
to one of them out
in the woods?
No matter how far we
ran, no matter where we hid,
there was no getting away.
Behind your brain you'd always
hear the moans, the flood of
suffering and pain.
I am the resurrection and
the life.
He that liveth and believeth in
Me, though he were dead,
yet shall he live.
And whosoever liveth
and believeth in Me
shall never die.
FIttin' words.
Course, the last person
to say those words
brought a man back
from the dead.
Sure you want to be
standing next to that
sumbitch while you're
speaking them?
Never knew you were
into the Word.
Got no practical use
for what's between
chapters one and five
hundred in that book of yours.
I just always enjoyed
a good story.
And a carpenter's son bringin'
a man back to life is
damn near top of the list.
Ever wonder why
I never went?
What's that?
To church.
Why I never went to church.
Just figured it had something
to do with my sermons.
You're a damn fine orator,
don't sell yourself short.
Well, some people just take
a while to find their way in.
Thought you'd come around at
some point or another.
Hope you're a man of
patience.
You ever do something
as a kid in school
something you weren't supposed
to do, and you got caught?
All the time. I was a
hellspawn as a kid.
You remember how the
teacher would call you out to
the head of the class, and
you'd have to stand there while
she whipped the fire out of your
ass in front of all the
other kids?
I seem to recollect
something like that, yes.
See, for me, it wasn't the
whippin' that hurt.
It was knowin' that I was
going to turn around and
do the same shit again, and
have to go through that
same beatin'.
That's what I couldn't take,
sitting there in that desk.
Figured sitting in that pew,
might as well be chaffing my
ass with the teacher's paddle
every day for the rest
of my life.
Besides, I got my own
temple.
Think this is
Revelation? Dead rising?
Entertain me on this.
Fairly certain
we're short a couple
horsemen, but I don't
know. Maybe it is.
So if it is, don't you think
it's mighty odd that you're
still here?
Did you just oversleep
the Rapture?
All I know is what we're
seeing out there ain't alive,
and it ain't exactly dead.
How do you reckon
they ain't dead?
I reckon that by the fact that
they still run around and eat
just like normal folks.
Only in this case, it's the
normal folks they like to eat.
They're stuck in a hell of their
own. They can't pass on.
They can't be judged.
By who? You?
By the one who'll judge
the quick and the dead.
And these things-these people-
are neither one of those.
Until we deliver them,
they can't be judged.
So that's why there's all
that whispering and prayin'?
Here I thought you was just
payin' your respects and sayin'
sweet nothings, but here
you are, a fine instrument
of God, delivering them!
Goddamnit we got
fast ones now!
Looks like one of our
boys was a farmer.
Thought you might like
an early birthday present.
♪Orchestral Music
I ll go in.
I think you need
to see this.
I was going to say
the same thing.
Looks like the whole
congregation held out
here for a while.
Must've put up
quite a fight.
Well, thank Jesus
for that!
I shit you
not. Catfish Pete comes
bursting through those doors,
naked as a jaybird, all covered
in hay. He sets that bottle
of moonshine down
on the table and all he says is,
"I'm going to wait till whiskey
dries off," and passes out!
Got up and gone before I
was even able to wake up.
And I haven't seen that
bastard since!
I swear to you, in all
my born days...
I wonder what ever
happened to him?
Same thing that will
happen to us, by and by.
What with us taking all
those guns and rags off
of 'em everyday.
We're bound to have
the sickness in us.
No. You have to get
bit.
Oh, now what
makes you so sure?
We've tussled with them.
I've buried them.
Only ones I've known
turn are those bitten.
Like who?
Present?
Anniversary of when
we first met.
That so?
Twelve years ago. Middle of
the street in Burnham's Hope.
Well, once we find a proper bed
and a fittin' plan of action,
I would very much like to see
that street where the hellion
became the preacher.
Well, anyway I
Hold on! It's alive.
Think you might be able
to make good use of a
stiff drink, Preacher.
I'm considering it.
Wake up Padre!
Looks like
your kind!
Goddamnit do something!
Do something,
goddamnit!
Get out!
NOW!
Didn't think
you had it in you.
I don't.
Three shots to feed
them maggots.
That's not enough to last
two hours out here
much less two weeks.
Last I recall,
two and three made five.
I like to save the
extra, just in case.
You really plan to do that?
I plan to do what
I have to do, Preacher.
Whether that means eating a
bullet so I don't turn into
one them sons of bitches,
or you ponying it up
and doing it for me.
And that's why we
only have three.
Easy! Easy!
Oh
God my boy!
What
happened?
Oh god-
They just attacked us.
They just...they didn't want
any money or food or
anything...they just...
bit him all over!
My boy...
IAN!
My boy!
Ian! Oh god, my boy!
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
No! Wait!
Why?!
Because it had
to be done!
It had to be done?!
He was a human being!
As soon as he saw his
son's blood on that tarp,
there was no difference between
him and what's out there!
He'd a killed both of
us if he had the chance!
I did what I had to do.
What you had to do?
Just like the people
who lynched that boy?
Remember?
I goddamn remember that
very well.
You remember those pieces
of shit in that barn?
You remember burning
them all to Hell?
Think they had a pa who
would have done anything to
keep them from being killed?!
And I will pretty well
remember this as long
as I breathe.
But you can get down off
of your pulpit right now.
Cause I don't want none
of your sermons about
what's right, and
what's wrong.
Because there ain't no
goddamn Bible verses,
and no goddamn sermon,
that's going to change
the fact that we're out
in the middle of
this goddamn woods
with a handful of shot
and hundreds of those
beings out there
who don't care about
right and wrong!
These people weathered the
storm.
They're not the
only ones.
We're going to meet
them soon.
How much further?
I don't know.
But when we get there, I'll
have that drink with you.
♪Orchestral Music
I reckon going from sheriff
to marshal's a lot like
busting a bronco.
Kick the fire and piss
out of you until
you're almost docile.
Free of any
dangerous notions.
Sounds about
like seminary.
Well, young shithead that
I was, I had all the balls
but none of the methods.
Don't reckon you all
are missionaries.
So much for that drink.
♪Orchestral Music
Searched 'em
thorough, sir; no bites.
Their horses are out with
the others.
Well, ain't that just
screaming.
Boys, you can go back
to your posts.
After you bring our
guests some libations, that is.
Gentlemen.
Your hospitality is
most appreciated, Mr...
Samuel Beard.
Well, thank you,
Mr. Beard.
We do appreciate the
kindness, Mr. Beard.
If it wouldn't put you out,
we'd like to bring
our horses in.
Well, I'm afraid reality
keeps check on our hospitality.
We keep all livestock outside
these walls.
figured they'll make good
bait if those savagerous
bastards ever show up
en masse.
Gives us some time
to reinforce the gates.
We've been finding it ain't
exactly the horses they
enjoy eating.
You'd be amazed at these
desperate times.
Even for those things.
So tell me. What a...what brings
a sinbuster and a lawman
way out here to
the edge of chaos?
Just passing through.
We left Highland Mills just
before harvest.
Trying to get to Burnham's
Hope, that's all.
Just got a little
sidetracked, you could say.
We were hoping we might
rest here a day or two
if that wouldn't trouble
you or your men.
Ha!
I tell you what I'll do,
gentlemen.
I can give you a place to
sleep on.
Might even steal a warm meal if
you catch someone snoozing.
That's a whole hell of a lot
more than you're going to find
at Burnham's Hope.
How's that?
A week ago, I had ten scouts
under my command.
Sent four of them up that way.
This week, I have six scouts.
You can scratch
Burnham's Hope off the map.
What about the rest
of your unit?
How many men do
you have here?
Unit?
We...we found some of the things
left behind very useful in
keeping a semblence of
order around here.
The uniform goes a
long way, don't it?
Left behind. You mean
ther army's gone?
What was left of
it is, at least.
Most of the unit
been gone quite a spell
when we found this place.
Comanche hunt.
My money is on those
filthy cockholsters
for starting' this mess.
More to the point,
the army never came back.
When this whole shit
storm started,
the fellas that were left
either ran into the woods
or stayed here and joined us.
Who's us?
Farmers. Miners. Stragglers.
Gamblers. Whores...anybody who,
wanted a place to rest, and
came across our humble doorstep.
Even the occasional padre.
Before long, we had us a
homey little commune.
And you're the mayor.
The uniform surely does
go a long way.
Oh God.
Pray for me!
Please God, have mercy!
I'm sorry, Lord! I'm sorry
I did it to them!
I'm sorry I did
it to them!
Tell Him I'm sorry, father.
Tell Him I'm sorry!
I know that He hears you.
I'm sure that whatever you did-
I killed them!
I killed my babies.
I knew if I didn't, they'd be
like them demons!
I burnt them up!
I couldn't let them become
like them monsters.
Now Satan's Satan's
waiting for me.
Lucifer on a hot bed of coals
is waiting for me!
Father, oh God, Jesus
Christ...
Please pray for me.
Please pray for my babies!
I will.
Looks like you found
yourself a new friend.
Sounds crazy as crazy comes.
When you've witnessed what she
has, and done what she's done
I don't know if you can blame
her for the way she is.
Says the gun totin' gospel
sharp who buries the bastard
that just tried to eat his arm.
We all deal in different ways.
Perhaps we'l all be on trial
in the big courtroom one day.
Well that's awful fascinating.
Gotta tack that on to your
sermon, next time you're out
there passing the collection
plate with those things.
You're an odd bird, Preacher.
A good one, but odd.
Mornin' sunshine.
Almost enough to make a
man feel guilty for sleepin'-
Ten hours.
I was hoping
for thirty.
Thoughts?
I give this place an hour.
Maybe two.
Then those things'll come
pouring over these walls.
You up for a walk?
Wait!
Looks like we
got ourselves a native, Joseph.
Mr. Beard seems to think you're
the mongrel fucks that started
all this.
Got anything to say about that?
I asked you a question,
blanket-ass!
What do you have to
say about that?!
What's that, featherhead?
They're right behind me.
RUNNERS!
KILL ME! KILL ME PLEASE!
Please!
So the ship's speeding
towards the Union blockade.
Smoke rolling out of it
but no danger to us
and with a good wind
we were sailing.
Well, it was then the
captain says,
if we don't lose these
guns, Beard, we ain't gonna
make it through the
blockade!
So, I hands him my crowbar,
and he asks, what's this for?
Alls I says is, if he throws
those guns overboard
he's gonna need it
to pry Stonewall's pistol right
out of his arse!.
You know, I must commend you
on the way you
handled yourselves
out in that wood
today, gentlemen.
To save three people
and bring them safely back
in the middle of a runner
attack is quite impressive.
God pulled us through,
Mr. Beard. He always has.
I believe he was with
those people today.
Seems your friend
finds something about divine
help a touch humorous.
Somebody was looking out
for the two of you
when my soldiers
was butchered.
Got nothing to do with
no fluffy Jesus God.
And if those men were any
measure of the caliber of
soldiers you got in these walls,
I'd say we're all but fucked
when those things get here.
Not always a good idea to
insult your host at dinner.
'Specially when he's joined by
some of those very same
soldiers you're speakin'
ill of.
I've seen men hanging from
nooses with more integrity
than I saw out
in those woods.
I apologize.
On behalf of my men,
I accept your apo-
To the men hanging.
If you'll excuse me.
Your hospitality's mighty
appreciated, Mr. Beard,
but I do believe we'll
be taking our leave tomorrow.
Sure we can't persuade you
to stay a while longer?
It's rare that we get
guests of such...cordiality.
I think we've imposed enough.
If any man walk in the day,
he stumbleth not,
because he seeth the light
of this world.
But if a man walk in the
night, he stumbleth,
because there is no
light in him.
That's what is says right
here in John 11.
I took my babies' light
away, I did.
Can you tell that to God?
Can you make him forgive me?
Nothing can change what
you did, ma'am.
Nothing will ever bring
your children back.
Nothing will ever wash
you clean of blood.
We've all seen and done things
today that we would have never
thought of yesterday.
But you can still walk with the
light in you, whatever
that light is.
I want to hear that from God.
I want Him to hear my voice.
What's your name, ma'am?
Don't seem fit to have one
after what I'd done.
But you can
call me Legion.
No ma'am.
You're just one person
looking for grace like
the rest of us.
That's what separates us
from them. We will never
quit seeking grace.
They'll walk forever as
one mind, seeking nothing.
Do you really believe I can
make God hear any of us?
No.
Papa, look!
James!
I see it.
Why don't you stay
a while, Preacher?
Please! No! Don't do this!
Three of 'em come
in this morning.
Woman, the little girl
and the old man.
Looks like her husband's got
a mighty bad hurt on the leg.
Is it a bite?
Dunno.
Phineas, if these two want to
stay, tell them to find a use.
Otherwise, they're more'n
welcome to join him outside.
Soon after we came here, a man
shows up at the gates.
Crazy for the Lord.
One of yer fellas.
And he had a...bloodied arm.
Thought nothing of it. Patched
him up, put him to work.
Week later, the whole goddamn
fort wakes up to this man,
wailing about how we're all
sinners needing to be cleansed.
We're all due judgement from
God Almighty Hisself.
Ordinarily, I got no problem
with these proclomations.
Except that this old croaker
had taken it upon himself
to lead two of those wretches,
in through the rear gate.
Lost a good man that night.
Never did learn if the arm
was a bite or a scratch.
Did learn that either way
you turn it,
a bullet clears things
up, mighty quick.
Gentlemen.
Ever afraid of what
you're becoming?
What's that?
Is it too natural to
put a bullet in one
of those things and not
worry about who they are,
or who they were?
You ain't Beard,
Preacher.
Samuel Beard became
what he is.
He wasn't made
that way.
This have anything to do
with that bastard congregation
you blew straight to Hell?
Even when the
world turns to shit,
folks will still maintain
some shade of a normal life.
These folks here still dance.
Those folks worshipped.
What for?
Shelter from the storm.
Indeed.
But they got no clue as to
the formation of that storm.
Where it came from,
where it ends.
One day the storm takes up
and suddenly it's us out there.
Walking worm food, scratching
at the walls outside.
Ever since we left Highland
Mills, you've been dancing
just like them.
Trying to do what's normal
in a time when there's
no such thing.
I don't understand what goes
through that mind of yours
when you're burying one.
To be truthful, I think you're
a goddamn loon.
No offense to God.
Or loons.
But I do understand you're
not a man who'd cut someone
down in cold blood.
You may have a few wheels
loose on the wagon,
but you ain't a murderer.
It's the Beards of the world
who worry me.
Samuel Beard's only a man.
When his time comes, he will
be cut down by powers bigger
than any of us.
If that's any comfort
to you.
None whatsoever.
Mr. Beard!
Mr. Beard! Where's Beard?!
Mr. Beard! You gotta pull
everyone out now!
Now!
I spotted them out there!
We find those
damn things all the time.
What in the holly hell has
gotten into you-
Scores of 'em!
Hundred. Maybe double that!
Which way're they coming?
This way sir. Following
the gathering trails.
I want everyone inside the gate
within the next half hour.
Have them bring all
the supplies and
firewood that they can.
Leave the rest.
Set up a standard rotation
in those towers
and along the perimeter.
Two hours on, two hours off.
I want ever pitchfork, every
shovel and knife in this yard
immediately.
All women and children are
pected to fight directly, or to
supply the tower positions with
amunition and fresh supplies.
I want everyone armed with some
form of weapon.
Everyone fights, everyone lives.
Abandon your post, or fail to do
your job,
and I will end you myself.
How were they comin'?
Headin' in through the forest,
sir. D'rectly to us.
I'd say about
two hours out.
As soon as those farmers
are in, close the gates.
No one in.
No one out.
Mr. Beard, we've still got
three scouts out there, sir.
What about them?
Leavin' so soon?
You want to stay around
and meet Old Scratch,
we won't be getting in
your way.
We figured we got a better
chance on the move.
If we leave now-all of
us-we can put five miles
between us and them
by daybreak.
Under my orders, no man
is to leave his post
under penalty of death
by firing squad.
And that includes
the two of you!
What gives you the right to
condemn these people to death?!
Got 'em! Three hundred yards!
What is it, Morgan?
Only a few of 'em.
Think the kid was just scared
shitless when he said hundreds?
That's all it takes to
knock in a door.
We got about a dozen
stragglers out there.
Some of them look to be
carrying some provisions
we might be able to use.
Now since you two
held your own
pretty well in the woods,
you're going to take three
men out there and bring
us back what we need.
You mean to tell me that a
few rifles and some dirty shot
is worth more than the lives
of three of your men?
You really are a
worthless cun-
I mean to say that I want those
provisions in this yard
in a half hour with as few
shots fired as possible.
Now shall I further
clarify my point,
or is it pretty mother
fucking clear?!
Looks like we got about
a dozen roamers.
Beggin' your pardon?
Now see, these devil
bastards come in all sorts of
flavors, Marshal.
Carpetheads.
Chinks.
Stumblers. Runners.
Roamers-like these is-
and lingerers.
Lingerers are
the damndest.
They just stick to where they
was when they fell out.
We've come
across some of them.
I reckon.
Eventually something inside
a lingerer drives 'im away
from the place where
he dropped off.
And then they's roamers.
Like we got here.
Ain't that right, Thomas?
Yes sir, it is.
I think is our
chance to exit.
Two problems there.
We're without hooves and
I'm not leaving these people.
Thomas!
It's not a bite. Sumbitch
just scratched me is all.
He ain't gonna
let you back in!
Goddamnit it's just a
scratch!
I can still shoot a gun! I can
still kill these cocksuckers!
This don't gotta be anyway
but quick, Thom-
Goddamn you both!
I'm thinking now
or never, padre.
I'm thinking Beard's had a
sharpshooter trained on us
since we left his gates.
Like the man said, no one's
to abandon his post.
About a month.
What's that sir?
He'd been here about
a month.
Tommy?
Thomas. That's it.
Came in here about a week
after I did.
Him and his sister.
Jillian, right?
I reckon.
I can still smell that soup
she used to make.
Wouldn't have thought a man
could feast so on naught but
potatoes and berries.
Beautiful woman.
Morgan...
If any of the others
go that way,
shoot them.
You boys haven't
seen the full show yet.
Killin's only half the fun.
This is where the good
stuff begins.
That must've been their
scouting party.
You're better off
saving that shot for yourself
you stupid son of a bitch!
Father please protect
us inside these walls this
evening. Give us the clarity
to make the right decisions
and to protect one another
in dark times.
Guide the souls oustide those
gates so that they may find
Your glory in eternal Heaven.
You read to leave, or are
you just going to be
chatting all night?
Amen.
Don't imagine Beard's going
to let those sharpshooters
on a piss break.
I think Beard and his shooters
are going to have a whole
hell of a lot more to worry
about than the two of us
in a few minutes.
Even if we could get past
the gate, we've still got
dozens of those things out
there waiting for us.
Well you got your shovel
right? Should be a goddamn
barn dance for you. C'mon,
let's take a walk.
Battle commotion through scene.]
That scout mentioned that
they're coming in through
the main outlets in
the woods.
All those outlets lead to
that front gate.
Which happens to be where Beard
has most of his men waiting.
Now anybody not there now will
be when those fuckers hit
the wall. Which means you're
going to head to that gate.
Now in about two minutes
you're going to have your
moment to get through there.
And what happens to everyone
else? What happens to you?
Someone's gotta distract
Beard's men.
Once you get through there, you
get to the horses and you ride.
Don't stop.
Ride until you get about a half
days out.
That should give you
enough tme.
We can funnel everyone through
the rear gate and you're right
behind us. Beard doesn't have
enough bullets for-
Hey, Mr. Beard says-
Now. If you were to go
on main road,
it'd take you a day to
get to the crossing.
I'd stay in the sticks.
Put you going a day
or two more, but
maybe you'll avoid the
bulk of them cocksuckers.
I told you.
I'm not leaving these people
and I'm not leaving you.
You don't have to do th-
Oh there's plenty of things I
didn't have to do!
Probably shouldn't
have, either.
But this ain't one of them.
You don't have it in you.
Like hell I don't.
When those things get here,
you're either dead or on your
way to becoming
one of them!
You better be goddamned
sure I don't want to see
that happen!
Now you get to
Burnham's Hope!
When you get there
you go to my church.
The first one's on me.
EDWARDS!
Watch
those close to the wall!
Guns have never been
a problem here.
Weapons. Provisions. People.
All stocks in trade we've
never been short on.
Fire a bullet, reload.
Lose a man, a whole family
shows up at the gates.
The wheels keep turning.
Life...goes on in circles.
Because you love the people,
and the sanctity within these
walls, you make sacrifices.
I've made them.
I've had them made in
my name.
Not proud of it.
Sacrifice keeps the circle in
motion.
Allows the sanctity to exist.
Sacrifice ain't the problem.
Problem ain't outside
these walls.
Problem ain't inside
the walls.
It's here.
A man starts to forget.
Names. Faces. Hopes.
That's when the ground
starts to fall away.
Order never forgets.
You make a man real when
you give him a purpose.
You tell him what to do. When
to walk out those gates.
When to piss. When to sleep.
Reward him when he comes
safely home. Smite him...
...when he steals.
Our enemies made
a Hell from chaos.
We made a home
from order.
Now, I thought my orders were
clear tonight.
All men on the line,
Marshal Edwards.
Too nice a night to be
takin' orders, Mr. Beard.
If this was the army...
...I'd say your nice night
just cost you your life-
Last time I remember
a night this nice,
was almost twenty years
ago.
There was this negro boy.
Fifteen. Sixteen years old.
Supposedly got caught stealin'
a chicken and some lumber
from a couple of farmers.
And while everyone was so
damned concerned about sticks
and birds, all I could think
about was his little brother
screaming wildfire.
Couldn't have been five years
old, watching them drag his
brother to the rope.
We strung him up that night.
Said all number of unholy
things to him while he was
kickin' and screaming.
Don't know if he did it,
really. Never did.
But I do know he deserved
a bit more justice than he
got that night.
I know his little brother
shoulda never have seen
what he saw.
Just like I know that little
girl deserved more than to
watch her pa rot outside
these gates.
And I know...
...there's no room in Heaven or
Hell for monsters like us.
Hell of a nice night.
Get the gates!
I need more ammo!
They're banging in the gates!
♪Orchestral music
I know that what you done
was what you had to do.
The alternative coulda been
much worse in these times.
Lord knows I've seen and done
things that at any other time
I'd have thrown myself before
the cross and begged for mercy.
That doesn't matter.
What matters is you felt it
was what you had to do
at that time. At
that moment.
A friend of mine once said,
it puts a mighty hurt on the
brain when you realize what
a person will do when they
believe in something.
So.
If you believed that's what you
had to do, I understand.
And I know He's out there,
waiting, with open arms.
I've seen died up gamblers spend
less time in there than that.
Just waiting for someone.
No show?
He's out there.
Where the wicked cease
from turmoil,
and the weary are at rest.
Too late to catch a train there?
About thirty more approaching
from the north.
What'd you want to do,
Preach?
You don't mind getting
a little dirty, do you?
If that were coming from any
other man, I'd say that sounds
like a proposition.
But if you were any other man,
I doubt we'd be digging
holes all night now, would we?
Same thing that drove
them to murder that boy,
is the thing that keeps
you going.
Belief.
Belief pushing you to a point
you never thought possible.
We all got belief in something.
You've got the Man. I've got
the Law.
But it's there for
all of us.
You just better hope what
you believe in is worth it.
Worth what you're willing
to do.
What you're willing
to lose.
And in the end...
...you just better
hope it's right.
♪ The stench of the
undead is overwhelming.
♪I know that I'll be
joining them one day.
♪But I promised you
I'd try, though I don't
♪remember why.
♪What's the point of
going on this way?
♪I close my eyes and
hear you say you love me.
♪I feel your gentle
breath upon my face.
♪And I can hear the Devil,
♪he's laughing in my ear.
♪He asks me if I'd
like a little taste.
♪Where have you gone
my beloved?
♪Why have you left me
all alone?
♪This ache, in my heart,
sure to tear me apart.
♪I'm sick, there's a crick,
in my bones.