[film reel whirring] [gentle music]
Provided by
explosiveskull https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[upbeat music]
Christos, this is like the
third message I've left for you
and you're ignoring me, obviously.
I thought you were gonna be here.
That we could like say
goodbye to each other
like civilized human beings.
But obviously you're not up for that, so...
So you know what? Fuck you, Christos.
Fuck you.
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ So good ♪
You have a nose for American chick.
Come on, that girl looks insane.
Go talk to her, man.
No, I'm working.
Come on, I know your playlist inside out.
It's the same R&B shit and
then later on a bit of disco.
It's not R&B and it's not disco!
This song is 20 fucking
minutes long, come on!
Hey!
Fuck!
Ow!
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
So, listen, guys.
You're an American, you're an American.
You're a man, you're a woman.
There you go.
- Oh, you fuck! Argyris!
- Who the fuck is that guy?
Argyris. You know him?
- No.
- He's an asshole.
[crowd hollering]
You guys are doing it, yeah!
You wanna get out of here?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
Come on.
[kids chattering]
[speaking in foreign
language] Good morning!
- We have children here!
- Alright madam, return to your towel.
Can I get you a coffee or something?
What's all that?
Get dressed already.
We have small kids here.
Please do something!
Return to your towel madam!
That's what we're here for.
Get dressed, let's go.
Oh they're hammered.
Handcuffs and off we go.
Hi, I'm Mickey.
Chloe.
Nice to meet you.
- [speaking in foreign language]
- Come.
Come, come, come.
[speaking in foreign
language] Welcome guys!
- Good afternoon Commissioner
- What have we got here?
We caught them stark naked on the beach.
And what you want me
to do? Get them dressed?
- We got them dressed already
- Take the cuffs off!
Do you have IDs? Passports?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Passport? ID?
Oh shit, my bag, I lost my bag.
We...
[speaking in foreign language] Americano's!
We're Americans.
Which basketball team you support?
The Cavaliers.
There you go. You?
Milwaukee.
- Ah, Greek Freak.
- Greek, yeah!
- Oh, yes.
- Yeah.
[speaking in foreign language]
Get them to sign and send them off.
- Mister.
- Yeah.
- Clothes, eh?
- Right.
- Beach, clothes.
- Yes.
Yes, of course.
Home, no clothes.
Where are you going?
I've gotta find my way back
to that house to get my bag.
I'll come with you.
I gotta get my bike.
Okay.
You're going back to the beach, right?
Smoke.
Hey, come on, please.
Smoking is bad for you.
Just one ride.
Come, come, I'll take you.
For fucks sake...
Thank you.
[dogs barking]
Thank you so much.
Jesus!
Hope everyone's alive.
[Chloe] Is it locked?
[Mickey] Yeah.
Hello!
- I don't think he's here.
- Hello.
Well, who are you calling?
- Argyris.
- Who?
The guy who introduced us.
[Chloe] Asshole.
Yeah, this is his grandmother's house.
Or one of them.
All right.
Shit!
Come on, we've gotta go back to the town.
No, I've gotta wait for my bag, I need it.
No, no, no, we'll call him later, let's go.
I'll take you back.
You'll take me to my house?
I'll take you anywhere you want.
[soft music]
[upbeat music]
Just here.
Oh, thank you so much.
Wow, very nice.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thanks for taking me home,
I really appreciate it.
Sure, absolutely.
It's been nice.
Yeah, it was really nice to meet you.
Mickey.
I know.
- Chloe.
What are you doing tonight?
I'm packing.
I go back to the States tomorrow.
Really? For how long?
For ever.
I've had enough of Greece.
Well, if you wanna have a proper goodbye,
I'm deejaying on this island tonight.
It's gonna be a lot of fun.
I think I should probably
just get ready to go.
I'm gonna go, okay?
Thank you, and thank you
for not being an asshole.
It's like a new thing for me.
Try not to be an asshole, yes.
Okay, I'd better go.
You don't have your keys, right?
They're in the bag?
Yeah.
But one of the neighbors, I mean, though.
You wanna go to an island?
Come on in.
Well.
Sorry, it's a bit of a mess in here.
It's nice.
Well, yeah, I mean...
Kypseli.
It's your friend, Argyris the asshole.
Yeah, he is an asshole,
but he's got a big heart.
Do you just have pictures
of him or is this his place?
Well, it's his
grandmother's, but she's dead.
But she was loaded.
Alright, if we're quick,
we can catch our ferry.
I need to take a shower
or wash or something.
Do you? Do you need to take a shower?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
Please. And have you got
something I could put on?
I can't wear this any more.
[Mickey] Yeah, yeah, here.
- Oh.
- There's that.
And then...
Okay.
- Thank you.
- It's good.
- And a towel.
- Right.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Okay. It's in here?
No, no, it's right here, actually.
- Thank you.
- It's my roommate's room.
Okay, great, thanks.
Yeah.
Think you're gonna be alright or...
Sand.
I think I'll be fine.
- Okay.
- Okay? See you later.
Hey, Mickey?
Ta-da!
[dramatic music] [both laughing]
No, I mean...
What are you doing?
But you're ruining your pants.
Patience is what we need to have.
Can you do the other?
Still, lots of sharp
objects going around the...
I don't know you well
enough to let you do this.
- Well...
- Oh my God.
It's all right.
Okay.
All right, I can work
with this, this is good.
All right. I'll pull
these down a little bit.
There we go.
And these?
Here.
Yeah, it's...
It works?
Hey!
Alright, we gotta go.
Quick shower, come on.
[gentle music]
So what have you been doing in Greece?
I'm a lawyer, an immigration lawyer.
Freelance.
Oh God!
- Oh God!
- Come on.
I just try to help people get into America.
Well, that's great.
What, you don't like lawyers?
Depends on the person, you know.
Everybody's different.
'cause you seem to like this lawyer.
We'll see.
[Chloe laughing]
If I get to sing, you're gonna
have to take your shirt off.
Get ready.
You're gonna miss this, right?
Well, I gave it 18 months.
I think that's long enough.
Is it?
What's the reason now, come on.
You got an ex-husband?
You have some kids?
Did you get fired?
I have a variety of reasons.
Yeah, okay.
You're so secretive!
How long have you been here?
Seven years, baby.
Wow, really? Why?
Why not? Look around you.
Yeah, I guess.
And you're from Cleveland?
You like the Cleveland Cavaliers?
Actually, I'm from Blanchester.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
It's Ohio.
It has a population of 4,763 people.
All those nice people.
Did you sleep with all of them?
I'm related to all of them.
I bet.
I moved to Chicago though.
So I sort of see myself as a big city girl.
I like Chicago, they've
good deep dish pizza.
Where are you from, that's
so fucking fantastic?
Originally New Orleans,
but I lived in New York
for 10 years, 'cause I was in a band.
Oh my gosh, so cool.
Very cool.
So why did you leave?
So I can have sex with you on a beach.
[chilled music]
[speaking in foreign language]
How are you?
I'm alright, how are you?
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- This is Chloe.
- This is Takis.
- Nice to meet you too.
Well, he usually leaves with one.
Now he comes in with one.
- Well...
- Good to know.
- Thank you.
- People change, so...
Listen, I want you to do something.
DJ Fever checks in late
last night and he says
"I want to play the sunset slot".
DJ Fever wants to play the sunset?
Yes, he wants to play the sunset slot.
He's going to send the sunset to the stars.
Is he?
He's going to destroy all this beauty.
- Problem?
- Sure. No, I love it.
He's great, he's great.
You better watch out for this guy, right?
I'll keep my eyes on him, thank you.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
We're all gonna die tonight.
[upbeat music] [crowd chattering]
Hey, come on!
Hi!
[upbeat music]
Come on.
[crowd cheering]
[upbeat music]
You're amazing.
I never ever dance, ever.
Come on.
Oh, come on, you were so good.
Look at this.
People wanna hear fucking shit.
Stop.
♪ Take me to your leader ♪
♪ Sipping on tequila ♪
♪ Holding on that drink ♪
♪ My face is on the ceiling ♪
♪ Take me to your leader ♪
- ♪ I'm an angel ♪
- This is Chloe.
Hi, I'm so glad.
♪ I will see the stars ♪
♪ With the leader ♪
[Chloe moaning]
[gentle music]
Today is the big day, huh?
24 hours.
And less.
Do you ever think, "Oh
what the fuck am I doing?"
Like, what am I actually fucking doing?
Not really.
Never?
I mean, sure, but it's more like,
"Why did I just open the fridge?
I know I didn't really want to."
Oh my God.
This is so fucking...
That is such a good way to live.
Is that how you've lasted seven years here?
Yeah.
And I have a son.
You have a son?
Yeah.
- Wow.
- Does that freak you out?
No, no.
'cause I'm a really great father.
No, I'm not saying that...
You just didn't see me as a father.
[both laughing]
It's not...
Hey, listen, you know, it's...
What's his name?
His name is Hector.
It's a good name.
It is.
How old is he?
He is six years old.
That's the room in the house.
- Oh.
- My roommate's room.
That's sweet.
When do you see him?
Whenever I can, but it
depends on his mom too.
Things are bad with her?
You're not together with her, are you?
No.
Okay, I was just...
- No, I'm not.
- I was just checking.
Oh, it's fine.
I mean, look, it's, you know...
It's a work in progress.
Still.
But you wanna see him, right?
Of course.
Oh, that's nice.
I wouldn't wear it, though.
Why?
Because it's not very me.
Maybe it's me.
You'll look good in it.
Could we get two coffees
please, the cold ones?
Thank you.
I've gotta call Argyris.
- Why?
- 'cause of your bag.
Oh, what's your last name?
Gains.
- Gains?
- Yeah, Gains.
Like, gains momentum?
Argyris, are you drunk?
It's a handbag, like a bag,
like a, you know, like a thing.
Yeah, with a purse and a ID in it.
Exactly.
And her name is Chloe Gains.
That's her name.
All right, I'm gonna come and get it.
Thanks.
[speaking in foreign language] Thank you.
Thank you.
There's a ferry every two hours.
[soft music]
You know what I think?
We can skip a couple of boats.
You know what?
What?
You're not going back.
What are you talking about?
America, you're not going back.
I'm leaving in like hours.
Well, you're gonna make
a big mistake if you do.
What are you talking about?
You're always gonna
regret not doing something
rather than doing something,
and you're gonna regret it.
How do you know what I'm gonna regret?
Look, do you wanna go back?
It doesn't matter.
I told you, we talked
about this, it doesn't...
Do you wanna go back?
Okay.
You shouldn't make assumptions
about what you think is good for me
when we've only fucked a couple of times.
Wow.
I'm sorry, I'm not trying
to tell you what to do.
I'm just...
Well, it sounded like you were.
[soft music]
You're free.
Of the helmet.
He should be here soon, I guess.
I'm really sorry about
what I said on the boat.
No, no, no, I'm sorry.
No, I didn't mean it.
It's all right.
Really, I didn't mean it.
[motorcycle engine revving]
Oh my God!
You wanna go through the door?
Check this out, perfect timing.
- There you go.
- Thank you so much.
Sorry, I lost a few
condoms on the way over.
Funny.
Thank you.
You guys have been fucking, right?
It's written all over your face.
Okay, on that note, I'm gonna go.
Thanks for my bag.
All right.
Okay, thank you, Mickey.
It's been really nice.
So this guy has been living
in my dead grandmother's house
for over six years and
he hasn't touched a thing.
What's wrong with you, man?
What's up man?
You look like I shot your back, what's up?
Nothing, nothing.
Come here, come here, I
wanna show you something.
What, man?
What's wrong with you, man?
You look like a crying pussy.
Who the fuck are all these people?
These people are our buddies, what's wrong?
I'm tired, I had a long weekend, all right?
I don't wanna fucking deal with anybody.
Are you in love with this girl?
Fuck you.
[Argyris laughs]
- Stop.
- You fucker.
You're in love with this girl.
Stop.
Do you know what you are?
You are fucking lucky. Where is she now?
She's at the airport.
Let's go fucking find her.
No, I'm not fucking...
It's ridiculous.
No, what's ridiculous is you sitting there
farting into my couch feeling
sorry for yourself all night.
Come on, we'll take the bike.
Come on. We'll get the bike.
- Come on.
- Fuck!
[gentle music]
[motorcycle engine revving]
Good luck, man.
Chloe!
Fuck.
[Chloe] Hello?
[Mickey] Excuse me, who are you?
Who are you?
Who are you? Why are you in my house?
- What is this?
- Why are you in my house?
You wanna fight?
Yeah, I do.
Come on. Come on.
- Hello.
- Hi. Hello!
What's with the swimwear?
I was cooking and crying.
Cooking and crying?
- Yes.
- Oh my God.
I was chopping onions.
So I had to, you know?
Because you were cooking for me?
Yeah, because I was cooking for you.
- Oh my God, that is too hot.
- Because it's...
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday ♪
Oh my God!
You got me a present.
I got you a little something.
You got me a helmet.
- With my name on it.
- Yes.
Oh my God.
This is a very special helmet.
For very special people.
And then it goes like that.
Wow.
Yeah.
Helmet sex?
You know, it's perfect
when you can't see what's happening.
Oh my God.
Wait, wait, wait.
What about the van? Did you get a van?
- The van?
- The van to move my stuff.
I did not get the van.
But I sent you everything to get the van.
Yes, I know, but you know what?
You can't rent a van in Greece, okay?
There's not any free vans and...
You're gonna call for a van now?
It's gonna take me two seconds.
- Can I get one?
- Excuse me.
Excuse me, I'm busy on my phone.
Please don't look at my phone.
Girl, I can't do my work.
- You get me a van...
- I will get you a van.
Then I will give you all of this.
Come on, I'll get you a van.
Hey!
[gentle music]
Fuck.
Argyris?
[speaking in foreign language]
You're a fucking legend, man.
Yeah.
Okay, thank you.
Text me the address, please.
Okay.
I got a fucking van.
Oh my God, how did you do that?
I got a van.
How did you get it?
Did I say to you I'll get a van?
- You said, you said.
- Did I say?
- We have a van!
- You said.
Come on, let's go.
God.
To the people of Kypseli,
Mickey Henry's got a fucking van.
God, it better not be that one.
Hey!
Hi.
We're looking for Pantelis.
Pantelis!
[speaking in foreign language] Yeah?
Some foreigners...
- Pantelis.
- Hi.
- Oh.
- Sorry.
Next time.
Listen, we're here for the van.
There.
Great, I like it.
I need 100 Euros.
- What?
For the deposit, you know.
But you said it was free on the phone.
The van is free.
You pay for the damage, you know.
The damage to that?
No, no, no. That makes...
That's true. okay.
40.
Do you have...
Here.
Okay.
It's...
It's disgusting.
Let's be roomies.
Oh, hang on.
Hello.
All right.
What's coming?
- Everything.
- Everything?
- This is all coming?
- Yes.
Yeah, but look how neat
it is, it's like perfect.
It's really easy.
What were you gonna do with this stuff
when you were going to America?
Everything was going to America
but now I'm not going to America,
everything is going to your house.
What did you think was gonna happen?
I was gonna bring my handbag?
- Yes, of course.
- I have a life here
and it's in these boxes.
But this is staying.
No, this couch is the only
thing I invested money in
in my entire time-
- See, that's so troublesome.
- In Athens.
We're gonna have our first
really, really big fight.
You wanna fight?
- I will fight you-
- Do you wanna fight?
To the death about that couch.
[soft music]
[Chloe giggles]
[phone ringing]
Well, well, I see you're in Athens.
What do you know?
[upbeat music]
By the way, I've peed in that corner.
My God, I believe that.
I think you've probably peed
in a lot of places around here.
Yeah.
It's quite territorial.
Well, I need to find my way home at night.
Come on! [Chloe groans]
Really?
Hey!
Come on!
Listen, in this country you have to scream.
That's how it is.
- It's not helpful for me.
- I'm going right.
- I don't care, I'm going right.
- It's a dead end.
Oh my God.
Hang on, I'm going right.
- It's a dead end!
- It's not a dead end.
Nothing in Greece is a dead end.
What is it? What is it?
Tell me what it is.
Tell me what it is, Mickey.
- Tell me what it is.
- It's a dead end.
[Chloe] Yeah, it's a dead end.
You know what?
You're gonna have to pay the ticket.
Oh my God, what are you doing?
No, no.
- We can't do it here.
- Yes we can.
It's too uncomfortable.
Sh!
[both giggling]
Well, here we are.
Here we are.
All right.
[speaking in foreign
language] Mrs. Kostopoulos.
Very helpful as always.
- All right, okay.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
You got it?
Oh, fuck.
Hey.
[Chloe heaving]
Okay.
I know you don't wanna use this room.
I know you wanna keep it the same
so that when he comes
back it's here forever,
and that's everything I
think is great about you.
But I think we need to use the room, okay?
It's important to me too, I'm
gonna help you get him back.
And he'll be here, and
his room will be here.
Okay?
Is that a yes?
- Yes.
- It's an okay.
- Come on, oh.
- Stop, hold on.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, my arm, my arm, my arm.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Hold on, okay.
- Let's go.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- You good?
- Oh, fuck.
- Okay.
- Come on.
Oh shit.
All right, come on, hold on.
Just...
Wait, wait wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, I got it, hold it.
Okay.
Oh fuck.
Oh no, no, no.
- Okay, it's okay.
- Easy, okay, okay, okay.
- You got it?
- Slowly, slowly.
All right, here's what gonna happen.
I'm gonna go up first a little bit,
I'm gonna bring it up a little bit.
So just hold and stay in place
and then I'm gonna come
and switch with you, okay?
- Okay.
- So just wait.
[Chloe] Okay.
- Fuck!
- Okay, okay.
Alright, switch with me, okay?
Switch with me. Go, go, go.
[Chloe] Are you okay?
Yes.
- Are you sure?
- Are you holding it?
Fuck.
[Chloe] Push it up.
- God.
- Fuck!
Okay.
This is your couch, it descends.
I know!
It's like giving birth.
Fuck! Come on.
Oh, shit.
- Fuck.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Please don't ruin it.
You wanna know what I think?
Tell me.
I think we're gonna have to
say goodbye to this thing.
No, it's my, the one thing.
And I know exactly what to do.
This is the only thing I spent money on.
I know exactly what to do.
Oh, no.
We can keep trying.
We did.
No, I love this couch.
Hey, hey, hey.
I know.
Twice in a day.
Perfect.
[Greg] Hey!
Hey!
What's going on?
What's up?
Alright.
[speaking in foreign language]
Come on guys, let's go!
Oh my God!
Yo, easy Mickey!
- We can see you.
- [Mickey] Hello.
Wow, who's that guy?
This is Greg.
Oh my God.
Oh.
How old is your friend?
Like, 40, 42.
[Chloe] He looks like a giant baby.
They're gonna be your friends now.
I'm so excited about it, that's great.
Okay?
More than okay.
[upbeat music] [crowd chattering]
Hey.
[speaking in foreign language] Hey!
What's with that racket every night?
Please, please come down.
Juliet, come on.
Hey!
Oh my God!
How are you?
You look great.
No, you look good.
This is Mickey, guys.
This is the one I was telling you about.
Hey, this is Chloe.
- Oh, hi!
- Hi!
- I'm Bastian.
- This is Bastian.
I know who you are. Oh my God.
- Nice to meet you.
- Very, very special person.
Happy fucking birthday.
Thank you so much.
- Here he is.
- Come on, let's go, let's go.
What the fuck!
What is this?
This is fucking amazing.
Hey, hey, hey. Listen up for a second.
You know who this is?
[crowd cheering]
Well, she's gonna take
over for a little while.
So make sure you give her a
little bit of love, all right?
And also, Chloe Gains.
I know that today we
lost your favorite couch,
but today we gained a family.
[crowd cheering]
You guys wanna be Chloe's family?
Fuck yeah! [crowd cheering]
[upbeat music] [crowd cheering]
- I love you.
I fucking love you.
Okay, back up, back up, here we go.
Hey!
Back up.
It's time.
Oh shit.
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit!
Give me that, give me that, give me that.
You don't want it anymore.
It's gonna be, baby, I'm sorry.
There you go.
Fucking do it.
- Whoo!
- This is Kypseli!
[crowd cheering]
Bye bye!
[upbeat music]
[sirens wailing]
- Fuck, that was crazy.
- Oh, I'm glad.
Everyone is lunatic in Athens.
- There you go.
- Oh, thanks.
No more couch.
We did it.
I can't believe you did that.
It's gonna be all right.
It's gonna be okay.
You got what you wanted,
that's why it's okay.
Thank you for coming.
Ah, you're welcome.
I really like that shirt you're wearing.
Oh yeah.
This was your band?
Yeah, that was...
And you had T-shirts?
- We did. Yeah.
- It's a neighborhood
in New Orleans where we did our first gig.
- Oh, wow.
- When we were very young.
[Bastian] Yeah, and we got a deal...
You got a deal.
No, we got a deal.
- Don't fucking start that.
- You got a deal.
And we were just there for the ride.
- So tell me what happened.
- What really happened was,
we fucking got our deal.
We made our album, it was fantastic.
Okay.
We take the album on tour, right?
Tour's amazing as well.
Right at the fucking end,
at peak, peak success,
this fucking guy, this
Mickey go lucky goes solo.
Out of nowhere.
Leaves us hanging.
I went to New York because I
didn't really have a choice.
And you were doing
- your own thing and you went-
- You had a choice.
- And you had your own thing
- Yeah, what else
- was I supposed to do.
- Because it was
the Bastian show, and it was great.
- We made that band.
- And it was great.
You became super famous, you
got like 18 million followers.
You're good on Instagram, whatever.
Yeah, I had to go make an
album because you fucking left.
And I think it's a great album.
- It's not the fucking point.
- Come on, I love it.
No. No, fuck you.
You know what, he kept
every fucking bad review
the band got.
Every single one.
Why keep them?
'cause I don't, I can't...
- I wanted to improve
- Tell her why.
- And I wanted to know...
- Every single one.
I wanna know
- what everyone thinks.
- No, you done it
because you fucking hate yourself.
That's your fucking problem.
That's not, that's not...
You are not happy unless you're failing.
- Whoa.
- And that's why
you left the band.
Wow.
So I guess I'll get
happy with another drink,
I mean, you know.
- Yeah, fucking get me one.
- Oh no, fuck.
Jesus.
I'm gonna put some music on.
Okay, put some music on.
Hey, what the fuck are you doing?
What does it fucking look like I'm doing?
Oh God, come on, let's go.
Grandma's asleep, don't fucking...
Come on, let's go, let's go.
For fuck's sake.
Do you ever think about coming home?
No.
Why?
Why think about it?
I think you should come home.
Like, people have changed.
Hey.
Hey, babe.
Do you wanna...
- Do you want some?
- Can you hurry up?
I need to pee.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we'll be right out.
Fuck.
Anything I said?
Oh bug.
Are you even serious?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Like what, met your kid serious?
No, no, she hasn't met him yet.
But she's going to, she's...
I got a fucking kid now.
- I know.
- What the fuck!
I mean, I saw that.
I couldn't believe that.
Like, how the fuck have we got kids?
We're getting old.
Listen. I think we should
start writing again.
Like seriously.
I've got fucking six months left.
Come with me. We can
start writing on the road.
It will be great.
- No.
- No, look.
I'm fucking sick of doing
the same shit over and over.
They sent me to work with
these fucking weird guys
in New York, LA.
They've got fucking plaques
on the wall, blah, blah, blah.
I work with fucking Maroon 5.
We fucking hate Maroon 5.
I mean, think about it.
[Mickey] All right, yeah.
Like, I miss you.
Come with me.
Is it true you're only
happy when you're failing?
No.
I'm so sorry about that.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah, fine, thank you.
Again, I'm really sorry
we have to do this here.
I'm still between offices at the moment.
That's fine.
Thank you for squeezing me in.
No problem and I'm really
sorry about the noise.
We're both trying to work
from home today, so...
Okay, so, the reason that there
was a problem with your J-1
is because you already held that status
of a researcher in the US.
So you're no longer,
you don't meet the eligibility criteria.
Does that make sense?
[speaking in foreign language] When
Greece becomes the centre of the world.
Then the only solution
is Lioggos fertilizer.
Lioggos: certified
fertilizer for the new era.
- Wow.
- Good job, man.
- Beautifully shot.
- Good job, yeah.
Nice music, man.
Okay, are you done congratulating
each other, okay, yeah?
[speaking in foreign language]
No. This is totally not what we discussed.
[speaking in foreign
language] And it's total crap.
- Total crap?
- This is a total crap.
Total crap, and there is a
basic, very basic reason for it.
It has no Greekness that kinda
comes from the Greek soil,
from the Greek nature,
from the mentality...
Can you stop interrupting me?
Would you mind not smoking, also?
No, I like smoking in my house.
- [men chattering indistinctly]
- Come on Manos, it's my house.
It's okay, it's okay.
Manos, he can smoke.
- Is it okay if I smoke?
- Of course it's okay. Go on.
Let's get the briefing first.
I'm trying to help you here.
Yeah, the briefing was,
you know, a little funny.
The briefing is that
we simply need something
that has modernity, that is the same-
- Contemporary.
- Contemporary,
but at the same time, it
conveys a feeling of Greekness.
Something that the Greek
audiences can relate to.
And this is not? This is not?
It's something that you
obviously don't understand.
[speaking in foreign language]
So this is what you think
when I tell you Greekness?
This is what you come out with?
You come out with a
bouzouki as if we were...
[speaking in foreign
language] It's traditional man!
I wanna play it safe
'cause I feel like you want
something more safe, so I...
Cut the fucking bouzouki.
I'll cut the bouzouki.
- Thank you.
- If we combine, Manos,
if we combine the bouzouki now
with the modern style...
[speaking in foreign language] I don't
want the bouzouki man! No bouzouki!
We'll try something else.
What the fuck is this?
Like, this is an amateur night.
Sorry, I have a client.
I am the fucking client here, okay?
Yeah, yeah, we'll be all
right, we'll be quiet, sorry.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
I would have booked an appointment, but...
There's not enough time.
Christos said...
Said that you're a wizard.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Christos?
Sioutis Christos.
He...
He spoke very highly of you.
He's the reason I called.
Oh...
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
I'm really embarrassed
but I've just realized
I can't take on another client right now.
Wait, sorry, you can't help me?
I mean, did I do something wrong?
No, of course not, it wasn't you.
It's not you, it's me
and I really apologize.
But I'm gonna have to show you out.
I'm so sorry.
[speaking in foreign language] But
Manos, you're a little too dogmatic now...
Sorry, am I not being as
clear as possible here?
- We need something-
- No, you're actually being
very contradictory with yourself.
I'm not contradictory with myself, man.
Guys, [speaking in foreign language].
Contemporary briefing.
That could mean one, two, three,
four, five different things.
Give me a minute. I'm
gonna talk to the guy.
I can bring up the musicians
that can fucking do that in a snap.
- Hey.
- Sorry.
Are you finished?
- Oh God.
- I'm sorry.
I told you that might happen.
I mean, it seems to take so long.
Does anyone actually care
whether you use a keyboard or-
- I care.
A little bit, I care.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean it like that.
I meant them, you know?
It must be frustrating for you.
You're talented, you know
what you're doing and it's...
Embarrassing, it's embarrassing.
No, I'm not...
Yeah, it's just, you know.
It's just a fucking jingle,
you know, it's all it is.
It's just a fucking little jingle.
No, that's not what I'm saying.
Stop, please, stop.
We've both had a really shitty day.
[speaking in foreign language]
I want a contemporary
take in traditional tunes!
- Alright, we'll have it.
- Will you?
Yes, we'll work on it today
and tomorrow you'll have it.
It should have been ready
yesterday, as you know.
You'll have it and it will be perfect!
Yesterday!
We got one more shot.
- Yeah, yeah.
- One more shot!
So good, all right.
- It's gonna be great.
- Let me see him out.
- Very Greek.
- Take it easy, huh?
Sure. Sure.
See you tomorrow, man.
[phone ringing]
Hey.
Why?
[speaking in foreign language] Asshole...
No, it's okay.
Yeah, yeah, fine.
What happened?
No, Argyris and Manos, you know,
they can't come over until two, you know.
Okay, so they don't come over then.
Well, it's not that
easy. We have a deadline.
Explain to me what you're saying.
I have to finish the thing.
This fucking jingle thing.
Well, you have to come with
me to see your ex girlfriend.
This is what you have to do.
- Don't start laughing at me.
- I'm not. No, no, no.
- Let's talk about this.
- No, you are coming...
No way!
We are not talking about this.
You cannot leave me.
- Don't try that with me.
- I'm not leaving you.
I'm not leaving you.
You know what I think?
I think it's better.
Let me tell you why.
- No.
- Hold on.
I'm not letting you tell me anything.
No, no, and you're this fucking sexy lawyer
who just can convince
anybody of everything.
- Mickey, no.
- You're amazing
and you're walking like the light
and she's fucking crazy.
Mickey.
Listen to me, listen to me.
It's gonna go wild in two seconds.
And if I'm there, she's
gonna get all hysterical
and try to...
First of all, she's gonna be all jealous.
She's gonna try to one-up
you and it's about...
But what about the party?
Why don't we...
Party's gonna be great.
Yeah, but we can cancel this.
I'll have everything ready.
- No.
- Listen.
It's just this one time, I promise.
I'm laughing but this is not funny.
- It's just this one time.
- And you can't...
Come on, I'll have sex with you.
You wanna have sex with me?
- Let's go.
- Never.
- I'll do that thing.
- Never again.
- You know that.
- I hate you.
- Come on.
You're the best.
[upbeat music]
What about now, man?
This is Greek.
What do you think?
- Greek.
- Fantastic, fantastic.
Gorgeous.
- Hold on.
- Okay, okay.
- Are you joking?
- Can we just...
Thank you. All right.
So, okay, tell you the truth, okay?
I appreciate the work that I've seen
that you've invested but the truth is,
come on Argyris now, you know.
This music is totally not
what we're talking about.
- Oh man.
- This is for fairs.
Like where gypsy people go.
- Manos, sorry, I...
- For fairs?
I honestly...
- For fairs.
- That's the truth.
Let's go, we can...
I want what I asked, Argyris.
You know very well what I want.
We can also go with one more.
- We'll try one more.
- Okay.
- One more, okay.
- You want one more?
- Go one more.
- One more, last one.
Okay.
[gentle music]
I love this. Yes!
That's it, man. Yeah!
Yeah, that's perfect.
That's what we talk about, man.
- Are you joking?
- No, I'm not fucking joking.
That's perfect.
The minute I hear it, I see images.
- I immediately...
- It's familiar.
It rings home.
- It feels familiar, but...
- It feels familiar,
it has images.
It reminds me of my
grandma, my grandfather.
It combines the elements.
I mean, I see pictures.
I don't have to see the actual video.
I can imagine it just by the sound.
Total.
This is what you put in the brief.
This is the thing you gave me.
Okay, man.
This is like totally,
totally disrespectful.
You like it.
[Manos] I'm here, I'm trying
to get you a fucking job.
- You like it, so use it.
- You asshole...
I'm not here because I like you.
I'm here because Argyris asked me to come.
Mickey, sorry.
- Fuck off.
- [speaking in foreign language] Manos, can I talk to you for a minute?
What you want to talk about, Argyris?
Did you bring me here so this fucking
Alabama cowboy can make fun of me?
I really apologize, in two hours
you're gonna have what you need.
A good track, in two
hours with this asshole?
Don't worry, you'll have it.
- Hi.
- Hello.
There's a reservation under Aspa Karra?
Yep.
This side.
Aspa, hi. I'm Chloe.
Nice to meet you.
Look at you.
You're at his age, aren't you?
I'm older, actually.
That's funny.
Why funny?
Should we order?
Sure.
After you.
No, go ahead.
I insist.
- [speaking in foreign language] Ice tea for me please.
- Same for me please.
Thank you.
- So...
Am I meeting Mickey's
attorney or his girlfriend?
Oh, he's not a client.
Why isn't he here?
I asked him not to come.
That's a great idea.
You knew he would do
something stupid, didn't you?
Aspa, I know this is difficult
but Mickey really wants a
relationship with his son.
- Oh, does he?
- Yes.
- And you know about it?
- Yes, I know that.
I know him.
You know nothing.
You don't know what you're doing,
you don't know where you are.
Mickey can't be bothered to
learn one single word in Greek
to communicate with his own son.
So he has to rely on Hector's English.
Look, that was then, and this is now.
I'm here because I...
- Look-
- Mickey is not the same
as he was six years ago.
Mickey is a baby.
He's a little boy.
Will you be happy with that?
I don't need to talk to you
what I'm gonna be happy with.
It's so fucking Greek.
It reminds me of the Aegean
sea and Athenian women rising...
And I see the corn, I see my grandmother
coming out of the grave!
And so but the Greek is there.
And he's like playing the flute
and eating the fucking
souvlaki and taking humus.
No, humus is not Greek, man.
- Humus is not Greek.
- Then tahini.
- Is tahini?
- Yeah, tahini, yeah, yeah.
- Tahini is Greek.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Hi.
Hi. How was it?
Yeah, she's young, beautiful.
She's fucking angry.
Well, of course she's angry.
She saw you, look how beautiful you are.
Did you do the food?
I have a plan.
So you didn't make the food?
Because I have a plan,
I'm gonna surprise you.
All I asked you to do was
make the fucking food, Mickey.
Okay.
[doorbell ringing]
[speaking in foreign language]
Can I help you?
It's delivery for Mickey.
Okay, thank you.
How much is that?
[Delivery Guy] It's 52.60.
One second.
This was your plan, to order in food?
Here you...
[speaking in foreign language]
Falafel, souvlaki.
Sushi.
It's good, right?
- It's good.
- Yeah, some more sushi.
Hey, are you good?
- Yeah, I mean...
- Come on, it's funny.
Really, is it though?
Yeah.
You know, it's real.
It's like we don't care,
but we care, that kind.
Yeah, I care.
I know.
That's good.
Yeah, it's not for now, Argyris.
Yeah, okay.
- Now just...
- Very good that.
Oh my God.
Thank you so much for coming.
I didn't know if it was a birthday party.
Should I bring a present?
Yeah, we're calling it a pointless party
because there isn't any point to it.
But we just wanted
everyone to meet, you know?
But it's great to give parties.
No one throws parties any longer.
That's exactly what we said.
- No!
- So, this is home.
So, you're not house sitting?
No, this is Mickey's...
This is Mickey.
- Mickey, this is Elli.
- Hi!
Nice to meet you.
You want a falafel?
I'll have one later.
- Okay.
- Great.
- Yeah, so that's Mickey.
- So that's your boyfriend?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So are you still in Kolonaki?
No, we moved to the northern suburbs.
We?
Kostas and I.
My fiancé.
Oh my God! That is a rock.
- Wow!
- No, it's great.
Oh, congratulations, I'm so happy.
Thank you, Chloe.
Well, I wish you the same, you know?
Oh well.
Let's go get a drink.
Yes, I need a drink.
[phone ringing]
Hey, what are you doing, man?
I ordered this one.
Nobody ordered, it's a buffet, you share.
Oh, it's okay, this is good for me.
Come on.
- Hey, Mickey!
- Hey, wow.
Look at you.
Got a little beer.
Looking good, looking good.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
[all laughing]
[speaking in foreign language]
What is little Argyris doing here?
Are you having a poo? A little shit?
Look at this cute boy taking a dump!
Come on don't be an asshole,
leave it. My mom framed it.
Come on man, leave it!
It's great that you put together, you know,
his people, your people.
It's really fun.
I wanna introduce you to somebody.
Excuse me for just a second.
- Oh, okay.
- Come with me.
So, you guys are both from London.
So, I thought I should introduce you.
Johnny, Tim. Tim, Johnny.
Hey Johnny, how are you, man?
- Good.
- Can I get you a drink?
Ah, do you have juice?
- Orange?
- Is it fresh?
- Yes.
- Okay, great.
Okay.
So yeah, where are you from in London?
Dagenham.
All right, so not kind of...
Yeah.
London too, huh?
Well, I mean, Holland Park.
But I'm barely there.
Kind of spending a lot of time here.
Oh, what are you doing here?
I'm doing a startup.
Okay.
It's called Your Home.
It's sort of housing solution
for the global citizen.
So places like this, you just get in,
rip these places out and make these cool,
quite functional pods.
Well, we're trapped in
this bar in Switzerland
because it was like six
feet of snow outside.
Oh, yeah!
You guys, you put like
200 francs into the jukebox
and played "Last Christmas"
on repeat 100 times.
- That's so embarrassing.
- I love that song.
They were so fucking wasted, you know.
And Christos, you know, he threw...
He's a good guy, that guy.
He threw down 3,000 francs
on the table, you know?
And everybody was doing shots.
I don't remember.
And he looks very, very nice.
Yeah, he's a really good guy.
He is. It's fine.
You want a drink or not?
Yes, I would like a vodka please.
Sure.
Dude, it's fucking
disgusting what you're doing
and you should be ashamed
of yourself, seriously.
I should be ashamed of myself?
What do you do? What do
you do with your life?
Mate, I left London 'cause London
was like fucking ridiculously expensive,
I couldn't afford to live there anymore-
- Because you don't have a job, probably.
I guess you don't work.
Mate, you're a fucking cock.
Oh, okay.
Cheers, mate.
Wow, I'm so glad that went so well.
- That's your juice.
- Thank you so much.
You know, it's funny,
like people always do that.
"Oh, you're from London"
kind of like when you're gay,
like, "Oh, hey, meet my gay friend."
Oh, you're such a dick.
Wow, okay.
You wanna come and have some food with me?
- Sure.
- Sure, let's do that.
- Really nice to meet you.
- Okay.
It's like having 100%
of your daily nutrients
for less than 800 calories.
And it's raw and it's vegan.
For 300 Euros?
[guys chattering]
Guys, hey.
Have you met these guys?
This is Miltos, Orpheus,
Dimitrios, Prometheus and Greg.
- Are you making fun of me?
- This is Stephanie.
No, no, no, Stephanie.
Where are you from, Stephanie?
Athens, you fucking moron.
[guys laughing]
[Miltos] Oh, you're a
bit aggressive, Stephanie.
Where from Athens?
[speaking in foreign
language] Papagou, mate.
So what's with the accent?
Because I have the ability and you don't.
Sorry, baby.
I'm speaking English to an
American because it's polite.
Same reason I don't turn up like a shit
in fucking cargo shorts.
[Orpheus] Sorry, pussycat. Sorry.
Are they your friends?
- Are they your friends?
- He is a shit, he is a shit.
- Good for you.
- Bye bye, bye bye!
Oh, fuck.
Argyris, what the fuck are you doing, man?
You shit in your pants, do you know that?
You shit in your pants.
What?
- Come on. Come on.
- Oh fuck!
Get up.
What the fuck did you
drink for fuck's sake?
- Oh shit.
- Fuck.
Shit. Hold on, hold on.
Oh.
You know, I've gotta
tell you, Manos texted.
They hated the song, they said it's shit.
Awesome.
You almost got my drink.
- I'm sorry. Almost.
- Almost.
Cheers, Stephanie.
Yeah, Stephanie.
Bottoms up.
- [speaking in foreign language] What are you drinking, Stephanie?
- Gin Tonic. Wanna try?
No, no.
Could it be Jizz Tonic?
Maybe a Penis Colada?
Don't worry if you find
anything funny in it.
It's probably just angel hair...
Oh my God!
- Stephanie!
- What?
- What happened?
- What's going on?
- Are you okay?
- Oh my God, what happened?
Guys, what did you do?
They put something in my drink.
Guys, come on!
I'm gonna fucking sue you.
Thank you, guys. Bye.
Thank you so much for coming. Bye.
Oh my God.
That could not have gone worse.
[both laughing]
[Chloe moaning softly]
Oh, fuck.
This is, it's so hot.
It's okay.
[gentle music]
How do you feel?
Don't worry.
It will be over soon.
We'll talk later.
You will be experiencing some cramps.
- Yeah.
- That's to be expected.
Okay.
- Don't worry.
- Oh yeah.
And try to take it easy the next days.
Yeah, I'll try.
Do you smoke?
Yes.
Can I have a cigarette?
In here? 'cause it's not allowed.
Thank you.
Fuck.
[dramatic music]
Careful, it's really hot.
Thank you.
Thanks.
So they didn't say what it was?
Well, it's like a stomach flu.
It's what they told me.
What time is she coming?
A couple of hours.
Okay.
I'll be alright.
I'm sorry you feel shitty.
You still look good though.
I don't actually know
what this window is for.
[Chloe] But it's safe.
I'm not here to inspect, it's not my job,
but my client, Ms. Karras,
insisted to make sure
that Hector will spend
time in a safe environment.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Yeah, of course.
I know the whole situation
is awkward, but...
[Chloe] No, of course, it's fine.
Absolutely.
- Should I show you his room?
- Oh yeah.
His room is over here. Yeah.
This way.
You both live here?
- Yeah.
For how long?
- A few years.
- Six months.
I moved in six months ago.
So, this is...
Yeah.
It's nice.
You understand that Hector's mother
has assigned guardianship
and visitation rights
to the both of you.
Oh.
Both of you, as a couple
will be legally allowed
to take unsupervised custody of Hector
for the allotted time period
stated on the documents.
- And...
- Okay.
So we just have to be there
at the same time to see him.
- Yes.
- Okay.
And that's the only way we can have access?
Well, it can be overturned
on appeal from either party,
but provided you remain in a stable
and committed relationship.
Do you consider yourselves being
in a stable and committed relationship?
- Yeah.
- Yes, of course, yes.
Great.
Nice room.
Yeah, it's great.
So yeah, anyway, there's...
There's just this one other room here.
This is the...
[Lawyer] It's your bedroom?
Bedroom.
And then that's it.
That's pretty much it.
[Lawyer] Thank you very much.
Yeah.
You're welcome.
- How are you feeling?
- Okay.
Just okay?
That's not good enough.
I can't, I can't, I can't.
I'm sorry, I can't do it now.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's fine.
I just wanna make sure you're
feeling good, that's all.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hi. Chloe Gains.
Hello, welcome.
Chloe Gains.
- Yes, you're right here.
- Great.
This gentleman is your plus one?
Mickey, yes.
Yeah, plus one.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your night.
Thank you.
Hey guys, smile.
- Thank you.
Hi guys. Okay.
- Maybe we can like...
- [Argyris] Hey, guys.
Wow, hey, how are you?
- Hey.
- Perfect.
What's up, you look fucking miserable.
Well, it was a long journey.
How was the ceremony?
Oh, so good!
There was this girl, Elli's niece.
She sang a song.
She was fucking beautiful.
And her voice made me hard.
I sat in the church with a
huge boner, like, what the fuck!
I wanna meet her but I
can't find her anywhere.
Yeah, I'm gonna be sure to
tell her to stay away from you.
As far away from you as possible.
No.
Oh, my friend is here.
One second, I'll be back.
Where did you get that drink?
There are people with trays
with champagne and shit
all over the place.
Come on, I gotta get one.
We really miss you.
I know, and I miss you too.
We talk about you all the time.
All the girls they said
to me "Where is Chloe?"
I say I don't know.
You know what it's like.
You meet somebody and
you go into the bubble
and all you can see is them, but I'm good.
I'm okay.
Okay.
It's new but it's good.
He's kind to you?
Yeah, he's great.
Okay. Then I like him.
Yeah.
I had to step out for a bit.
You know, it was a lot.
What happened with Christos was a lot.
What happened with
Christos is something else.
Tonight, we'll have a lot of fun.
A lot of fun.
Yes.
- Here's to that.
- Tonight, a lot of fun.
[speaking in foreign language]
Hey.
Oh, hey.
Here you are.
How are you? Okay?
- I'm good. How are you?
- Let me introduce you.
This is, you remember
Anna that I told you about?
And Virginia and Caterina.
- Hi.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
Yeah.
I'm gonna be right here.
Okay, I'll come and find you.
I'll be around here.
Okay.
Mickey.
Mickey, is that you?
Mickey, right?
[laughing]
Vodka soda, double.
[Barman] Yes, please.
I am keeping a tight
hold of my drink tonight.
Stephanie.
How are you?
Good. How are you doing?
I'm fine.
I'm glad you made it.
I was always gonna make it.
I think it's probably the first time
they've seen each other
since they broke up.
He has this way of...
I don't know, gas lighting people.
Do you know gas lighting?
Yeah, I know what gas lighting is.
Because of all the family
money and the connections,
he thinks he can move people
wherever he wants them.
After he and Chloe broke up,
he set her up with this
big new job back in Chicago.
Like it was nothing.
So he got her a job, that's...
That's nice.
So...
I'm here with someone.
I'm very happy for you.
I'm sure you are, I can tell.
He's the reason I stayed in Athens.
He is the reason?
Just pure, innocent, romantic.
Just love at first sight, right?
It was, actually.
So you were not picturing
one of my biggest clients calling to ask me
why their new hire had not shown up
at her first day at work?
I didn't wanna take a job
that you had arranged for me.
Since when?
What's that...
I don't wanna be controlled by you.
Stop doing that, I fucking
hate when you do that.
Oh.
Should you be drinking?
My drinking is none of your
fucking business, Christos.
We're finished.
You need to stop embarrassing yourself.
I'm embarrassing myself?
Really?
Embarrassing myself?
Did you just say this?
Look at you.
Enjoy your night, Chloe.
Fuck you.
Talk to me, bro, you look
like you're gonna kill someone.
You're desperate to
blow this thing up, huh?
'cause it's still good?
And you take good things
and you turn them into shit.
I've seen you do this.
She loves you, and she makes you happy.
And you fucking deserve this.
Come on, say it. Say.
Do you deserve it or not?
I deserve it.
Yes, you fucking deserve it.
And you'd better fight for it and keep it.
'cause it's the best fucking thing
that ever happened to you.
You either sort your shit out
and decide you're worth
something to someone
or you die sad and alone
and fucking perverted.
Dammit!
[upbeat music]
[crowd cheering]
[singing in foreign language]
Come on.
Ooh!
That was fucking great.
Can we give it up for
this lovely woman, please?
[crowd cheering]
Yes!
What a lovely woman and this lovely couple,
these two people...
- What's your name?
- Loukas, Loukas.
Ah, Loukas, what a man.
So nice.
Eleni is the name.
Okay, good, are you having fun tonight?
- Yeah.
- Cool.
Do you trust each other?
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's nice.
Did you ask each other before you got here,
how many people you slept with?
Whose dick she sucked
or anything like that...
- Come on, buddy.
- Don't worry, Argyris.
I got it.
I'm so sorry, Loukas.
I'm sorry, hold on, please.
The point is the past is the past,
and it's about the future, right?
Right, Christos?
Hey.
It's somebody else's party, you know?
Anyway, so it's not about the past.
It's about the future.
And when you meet someone
that you wanna die with,
that's the person you gotta hang on to.
And I don't wanna die alone,
I wanna die with you, Chloe Gains.
Okay?
So, do you wanna die with me?
Do you wanna...
Hey, Chloe, look at me.
You wanna be my future?
- Mickey, stop.
- Would you be my wife?
Come on.
- Come on. No, no.
- Hey.
- Please, come on.
Fuck.
So we just don't have a sink now?
[Mickey] What?
We don't have a sink now.
I called the guy, he was
supposed to come yesterday.
Baby, you have to call a professional.
He is. He's a fucking
plumber, okay? It's fine.
- He's gonna come today.
- It's been like this
for three days.
Don't start fucking with it
unless you know what you're doing.
I told you, just call someone, please.
Calm down.
- It's a fucking sink.
- Don't tell me to calm down.
- The place is like-
- Relax.
Don't tell me to fucking relax, Mickey.
Hector arrives on Monday.
- The place is in shit.
- So what?
We're not gonna have to take him
into the fucking kitchen, okay?
He can go to his room.
Oh, my God it's like living
- with a fucking teenager.
- We'll go to the fucking park
it's not a big deal.
No, I will have to fix
it, like everything else.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to get so upset.
I think I'm just scared.
I'm scared.
Well, I've had an idea.
- Was it-
- I bought you this.
It's a book of songs in Greek.
But I thought we could learn a kid song.
- And then we could get him to sing.
- Yeah?
There's like one that's really famous.
Here.
Okay?
Here, here.
Okay. [gentle music]
Yeah!
- So...
It's...
[singing in foreign language]
♪ What does that mean ♪
[Chloe laughs]
So it's like, I had a love
and my love was like a cloud.
- That sounds true.
- It's Greek.
[both laughing]
Okay, you play, you play.
- Okay, so-
- Ready?
What's this next part?
And then we do the chorus, is...
[singing in foreign language]
I'm gonna get us a drink.
You're so good.
[singing in foreign language]
What a dummy!
[Chloe laughing]
It's perfect.
Here.
Oh my God, are you serious?
Yeah, why not?
Yeah!
There she is.
My favorite person in the world!
Yeah!
You know what I wanna do?
What do you wanna do?
Can we go dance?
We haven't been dancing in so long.
[soft music]
This is pretty.
Uh-huh.
- It's nice.
- It's Christmas.
Come on.
Strict faces.
- Don't say nothing.
- Okay.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Hi, welcome.
- Welcome.
- Hi, hi, hi.
[speaking in foreign
language] Merry Christmas!
Have fun.
Thank you. Thank you.
Wow, this is crazy.
Hey.
Hi.
Can we get four shots of tequila?
Shots of tequila.
- Six of them.
- Six shots of tequila.
Six, baby.
- Sure?
- Yes.
Alright, okay.
It's our final weekend.
Final weekend before being parents.
Oh yeah.
All right.
- Okay, to whatever saints
- Oh my God.
The last weekend.
Fuck.
Can I have a gin and tonic?
Oh man, I could have been on
that goddam floor right now.
I could have done the whole game
and the thousands of
people, and the fucking...
Can you get drugs?
- Drugs?
- Can you get drugs?
- What do you mean drugs?
- Let's get some drugs.
You don't do drugs.
Yeah, but I wanna do some drugs now.
What drugs?
Just get some drugs.
You can get some drugs
here, don't you know people?
- Come on, get some-
- Yeah, I know people.
Get some drugs. Get some drugs.
Okay.
Okay. I'll wait here.
I'll wait here.
- Okay, I'll be back.
- Okay, bye.
- Stay right here.
- I'm here, I'm here.
I don't...
Yeah, but I don't know. Cocaine?
Whatever you have.
No, a gram?
No, no, no, I need like...
Never mind, never mind, never mind.
Hey.
Come outside.
Where did you get it?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Come on.
Where did you get the drugs?
It doesn't matter. I got it from somewhere.
- What are we doing?
- Come on, put it...
- Little bit.
- How much?
All of it, just fucking...
No, I may need some for later.
That's good, that's good.
Oh my God, why have I
never done this before?
You're gonna do the
one in the middle, okay?
- Okay.
- It's a big one.
- You're sure?
- I don't know.
I've never done it before.
- Okay.
- Okay. So just one...
Okay.
Go.
- Okay, there you go.
- Fuck!
You okay.
Wow.
- Okay.
You want another one.
All right, that's good.
Oh fuck!
Oh my God.
- You good?
- Yeah.
Okay, let's go.
Fuck. [upbeat music]
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Fallen tree, fallen
tree, fallen tree, fallen ♪
You're like a snowflake.
What?
You're like, white as a snowflake.
Do you still find me sexy?
Do you?
You are the sexiest woman I know.
You are.
- Hi.
- Oh, hi.
What's your name?
Caterina. Yours?
I'm Mickey, nice to meet you.
- Hi, Mickey.
- Come on.
It was really nice to meet you.
What are you doing?
Hey, you were dancing with the guy.
What was I supposed to do?
One second.
Don't worry about him.
It's okay.
[speaking in foreign language]
What's going on?
Come on, piss off.
Guys, don't fight. Don't fight.
Hey, hey.
What?
[speaking in foreign language]
You're a [speaking in foreign language].
That's what you are.
Hold on, wait a second.
Okay, okay.
Okay, give me a second.
I have the leather jacket.
It's Christmas.
It's fucking Christmas.
No wait, he didn't do anything!
Mickey!
He didn't do anything!
Okay, [speaking in foreign language],
and now I'm gonna have a
cigarette because I can,
because it's Greek.
Oh, let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
Don't! Let's go.
[soft music]
[car honking]
- Oh shit.
- Oh fuck.
Oh my God!
We should stop and have sex.
I wanna have sex with you.
- Really?
- I wanna have sex right now.
I want you to fuck me.
I'll fuck you.
Come on, let's stop somewhere.
Let's fuck somewhere.
Wait, wait.
Oh gosh, my heels.
I got you, I got you.
Fuck, this way.
This way.
[Chloe heaving]
Fuck.
Come on.
[Chloe sobbing]
Hey.
Hey, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
I'm so sorry.
What?
What's going on?
I love you.
I love you so, so much.
I love you too.
I have to tell you something.
I was pregnant and I'm
not pregnant anymore.
I had an abortion and it...
I didn't tell you.
I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not.
I didn't know you and I was not sure.
- It's okay.
- I thought you wouldn't want-
It's okay.
What do you mean it's okay?
Come on.
I don't understand why you're not upset.
You can be mad.
- I'm not mad.
- Why? Why not?
Because it doesn't fucking matter.
I mean we just...
What do you mean?
We used each other and it's okay.
Do you think I used you?
Listen, what I'm saying is,
you were coming out of your
shit with Christos and I...
- This has nothing to do with-
- And we had a crazy weekend
and it was fucking amazing and then...
You know, but like...
It doesn't matter because
I'm here and I love you
and I really mean that.
Have you no fucking
idea what I've been doing
to try and fucking keep us
together since we got together
and you're telling me that you think-
- I know. I know. I
know. Please, be quiet.
[speaking in foreign language]
- Shit.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Go, go, just go, let's go.
Come on.
Fuck.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Wait.
- What?
What happened?
What happened to us?
Remember the night we were on the beach?
I love that fucking night.
Yeah, and we were naked
and everything was great.
Yeah, we got arrested.
I have an idea.
Let's go to the beach.
Come on, let's go to the beach.
Are you fucking...
- Is that what you want?
- Oh my God.
You wanna go to the beach?
Let's go to the beach.
Fine. Let's go to the fucking beach.
- [Chloe] Let's go to the beach.
- Let's go to the fucking beach.
Oh my God.
You wanna go to the fucking beach?
Come on, let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Let's go to the fucking beach.
[mellow music]
Let's go to the beach.
Yeah!
Fuck, I love you so much.
I love you.
I love you. I love you.
I really, really love you.
Oh fuck!
This is fucking amazing.
Hi.
[speaking in foreign language]
No, no, no, no.
You wanna come to the beach?
[siren wailing]
- Go, go, go, go.
- Fuck!
Oh, great!
- Whoo!
- Oh, we're gonna die.
We're going to the beach.
- We're going to the beach!
There's two of them, I've got to pull over.
No, no, no.
Come on, I've gotta pull over.
No!
Okay.
Stop the bike.
- Fuck you!
- We're going to the beach.
Okay, okay, okay.
Fuck you.
Okay.
No, no, no, no.
Chloe!
Ow!
[phone ringing]
[speaking in foreign language]
Actual bodily harm.
Assault and affray.
[speaking in foreign language]
Driving under the influence.
Reckless endangerment.
[speaking in foreign language]
Evading an officer.
Indecent exposure.
[speaking in foreign language]
That's a lot of charges.
Can you tell us what's gonna happen?
What happens now?
Depends on what the judge says on Monday.
- What?
- Wait, what do you mean?
We can't do Monday.
Sir, we can't do Monday.
We have a legal thing. My son.
We can't stay here until Monday.
We can give the bail money or something.
It doesn't matter but we can't do Monday.
No.
- We can come back.
- Fuck!
[gentle music]
- Mickey!
- It's gonna be alright.
[speaking in foreign language]
Here, have a cigarette.
Yes, please.
It's really kind, I appreciate it.
[speaking in foreign language] I don't
understand English, but please be calm.
Everything will be over soon.
I don't understand.
Thank you.
[speaking in foreign language]
Wakey-wakey girls, move it!
- Hi.
I brought you some clothes.
Oh, thank you.
Put them on.
Wash your face, you'll feel better.
Thank you.
You will be fine.
Okay.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
[speaking in foreign language] The court
finds the defendant guilty as charged
and passes a six month sentence,
suspended for three years
as well as a €600 fine.
It's okay.
It's six months, suspended
for three years and 600 Euros.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
No, it's okay.
Where's Mickey? Where's my boyfriend?
Do you know what happened with him?
I think that his case was dismissed.
Oh.
Okay.
Look, how do I get these...
Don't worry about the clothes.
It's okay.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
- You're welcome.
- Thanks.
Bye.
Oh my God. Come here.
What are you doing here?
I thought you were getting out at 12.
[Chloe] How are you here?
I got here on Saturday.
Look at me. Hey.
What do you mean you got here on Saturday?
I got out. I got out early.
Well, obviously you got out early.
How did you get out
early? Stop touching me.
How did you get out?
I got out.
I made some phone calls.
I tried to call somebody,
I called Argyris and he...
Argyris got you out?
He hooked me up with someone
and I tried to get out
and I tried to get you out.
Who? Who did he hook you up with?
It doesn't matter.
Who did he hook you up with, Mickey?
Who did he hook you up with?
He called Christos.
- It's fine.
- You called Christos?
And Christos got you out
and you left me there?
I didn't leave you there, hold on.
- You left me there.
- I didn't leave you there.
I was gonna come back for you-
- For three fucking
days you left me there.
Listen to me.
I talked to him, I asked
him if he can get you out,
ask the DA or whatever and he said...
Any fucking idea what
you have fucking done?
Calm down. Listen to me.
No, I won't fucking calm down.
You called fucking Christos...
- Yes I did.
- And you left me
- in fucking prison.
- I didn't wanna leave you.
I didn't wanna leave you, listen to me.
For the fucking weekend
while you fucking sit here.
God, fuck you.
Oh my God, what am I fucking doing?
Fuck me?
Did I get us in jail?
Did I fucking hit a cop?
Did I tell me to take
my fucking clothes off?
Did I wanna run around fucking naked?
You dumb fucking thing!
Is that me? Did I wanna fuck with you?
Or was that you?
You hit a fucking cop.
I tried to get you out, he
couldn't fucking get you out.
I had to come here for fucking Hector
'cause I didn't know when the fuck
we were gonna get out and here we are.
[Chloe sobbing]
[indistinct chattering]
[gentle music]
Provided by
explosiveskull https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[singing in foreign language]
[gentle music]