(dramatic music)
(soft footsteps)
(woman screaming)
(horse galloping)
(man grunting)
(woman screaming)
(horse galloping)
(horse neighing)
(enchanting music)
- I've come to take you away.
(grunting)
(soulful music)
- [Miss Jane] Amanda is
the name, and judging from
her accent, I do believe
she is from the south.
Her husband's in town so please stay away
from the strip and the shows.
♪ You damn right I've got the blues ♪
♪ From my hair down to my shoes ♪
- [Miss Jane] She just wants
some in-house servicing.
Make sure she pays upfront.
I've never done business with her before.
♪ I can't win ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't have a thing to lose ♪
- Miss Jane?
- What is it, baby?
♪ You know I just want to use the phone ♪
- Never mind.
♪ I stopped by my daughter's house ♪
♪ You know, I just want to use the phone ♪
- [Miss Jane] Is something wrong, Navy?
- No.
- [Miss Jane] You do
know that if there's ever
anything wrong...
You would just come to me, right?
You've always been my favorite.
(Upbeat Blues music)
- [Braydon] Look at that shit.
- [Navy] Oh yeah, I
talked to her one night
on the strip.
It's a fucking whacked chick.
She kept talking and
talking about this knight
in shining armor who's
gonna come and rescue her.
- You sayin' she's some sorta...
Princess, some bullshit like that?
- She will just be another statistic
lying face down in the gutter.
♪ You know I can't win, now people ♪
- So Mary Jo.
Where you been?
Didn't see ya around lately.
- I've, I've been around.
I've been around.
What are you lookin' at?
(snickering)
- Anyway, pass the Tabasco.
(upbeat Blues music)
♪ Yeah ♪
- Do you guys ever wonder if there's more
to life than this, huh?
(guys laughing)
- Navy, man, you fuck only
beautiful, rich women,
and you have the audacity to
ask is there more to life.
For you, Navy, no.
- I'm thinking about
gettin' out of this city,
you know?
Livin' up north, maybe, I
don't know, maybe Montana.
- Hey Arnold Zifferman, this
isn't fucking Green Acres.
You gotta snap out of it.
- Shit man, you're a gigolo, man.
That's the god damn American
dream, yeah, you know.
(laughing)
- You know, feeling
guilty, that'd make you
better than us.
We'll see ya at nine?
♪ You damn right I've got the blues ♪
♪ You damn right I've got the the blues ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
(car door slams)
- Miserable fucking whore, you need me.
You need me!
Fuck, do you need some money?
You know what?
Keep all of it, huh?
(Mary Jo cries out)
My coke ain't cheap!
Get outta here.
I'm the man!
I am the man!
That's it.
(Mary Jo crying)
Pick it up.
Pick it up!
(Mary Jo crying)
I'm going to piss all
over your fucking head
right now, bitch.
Do you understand what I'm sayin'?
What up, bro?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What the fuck you doin', bro?
What the fuck are you doing?
What the duck are you doing?
Hold on here, man, whoa.
Hold on right there, man, all right?
You want the chick?
You can have the chick.
Big man, huh?
Take a little bit of that.
That's her cocaine for you, okay?
It keeps her happy.
Fuck you, man!
Fuck you, huh?
Okay, dude.
Yeah, yeah, you want a piece of me?
Come after me, motherfucker.
Hey, fuck you!
(Benny spits loudly)
Piece of shit!
There you go, fuck her from
behind right there, baby.
Yeah, that's it!
- It's all right.
Pick this up.
(Mary Jo sniffling)
(Navy sighs)
- [Benny] Fuck!
Nice.
(spits loudly)
Yeah, nice.
(car engine turns and revs)
(tires squealing)
(gentle music)
(vocalizing)
- Hey.
That's a pretty fire.
So, did we fuck?
You goin' someplace?
- Uh, yeah.
I'm leaving.
I'm uh, driving to Montana.
- Huh, so I guess you
didn't feel like packing.
- Where should I take you?
Do you have a place?
- How about I go with you?
- I'm sorry, I can't do that.
- Why?
- [Navy] I just can't.
- I'm really being serious, you know?
Look, it's a really long drive
and well, I can help you
do some of the driving,
you know?
And I have this really cool book.
It has all these stories like Cinderella
and the Wonderful Wizard of Oz.
And King Arthur and His Court.
Well, a lot of stuff like that and I can
just read it to you and
it would pass the time.
I mean look at me.
I'm pretty low maintenance.
My name's Mary Jo, what's yours?
- Navy.
- Navy?
- Yep.
Why don't you grab your things.
I'll take you to your place, okay?
(upbeat music)
- It's uh, it's my day-job.
I dreamt of you.
You saved me in this dream I had.
And you said, I've come to take you away.
- I can't take care of you.
I'm all fucked up.
- I cam take care of you.
- I gotta go.
- Have fun in Missouri.
- Montana.
("Jam It Jam" by She Rockers)
- So this light from
heaven shines up above him.
- Light from heaven.
Go on.
- Well then he puts me on his wild horse.
- [Monet] Wild horse.
Wow, it must've been thrilling.
- It was.
Monet, get this.
I don't remember a thing, right?
Until I wake up the next
morning and all his stuff
is in this huge pile and
there's like all these
precious jewels and stuff.
And he gets down on one knee and he says,
I've burned all my worldly possessions
for the greater love of thee.
- Wow, Mary Jo.
(Monet chuckles)
- So I say, where will we go?
And then he said, I will
take you to my palace.
I mean, I was speechless.
- Now that's hard to believe.
- I was, believe it.
I mean, never before in my entire life
have I been championed so greatly.
- Yeah, so what's this
champion's name, huh?
- Navy.
It's a great story, Mary Jo.
You have one hell of an imagination.
- He's gonna be here any
minute now to get me.
- Yeah, of course he will.
- [Mary Jo] Any second now.
- Mary Jo, why do you do this to yourself?
- Any moment now.
(enchanting music)
- Come on, let's go.
- Who's this?
(charming music)
- It's Navy.
Have you come back for me?
- Yeah, so uh, why don't
you grab your things
and let's go.
(enchanting music)
What's wrong?
- I can't move my legs.
- I'll carry you out then.
Come on, baby.
Let's go.
(Navy groans)
(upbeat dance music)
(background chatter)
- Shortly afterward, the crocodile made
a sound so very human that
it was almost a remark.
Ac-acho observed the reptile.
Ac-acho, ac-acho, ac-acho it repeated
in intervals.
Opening its jaws wide every time.
So how many has that been?
- I think about 13.
Not including Cinderella
which you read twice.
(Mary Jo sighs)
- Wow, we're going to Missouri.
(Mary Jo chuckles)
- It's Montana.
- Oh, okay, wow, we're
going to Montana, ah!
(Mary Jo sighs)
You know, when we get
there we're gonna have to
get a house, like a brick one, you know,
like the smart little piggy did.
And of course, you'll have to build it
and I'll decorate it.
Oh, and we'll get lots
of friendly farm animals
like cows and chickens and sheep
and camels and pandas.
And there's the whole issue of kids.
Um, well at least two but
no more than 10, okay?
And that way we can live
happily, happily ever after.
Do you think I'm pretty?
- Yeah.
- Do you think I'm cute
pretty or pretty pretty?
- Look, are you gonna
talk the entire trip, huh?
I mean, the reading you warned me about,
but the questions--
- Fine.
Anyway, where were we?
- How old are you, 12?
- 36.
- 36, you're not 36.
What's this?
Mary Jo Tetelen from Houston, Texas.
Where did you get this?
- What do you mean?
It's legit, look.
Look at my picture, see?
Born March 6th and I'm a Pisces.
- That doesn't look anything like you.
- That is because I don't
photograph well, okay?
Look, I'm obviously
much cuter in real life
than I am in pictures or else I would've
been a model.
- No water.
No water.
We are going to follow the
rules of the road here.
- Rules of the road?
- Yes, the rules of the road.
Which means we only stop to get gas.
And we never, never stop to eat.
I knew it.
- And what exactly are
you doing over there, huh?
- I might as well since we had to stop
because your bladder was going to burst.
- Wait a second, I really
thought it was going to, okay?
- Put your seatbelt on.
- You know, you'd make a great husband.
You would.
I mean, I'm being completely serious.
The whole rules of the road, I mean,
that is so male.
It's a real turn on.
- Well then follow them, shit.
- You know, I can just
see you with your kids
on Christmas Day.
- I don't have any kids.
- Oh I know, I'm just when we do.
Well, when you do, with your wife
or whoever.
And I can just picture
you there with your son
in the driveway showing
him how to use his new
remote control car.
And you have this baseball hat on
and these flannel pajamas
with big fuzzy slippers.
(Mary Jo chuckles)
- Fuzzy slippers?
- Yeah, yeah, it's must what I see.
You know, I can't help it.
Oh and you know what?
There is something else.
Oh wait, yep, I'm seeing your wife.
And she's got like long brown hair.
Kinda like me.
And big blue eyes, kinda like me.
And a smile kinda like mine.
And well, in general, she's
looking a lot like me.
And she's looking on with love.
(Navy sighs)
(gentle rock music)
(bell dings)
- [Cook] Melly, pickup BLT.
- Thank you.
- All right, two corn dogs.
A fry and a root beer float.
- Is that three scoops?
- Three scoops.
- So what was the bonfire all about, huh?
- I didn't need my stuff anymore.
- You know, I've done this before.
- Done what?
- You know, just gone off with someone.
Except they were never serious, you know?
Where did you get a cool name like Navy?
- My mom.
Like sailors, booze, and one night stands.
Voila, here I am.
- So what happened to her?
- She left me at a department
store on my birthday.
And I never saw her again.
(Mary Jo laughing hysterically)
So what about your family?
- I don't have any.
- I figured.
So listen, about Montana.
- What?
- Well.
Why don't you just finish
what you're eatin',
so we can get back on the road?
Make sure you pee first.
- All right.
♪ So long since I made a friend ♪
♪ Old wounds that I have to mend ♪
♪ I keep waiting for the long run ♪
♪ Inside ♪
♪ My faith is a glowing sun ♪
♪ And sometimes he's the only one ♪
♪ Who shines ♪
♪ When the ice falls all around me ♪
- [Mary Jo] It was tossed up.
A toy of the waves was thrown upon
the level sandy beach.
And now some part floats
amoat in the sunbeam.
Some part falls in a dew.
Some part has become a
happy, graceful flower.
And some part billows and
sweeps in the distant shores.
And today some part pours silent blessings
from that white cloud which drifts idly
in the high blue air far above your head.
The end.
- That's great.
- I have this uncontrollable urge to stick
my gum in your ear.
- That's great.
(Mary Jo giggles)
What are you doing?
- What?
What did you do that for?
(Mary Jo gasps)
Are you fucking crazy?
What, do you think it's fucking easy
to get coke in Utah?
God!
Asshole, asshole!
- That stuff will kill you, all right?
I know exactly how you feel.
Exactly.
- There.
- What, are you nuts?
- There!
There!
How does that feel?
- No!
(tires squealing)
Shit.
- Huh, how does that feel?
Huh, ha ha ha.
How does it feel, huh?
How does it feel?
Ha, serves you right.
Serves you right, stupid.
How does it feel, huh?
Monkey see, monkey do, ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha.
- Here's your shit.
Here's 200 bucks.
Do whatever you want.
Go back to Vegas, I don't care.
You are no longer my problem.
It's been fun, bye.
Shit.
All right, just start up the car
and drive away.
Come on, let's go.
- Did you miss me?
- Just uh, just get in the car.
Unbelievable.
♪ Your knuckles whiten on the wheel ♪
♪ The last thing that
your hands will feel ♪
♪ Your final flight can't be delayed ♪
♪ No earth, just sky it's so surreal ♪
- I'm sorry about the money.
I am, I really am.
- Don't worry about it.
It's only money, okay?
- My real name is Rachel.
- What?
(Rachel sighs)
- I said, my real name is Rachel.
- So you're not 36 and from Texas?
- Hey, are we in a hurry?
- Pfft, what, am I driving too fast?
- No, I, I just wanna stop
someplace, that's all.
- Dammit, you know what?
You've got to stop drinking so much water.
- No, excuse me.
It's not that, okay?
It's just, it's only about
20 minutes from here.
Okay?
♪ I'm standing warm against the cold ♪
♪ Now that the flames have taken hold ♪
♪ At least you left your life in style ♪
♪ And for far as I can see ♪
♪ Ten twisted grills grin back at me ♪
♪ Bad money dies I love the scene ♪
♪ Sometimes I fantasize ♪
♪ When the streets are cold and lonely ♪
♪ And the cars they burn below me ♪
♪ Don't these times fill your eyes ♪
♪ When the streets are cold and lonely ♪
♪ And the cars they burn below me ♪
(children chattering)
- Rachel?
Rachel, is that--
- Hi Dad.
- Oh, what a surprise.
What a wonderful surprise.
Oh.
I've prayed to see your face again.
So many times.
Oh.
- Navy.
Dad, this is um, Navy.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
- Well you're just in time for dinner.
Come on in.
I gotta tell ya, I'm just so, so happy
that you came by.
Come on in.
That's fine, Navy.
Leave the door open, it's all right.
The house has changed a little bit
but it's still...
It's still the same place, you know?
Honey, I'd like ya to meet somebody.
Come on in this way.
Rachel, this is my wife, Joanne.
This is my daughter, Rachel.
- Hello.
- Joanne and I were married two years ago
in the temple.
Oh, and this is Joanne's
youngest one, Paige.
Honey, this is Rachel's friend, Navy.
And hopefully they're
gonna be staying with us
a night or two, okay?
- Please, we've got plenty of room.
- I'll be back.
I always kept an extra bed in here
just in case you ever came home.
Honey, you know, it's been six years.
You didn't really expect to find your room
exactly the way you left it, did ya?
Huh?
(spooky ambience)
- Billy, wait.
- Is Billy around?
- Oh yeah.
He got a girl pregnant, married her
and they live in some trailer park
the other end of town.
- You have not changed, have you, Dad?
- What?
- I said, you haven't changed.
- Hi.
- [Stan] Oh hi, Lilli.
That's Rachel's friend, Navy.
And this is my daughter, Rachel.
You remember, I told you about her?
- [Lilli] Yeah.
- This is Joanne's eldest daughter, Lilli.
- Hi.
- Lilli was the first
runner up in the Miss Utah
pageant last year.
- Mother, please.
- Well she was.
(carousel music)
Well, Joanne, would you
offer up the prayers
for this meal?
- Our dear kind and
gracious heavenly father.
We are so grateful for this day
and for all of our many blessings.
We are thankful for our family
and for our home.
And heavenly father at this time we ask
a special blessing that
will be strengthening
and nourishing to our bodies and that it
might do us the good that we need.
We pray for these things in the name
of our beloved son, Jesus Christ, amen.
- [All] Amen.
- Awesome.
- Everything looks wonderful.
Just great, honey, great job.
So where were you two headed?
- Montana.
- Oh Montana.
What's in Montana?
- Oh, Navy has a real bug home there.
It's kind of like a castle.
Could you please pass the potatoes?
- Oh it's not that big.
It's not a castle.
- So Navy, your job?
In Las Vegas, what were you in?
- Investments.
Financial investments, yeah.
- Hmm.
Must be rewarding, huh?
- No, not as much as you think.
- Rachel, what exactly were you doing
in Las Vegas?
- [Stan] Honey, would you
pass the string beans, please?
- Actually, I was on my knees a lot.
You know, scrubbing floors,
kind of like Cinderella.
And then Navy found my
glass slipper and now
I'm a princess.
Where is the applesauce?
- Applesauce.
Give her the applesauce.
Who's up for ham?
- I'll have some.
- [Stan] Okay, big slice, little slice.
- Big slice is great.
- [Stan] Big piece, little piece?
- [Navy] Big piece.
- All right.
- Hi.
- Do you have blankets and stuff?
- Oh yeah, I got enough.
So where's your real mom?
- She died a long time ago.
- Oh, sorry.
Listen, I'm gonna be...
I'm gonna be heading off tomorrow morning.
- Oh, okay, we're in a rush.
That's okay.
We'll leave tomorrow
morning then, that's fine.
- No, I'm going to be
heading off tomorrow morning
without you.
- What?
- Look, Rachel, I just gotta get going
and you got a lot to deal with here.
- No, no I don't.
Navy, I just brought you here so that
you could meet my dad and stuff.
I don't need to do anything.
- Rachel, you are not
listening to me, okay.
I'm leaving tomorrow morning by myself
like I planned.
Rachel?
- Can I turn off the light?
- It's your room.
Hey.
Do you always get what you pray for?
- Most of the time.
- Could you pray that Navy
won't leave me tomorrow?
- Sure.
(ignition clicking)
(gentle music)
(children chattering)
- [Navy] Well, the
mechanic says it'll take
about three days to get a part for my car.
Said the starter was completely removed.
And just so you know, I know you did it.
- Did what?
- Look it, look it, if
you touch my car again--
- Yeah, yeah, you'll what?
You'll what?
I didn't do it, Navy.
Besides I knew you
weren't going to leave me
here anyway.
- Look, I never said
anything about taking you
to Montana.
I was waiting to do the right thing.
And leaving you here is
the right thing to do.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
(man whistling)
- Let's go.
- Look, look, those guys.
They call them tenters, they come here
about once a year, and
they camp in the mountains.
Hey.
(tenters cheering)
They're like gypsies, they
move from place to place.
- [Navy] Great.
- That's him, that's him.
I told you he was hot, huh?
Oh gosh, look how slutty she's dressed.
- Hey, you two, how you doing?
- Oh, pretty good.
- Lilli will be here
in a couple of minutes
to take your order, okay?
Have anything you want on me.
- Oh, my God, oh, my God, it's Jay.
Look at how clean cut he is.
- Yeah well he's been
home from his mission
for a couple of years now.
He married the Bishop's daughter, Peggy.
- Now that's really funny
because, see we used to
get stoned every Saturday
night behind the house
and he swore up and down
that he wouldn't go on one.
- Well Rachel, maybe
he's cleaned up his act.
- Hmm, too bad none of your kids
could've turned out that good.
- I've got to go.
- Well, they seem to be happy.
- Yeah, right.
Look at her.
She's a molly-queen.
She makes Marie Osmond look like Madonna.
All she used to say was, nice to see ya.
And, oh my heck.
You know what, a friendly word of advice.
Stay away from anybody who
ends a sentence with ya,
see ya, nice to meet ya.
Give me a break.
- Hey, what can I get ya?
(upbeat piano music)
- Back, yes and yes.
Smile, enjoy yourself.
(Rachel sighs loudly)
Sweetheart, I think
that's enough for tonight.
Okay, why don't you run up and go to bed.
Goodnight, sweetheart.
- Goodnight, mom.
(gentle piano music)
- You like chess, Lilli?
- I better go check the cookies.
- Yeah, you better do that.
(Rachel sighs)
So dad, you seen Billy lately?
- Yeah, a couple of days ago he was,
he was over here for something.
I don't know.
- Mm, why?
Doesn't he come over for dinner and chess?
- Rachel, don't start, okay?
- Stan, she likes to argue.
- Rachel, Billy's been sick.
And it's all I have to do is pray now.
So he can find his way back, all right?
- So that's why you never
came looking for me, huh?
Too busy praying.
Well your praying doesn't work.
- You're here aren't ya?
- I'm gonna go see Billy.
(gentle guitar music)
- [Billy] Oh my God.
Oh, my God.
(Rachel laughing)
Oh dude.
I cannot believe.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Would you like a
cookie, it's fresh baked.
- Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
- You mind if I sit down?
- No, no, go ahead.
Best cookie I ever had.
- Yeah?
- So, how ya been?
- You know me.
I manage.
- Look, Rach.
Everybody knows.
They know what you were doing in Vegas.
- I don't care.
- You should never have sent that letter
to Sarah.
I mean, she has the biggest fucking mouth
in all of Fall Valley.
- That stupid bitch.
- I mean, dad and me were a mess.
♪ Now it's time to face the music ♪
- He's got a whole new family now.
- Yeah.
- Lilli?
She was almost Miss Utah.
(both laughing)
And Paige, Paige most definitely some day
will be...
- [Both] Miss Utah.
- You were runner up for Miss Utah?
- Yeah.
Yep.
I'm a tomboy really, you know.
But my mom sort of turned me into
this pageant girl, I guess.
- So did you ever meet
Regis and Kathie Lee?
- No, but I got to meet the Osmonds once.
It was great.
- I know.
- So you play any football or anything?
- Not since I was a little kid.
- No?
Well a bunch of us are playing tomorrow
if you'd like to play.
(Billy sighs)
- Dad tell you I have a little girl?
- [Rachel] Yeah.
- She's beautiful.
Reminds me of you when you were little.
- Really?
- [Billy] Named her after mom.
- She wasn't perfect, Billy.
(Billy sighs)
- [Billy] God, I'm glad you're back.
Look, I gotta go.
Walk.
- You walk?
- Yeah.
(background chatter)
- [man] Get him, Rachel.
(glass shattering)
(Rachel coughing)
- What's going on?
- [Stan] I don't know.
- [Navy] Listen uh--
- [Stan] Oh, my God.
- [Navy] I'll clean her up
and put her to bed, okay?
(Rachel moans)
Come on, it's okay.
Sorry.
(Rachel giggling)
Come on.
- [Rachel] Wait.
(Rachel vomiting)
- It's okay, (mumbling).
Come on, come on.
(Navy groaning)
There you go.
- [Rachel] Bye.
- [Joanne] Girls, I
want you to go upstairs
and go to bed now.
- We're going.
- I know, (mumbling).
A bad spirit came into this house
the moment she got here.
- [Rachel] Whoa, a bad
spirit in this house.
(Rachel laughing)
- I'm gonna clean it up.
- [Rachel] Clean it up, clean it up.
- [Child] Come on.
- Oh, I feel like shit.
Nice doilies.
- Thanks, I love this dress.
- [Rachel] Are you wearing that to school?
- No, it's 3:30.
I'm going to ward flag football game.
You wanna come?
- Oh, can I please?
Hey.
I'm sorry.
- Well, Navy's playing.
(gentle music)
(background chatter)
(crowd cheering)
- [Rachel] Hey Navy.
- Here, I'll be right there.
- [Female] Okay, clean it
up guys, we're up 14-7.
Come on.
- Look, I'm sorry about last night, okay?
They just kept handing me those shots.
- It's okay, I understand.
- Well, it looks like you're
really fitting in here.
- Well the people are friendly, you know?
- Oh yeah.
- Hey Navy, we're back on offense.
- I bet they are.
- Just a second.
You wanna play?
- Yeah, right.
Um, listen.
Billy and some of his
friends are getting together
tonight at the bar to
play pool, and well Billy
really wanted to meet you,
you know, so you wanna come?
- Yeah, sure, why not?
See ya.
- See ya tonight.
- Wait up.
- Nice shot, would you like a shot?
- Yeah.
So, what should we drink to?
- [Rachel] Me.
- You, welcome home.
- We're leaving in a
couple days, right Navy?
Are you gonna tell Lilli about us?
Or am I going to have to?
- What are you talking about?
(upbeat rock music)
(background chatter)
♪ Are you strong enough ♪
♪ Give me what I want ♪
♪ Can you please me, right now ♪
♪ Are you strong enough ♪
♪ Give me what I want ♪
♪ Can you please me, right now ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Now, now, now, now, now ♪
- [Man] Get her, Pete, get her, Pete.
♪ So you know my name ♪
- Hey, you know what, I got to go, okay?
- [Man] Get her, Pete.
- Come on, baby, we're
just getting started.
- Stop, get off of me!
Come on, get off of me!
Go ahead, get off of me!
Come on, let me go.
Let me go, asshole.
Get off of me.
Go ahead, get off of me.
- Listen, all right, she's a little drunk.
Just leave her alone and I'll
take her home, all right?
- Hey, why don't you just
go the fuck home, huh?
Huh, huh, huh, huh?
- I can't, okay, all right?
- [Pete] I guess you
didn't understand me, huh?
- Listen, I don't want any trouble.
- I don't think...
(Navy groaning)
- [Rachel] Hey!
Hey you guys don't know
who you're dealing with.
Hey Navy!
Get up, come on.
Punch them!
Navy, fight, fight.
Navy!
- [Man] Hey!
Had enough?
- All right, get out of here.
Let's go, come on.
- Navy?
Are you okay?
- You stay away from me.
- What?
- You get away from me
and never touch me again.
- What is your problem?
- What is my problem?
Are you kidding?
My nose feels like it's broken.
But that is not my problem.
You are my fucking problem.
You are.
- It's not my fault that you can't fight.
- Fuck you, Rachel, fuck you!
You know what?
I am through with your
immature fucking shit.
All the drugs, you know, all the flirting,
and all that prince and princesses
in a castle in Montana,
it's fucking bullshit
and you're bullshit.
And you fucking know it.
- I'm sorry.
- Well you know what?
You know what?
I forgive you, now leave me alone.
Leave me alone.
(background chatter)
- Navy, are you okay?
Oh my heck.
Did somebody hit you?
- Yeah.
- Let me see.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You poor thing, let me look.
Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'll be fine.
- Do you want any aspirin or anything?
So you'll be okay then?
- Yeah, yeah, I'll be fine, thanks.
- Well, I better get to bed.
Goodnight.
- Goodnight.
- Did you want me to shut
the light off for ya?
- Yeah.
- Navy, I don't...
- You bitch, you fucking bitch.
Get off of me.
I fucking hate you.
- What is wrong with you?
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
(Navy groaning)
(gentle music)
- Hey.
Can I get a hit?
- What's your name?
- Mary Jo.
(whimsical music)
(Rachel crying)
- [Mother] Billy, Rachel, come here.
(woeful music)
(gunshot)
- I cleared out the basement for ya.
So if you decide that you'd
like to stay, you can.
(gentle piano music)
You're thinking about Rachel, huh?
- Yeah.
I um, I just feel bad about last night.
I didn't mean to hurt her like that.
I don't know.
I just don't know what to do.
- [Lilli] That's the temple.
- [Navy] I've never seen anything like it.
- No?
- Hmm-mm.
- Hm.
Oh, you know, I'll only
get married in a temple.
- You have to be a Mormon to be married
in the temple?
- Yeah.
Most of my friends are married, you know.
And they say it's wonderful.
- What's wonderful?
- Being married.
I can barely wait.
- Yeah.
- So, would you, would you like to know
more about the church?
- Don't stop, you look wonderful.
- Yeah, this isn't exactly
my kind of dancing, you know?
- Well, I can show you.
Third, your heel touches
the inside of your foot.
This arm comes up, and this is down.
Fourth, your foot slides up.
And we change arms.
And fifth, you heel touches your toe.
And back, ta-da.
- Ta-da.
(both laughing)
So, have you seen Navy?
- Yeah, he's with Lilli.
They're picking up the car.
- Oh.
You know, I betcha anything that Lilli's
the one that messed with Navy's car.
- I took auto shop last year.
- [Rachel] Now you're it, you're it.
- [Paige] It's a coin
my grandfather gave me.
He said it's from the ancient Lamenites.
It'll grant you what you wish.
Any wish imaginable.
If you just throw it on
water that lays still.
I want you to have it.
- Oh, Paige, I can't, I--
- Please.
- All right.
Does this mean I can
consider you my sister?
- Of course.
- Yeah.
- I am your sister.
- Okay.
(gentle instrumental music)
(audience applauding)
Hi.
- Hi.
She was really good, wasn't she?
- Yeah, yeah she was.
(upbeat piano music)
- You're really falling for her, right?
Just tell me you're not
gonna do this to me.
Tell me that you're not
gonna move into my house
and marry my evil stepsister and live
happily ever after in my own backyard.
Okay, just say you're not gonna break
my heart like that.
Navy, I have my problems, I know.
In the bar the other night, I just,
I wanted you to have
to save me like before.
- Rachel, forget about it.
This has nothing to do with the bar.
- Then why are you doing this to me?
I thought you were gonna
go to Montana, Navy.
You know, this isn't Montana.
It's Utah.
- Maybe, maybe this is Montana.
Maybe Montana was just a
thing I was looking for.
- Then why did you come back for me?
- For a million different reasons.
But not the one you're looking for
and I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
(sorrowful music)
- Aren't you a little
old to be hanging out
in playgrounds?
And I'm sorry about the other night.
Friends got a little rowdy.
My name is Cole.
Those guys over there monkeying around,
that's G and Samantha.
They're harmless.
They just like to party a lot.
- So you guys are, you're tenters right?
- Tenters, that's what you guys call us?
Well I prefer to be called fucked up, but,
tenters does have a nice ring to it.
My God, you smiled.
What a beautiful smile.
You did it again.
So uh, you gonna sit
here and swing all day?
Why don't you come with us?
We're having like a
little rave at the camp.
It's great.
You never raved before, have you?
- Hmm-mm.
I don't even know what it is.
What is it?
- You know what?
Why don't you come with us.
I'll show you.
It's real easy.
It's like, it's kind of like dancing
but, well I'll show ya.
You'll like it.
I got your sweater.
I'm watching it.
(gentle music)
Yeah, yeah, it's beautiful here, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- If I were to kill
myself, uh, I'd kill myself
right here.
I'd want this to be the
last thing I ever saw.
Listen to this.
You'll like this.
Help me!
(echo)
Did you hear that?
Yeah, it's my own fucking voice
bouncing off the rocks, mocking me.
(Cole sighs)
All right.
Go ahead, you try.
Scream, scream help me.
- Help me!
(echo)
(Rachel laughing)
Wow, I like it here.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- I'm glad you dig it.
You look a little nippy.
Here is my coat.
(upbeat rock music)
(background chatter)
This is my family.
I feel safe here.
I never really felt safe
growing up, you know?
- Yes, I do.
- I hated my real family.
I'm gonna go see my family.
- Hey.
Thanks for this.
I've been having a really nice time.
- Hey, we're leaving tomorrow morning
going to Wyoming.
You can come if you promise me two things.
- Yeah, what?
- One, you smile for
me at least once a day.
And two, once you join us,
you gotta stay with us.
You can never leave.
That is our pact.
If you decide to go meet
me at your swing at nIne.
Come on.
You just gotta close your eyes and move
your head real slow.
It's real easy actually.
It's kind of crazy.
Just be careful, these
people are very physical
around here.
You have to put yourself
in here like that.
Yeah, there you go.
There we go, yeah, oh.
(upbeat rock music)
(knocking at door)
- Hi, Jed.
- Hi, Stan, how are ya?
- What's the matter?
- Sorry to bother ya but the gentleman
that's staying with you
is driving a stolen car
and it belongs to this lady.
- What?
Stolen?
- Navy!
("Space Age Love Song"
by A Flock of Seagulls)
- Lilli, I'm not who you think I am.
I have a lot of skeletons.
- Navy, me too, I mean, when I was 13,
one time I, I smoked
cigarettes for two weeks
and one time my parents went out of town
and I got really drunk.
And I almost had sex with
this black football player
at Dixie College.
- I've done a lot worse.
If you only knew.
- Navy, please don't make fun of me, okay?
If any of my friends knew that I did
half of the stuff, they would never talk
to me again.
- I need to tell ya what
I was doing in Vegas.
- I don't wanna know.
And I don't care.
All I care about is how
I feel about you, Navy.
- Hey, hey, hey, it's okay.
- It's hard for me.
- It's okay, it's okay.
Come here, come here.
♪ I saw your eyes ♪
♪ And they touched my mind ♪
♪ Although it took a while ♪
♪ I was falling in love ♪
- Hey.
What's up?
- Navy, there's a lady in the kitchen
who would like to speak to you.
- Here.
- Sit your ass down.
What is the matter with you?
Did you know I was worried sick over you?
You did not tell anybody.
You just left!
That's so rude.
- [Navy] I just couldn't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
- You stupid little fuck!
You are sorry.
I called every damn police
officer in the world
to find out where you are.
I saw the law!
I didn't buy you that fucking car
so you could go joyriding in Utah.
Come here.
Come on.
Pack your stuff and we're going to go back
tonight, okay?
Come on.
- I'm not going back.
- What?
- I said I am not going back.
- I don't have time for your stupid little
immature temper tantrum.
Do you understand?
Who are you without me, hm?
You are the same punk teenager
who stood on the street corners soliciting
dirty old men.
I took you off the streets.
I treated you like you were my own son
and this is the thanks that I get.
Now let's get going and that is final.
- You are not listening to me, all right?
I don't care if you
take every penny I have,
you can keep the car and
take the car, I don't care.
I am not going back with you.
- Let go of my arm, you're hurting me.
(Navy sniffling)
You can keep the fucking car.
It's replaceable just like you.
- [Joanne] Lilli, why
don't you go upstairs
and go to bed.
We have church in the morning.
("Virtual Blue" by Coppè)
- [Rachel] What was the
happiest day of your life?
- I don't know.
- You ask me.
- All right, what was the happiest day
of your life?
- The day I met you.
♪ I wanna see you in this virtual blue ♪
♪ Your golden hair ♪
♪ Sweep my tat ♪
♪ Two to tango in this virtual blue ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ I don't care if we do, do, do ♪
♪ I want you ♪
- Oh hi, honey.
- I just came to say goodbye.
- Rachel.
Rachel.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
(whimsical music)
- Thank you, daddy.
- So where are you goin'?
- Does it matter?
- Listen, I...
I'm sorry about...
About how all this turned out.
- [Cole] Rachel!
- I gotta go.
- Listen, Rachel.
Rachel.
Please don't leave.
- Where is she going?
It's your fault.
Dear mom and dad.
I'm leaving with Rachel.
I'll write to you soon.
Love, Paige.
P.S.
Please don't be mad.
(mellow music)
- [Navy] Mr. Hodges, I just want to
thank you for everything.
- [Stan] Are you leaving?
- [Navy] Yeah.
- Good luck, Navy.
- [Billy] Take it easy, man.
- Stan, Stan!
- Yes?
- My baby's gone.
- What?
What the...
- Right over here.
It's okay, you can stay in my tent.
- Right here?
- Yeah, this is it.
- I don't know what's the matter with me.
- Could you take me home?
- What?
- I wanna go home.
- Why don't you sit tight here.
You made a promise, remember?
You haven't smiled all day.
You hurt my feelings.
(gentle guitar music)
- Hey, I'm going to take off.
I'll just hitch another ride.
- What's wrong?
Everything is all right.
We just needed some gas money.
Just hang for awhile.
- I understand, okay?
It's okay, I'll just go.
- No, no, no, wait a minute there.
I said don't leave.
You don't just leave.
There's an order to things here.
Isn't there?
All right first, now we steal your money.
- [Samantha] There's no money, Cole.
- Now you know what, since you don't
have any money, well...
I will fuck you up the ass.
And finally, you know, I
will blow your brains out.
And you wanted to leave after only being
a third done with the ceremony.
Shame on you!
Bad, bad, bad!
- Come on.
(police siren blares)
- Oh my God.
Oh I do have a surprise for you.
Look who has been looking for you.
- Paige, what are you doing here?
- I had to find you.
- Okay you guys.
Let her go, let her go, okay, she's just
a little girl, okay?
Just let her go, let her go, please.
- Would you shut the fuck up?
- [G] Hey what you got under that dress?
- Get away from her.
- Get back, get back, hey.
Get back, hey, hey, hey.
You know what?
Let's get them out of here.
Come on, come on.
(intense music)
- [Rachel] Could you
pull over, I need to pee.
- [Cole] Oh, you need to pee.
Oh well.
- Paige, you need to go too, right?
(Paige crying)
- [Cole] Now hurry.
Are your shoes tied?
- Yeah, of course.
This is the best part.
- Oh yeah?
(Paige crying)
- Hey.
- I'm so scared.
- Listen to me.
- We're gonna die.
- Sh, listen to me, listen to me, okay?
- No, we're not gonna die.
We're not gonna die.
I need you to look at me.
Look at me!
You are not going to die.
- Yes, I am.
- You're not.
Look at the mountains.
We're gonna run, okay?
You and I, we're gonna do it together.
We're gonna run.
We're gonna run and
we're gonna keep running
no matter what happens.
Whatever happens, you keep running.
(Paige crying)
Okay?
We can do it.
Okay, you ready?
Come on.
One, two, three, go, go, go.
Go!
- There they go!
Whew!
(intense music)
Whew, whew!
(G yelping)
(intense music)
- [Cole] Come on.
(G yelping)
- Keep running.
Run, Paige, run, keep running.
Don't look back, okay?
I'm right behind you.
Keep running.
(G yelping)
- [Billy] Rachel's bag.
Come on.
(intense music)
(G laughing)
- Hey, shut the fuck up
and go get the Molly.
(Rachel screaming)
(loud thud)
- Rachel!
- I liked you.
I thought you were one of us.
- Come here, cutie.
(Paige screaming)
- Leave me alone.
- Let's us dance now, come on.
(Paige screaming)
(G laughing evilly)
- [Cole] Hey.
(Rachel yelping)
Hey.
Fucking answer me when
I talk to you, girl.
Get up.
God, you are pretty.
(Cole cries out)
(intense music)
(Rachel crying)
That was bad.
(gun cocks)
There's no place like home.
(gun clicks)
(Rachel cries out)
- Oh, my God.
Only one bullet in there, I forgot.
(gun clicks)
Oh.
(Rachel whimpering)
(Paige crying)
(G growling)
- Get off her, man.
Get the fuck out of here.
- Dude, let him go, let him go.
It's okay.
(Paige crying)
Paige, are you okay?
- He put his tongue in my mouth.
- You'll be okay.
You're going to be okay.
Where's Rachel, huh?
(gunshot)
Billy, come here.
Stay her with her, okay?
- I got her.
It's okay, it's okay.
(water sloshing)
- [Navy] Rachel.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Where's Paige?
- Paige?
Paige is with Billy, it's okay.
Hey, she's gonna be all right.
It's all right.
Come on, let's go, all right?
Let's get out of here.
(gentle music)
- Hi.
- So how much longer?
- It's right over this mountain.
- What are we gonna do when we get there?
- I don't know.
There.
(gentle music)
- Hurry, hurry, hurry.
(camera timer beeping)
(camera shutter clicks)
(mid tempo music)
- You bettin' on the fight, man?
- I put a couple hundred on it.
(laughing)
- What's up, man?
- What's up, Jay?
- I got a letter from Navy.
There's no return address
but it's postmarked Montana.
- Like a pig farm.
- It says to open it at the table.
- Yeah, how long has it
been since he's been gone?
- Almost four years, yeah.
What's it say?
- It says, there is more to life, Navy.
That's all he wrote.
- He has kids.
- He looks happy.
Man, that's touching.
(background chatter)