♪ He knows everything about me ♪
♪ What I love, what I hate, what I dream ♪
♪ Ain't nobody could
love me like he would ♪
♪ But he don't love me like that ♪
♪ You see, he's the one
I can't get out my head ♪
♪ Every touch, every word that he said ♪
♪ I play it back again
and boy it makes me spin ♪
♪ But he don't love me like that ♪
♪ And oh, I get so close
to losing control ♪
♪ Pouring our my heart and my soul ♪
♪ But I'd rather have him in my life ♪
♪ Than watch him say goodbye ♪
♪ You're the one that's
always got my back ♪
♪ When I'm running, you are my shadow ♪
♪ And I can't let go ♪
♪ I wish that there was
something I could do ♪
♪ But I can't unlove you ♪
♪ When I'm low, you
always stake me higher ♪
♪ When I'm cold, boy, you are my fire ♪
♪ And you brought me through ♪
♪ I wish that there
was something I could ♪
♪ But I can't unlove you ♪
♪ I, I, I can't unlove you ♪
♪ He's the one who
slowly breaks my heart ♪
♪ Every time him and I are apart ♪
♪ I was someone else,
not knowing how I felt ♪
♪ But he don't love her like that ♪
♪ Yeah, I wish I would be swept away ♪
♪ And I would forget all about your face ♪
♪ Ain't nobody could be
better than you would ♪
♪ So I wouldn't love him like that ♪
♪ Hey, oh ♪
Oh, yeah.
Woo!
Oh, yeah, here we go.
And I'm feeling right.
Oh, yeah, getting close.
Oh, here it is.
Ready?
Fire in the hole.
- I love you.
- Oh, yeah.
That made this whole work week worth it.
Glad you enjoyed it.
What, you didn't get anything from that?
What, nothing at all?
All right, well, what
would you have liked?
I would like to feel
that we are connecting.
Seriously?
You didn't feel that?
All right, what did I do wrong this time?
You seem to be turning
this into a competition.
I'm not a goal.
See, you don't care how I feel.
It's always about you.
Oh, come on.
You know I have a sense of humor.
I was just thinking about something funny.
You think this is funny?
I thought you liked it whenever
I took you to pound town?
Baby, I was joking.
I'm not dealing with this shit.
Fuck this.
So, what, you're gonna go hang out
with your buddies instead
of dealing with this?
Nope.
Then what are you doing?
Avoiding this mess.
What does that mean?
I want a divorce.
Come on, I'm not a total dick.
I let you keep the house, didn't I?
How many times do you
have to read the thing?
Just like that, it's over?
No, you still haven't signed it.
Come on, I got a new girl now.
She's younger, better looking,
does what I want her to,
and complains a whole lot
less than you ever did.
Quick and painless.
You're an asshole.
I know.
I'm a free asshole.
Enjoy your life.
I know you're in here.
I heard the phone ringing.
Or I can just let myself in.
What is this?
Are we enjoying a self-pity party?
I need to be alone.
Oh, yeah, because that works.
It's been a month and honestly,
you look like you're on your
way to alcohol poisoning.
Spill it.
It's over.
What?
Your hopes, your dreams, world hunger?
What's over?
Andrew and I.
Oh, God, babe, that was over months ago.
What I need right now
is a "I told you so."
Oh, yeah, well I mean when
you're right, you're right.
And you staying in and getting
drunk isn't really helping.
We need to get drunk properly.
Come on, we have to get you up.
- What?
- And cleaned up, yes, yes.
- Oh, no.
- You're coming with me.
We are going out.
Oh, come on.
You're getting dressed now.
I don't want to.
We're gonna have fun.
Get dressed.
Take a bath, do it.
We're going out.
Hey, sweets.
Hi, Mom.
The delivery guy just dropped this off.
Perfect, just in time.
I had to forge your signature again.
Again?
Yeah, well, I'm gonna go to the mall.
Okay.
All right, be home by nine o'clock.
Why, it's not like you'll be.
Oh, young lady, you do
as I say, not as I do.
Come here, give me a kiss.
Oh.
Go, and nine o'clock!
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye, I'm serious.
It's heavy.
This is awesome.
Woo hoo!
What the hell?
Sam, what is this?
I wanna fuck you.
This is your new lover.
A teddy bear?
Well, you're either gonna
make Andrew really angry
with another man or you're
just gonna fuck up your life
with a trail of new losers,
so I figured I'd bring you
something that would make you smile.
And you know what is name is?
It's Bearry.
Oh, oh, oh, wait.
I love you bearry much.
Oh, so cute.
All right, are you hungry?
Yeah.
Yeah, let's get outta here.
Oh, I need a drink.
Okay, whew!
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Um.
- Oh.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Stephen, your girlfriend is at table 16.
Stop it.
Here you are.
Oh.
Is there anything else I can get you?
No, thank you.
Hm, he's cute for an older guy.
Can I just enjoy my meal, please?
You can try.
Oh, this kid.
Hey, Mom.
So, I think I left my purse
in the trunk of your car
or in the locker at the gym,
in which case I might have to
replace your credit card.
So, I'm really hoping it's
in the trunk of your car.
What?
You'd forget your head
if it wasn't attached.
Did you at least remember
to lock the front door?
Yes, Mom, I'm not an idiot.
I'll be back.
Is everything okay?
Good.
You need anything else, just let me know.
No, I'm good.
I'm just checking.
Enjoy.
Are you done yet?
We need to get you white girl drunk.
Let's go.
Sam, you forgot these.
Thanks for coming.
Anything else?
Okay, ladies, here's your tab.
I think you've had enough.
What am I going to do with you?
I guess I'll be snuggling
with you tonight.
I love you bearry much.
Aw.
Mm.
Cute, but I'm not in the mood.
You sure are needy.
Crap, what time is it?
Oh, God.
I'm late.
I can't believe I let Sam set me up.
Let me tell you a
little bit about myself.
I enjoy a rousing fencing tournament,
I am well versed in Shakespeare,
and I enjoy occasionally the odd cricket,
or the delightful fox hunt.
Now, tell me a little bit about yourself.
You're vegan, am I
understanding that correctly?
Or is it that raw thing?
I don't know.
I enjoy haggis myself.
Oh, my goodness.
Have you ever had haggis?
Oh!
No, you got it wrong.
I'm not looking for a girlfriend.
I'm looking for girlfriends.
- How old are you?
- Oh, I'm 18.
I'm legal.
I'm into MILFs.
Wow.
You're pretty.
Woo wee!
You're prettier than Betsy.
Who's Betsy?
That's my prize winning heifer.
Move along.
Yes!
Bitch.
I can't believe it.
I might be getting that promotion.
Yes, I'm going to dinner with my boss.
No, it's not a date.
Sam, why do you have to
crap on every good thing
that happens to me?
Yes, he just got out of a marriage.
How long?
I don't know, who cares.
No, it's just business.
Besides if it wasn't, he'd
be better than any of those
losers you tried setting me up with.
They were horrible.
Sam, come on.
Whatever.
Mm hm.
Oh, come on.
Be happy I'm getting this promotion.
I earned it and not the way you do.
You support me, don't you, Bearry?
Tasty.
- Hi.
- Yeah.
Good to see you.
It's better to see you.
Thanks for considering me.
I figured dinner first, then
we can discuss the position?
I'm sure there are plenty
of positions you're good at.
I don't think we'll have
a problem finding one.
I really want this promotion.
Well, let's see if you earn it.
Yeah, that's fucked up.
I really know how to pick 'em.
Well, it seems like you
had a lot on your chest
you had to get off of.
Why don't we do this?
Go back to your place, get some drinks,
and I'll help you forget
all about that guy.
You know, earn your promotion.
Excuse me?
Look, lady, if I didn't
earn any trim listening
to that crap, tell me
what do I have to do?
You just wanted to sleep with me?
You're a pig!
So, is that a no?
Look, first you bring
me to this shit hole,
then you dump this crap of a story on me,
and you're telling me I
don't get anything out of it?
Get out of here!
Excuse me?
Is there a problem?
Yes!
You need to leave.
Oh, well, this place turned
out to be a bust anyway.
Looks like I have to find somebody else
that's more qualified for the position.
Better yet, why don't you take a vacation?
Unpaid, of course.
Fuck you.
Hit the road, bitch!
Okay, looks like my shift's over.
Are you okay?
What's wrong with me?
I don't think there's
anything wrong with you.
Why am I surrounded by losers?
Do you have anyone you can call?
Yeah.
Thank you.
All right, I've got something
to finish up in the back,
but I'll be close by if you need anything.
It's Sam, you know what to do.
Sam, call me back.
Hi.
I hate to ask, but would I be able
to get a ride home tonight?
I feel a bit uncomfortable calling
a complete stranger for a ride.
Sure.
Just let me finish up a few things.
Is there anything I can help with?
Yeah, grab a towel.
You know, I'm sorry you lost your job.
Hey, I can do this tomorrow.
Let's get you home.
We're here.
It's a really nice place you got.
What am I gonna do?
Look, I can offer you a job
till you get on your feet.
Thank you, but I'm not a waitress.
No, not as a waitress, as a bar back.
You were damn good tonight.
Hey, I got a laugh outta you.
There's a start.
If you need anything, I'm here to help.
Thank you.
You love me, don't you, Bearry?
I love you bearry much.
I know you do.
I love you bearry much, too.
Why are all men creeps?
That jackass made me lose my mind tonight.
I wish he'd lose his.
Hey, you need to hire another woman.
That bitch, Chloe, didn't work out.
I took her for an interview for dinner.
She was ungrateful, uptight.
Excuse me?
I got a position for any
woman in this goddamn office!
I'm the boss!
Exactly.
Now you make sure the
next one has big tits.
I need something to look at.
I don't know, email me your top three.
I don't have all night.
It's been wasted.
Get the job done.
Oh this is it, maybe this one.
Yeah, this is the one.
Yeah, you know you want it.
You can file some paperwork for daddy.
All these women are better
than that prude, Chloe.
I hope she goes further
than her preliminary.
That is a horrible way to die.
Coulda been a fetish thing.
Oh, good, that changes my
whole perspective on him.
He was a pervert.
What do you think this is?
It looks like the perp
might've had on padded gloves.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
So what do we know about our body there?
His last call was to
a business associate.
He said his business date didn't go well.
Uh huh, well then,
we know who we're gonna
talk to next, don't we?
Morning, Bearry.
I love you bearry much.
I love you too.
What happened?
You're hurt.
All done.
Do you want breakfast, Bearry?
I do.
Hi, can I help you?
Yes, ma'am.
We're detectives Clark and Seahorn.
We were seeing if we can
ask you some questions.
Uh, sure, would you like to come in?
Thank you, ma'am, that would be great.
This shouldn't take long.
Okay.
Just a few questions.
So, what's this about?
Do you know a Mr. Jeff Hardcastle?
He's my boss.
Well, was my boss.
When was the
last time you saw him?
Uh, I saw him last night.
Were you working?
- It was a business meeting.
- Dating?
We aren't dating.
It was just dinner after work.
Uh, well, we have witnesses
that say you two were dating.
- What witnesses?
- Work-related witnesses.
They said they two were a thing.
We're not a thing.
I was up for a promotion.
Can you please tell me
what this is all about?
Um, Mr. Hardcastle was
discovered dead last night.
What?
How, I was just-
We'll ask the questions.
What time did
your business dinner conclude?
- Around 9:00.
- Did it go well?
We won't be seeing each other again.
Yes, obviously.
Oh, my God, did you hear the great news?
That motherfucking prick got
exactly what he deserves.
And I when that and I thought
to myself, "You go, girl!"
These are the detectives
investigating Jeff's death.
Oh, okay, I actually
didn't mean that she did it.
I just meant that he was a dog
and he got what he deserved.
- Not helping.
- Okay, I'm actually going to
grab the wine and I'll be in the bedroom.
Hold it, who are you?
We may have questions for you later.
Okay, um, talk to my lawyer.
Wait a minute!
What the?
You're uh-
Um...
You know your story
has a lot of holes in it.
Would you like to fill in some of them?
Just a few?
We will check out your story, ma'am.
Not saying you're a suspect.
But everybody that knew him is.
I'll cooperate in anyway I can.
What about your friend?
Oh, she drinks a lot.
We're planning an intervention.
- Hm.
- Yeah.
We'll be in contact.
Thank you, ma'am.
- What the hell?
- I know!
Who the fuck let the cops in?
Bad move, sister.
What was I supposed to do?
Give a girl some warning, please.
So, how's Bearry working out for ya?
He's been a comfort to
me, unlike some people.
Harsh.
You know they don't really think it's you.
They probably do now.
Grab a glass.
Oh, quit worrying.
You know you'd be in
silver bracelets right now
if they really thought it was you.
They focused on me.
So cops have to do that.
I mean, they have to weed out the guilty.
I just hope I never
have to see them again.
Ugh, yeah.
Mm, he's so comfy.
I know, right?
I could just get drunk all day long
and hang out with Bearry.
Back off, sister, he's mine.
And you know, it's definitely a man.
Just the way he was killed.
Whew, brutal.
How was he killed?
He's here.
Oh, my God, we're in the bedroom.
Who?
- Ah, there he is!
- Oh, my God.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I hear you have man issues?
- Oh, great.
- I'm here to help.
Is all the wine gone?
No, we have a
bunch more bottles inside.
- Perfect.
- Ooh, yeah.
How did he die?
He lost his mind.
No, like literally, it
went rolling on the floor.
There he is.
I need to catch up.
And you know, it definitely wasn't you.
You're not that mean.
Okay, so the first batch didn't work out.
So let's get to the second batch.
- No, no more, please.
- There you go.
- You've done enough.
- Yeah, give me her phone.
What?
Mm hm.
Okay, this is a new dating app.
I found many a cute man
to spend my nights with.
I've already set her up
on a few dates already.
Oh, what?
So, I think it would be great
if you were to meet my mom
because she says that if I
find a girl who I really like
and makes me happy, I'll
always live in happiness.
And I think you look like my mom,
and I really would like
you to meet my mom.
It would be really nice.
$50,000.
What's this?
You marry me, I love you
long time, and you rich.
I like my women like
I like my chocolate.
White, mm.
I just got out of a
really bad relationship,
and I was thinking about you
know, trying dating again.
I can understand that.
So, you wanna try this dating thing?
I don't think so.
Hey, you'd look great as
a leading lady in my film.
But I gotta see the goods first.
Sup?
Name's Duane.
Gotta let you know I saw
you from across the room,
and if you want this to work out,
you're gonna have to start working out.
And that's not a problem
'cause I only charge
$100 a session.
And once we get that going and we get you
where I need you to be,
we can start dating,
and we can start dating hard.
Maybe some other time.
For real?
These could be yours.
Is it wrong to love somebody so much?
I gotta go.
What are you doing here?
How'd you find me?
I followed you.
Why did you leave me?
I thought things were going great.
You better leave now or
I'm calling the police.
Please don't.
My probation officer
will be very mad at me.
Come on.
We're perfect together.
I can feel it.
What are you, some kinda Jedi?
Just give me another chance.
Leave now or I'm calling the cops.
But I love you.
Leave, now!
Fine, I'll leave.
But you're gonna regret it.
Oh, God.
Look, I am so sorry.
I thought you'd hit it
off with one of them.
That was the biggest group of losers
I've ever encountered.
You'll find a nice guy.
It just takes time.
Well, at least I have Bearry.
Oh, fuckin' bitch.
Look what she's missing.
So, there's this guy at work who
I really want you to meet.
No, no more help.
Well, what if I told you
that I actually liked him,
but he was just way too nice.
Hm.
Yeah, look, I mean if she
rejected him for being decent,
you might wanna jump on that or I will.
No, I've had enough.
Okay, I just started a fantastic new job,
my divorce is final.
Okay, you guys, I'm happy.
I don't need a man right now.
Besides, I have you two.
Well, what if I told
you that I invited him
here for drinks tonight.
- Mm.
- And if you don't meet him
I'm gonna buy a strap-on for Bearry.
- What?
- Yeah, so you're gonna
meet him and you're gonna like him.
I think you need more wine.
I don't wanna do this.
Just go along with it, okay?
It's not like you have to sleep with him.
Come here, come on you go.
Hey, guys, this is Ryan.
- Oh, oh, God.
- He works with me.
Hi, guys, nice to meet you.
Hi, I'm Luis.
Back off, vulture.
Actually, Luis and I, we
have to go tonight to church-
- The mortuary.
We actually meant we have to go
to the mortuary-
Church.
Okay, come on, Luis.
You entertain my friend here.
Take good care of him.
That was subtle.
Well, you know what?
I think they're gonna work out.
He was just too nice for me.
I am so sorry about this.
I didn't know about
this until just before.
It's not your fault.
She is who she is.
Do you wanna have a seat?
Sure.
Well, it is refreshing to work with her.
She always does make you laugh.
You seem like a nice guy.
You don't have to stay.
You seem nice too, and I wanna stay.
So, looks like we're
both stuck here together.
Might as well make the most of it, right?
I'm a really good cook.
So, what do you say I say
thank you for your hospitality
by making you a nice meal?
I don't have anything here to cook.
Okay, well, how about
I take you out to dinner?
You pick the place.
Well, there is this restaurant I go to.
I eat there a lot actually.
May I have the honor of
taking you out to dinner?
I'm sorry for talking so much.
No, no, get it off your chest.
It's not good to hold in bad stuff.
Did I say something wrong?
No, it's just the last time I had dinner
with someone it didn't end well.
Well, I'm not that guy.
An average guy, not as crazy as Sam.
Thank you.
Can I share something?
Please do, I would like that.
Are you guys ready to order?
- Yeah, are you ready?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
I had a really nice time.
I'm so glad.
I did too.
Now, I've got a request.
What?
I had a really wonderful time.
I'd love to see you again.
I will grant that request.
Let me tell you about the best date ever!
I can't believe how kind and gentle he is.
This one's a keeper I think.
And to think he came from Sam.
I had so much fun with you last night.
So, when do I get to see you again?
Sounds good.
I don't know, nothing.
Hey, Chloe, can I call you back?
Thanks.
You know he didn't
come into work either.
Don't read too much into this.
We hit it off so well.
You actually came through
and found me an awesome guy.
He said he'd call back.
Doesn't seem like the type
of person who plays games.
Is he?
I don't know, he's kind of like a loner.
I think he's the type that
just goes off into nature.
Oh, that reminds me.
Dad wanted to go camping next weekend.
Okay, not now, sweetheart.
I didn't say now.
I said next weekend.
Okay, you know what, Angela?
You're gonna go home, do your chores,
or you're gonna be camping
in your room for a month.
Go.
Seriously?
He's a hippie, he'll call you.
I hope so.
I really liked him.
Let's not focus on him not calling.
Let's celebrate the fact
that he's in your life.
Let's go to your favorite
restaurant tonight.
You really are a good friend.
Better than Luis?
Oh!
Eh, eh, eh.
Ah, shit.
Poor guy.
Looks like he was on the phone
with Chloe before he got butchered.
Well, then, I guess that moves her right
to the top of our list.
Evening, officers.
Is it that obvious?
Well, I guess so.
Ah, and I thought we looked just like
a pair of insurance agents.
What can I get you guys to eat?
Donuts.
And a cup of coffee please, sweets.
And a little information
on one of your patrons.
Do you know this woman?
Um, yeah, she's been in
here from time to time.
Oh, my God, that is the girl
that you drool over every time.
Well, well, well, that is interesting.
So, you've seen her in here with a man?
- Like a date?
- Yes, like a date.
Perhaps with this person?
Yeah, he's been in here.
That guy is a real piece of work!
Kelly!
I'll check on my tables.
What about him?
What do you know about him?
So she's been in here
with different men?
What can I tell you?
I mean, I didn't talk to them.
Did it look like
somebody was getting some?
It seemed to be going okay.
Huh.
Thank you for the information.
We'll be in touch.
Well, well, well.
Hello, Chloe.
What are you guys doing here?
We came to sample some local cuisine.
We learned a lot about
this spot, didn't we?
Oh, yeah.
We learned a lot.
Were you here last night
and last Wednesday night?
- Well, I-
- No, she was with me,
and another friend.
Now, either arrest her or leave her alone.
- What's going on?
- Don't worry about it.
We'll be in touch.
What did you say to those guys?
Nothing.
Yeah, well, why are
they acting like that?
They asked simple questions,
I gave them simple answers.
They asked about that creep
and then the nice guy.
Who?
The nice guy from the other night.
What happened to him?
I don't know, they were
fishing hard for something.
I don't know what it is,
but you need to figure out your next move.
Come on, let's go.
Why are they thinking you're involved?
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe because they found
my boss dead right after
I went out to dinner with him?
And now Ryan's missing.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
What?
Do you think I had
something to do with this?
I'm not accusing you.
It's just that yes,
first, there's your boss.
Then, there's Ryan.
Is there something you wanna tell me?
I just wanna know what happened to Ryan.
Are you sure there isn't more to this?
Yes, Sam, I'm sure!
God.
No, I told you everything.
I met him that one time.
He was a fucking creep and I left.
That's it.
These detectives' questions
are borderline harassment.
All right, sweetheart.
Listen, I believe you and
I love you, you know that,
but I have to ask.
Just give me a day and
I'll contact my lawyer.
Okay?
Yeah.
Thank you so much, Sam.
Aw, give me a hug.
It's gonna be all right.
What are you doing here?
I have a key.
This is my house.
Yeah, in all your
attempts to get over me,
you never even thought
to change the locks?
Nice to hear about the investigation.
My lawyer is just gonna love that.
May even renegotiate whose house this is.
Get the fuck out.
Baby, you are never
gonna have it as good
as you had it with me.
You know what?
I found someone better than you.
Oh, please.
Quit showing off.
Nobody cares about you.
All that you have is my house
and that neurotic little friend of yours.
I have someone that cares for me.
Oh, yeah?
What's his name?
- His name?
- Yeah.
His name is Stephen.
It's that right there.
Right there, you hesitated.
See, I know you.
You are lying.
Fuck you.
I'm gonna need your wedding ring.
See, I fucked up with the new girl.
I accidentally called her the
wrong name in the bedroom,
and I gotta play nice.
Absolutely not!
Tell you what.
Either you give me the
ring or I go tell the cops
that you threatened me with a knife.
How do you think that's
gonna go over with 'em?
Yeah.
Yeah, good girl.
That's what I thought.
Found it.
Will she ever fucking grow up?
Goddamn teddy bear.
I love you bearry much.
Eating alone tonight?
Yeah.
I like it.
It's peaceful.
I get to enjoy my meal.
I don't like eating alone.
You'll learn to like it.
Hey, Chloe.
How are you doing?
I'm feeling kinda down.
Let me buy you dinner.
That's my boy.
It's good to see you laugh.
Yeah, there hasn't been
much laughing lately.
Come on, there's plenty to laugh at.
Stephen, I'm done.
Don't do anything I wouldn't do.
Good night, Kelly.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
I'm sure it will be.
Would you like to go out with me?
That would be nice.
I feel used.
You looked so peaceful.
I didn't wanna wake you.
So what is this?
A wham, bam, thank you, ma'am?
I'll come by later for
dinner if that's okay.
I'd love that.
Hey, that's my shirt!
Mm, I love you, Bearry.
I love you bearry much.
I think I finally met the right one.
Stephen and Chloe.
It has a nice ring to it, doesn't it?
I'm really falling for him.
All right.
Thanks.
What am I doing?
I don't even like these kinda girls.
She's, she's too young.
Oh, but she makes me laugh.
Who am I kidding?
I love her.
What the hell?
First the boss, then the
date, now an ex-husband.
You reckon we got enough
evidence now to arrest her?
Oh, yeah.
Good.
Let's do it.
Hey, Stephen, it's Chloe again.
I've been trying to ahold of
you for the past few hours.
Just wanna make sure you're okay.
Bearry?
I love you bearry much.
- What are you doing here?
- That fucking teddy bear.
Chloe!
Get!
What the fuck are you talking about?
There is nothing wrong
with this bear, okay?
He's fine, look at him.
He's fine.
He's just a bear.
I don't understand you guys.
It's just Bearry, okay?
- Come on, come on.
- No!
I love you bearry much.
Hey, Chloe, have you seen my mom?
Mom?
Mom!
Mom, are you okay?
- Angela.
- Mom!
My beautiful daughter.
How was camping?
Mom, what?
Mom, what happened to you?
Mom?
Someone help!
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Okay, try it.
It's not working.
All right, how about now?
Nothing.
All right, one more time.
What happened last night?
It's a teddy bear!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, she's got a gun.
Hey, I've seen you.
Wait, you're the lady
from the restaurant.
There's a teddy bear trying to kill you,
and you're worried
about who the fuck I am!
Wait, it killed her
friend, it stabbed me,
and it tried to rape her.
It's killed everyone around us.
We have to get as far
away from here as we can.
Come on, let's go!
Goddammit!
We're not going anywhere.
Can you fix it?
Not without my tools.
'Cause I've been working on
it when all this shit started.
You know, this might just work.
I mean, we're out in
the middle of nowhere.
Bearry might not be able to find us.
Let's go.
Where?
I know a hunter's shack nearby.
There may be some tools there.
I'll go fist.
Do you think she's
using him to get away?
Has to be.
She's running out of options.
She knows she's about to be exposed.
Yeah, yeah.
I just don't get it.
I mean, she seemed like a
perfectly normal person.
What do you think makes
someone do something like this?
Man, people snap.
Yeah.
This ain't going anywhere soon.
Let's just go a little further.
Wait, wait,
wait, wait, stop, stop.
Over there.
I'll be damned.
That looks like our Hummer.
Let's go get her.
Let's finish this.
Hello?
Is anybody here?
Sit.
I don't think anybody lives here.
I know this place.
It used to be a testing site for MK Ultra.
It's abandoned.
I don't see any lights.
Ah, I go outside and try
and see if there's like
a generator or a breaker or something.
Be careful.
What is this place?
Ah, bingo.
Ah, let's see.
- Oh.
- Oh, much better.
I don't see any tools.
Did you see any fuel outside?
Yeah, there's a bunch
of cans by the generator.
Okay, let's build a fire.
Where'd you learn to
build a fire like that?
You've never been camping?
No, I never got the chance to go,
but I've always wanted to.
When all this is over,
I'll take you camping.
Sorry about your friends.
There will be more.
They can hide like a government fly.
Government?
Fly.
They program them to spy on us.
Okay.
How can he be stopped?
Bearry was a gift
after my daughter died.
He's killed everyone around me.
How?
He was just a normal teddy bear
till I said those magical words.
I love you bearry much.
He went from being just
a normal teddy bear,
to being alive.
I just wanna know how.
I don't know.
I've been trying to stop him ever since
I realized what he was.
He always chooses new owners.
Yeah, me.
Not just you.
Bearry's killed many families.
You're just next in line.
Between him and the reptilians,
I don't know who's killed more.
Reptilians?
Are you fucking crazy?
Oh, no, they're building
a new master race.
I don't even know what to make of that.
Look, we have to prepare.
We're not leaving.
How are we going to stop him?
How do you kill a teddy bear?
With a toy gun?
No, we kill him with fire.
I love you bearry much.
Go, go, save yourselves.
Get the fuck outta here.
Come on, you fucking fucker!
He's right there!
Run, run, come on.
Is she dead?
Oh, shit.
Oh, no!
Chloe, run!
Get outta here!
Oh, man.
Stephen, don't die.
What happened?
You're alive.
We have to go.
Can you move?
Yeah.
I love you bearry much.
That's enough, Bearry!
Stop it!
Please, stop this!
I love you bearry much.
I love you too, Bearry.
But you have to stop this.
Please.
For me.
I, I, love you,
be, be, bearry much, much.
I'm sorry.
Shit, it's a real fuckin' teddy bear.
No one's gonna
believe this shit, right?
Man, I don't even believe it.
Oh, sorry, my bad.
I just wanted to make sure it was...
It's a teddy bear.
Come on, we should take
you to the hospital.
What about everything that happened?
Ain't nobody gonna believe
there was a real teddy bear.
Nobody can believe this shit.
You ring it in.
Why I always gotta ring it
in and look like the idiot?
Why you can't ring it in this time?
- Is it over?
- It's over.
Let's get outta here.
I love you.
I love you too.