Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[Chrissy gasping]
[Chrissy whimpering]
Please.
Please help!
Help, somebody help me!
[fist banging]
Help!
[woman gasping]
[door clattering]
[Chrissy whimpering]
Okay, okay.
What?
What was that?
Oh my god.
[distant thudding]
No, not again, not again, not again.
[footsteps pattering]
Oh my god.
No I can't, I can't.
[distant banging]
Oh my god.
[suspenseful music]
[distant thumping]
No, no, no, no.
Please help, please!
[lock clattering]
Okay, I don't, I don't know if anybody's
ever gonna see this.
It's, oh god.
It's...
It's the 2nd of February 2020,
and I have no way to get out of my house.
All of my doors and my
windows, they're all locked.
From the outside.
[loud banging]
[Chrissy gasping]
My phone, my phone isn't working.
I have no reception, my internet is down.
[distant banging]
[Chrissy gasping]
I don't know, I don't
know why, but somebody or
some thing is trying to kill me.
Please just tell my Mom
and Dad that I love them
and that,
I wish I had done something
more with my life.
I tried, I really, really tried to.
If only.
[door clattering]
No.
No, no please.
Oh please, oh please, no, please, no!
[Chrissy screaming]
Oh shit.
[distant banging]
Oh god [gasping].
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit shit.
Okay, calm down, calm down.
Fucking get a grip,
get a grip, get a grip.
Okay, okay, okay.
[distant banging]
[suspenseful music]
Oh fuck fuck fuck fuck.
Come on come on come on.
Oh god, oh shit.
Shit shit,
shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Okay.
[door slamming]
Oh god.
If anyone finds this, tell my Mom and Dad
that I'm sorry I didn't
make more of my life.
I wanted to, and I'm...
I love you, and...
[monster-like snarling]
[loud banging]
Who's there?
[dark intense music]
[Max screaming]
[monster-like chewing]
I don't know if anyone
is ever gonna see this,
but
if I don't-
[distant quiet snarling]
[quiet intense music]
IF I don't make it,
it's it's it's February 2nd, 2020.
My phone won't work.
I have no reception and I can't,
I can't open any of the windows
or the doors to outside.
I think someone's-
[quiet distant heavy footsteps]
I think someone, some
thing is trying to...
[suspenseful music]
[monster groaning]
Why doesn't she just
break a fucking window?
I love you, Kip, but this script
literally makes zero sense.
♪ I got a vision ♪
♪ Made it my religion ♪
♪ Oh I'm going to break out ♪
♪ Break out of this prison ♪
[blood splattering]
[phone ringing]
Hey, where the fuck are you?
What?
Oh, come on, man.
You're supposed to meet
me a half hour ago.
Morning to you, too, Mark.
Who eats lunch at
three in the afternoon?
[dog barking]
[Declan groaning]
Oh dude.
You got news on the Sorkin show?
Yeah, dude, the network
didn't approve you.
Network?
It's on YouTube.
Fuck.
[pee guzzling]
All right, well whatever, look,
I've been thinking about
this next season of "Belle,"
and I wanna walk.
- They don't-
- Are you takin'
a fuckin' piss?
- Yeah.
- Are you kidding me?
Listen, I'm gonna make this quick, okay?
We decided to let you go.
What?
Yeah.
We're letting you go.
You're kind of an asshole.
You're not very good.
For somebody who thinks
that they're that smart,
you're pretty untalented.
And I'm really glad for you that
the DUI thing worked out in your favor,
but you're too much work.
It's not worth the effort.
Wow, Mark.
[Declan laughing]
You were so far up my ass
when I booked the show,
I thought you were
ready make a home there.
What was that whole fuckin' loyalty talk?
Oh god, you know, Mark,
you are why people hate agents.
Well, you're the reason
people love actors.
[Declan laughing]
You know what Mark? If you think you're
getting commission on next season
I will do anything to
keep that money from you.
My god, you really are so stupid.
You think that you're on hiatus?
Come on, man.
You guys are getting canceled.
Good luck finding more work.
Fucking clown.
[phone beeping]
What?
[intense music]
[Kip] Now look, watch this.
[voice fast forwarding]
[monster snarling]
I think someone, some thing is trying to-
- [Kip] Wait for it.
Wait for it.
Why doesn't she just
break a fucking window?
And there it is.
Look, Alex, I'm just saying,
it woulda helped if you took
it a little more seriously.
Yeah, well I think Chrissy
took it seriously enough for all of us.
Was it too much?
And Kip, why are we
all doing the same scene?
What up motherfuckers?
[Max laughing]
Holy stache, Kip, what are you doin', man?
Yeah, you dig?
You dig?
- No, no one digs.
- You look like
Chris Hansen's wet spring break fantasy.
- Okay, is Kelly coming?
- I don't know what that means
but fuck you.
You know, she probably
just wants us to wait.
Why?
'Cause she's Kelly.
No, I just mean it's
like classic Sagittarius.
- Hey Kel.
- What?
Did you guys laugh
at my Instastory or no?
- Every time.
- I chuckled.
I wouldn't say I laughed.
Wait, was it supposed to be funny?
Fuck, I'm deleting it.
Where's Declan?
I don't know, jail in Thailand?
That's not funny.
Rehab?
What is on your lip?
[Alex laughing]
Thank you for joining, Kel,
and I am growing my mustache.
On purpose?
What do you mean, yeah, on purpose.
- Thank you.
- Hey, let him live.
Let him live?
I'm giving him all the space he needs.
Okay, I'm here, what do you want?
Okay, Kip and I were talking,
and we both think that with
the show going back next month,
if we all band together, like they did-
- Yeah, like they did on "The Simpsons."
Good show.
Nope, like they did on "Friends,"
if we all band together
we could have a better
chance at getting more money.
Yeah, but we're all
in different amounts.
No, we would agree on
a percentage increase.
So say it's like 10%.
10% is like nothing.
I took "Peanuts" season one
because it was my first pilot.
Yeah, I mean, some
of us are on literally
a fifth of everybody else.
Yeah, but some of us have been
in more seasons than others.
Hey, what'd I miss?
Manners, apparently.
Okay, when people say 11, they mean 11.
Jesus Christ, Kip, Amber Alert.
[Declan and Max laughing]
Okay, guys, we're
talking about next season,
and we need to all band together
if we wanna get more money.
Are you guys stupid?
The show's getting canceled.
- Oh my god.
- What?
- Fuck you?
My agent called me yesterday.
Wait, no, how does he know?
Molly told me we were going back.
Yeah, me, too.
How can they
- just change their minds?
- No, no, no,
there's no way they're canceling the show
without telling me.
I am the lead.
I'm Belle, and I would know.
So I'm calling my agent.
My agent's brother-in-law
is the VP of the network,
so if anyone's gonna know it's him.
Oh, that's how you
stay on the show so long.
What are you pissy about?
You complained every
single day on that set.
You know what?
Just 'cause I didn't want to prance around
pretending to be a 14th century warrior
trapped in the body of a 17 year old
doesn't mean I don't like getting paid.
Oh my God, I just bought a new house.
You guys, I knew this was gonna happen
the second that Bobby
took over the network.
He doesn't see our show
for what it could be.
Yeah, I think it's I-E, not Y.
Oh, hey, congratulations on
your new gig in spell check,
the TV series.
That's not even a real fuckin' show.
Name's Bob-I-E Brower.
[Max laughing]
That's a stupid name.
Look, let's all think on
the bright side, guys.
Okay?
We can all start auditioning again.
Meaning I can show what I
can really do as an actor.
God.
That's exactly what somebody
who booked their first audition would say,
but that's okay, you should.
Okay, it wasn't my first.
It was my second.
Max, we can't audition.
We're not allowed to.
The studio owns us for another 12 months.
They're not gonna release
us from our contracts.
Okay, but if the show is canceled,
then technically-
- They'll keep us under contract
for as long as they can just in case.
Yeah, but in case of what?
I mean, how are we supposed to make money?
They'll give us a holding fee.
How much?
A few grand.
- What?
- Oh my god,
- I can't even.
- Look, I told you idiots
to save your money.
Oh, by the way, speaking of saving money,
Max, how's your new Porsche?
Ha ha.
Okay, I didn't know it
was like burn Max day.
But you know, I look dope in that car,
- so shut up.
- That's amazing,
'cause you're gonna be
living in it soon, so.
Oh my God, what am I gonna do?
You could always do
another banana bread
tutorial on Instagram.
[Declan laughing]
Oh yeah, the sourdough one was good.
You guys follow me?
No, I don't follow you on Instagram.
Guys, this is is bullshit.
I can't go back to go-go dancing.
Acting is the only real skill I even have.
And you barely have that.
What am I gonna do?
[gentle music]
We could keep making my movie.
Okay.
What movie?
Oh, I am trying my hand at writing.
I have this horror concept
- that's pretty-
- Yeah, but we're still
under contract, right?
No, we make it ourselves.
The scenes you guys
filmed were pretty good.
The scenes they filmed?
Uuuhhh.
Yeah, yeah, a few of 'em
helped me film some scenes
so I could just see what it sounded like.
A few of 'em.
And was that everyone?
Or just...
No, just Alex, Chrissy, and Max.
Just everyone.
He asked me too, but I said no.
Of course you did.
You know what, fuck you, Kip.
That is really mean.
[Declan laughing]
Come on, Kelly, it's not
like you would have done it.
I might have.
No, you wouldn't have.
Okay guys, can we all
just take a breath, please?
Together?
Good idea, everyone,
one, two, three.
[everyone inhaling]
Now let it go with a...
[Max groaning]
I can't concentrate.
Is he okay?
You sound like you're cumming.
Are you finished?
It works.
Okay, seriously guys, though.
Kip, if the writing
gets a little better,
just being honest, just being honest,
do you think that there
is something there?
I, to be honest, back at ya,
I really think we have something here.
The scenes you guys filmed were good.
And if we all did it and took it seriously
we could definitely sell it.
Especially if the show is canceled.
I mean, honestly,
our fans would love it.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
You know you need more than actors
and a script to make a movie.
You need financing.
You need a director.
Kelly, please.
Don't for one second pretend like you have
ever needed a director
in your entire career.
Okay, maybe I haven't needed
one, but you have needed one.
- Okay, wow.
- Okay, okay, guys, guys.
- If we keep doing-
- That's hostile.
- What we've been-
- Let's be nice.
We keep doing what we've been doing
and we just shoot it ourselves.
On what?
On our phones.
[Kelly laughing]
Okay, I'm hanging up now.
Okay, no, Kelly, listen, Kelly.
- Kelly, come on.
- Kelly, just listen,
listen, listen, listen.
The new phones they shoot in 4k.
It's basically like, movie worthy.
Look, I'm not being
funny, but I was the lead
of one of the highest
grossing horror films in 2017.
And I'm just not making a home movie.
- So.
- Okay, well,
this is found footage,
so it doesn't matter if
the quality isn't the best.
Oh wait, I'm sorry, but
everybody always looks
super ugly in those movies.
Well just use your
ring light then, sweetie.
You know guys, I was
listening to Kevin Smith
on Joe Rogan's podcast last night,
- and he's-
- Oh god.
Was a mullet required to
listen to that episode or?
[group laughing]
Anyways, they were
explaining that there's
a lot of freedom in
filming your own stuff.
That's what everybody
who can't get a studio
to finance their movie says.
I'll go fuck myself then, Declan.
Okay, come on guys, come on.
This could really be something.
Okay?
We could be our own producers.
Call our own shots.
Nobody holding us down.
Okay.
I mean, there is
something to that, yeah?
Like taking a break from
the archaic patriarchal
system of Hollywood.
Look, I want to agree,
but what did you say?
Babe, I'm in.
[Kip clapping]
[Alex] Okay.
I don't understand
any of it, but I'm in.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Declan?
Come on, dude.
Just do it.
- Sure, sure.
- Decky?
There's only so many times
you can jerk off in one day.
Gross.
Not proven scientifically.
Okay, one more, one more.
- Kelly.
[Group] Kelly, Kelly Kelly.
What's it about?
Oh my god, okay, it's about,
it's about a spirit that
attacks people who sin.
That's literally everyone.
Exactly, exactly, exactly.
Okay, okay, all right.
Why don't we do this?
Why don't we all get the scene
and shoot it and then
we'll see what happens.
We'll see what's there.
Okay, perfect, perfect plan.
I'll just, I'll re-tweak it
and then we can go from there.
Great, and then send
it to us tonight, yeah?
No, I have to write it still.
Yeah, yeah, well write it now,
and then send it to us tonight.
No, it's not that easy.
Dude, it's like 2 p.m.
Ooo, I'll make a Dropbox.
You download the app
and then you click the
add all new videos tab,
and then everything you film
will automatically upload.
That sounds dangerous.
Why?
I have some notes.
Can I be the lead?
Let's just meet again on Thursday.
Yeah, same time?
Ah, I dunno if I can, you
know I got Lesly Kahn 'til noon.
- [Declan laughing]
- I have Botox at 11, so 11-
- Lesly Kahn.
- What are you
fucking laughing at?
You do Botox?
Botox, Kelly?
What?
Wow.
I had no idea.
You look so natural.
Okay, guys, 2:30, Thursday.
Yeah?
- All right.
- Okay.
- Whatever.
- Bye.
- Peace and love babes.
- Oh, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
What?
[camera clicking]
- I was not ready.
- What was that?
You're gonna post that aren't you?
- Dude I-
- What the fuck?
You're gonna fucking post it.
I fucking know you are.
I need content for my Only Fans.
It pays my rent, fuck.
- Yo yo yo, tag me.
- Oh my God,
- please send it.
- No, don't tag me, okay?
[indistinct]
Guys.
[intense music]
If anyone finds this
tell my mom and dad...
[intense music]
No, no, no, please, no.
[Max grunting and screaming]
[intense music]
It's good to be back.
No, this can't be happening.
Oh but it is.
[Chrissy gasping]
No, please.
Please please stop.
Why are you doing this?
No.
Oh wait, I gotta fix.
Oh my God.
Okay, I'm gonna take that again.
[sighing]
Cleansing breath.
[intense music]
No, no, no, please.
Please, please, why are you doing this?
Stop, stop.
[Chrissy grunting]
Making life more interesting.
[Chrissy laughing]
[Max groaning and gasping]
No please, please don't do this.
[Alex laughing]
Don't do this please.
Please don't do this.
Oh, she's so scared.
Who are you crying for?
No no no no, I won't let you.
I won't let...
I won't let you?
I won't,
I won't let you.
You're not in control anymore...
This, I mean, this feels so cliche.
Everyone else is doing this?
[Declan groaning]
Okay, I just, I wanted my family to know
that I loved them and I wish
I stayed in dental school.
I wish...
I won't let you.
[Chrissy laughing]
Well, you are not in control anymore.
Yes, I am.
This feels really stupid.
Like do I do voices?
[Max grunting and groaning]
No please, I can't, not again.
No, I, I won't let you.
I won't let you do this.
But this is my favorite game.
Princess.
[all laughing]
You're not gonna get me.
I won't let you do this.
This is, this is like a lot,
there's a lot happening here.
[Chrissy screaming]
[Max groaning]
No.
Oh, don't don't, don't, stop, please.
[Max grunting and panting]
I wanna tell my mom
and dad that I'm sorry
that I didn't go to dental school.
[Declan laughing]
[Alex laughing]
[Chrissy laughing]
I'm just gonna ad lib something,
because I feel like that's, this is not-
- Dental school?
The only reason that I would
be going to dental school
is for the fucking gas.
I don't think they give
you that in dental school.
This demon has zero intention.
What, what is the point?
What is the actual point of this demon?
Like, that's just, like fuck, dude.
I don't know,
I don't know what to play.
[Alex sighing]
It's not that, I'm just
saying that possession
is such a cliche.
And why are we all reading
the same character?
Dude, I asked that day one.
Okay, it's a work in progress, you guys.
And I'm just tryin' to
figure out everyone's flow.
Well, I thought Kelly did great.
Yeah, me, too.
I mean, it was super subtle,
- but like raw and organic.
- She did.
Thank you.
But there's no way you're
releasing any of that
because the lighting
looks cheap and desperate,
and what's with the whole,
this is a true story thing?
I mean, the audience is gonna know
if we're actually dead, we're famous.
Most of us.
Can hear you, clearly.
Wait, do you guys actually
think the lighting looks cheap?
Because I really don't
want people to think
that I'm desperate.
You should probably
rethink a lotta things then.
[Max laughing]
- No, listen, Chrissy.
- Wait, what?
Don't worry, it's raw, okay?
If we do it black and white
everyone would think it's like art house.
Exactly.
Guys, it shows that we are serious actors
that only care about
the quality of the work.
Yeah, I mean, Allison Janney
didn't win her Oscar for "The Help"
when she was dripping in pearls.
She won it for "I, Tonya"
when she was literally
strapped to an oxygen tank.
Exactly.
Oh my God, that was Allison Janney?
Wow.
What?
Vanity aside, the plot's whack.
Like there's a spirit attacking
people with bad shit in them
- and then what?
- Exactly.
That's what's scary.
It's relatable.
It's relatable for about 20 minutes
and then you lose your audience.
I mean, people wanna be
challenged, not spoonfed.
You know, Lesly Kahn always says-
- [Declan and Kip laughing]
- Again.
What is the-
- Oh Christ.
what, what, what's so funny.
Nothing dude.
Well, how do you know
if someone's studies with Lesly Kahn?
- Don't, don't.
- They'll tell you.
[Alex laughing]
Well, you're an idiot.
Good one.
Okay guys, okay, okay, look,
Kelly does have a point, right?
We should give the characters
something to fight for.
So, I don't know how are
they gonna beat the spirit?
How do you beat something unbeatable?
Deep, Chrissy.
What is she doing?
Chrissy, why are you
talking to a necklace?
What?
Oh, this is actually a pendulum.
So it helps me make decisions.
I just ask it a yes or
no question, and then-
- You should be careful with that shit.
You never know who or what
you're calling on to answer it.
Those things are like
pretty little Oujia Boards that you wear.
What do you mean?
It's a necklace.
No, Kel, I got this at the Rose Bowl.
Okay, nothing bad ever
happens in Pasadena.
According to who?
Fine, how does it move?
Physics?
No, it connects to your higher self
- to give you divine guidance.
- Exactly.
Divine, also known as spirituality, God.
It's a conduit.
It's a necklace.
All I'm saying is, who's
pushing the pendulum?
Can't answer a door without opening it.
Wait, hold on, wait, wait,
wait, that's kinda good.
That might work.
Yeah, who's pushing the pendulum?
Yeah, that's kinda great, Kel.
I mean, I wrote most of
my own stuff on "Belle," so.
So, what if our
characters use the pendulum
to summon a spirit to help them
banish the spirit that's attacking them?
Yeah, I love that.
I'm pretty sure that's not
how it actually works, guys.
I do have some experience in this field.
Oh, it'll be like "The
Craft" meets "Poltergeist."
I'm into it.
Just be careful, Kip.
'Cause supernatural stuff
gets so cheesy really quick.
Well actually, I might
have something, you know?
I saw it on Reddit the other day.
- Banishment curses.
- Banishment curses?
Why you lookin' up
banishment curses, Declan?
I was gonna send one to my agent.
Wow.
Yikes.
- [Alex laughing]
- You're so creepy.
I take back calling you an idiot,
'cause now I'm terrified.
- Just fire him.
- Here, here, here, here.
Someone read this.
I got it.
I call upon the darkness, for
only you can halt the attack.
I call upon your forces to take them away,
to take them back.
On the road to evil from my home to yours,
I consent to your power for
all the days and all the hours.
[loud banging and static]
What the fuck?
Okay, what the fuck?
That's a little on the
nose, don't you think?
Declan, did you do that?
That was amazing.
I can play around with it a
little so it's not so obvious,
but that's good.
Great, so then we'll
just shoot the next scenes,
and then we'll see if we
can stitch some together.
- Cool, okay.
- Okay, wait, wait, wait.
I mean, yeah, it's not that easy.
You can't just put it together-
- Do we have a name yet?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, I was
thinking "The Reckoning."
No.
- Why?
- I don't like it.
All around?
No, nobody?
Pendulum, "The Pendulum."
No, that's for sure not it.
"Untitled Horror Movie."
- What?
- Meta.
This is weird.
No, when you Google it it's gonna be
the first thing that
comes up, that's genius.
Oh come on, you guys
come on, that's lame.
I mean, will people get it?
- It's funny.
- No, no, no,
but then, but then, who's
pushing the pendulum
could be the tagline.
That's kinda long for a hashtag.
Okay, all right, all right.
Well, Kelly, why don't you check with CAA?
See which one they like best.
I'm telling my agents about this.
They'll shut it down quicker
than the time it takes you to ejaculate.
- That is-
- Wow.
You know what, that's my cue.
- I'm for sure, bye guys.
- I don't.
Okay, peace and love.
- It's not that easy to write.
- Bye.
We believe in you.
I thought "The
Reckoning" was way better.
[phone ringing]
Hey, Kel, what's up?
Kel?
What do you think my
strengths are as an actor?
Oh Jesus, I.
I'm serious, I wanna know.
Okay, you're good at
making scenes feel real.
You always hit the emotional connection.
I mean, you can cry like nobody else,
- so that's good.
- Good, so you do know.
Now can you actually
write me some scenes
that show my range?
[Kip laughing]
Kelly, that's not really how it works.
You can't just tell a
writer what to write.
Of course you can.
Vin Diesel does it all the time.
I mean, why do you think The
Rock was in a hospital bed
for the entire "Fast Eight"
or "Furious 11" or whatever?
What?
Look, you play a dick on the show.
Don't be one in real life.
- [phone beeping]
- Okay.
How did I ever date her?
["What Can I Do"]
Okay, I don't have a pendulum.
So like somebody gifted me this.
I'm gonna use it.
["What Can I Do"]
[Max grunting]
I have no choice.
If I wanna live,
I must involve the darkness.
I must complete the ritual.
["What Can I Do"]
With this candle I call upon and stir...
Fuck.
With this candle.
I call upon and stir.
I call him call upon and...
Fuck me.
The lords of fire.
[lighter clicking]
["What Can I Do"]
Fire
and the south.
With this sage I call upon and stir.
The lords of the air and the east.
["What Can I Do"]
With this bowl, I call upon and stir
the lords of water and the west.
[Lesly] I'm sorry, I have to stop you.
Sorry, hold on, hold on.
How was that?
It was very good.
But there are a couple things
that we need to talk about.
I don't really understand
your relationship
to the water and the west.
You're just saying them
like they're words.
I'm not getting an image on water.
Okay.
Do you follow?
I'm not getting an image on west.
- That was dumb, yeah.
- And also, aren't you
talking about stirring
something in a bowl?
Where's the bowl?
I don't see a bowl.
Why are you miming?
- Don't mime.
- Stupid.
Why would you mime?
[Max grunting]
Okay, so repeat after me.
Don't mime.
You're not going to mime.
Okay.
- I remember now.
- Don't mime.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Let's do it again
and remember why you're doing this?
[Max grunting]
You're doing this
to entertain the people.
Got it, got it, got it.
["What Can I Do"]
With this bowl.
With this bowl [laughing].
I call upon and stir the lords of water.
The lords of water.
And the west.
["What Can I Do"]
Oh my god, Max.
Yeah?
Oh my god, Max, that was,
that was incredible.
Oh, yes, thank you, Lesly.
Did you see how you were
listening to the water?
Yeah, I was in it, palpable.
You are on it.
- Yes.
- I am really happy
- with what you're doing.
- Yes.
Thank you, Lesly.
[Lesly] That's really good.
This is why I work with ya.
[Max laughing]
With this soil.
I call upon and stir the lords
of the earth and the north.
I call upon the darkness,
for only you can halt the attack.
I call upon your
forces to take them away,
to take them back.
On the road to evil.
[bowl clanking]
From my home to yours
I consent to your power.
For all the days
and all the hours.
Yes, Max.
Yeah?
Oh, thank god.
That's exactly what I was talking about.
Did you see what happened to Khaleesi?
She was panting like a motherfucker.
[Declan snoring]
[gentle intense music]
On the road to evil,
from my home to yours.
I consent to your power.
For all the days and all the hours.
[loud banging]
[intense music]
[Chrissy yelling]
That was better, Kip.
Thank you.
I added that part-
- You could dig deeper, though.
Okay, everyone, that
was a really great job.
Chrissy, nice fall, by the way.
I mean, I coulda done more,
but I didn't know if you
wanted full Charlize.
Guys, guys, guys, guys.
I have awesome news.
Imagine what we could do if we had
a script by an actual writer.
- Isn't-
- I can hear you Dicklan.
Yeah, I know [laughing].
Wow.
What's on your neck?
Oh my god.
It's a tat.
My character has tats, so.
That's commitment.
His character's edgy.
Can you guys hear me?
- Is this a wifi thing or like?
- Yeah, what?
Okay, yeah, you guys
are just being assholes,
like I thought.
I have awesome news.
I cut up some of the
footage, just in iMovie,
sent it over to my manager.
You what?
Max!
Oh my God.
You can't just send out
unedited, unfinished footage.
Okay, okay, relax, guys.
It was just to my manager
and her friend at Lionsgate.
- What?
Max, what the fuck, dude?
You're so stupid.
What, guys?
It's a good thing.
They went nuts for it.
- Wait, Lionsgate?
- What?
Yeah.
Like actual Lionsgate.
Lionsgate.
Yeah, Lionsgate, Lionsgate.
And she said that if we put together
about 15 minutes of the footage
she will walk it right
into the studio herself.
Puh!
[Kip laughing]
Oh my god.
What's that gonna cost us?
5% of the movie plus her producer credit?
Dude, it doesn't matter.
That's great news.
Thank you, Kip.
No, tell me you at
least colored it first.
Yeah.
Well, I thought we were going for
the whole raw, "I, Tonya" thing.
Oh god.
Just 'cause it's raw doesn't mean it's-
- Oh I have this app that makes videos,
they look like super vibey.
Oh my god, it's amazing.
That's still-
- Are we mad about this or happy?
'Cause I don't really understand.
Listen, Max, it is awesome.
Happy.
- Yes, but.
- Okay, thank you.
I don't think we should sell it
to the first studio that wants it, right?
We should play the field,
start a bidding war.
No, that's, that's
actually a great point.
They're interested because
the stuff we shot was good.
And if they're interested,
then others will be, too.
- Exactly.
- So,
I'll finish writing a scene,
and then we could just
film some more stuff.
Great, just take your time.
Okay?
Don't rush it.
It needs to be good.
And Chrissy, how did you
do that shadow thing?
Oh yeah.
It was extra, but it worked, so.
What shadow thing?
Come on.
What?
what?
I'm sorry, guys.
- I don't know.
- Here we go again.
No, like I really don't know what
- you're talking about.
- Okay.
We get it Chrissy,
- we get it.
- Keep your secrets.
- That's fine.
- Okay, bye.
- Peace out weirdos.
- Bye bye.
Kip, does she think we're stupid?
I mean, it's like, do you want
this thing to be good or not?
Listen, I don't think she knows
what we were talking about.
No, she used to do this
all the time in rehearsals.
She would phone it in,
and then she would pull out her choices
when the cameras were actually rolling.
Like I would ever steal from her.
Listen, Kelly, maybe she
just had a record player
and the light on it so when
it turned, it just made this,
I don't know, light on the wall
- or something.
- I actually,
I think I have one of those, I can-
- Wait, Kelly, just,
Kelly, let her have it.
Okay, you know you're gonna shine.
You always do.
You should come over.
We can practice the scenes.
I would but I have to work.
It's just that I'm so scared.
The scenes are so good and
I'm having trouble sleeping.
Okay, yeah, nice try.
Call me if you need me, okay?
I need you.
If you really need me.
And it's gone.
What, is it the mustache?
- Really?
- Goodnight, Kipper.
Oh my God, you guys are ridiculous.
[intense music]
I figured it out.
It's you.
I should've known.
Penny, Penny, there is not one single day
that goes by that I don't miss you.
I wish we could just go back
to sitting on the couch and watching TV
like we had all the time in the world.
Because we did.
At least I thought we did.
I know you're angry, and I'm sorry.
I shoulda tried harder.
[gentle music]
I shoulda been a better friend.
If I could take it all back, I would.
[gentle music]
Penny, I miss you.
I hate you for what you did,
but it doesn't deny the
fact that I love you,
and I probably always will.
But maybe our love
just wasn't meant to be.
Maybe our love was always
just meant to be free.
The way that you are now.
[gentle music]
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I coulda done better.
I should have done better.
And as much as I wanna
see you and keep you,
Penny, I, um...
I have to let you go.
It has to,
it has to end here.
[intense music]
[hand slapping]
[Chrissy grunting]
[intense music]
[thunder crashing]
You don't have to be like this.
[intense music]
[thunder crashing]
[Chrissy grunting]
[hand slapping]
[intense music]
What the?
I'm so sorry.
It has to end here.
[intense music]
it has to end here, Penny.
It has to end here.
[intense eerie music]
[Chrissy grunting]
[hand slapping]
Did anyone see the weird
lightning last night?
Like it wasn't raining,
but it was lightning.
- No.
- Hmm-mmm.
No, but dude, something
really strange happened
while I was filming.
I rolled camera and I'm
- going into the scene-
- Where's Chrissy?
It's really unprofessional
to keep people waiting.
Hi Kelly.
Is it Kelly?
Unprofessional to keep people waiting?
No, I haven't heard from her.
She's probably still at rehearsal.
Rehearsal?
Wait, rehearsal for what?
She kept talking about some play
she was thinkin' of doing.
Honey, if I had an Oscar for
every time I used that line
- I'd be Meryl Streep.
- I'm sorry,
Chrissy's doing a play?
Yeah, she didn't tell you guys about it?
She's been busy like all week.
- Every time I've spoken to her.
- Yeah, no.
There's no way she's doing a play.
You actually have to
have talent to do that.
So that's a lie.
[Alex scoffing]
Okay. Thank you, Kelly.
I will try calling her really quickly.
Okay, but not to be mean,
but does it really matter?
I mean, she's not adding
that much value to the movie.
- Declan.
- Dude.
Declan, she's literally
one of the leads of our show.
She's not the lead, though, so,
people will still watch without her.
Here we go.
What?
You guys would all get a pay raise, okay?
So don't give me that.
Oh, you are unbelievable.
You guys,
you won't believe what
just happened to me.
- Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa.
- Oh my god, Chrissy, what?
Babe, what happened to your eye?
Are you okay?
Are you doing a play?
- Who's directing?
- What?
- Oh my god.
- Kelly.
No, I'm not doing,
listen to me, you guys.
I was, I was trying to
shoot one of the scenes,
and all of a sudden, I don't,
I don't even know how to say it.
[Chrissy crying and hyperventilating]
Chrissy, we can't
understand you if you overact.
You gotta bring it down.
Just like a little bit.
Just give yourself somewhere to go.
Okay, okay, you guys, just listen.
I was doing this scene,
and all of a sudden I just
started slapping myself.
Like I couldn't stop.
I was so scared, you guys.
And it was just my hand to do
over and over and over and over.
Chrissy, Chrissy, Chrissy, me, too.
Me, too.
I punched myself right in the chin.
And it's like it took over me.
I only did it once and
I think I passed out,
but I decided when I got up
that I needed to use this in the scene.
Ah, you're a fuckin' pro, Max.
What?
That's one name for it.
Thanks, Kip.
Chrissy, are you, babe are you okay?
Do you need me to come over?
No, I'm gonna be fine.
I think.
I told you not to
mess with the dark arts.
What?
Oh my god.
Is this Hogwarts?
Okay, you guys, maybe,
maybe, Chrissy, maybe your performance
was just so good that
you got carried away.
You know?
Been there.
Is that a thing?
Oh totally.
- Yes.
- Yeah, of course.
You're just so in the scene
you get lost in the moment.
You're just so in character
you lose track of everything.
It's like performance amnesia.
You guys actually think?
Definitely, like a hundred percent.
Totally.
How is there any doubt about this, guys?
I mean, do you not
remember season two finale?
When I was under that curse,
the big scene, Universal
backlot, right by "Jaws."
You remember?
What?
Anyways.
I really started to
believe that I was evil.
I mean, my mom wouldn't
talk to me for like a week.
That feels very unrelated.
It's in the same lane, but okay.
Kelly?
Kel?
Yeah, yeah.
A few years ago I trained
with the USC diving team
for this aquatic film I was doing,
and well for like a month,
I thought I was a diver.
Wow.
All right, listen, why
don't we all take tonight off?
It feels like that's much needed.
Kip can work on another scene,
and then we will chat again tomorrow.
- Okay?
- Yeah,
Yeah, sure.
Okay, thank you guys so much.
I'm sorry I like freaked out.
[Chrissy laughing]
Oh my god, it's also like a full moon,
and so maybe I just got like, so in it.
Isn't it daytime?
Anyway, I'm gonna go cleanse my aura,
- do a face mask, just TLC.
- Move your,
Move your crystals around the house.
Bye.
- Bye.
- Don't go chasing waterfalls.
- [Alex laughing]
- Okay, bye.
What the fuck is going on?
What?
No, don't treat me like an actor.
We all know that method acting is just
made up shit to justify bad behavior.
Who's being naughty costars
having secret meetings then?
Okay, we're not, we're just,
we just haven't hung up yet.
We're not having a meeting, Declan.
Shit's goin' down isn't it?
Oh my god, it is.
Fuck, I knew I wasn't tripping last night.
Like I was tripping,
but I wasn't tripping.
Declan, this isn't funny.
Okay, it's serious.
Yeah, she obviously got carried away.
I mean, if anybody's gonna do it
it's gonna be a bunch of actors.
Well, I didn't get carried away.
We all know I'm not that good.
Exactly.
No, I felt something
weird last night, too.
Okay, I just felt like
this wind wash over me.
Did you maybe leave a
window open, possibly?
Kip, you know how
sensitive I am to this stuff?
Okay, so don't-
[Kip laughing]
Okay, what are you saying then, Kel?
Are you really gonna make me say it?
I'll say it.
Something ooky spooky's goin' on.
[laughing] oh come, Come on, you guys.
I mean, Kelly, what's more believable?
Chrissy overacting or that she's
boxing with zombies in her apartment.
Don't play to the judge, okay?
That's actually a good idea.
That would make a good movie.
You know, like a bunch of people
go out to make a horror movie
and then real shit
starts happening to them.
It feels very meta.
One too many metas.
You know, this is making me think
that that shadow she
did, that it wasn't fake.
True.
Oh, Kel, come on.
You saw Alex's tape from last night.
She did the exact same thing.
Me, what?
No, I didn't.
What?
- I didn't.
- Wait, are you,
are you kidding?
Are you fucking with me?
No, I'm being,
no I'm being serious.
What are you talking about?
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
You guys are crazy.
Here, let, I'll pull it up.
What the fuck is that?
Wait.
Zoom in and enhance that.
- I can't-
- Oh my god.
She does one episode of CSI
and thinks zoom in and
enhance it is a thing.
Okay, I mean, it's
obviously the ceiling fan.
You guys, they just installed the light
too close to the fan, right?
- Are you serious?
- So you didn't,
you didn't make that,
- you didn't make that shadow?
- Okay, you know what?
You guys are tryin' to scare
me and it's not gonna work.
I'm leaving.
- Bye.
- You two are just fucked.
Okay?
You're fucked.
Both of you, fucked.
And let me tell you something,
I don't like this one bit.
Okay, close your window
- before you go to bed.
- Goodbye.
Personally, and this is just me,
but I think it's fucking great.
I know [laughing].
We are losing it.
[intense music]
[phone ringing]
Kip, what time is it?
I'm sorry, it's late
or early, I don't know.
Look, something really
weird just happened.
What?
Chrissy just uploaded a video.
So call Chrissy.
No, listen, she's sleeping in the video.
It's like the camera's
moving, but she's sleeping.
It's really fucking creepy.
Come on, that doesn't make any sense.
You can't upload footage
- when you're unconscious.
- No, that's
not what I'm saying.
It's just, I don't know.
It looks like someone else is there.
What do you mean?
- Okay, hold on.
- Just send it to me.
I'm gonna show you.
[intense music]
[clock ticking]
[dark intense music]
Damn, I mean, she really went for it.
I mean, she's good.
Have you shown Kelly?
She's gonna shit her pants.
No, no, I didn't show Kelly.
No.
I mean, come on, Kip,
she obviously just got Max to
go over there and shoot it.
And I mean, it works.
It's a hell of a lot better
than just holding the camera yourself.
Okay, yeah, but no, that's
that's not like Chrissy.
I mean, she wouldn't do that.
What, you think it's Casper?
I mean, what, who are you, Kelly?
Okay, I'm not saying
it's a ghost or something.
It's just, I don't know, it's
not like Chrissy to do that.
And it's really frickin' creepy.
Fine, just call the others.
[call disconnecting]
Sorry for waking you,
Kip's having a fit.
It's all good.
I was just chasin' the worm.
Who still smokes?
[Max laughing]
You said worm.
Well, there he is, our
very own Dean Cundey.
[Max yawning]
Who is Dean Cundey?
Dude, he shot "Halloween,"
"Back to the Future,"
"Jurassic Park."
Oh my God, what the fuck
is Lesly teaching you?
Don't speak to-
- Okay, where's Chrissy?
He said he doesn't
know, he hasn't seen her.
Bullshit.
I swear on my mother's life.
I just woke up.
Do you see-
- [indistinct]
- Okay, wait, wait, wait, Max.
Swear on Lesly's.
[Declan laughing]
Have any of you even tried to call her?
Seriously?
Oh my God, what the fuck
is wrong with all of you?
Okay, Max, if she's not
with you, then who is?
Why do you keep asking me?
Yo?
Yeah, get in the meeting room.
Okay, bye.
She's coming.
So she's fine.
She's fine.
Will someone please tell
me what the hell is going on?
I was asleep.
Do you know how many pills I had to take
to make that happen?
A pharmacy worth.
Look, there she is.
- Hey, guys.
- Chrissy.
- Hi.
- Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Mmhmm, oh my God, you guys.
I had the best dream.
I'm gonna journal it later as soon as
- we're done with this.
- Are you alone right now?
Yes, Max, I am alone.
What kind of a question is that?
Listen, a video of you
- got uploaded to-
- What?
What video?
I swear, I deleted all those.
No.
Oh my god, the one time I drank tequila.
Wait, wait, wait a minute,
let's talk about that for a minute.
- What?
- No, Chrissy,
it was a video of you sleeping.
Yeah, it was like an hour ago.
Wait, what?
Okay, all right, hold on.
Let me pull it up.
I don't.
What videos were you-
- I'm confused.
Me, too.
[intense music]
[Chrissy] Oh my God, that's my house.
Okay, who's filming it, though?
Like what the?
Chrissy, you're obviously doing that.
It's not me.
It's like so weird.
[intense music]
[Alex] Cute jacket.
You see?
Oh my god.
Wait a minute.
You-
- See it's not me.
- Come on, Max.
- I told you.
- That's not you?
[Declan] Whoa, what the fuck?
[intense music]
I didn't film that.
What the fuck?
[intense music]
- Oh my god, guys.
- Was it?
I didn't film that.
I told you all,
but nobody ever trusts a pretty blonde.
Fuckin' told you.
What am I gonna do?
Okay, okay, we need to calm down, okay?
- Okay-
- No, no,
we do not need to be calm.
We need to call the cops right now.
Whoever did that could
still be in your house.
What?
Why would you say that to her?
911, Chrissy, now.
Max, Max, this isn't funny anymore.
If you were actually there
and you actually shot it,
- fucking say something.
- I'm not fuckin',
why am I fucking around
tell her to call the cops?
I'm not kidding.
[Dispatcher] 911,
what is your emergency?
Hi, yeah, is this 911?
What?
- Wait, shit.
- Chrissy.
- Fuck.
- Where'd she go?
Where'd she go, where'd she go?
- Somebody call her.
Somebody call her.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
It's not gonna work
if we're all calling her at the same time.
Good point, Declan.
Well, who's calling?
I am, just hold on.
Okay, she's calling me.
Hey, what the fuck happened?
My computer died, sorry.
Oh my god.
Her computer died.
Jesus.
Oh god.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I mean, no,
but they're sending cops.
They're sending a cop.
Oh God.
Declan, Declan, I don't know what to do.
Why did you hang up from the police?
To call you guys back.
This is super fucked,
- you guys.
- I don't think
we can help you.
Ask her if she wants me
to go over to her house.
I can see you, dickhead.
Max wants to know if
he should come over.
[loud banging]
[everyone gasping]
What was that?
What the fuck?
Shhh, shhh, you guys, guys.
What the fuck was that?
I think somebody's in my room.
[intense music]
- What's she saying?
- What's going on?
Declan, talk to us.
What's happening, man?
Is she using the pendulum again?
No, stop using that thing.
Okay, I'm gonna look.
No, no, no.
- Did she just say she was gonna look?
- No no no.
[Group] No no no no.
- Stay where you are.
- No.
Chrissy.
[intense music]
Can you tell her to
stop shaking the camera?
Kelly, shut the fuck up.
What, it's making me nauseous.
Chrissy, just get the fuck out of there.
I am trying.
Would you be quiet?
[intense music]
[Declan] Oh sweet Jesus, what is that?
- Don't put it down.
- Shut up, Declan.
[Chrissy exhaling]
I trained for this.
- Oh god, no.
- No, no, no.
Just because you played a ninja on TV.
Why do you have that?
What could she possibly do with that?
Why do you have a samurai sword?
Relax you guys.
The stunt guy said that I was good enough
to be a professional.
No, he had to say that to you.
They were being nice.
That was pretend fighting, Chrissy, no.
[loud banging]
[Chrissy gasping]
- Christ.
- Shit.
[Declan] What was that?
Chrissy, what was that?
It came from the kitchen.
Well don't go in there.
Get your stuff and get out of the house.
Get out of the house.
Jesus, Chrissy, what are you doing?
Why are you looking for him?
Run.
[loud banging]
[Chrissy grunting]
[quiet intense music]
Is that thing even sharp?
Um,
no.
Kip, Kip, Kip, you should
be writing all this down.
Are you kidding me right now?
Now is not the time.
Don't worry about it.
I'm on it.
Oh you piece of shit.
Okay, you're not getting
a writing credit, though.
I'm just saying.
[Chrissy grunting]
But this is.
- Oh my God, oh my God.
- No, no, no.
- Now we're talking, yes.
- You should not be allowed
- to play with grown up knives.
- Yes.
Be careful you don't stab yourself.
Okay, listen, Declan,
tell those assholes
that I can still hear them.
Kinda.
She says she can still hear you guys.
[gentle intense music]
[Chrissy gasping]
[Chrissy laughing]
Okay, honestly, I am
literally losing my mind.
No, I don't, I don't,
I don't think you are.
I heard something, too.
Declan, there is nobody here.
Are you guys playing a trick on me?
No, you just need to go
back to your room, and-
- These pranks aren't funny, okay?
[door banging]
[intense music]
Shit.
Fuck.
[door banging]
I think it's the cops.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That was way too quick.
Don't answer it.
The police are here, it's fine.
[Declan] Chrissy, don't answer it.
Declan-
- Okay, wait, wait-
- No no no,
- don't put your phone down.
- Chrissy,
maybe you should just-
- Just bring it with you so we can-
- Bring your phone, bring your phone.
Also, no more shrooms.
Who else would it be?
Come on.
[Max] Guys, I don't like
this, I don't like this.
Can someone call the cops?
[Chrissy] Wait, no.
[Chrissy screaming]
[intense music]
Chrissy.
Oh my god, oh my god, no.
[intense music]
What are you doing?
Chrissy, stop doing that!
[intense music]
Chrissy.
What just happened?
What is happening?
[intense music]
[knuckles crackling]
What the?
[intense music]
[knuckles crackling]
What the fuck?
[intense music]
What the fuck was that?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh my god, oh my god.
I just, I just saw someone die.
Oh god.
Okay, I'm gonna call the cops.
That was fuckin' weird.
Where's Alex?
I am never gonna unsee that.
I'm gonna have to carry
that with me forever.
Shut up, where's Alex?
- Guys, guys, I'm so sorry.
- Oh my god.
- I'm so sorry.
- Where did you go?
ALl of my power went out.
Like even my phone.
I don't know what happened.
That was so weird.
Dude, not cool.
What did I miss?
Is Chrissy okay?
No, Chrissy's dead.
Dead?
What do you mean dead?
She's fine.
What?
The police said that she called back
three minutes after the
original call to cancel it.
Wait what?
No.
We fuckin' saw it.
No, no, I was still on
the phone to her then.
It would have been after you hung up.
What an asshole.
Why would she do that to us?
Will someone please
tell me what is going on?
Chrissy was strangled with her own hand.
Okay, you guys,
- this is really fucked up.
- And then-
- You know what?
I'm goin' over there.
Oh geez.
Declan, come on man.
That's not a good idea.
No, that does not sound
like a good idea at all.
I mean, what if there's
someone still in the house?
Who?
[door shutting]
And there he goes.
Look, I am just saying, okay, Declan
is a bit of a wiener.
Like, what is he-
- Okay, Max, Max, we get it.
- Really going to do?
Why don't you just go ahead
and go over there yourself?
- No, no.
- You should both go.
This is not fake.
It's not fake.
Oh, Kelly, come on.
Shut up, Alex.
She strangled herself.
That's physically impossible.
If that's not some supernatural shit
then I don't know what is.
Super, okay, then why is
it only attacking Chrissy
and not all of us?
Right?
We all did the spell.
Fuck.
It's the fucking pendulum.
Fuck, oh my god.
- [Kip laughing]
- I was right.
I was, I was right.
All along.
I was right.
Again, fuckin' right, fuckin' pendulum.
Oh my god.
[intense music]
[phone ringing]
Chrissy.
Hello.
Chrissy, come on, this isn't funny.
[intense piano music]
Okay, we're glad you're not dead.
Okay, Chrissy, good talk.
[intense piano music]
[phone ringing]
Hold on just one sec,
Chrissy, Kelly's callin'.
I'll merge us.
[phone ringing]
Hey, Kel.
I want an apology.
No, it's, Chrissy's fine, okay?
She just called me.
She's on the other line.
Hold on, I'll just, I'll merge us.
Hold on, hold on, one sec, one sec.
Where is she?
[Kip sighing]
You know, I don't know.
I actually haven't seen her yet,
but this is her apartment, so.
[intense music]
Chrissy.
She's alive.
Wow, she can act.
[loud banging]
[intense music]
[intensifying music]
Wait, how did he get there so fast?
You idiots know we're
not filming this, right?
You called us.
Hey.
[intense scary music]
What is he doing?
I have no idea.
This is weird.
[dark intense music]
[banging on window]
Again, with the strangling.
[dark intense music]
- Okay, that was kinda creepy.
- What the fuck?
I'm calling him.
[intense music]
[phone ringing]
Do you guys know how
dangerous it is to call people
while they're driving?
You piece of shit.
What the hell is wrong with you?
What?
We saw Chrissy strangle herself,
and you were there.
Yeah, I know I was on
the same call as you.
No, no, you were there, and
she strangled herself again.
Fucking crazy town over here.
What?
Where the fuck are you?
I'm going through West Hollywood.
Well, show us.
What?
Show us.
Wait, he's not even,
he's not even close.
Yeah, I just said that.
I'm still like 20 minutes away.
Declan you need to get
over there right now.
I don't know what the fuck is going on,
but it's some weird magic shit,
and just get over there and call me.
[quiet intense music]
I'm here.
[intense music]
[dog barking]
I swear to god, if
she's fucking with us,
I will kill her myself.
[intense music]
[gate clanking]
No, something feels weird.
Knock, maybe.
Why do you have a key to Chrissy's?
Max, shut up?
Dude.
She gave me one when we dated.
You are the worst.
[intense music]
[door creaking]
Oh my god.
[door slamming]
[dark intense music]
I see her.
[intense music]
What?
She's not moving.
Okay, she's pretending.
Go in there and poke her.
Are you insane?
I'm not going in there.
She's messing with you.
Declan, she's not dead.
[intense music]
[Declan] Oh my god.
Do something, Declan.
[banging on door]
Oh god, she's not moving.
She should have moved.
[banging on door]
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, why is she doing this to me?
She should have moved, guys.
- She should have moved.
- Are you sure, Declan?
What do I do? What do I do?
- What do I do?
- Just don't touch
anything and just get out of there.
Okay?
Do you want me to call the cops?
Is that gonna make you feel better?
- Have someone come over?
- No, no, no, no, no, wait.
You need to get the pendulum.
Kelly enough with
- the pendulum.
- Get the pendulum.
I know it has something to do with this.
I'm not stealing from
our dead costar, Kelly.
Just do it, you little piss wipe.
It may be the only way we can figure out
what the fuck is going on.
So do it.
You go in there, and be a man, and get it.
Fuck you.
[door slamming]
You guys, you fuckin' owe me.
Thank god.
[intense music]
[person screaming]
Did you guys hear that?
Hear what?
- What?
- You-
- What, what?
- Hear-
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Have any of you guys
watched a horror movie?
Declan, just get out of there.
Wait, shut up.
[gentle intense music]
I think there's someone in there.
[Max] What do you
mean someone's in there?
[Alex] What are we looking at?
[Declan] Right there.
Right past her body.
See that shadow?
- Right where?
- Where, where, where?
What are you talking about?
[Declan] Fuck.
Oh my god, what the fuck is that?
Is that a guy?
Okay, okay, just
fucking get out of there
Declan.
It's not funny anymore.
[loud banging]
My god.
Oh my god.
Her body's gone.
What?
What do you, what do
you mean her body's gone.
How does a dead body walk away?
I don't know, it's gone.
What the fuck?
[Kip] Maybe she walked away.
I mean, how did she just get up there?
[sudden intense music]
[everyone gasping]
Holy shit, that was good.
[dark intense music]
Don't be ridiculous.
They must be working together.
- Don't you dare.
- Obviously.
Enough with the whole
it was a fucking turntable
and a fan bullshit.
That bitch got possessed
and she killed herself.
- Kelly's right.
- Or Declan killed her.
I don't know, but something
- fucking happened.
- I didn't kill her.
And you know what, Kip,
I am sick and tired of being told
that because I am a woman I am crazy.
We're not crazy.
- We're the only ones who-
- Kelly, shoosh,
- shoosh shoosh shoosh.
- What are you talking about?
Shoosh shoosh shoosh shoosh
shoosh, guys, it's my manager.
Hold on, hold on.
[intense music]
Hey Alissa, yeah.
Yeah, I have a minute, mmhmm.
Okay.
Wait.
You're serious?
That's amazing news.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, yeah, we'll
talk about it more tomorrow.
Okay, you let me, I'll call you.
You call me.
I'll call you.
Okay, yeah, okay, bye.
[Max laughing]
- Holy shit.
- Are you kidding?
Do not mute us.
- That is so rude.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry guys, guys, listen.
All right, that was Alissa.
- She called me-
- Also, you don't have
a huge problem with
your manager calling you
at three o'clock in the morning?
That's when she does her reading, Alex.
Anyways, she took some of
the footage over to Netflix,
and they are putting together
an offer to buy the film.
- What?
- Right now?
- Yeah.
- How much?
- Did they say how much?
- Are you for real?
Do you think you can do reshoots?
No, no, we don't need reshoots.
They love the footage how it is.
It's raw and tense and gritty.
They're saying 2021 is
all about found footage.
[Declan crashing]
- But when do they want it?
- How is this gonna work?
Do we get a percentage?
Well, we need to finish the story.
No, no, fuck the story.
The story doesn't really, even
really matter at this point.
They just love the energy of it.
All right, but now we need to
- figure out the why now factor.
- You guys, did you see that?
What does that even mean?
[Declan crashing]
[intense music]
Whoa.
Declan.
Explain that Kip.
He's obviously making
it about himself right now
because this is a victory for
my writing, quite frankly.
Guys, something's
- in my apartment.
- Declan, what are you doing?
Declan, where is the pendulum?
- Declan?
- You guys.
- Is he fucking around?
- Declan,
where is the pendulum, you dipshit?
Why are you wearing it?
I told you it was a necklace.
You just told me to take it.
You didn't tell me what to do with it.
Wait, do we really think that
this stupid fucking necklace thing
is controlling all of this?
It has to be.
I don't know-
[Kelly gasping]
- Kelly.
- Guys, guys, Kelly.
Kelly, Kelly.
I'm okay.
[loud banging]
[Kelly yelling]
What the fuck is going on?
[Kelly] Oh my god.
[Kelly gasping]
Oh my god.
Kelly, are you okay?
Yeah, it didn't end with Chrissy.
It started with her.
I could have just died.
I might've actually just
died for a minute there.
Well, you didn't, 'cause
you're breathing, but.
I can't die as an
unemployed television actress.
Okay, okay, okay, okay,
Kelly, just take a breath.
Just breathe.
- [Kelly hyperventilating]
- Do it with me.
[Max groaning]
Oh my god.
What is happening?
Are you guys all in on this together?
Fuck off, Kip.
- No.
- Fuck you, Kip.
- Okay, okay, shit.
Jesus.
Okay, so why?
Why now?
Because we started meddling
with this magic shit.
The why now factor.
Guys, the text.
The answers are in the fucking text.
Not now, Brando.
Listen to me.
Scene two, guys.
All right, we called upon a
spirit during the FaceTime
while Chrissy was swinging the pendulum.
He's right.
- And I said it was a conduit.
- Thank you.
We said I call upon the darkness
for only you can halt the attack.
The pendulum is the condiment.
We must have literally
called upon the darkness.
Wait, Declan, you're the
one that sent it to us.
Where'd you find it?
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
On Reddit somewhere.
Okay, find it again.
Fuck.
Pull it up, pull it up, pull it up.
Declan.
Here, here, here, here.
I call upon the darkness,
from my home to yours
I consent to your power
for all the days and all the hours.
All the days and all the...
That sounds pretty permanent, guys.
That's like forever.
Does it say anything else?
Scroll to the bottom.
Do people say anything in the reviews?
You don't review a Reddit.
[Alex crashing and grunting]
- Alex.
Alex.
- [Alex groaning]
- Are you okay?
In the comments.
Check in the comments.
Does it say anything?
Nothing, just ton of you
got rid of my cheating ex,
praise be, bullshit.
[Alex crashing and grunting]
Oh wait, wait, wait, here, here, here.
I'm next, I'm next, fuck.
Fuck, hurry up Declan, shit.
How do you undo the curse?
The original.
[indistinct] open a
flood gate, how do you?
How do you stop something
that's unstopabble?
Isn't that what Chrissy said?
Get to the point, get to
the point, get to the point.
No, wait.
It must, it must run its course.
It must run its course.
That sounds like it's from "The Craft."
That's directly from "The Craft."
Well what's the course?
What does it mean?
The author has no imagination.
No, it has to run its course.
It must fulfill its objective.
What's the objective?
Wait,
so we all have to,
do we all have to die?
- No, no, no, I don't think-
- please don't say-
[indistinct]
- Guys, we said,
- What's its objective
if not to kill us then?
I call upon the forces,
to take them away, to take them back.
To where?
I mean, I guess the
spirit must be attacking
what is evil inside of us?
Like my original script, hold on.
So we have to get rid of the evil
that is inside all of us?
How do we do that?
Or pass it onto somebody more evil?
Wait, you're talking
about killing someone.
You don't even believe
in this shit, remember?
Okay, no one's gonna die.
No, one's gonna die.
- No, one's gonna die.
- It's a little
suspect now, okay?
[Max whooshing and grunting]
Max.
- What the?
- Declan,
you have to get rid of it.
Yeah.
- [Max crashing and grunting]
- Max.
Declan, I do not care
who you send it to,
just make sure that they've read
the entire passage out loud.
- It's the only way-
- Yeah, okay, okay, okay.
that we can break the curse.
I'm on it.
Fuck, dude I spilled my milk.
I spilled my milk all
over the fuckin' floor.
It's just, it's on my socks.
[Max crashing and grunting]
Oh shit, oh my god, oh fuck.
It's everywhere.
[Max crashing and grunting]
- Oh, god.
- Not okay.
Not okay, not okay,
- not okay, not okay.
- I'll put on
a new pair of socks.
[Max] Declan, throw
away the fucking necklace.
[phone ringing]
[intense music]
Hey.
Oh shit, dude, you don't look so good.
Oh well, I've seen worse.
Well, hey did you get rid of it?
Yeah, I'm on my way.
Who, Declan?
Who are you sending it to?
Seriously?
I know, I know, I know, but,
I just, I need to know.
Dude, is this why you're calling me?
'Cause I'm trying to save our lives, okay?
No, no, they found Chrissy's body, man.
It's all over the news.
Fuck.
I told you guys.
I swear to God, I believed you.
It's just-
- What are they saying about it?
It still doesn't make any sense, okay?
They're calling it an accident.
That is fuckin' bullshit, isn't it?
[intense music]
Declan, do you think if
I woulda listened to Kelly,
do you think Chrissy would still be alive?
No I don't.
And honestly, man,
there's no use going down that road, okay?
Look, this is almost behind us.
I even wrote out instructions
to read the fucking thing out loud, okay?
But why, why would anyone do that?
Why wouldn't they?
We did.
Look, I gotta go.
Wait, Declan, Declan.
Do you think this is gonna work?
[intense music]
Honestly, Kip, I don't fuckin' know,
but we're about to find out.
[intense music]
[Kip] Did you get this
email from the network?
Yeah, it looks like we're all on it.
Dude it's from Bobbie Brower.
Wonderful.
Now on top of everything else,
our show's officially getting canceled.
Dammit.
Fuck.
Hey, Max.
Are you okay?
You kinda look like shit, dude.
No, no, no, I'm not okay, Alex.
Frankly, it's kinda disconcerting to me
that you guys are so calm, okay?
- And I'm having panic attacks-
- Okay, okay, okay, okay, Max,
- Max, Max, Max.
- Every two seconds.
Hyperventilating likes it's my job.
Okay.
Let's not jump into anything.
We don't know what this
meeting is about yet.
What meeting, Kip?
- What meeting?
- Bobbie Brower wants to talk
to all of us on Friday.
Bobbie?
Yeah.
Okay, maybe we should all go together,
because I don't really think
I should be going anywhere
alone at the moment
or just being alone in general [laughing].
Dude, it's summer hours.
Meetings aren't in prison.
Guys, screw, no, it's great, it's fine.
Where the hell are you?
I'm at my mom's house
because I got my ass beat
by a ghost in my bedroom.
[vacuum whirring]
God mom, you can't just
sneak up like that.
I'm on the phone.
[Mom] Oh, sorry.
- Okay, Max.
- Did Declan
get rid of it yet?
Because I'm really starting
to lose my shit, man.
And I don't really think
I can do this anymore.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He sent it a couple days ago.
Okay, okay.
Then why do I still feel
like I'm being watched?
I don't know, I don't know.
Okay, I haven't felt right either.
Ever since he sent it, I,
I should have stopped him from sending it.
Yeah, but come on, what
other choice did we have?
[Kip sighing]
Yeah, I mean maybe this thing
really does go after people who sin.
[intense music]
[water flowing]
[dark intense music]
[Declan gasping]
- Hey.
- What up man?
Hey guys.
It's so good to see you all.
Yeah.
I'm glad you guys are okay.
Listen, I just wanted to check in
with everybody before we have
this meeting with the network.
Who cancels the show of a dead girl?
I mean it's so short sighted.
Well, we don't know
if they're canceling us.
I'm sorry, let's just take a moment
for Chrissy's grieving
best friend, everyone.
Don't be jealous.
Jealous?
Yeah, that's the word.
Because I would love to be Chrissy's,
what's that basic ass
hashtag she keeps using
- in all the photos?
- Soul sister.
Soul sister, yes, yes.
How does it feel with
half your soul missing
right now, Kelly?
You know what?
We played sisters and the
people wanna hear from me.
Okay, has anyone heard from Declan?
I haven't spoken to
him since he was gonna-
- No.
- Mail the thing.
No.
- Yeah.
- Wait,
he didn't respond to the email.
No he didn't, but it's Declan so.
I'm gonna call him.
[phone ringing]
So
any of you know what this meeting's about?
No idea.
Come on, it's obvious.
When was the last time we
had a call with network?
When we got hired.
And when Declan got arrested
for hitting that Uber driver in Miami.
Exactly, they don't just call to say hi.
Okay, he's not picking up.
Hey listen, guys, if it is a cancellation,
let's just play it cool.
Okay?
I mean, realistically
they'll probably just
offer us therapy or something.
I don't need their shitty therapist.
I have my own.
Of course you do.
[gentle music]
Okay, let's just not give 'em a reason
to keep us under contract out of spite.
Okay?
Otherwise we'll never be
able to finish our movie.
What?
You guys wanna finish the movie?
Chrissy's dead.
Kip, it's her best work.
Oh my god.
Yeah, I mean, I do think that
she'd want us to finish it.
- Jesus.
- She might
even get nominated.
You are the worst person I have ever-
- Are you on your period or something?
I don't know what's going on.
- Fuck off, Kelly.
- Okay, wait, shit,
guys, it's time for the meeting.
Okay?
You ready?
- [Max sighing]
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Blah, blah, blah.
[intense music]
Hey guys, good afternoon.
Thank you for coming.
We've got Bobbie Brower on the line.
Welcome, everybody, welcome.
[Max] Thank you for having us.
Yeah, especially now
considering everything, so tragic.
Although the show's never been so popular.
Yeah, oh yeah it is.
It's super tragic.
Guys, you know Michelle,
from marketing, right?
Okay, good.
Hey, isn't there supposed
to be one more of you?
Yes.
Wait, what is, what's this?
This is going immediately, right?
Like as soon as we hang up?
Get it off.
I don't even understand
your face right now.
Yeah, where, is, was it, Declan, is it?
Declan is,
making a video.
Yeah.
From all of us to commemorate Chrissy.
It's a goodbye from her "Belle" family.
"Belle" family.
Hmmm.
Yeah, well, that's actually
really good thinking.
We were gonna send it over to
you guys when it was finished.
Thought it would be great press.
I mean, look guys, I know
that you guys were all,
I mean from your social media, very close,
and I'm sure this has gotta
be really hard on all of you.
God, I'm just, I'm not
really good at that stuff.
You know what I mean?
- Can we just-
- Bobbie, no, no, no,
you're you're wonderful.
You're great.
You know, I think that
we should just push on
because I know that you know
how valuable everyone's time is
and you wanted to give the cast some news.
Yeah, I did.
Guys, I wanted to let
you know that "Belle"
is being renewed
for three more seasons.
- Congratulations, guys.
- What?
Oh my god, what?
Oh my god.
That's great, that's great news.
This is so epic, thank you, thank you.
It is, it is indeed epic.
And you did that.
I know, I did that.
Oh my god, what a relief.
You know, we just,
we have an opportunity
here to really seize a moment.
We should seize the moment.
- Yes.
- This is the show.
It's,
it's a survivor, isn't it?
And I honestly just think it would be,
it would be a mistake
not to capitalize on...
[phone ringing]
Guys, I need to take this call, okay?
Harry, how do I mute this thing?
[Harry] Just turn the volume down.
Yeah, it's on the side.
The button with the bracket.
Just press that, yeah, go down.
Keep pressing.
Okay, all right.
[phone ringing]
Brower.
- No.
- Um, um,
- No, no, not at all.
- Wait, wait.
- I think you forgot to-
- No, I said no.
I don't understand how
you can't understand
a word with two letters.
It's no, he's a fucking prick,
and I will not tolerate this shit anymore.
- Oh, it's Bobbie with an I-E.
- Melanie, what is this?
Is that the?
- No, listen.
- Wait a minute.
- Guys.
- I don't give a fuck.
I'll put $10 million of my
own money into this thing
to crush that fucking guy's spirit.
Do you understand what
- I'm saying?
- No no no no no.
- Oh no no no no no.
- I don't even care-
- No, Bobbie.
- No, stop, no.
- What is this crap?
- Stop, just throw it out.
You're muted, she can't hear you.
What?
Oh, it's from that asshole, okay.
She didn't mean that.
You know what?
This is already more than I've talked
to anyone I've ever fucked,
male or female, okay?
So I'm bored.
I'm bored with you.
I'm bored with this conversation.
All right, just write something up
that I can sign on Monday.
And if I feel like it, I'll fucking do it.
And if not, you can go yourself.
Declan, what the fuck did you do?
- You sent it to Bobbie?
- Really?
No no no no no.
Can you do that for me?
I hope it ruins your fucking weekend.
Goodbye.
So inspiring.
Harry, you can't let her read that.
Please do not let her read that.
Wait, you can hear us?
Yeah.
All right, what the fuck is this?
Oh no, please don't.
I call upon the darkness for
only you can halt the attack.
Oooo [laughing].
I call upon your
forces to take them away.
To take them back [indistinct]
evil from my home to yours
[indistinct]
- We're fucked.
- Days and hours.
Why does every fucking actor
think that they can write poetry?
Oh my god.
Where did he buy this?
From like a crafting hobo?
Oh this is...
Did we just hear that again?
Oh fuck, it's too late.
If it wasn't after us before, it is now.
Oh, we're screwed, we're screwed.
[moaning] All right, fine.
Hey guys, sorry about that.
I just had to take that call.
So hey, there you are.
Hi, I got your gift.
So thoughtful and honestly too expensive.
You really shouldn't have,
you shouldn't have done that.
That was really too much.
[thunder crashing]
[intense music]
[Declan's head banging]
Ooo.
Are you okay?
Is this a viral thing?
[dark intense music]
[Declan's head banging]
Jesus Christ.
Fucking actors, man.
["So It Goes"]
Are you guys rolling?
Is everybody rolling?
Scene 12, shit.
Take.
Scene two, wait, scene two, take three.
Three.
Scene 22, take three,
Declan, motherfucker.
[cast clapping]
I was early.
I just clapped.
I did my thing and I clapped.
We're fucked.
[Katherine laughing]
Guys, this is gonna be really
great on the blooper reel.
[Claire laughing]
[Emmy] No.
Oh shit, Kevin you're
gonna bloody kill me.
It did fall out.
[Luke grunting]
Sorry, lost camera.
Are we supposed to cut?
Sorry.
Fuck.
["So It Goes"]
I'm embarrassed.
I'm actually embarrassed to
be touching this right now.
Smells like urine.
Holy god, look at that stache.
No, no, I, this is, I
dug my own grave here,
and I love it,
but I'm ready to lick my
lip and have it be smooth.
Oh my god, I can't.
[Katherine laughing]
["So It Goes"]
It's real, Kip, it's real.
God, mom, you can't sneak up like that.
[Emmy laughing]
I'm on the phone.
You can't sneak up on me like that.
[Timothy laughing]
Fucking, I'm sweating.
I'm so hot right now.
[Emmy laughing]
["So It Goes"]
Mom, we're gettin' renewed, ha ha.
Shit.
It's like performance...
Yeaaahhh.
That was fucking brilliant.
Are you fucking serious?
More vodka.
["So It Goes"]
That's great.
[indistinct]
Oh my god, guys, I wasn't rolling.
I wasn't rolling.
[group laughing]
Yes, did you build that monologue?
Did you build it?
I'm gonna.
No you did not build the monologue.
Build the fucking monologue, Max.
Are we gonna get an X rating
from all of our fuck yous?
It's a lot of fucks.
["So It Goes"]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
You guys, I don't really
know how to work this.
How do I hang up?