(door creaks)
(tense background music plays)
(man pants)
(door knocks)
(animal growls)
(man screams)
(gunshots)
(animal growls)
(punk music plays)
♪ One nine eight four woo! ♪
Nice door freak show.
How does it feel to be the
least popular girl in school?
(girls laugh)
Hey girls!
Okay. See you later.
They must not have heard me.
Yeah, that's it.
What's up?
My report's today.
Check this out.
It's this.
Whoa. Now that's hardcore.
My great grandfather was an archeologist
and they found that in his office
after some local slaughtered him.
Rad.
It's for my report.
(guys high five and grunt)
Oh, come on! Homecoming
week is totally hardcore.
(bell rings)
(punk music plays)
♪ I don't wanna hear it ♪ ♪
All you do is talk about you ♪
♪ I don't wanna hear it ♪
♪ 'Cause I know that none of it's true ♪
♪ I'm sick and tired of all your lies ♪
♪ I don't wanna hear it ♪
♪ When are you gonna realize ♪
(football impacts)
(students laugh) ♪ I
don't want to hear it ♪
♪ Know you're full of shit ♪
♪ I don't want to hear it ♪
♪ I don't want to hear it ♪ ♪
All you do is talk about you ♪
♪ Oh shut up ♪
(school bell rings)
Dramatizing Euripides play
the Bacchae, women followers
of the cult of Dionysus
would perform grizzly rites
intended to propel the revelers
into a state of frenzy.
And, I, Priestess Penny call
Dionysus to roar there, too,
as it were a thunder
underground born on the air.
Heavy with dread.
(girl clears throat)
Yes.
I don't think it's
appropriate to be subjected
to pornographic cult
rituals in a history class.
Was there a question in there?
(class bell rings)
[Teacher] That's class.
Nice dress, fag.
Do I turn you on?
(ominous music plays)
(gargling) Rand- Randy!
(Randy laughs)
Fuck you, Randy!
You kiss your mom with that mouth?
(ominous sound cues)
Oh, Devon is so loyal and nice.
Hey Devon. Do you wanna go
to the game with me on Friday?
Ha ha ha.
Devon. Are you okay?
No. What is this shit
that I'm covered in?
Hey Devon.
Look, Casey.
I don't know what you and your
friends are trying to pull
but I'm not having a very good day.
So, I'd appreciate if you'd
walk head long into traffic.
Thank you.
What was that?
(car crash sounds)
Blackwood High School's
homecoming nearly started
in tragedy when a car struck
junior, Casey Brownfield,
at the corner of Walker and Fisher.
She just walked right on past me
and walked right into the traffic.
I don't, I don't know why.
Right now we're all just praying
Heavenly Father will pull her through.
She wasn't supposed
to take me literally!
But she did.
What other girls saw
you covered in that goo?
Well, you saw me.
No. I said the words. I
don't count, I'm the priestess.
Well, Judy and Wendy saw me.
Devon is so trustworthy.
It's the cheerleaders.
Devon is way hardcore.
And cute.
And Christie.
(angelic sound cues)
Hi!
Hi.
Gross!
So, what, I can control these girls now?
What should we do?
We test them motherfucker.
(punk music starts)
(girls gasp)
♪ Do you really know just who I am ♪
(Penny and Devon reacting)
♪ I'm the thorn inside your
heel, your master plan ♪
♪ Do you really care what people think ♪
♪ You have ideas
but do you really think ♪
(car horn sounds)
Hey.
Ow.
♪ Do you really know just who I am ♪
♪ I'm the thorn inside your
heel, your master plan ♪
♪ Do you really care ♪ (door knocks) ♪
♪ What people think ♪
Where have you been?
(girls slapping and giggling)
[Wendy] You're a bad girl.
(girls giggling)
♪ Kill joy ♪
(Penny sighs in disgust)
Penny wait.
What's the big deal?
Nothing, Mr. Popularity
Devon, Judy drank all my wine.
I think she needs a spanking.
Go to Hell.
You know Devon, I really
expected more from you.
That's not fair.
Look, I know you get off
on being the least popular girl in school,
but I can't do that.
I need people to like me.
Get in the house! I'm going to get you.
(animal growling)
(Penny gasps)
(intense drum music plays)
Blood orgy?
(school bell rings)
Hi, Christie.
Dude, what's with your truck.
(Christie moaning)
Get your hands off her, fag.
Fight!
(punk music plays)
(students cheering)
(punches land)
(animal growling)
(in demonic voice)
Leave him the fuck alone.
I love Devon now, okay?
You're so dead.
What did you do to Christie?
- I didn't do anything.
That doesn't happen by itself.
Listen, I think I know how to
reverse what I've done to you.
No way, Penny. I feel great.
Fucking fantastic.
Tonight, there's gonna be a blood orgy.
I'm gonna be a king of this school.
Listen to yourself.
This isn't the Devon I know.
The Devon you knew was
pathetic and nobody liked him.
I thought he was hardcore.
(crowd cheering)
[Announcer] At two minutes to the half,
the Broncos are trailing the Tigers by 13.
(cheerleaders cheer)
[Announcer] Number 8,
Randy Dayton, hit hard.
Number 84 Bowen Lopez with the sack.
What the hell is wrong with you, Randy?
Get your head in the game!
[Announcer] And, that's halftime.
Idaho Falls, 16, Blackfoot, three.
(tribal drum music plays)
For your halftime entertainment,
The Blackfoot High School marching band
and your Blackfoot High cheerleaders.
We have a special cheer for you.
Hey, Randy.
(tribal drum music intensifies)
(tigers roaring)
(bones cracking)
(Penny panting)
Call it off, Devon.
Not on your life.
This whole school is gonna pay.
Undo the image of thunder underground.
Undo the-
I said no!
(ceramic shatters)
You better run fast, Randy.
(drum music intensifies)
(animal growls)
(Randy screams)
(ax unsheathes)
(Randy grunts)
(Randy screams)
(animals roar)
(spectator screams)
(crowd screams)
(bones cracking)
(animal roars)
(football player screams)
Yes, get him!
(wind cutting)
You've gone too far!
You're gonna go against me?
Nobody goes against me anymore.
Make them stop now!
Who the hell do you think you are?
(ax pierces)
I'm the least popular girl in school.
(Face Against the Wall by Teen Meanies)