Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[Man] My lord.
My lord.
Why has thou forsaken us?
The crimes of this guilty land
will never be purged
but with blood!
[spiritual vocalizing]
[Man] All rise.
This court is now in session.
The honorable Judge
Ramage presiding.
[eerie tense music]
[woman gasping]
[low eerie whispering]
[Ramage] Continue,
Mr. Newbold.
Prosecutor.
[Newbold] Evidence will show
far beyond a reasonable doubt
that Thomas and Meeks Griffin,
on the night of
September 29th, 1913.
Did enter the home
of John Lewis.
Liar!
[men grunting]
What the fuck?
[woman sobs]
[Newbold] Go on, Mr.
Stevenson, you have the stand.
[Stevenson] Then
they robbed him good.
Took his money, his watch,
even the gun they used.
[eerie tense music]
[Newbold] How are
you aware of this?
[Stevenson] They
tried selling 'em to me.
Evil motherfuckers.
[Newbold] Then they
turned the gun on you,
a small, scared,
defenseless woman.
Isn't that right, Anna?
[woman grunting]
[Anna] Yes.
They.
[Newbold] Ms. Davis?
[Anna] They put in
my mouth while they...
[woman sobs]
[Newbold] While they
violated you repeatedly.
[Anna] Yes.
[crowd grumbling]
They don't see us as men.
Just slaves.
They will put us in chains.
Has your avarice
not been satiated
by your peculiar institution?
You must seen in all this
a state of affairs
dangerously diseased.
Today you weigh her
scales of justice,
tomorrow we draw her sword.
There will be restitution.
[gavel banging]
- Order.
- For we are innocent men!
[Ramage] Order.
- Blood will have blood.
- I said order.
Prosecutor, continue.
[Newbold] When
through with their fun,
they turned their
attention back toward Lewis
who, has only a proud
Confederate veteran could,
had gathered his
sense in an attempt
to defend himself, his
home, and this young woman
here before you.
[gun shot]
[eerie tense music]
And for his valor, they
murdered him in cold blood.
[Anna] Yes.
[crowd grumbling]
[gavel banging]
[Ramage] Please rise.
For your crimes of
robbery, rape, and murder
I hereby sentence you to
death by electrocution.
[eerie tense music]
[mumbling]
Let everybody honor your name.
'Cause you the holy.
The greatest one who
rule over all of me.
With everything you do, lord,
let me be in this world.
Sing like everyday in heaven.
[Ramage] Thomas
and Meeks Griffin,
you have been denied your appeal
by the Governor of our State
and have been condemned to
die in the electric chair.
Sentence passed by
a jury of his peers
and imposed by a judge in
good standing in this state.
God save the people
of South Carolina.
Do you have anything to say
before the sentence
is carried out?
We have told the truth.
[Ramage] Electricity
shall now be passed
through your body
until you are dead
in accordance with
South Carolina law.
May God have mercy
on your souls.
Roll on two.
[electricity crackling]
[men panting]
[men shouting]
[men groaning]
[eerie tense music]
[upbeat country music]
♪ There's a girl round here ♪
♪ With so much fear ♪
♪ Trapped in her
sweet brown eyes ♪
♪ No where for her to go ♪
♪ She can never know ♪
♪ The watch is out of time ♪
♪ She was flat out of luck ♪
♪ And she ended up stuck ♪
♪ In this small town world ♪
♪ She made a vow to break out ♪
♪ Make everyone proud ♪
♪ But it all went wrong ♪
♪ It all went wrong ♪
♪ Oh yeah yeah ♪
♪ Why'd you have
to break my heart ♪
♪ Heard that you were
running 'round town ♪
♪ Yeah I found out ♪
They'll have a
store there, Lyndsy.
Yeah, okay.
I can feel the
humidity already.
Yeah, listen.
They know what air conditioning
is down there, right, Sarah?
And this is September, Jamie.
I can't imagine you and
Chloe in the summer.
Hey it is still
south something.
Carolina.
Blackstock, South Carolina.
In case you need the info
for your Facebook updates.
Whatever, it's still
deep woods country
back ass way.
Hey, you know you two
didn't have to come.
No way.
Yeah, no we are
so here for you.
We're here to support.
Good, because
the closer we get,
the more it weirds me out.
So what is it?
I'm still confused.
So am I.
This guy with a thick
southern accent just calls
and was going on about a
bunch of land and dead people
and way too much money
and it's just weird.
This peach cobbler is
the best I've ever ate.
Now go and down there
and fetch me my rifle
so we can get to church.
Get 'er done.
But it does sound like
you're gonna get paid.
Yeah and you got fired
for like no good reason.
So you need cash, like
Snapchatted to you.
Thanks for the reminder.
I'm shocked but I have to
agree with the Double mints.
I mean, you're so
good, you're so nice
and you get walked
on left and right.
It's about time something
good come your way.
It's like...
Justice prevailing
for one and all.
I was gonna say karma
but I guess that works.
Yeah.
Fantastic.
Let's just get down there first
and make sure it's legit.
Cool?
- Cool.
Cool.
♪ Why'd you ever
break my heart ♪
♪ Heard that you've been
running 'round town ♪
♪ Yeah I found out ♪
Good morning, young ladies.
Thank you, Mr. Newbold.
[rock music]
Hey, Rog.
Rog.
Roger!
Hey, man, how you doing?
Look, I've been meaning
to talk to you, man.
I slipped at some
coffee at Sally's.
She aint got nothing, George.
But, Rog.
Next time, fall at somebody's
place that aint broke,
then we'll talk.
Really?
Really.
Shit.
[knocking at door]
Yeah.
I'm, that's what I'm saying.
Yes.
I'll get back with you.
They're trying to
fuck us on the price
- at the last meet...
- It's on us, CJ.
Yeah, their attorneys dug up
another owner of the land.
What the hell are
you talking about, who?
[phone ringing]
Yeah?
Fine.
She's some young, dumb kid.
How'd you let
that get past you?
If was earning
corporate attorney money,
I'd do better research.
You'll be making more
than them soon enough.
But in the meantime,
do your job.
I contacted her, fed
her enough to get her
to come down here.
She's on her way.
It's all taken care of.
Taken care of?
She's cutting out
a big ass chunk
of my goddamn pie.
[pounding on door]
Yeah, get in here.
About time.
George had said it be
here and by nine am.
It's 10.
I'm sorry, Judge Ramage,
we had another delivery.
One more important than mine?
Shut up and hang it over there.
Who is she?
She's a descendant
of Anna Davis.
[tense music]
You, you dumb shit.
If you damage it, I will
put a boot up your ass.
Do you see that?
I'm sorry, Judge
Ramage, I got distracted...
Don't interrupt me, boy.
Just leave it and
get the hell out.
Call George and have both
your black asses fired.
Now!
Where's a nice sturdy
oak when you need one?
She didn't have a clue as
to what I was talking about.
Anna Davis, huh?
And John Lewis?
Looks like it.
Is she white?
Mhm.
You tell anybody else?
No, I wanted to
tell you first.
Are you sure there's no
way we can cut her out?
No, nothing.
Anna's on that deed
going back to 1913.
This girl is blood.
Her only one left.
Legally that land is hers, too.
Savemart won't buy, unless
it's straight by the book.
Either she gets
on board and signs
or it's nothing.
Then I guess she's
just gonna have to sign.
And if she doesn't?
She will.
She sure will.
[upbeat country music]
So where's your
other half, Ms. Ramage?
Well, you see.
It's been forever
since you paid nothing.
The two of you are
in here most nights.
Are you sure it's
been that long?
Well, I suppose I
could be a bit off.
Don't get any
stupid ideas, Billy.
Now pour me a drink.
Let's go, Corey.
White pride.
World wide.
World wide, motherfucker.
Hey, we having sex
today, beautiful?
I am, Dex.
Not with you.
I don't think so.
Shit head.
What you gonna do, huh,
what are you gonna do?
Come on, come on now, Dex.
Do it, do it.
Do it.
- Back off.
- Throw that punch.
Back off.
Come on, come on.
You don't wanna get
locked up for the weekend.
Come on, come on.
Better listen to your friend.
That's right, sit down.
Bitch.
Sit down.
I'm gonna fuck
that motherfucker up.
[upbeat country music]
[low tense music]
Yo, Dad's looking for you.
For what?
I don't know,
something about the land.
Still waiting on
some out of towners.
Let me guess.
[tense eerie music]
[Lyndsy] We are here.
I actually have no service.
[Woman] Oh, I know
right, this town.
Is this it?
[Woman] I think so.
What, no bars?
God, you've gotta be kidding.
OMG.
No Facebook updates, no Tweets.
How will the world
follow your every move?
So, now what?
Good morning, ladies.
Welcome to Blackstock.
Thank y'all for getting
here as fast you did.
Yeah, listen.
Is there seriously no
cell reception out here?
Yeah, what's up?
Ridiculous.
Hi, I'm Lyndsy.
Oh, very nice to meet you.
I'm the attorney you
spoke to on the phone.
I am sure you are
interested in learning
all about what's going on here.
Yes.
Well, why don't
we go head over
to the other partner's office
and we will fill you in there.
[low tense music]
It's simple.
Savemart is buying
a chunk of land
to build on right
here in Blackstock.
You, the descendant
of Anna Davis,
a woman who bought the
property 100 years ago,
along with two other buyers.
My great granddaddy, for one,
Judge Carol Johnson Ramage,
and Roger's here
great grand pappy,
the DA at the time.
They bought it together?
Yup.
And we all get an equal slice.
Sign on the dotted line
like Roger and I did
and you'll be cutting yourself
a substantial slice of
Southern hospitality.
How am I related
to this woman again?
You'll be doing this
town a real service.
Slow economy leads
to tough times.
Hurts small towns
like Blackstock.
Savemart means jobs.
Lot's of jobs.
This is all
happening very fast.
I understand but, without you,
this opportunity
won't happen for us.
For all of us.
I need to think
about it a little.
Fine.
I'd like to have
an answer tonight.
We're planning on
announcing Savemart's
arrival here in Blackstock.
Wouldn't want to
disappoint the people.
You understand?
Yes.
Good.
We'll have dinner later tonight.
Yeah.
Have a look around
in the meantime.
You'll see we're all good folk.
You let us know what
you decide then.
Thank you.
Oh, and one more thing.
I trust this conversation
will stay in this room.
Wouldn't want to get
the town's hopes up.
You know, in case
anything goes south.
I won't say anything.
Good.
So I don't understand
what you're worried about.
It's just weird.
One minute I'm getting fired,
thinking I can't make rent,
the next, some
random I've never met
is telling me I have a
ton of money coming to me
from some relative
I've never heard of.
That doesn't
mean it's not true.
Davis, that's not
even my last name.
So?
People get married,
names change.
And it's not like it's
some mom and pop shop.
Savemart is a huge company.
They're not gonna get involved
in some illegitimate
business deal.
That's not it.
[Sarah] What's your
hesitation, then?
It's just happening so fast.
That wouldn't make
you a little nervous?
A little.
Not enough to say no.
Did I say I was
going to say no?
You haven't said yes.
[eerie tense music]
Are you a relation
of Anna Davis, dear?
I guess so.
Oh.
You're lighter than I'd expect.
Must be from John Lewis
and good breeding down the line.
Who?
What brings you to town?
Just some land I inherited.
Who's John Lewis?
Was that the old Griffin Farm?
Have they finally decided
what they're gonna do with it?
The Griffin Farm?
I don't know.
Well, good for you.
I'm sure you deserve it.
Just like Anna
deserved ever acre
of land she received
for her part.
Her part in what?
You mean you don't
know about Anna Davis?
They haven't told you
about her and John?
Well, they're your blood, honey.
A person should
know their roots.
John had been a proud
confederate soldier
who fought with
Hatch's coast rangers.
After he came home from the war,
he and Anna were
having a love affair.
One night, the Griffin brothers
broke into John's house
Anna was there.
Well, John tried to defend
himself and save Anna
but they were too big,
too young, too strong.
Shot the brave old
man with his own gun.
What about Anna?
Well, those two murderers
beat Anna and left her to die.
But she didn't.
Without any hard
evidence, everyone knew
they were gonna go free.
So Anna had to testify.
Well, she got up there
and told her story
and got those two murderers
sent to the electric chair.
That's why she got
that piece of land.
Biggest trial and victory
Blackstock's ever seen.
Everyone here knows the story.
So, she got a piece of the
Griffin Farm for testifying?
[eerie tense music]
138 acres divided
equally between Anna,
the Judge, and the
District Attorney.
Been in their families
for generations.
Oh and those men, they
died because of her?
Oh don't worry about
that dear, not one bit.
Them two niggers deserved a
fright for what they done.
[eerie tense music]
[Woman] Did you
just hear that?
[Woman] Oh my Gosh.
[shushing]
They already don't
like outsiders.
Last thing we need
is for them to know
we voted against segregation.
Then they'll really
want to kill us.
Yeah.
You vote?
It's like blood money, now.
Wait, what?
Well you heard
everything she said.
Plus Anna got the land for
putting those guys in the chair.
Forget for a second
that crazy old coot
and what those guys, did.
Don't look at this like
you're inheriting guilt.
You have nothing to atone for.
Take this for what
it is, a blessing.
Guys, can we just
get out of here.
I think I heard I
just heard a banjo.
You should listen
to your friend.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Judge sent us.
We're here to make sure
you get to him tonight.
I think we could find it.
Judge wants to make sure.
Let's go.
[eerie tense music]
There you go.
They don't want us.
[doorbell ringing]
Lyndsy.
Thanks for coming so late.
You remember Roger.
Hi.
Oh, none for me, thank you.
[eerie tense music]
Man, this is some
fucking bullshit.
We didn't even do nothing.
And George.
His bitch ass didn't stand
up for us for a second, bruh.
Are you surprised?
Like he's always trying
to screw somebody
out of their hard earned money.
Yes, I'm surprised.
Second of all, like
I'm telling you.
We need to call somebody
and we need to do something.
What are we gonna do, Bennie?
Sue the town judge?
This motherfucking
town is cursed.
Fuck.
Look, we'll find
new jobs tomorrow.
Look, there's a few
stores looking for people.
Seriously, we'll be cool.
You got a couple
dollars saved up, man?
I'm okay for a few weeks.
What about you?
Yeah, I'm good.
See you tomorrow, man.
Hey, keep your chin up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And that was it.
Son of a bitch got up
and took off running
with an arrow in him and
three 30 calibers in his ass.
Poof, gone, without a trace.
We go out there,
what a week later,
and there we was.
Laid up dead by the fear.
Now he's mounted on my wall.
Sure is getting awfully late.
Another round.
Oh none for me, no thanks.
Oh come on now.
[eerie tense music]
So, tell me, Lyndsy.
Have you made up your
mind on the land?
Will you join us?
I'm gonna be straight
with you, sweetheart.
Opportunities of a
lifetime like this
don't come along very often.
You were lucky enough
to have an ancestor
who had the good conscious
to do the right thing.
And was rewarded for it.
Now, 100 years later,
you have a similar choice.
You have your whole
life ahead of you.
Think of what you can
do with all that money.
Think of our town.
Like this here, is
a win win situation
for all of us.
But I just met you.
You're doing business now
with the third generation judge
and an attorney.
What can possibly go wrong.
[eerie tense music]
[electricity crackling]
Cheers.
[eerie tense music]
[storm raging]
[rock music]
What, what?
Where you headed?
White mans asking
you a question, boy.
You better answer him.
Yeah better answer.
[grunting]
[laughing]
[siren chirping]
[man coughing]
Hey, boys.
Dex, Rhett.
What you up to, boys?
Oh nothing much,
Sheriff Brice.
You sure about that now?
There aint gonna be any problems
in town tonight, are there?
Nothing much.
No, sir.
You boys have a nice night.
You, too.
[man coughing]
[rock music]
Now how about that lift.
[coughing]
[grunting]
We're gonna go for a ride.
[energetic rock music]
[man grunting and coughing]
Now come on.
Get him back there.
Hey, hey, hey.
[man coughing]
Blackstock folk used
to use this beauty
to string you boys
up all the time.
Good folk.
Good Klan folk.
Grab him, Bear.
[eerie tense music]
[groaning]
No, please, please.
No, no.
[eerie tense music]
[Dex] Come on, Bear.
Pull 'em up, Bear.
No.
Get 'em up.
Pull 'em up.
Yeah, pull 'em up.
There you go, Bear.
Keep him up there,
let him swing.
Up again.
Leave him up there this time.
Tie it up.
[eerie tense music]
Oh, what the fuck?
Shoot him.
[gunshot]
[gasping]
[eerie tense music]
[whip snapping]
No, no!
[man screaming]
Don't worry about it.
[group laughing]
That was so good.
Yeah, amazing.
Okay, but I cannot believe
that you two ate that.
Everything was deep friend.
And slathered in butter.
I need that sunscreen.
You're actually
gonna go back in there?
Speak of the devil.
Do you see another option?
[eerie tense music]
[soft muzak]
Hey, excuse me,
do you work here?
Uh, no.
I wish I did, though.
Hopefully.
I had a job until yesterday.
Oh no.
I know how you feel though.
I'm Jesse.
Lyndsy.
Lyndsy, I found it.
Huh?
Yeah, what SPF are you?
Just one second.
Okay, he is so cute.
Yeah, he is.
I thought you said
you found the sunscreen.
Yeah no, what
made you think that?
Can you please find
me the sunscreen?
SPF 30, dry touch sunblock.
Wait, wait, wait.
What do you think?
Is he cute?
Yes.
[eerie tense music]
Fuck it.
[laughing]
You go on and try it.
Oh my God, what is this?
You've never had a
chocolate ball before?
Chocolate turtle with
pecans, caramel, chocolate.
Look, it's made right here.
I'm not interrupting, am I?
Uh uh.
Here's your sunscreen.
You want the one
with the coco butters.
Better for the
skin, moisturizes.
So I'm told.
[eerie tense music]
[indistinct dispatch chatter]
[Dispatch] Wait, 18 roger.
[eerie tense music]
If you've come to tell
us them boys did some harm,
all I can say is we
didn't see nothing.
Y'all looked happy as a couple
of pigs in the slop to us.
Look, I'm just here to
tell you they're dead.
What are you
talking about, boy?
Did you kill 'em?
No, no someone,
something did it.
I don't know what it was.
You better get yourself
and your story straight,
right quick.
It was like the devil.
Say again?
[Deputy laughing]
It was huge and
it had a pitchfork.
Was it red?
What about a tail?
No, no, no.
It was a man but in all black.
[Both] Kinda like you then.
Look, it just threw
'em like paper dolls.
It tore 'em to pieces
and after it tore 'em to pieces,
their asses were gone.
[laughing]
Look, screw you.
Screw you.
I'm out.
And I'm telling everybody.
Where do you, where do
you think you're going?
We can't have you running
around town causing trouble.
Especially if you're
our prime suspect
if those boys are hurt.
You aint going nowhere, boy.
Fuck.
Are you sure
they're gonna be fine?
What your friends?
They'll be fine.
What's gonna happen to them?
So, why'd you say
you know how I feel?
What?
Earlier when I
said I'd been fired
you said you knew how I felt.
Oh, I was, too.
Just before coming here.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
My manager was a jerk.
He was always coming on to me.
He would say all
kinds of things to me.
I just ignored him
but he wouldn't stop.
Finally, when I told
him I wasn't interested,
he was really mean to me.
Then one morning I walk in
and there he is waiting for me
and says you no longer work here
and he hands me a box
with all my stuff in it.
That's messed up.
Yeah, so.
It's for the best.
I wasn't appreciated, anyways.
What about you then?
I dropped a stuffed animal.
[laughing]
No, seriously.
My friend, Bennie, and I
we've known each other
since we were born.
We were like brothers.
We're all the others got.
My families been in Blackstock
since Andrew Jackson
was president.
And we worked for
a delivery company
and we were on a
run to a guys office
and I guess he got some bad news
because he tore into us.
He's a powerful
guy in Blackstock.
Like real powerful.
He had us fired before
our next delivery.
That's terrible.
It's for the best.
I wasn't appreciated there.
[laughing]
[soft country music]
Come on, I wanna
show you something.
Cool?
All right.
Ah, it's so beautiful here.
So peaceful.
So different then
from where I'm from.
What brings you to
these parts, anyway?
A relative passed.
I had to come down here and
take care of some legal stuff.
I'm sorry.
Were you close?
No, we never met.
Well you know, there's
a cemetery near here.
Some of my family
is buried there
and I go there
sometimes to think,
clear my head.
Cemetery?
Yup.
You just gotta stay
away from the boo hags.
The boo whats?
Guess you don't have
those where you're from.
No, what are they?
Spirits kinda like vampires.
Except they feed off your
breath, not your blood.
Yeah, they have no
skin so they're all red
but then, they look for people,
wear they skin
and they rock 'em.
They're South Carolina legend.
Gross.
Yeah.
They're supposed to hang around
like old slave cemeteries
and displaced burial sites.
You see, much of Blackstock
is built on used land.
Some of which was colonial
era slave cemeteries.
Yeah.
I sure could have used a
place to think yesterday.
So have you figured it out?
I think so.
That's good.
[eerie tense music]
Heading out for a smoke.
You know them things
are gonna kill ya.
Later rather than sooner.
So to ease her pain,
he keeps putting
a shot of whiskey,
every day a little bit more,
a little bit more into her milk
and on her death
bed, the last day,
she says, Son, whatever you do,
don't sell that cow.
[both laughing]
Get a room, you two.
Samantha.
She's here.
Oh.
Remember, business
first, pleasure later.
[eerie tense music]
How long till later?
[Newbold] Oh, here she is.
[Lyndsy] Wanna hang
out tomorrow, maybe?
[Jesse] Yeah.
Lyndsy, they were
wondering where you were.
They're ready for you.
Excuse us.
Hey, I'll be right
back, you guys.
[Samantha] Corey.
Cheers.
What I tell you?
Alrighty then.
I assume we all
have a clear head
and are still on board here.
We agree this is a
very generous offer
for that land, isn't that right?
Yes.
Good.
Let's get it signed and
head over to the courthouse
there's a fax in
the clerk's office.
Why don't we just
scan it and email it?
I want in their
hands, damn it.
Let's go.
Everybody head over
to the courthouse.
Samantha.
[eerie heavy breathing]
Yes, daddy?
You make sure she gets there.
[Samantha] Where you going?
Office.
I need to grab a few things.
Look what I found.
You ready?
Yeah.
Great.
[eerie heavy breathing]
Hey, I just have to
go to the courthouse
and sign something.
And then we can leave?
Yup.
Hey, you wanna walk
us over there, Jesse?
Fine.
Uh, Jesse.
Everything okay?
Yup, we're cool.
What's wrong, are you mad?
Hey, will you tell
me what's going on?
Look, what's the name of
your relative that died?
Anna Davis.
So you just left
out a few details
like who you're
related to and the fact
that she died 75 years ago?
Hey, two days ago I didn't
even know she existed.
And your inheritance.
He told me not
to say anything.
Who told you not to
say anything, was it CJ?
So I'm sure you
heard the whole story
behind the Griffin Farm, right?
I heard a few things,
I don't know if it
was the whole story.
Ah, just the
important parts, then?
You actually believe
everything you hear?
I don't know why they
would lie to me about it.
So, you going through with it?
You're actually gonna
go into business with CJ
and sell the land?
I don't see why not.
Why not?
Because CJ is a liar and a cheat
and over all just a sad
excuse for a human being
and that's just one reason.
Look, I got called
down here out of nowhere
and this whole deal was
just thrown in my lap.
I don't know these
people hardly at all.
I don't know who they
are and what they do
and I sure as hell
don't know why
you're acting like
this right now.
Someone basically handed
me a winning lotto ticket
and I'm cashing in.
Just like that?
Just like that.
All right then.
You and your girlfriends
have a safe trip home.
I knew we should
have never let you out
of our sight tonight.
What just happened?
He's a Griffin, sweetheart.
Somewhere way down
the line his great,
whatever, uncles seriously
fucked up your family.
Griffin?
Two guys a long
time ago killed a man
and then raped the
woman he was with.
John Lewis.
But what does that
have to do with me
and why would that make him mad?
Wouldn't it be the
other way around?
They've all been
crazy as shit since.
It's all in the blood.
Come on, let's go cash in
that winning lotto ticket.
But...
[eerie tense music]
[eerie heavy breathing]
What are we gonna do with
that piece of shit in there?
We gonna charge him
or cut him loose?
Something.
You know that boy Jesse's gonna
be coming looking for him.
You know, that was a
great uncle of mine
that pulled the switch
on them two brothers.
Is that right?
Yup.
He always said it
took four tries
to get one of 'em down.
He had to crank that
needle up to 2,500 volts.
Enough to put a horse down.
[both laughing]
Damn, Sheriff.
That's something to be
proud of right there.
Did this town a service.
It is indeed.
I oughta have a
bumper sticker made.
[both laughing]
[eerie tense music]
From what I heard,
them two niggers had
to sell their land to
pay for their defense.
How much land did they own?
138 acres and
would you believe
it only bought 'em
two days in court?
[both laughing]
[eerie tense music]
What the fuck?
[bones cracking]
[eerie tense music]
No, no.
No!
[eerie tense music]
Hey, CJ, can I talk to you?
Busy at the moment, Billy.
It will only take a minute.
What's up?
[eerie tense music]
Bennie, please don't
be out here, man.
[eerie tense music]
I'm telling you, CJ.
It was brutal.
Blood, guts, shit
just everywhere.
Have you told
anyone else about it?
No one.
I was just finishing
up my hunt down
near the cemetery and I saw 'em.
I came straight over here.
Good.
I want you to go on home.
Look after your family.
You don't tell
anybody about this.
I'll take care of it from here.
Understood?
Billy.
Yeah?
Not one word.
No one.
We'll get who did this
and they'll get
what's coming to 'em.
You understand me?
I understand.
[eerie tense music]
[indistinct conversation]
That does it.
All of our John
Hancocks on the page.
Congratulations.
We all just got rich.
[laughing]
Very rich.
All right, go
throw it in the fax
and Roger, get it right back.
[eerie tense music]
All right, let's get torn up.
That's what I'm talking about.
[Corey] What you
guys wanna drink?
Shit, he better
remember to make copies.
Hey, is someone there?
You ready do you
wanna go celebrate?
Hello?
Spacing out on us over there?
[eerie tense music]
Did you see it?
See what?
[eerie tense music]
[Newbold chuckling]
Yeah.
[eerie tense music]
Ew, what the?
Oh my God!
[woman screaming]
Nobody touch him.
Get back.
[Corey] Is it dead?
Back up.
What is that thing?
[eerie tense music]
[CJ] Run!
[people screaming]
Come on.
Ow.
[eerie tense music]
[Woman] Oh no.
Which way did we come in?
I don't know.
Everything looks the same.
[eerie tense music]
No.
Come on, come on.
Fuck.
Guys, what the hell was that?
Whatever it was,
it tried to kill us.
I don't know.
We shouldn't of
come down here.
[eerie tense music]
Guys, hide.
Hide.
[eerie tense music]
[Newbold gurgling]
[CJ gagging]
[tense music]
[woman whimpering]
Jamie.
We gotta find our
way out of here.
Jamie, no.
[eerie tense music]
No.
Jamie, no!
[woman screaming]
[sobbing]
Okay come on, we need to go.
No, I can't.
It's okay.
It's okay, come on.
[eerie tense music]
Where are we going?
Out the way we came in.
There, let's go.
What the fuck?
- Why aren't they moving?
- Come on!
Open up!
Damn it!
What, seriously?
Damn it.
These are always open.
Why aren't they opening?
Did you try unlocking it?
Great, now what are we gonna do?
This is our only way out.
What?
I said this is
our only way out.
These should be open.
[eerie tense music]
Oh my, go go.
[tense music]
Oh god.
Are you kidding?
Fuck.
How the fuck are we
gonna get out of here?
I don't know.
[eerie tense music]
Do something.
I'm trying.
You have a fucking gun.
Come on, damn it.
- Guys, over here.
- Are you seriously?
Come on, go, go, go, go.
Get over there.
Damn it.
Of course.
[woman shouting]
Great, now we're
stuck in here.
Shut up.
[woman screaming]
[eerie tense music]
Help us.
Open the door.
[screaming]
God damn it.
Is it even loaded?
Yes, it's loaded.
Damn it.
[gunshot]
[ethereal tense music]
[heart beating]
Now shoot him!
[Corey grunting]
[eerie tense music]
[Sarah gasping]
[ethereal heavy breathing]
[sobbing]
Help us.
Open the door.
[woman sobbing]
[woman screaming]
Open the door.
Chloe, we need to keep running.
I can't, I can't.
Chloe, I need you
to calm down, okay?
I can't leave Jamie.
- Chloe.
- I can't leave her.
[eerie tense music]
Come on, Chloe.
Jamie is dead.
You want to die, too.
Now come on.
[Lyndsy shouting]
[Lyndsy groaning]
Chloe!
[grunting]
No!
[shouting]
[low tense music]
[both panting]
Find something.
[Corey] Hurry up.
I'm trying.
Trying.
[eerie tense music]
Sam.
Sam!
He's here.
- I'm trying.
- Sam.
- Sam, he's here.
- I'm trying, I'm trying.
Sam, he's here.
Sam, hurry up.
Do something.
Sam!
[Corey groaning]
I'm trying.
[tense dramatic music]
[ethereal screaming]
Fuck you!
No, get off of me.
Please, no.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
No, please stop!
[Samantha screaming]
[Lyndsy groaning]
Sarah.
[Lyndsy sobbing]
Sarah, wake up.
[sobbing]
Sarah.
[somber reflective music]
Please wake up.
[sobbing]
Please.
[somber reflective music]
[eerie tense music]
John Lewis?
[Old Woman] They're
your blood, honey.
A person should
know their roots.
What the fuck?
[Old Woman] One night,
the Griffin brothers
broke into John's
house, Anna was there.
Shot the brave old
man with his own gun.
Anna had to testify.
[gunshot]
That's why she got
that piece of land.
138 acres divided
equally between Anna,
the judge, and the
district attorney.
Been in their families
for generations.
[chain rattling]
[eerie tense music]
[gunshot]
[triumphant classical music]
Now come on.
[Lyndsy grunting]
No.
[bones cracking]
[Samantha coughing]
[eerie tense music]
[Lyndsy groaning]
Jesse, you came back for me?
I knew you were in trouble.
How?
Those two chasing you,
their names are Thomas
and Meeks Griffin,
they're my great uncles.
Wait, there are two of them?
That means they're
still out there.
Now they're back from
the grave, pissed off,
and coming after you.
I guess the boo
hags exist after all.
But what did I do?
You're the last link
of the conspiracy.
What conspiracy?
I thought they killed someone.
They didn't kill John Lewis.
Look, the murder, the
trial, it was all a set up.
Anna Davis testimony was a lie.
Her story put them
in an electric chair.
For some money and a watch?
No for their land.
Look, my uncles were
prominent and wealthy farmers.
They had 138 acres.
That's more property and money
than anyone in
Blackstock back then.
Dangerous territory if
you were black in 1913.
But what about the trial?
That was all bullshit.
Look, they were framed
and wrongfully executed
so the people involved
could get their land.
Thomas and Meeks sold all of
it to pay for their defense.
Look, all of you
owners have direct ties
with the conspiracy.
CJ's great grandfather
was the judge
who plotted the whole thing
and Roger's related
to the prosecutor
who sent them to the chair.
And me?
[eerie tense music]
[gunshot]
You're the one with
the blood all on you.
This is his gun.
She shot him with this gun.
- It's been in...
- CJ's office.
I never realized it.
Look, we need to
get out of here.
They're coming after everybody
that was involved in any way.
This is all happening
because of my family,
because of me.
I signed that contract.
Look, CJ would of
found some other way
to profit off the land.
Without me, all these
people might still be alive.
You can't think
about that right now.
'Cause there's nothing you
can do to take it back.
Right now, we need
to get out of here.
You're wrong.
There is something I can do.
I can make it right.
I can take my name
off that contract.
Where is it?
Roger went to fax it.
Where?
The clerk's office.
Do you know where it is?
Yes.
Take me there.
[Lyndsy groaning]
[eerie tense music]
No one deserves that.
You reap what you sow.
Now come on, let's
find the contract.
[Lyndsy] Here.
You got it?
[Lyndsy groaning]
It's just a page.
They were here, too.
CJ.
[CJ panting]
[CJ screaming]
[eerie tense music]
[CJ groaning]
Go.
What are you doing?
Go!
[eerie tense music]
[Lyndsy groaning]
Come on, where is it?
I know it's on you,
I know it's on you somewhere.
Nothing gonna keep you away
from that kind of money.
Here we go.
You little prick!
[eerie tense music]
[Lyndsy groaning]
[chains clanking]
[ethereal screaming]
[Lyndsy groaning]
[eerie tense music]
Lyndsy, I got it.
Give me a pen.
[eerie tense music]
Oh here we go.
[gunshot]
Jesse, no!
Three Griffins killed
on the same bench.
[Lyndsy grunting]
[CJ shouting]
That's my money.
I object.
[gunshot]
[Lyndsy whimpering]
Jesse.
Jesse, wake up.
Jesse, Jesse.
Please wake up.
Jesse come on, wake up.
Jesse.
[Lyndsy sobbing]
[soft hip hop music]
♪ It's nothing ♪
♪ It's really nothing ♪
♪ I'm about to wear
this track out. ♪
What a beautiful day.
♪ Jeans you will never
see me slacking ♪
♪ Fresh to death like I
stepped out the casket ♪
♪ Somebody please just
show me where the cash is ♪
♪ You gonna make it look easy ♪
♪ Throw it up ♪
How you doing today?
Good morning, Deputy.
How you doing, man?
Good and you?
Excellent.
Yeah.
Hey, good morning, Bennie.
Deputy.
Excuse me, deputy.
You get that money back
to Sally like I told you?
Sure did, man.
Deputy.
All right, let
me hear different.
[chuckling]
[soft reflective music]
[upbeat country music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ Black as night ♪
♪ White as snow ♪
♪ Left to right ♪
♪ I don't now which way to go ♪
♪ The road is long ♪
♪ And the day is short ♪
♪ Though I'm heading back ♪
♪ To what I forgot ♪
♪ Who's gonna save me ♪
♪ Who's gonna save ♪
♪ Yeah who's gonna
save me from myself ♪
♪ He walks away ♪
♪ You got my faith ♪
♪ He took my name ♪
♪ And you took me to my grave ♪
♪ You lied to me ♪
♪ Told me never happy again ♪
♪ When you did ♪
♪ You know I said ♪
♪ Who's gonna save me ♪
♪ Yeah who's gonna
save me from myself ♪
♪ Who's gonna save me ♪
♪ Who's gonna save
me from myself ♪
♪ Some call it voodoo ♪
♪ Others call it love ♪
♪ Some say it's a curse ♪
♪ Some say it's
heaven down above ♪
♪ Who's gonna save me ♪
♪ Who's gonna save
me from myself ♪
♪ Who's gonna save me ♪
♪ Who's gonna save
me from myself ♪
[upbeat country rock music]
♪ Some call it voodoo ♪
♪ Others call it... ♪