[narrator] in the 25 year
history of the sport,
Excellence at battlebots h
been measured in hardware.
[commentator] world champions!
[narrator] tonight, the ques
for a brand new trophy
Culminates in an epic
winner take all tournament.
Featuring eight
of the deadliest robots
Ever assembled.
With a fanatical crowd
packing the house
On this special night
in las vegas.
[commentator] are you
guys ready?
[narrator] who will
become the first team
To hoist the golden bolt?
This is battlebots champio.
[automated voice speaking]
robots activate.
[crowd cheering]
Whoo! Wow!
Love it!
Hey, everybody and welcome
to battlebots champions.
This is the big one.
It's the golden bolt
championship tournament!
[crowd cheering]
I am chris rose,
I'm joined as always
By ufc legend and the goat
Of robot combat
color commentary,
The one and only, kenny florian.
[crowd cheering]
Thank, chris. I love the
energy in here tonight.
Are you guys ready for this?
[crowd cheering]
[chris] six weeks ago,
we kicked off
Battlebots champions with
the first sin city slugfest
Since then, 45 bots
have gone to battle
In hopes of claiming
a spot here tonight.
Oh, it's all over!
After five qualifying
tournaments of
Weapon trashing, glass smashing,
Hope eroding,
face exploding action.
Eight battle tested champion
will put it all on the line
To reach the top
of the mountain.
That's right, chris.
We have the most
Deadly tournament
lineup imaginable.
Three giant nut winners,
Tombstone, endgame,
And 2021 world champion, tantrum
Have been joined by the fiv
sin city slugfest champions
For the most elite
field ever assembled.
Short of taking home
the giant nut
A flawless run here
Provides the ultimate
bragging rights.
And that's why all eyes tonight
Are fixated on the
newest trophy in this sport.
[both] the golden bolt!
[crowd cheering]
All right. I don't know
about you kenny,
But I'm ready to
get this thing started.
Let's take a look at
the murderers' row
That will be competing tonight.
After being disqualified
from last year's
World championship tournamen
due to technical issues,
Glitch has a shot at redemption
Against its original
round of 32 opponent,
Two-time giant nut
runner-up, witch doctor.
[kenny] we'll see former world
champ, ray billings and tombstone
Take on the current
world champs,
Ginger schmidt, alex
grant and tantrum.
[chris] and the bot with
arguably the most momentum
Heading into this
championship tournament,
Fan-favorite, hypershock
As an opening matchup
with mister and missus plow
Zachary lytle, diana
tarlso and skorpios.
But up first, the former
champs from new zealand.
Nick mabey and jack barker
are running a ponzi scheme
As end game plans its attac
On david jin and
the mighty frog,
Ribbot.
[crowd cheering]
[kenny] after their
giant nut win 2020,
This team had visions
of becoming a dynasty.
But those dreams were bulldozed
By daniel freitas and minota
In last year's world
championship tournament.
Now, they're refocused
and bolstered by the knowled
That they have knocked out five
of the seven robots in this field.
End game is a shark and
the smell blood in the water.
[chris] well, I hope they
have a taste for cold blood
Because that's all
you can squeeze out
Of the amphibious phenom ribbot.
David jin was ruthless
in his slugfest qualifier.
Literally flattening the
gatekeeper lockjaw.
We'll see if the frog can
ta a bite out of end game.
Or if the kiwi killers will
grab it by the tongue.
[crowd cheering]
It's gonna be a brutal night
in all the best ways possible.
- Are you ready my friend?
- Chris, let's do this.
Are you guys ready?
[crowd cheering]
I thought so.
Faruq, take it away.
[faruq] ladies and gentlemen!
Are you ready?
It's robot fighting time!
[crowd cheering]
[faruq] in the red square,
From worcester, massachusetts,
There's some blood
on the hands of the frog
On the log in the hole
in the bottom of the sea,
It's ribbot!
[crowd cheering]
- [chris] david jin.
- [kenny] oh, look at the shades on ribbot!
[chris] yeah, kenny,
somebody's enjoying vegas.
[kenny] yeah, the frog
wore those same shades
When it knocked out
end game back in 2019
To grab its first career win
The team used its vertical
weapon for that fight.
They've been secretive abou what attachment
they're gonn choose for this rematch.
You can see they're
going with the undercutter.
David jin playing
some mind games here.
I like it.
[faruq] in the blue square,
From auckland, new zealand,
These kiwis are ready to bring
you the fight of the conchords
It's end game.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] here comes the
pride of new zealand,
2020 winners of the giant nu
Nick mabey and jack
barker, team end game.
Future's so bright, they
got wear shades, kenny.
[kenny] right. As a former
champion, end game is in
Automatic qualifier tonight
But after an early exit
in last year's tournament,
They're coming in with
a chip on their shoulder
And on a mission
to remind the world
That this robot is one
of the heaviest hitters
In the history of the sport
[crowd cheering]
Back in 2019, our rookie season,
We actually had our first ever
battlebots win against end game.
So, this is kinda
full circle for us.
The team is definitely ready to
have three fights in a single day.
However, the tournament
is kind of insane
Because all the bots in the
tournament are so destructive.
Tombstone, hypershock,
the bots all hit so hard.
The bots, all have the
ability to fully retire our robot.
Luckily, we did
bring a lot of spare,
So hopefully we'll be ready for
each match that we have to fight.
But it's a big deal.
So, we're playing ribbot
in our first fight today.
And they're modular
robots, they could be running
A horizontal spinner
or a vertical spinner.
We know what we want 'em to play
And we have kind of a back
up plan for if we're not sure.
It's really important for
us to win this golden bolt.
I think we've got the best
robot in the world right now,
So we want the
opportunity to show it.
[crowd cheering]
[automated voice
speaking] robots activate.
[crowd cheering]
[chris and kenny exclaim]
[chris] end game just
knocke their own forks off.
Are they the ones
playing mind games here?
Talk to us, pete.
[pete] yeah, ribbot was
keeping them on their toes
In the pits in terms of whic
weapon they were going to us
Jack and nick were hoping
they'd run the vertical.
Those forks were intended
to counter that configuratio
Ribbot choosing to go
with an undercutter here,
So end game says,
"hey, no problem.
We'll just go to plan b and
shed the forks." amazing
[chris] that of course was
the third member of our team
The bot whisperer,
pete abrahamson.
And like he always says,
"pays to have a plan b."
[crowd cheering]
[chris] it's gonna take thre
consecutive wins tonight
To take home the golden bolt
Do either of these two team
have the juice to get it don
The war of attrition starts now.
[crowd] fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight!
[chris] let the
bot battle begin.
Ribbot coming to end
game from an angle.
[all exclaiming]
The glasses and head
have been dismantled,
But what about
the rest for ribbot.
[kenny] ribbot is
inverted right now,
Taking big shots from end game.
[chris] the 2020 world
champion's here and it looks angry.
- [kenny] yeah.
- [chris laughs]
Oh, my god! Tapping that fro
Oh, man!
End game is
smashing and crashing
And perhaps dashing the
hope of ribbot here tonight.
[kenny] yeah, ribbot alread
having issues and of course
End game attacking
the tires now.
[chris] another big shot. Wo
End game, I wonder when they're
gonna pull back and here it is.
Because once again, they're
just not looking to win one fight,
They're looking to
win three tonight.
And here is number one.
- The countdown is on.
- [referee] five.
- Four, three.
- [chris] ribbot is doa.
And end game is moving
on to the semi-finals.
[buzzer sounds]
[chris] wow!
Well, tough day at the
offic when your head lands
Five feet from your
body after a collision.
[kenny] yeah, end game
just kinda stalked them,
Like a great white shark,
just bit down right on ribbot,
Sent him flying, you see
th weapon belt came off of
That undercutter of
ribbot immediately.
David jin, perhaps
regretting that
Configuration choice
right about now.
[chris] well, we now,
few drivers are more
Aggressive when they smell
weakness than jack barker.
Got the frog in
the short corner.
That was it.
Time to back up. Give
'em one more shot.
And end game's
moving on to the semis.
All right.
Nick mabey, jack
barker, congratulations.
- Wow!
- Thank you, thank you.
Got another one of these.
Hey, jack.
Were you a little ticked
off that ribbot came out
With the shades on their frog
And they were trying to
get under your skin a bit?
Well, last time they
came out with the shades,
They absolutely
kicked our butts.
So, we just needed to
make sure that, you know,
We keep the shades
And just smash them
up even after the fight.
Yeah, that fight went pretty
differently from last time.
You guys came out with
those forks and then you didn't.
Talk about that a little bit.
So, like, we know
what they can do.
They can either be
a vert or a horizontal,
So we went for the wedges.
But if they were
gonna go for the vert,
We put on a little contingency.
And, you know, we saw that
they were running the horizontal,
So we don't need those
anymore, we'll get rid of them.
And just gonna give them away
and they're gonna count for damage,
So we'll smash 'em up
before the fight starts.
[kenny] had fun watching
you play chess out there.
All right guys, congratulations.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
[jin] nick! Nick!
One to one.
- One to one?
- One to one.
[chris] so, the former
champ end game
Move on to the second
round in convincing fashion
Where they will
await the winner of
Tombstone versus
tantrum later tonight.
And kenny, we
have to say goodbye
To david jin and team ribbot
They have a come an awfully
long way the past few years
But end game was just
too much for them tonight.
[kenny] yeah, no doubt
we'll see this squad back
With an even stronger ribbo
In the 2022 world championship.
Where they will
considered a top ten team
Straight out of the gate.
[chris] all right, coming up
Can the consummate
showman, will bales
Keep his kill streak alive
Or will skorpios pump the brakes
On hypershock's
remarkable tournament run?
The fight for the
golden bolt continues,
Next.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] welcome back
to battlebots champions
Where tonight a murderer's
r of the best combat robots
Anywhere in the
world are competing
For a brand new piece
of battlebots hardware,
The golden bolt.
Up next, we got
skorpios and hypershock.
And let's start with
will bales' squad.
Hypershock was out of this world
In its slugfest qualifiers,
Tearing through the bracket
And decimating the
gatekeeper, gigabyte.
Oh, are you kidding?
[exclaims]
[kenny] yeah, the amount
of destruction it caused
That night was
absolutely insane.
Everything is clicking
for hypershock right now.
And in a very short
time, it's gone from
One of the most entertainin
bots in the competition
To one of the deadliest.
But it's a tough
draw for 'em tonight
Because in their two
matchups with skorpios,
They have dropped both of them.
[kenny] yes, zach
lytle's robot was built
For a format like this.
Remember, it won four
fight in a single night
At last year's
bounty hunters event.
Skorpios is as
durable as they come
And it was designed to defen
against high energy weapons
Like hypershock's.
It's gonna be a fun one.
Faruq, take it away!
[faruq] in the red square,
From crockett, california,
Make way for the king of sting,
It's skorpios!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] there's skorpios,
one of only two gatekeepers
To make it out of their sin
city slugfest qualifiers alive.
The other being witch doctor
Kenny, zach lytle
and diana tarlson
Don't back down from anyone
Can they stop the
red hot hypershock?
[kenny] well, like everyone
else, they were blown away
By what will bales
did in his qualifier.
But skorpios has beaten
hypershock twice before,
So don't expect
them to be intimidated.
[chris] they've welded a series
of ridges to the front of their bot
Prepared for this r-rating
version of hypershock.
They're ready.
In the blue square,
from miami, florida,
The bot from the 305
That fights like he's
possessed by the 666.
It's hypershock!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] the always
entertaining, will bales.
Oh, look at this.
They have stepped up their game.
We are in vegas.
I see you, girl!
[kenny] amazing.
[chris] the robot's
looking tip-top as well.
[kenny] yes, it is.
With virtually no
damage in its qualifiers,
But the team tore it down
And inspected every
nut and bolt regardless.
While winning the
world championship
Is their ultimate goal,
Taking home the golden
bolt would catapult this squad
Into elite territory
here at battlebots.
They are not taking this
opportunity for granted.
[crowd cheering]
So, originally when
I got hypershock,
I was like, "dude, I've
already done this twice.
The fans aren't
gonna wanna see this."
But then I watched his
footage from this season
And, oh, my god!
Will finally fixed it.
This is not the same
hypershock I have fought.
And I'm gonna need
a few new tactics.
My big goal is to
get him upside down.
And I'm hoping if I just fling
myself into the blade long enough,
He'll flip over, I'll flip over.
The difference is
I can get back up.
They're the best wedge in
the competition, bar none.
They have the best, you
know, ground game upfront.
You know, in terms of armor,
They always have little
attachments to put on.
We will not get under it,
at least not from the front,
So I have to do a very good job
Of being incredibly patient
In getting our
forks under his side.
Or under the back or
under a wheel or something.
But that's the only
way we can deliver a hit
And that's what we gotta do.
[crowd cheering]
[crowd] fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight!
[chris] let the
bot battle begin.
[kenny] will
charges at skorpios.
[chris] nice shot
though from hypershock.
Skorpios flipped over.
Almost flipped out of the box.
It's over!
[all exclaiming]
[referee] nine, eight, seven,
- Six, five.
- [chris] you broke it, will
- You broke it.
- Four, three, two, one.
[buzzer sounds]
[chris] 24 seconds.
[laughs]
Wow!
24 seconds, kenny florian.
[kenny] yeah, I think the ke
was those forks on the front
Hypershock was able to
get underneath repeatedly.
Speed, power, aggression,
This was no fluke,
this was domination.
[chris] boy, it was three shots,
Then finished the
blue monst for the night.
As hypershock is moving on I
the tournament of champions
[laughs]
[crowd] hypershock!
Hypershock! Hypershock!
[chris] will bales.
This place is jumping. I
don't know if you can hear me,
But this place went
nuts on that shot.
Yeah.
[crowd cheering]
I was not aware
scorpions could fly too.
[all chuckling]
I'm frankly a bit surprised
that we got under the front
And got those hits in.
They are the definition
of floor scraping
And perfect front end,
so must be a lucky shot.
-And then we bent it up...
-[person in crowd] I love you, will!
Thank you.
So, I'm really sorry about
picking this particular door,
It's like the door to
throw people out in,
It's a nice door.
You've become the
battlebots bouncer.
Congratulations, thanks for
throwing everybody out of the club.
You're out of here!
- Great run so far.
- Thanks, guys.
We'll see you in the
next round hypershock.
So, skorpios falls
in dramatic fashion.
And it's yet another victim
of the seemingly unstoppabl
Hypershock, kenny.
[kenny] yeah, this
marks five straight wins.
All of them violent
and dominant, chris.
Hypershock could very
well b the last one standing
When all is said
and done tonight.
[chris] what an
unbelievable run.
Hypershock moving
on to the second round.
All right, coming up,
Is there a doctor in the house?
Can andrea and mike gellatl
Put an end to kyle miller's
miraculous 7-0 career start
It's witch doctor facing glitch.
The golden bolt
tournament continues
Next!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] we continue
on. It is the chase for
The golden bolt at
the end of the night.
We just saw team
hypershock advance
To the second round
in convincing fashion.
And we caught up
with captain will bales
After his knockout
victory over skorpios.
Win number five in a
row. It's feeling good.
Feeling good.
That was much quicker
than we anticipated it to be.
But once again, not a scratch.
Not a single blemish on the top
armor or the side armor or anything.
It's just the weirdest event.
We've gone five for five
now with some serious robots.
And no one has
damaged any armor.
No one.
So, who's gonna do it?
[chris] another flawless
victory from team hypershock
[kenny] yeah, the run they'r
on has just been insane.
Will bales is a
man on a mission.
The rest of the bracket
better watch out.
[chris] and it continues on
with witch doctor and glitc
And if I had told
you an year ago
That glitch would have
been in this tournament,
You would have
said, "who's glitch?
- I don't know who they are?
- [kenny chuckles]
[chris] they were a
rookie bot in 2021.
They went 3-0 during
the regular season.
Was the number nine
overall seed in the round of 32,
But because of mechanical
issues could not answer the bell.
And they were forced to
bow out of the tournament
So, you know what?
They entered the
golden bolt qualifier,
They ran through that.
Dismantled the
legend in rotator,
Like we have never seen before.
And believe it or not, this crew
Of young college students
Now sit at 7-0 lifetime
in their battlebots caree
Yeah, this team is
easily the biggest surprise
In 2021 and here as well.
It hasn't been the
smoothest journey.
They've battled significant
mobility issues inside the box.
But there's something
about this bot's
Unorthodox, low profile desi
That has left its
opponents dumb founded
As to how to attack it.
And to say glitch's
weapon hits hard,
Well, that would be a
serious understatement.
[all exclaiming]
[kenny] they will finally
get to face the team
They were slated to
fight in the opening round
Of the 2021 world championsh
tournament, witch doctor.
The fans are
foaming at the mouth
To see how this shakes out.
[chris] and as for witch doctor,
Twice they've been within
arms reach of the giant nut
Falling just short in
2019 against bite force.
Most recently
finishing runner up
To the 2021 champion, tantru
And despite being one
of the most popular teams
In the sports history,
the only battlebots trophy
Mike and andrea
gellatly have ever hoisted
Was a giant bolt in the 2019
all star vegas challenge, kenny.
[kenny] that's right, chris
witch doctor is unquestionab
One of the best combat
robots in the world.
But this team is still
sitting just outside
That elite inner circle
of battlebots champions
Winning the golden bolt tonight,
Would mean as much
to this squad as anyone.
It starts with glitch.
Winner moves on
to the semi-finals
And will have a
date with hypershock.
Let's see what happens. Faruq!
[crowd cheering]
In the red square,
From miami springs, florida,
The lean, mean, purple
and green machine,
Give it up for, witch doctor!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] no one quite like 'e
The voodoo
children, witch doctor.
Led by the husband and wife duo
Of andrea and mike gellatly
You know they are definitel
ready for the challenge.
[kenny] they sure
are and check it out,
Underneath those mittens
on the front of witch docto
Are ground scraping
fork attachments.
Mike has avoided
that trend for years
For fear of them
inhibiting his driving.
But glitch is so low to
the ground on all sides
The team feels it
has no choice here
If it wants to find a
way to catch an edge
And dish out meaningful damage.
[faruq] in the blue square,
from berkeley, california,
This little rider
is ready for war,
It's glitch!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] and now we
get a look at the kids
From the university
of california
And that deadly
egg beater spinner
That has shocked
the world, glitch!
They may keep their
run alive, kenny florian.
[kenny] listen, I think
kyle miller would tell you,
He's as surprised as anyone
To be sporting a
7-0 lifetime record.
But facing witch doctor,
He understands the
symbolism of this match
What I'm looking
for is whether or not
The team has addressed
glitch's mobility issues.
There is very
little room for error
Against a driver as
skilled as mike gellatly.
[crowd cheering]
Their weapon is looking,
like, very powerful,
But they seem to have
pretty unreliable drive.
But the people that
have lost to glitch,
Drive straight
into their weapon.
We are gonna be very patient.
I know it's only three minutes
and it feels like an eternity,
But we're gonna make them
engage us if that's what it takes.
If you don't move,
you get counted out,
So we're gonna take our time
And make sure that
we land the hit we need.
We're doing our best that we
can to get our drive working.
Not really been the
case in a lot of fights,
But we really need it.
We're gonna do our best to keep
our weapons pointed towards them
And try to hit them
whenever we can.
It's kind of a chance to prove
That we could have gone
farther in the round of 32.
That we would have had a
great fight against witch doctor.
And we could have beat them.
So, this one's personal for us
And we really
wanna take 'em down.
[automated voice
speaking] robots activate.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] kenny, you mentione
witch doctor going with thos
New fork attachments.
Looks like glitch has actual
ditched their forks for this match.
[kenny] yeah, kyle miller
told us before the fight,
He was tired of his fork's
continuing to get hung up
On the battlebots' floor.
He's hoping scrapping them
will improve glitch's mobility here.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] it's one of the
biggest names in the sport,
Witch doctor,
Taking on a team that is
making a name for itself
In glitch.
Winner moves on to the
golden bolt semi-finals
To face hypershock.
[crowd] fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight.
[chris] let the
bot battle begin.
Oh, it's interesting to
see how glitch is moving
On this floor, kenny.
[kenny] so far so good.
Looks like they're waiting.
For witch doctor.
Just pointing their
weapon at 'em
To say, "come on,
what do you got?"
[chris] you can hear it.
Both of those powerful
weapo up to full speed.
Witch doctor
looking for an angle.
Uh-oh, gets caught up
on the battlebots' floor
[kenny] yes, something
to keep an eye on.
Witch doctor with those
ground scraping attachments
On the front of the bot.
Will that affect its mobilit
[chris] so much of what mik
does is based on his speed
And if he can't drive proper
It takes away a huge
advantage for this team.
[kenny] and mike
gellatly clearly vary of that
Nuclear weapon
on the front of glitch.
We saw them send rotator 15
feet in the air in its last match.
[all] oh!
[kenny] glitch very close
t a shot to the back side.
And witch doctor now...
Witch doctor going
on the offensive here.
[chris] and one of those little
forks got caught in the kill sauce.
Glitch is having
trouble in the corner.
Just avoids disaster there
With a heart
charging witch doctor.
[kenny] mike gellatly
forcing glitch to work hard
And stay squared up.
[chris] oh, there's a
big hi by witch doctor,
First of the match.
[kenny] glitch was
moving well up to that point.
Witch doctor has a window here.
[chris] and now, witch
doctor's gonna take advantage.
Oh, huge shot on
the college kids.
Those front forks paying
of right there, kenny.
[kenny] absolutely, sent
glitch right into the weapon.
[chris] mike gellatly
with a follow up shot.
Oh, another!
Oh, they're teasing
and testing glitch
To see if it's still moving
I'm not seeing any movement.
[chris] witch doctor
has to be careful here.
They cannot afford to
take glitch off the hook
[kenny] they're
done, are they done?
[chris] their weapon's
too powerful.
There's a possibility...
They're stuck under the
scre and so witch doctor
When back in for a shot.
[kenny] that's how
you finish the job.
- [referee] nine, eight.
- [chris] yup, here's the countdown.
Someone has finally
caught up to glitch.
- [referee] five, four.
- [chris] the veteran tandem
- Andrea and mike gellatly are on to the semi-finals.
- [buzzer sounds]
[chris] that will do it.
Witch doctor is moving on.
[exclaims]
[chris] well, two
dangerous robots
Playing the game of cat
and mouse in this one, kenny
[kenny] yes, they were.
Glitch was actually
moving much better
Than we're used to
seeing to start this match,
Ditching those front forks.
Looks like it
was the right call.
May have missed a few
opportunities to attack
When witch doctor's
forks got hung up
On the box floor though.
Eventually, witch
doctor found an opening.
[chris] yeah, glitch
did a good job
Of staying squared
up to the veteran.
But mike gellatly, dude
is so patient and surgical,
Landed a shot to
the side of glitch.
Got underneath and laid it o
[kenny] no doubt. I thought
mike made the right choice
In continuing to attack glitch.
Once he had it
against the screws,
You cannot afford to give
a bot as powerful as glitch
A second chance.
[chris] the cinderella run
of kyle miller and team glitch
Comes to an end
At the hands of
the voodoo children.
Andrea and mike.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- What was the idea behind
Being so patient
there at the beginning?
So, I mean, glitch is a
very innovative robot.
They have this really
cool driver where they can
Translate and drive around.
They're 7-0 I
think at this point,
So we did not wanna drive
right into their weapon, obviously.
They had huge,
huge hits this year.
And it looks like they
actually were driving
Super well in this match.
Better than they have
in any other match,
So we weren't sure how
well they'd be able to translate.
And I knew I needed to
stay out of the path of that
Monstrous weapon.
Mike, you went with the
forks configuration there.
- Finally.
- Are you happy you did that? Yeah.
Satisfied?
Yeah, I mean, we got
hung up in some of the
Saw slots a few times there.
But glitch is so low, you know,
We figured this is like
the perfect opportunity
To use 'em and I think
they worked pretty all right.
Andrea and mike gellatly, team
witch doctor, congratulations.
We'll see you in the
semi-finals against hypershock.
Thank you.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] so, for team glitch
their miracle run ends here
But kenny, kyle miller has p
the battlebots world on notice.
He is one of the
brightest young builders
In the entire sport.
[kenny] absolutely.
Hats off to this entire squa
Now, 7-1 lifetime at battlebots.
That's more wins than
some teams collect
In their entire career.
[chris] but it is witch doct that's
moving on to the semi-finals
Of the golden bolt championship
Where they will square
off with longtime friend,
Will bales and team hypershock.
All right, coming up.
How about this?
2016 giant nut
winner, tombstone.
2021 title holder and
reigni champions, tantrum.
You want the best of the bes
We got the best of the best
The mind blowing matchups
In tonight's golden bolt
tournament continue
Next.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] we continue on here
on battlebots champions,
The chase for the golden bol
And up next,
The champ is here.
In fact, the champs are here
2016 giant nut winner, tombstone
Is ready to enter the
arena for a showdown
With the reigning
champion, tantrum.
And what an amazing season
for the brand new co-captains,
Alex grant and ginger schmidt.
They led the little puncher
that could in its undefeated run
That culminated with
winning the 2021 title
And taking home the giant nu
But kenny, all the
way back in 2018,
Tantrum faced tombstone
during its rookie season
And let's just say
it was memorable,
But for all the wrong reason
[kenny] yeah, tombstone
not only knocked tantrum out,
It ripped its fists off
And embedded
it in the battle box.
Alex and ginger told
us the whole thing
Was a little embarrassing
And that they've been
waiting for a rematch
With ray billings ever since
[chris] well, they're
finall gonna get it tonight,
But much like this is
a vast different tantrum
Than the last time
these two fought,
We may now be talking
about a different version
Of tombstone as well.
Dare I say
That tombstone has a little
something to prove to everyone tonight.
I think they do.
Ray billings is obviously a
legend and a former champion
But tombstone 5-5
in its last ten fights
And the battlebots worl
is starting to openly wonde
If the king of kinetic
energy still has it.
Ray's made some significant changes
to the weapon in the past few years,
Searching for even
more knockout power.
I think that has led to
some inconsistency,
But this is still one of th
hardest hitting robots in the world.
I think that beefy
armor on tantrum
Will be tested.
Ray billing says don't
underestimate us.
Everybody should
still be afraid.
Let's see for ourselves. Faruq.
[crowd cheering]
In the red square from
placerville, california,
He likes his pizza with
pepperoni, pineapple
And the blood of his victims.
I know, gross, right?
Pineapple. [retches]
It's tombstone!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] here comes the
grim reaper, ray billing
Son, justin on the right.
Longtime friend and grid
chief rick russ on the left.
And of course,
the star of the show
Has its own motorcade,
if you know what I mean.
[kenny] yeah. Just robots
helping robots, chris.
Tombstone still
a sight to behold.
Ray going with the
s7 steel blade here.
Told us that team spent
hour sharpening their weapon
In anticipation
of this showdown.
He wants to use it to cut
directly into the armor of tantrum.
[faruq] in the blue square,
This crybaby will
hit you so hard,
You'll have to call
the whambulance,
It's tantrum!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] the reigning king
and queen of battlebots,
Ginger schmidt and alex gran
Still beaming after
winning the giant nut.
How have they setup tantrum to face
a bot as powerful as tombstone, kenny?
[kenny] such a durable
robot this thing is a little tank
You see that front wedge there,
That was designed specifical
To defend against
horizontal spinners.
They wanna use it to
jam up tombstone's blade,
Then drop it into
attack mod with their fist,
That sliding vertical disc spin.
I believe that I can
beat them in this match.
We're gonna be hitting
'em a little harder than
They've been hit up
to this point in time.
He'll have some sort of big
steel arrangement on the front
To try to stop the spinner,
So he can corner me and
get his weapon into play.
So, my strategy is gonna
be I'm gonna have to try to get
Away from the arena
wall as quickly as possible
And try to just keep fighting
in the center of the arena.
'cause if he gets me pushed into
a corner, I'm gonna be in trouble.
It's gonna be a great tough
match between two champions
And I'm looking forward
to getting in the arena
And doing our thing.
I think this is a sort
of an inflection point
For tantrum
To prove that we are part
of the big leagues now.
Tantrum is not who we
were three seasons ago
When we first fought tombstone.
And this is really,
the difference in fight,
I think will show the
world how far we've come.
To prepare tombstone, we added
some gruff bars to the front of our robot.
Gruff bars are what
we call really strong
Steel bars that
we add to the front,
So that we can knock
tombstone's blade in half.
All right, we got this.
Let's go, tantrum.
[automated voice
speaking] robots activate.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] all right,
buckle up, folks.
Can ray billings make
a monumental statement
And take down the reigning
battlebots champion?
Or will ginger and alex power
tantrum to even greater heights
And make a run
at the golden bolt?
A fight you cannot
afford to miss
When the golden bolt
tournament continues.
[chris] welcome back to
the golden bolt tournament
Here on battlebots
Where we have two
champions ready to throw down.
It's tantrum versus tombston
Winner moves on,
loser goes home.
[automated voice
speaking] red team, ready?
- [buzzes]
- [crowd cheering]
[automated voice
speaking] blue team, ready?
[crowd cheering]
[buzzes]
Yeah, tantrum.
[crowd] fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight.
[chris] let the
bot battle begin.
Here comes tantrum.
- Takes a big shot.
- [all exclaiming]
And tombstone
with kinetic energy
Wielding it all
over the box. Wow!
[kenny] watch for
this whip here. Whoa!
[chris] this is where
tantru wants tombstone,
They wanna try to
get 'em in the corner.
Nice driving by ray billings
[kenny] nice shot to
the side of tantrum.
Uh-oh, tombstone
up on its wheels.
[all exclaiming]
[chris] ray billings' bot
completely out of control
And flirting with disaster now,
Trying to avoid the rails.
[kenny] well, this is where
needs to shut down that weapon.
It looks like he's
having an issue with it.
[chris] yeah, it is
pointing right at us.
Tantrum hanging back.
Watching, waiting to see
If the king of kinetic
energ destroys itself.
That blade is still spinning
Oh, my goodness!
Oh!
[kenny] I'm not seeing
a lot of control here.
[chris] tombstone is smoking
Tantrum is taking the
2016 champ into the rails.
The weapon is no
longer functioning.
And ray billings is in a
world of trouble now, kenny.
[kenny] yeah, tombstone
is hurt badly, chris.
Just crab walking now.
Ray is gonna run
out of rope here.
- [referee] ten, nine.
- [chris] the countdown has started.
The reigning champions,
tantrum brings it full circl
With a statement
win over tombstone.
It's going to be moving on
to the golden bolt tournamen
- [referee] countdown!
- [buzzer sounds]
[chris] kenny, we have spen
years watching tombstone
Destroy its opponents
by delivering
The hardest shots in the gam
But tantrum can
certainly take a punch.
[kenny] my goodness, it's ju so
difficult to knock this robot out.
Combine that with well
executed game plans
And world class driving,
That's why tantrum is
your reigning champ.
[chris] able to deflect
tombstone's energy here
And send it
careening out of control
And that spelled disaster
in the short corner.
Yeah, we had a front row
sea as tombstone's blade
Slammed against the
rails and the battle box floor.
That damaged the drive
And eventually,
blew out the weapon.
Tough night for ray billings
[chris] tantrum
hanging back saying,
"we're all grown up now, ray
we don't shine shoes anymore."
Alex and ginger,
What a run tantrum has been on.
It is a run.
You win the giant nut.
You take down a
legend in tombstone.
What is going on here, ginger?
I mean, in tantrum's
first season,
We had to actually go
up against tombstone
And we were
hobbling into that fight.
I mean, I think we only had
half of our drive train working.
It was a rough year for us.
So, to be able to come back now
And be able to
take tombstone out,
I mean, it is an
incredible feeling.
Honestly, it's amazing.
[all applauding]
Well, guys, congratulations.
We will see you
in the semi-final
In the chase for the
golden bolt. Congrats.
Thank you.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] so, as team tantrum
heads back to the pits
To prepare for their next match,
Let's take a step back.
It's been a while since
ray billings has really left
His stamp on the sport,
- The way that he wants to.
- Right.
[chris] can the legend find
a way to turn things around
And return to form
At the upcoming world
championship and beyond.
[kenny] listen, we've
said it a lot lately,
The sport is evolving so fas
And getting younger every year.
Tombstone isn't anywhere
nea as dominant as it used to be
But the fans want to see th
grim reaper back in the box
And I have faith, ray
will d what he needs to do
To answer the bell.
[chris] all right, and with that
Our first round
action is complete
And we are down to
just four contenders.
And check out this
quartet of killers.
2020 giant nut winner,
end game is gonna square of
With reigning battlebots
champions, tantrum.
And coming up,
Two ferocious vertical spinners,
The red hot hypershock
Will collide with two-time
runner up, witch doctor.
The golden bolt
tournament continues
Next.
We are back on
battlebots champions,
The chase for the golden bolt.
It is time for our first
semi-final between
Hypershock and witch doctor
This is a dream matchup.
On one hand,
you have will bales,
Who electrifies the crowds.
He's captained hypershock
through one of the most
Insanely destructive winnin
streaks in recent memory.
Then there's witch doctor,
Perennially in its prime.
Captained by the iconic duo
of andrea and mike gellatly
These two squads actually
share a shop together in florida,
So they're very familiar
with each other, kenny.
And now, they're gonna
destroy each other. I love it.
You know, witch doctor
obviously has the pedigree
And they had no problems earlier
with the rookie juggernaut, glitch.
But no one has been
as hot as hypershock
Throughout this tournament.
In the first round they had
skorpios out of the arena
In ten seconds flat.
Will bales has been
a man on a mission.
This is a kind of fight you
pay good money to see.
[chris] and now,
one of these bots
Is just two wins away from
hoisting the golden bolt.
Let's find out who's punching
their ticket to the final.
Faruq!
[crowd cheering]
[faruq] in the red square,
She'll make you feel bad as hell
Like lizzo in reverse.
She'll make your death a reality
And you know that truth hurts.
Blame it on her juice,
So speedy when
she throws the switch,
Just took a dna test,
Turns out she's 100
percent that witch.
It's witch doctor!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] for witch doctor,
A March to finals always
feels like an inevitability
This team knows what it
take to get to the finish line.
But they have yet
to cross it, kenny.
[kenny] professional sports
are littered with all-time greats
That simply couldn't
break through to win a title.
And trust me, it drives
the gellatlys crazy.
Of tonight's semi-finalists
no team is as hungry
For the golden
bolt as witch doctor.
In the blue square,
Ever had a case of the mondays
where you're feeling out of whack?
Well, will bales will
make you hate every day,
Like a boomtown
rat with a broken bat.
The silicon chip inside his head
Has been switched to overload
And now you'll have
that song in our head
When he runs you off the road.
I don't like mondays,
But I love hypershock!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] I look forward
to their tunnel entrance
As much as their fight, k.
Will bales leading the crew out.
Let's see what he's got in
store for the semi-final matchup.
[all exclaiming]
[chris] it is technical t-re
The unofficial mascot
of team hypershock.
I suppose you can never have
too much paleo in your pit crew.
[kenny] never. And
unlike witch doctor,
It looks like they're sticki with
their fork configuratio for this one.
Worked pretty well against
skorpios earlier tonight.
We'll see whose ground game
strategy pays off in this fight.
Hypershock!
[crowd cheering]
Hypershock is like one
of the fastest robots here.
Will's one of the
best drivers here.
But we're hoping
he'll make a mistake,
You know, he's overconfident.
- [chuckles] will bales?
- Yeah, he's pretty much the epitome of overconfidence.
Hypershock's gotten some
huge ko hits and so have we.
So, it's going to be a huge
slugfest between two robots.
It might not be a long fight,
But there's guarantee
there'll be some crazy air-time.
We have these rally long forks
And we spent the whole
off-season complaining with them
About how wedge
lids are killing the sport
And forks are killing the sport
And they made some
little ones, I'm like,
"rats, I need to make some too."
And we threw them on and
they've been working like a charm.
So, guess what
you're getting mike?
It's going to be a
heck of a match.
My goal is to set
a high fast paced,
You know, event here.
And do a good, solid
drifting clinic on 'em.
[crowd cheering]
[automated voice
speaking] red team, ready?
[buzzer sounds]
[chris] these teams
may be friends,
But the fun and games are
ov once that light turns green
[automated voice
speaking] blue team, ready?
[buzzer sounds]
[kenny] chris, a true frien
accepts you for who you are
Even after you try
to rip their face off.
[chris] stove's
on fire, let it burn.
You gotta pee, hold it.
This is can't miss
robot combat matchup,
Witch doctor and hypershock
Winner takes the first
spot in the golden bolt final.
[crowd] fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight.
[chris] let the
bot battle begin.
Both drivers moving
well on the battlebots flo
Always a key in the early going.
[kenny] two fast robots here
hard to tell who's chasing whom.
[chris] and the first hit goes
to hypershock, and a second.
Hypershock able
to get underneath
Witch doctor with
those front forks.
Oh, but here comes witch doctor!
Oh, in front of hypershock!
A driving error
by will bale uh-oh!
Witch doctor rips a
tire off of hypershock.
And now it's lodged in
witch doctor's spinner carry
- [andrea laughs]
- oh. [beep]
[chris] a one in a million shot.
[kenny] are you kidding me?
Will bales down a tire
And mike gellatly
down a primary weapon.
Hypershock perfectly
capable of operating
On three wheels though, chri
This may be an
advantage for will bales.
Mike has to be careful here
[chris] and talk about
saving a souvenir.
Witch doctor tried
to shed that tire.
Hypershock is
out of control now.
Inverted but delivers a sho
to the top of witch doctor.
[kenny] mike gellatly
doing the math on just
How aggressive
he wants to be now.
That spinner on
hypershock, still active
And still dangerous, chris.
[chris] and still inverted
hypershock trying to self-right.
[kenny] great job by will bales.
[chris] oh, you can see smok
coming out of hypershock.
- Will asserting so much energy.
- [all exclaiming]
[chris] and look at that.
[kenny] that's gonna
free the weapon, the tire
Was just freed from
the weap of witch doctor.
Now, they're
spinning at full speed.
[chris] and mike gellatly
has gotta be licking his jaw
He's gonna go in for the
kill shot on hypershock
[kenny] that might be a risk
Both weapons
spinning furiously here.
[chris] hypershock
keeping that big weapon
Pointed at witch doctor saying,
"come on! Come at me, bro!"
[kenny] mike trying to
thro hypershock off balance
And create an opening.
How long can will bales
keep this up on three wheels
[all exclaiming]
[chris] what a shot
by hypershock!
But witch doctor still movin
The weapon still operating
at full speed as well.
An unreal first two minutes
this golden bolt semi-final
[kenny] the stand-off continues.
Hypershock still commanding
the center of the box.
[chris] oh, nice
little kick shot.
- [kenny] uh-oh.
- [chris] oh, no.
And hypershock back inverted
[all exclaiming]
[kenny] is that
the kill shot from...
- [all exclaiming] - [chris] oh,
trying to get I on the upper deck.
Mike gellatly trying to fini
the job against hypershock.
[all exclaiming]
[chris] will bales
wondering "can I still move?"
He cannot.
- [referee] ten, nine.
- [chris] he's been counted down.
- Hypershock will be done in by their good friends.
- [referee] seven, six, five,
- Four, three.
- [chris] and shop mates.
- As witch doctor is on to the golden bolt final.
- [referee] one, knockout.
[buzzer sounds]
[chris] wow!
[all exclaiming]
[crowd cheering]
[chris] kenny, the
phrase, back and forth
Just wouldn't do this
unbelievable match justice.
[kenny] unreal action here.
Hypershock landed a
big sho to start the match.
And we thought we were
goin to see another epic
Will bales onslaught.
[chris] but witch doctor sai "I'll
do you one better, will bales."
And tore the back
right tir off hypershock.
And look at this,
I mean, talk about
a hole in one.
The tire gets stuck in
witch doctor's spinner.
[kenny] that is one of
the craziest moments
I have ever seen in this sport.
I mean, how? What? Huh?
[chris] eventually,
hypershock actually
Helped witch doctor
out by dislodging that tire.
And allowing witch doctor's
weapon to return to full speed.
[chris] big credit to hypershock
Staying squared up
on only three wheels.
Even landing this massive shot,
But mike gellatly managed t
create the opening he needed
[kenny] mike started drivin circles
around his hobbled opponent.
And then, here
the finishing shot
Right near the upper deck.
Hypershock gave
an all-out effort.
But put 'em in the body bag.
Andrea!
What was it like watching
your husband run roughshod
Over your good friend,
will bales and hypershock?
I have to tell you, we did not think
that match was gonna go that way.
Witch doctor has
had so much damage.
We did not know
how it was going to go.
And will bales is
an incredible driver.
His robot's so fast.
I think we shocked ourselves
as much as anybody else.
- Hyper shocked, you could say.
- Hyper shocked.
[mike chuckles]
It was a crazy fight.
At one point, you
took one of his tires off.
It actually got stuck.
It was jamming up
your primary weapon.
How nervous were
you guys at that point?
Well, I was trying to
dislodge it with the weapon,
But the weapon's spins in a
direction that lodges it further up,
So mike was trying
with the self-righter.
We talked about
going to the hammer
And try to see if the
hammer could get it out.
But just hitting him, he
took it out for us, I think.
[all chuckling]
Congratulations.
We'll see you in the
final of the golden bolt.
Thank you.
[chris] hey, will.
How discouraging was it whe
they popped your wheel off?
I'm fine.
You know, I'm happy someone
finally gave us some damage
In this competition.
- We went...
- [crowd booing]
Hold on! Hold on! You boo.
We went all the way here
without anyone touching
The side armor,
the top, the bottom,
The back, anything.
They did! They
deserve it! They won it!
[all applauding]
[chris] love to hear that.
An amazing run by you
and your entire team.
- Congratulations, will.
- Thanks, guys.
[all applauding]
[chris] so, witch doctor's
moving on to the finals.
Familiar territory for them
But I think the story
coming out of this fight
Is the recent success
of team hypershock.
I applaud all of them.
I'm so happy for will
bales and his team.
Their performance
throughou this tournament
Is the stuff of legend.
I can't wait to see if they can
recapture this magic next season
And finally make a
run at the giant nut.
[chris] all right, coming up
it's the semi-final matchup
Between the two most
recent world champions,
End game and tantrum.
And on that note, it's
gonn take a herculean effort
Not just in the battle
box, but in the pits as well
For one of these
bots to triumph.
And no team
understands that more
Than the 2021 world champs,
Ginger schmidt, alex
grant and team tantrum.
We just got out of our
fight with tombstone,
We took some really
massive hits from them.
We got a really fast turnaround.
We took massive
hits, you can see here,
Chunks of our armor
completely missing.
And our weapon
is also not spinning.
So, we don't know why.
We're gonna take it
all apart and look at it.
But we can't waste
a single minute.
[chris] we continue on with
the tournament of champions,
The chase for the golden bolt,
The semi-finals between the
last two winners of the giant nut.
We got the 2021
champion, tantrum
Taking on the 2020
champion end game.
And let's start with
the bo co-captained by
Ginger schmidt and alex gran
We said it earlier tonight,
This tournament
is a war of attrition.
Kenny, tantrum is a bot
that can take a beating
And keep on ticking.
[kenny] yeah, I mean,
the first thing I think of
Is they are unkillable.
Doesn't matter what
you throw at them,
They find a way to
survive, keep going.
[chris] remember,
back in the semi-finals
Of the 2020
championship tournament,
Tantrum was flipped by
end game and counted out.
They've since
added a self-righter,
So they're not gonna
make anything easy
For the former world
champs this time around.
Did you say that
tantrum's unkillable?
Because I think that jack
barker and nick mabey,
The co-captains of end game
Their ears kinda
perked up a little bit
'cause they're
like, "wait a second.
We got a great weapon
that c kill just about anything."
- Including your dreams, kenny florian if it must.
- [kenny laughs]
How's it gonna do
against tantrum?
Well, what's the key
here for end game?
Well, listen, if there's
one weapon out there
That can do some
serious damage to tantrum,
It's probably end game.
You know, if it wasn't
for a vintage performance
From daniel freitas
and minotaur,
We could very well be
talking about end game
As a back-to-back champ.
It is still at the top of the
food chain and believe m
They are already envisionin
a championship battle
With witch doctor.
Somebody's moving
on to the finals.
Let's find out which bot it is.
Faruq, take it away.
[crowd cheering]
In the red square,
Play this game of death
And you'll get
popped in the chops.
He throws hands like bruce lee
And his fists of
fury don't stop.
Jeet kune don't test him
Because he's earned his clout
And when he enters the box,
They'll be dragging you out.
It's tantrum!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] in a year we all agr
featured the highest level
Of collective talent in
the history of the sport
It was tantrum who climbed
to the top of the mountain
And took home the giant nut
What would it mean for them to
also bring home the golden bolt?
[kenny] oh, my goodness.
I mean, they would definitel
go into that upper echelon
Of legendary robot teams.
Just really, wow with what
they've been able to do here
They're going with their arm
design for vertical spinners
They used it against
cobalt in the quarterfinals
Of the 2021
championship tournament,
Worked out pretty
well for them that night.
We'll see how it handles
the mike tyson of battlebot,
End game.
[faruq] in the blue square,
Once upon a time in hollywood,
This team won the giant nut.
Now, these natural
born killers are in sin city
And they're kicking butt.
They were death proof before
Winning battles
from dusk till dawn,
Now it's the same story
Except they're dressed
like the reservoir dogs.
By the way, did you
know that in new zealand,
They call the golden
bolt a royale with cheese.
Pretty crazy, huh?
Give it up for end game!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] the 2020 giant
nut winner, end game,
A true knockout artist
As evidenced by their
first round ko of ribbot.
This is unquestionably
the most feared robot
In the sport, kenny.
So, how's it looking?
[kenny] well, they're
going with their wedge lit
And fork combination
to try and pop up tantrum.
When end game
controls the low ground,
The forecast is deadly
With a 100 percent
chance of pain.
[crowd cheering]
In our fight against tombstone,
We took some really serious
damage to our weapon.
Usually, you have a bit of time
To fix the robot in
between matches,
But we're flying by
the seats of our pants
Just trying to get
everything working
And we're really hoping
we're kicking at full power
In the end game match.
End game is a beast.
We're definitely scared of 'em.
They're a hard hitter and
it's not gonna be an easy fight,
But we do think
we have a chance.
We've noticed in the past,
they like to circle their opponents,
Wait for them to make a mistake
And then get into the side.
We're gonna make sure
that we don't let that happen.
We've got a big weapon up front.
They can't compete
with that with theirs,
So they're not gonna
wanna engage that,
But we're gonna make sure
that it's always facing them.
Tantrum won the giant nut
in 2021 and that's awesome.
But they didn't beat
us along the way.
So, we wanna prove
that if we had their run
And they had to
play us along the way,
Then we would have
an answer to them.
- [referee] you good?
- Sorry?
- Yup.
It's ours.
[chris] it's a semi-final wa
between battlebots royalty.
Tantrum and end game,
One of these world champs
is gonna move on to the fina
And battle witch doctor
for the golden bolt.
[crowd] fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight.
[chris] let the
bot battle begin.
Tantrum, quick
out of the square.
End game exposes
its side momentarily.
Dillon carey unable
to take advantage.
Now the bots locking horns,
The battle for low
ground begins.
[kenny] both teams
know from experience
Just how important it is to be
the one that strikes first, chris.
They are jockeying for position.
[chris] end game
backing tantrum down.
Who's gonna draw first blood
Okay, those forks
get untangled now.
Tantrum resets.
Uh-oh.
End game gets hung up
on the floor momentarily.
[kenny] always a risk
when you're running
Ground scraping
attachments, chris.
So far both robots
going head-to-head.
- [all exclaiming] - [chris]
big shot by end gam
That was a huge shot.
The pulverizer just
missed tantrum as well.
[kenny] I think that
was little sneak peek
Of what end game means.
Clean attack to the sides.
[chris] quick turnover.
Tantrum rights itself.
Trying to get up again
to face end game.
[kenny] considering tantrum
came into this fight beat up
It's holding up very well.
- [all exclaiming] -
[chris] oh, nice shot there
[kenny] tantrum is so well
armored, but end game
Knocking it around
the battle box right now.
[chris] yeah, dillon
carey going in for more.
Kenny, tantrum just cannot g that
disc where it wants to on end game.
[kenny] now, those
forks on end game,
Those wedgelets are
winning the ground war, so far.
Oh, nice shot there by end game.
[chris] oh, but the pulveriz
just landed on the 2020 champs.
[kenny] tantrum's starting t slow
down a bit here, chris it looks like.
[chris] yeah, that punching disc
is starting to lose some steam
And the big shots are starti
to catch up with tantrum.
[kenny] they're gonna need
t find a way to close the gap
In the damage column, chris
[chris] whoa, look at
that gyroscopic move.
[kenny] looks like tantrum is
going into tank mode here, chris.
Their primary weapon is
down they have no choice
But to try and break
end game's weapon
And even things up.
[chris] now, end game
loves having its opponent
Right against the rails.
We have bits and pieces
of tantrum on the box.
We're approaching desperatio
time here for tantrum.
Under a minute to go, you
can see the killsaw very active.
[kenny] yeah, both forks
are gone right now, chris.
This could be
trouble for tantrum.
-[all exclaiming] -[chris] end
game knows it. They smell a victory.
Goes in for a shot.
Try to follow it
up with another.
[kenny] I think one of the
weapon belts just came off
Of tantrum as well.
End game scoring some
serious damage here.
[chris] under 30 to go,
But end game's weapon
right now is down.
Don't know if that's
by choice or not.
Looks like it is 'cause
it's back spinning.
[kenny] chris, nick and
jac are throttling that
Weapon down as a way of
countering tantrum's strateg
If it's not spinning,
tantrum can't break it.
And if they can't break it,
they're gonna lose this matc
[chris] under ten
seconds remaining,
Which means this one's
gonna go the distance.
Tantrum, kicking and
scrappi to the bitter end.
- [buzzer sounds] - [chris]
but that's gonna do it.
Lot of energy.
Lot of physicality.
And a lot of fun.
So, now this goes to the judges
For the first time tonight.
We will see all former
battlebots participants,
Lisa winter, jason
bardis and derek young.
They are scoring on
an 11 points system.
Up to five points could
be awarded for damage.
Three for aggression.
And three for control.
[chris] kenny, end game got
the first mammoth shot in this one.
[kenny] yeah, they sure did they
were able to get underneath tantrum.
And if tantrum can't
get underneath you,
They can't control you.
That's where tantrum has
defeated all of its opponent
Is with its control.
And they just weren't
able to do that here
Against end game.
[chris] and how about the
quickness of end game here.
Able to use its
speed and agility
To counter the
lightning fast tantrum.
[kenny] it's a great point,
End game quick enough
to get around the sides
And attack the flanks,
as well as put together
Those deadly combination sho
That kept tantrum
off-balanc and scrambling.
[chris] hey, you said
tantrum was unkillable,
Certainly lived
up to that billing.
But boy, end game
just too good tonight.
Even powering down its
weapo in the final seconds
To avoid unnecessary damage
What a performance.
Here's the decision.
[crowd cheering]
The results from
the judges are in.
The winner by
unanimous decision is
End game!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] jack and nick,
Congratulations.
Nick, how did you win
that brutal battle tonight?
My god.
We were not expecting
such a, like, brutal fight.
- My heart's pounding still.
- [all chuckling]
This is a battle of
attrition, guys, as you know.
That was a brutal fight.
Can you go in there and rebuild?
We gonna have to.
There's definitely
some stuff broken, like,
You've probably damaged us most
This entire year.
So, we'll check it out and
we'll get back in the box.
Sounds great. We'll see you in
a little bit against witch doctor.
Thank you.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] hi, alex and ginger.
- Hi.
- Hello.
First time that you guys
have lost as co-captains.
Alex, this is weird.
[alex] it's a little weird but
To lose to end game,
like, in that sort of a bout.
Like, tantrum just kept kicking.
Self-righter worked
more than once.
- [all laughing] -
mind you. Yeah.
And it's great. I'm
excited. It was a good bout.
Ginger, what was the
difference in that three minutes?
I mean, tantrum
went all the way.
We were agile, we were
running around the box
And, you know, we were
even able to control end game
A little bit towards the end
When their weapon
was slowing down.
It's okay. This is
another lesson to us.
And we're gonna be, you
know, that much better next year.
Congratulations
on a remarkable run.
- Thank you.
[all cheering]
[chris] well, kenny,
before start drooling over
This finals matchup,
Let's first say our
farewells to tantrum.
It's alex and ginger's
first loss as co-captains
And this one certainly sting
But you said it
before the fight,
You cannot kill this bot.
They can be beat, but
they cannot be killed.
Tantrum is no fluke.
And they still have the chan
to do what end game couldn't
Win back-to-back-giant nuts
[chris] all right, folks,
The golden bolt
championshi final is all set.
When we return,
we're gonna break down
This unbelievable matchup.
Will it be end game?
Who once again takes home
the prestigious hardware.
Or will witch doctor
finally break on through
And become a champion?
Who will be the first team
to hoist the golden bolt?
We will find out next
On battlebots champions.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] welcome back
to battlebots champions
Where the conclusion of
the golden bolt tournamen
Is just minutes away.
This incredible
new one night event
Has given las vegas the bes
action robot combat has to offer.
And now, it is down
to just two teams
And they are true legends.
The 2020 winner
of the giant nut,
End game is here.
And they are squaring
off against the runner up
In 2019 and 2021,
Let's hear it for
witch doctor as well.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] now, both these
squads are coming off
Violent brawls in
the second round.
And this was the
scene in the pits
As they scramble
to get their bots ready
For the golden bolt final.
It's our third fight of the day.
It's been a really,
really intense day.
[mike] our last two fights
have just been insane
With, like, all hands on dec
Working on the robot
we're out of our spares.
We're putting
spares, spares, spares
And frankenstein
motors back together
Just to be able to
get to the next fight.
[nick] this is grueling.
Like, having three fights
in one day is insane.
Normally we like to spend
a lot of time making sure
Everything is perfect.
Right now, we've just
put together what we have.
And it's gonna have
to be good enough.
And flipside.
Nothing.
Still nothing.
[jack] I guess, tantrum,
we took a lot of damage.
We kinda smacked them about
But everytime we hit them,
we take that force back into us.
So, in that fight,
we sheared the bolts
That attached the
weapons, the pulley.
And we also had an issue
with weapon electronics.
One of our custom
features on our control board
Has stopped working.
So, we've replaced them.
We are about to roll into
the box and hopefully,
Everything goes
right. We have no idea.
[chris] okay, kenny, both teams
dealing with some uncertainty
At the end of this grueling
push towards the golden bolt
So, what are you
expecting to see tonight?
Yeah, absolutely,
just to get here
Is a huge accomplishment.
And taking a look
at the numbers,
You can see just how
close this matchup really is
Both bots are quick and agil
Thanks to their
impressive drive trains.
And while end game have
significantly lighter armor
Let's talk about where
that weight is distributed.
Witch doctor carries most of
its ar 500 steel armor up front.
While end game
spreads its hardox steel
Out over the entire frame.
And yes, end game
has the bigger weapon,
But if these two
discs collide head on
The only thing that's
guaranteed is chaos.
These are two of the heavies
hitters in the history of the sport.
Buckle up.
[chris] we can't wait.
Can you show 'em
what they're gonna win?
- Let's go, muscles. Come on!
- Of course, I have to pick this up.
Show this thing off.
- Here we go. Huh?
- Look at that.
- The first ever.
- [crowd cheering]
[chris] so, let's get to it
Witch doctor against end game.
Faruq! It's all yours.
[crowd cheering]
Ladies and gentlemen,
Are you ready?
[crowd cheering]
It's championship
robot fighting time!
[crowd cheering]
[faruq] in the red square,
The winds whip wildly around
this wicked witch of the east.
There's a big storm coming
And that's just fine
for this vicious beast.
Because she's
stronger than a tornado
And quicker than a twister.
So, you better show
heart, brains and courage
Or she'll drop a
house on your sister.
Dorothy, I don't think we're
in the battle box anymore.
Give it up for witch doctor!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] what a run
witch doctor has had.
The brutality they've
already faced tonight
Between glitch and hypershoc
And after falling just
shor of the giant nut
Last season, kenny,
I think they're looking at this
As their championship fight
[kenny] yeah, I mean,
the giant nut is obviously
The top of the mountain
here at battlebots.
But if that's 1a,
This golden bolt trophy is 1
They ditched the
front fork for this match,
Meaning mike wants
maximum mobility
In order to try and get arou
to the flanks of end game.
[faruq] in the blue square,
This team of dreamers made
a serious off-season glowup.
Started dressing extra spiffy,
While they made robots blowup.
They're gonna
hoist the golden bolt
And watch it sparkle.
Going from suits to royalty,
Like meghan markle.
It's end game!
[crowd cheering]
[chris] end game
made fast work of ribbot
Before going the
full three minutes
And winning a decision
against tantrum.
The bot looks
pretty good, kenny.
[kenny] yeah, but it's what we
can't see right now that matters.
The mechanical attrition
end game is facing
Is the x-factor here.
They're going with their
wed lifts and forks to the front
As always nick and
jack believe that they can
Win the battle for low groun
That legendary weapon
will b able to finish the job.
[crowd cheering]
We already faced end game
once before in the fight card
And it didn't go our way.
We're gonna use the
same strategy again
And I think we've
fought a lot of robots now
That fight the way end game does
And kinda sits at the
center and aims at you.
We're actually using our
single disc configuration
That we've been using
these last few fights.
So, which is different than
our first fight against end game,
So maybe that will
give us an advantage.
We'll have to see how it goes.
So, the tantrum fight
was actually really hard.
We lost a couple
of speed controllers,
So we had to, like, swap
them out with entirely new ones.
Ones that we actually
haven't run before.
So, it's a little unknown,
We're little nervous
about the fight.
Mike is obviously
a really good driver.
They made it to the finals of
the 2021 giant nut tournament.
And, you know, we did beat
them in the qualifying round there.
I think they're really
on form at the moment.
Coming through this tournament,
It's gonna be real hard
to try and avoid his attacks
And try and get under him.
[crowd cheering]
Here we go.
[automated voice
speaking] robots activate.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] all right. This is I
The greatest 18 tournament
field in battlebots history
Is down to just two contenders.
Will it be the former
champions, end game?
Or the two-time
runners up, witch doctor?
One of these teams is gonna
hoist the golden bolt troph
When we return.
[kenny] at battlebots,
no season is complete
Without our best in
show awards ceremony.
In 2021,
The rookie of the year
awar was split between
Two breakout teams,
Glitch and riptide.
Each receiving a retired
pulverizer from the battle box.
Most destructive as
voted by the judges
Went to will bales
and hypershock.
The prestigious best
design award named in honor
Of the late robotics
legend grant imahara,
Went to aren hill's
cutting edge flipper, blip.
And last but not least
Was the founders'
award given to the team
That best embodies
the spirit of battlebots
Inside and outside of the arena.
There's no better person than that
who deserves this award this year,
Than jamison go from sawblaze.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] welcome back
to battlebots champions
Where we are moments away
from crowning the champion
Of tonight's golden
bolt tournament.
- [referee] good to go?
- Good to go.
[chris] we started with
the best of the best,
So it's only fitting
to finish things off
With a clash of the titans.
It's the 2020 giant
nut winner, end game
Taking on the two-time giant
nut runners up, witch doctor.
[automated voice
speaking] red team, ready?
- [buzzer sounds]
- this time.
[automated voice
speaking] blue team, ready?
[buzzer sounds]
Here we go.
[crowd cheering]
[crowd] fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight.
[chris] can end game add to
their championship trophy case?
Or is it finally
witch doctor's time?
Let the fight for the
golden bolt begin.
Both bots exit their
squares cautiously.
End game in pursuit.
[kenny] witch doctor trying shake
'em and get around the flanks.
- [chris] okay.
- [kenny] oh!
[chris] great shot from
witch doctor to get it going
[kenny] ripped the chunk
of end game's wedge off.
Oh, wow!
[chris] nice shot there.
[kenny] witch doctor going t
work on the front of end gam
[chris] oh, and witch docto
goes flying through the air
[kenny] big hit.
Witch doctor inverted.
[chris] can witch doctor
work its way back right side
And, oh! End game's
right on top of witch doctor.
[kenny] what a great
reversa by mike gellatly.
[all exclaiming]
[chris] there comes
part of the rib cage!
[all exclaiming]
[chris] another enormous shot!
Witch doctor is
no longer moving.
[all exclaiming]
End game is about
to go for the kill.
[kenny] this is going
to be a knockout.
-Eight, seven, -[chris]
the countdown has started.
Witch doctor can only
watch as another chance
- At the trophy slips through their fingers.
- [referee] four, three, two,
One, knockout!
[all exclaiming]
[chris] team end game
will add the first ever
Golden bolt to its mantle.
Wow!
Kenny, we knew his fight
could be over in a hurry
Given the destructive
natur of these two weapons.
[kenny] listen, when it
come to robots, this skilled
And this powerful,
The margin for error is
jus razor thin out there.
[chris] after an impressive
start by witch doctor
It seemed like end game
just decided to throw
Caution to the wind
and push its chips all in.
[kenny] I think that's
exactly right, chris.
Once it lost those wedgelets
end game went into kill mode
Threw everything it
had at witch doctor,
Got underneath repeatedly
And proved why it's the
mos feared robot in the world.
[kenny] mike gellatly
did everything he could,
But to the victor go the spoils.
End game, your inaugural
golden bolt champion.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] nick and
jack, congratulations.
You are the winners of
the first ever golden bolt.
[all applauding]
Nick, what's going through your
heart and your mind right now.
Oh, I was pretty crushed
when we went out of round of 16
Earlier in the year.
But, you know,
this makes up for it.
I think the champion of the
champions, it's pretty good.
[chris] all right, guys.
The co-creator of
battlebots, trey roski
Has a little something
special for you right now.
Thanks, trey.
[chris] there it is, the
first ever golden bolt.
Congratulations, team end game.
[crowd cheering]
Nick and jack, you now
have a golden bolt to go
With your giant nut.
Lift that thing up, guys.
Congratulations.
[crowd cheering]
[chris] a familiar sight.
End game back on top.
For faruq, our bot
whisperer, pete,
My man, kenny florian and
our amazing staff and crew
Here at battlebots,
I am chris rose.
Thank you so
much for joining us.
We will see you next time
here on battlebots.
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org