Can't you go a little faster,
I'm gonna be fucking late.
Relax, we'll be there.
I'm going as fast as I can pal,
don't have a heart attack.
It's like 20 minutes.
- 20 minutes?
You alright?
- I just can't be late to this.
I'm getting out.
Pull over, I'm getting out.
- Ah jeez.
Hey, it's Chubby.
Chubby!
Have a seat.
- You want cake?
- Hey she asked if
I'm ready for my cake.
Cake, cake, cake, cake, cake.
Cake, cake, cake, cake,
cake, cake, cake, cake.
- Tell your boss what
happened here today.
Make nothing up,
leave nothing out.
My part of the deal is
done, not it's his turn.
- Hey.
- So what do you
want for dinner?
I'm cooking.
Really?
What's the occasion?
- I just feel like it.
You not going out tonight?
- Nah, they want me to but
I don't really feel like it.
It's been a long week.
- You're not still
moping over Rob are you?
- No, I'm done with him.
I just feel like
staying in, that's all.
- You're sure
nothing's going on.
Nothing is going on.
I am offering you
fresh cooked food.
Dutiful Asian daughter
and all that shit.
What's not to like?
- Okay, let me think.
- Do you want me out?
- What do you mean?
- Ooh is somebody
coming over maybe?
Is that it?
- No.
- Oh, that's disappointing.
I never want you to use me as
an excuse not to, you know.
What?
- Bring someone home
with you, that you like.
- It's been a long week too.
Let's make dinner.
- Don't forget we have the
councilor meeting on Monday.
You bet.
- We still can't tell them
you're really my uncle?
- You know the drill.
- Alright, I just think
it'd be cool that's all.
It would make me more exotic.
You're a gorgeous,
young Korean American.
Piano virtuoso getting a full
scholarship to Juilliard.
And a multiple black belt.
You wanna be more exotic?
- Boring, boring, boring.
You want some tea?
- Yeah.
Jaime?
Jaime!
Dono?
What the hell is this?
- Hey Jack.
Long time no see.
How you been?
- Good.
How about you?
- Day started off good.
Had a really great
dump this morning.
- Where did they take her?
- I'm just a soldier
man, you know that.
- I know your Michael's guy.
Where?
- If I tell you
Michael kills me.
- That's right, what's the code?
You fail, you die.
Michael will kill you, slow.
I'll make it quick.
I liked you.
You used to make me laugh.
- Jesus Jack.
You worked for Michael once.
What do you expect me to do?
- Come on.
Go on.
Say it.
- Don's Restaurant 18th
and Harrison, in the city.
Talk to me.
- Put Michael on.
Who the fuck is this?
- Jack Lee, put him on.
Dono, I hope you
ain't fucking with me.
- Why'd you take Jaime?
Jack.
- We had a deal.
A deal, right.
Well the deal on the premise
that your brother in
laws death was permanent.
- It can't be.
Oh a beautiful place
he's got down there in
Florida, right on the coast.
You know you can see all
the oil spills in the Gulf
right from his desk.
Five million can buy an
awful lot of property,
so tell me, why didn't
you get one yourself.
- I didn't know,
I wasn't in on it.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
I know you guys weren't
the tightest but come on,
you were married to
his fucking sister.
You know that was a beautiful
plan that you come with.
You fooled me.
I mean you really fooled me.
- Why Jaime?
She's got nothing
to do with this.
I'm out five million and
I need some merchandise
to sell to recover that.
Something of great value.
- I made it square with you.
I hit Z for you.
That settled it.
You made it square
for Harry stealing
five million from me.
Money I thought was lost.
But since he faked his
death, all deals are off.
And the both of
you are gonna pay.
The pay being different.
- You want ransom?
How much?
Oh this is much
bigger than that.
Just know that she'll
be taken care of.
In very good hands, we
can promise you that.
- You deal with me!
You don't take Jaime!
- A professional hit.
And they lost.
Koehler here yet?
- Don't think so.
- Is he coming?
I don't wanna have to
repeat anything to him.
I know I have to work with him,
I am just tired
of always waiting.
Did they find out
who lives here?
- Father and daughter.
Asian, kept to
themselves the most part.
Only thing a noise complaint
a couple of years ago.
Turns out it was a sweet
sixteen for the daughter
and some of her friends.
You know, normal stuff.
Do we know where they are?
- I don't know.
- Never fear the FBI is here.
Okay, let's get this
show on the road.
We haven't met, Hap
Koehler, Special Agent FBI.
Detective Ashley Jordan,
how are you this fine evening?
I want a full report.
- Three dead.
- Neighbor saw a car
leaving the garage
after all this went down.
- Call in an APB.
- Yes sir.
- Well, well, well
what have we got here?
- Plenty here is your caretaker.
You be nice to him,
he'll be nice to you.
You piss him off, he'll
hurt you, got that?
- Got it.
- I'm not talking to you.
You hear me?
- I'm not stupid.
I'm not gonna get
my head blown off
by one of you motherfuckers.
I don't know where I am,
I don't know how the
fuck to get out of here.
So I'll do what you want.
I'll obey, I'll be compliant.
Except for just one thing.
If you try to rape me,
I will fucking kill you
in any way that I can,
and I won't care what
happens to me after it!
And if you hurt me, you kill me,
my Uncle Jack will make sure
that you live long enough
to see your heart ripped
from your own chest.
Okay.
- Jesus Christ.
White Honda has been spotted.
License plate Alpha Omega
Charlie Eighth Six Eight.
Repeat Alpha Omega
Okay we have 42 coming out
over the hit and run
you might wait for him.
Will do.
- I know this guy.
Dono Marro, one of
Michael Banducci's men.
- You sure?
- Been tracking him since the
first day I got this case.
That means everyone else
here is a Banducci man.
That's good.
I can clean out my database,
it was getting pretty cluttered.
Suspect is in custody.
480 at Douglas,
permission to 20 flash.
North on two-one we got this.
10 six.
- I'll make you a bet.
Ballistics will match
every weapon in there
with a bullet in
each of those bodies.
And those bodies will be found
to be the owners of the guns.
- Meaning?
- You're intrigued right?
- Meaning, maybe we should
discuss this case
further over drinks?
Koehler.
Ash!
Patrol car found
our man in the city.
- Fuck this jurisdiction shit.
I am sick of your goddamn
political bullshit.
- You need to calm down.
- We are not your
fucking lackeys.
We led you to Bendu Chief,
we gave you all his
locations, all his contacts,
all his bank accounts,
you took it and you put it in
your precious little database
and you keep taking
all the credit for it.
And I am sick of it.
You can't have him.
- We're on this together.
We're the ones
with the resources.
You got a safe house
where we can take him?
- Yes it's called jail.
- Oh jee.
You're way out of line,
you know that lady?
I think maybe you
need some time off.
You can force for me
to pull rank on you.
I can throw you off this
case, is that what you want?
Look, we take him
to a safe house,
you're there with us and
I'll debrief you on Jack Lee.
Trust me detective.
You have no idea what
you're up against here.
What's your answer?
- Do it.
- I tell you, she's like that
girl from The Exorcist movie.
I was waiting for the
green gunk in my eye.
- What are you
getting soft on me?
She's 17 for Christ sake.
- We've got her no
problem, and cops got Jack,
can you believe that?
We watched the whole bust
out of the front window.
- Yeah, we'll deal
with that next.
Who's watching her now?
- Testo and The Machine.
- The heat got Jack right
outside our fucking door.
They're gonna be
back to look around.
Have them take her
to the warehouse
and babysit until
we get there okay?
- Done.
- What's the code?
- Failure is not an option.
- Now say it the right way.
- You fail, you die.
- Okay, next item on the agenda.
- What agenda?
- Jack.
- Oh, we'll get him.
- SFPD owns him now, unless
he does something about it.
If you want him, you've
gotta go through them first.
Yeah I thought so.
It's time you met somebody.
Pull the car around.
- What is it a Chinese
medicine or something?
- Patience trust me.
Michael Banducci, enter Senor.
- Thank you, good to see you.
- Please.
My nephews Alejandro,
Diego, my sisters sons.
They've come into the business.
- We have not needed
your special services
in quite a while
now as my business
has been stable and growing.
- I take it a
pleasure to hear that.
I'm sorry things are
different now huh?
- A single issue only and
you can help me with that.
I want only the best you have
to offer, as we will need it.
- Consider the
fee paid, in full.
As it happens the best is
here with us as we are speak.
Let me introduce Diego to you.
My nephew, a Navy Seal.
Can you believe it?
- I feel better now,
we're in good hands.
You hungry?
- Sure.
- What do you feel like?
- Oh let's see we had
Italian last night.
- How about, I
don't know, Chinese.
- Yes sure, that sounds good.
What?
- Think back, six years now.
A little job I sent
you on for a client.
You were there only to
report what you saw,
as an objective and
trusted third party.
Do you recall this?
Tell me everything you
remember of that night,
can you do that?
- Yes.
I remember everything, as
if it were just yesterday.
I wish I could just forget.
- Open the door.
- I always open it.
- Open the fucking door.
That'll teach you, you
little fucking cunt.
Where you going
to run to now huh?
- Hey babe, it's
your favorite girl.
I'm maybe 20 miles out.
- Can y'all see me
from your station?
10 four.
- I could head over
later, that is,
if you're not doing anything.
- Johnson.
Go ahead.
- Stay there.
Copy that.
- See you soon, love you.
- Six years ago, the gang boss
known as Z was muscling in on
Michael Banducci's
territory and operations.
On the night of July 7th,
they shut him down, hard.
All the bullets and casings
that were harvested
from the crime scene
matched the weapons
of all of the victims.
On that alone it
would appear that
they just decided to kill
themselves for the hell of it.
It must've been a pretty
lousy birthday party.
Banducci arranged the
hit, that's a no brainer.
But there's never been any
evidence to link him to it.
The case went very
cold, very fast
and it's stayed
that way ever since.
Then last night,
when I saw what went down
at the home of Jack Lee,
I recognized something
that I hadn't seen
since the Z killings.
The victims weapons were all
taken and turned upon 'em.
All of the victims
were Banducci's men.
Shortly thereafter
we picked up Jack Lee
casing Don's Restaurant.
A front for Banducci
run by his ace boon goon
Dimitri Don Orloff.
Can you feel it?
Yeah, we can feel it.
- Yeah.
Jack Lee is sitting in there
waiting for us to have
a conversation with him.
If he's a $25,000 a
year security guard,
I'm the Shah Of Iran.
We get him to tell us
that Banducci hired him to do
the Z hit, we can prosecute.
I've waited six
years for this, okay.
You're welcome to
stay if you want
but there's not really
anything for you to do.
I'll keep you updated
on any new developments.
- I wanna review the photos,
is that okay with you?
- Passwords ghost,
all lowercase.
- I'm not here to
interrogate you.
Where's your daughter?
No tricks.
I am just honestly concerned.
- What are you doing?
You are here at my
sole discretion.
Do we need to have that
discussion about jurisdiction.
- Do you have a car?
- Yes.
- Front or back?
- Front.
Let's go.
Drop to the ground.
Drop to the ground!
On the ground now, hands spread.
The snipers on the East Side.
- What are you doing?
I'll draw 'em out,
if you're quick.
- There's a hospital 10
minutes away from here.
- No.
They found me here,
they'll find me there.
- You need to let me go.
- I have to find Jaime.
- Then she is alive?
- I die, she dies.
I'll tell you everything
you wanna know,
I'll give you Banducci.
Give him up.
- Come on, come on, let's go.
- Hi there, welcome.
- Good to see you
again Tashir son.
- If you'll excuse me.
- Okay.
You've kept me on the hook
for quite a while now.
- What do you mean?
- My warehouse, my
entire operations,
you know the work of it.
My offer still stands.
My retirements calling
to me louder every day.
- I've been following
your growth,
as if I've always
been an investor.
- Well I'm flattered.
You would've seen an excellent
return on your investment.
- I have particular appreciated
your escort services.
Executive class all the way.
- Thank you.
- And I'm also very impressed
by your shipping operations.
You've become the Fed Ex of
the contraband haven't you?
Then you know the
worth of my operation.
- Indeed, and it would supplement
my activities really well.
Your price has always
been reasonable
and I will pay when
I am ready too,
but I am not yet ready.
- Well I may have something
that will make you
feel you are ready.
- I'm intrigued.
- Six years ago when you were
just starting your
trafficking operation
and wanted girls of
distinction, I offered you one.
- She was Korean and
very young wasn't she?
- That's right.
Long story short, she
became a bargain chip
to another problem I had
and that chip has been used.
- Have you found one
of the same caliber?
- Actually, it's the same one.
She's back on the
market and as I recall
you don't like to pick
prematurely from the vine,
you appreciate a fruit
that had time to ripen.
- You have a good memory.
- Well she's 17 now and she's
become a very fine wine.
- And has the
bottle been opened?
- I would assume
so, kids these days,
but the bottle is full.
- I presumed she has
not yet been bargained.
- No she has not and I warn
you, she's wild, extremely so.
- That's a, this might
indeed close our deal.
- I'd like to arrange a
showing at your convenience,
I'm supremely confident
you'll be very pleased.
- Your offer is most generous,
I shall be pursuing this matter.
- Well consider it a bonus
and my gift to seal the deal.
It's looking really good.
Figure out where
you'd like to live
for the rest of your life,
maybe a tropical island
someplace like that.
Someplace you can
park your yacht.
You know, your smaller yacht.
Okay, unfinished business,
where did San Testaban say?
- Well he's making noises
that we didn't tell him
it wasn't just Jack.
- It was just Jack.
- Turns out there was another
person they had to fight too.
- So fucking what?
- The contract says one.
- Bullshit.
Alright we've gotta
send him a message.
What's his cousins name?
- Nephew, Diego.
- Whatever.
I want you to find him,
slap him around a bit,
leave some marks.
Send him back to
Testaban with a message
that I expect this
work to be completed
or we've got a very
serious problem.
- Done.
Ash, he's awake.
- Jack, can you hear me?
- Where the hell am I?
My brother Oliver's house.
He's taking care of you.
- Your brother?
- Adopted.
- How long?
- Well since the
orphanage and then I came,
oh, about two days.
No, you can't, no good.
You've gotta stay
flat as a board.
- Rest now, you're
in good hands.
- Are you comfortable?
Taken care of?
- Yes.
- Look, we got off
on the wrong foot,
but you've been behaving,
I'd like to reward that.
Do you remember me?
You were about so.
Cute as a bud.
Already a real looker.
Your father worked
for me back then,
I mean your real father Harry.
Call me Uncle Michael,
I'd like that.
- Okay, Uncle Michael.
- Now Jaime you like
nice clothes don't you?
Oh then you're just gonna
love what we've got for you.
You do as you're told, everyone
has an enjoyable evening
and we see about
getting you back home
safe and sound to Uncle Jack.
How's the sound?
- What do you want me to do?
- Oh no, no, no,
nothing like that.
I can find plenty
of girls to put out.
I just need you to be a
beautiful, charming hostess
to impress a very important guy.
Can you do that
for Uncle Michael?
- Okay.
- Terrific.
See that?
Kill 'em with kindness and they
eat right out of your hand.
Bitches are all the same.
- Did you mean what
you said in there?
Are you gonna let her go?
- What the fuck do you
think I'm gonna do?
- Well, I dunno, I
figured maybe like...
- I swear, the next guy I hire
has to be a college graduate,
I can't take this shit anymore.
- Man, his ass is so tight
only frogs in Peru
could hear him fart.
Come on Jack just
a little further.
- Outside.
- No man, this window's gonna
be all the outside you get.
Come on.
He's got about an hour
until his next pain meds
and then he's gonna
probably pass out.
- Are you ready for
some show and tell?
Koehler kept everything
about Banducci on this.
I've had the last few
days to figure it all out.
Who is Harry Mason?
I've helped you no?
And we had a deal.
- Yes you have.
- Your brother in law?
You may not like what I'm
going to show you next.
Did you know?
Harry Mason was married
to Alexa Lee, your sister.
She's deceased?
- Car accident.
- Suspicious?
- Drinking problem.
- They had a daughter, Alicia,
she disappeared right
after Harry's death.
No trace.
She's Jaime isn't she?
Tell me about this.
Harry kept the books for
the Banducci operations.
Over several years
he siphoned off
five million and disappeared.
Banducci grabbed Jaime as
leverage against Harry,
he figured he'd only
come back for her.
He didn't.
A month later it looked
like Harry bought it
in an arm's heist gone wrong.
Big explosion.
Lots of blood.
They ID'd Harry by
some loose teeth.
After than Banducci had
no more use for the girl.
He would've killed
or trafficked her.
I made a deal to get her back.
- You hit Z, take out his
rival, he gives you Jaime?
Banducci kept his
end of the deal?
- We disappeared, Jaime
picked a new name.
Those were good times.
A second chance.
Then they found
Harry still alive,
Michael thought I knew.
I didn't.
I thought he was dead too.
After all these years.
- What's happening?
- She's worried.
Just trying to work it
out for herself you know.
- So am I.
- I think it's you.
She says your some kind of
ninja, assassin,
killer, hitman, dude.
She said you saved her life.
- She saved mine.
- Did she tell you,
I'm not a doctor.
- What the hell are you?
- I'm a veterinarian.
Horses and dogs mostly.
- Oh shit.
- Don't worry man,
I learned the same shit as
those people stitchers did.
Hey, hey man watch it.
You don't know what
you're missing dude.
- I like this gun.
Fits my hand like
it's molded for it.
Koehler had good taste.
- You never come with a weapon,
so nothing can be traced to you.
- And nothing can ever
be taken away from me.
- You have to know how
to use every weapon.
- In my line, whether
you live or die
depends on your
weapon of choice.
Can I get my phone back?
It's the only way
Jaime can reach me.
- I found it in Koehler's
case, I'll give it to you.
- Thank you.
- Alright what happened?
- It got a little out of hand.
- I didn't tell you
to kill the fucker.
Slap him around is
what I said, okay.
- That's exactly
what I was doing.
He knew the rules.
- Oh Christ.
- Put the weapons down.
Then he pulls a blade.
- You're bringing the
heat on us, you know that?
- Only his brother knows,
he ain't going talk.
- What am I gonna
say to San Testaban?
This Diego was his cousin.
- Nephew.
- Whatever!
There's a big fat
fucking difference
between slapping a guy
around and putting him down.
- He came at me for the kill.
- Hmm-mm.
Him with a knife,
you with a gun.
Was there something
going on between you two?
- I caught Candy
with him at the club.
So we had a little altercation.
His big brother stopped
us from settling things,
so things ain't settled
if you know what I mean.
- That's it?
He was taking home one of
your stripper girlfriends?
- She was special.
- I bet she was.
Not like the others.
- That's right.
- She fooled you.
- What?
- You're a bonehead, but
you're not that stupid.
I was fucking her too.
Was there anything
else going on?
- I was doing his
girlfriend too, that's all.
- Ah Jesus.
- I didn't know she was
his girlfriend at the time.
Alright yeah, I knew.
- Hmm, goddammit.
- For me?
- It should fit.
How are you feeling?
- A thousand times
better than yesterday.
- My grandfather always
used to say afternoon naps
killed everything
except an appetite.
It should be ready
in about 15 minutes.
- Where are we going?
Am I under arrest?
- Sure, why not.
I always let someone
in my custody
run straight into sniper fire
and then I follow guns blazing.
- It works every time.
- You were hit.
- Only once, thanks to you.
Thank you.
- You're not under arrest.
Because I'm not a cop anymore.
I stopped being a cop
when we drove away
from the crime scene.
It was a long time coming.
Why did you?
- I didn't dislike Koehler
because he was such a doofus,
I was burned out
and he could see.
And I hated that he
knew that about me.
- What will you do now?
- Finish making dinner.
After that, anybody's guess.
If I wasn't a cop,
I would've loved to have
been a ballroom dancer.
- May I have this dance?
I can dance to this too.
- Can you now?
- I failed her.
I failed at being a good father.
- The last six years
prove different.
We found him.
Confirmed it's them.
What do you want us to do?
Check.
- Jack!
Who sent you?
If you wanna live you talk.
- San Testaban.
Working with Banducci?
- Don't know.
I'm just a soldier.
Of course.
Where is San
Testaban these days?
- Alright, alright.
88 Grant, Chinatown.
What's San Testaban's
connection to Banducci?
- He's freelance.
Custom services.
No loyalty.
He'll take a job for anyone
as long as money's right.
- You've met him?
- No, but I've heard of him.
He's a recluse.
But he's got his
hands in everything.
The FBI have used
his service before.
It explains how they found
us at the safe house.
I'll go alone.
- I'm going with you.
- I'm faster alone.
- I'm not asking permission.
I'll keep up, deal?
- I can't worry about you.
- Don't.
- Tie him up, even
if his arm falls off.
- I'm proud of you brother.
- Hey man.
You into weed at all?
- 72 Chevy Nova 350 38.
- It's my baby.
Upgraded it's cam intake,
the carb, dual exhaust.
- Sweet.
Where have you been all my life?
- Waiting for you.
- Get all the regulars
out of here by one.
Given them their bonuses
and tell 'em the boss is real
happy with their productivity.
- Okay, I'll tell 'em.
- Tashir's gonna
be here at three,
so if she decides to act
up today you deal with her.
And no messing
her up in any way.
No cuts, no bruises, no
black eyes, you got it?
- Say what?
- I've been keeping you
in the loop haven't I?
Tashir is our cash cow
and he's about to make
you very, very rich.
I've been trying to make
this deal with him forever.
And now we finally got the
sweetener that's gonna close it.
Our beautiful little honey pot.
On paper it's gonna look like
just another legitimate
real estate deal,
but what he's getting is my
entire fucking operation.
My life's work, for a
cool million Benjamins.
You got any idea
what that gets you?
We'll have more money than
we know what to do with.
Live like Kings for the rest
of our lucky fucking lives.
But it's all riding on the
sweet little snatch in there.
She's gotta be
absolutely perfect.
No damaged goods.
Not even a scratch.
Now you got it?
- I got it.
- What's the code?
Someone order a dress.
- Alright it's here.
- The tailor is not.
- What the fuck do you want?
- Excuse me?
Hi, I'm the stylist
hair, face and nails.
You Michael?
This is the address.
It's just shops, where
is he supposed to be.
- He said inside.
Like a rat in a sewer.
They live like a maze.
- What now?
- I found a way in.
- Good faith to our
remaining venture.
- This is the most
generous gift Tashir son.
I'm deeply humbled.
- Bullshit.
- Lose the dress.
- No.
- Lose the goddamn dress.
- Lose the fucking dress.
- No.
Magnificent.
- Take her back.
- We got a deal.
- Alright.
- It's Chubby.
Shit.
- Let him go.
Your problem is with me.
- My problem is with Banducci.
- Then why come here?
Go to Banducci.
- You're going to
take me to him.
- No, I do not betray clients.
- They come to me always,
'cause everyone knows that.
- Point it at me,
I'm the boss here.
, I ask for mercy.
I am humbled.
I will not forget this.
- Banducci has my niece.
Your assignment on me is unjust.
- I no longer work for Banducci,
I will return his payment.
- Even though he
killed your nephew?
Chubby told me.
- Don't confuse today with
what will happen tomorrow.
Emotion and business do not mix.
A time will come,
of my own choosing,
and my Diego will be avenged.
- Tell me where Banducci is?
- On the graves of all my
ancestor's I do not know.
They come to me, always.
'Cause everyone knows that.
I guarantee you safe
passage from here.
Should we meet again,
there'll be no
legacy between us.
Okay, okay, okay.
You alright?
Yeah.
Alright.
- I wouldn't let
her do that to me.
- I need your help, I
know where Banducci is.
Come on let's go play
cards, the boys are waiting.
- Why are the boys even here?
Why?
- Michael wants some back up.
- Yeah I can do the back up.
I can do the forward,
I can do all that shit.
- Shut the fuck up.
The money will be
here at 6:00 a.m.,
I'll be here at 6:30 and
we'll close the deal.
- Fantastic, see you tomorrow.
Figure out which island
you wanna live on yet?
- Yeah, Long.
- Excuse me?
- Long Island.
- That's your
choice, Long Island?
- It's where my family is.
Call San Testaban,
I wanna hear that Jack
is dead and gone okay.
- Shit, must have dropped it
while wrestling with the bitch.
- Well go get it.
- Getting it.
- Simple people.
- This is what I do best.
Alone.
- You can't fight Banducci
and get Jaime out
at the same time.
I'm looking forward
to meeting her.
Getting to know her.
How are we gonna get in?
- Got a crowbar?
- In the trunk.
- That will do.
- Titanium.
- Shoot.
Shoot.
- I'm Ash, I'm with
your Uncle Jack.
- He's here.
- Yeah, let's go.
- Hey Jack.
Somebody wants to say hello.
What do you have to
say for yourself?
Huh?
- Harry?
- Jack.
I'm so sorry for everything.
Everything in the world.
- All if forgiven Harry.
- That's sweet, you
hear that Harry.
Somebody's forgiven you.
- Alicia is she good?
- The best.
- Tell her I love her.
You can tell her yourself Harry.
- It's what I want the most.
- Alright enough of this shit.
I brought him out her
for one reason Jack.
To watch you die.
Then he'll know there's no
home for his little girl
before I put a bullet
through his face.
- Go.
Watch the back.
- Come on.
- Diego says hello.
He's waiting for you.
- You and what army?
- San Testaban.
- That's not like you Jack.
- Life is full of
surprises Michael.
- No shit.
- I'll kill him and
then I'll kill you.
Too bad you brought
knives to a gun fight.
Poor choice Jack.
- He's bluffing Jack.
He won't kill me 'til
he's got his money.
I'm worth millions to him
alive and nothing dead.
Don't kid yourself.
- How many times can a man die?
Farewell.
- You failed.
You die.
- You okay?
Unhurt?
- I'm okay, I'm okay.
- No.
I am so sorry, it's your father.
- You're my father.
- Where's Ash?
- She needs help.
- You have to get out.
We're taking care of this place.
Set the explosives, in the back.
- Ash!
I got it.
Ash.
Stay with me.
- Who is she?
- Someone very special.
I'll tell you about her.