[music playing]
Hi, Harry, I'm leaving early.
It's my kid's birthday.
SOPHIE: Bye, Diane.
So long, Sophie.
COWORKER: Bye, Diane.
What are you doing here?
You're supposed to be in
Hoffman's office in 10 minutes.
The conference
call went on forever.
If you can find me 301 I swear
I'll give you my firstborn.
No thanks.
I've met your firstborn.
Why don't you try
300, specific intent.
301 is general.
300, that makes sense.
I'll give it some thought.
You've got about
35 seconds then I
suggest you move your ass, sir.
If you could get your law
degree, I'd hire you like that.
You'd have to put me
through college first.
I'd cost you a bundle.
Now get out of here.
OK, we're going to
have to make this fast.
It's Sean's birthday and I
got a zillion things to do.
Can't let a little thing like
a reception for the governor
get in the way of
picking up my son's cake,
et cetera, et cetera.
OK, what have we
heard from The Grand?
OK, The Grand, the
international ballroom
holds 350.
That's good, but
check with the Regency
and see if they can match
the Grand's price per person,
and not with rubber
chicken either.
Music?
I have a call into the union.
I was thinking maybe
classical, what do you think?
That's great.
Press release, I'll
handle that myself.
You want to call the governor's
office and tell them that?
OK.
OK, that does it.
I'm so glad they asked you
to introduce the governor.
You know, the partners
are pushing for you.
That's because I'm female.
They're so 1960s around here.
They don't have
any lady partners,
as they like to call them.
OK, see you later.
Bye.
Thanks.
[music playing]
Don't let this happen again.
Going down?
Down to parking?
[honking]
[tire screeching]
Lady, what are you doing?
Sorry, ma'am, but
you can't stop here.
I'm sorry, where am I?
Where do you need to get to?
Could you-- could you
give me some suggestions?
Um Giffordsville, Porta City.
Porta City, yes.
Porta City.
OK, which side?
East side?
West side?
Where there are houses?
Um, Bryland, maybe.
Yes, Bryland.
OK, what you do
is you go straight--
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait a second.
Would you just wait a second.
- Sure.
- I just want to--
- No problem.
Write this down.
Yes.
Go straight, take
the first right.
You'll get to an overpass.
An overpass.
Go over the overpass.
And then when you
get to Haslet Avenue.
Haslet.
Just look to your right
and you'll see Bryland.
Thank you.
- OK.
- Thank you.
- Gonna be OK?
- I think so.
Great.
Thank you.
[vacuum cleaner]
Hey, Scamp.
Hey, little guy.
He's afraid of
the vacuum cleaner.
There's a first.
Say again.
What are you doing vacuuming?
Somebody has to do it.
I thought you'd be
home right after lunch.
I-- I--
I got stuck at the office.
What?
I had a million things to do.
Oh yeah?
Then why did they tell
me you left hours ago?
You called the office?
Of course I did.
What did you do that for?
Because those hotshot lawyers
think they own you, Diane.
You were supposed to have
the afternoon off, remember?
Where have you been,
it's 4:30 for God's sake.
Why are you giving me
the third degree, Jack.
Because I was worried.
I'm sorry.
Well, you could
have at least called.
I know, I'm sorry.
You should be.
When did the kids get here?
A couple hours ago.
Did you leave the
cake in the car?
My gosh.
Don't tell me
you forgot again.
You forgot again, didn't you?
What's wrong with you, Diane?
You used to be like an elephant.
I'm just going to
forget I heard that one.
I guess I should go
pick it up now, huh?
Would you?
It's paid for.
And the cold cuts.
The market's just
a few doors down.
You didn't even pick up
the food for the party?
Diane, there are
18 people coming
over here in a few hours.
I don't know what you
expected them to eat.
I'm sorry.
Hi.
He just fell asleep.
I'll put him in his
crib in a minute.
Hey, it's your grandma.
Whatcha looking for?
Grandma's picture, you know,
the one you said I could have
for the mommy and me group.
It's the graduation
one, I think.
You remember?
We're doing that
generational thing.
Oh, yes.
Yes, I was going to
show you, that's right.
Now where did I put
the [inaudible]??
Actually, you know what?
Don't worry about it.
- No, no.
I put it-- I put it in--
I put it in here I'm, sure.
Mom, don't worry about it.
OK?
I left work early to help you
set up, so let's get started.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I'm sorry.
I just wish you called.
It's like trying to
make conversation
with dad for two hours, it's
like total silence or Vietnam.
Give him a break, sweetheart.
It's been a long week.
Yeah, yeah.
I hope that's your husband,
we need help with the drinks.
OK.
What?
What do you need?
Glasses.
Ice.
That stuff.
- Will you watch him?
Yes, sure.
Where is that birthday boy?
For he's the jolly
good fellow, for he's
the jolly good fellow,
for he's the jolly good
fellow, which nobody can deny.
There you go, kid.
I've been working all day
on this, haven't I, Tracy?
Oh yes, slaved for
hours over those roses.
Make a wish, doofus.
I already did.
[cheering] And it came through.
She said yes.
Everybody, you are
all the people that we
love most in this world.
And we know about being
stupid and everything
but we wanted you to
be the first to know.
We got engaged, baby!
You can't do this.
You're supposed to be my
bratty little brother.
Wow.
DIANE MCGOWIN: Oh my goodness.
Did you know about this?
DIANE MCGOWIN: No, I didn't.
Is [interposing voices]
Oh goodness, darling.
Oh my.
We have to open the
champagne, champagne.
Oh, can I use the camera?
I just got one more shot left.
OK, go on, give him a hug.
Now, no getting married
till after grad school.
I'll get-- I'll get
some more film--
oh!
Diane!
Mom!
I'm OK.
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
I'm OK.
You're supposed to put one
foot in front of the other one,
babe.
You're all heart.
What did you trip on?
I'm fine.
I'm a klutz.
Stop looking at me.
I'm OK.
I'm really fine.
Go on now, stop.
I'm fine.
You really shaken up?
You fell hard.
I just slipped, that's all.
No, you didn't.
I saw it.
You didn't slip.
You didn't trip either.
I know, Paula,
something's wrong.
Excuse me, you
get some more film?
Yeah, um, I think in
the top-- oh, the top--
right there in the top one.
So how does it feel, pop?
Meh, he's too young.
What's he getting engaged for?
Remember love?
I do, and a lot of
the things that passed
for it when I was that age.
You'd better not be
talking about me, marine.
Because I remember you
camping out on my doorstep,
night after night,
begging me to marry you.
That's not the
way I remember it.
You just wore me down.
You were crazy about me.
Wasn't she, Paula?
I was crazy anyway.
Leave me out of this.
I'll catch up with you, later.
Now what's up, kid?
You told her something
was wrong, what is it?
My baby's engaged.
I heard.
His timing stinks if you ask me.
He's already lost
two years of college
because of the accident.
Between us, I hope she's
not pregnant because they
got absolutely nothing.
For that matter,
neither did we.
And that turned out
all right, didn't it?
You tell me.
I asked you first.
Mostly.
You sure you're all right?
Well, the party's downstairs.
You coming?
Yeah, I'll be there in
just a couple minutes.
Here's to looking at you, kid.
Mom, what are you doing?
There's a party
going on downstairs.
I found it.
Found what?
Grandma's picture.
Mom, I didn't mean for
it to be such a big deal.
Oh no, I've got it right here.
Look.
I found it.
Oh wow.
She was gorgeous.
Wasn't she?
I remember her being all
drawn and sunken, really old.
No, she wasn't old.
She was 55 when she died.
She was just sick.
There are all kinds
of things in here,
notes and letters, baby
pictures of you and Sean.
Mom.
There's 20 people downstairs.
Come on.
I'm confused.
I've never been confused before.
I'm forgetting words that
I've known my whole life.
I feel-- I feel--
I feel my thoughts just
slipping out of my brain.
Something's wrong.
I need-- I need
tests or some kind
of brain scan or something.
Something's wrong.
Is there any Alzheimer's
in your family?
Alzheimer's?
God no.
How old do you think I am?
I know, but there's an
early onset Alzheimer's.
The fact that it's
not very common
and there's no history your
family says that's not what's
going on here,
but I have to ask.
No, my father died
of a heart attack.
My mother had cancer.
You know that.
Both my parents
were sharp as tacks.
As are you.
But I'm sure it's just stress.
You're working 60 hours a week.
But if you want me to send
you to neurological testing,
I can do that.
I'll make some calls and
set up an appointment.
Now, let's see.
What's a good time for you?
Um, OK, um, all right.
I'll just-- I'll call you, then.
Uh, Jack still quality
control at Lockman?
Yeah.
They have good insurance.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Everybody does
that at some time.
Do they?
[music playing]
Mama.
DIANE MCGOWIN: So do I have it?
The spec test says you do.
It's not totally
accurate but your scores
were in the 95th percentile.
Really?
95?
That's the best
grade I ever got.
My mother would be so proud.
Do you really
think that's funny?
Probably not.
It's not even true, I
got 95s in everything.
So how long before
I'm a vegetable?
I wouldn't use that word.
How about, um, basket case?
Do you want to tell me
about how frightened you are?
what's going on in my brain?
Diane, we don't know.
With Alzheimer's you
can never be sure.
One of the most frustrating
things about this disease
is you will never--
you'll never be able
to know what to expect.
Depressions,
hallucinations, confusion.
There'll be times when you won't
remember how to dress yourself,
how to use a knife and
fork, even who you are.
Right now you feel
really bad because you
are in a downward spiral.
But there'll be
times when you'll
feel all right, whole periods
when everything will be normal.
I noticed you came by yourself.
Have you told your
family about this?
No.
You might think of
telling your husband.
And then again, I might not.
Why is that?
Can I go home now?
Hey, you're home early.
I went shopping.
Yeah, what for?
A dress, for the
governor's thing.
Am I expected to go
to that thing with you?
I hate those deals, you know.
You don't have to.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
You know, I got
league tonight.
Stampy, get off the bed.
You're not going in today?
Headache.
You want an aspirin?
You use a knife and fork
to eat with, don't you?
Answer me.
Yeah, of course you do.
I thought so.
Do you want me to call
the office and tell them
you're not coming on?
No, I'll go in later.
All right.
[music playing]
I got to run.
I'll see tonight, OK?
OK.
Mom?
[phone ringing]
On no!
Mom?
You awake?
Yes.
Feeling any better?
Is your headache gone?
What are you doing here?
Dad told me you've been
in bed a couple of days
with a bad headache.
Days?
I've been thinking, maybe
it's menopause or something.
I better call the office.
Dad did that already.
Did you hear what I
said about menopause?
Yes, I heard.
What do you think?
You've been forgetting things.
You never used to
get headaches before.
Mom, you should call a doctor.
OK, I'll go to a doctor.
Promise?
I promise.
Hey, you never showed
me the dress you bought
for the governor's party.
Oh, it's in the, um,
where I keep my clothes.
Wow, it's sensational.
You think?
Not too much.
Except for the price.
Well, the office
is paying for it.
Ah, then it's
definitely not too much.
[music playing]
Hi.
Hi, [inaudible].
Good to see you.
Come on, Diane.
Time to introduce
the man himself.
Oh my god, Diane McGowin
actually has stage fright.
- Knock 'em dead, Diane.
- Nobodies going to believe it.
So here's the gal I have
to thank for putting together
such a terrific evening.
I don't suppose you
remember my party?
What party?
Diane's not political.
It's part of her charm.
OK, let's go.
Diane, relax.
Let's hear it for Diane.
[cheering]
I'm sorry.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Is this 555-0196?
Yeah, mom?
Who is this?
So what happened?
Well, I got there
and Jimmy was there.
And mom said she was OK but
she was really freaked out.
Did she know who you were?
Yeah, of course
she knew who I was.
What happened at the thing?
Why'd she call you
in the first place?
Well, Ginny says that she like
froze on stage, on the podium.
JACK: You mean,
like, stage fright?
Yeah, and then she ran out,
like right through the crowd.
JACK: She just ran away?
Yeah.
JACK: Did she talk
about [INAUDIBLE?
No, she didn't.
You know Mom.
She said she was OK.
She didn't want
to talk about it.
But she didn't talk at all.
JACK: Did you tell her you knew?
I didn't what to say.
She wouldn't talk about it.
She was-- she was
quiet the whole way home.
JACK: You guys haven't seen her
taking any pills or anything,
have you?
- Give me a break.
Mom's never taken anything
stronger than an aspirin.
All the stress working
for those lousy lawyers.
Now she's losing it.
Somebody doesn't
just lose it overnight.
It's not overnight, dammit.
She's been losing it
for a long time now.
I've got Alzheimer's disease.
JACK: Diane?
Diane?
[dog barking]
What you doing, Scampy?
Diane?
What are you doing in here?
This can be very
dangerous, you know.
I was just thinking about
when I was a little kid.
And we used to go to Grandma's
every Sunday, everybody, aunts,
uncles, cousins,
the whole family.
I loved being part
of a big family.
We'd have dinner and
it would get late.
And my dad would drive us home.
And I'd curl up in the
back seat, close my eyes,
and I'd fall asleep.
Then we'd turn into
that long driveway
and I'd wake up and see my
house with the trees all around.
And it felt so safe.
You scared the hell out of me.
Sorry.
I don't know about this
Alzheimer's thing, Diane.
Well you're-- you're really
the smartest person I know.
I mean, even now, you've
still got a real high IQ.
And you know, nobody
has to know about this.
It's nobody's business.
You know, the next
time you're having
a spell or something like that,
you can just stay at home.
I'm going to die in a very
degrading, horrible way.
Oh, who says that?
I am.
I'm going to end
up like an infant.
Come on.
You're not going to
end up like an infant.
I am, Jack.
And you need to know that.
I need to know
that you know that.
It's an awful lot to take
in all at once, isn't it?
I mean, I'm sorry if I'm not
acting the way I'm supposed to.
I'm doing the best I can.
You didn't even tell
me in the first place.
Because you don't hear me.
I don't know how many years
it's been since you've heard me.
You've always got to get
your digs in, don't you.
OK, I didn't
tell you because I
don't feel I can count on you.
You're not there and I'm
scared because a really
big thing is coming
and I'm scared
you're not going to be there.
Are you?
Never really ever needed
anybody but yourself.
Is that your answer?
OK.
It's great.
I got a disease that
sounds like a beer.
It stinks.
Let me count the ways.
What are you going
to do for money?
Well, you know, I mean we've
got Jack's military pension.
And you know, he's
making enough.
Oh, bull.
It's always been
on your shoulders.
I talked to the partners.
We've agreed to give you
six months at full salary.
What?
We took a vote.
It was unanimous.
You don't have to do that.
There's no discussion.
Thank you.
I don't know what to say.
I don't know
what to say either.
I'm-- I'm sorry, Diane.
I'm just so sorry.
Toodaloo.
Want a cup of coffee?
I've already got one.
Don't forget, not a word about
my quitting to your father.
I know, I won't.
I still don't see
why not, though.
Because I said so, OK?
He'll just worry
about the money.
Well, maybe you should
start thinking about selling
grandma and grandpa's house.
It's been five years
since grandpa died, right?
Hell no, I'm not
going to sell the house.
Where would Grandma live?
Mom, Grandma's dead.
That's right.
Anyway, I don't want
your father to know.
Or your brother.
OK, what about Paula?
Paula.
I don't know where Paula is.
You haven't heard from her?
No
Are you sure?
Yes I'm sure.
What's wrong with you?
After a coffee we're going
to go for a walk, right?
I'm going to take him
for a walk in a bit.
Let me have him.
I'll take him for a walk.
Mom, no.
What?
Oh, you never know
where we'd end up.
I'm sorry, it's just--
I'd never do
anything to hurt him.
I know.
I know that.
Let's all go for a walk.
I don't want to go for a walk.
TELEVISION: Dr. Kevorkian--
I'm going to bed.
TELEVISION: To a
heart monitor then put
an intravenous tube in her arm.
He said she was
unconscious in 25 seconds
and died in five or six minutes.
Dedicated teacher all her
life, 56-year-old Adkins
was diagnosed with
Alzheimer's disease a little
over a year ago.
However, family
member she insisted--
No.
TELEVISION: That she was a
rational mind when she made
the decision to take her life.
They have made an
official request
to the district attorney hoping
there will be no prosecution.
Detroit city council
today voted on a measure
that would fund more than 15--
Have Lisa's parents said
anything to you about me?
No.
Do you-- do you
feel embarrassed?
Because I know your dad does.
Why do you say that?
Well, it's obvious.
He doesn't want anyone
at the plant to know.
He said when I'm having
one of my spells, you know,
I should just stay in my room.
And I'm-- I'm
embarrassed, you know?
I feel ashamed.
Mom, I have never been ashamed
of you, not even for a minute.
Even when you danced
with Benji Perkins
at my 12th birthday party.
I did, didn't I?
Janet Jackson, Control.
I was a happening girl.
You can remember that?
Oh yeah, I just can't remember
what I had for breakfast.
I don't know what
I'm going to be like.
So what?
Aren't you scared?
Your sister didn't
even want to let me
take the baby out for a walk.
Well you know, I hit a
tree at 65 miles an hour.
So not a lot scares me.
Are you scared?
You know, I think that
if you could rely on dad
a little bit more,
maybe this other stuff
wouldn't be so scary to you.
Your dad and I do just fine.
Now go to bed.
Go on.
I'm not leaving while
you're still scared.
Then I'm going to bed.
OK, I'll go to bed.
OK.
You always make me feel better.
Thank you.
[music playing]
You want me to pick up
something for dinner tonight?
I don't care.
I'm running late.
I'll see you, then.
[alarm ringing]
Keys.
Watch.
Earrings.
Dog out.
Wallet.
OK.
I got some take out.
I had a long day.
I'm not very hungry.
[clock ticking]
[alarm ringing]
Keys.
Purse.
Earrings.
Wallet.
Dog.
I'm going to put
you on new medication.
Hopefully you'll get some relief
from the most severe symptoms.
This medication seems
to be doing that.
It's had some good results
from people in your age group.
My age group?
Are there a lot of
people in my age group?
Not a lot.
Some people?
I'd really like to talk to them.
I don't know, Diane,
there are privacy issues.
Well, I'd sure be willing
to give up some of my privacy
to have somebody I could
share this stuff with.
I bet you--
I bet you you'd
find at least some
of your patients who
feel the same way.
This Alzheimer's thing, it's
really isolating, you know?
People get lonely.
Linda?
Yes, hi.
Hi.
Thanks for coming
and meeting us here.
He really loves this place.
He never would have
come to your house.
Oh, I like it here, too.
Is that him, there?
Yes.
So, should I stay?
No.
I really appreciate
what you're doing, Diane.
Albert needs this.
To be honest, I need this.
So should I come
back about 3:00?
I don't know, OK.
OK.
Don't let him scare you.
Hi.
I'm Diane McGowan.
We have the same
neurologist, Dr. Newman.
Your sister says
you like this place.
Does she?
I really like
coming here, too.
I used to bring my kids
here in the winter.
You want to go for a walk?
It's your party.
I'll just be quiet.
Somehow I doubt that.
I taught history at
State University.
They tell me I spoke
four languages.
Times have changed.
Awhile ago I wandered away
and was gone for three days.
Boy, I haven't done that yet.
Ah, but do you know
that for certain?
I went through a
divorce, you see.
My wife left me when I
couldn't teach anymore.
I couldn't convince
her that tying my shoes
was an adequate substitute for
her tenure on the Arts Council.
Boy, I'm sorry.
Don't be.
She was right.
Who could blame her?
I'm resigned to dying from
this pernicious illness.
I only hope my
deterioration is rapid.
I'm thinking of taking
up smoking again,
eating lots of nitrates,
hasten the process.
Look, you know, we
could change all that.
We could spend a lot
of time together.
We could take walks.
We could listen to music.
We could start our
own music society.
What kind of music do you like?
17th century, earlier.
Luca Marenzio.
Oh yeah?
When I was gone, I
slept in a laundromat
with my sister's dog.
The dog never came home.
They never found him.
We seem to be in the
same sinking ship.
Yeah, well, that
that's why I wanted
Dr. Newman to introduce us.
I was hoping maybe we
could help each other.
So, so is this OK with you?
Can we meet sometimes?
You want to be friends?
Can't promise
I'll remember you.
That's OK.
Then we'll start over.
ALBERT: Hello, Diane.
It's Albert Marelli.
I wanted to call
before I forget.
I would like to
get together again.
And for our music
society, I don't
mind listening to something
light like Alban Berg.
Yes.
Alban Berg.
Get the ball, you all.
Yay, team.
Hi.
Casual Friday?
Yeah, I got home early.
Yeah, the heating
system broke down at work.
I about froze my buns off.
Thought we might
go out for Chinese.
I could use a little
hot and spicy.
I can-- I can make dinner.
I know you can.
I just thought it might
be nice for a change.
Just the two of us.
OK.
Good deal.
What time should I pick you up?
DIANE MCGOWIN: So
now he's living
with his sister and her family.
He's had it a lot
longer than I have.
Anyway, he was
diagnosed some time ago.
What I was thinking
was that we could
all get together for dinner
or something, you know?
You and me and Albert and--
and-- I forget her name.
But I don't see the point.
They're very
interesting people.
But what would
we have in common?
Hello, anybody home?
Huh?
I'll be right back.
I'm going to the ladies room.
Are you OK?
I don't know.
Where were you?
I just went to get the car.
You just left me there.
What did you do that for?
I didn't leave you.
You did it on purpose.
Oh stop.
Go, get out of here.
Go on.
I will-- just, get out of here.
Wait.
You bastard.
I don't know how to get home.
[car honking]
[music playing]
So I sent out tons of e-mails
to all these neurologists all
across the Midwest
trying to convince them
to start support groups, right?
And I got an answer from this
one doctor in Minneapolis.
He wants me to come and talk
to some of his patients,
just for a couple of days.
But I don't know, you know,
Jack can't get off work.
And I don't know.
You think I should go alone?
You'll go.
You'll fret about it.
You'll talk it to death.
But you'll go.
What's the worst thing
that could happen?
Well, I could
lose it completely.
I could make a complete
fool of myself.
I could drool and fall on
my face and forget who I am.
You don't drool.
Even I don't drool.
How do you know?
Who would tell you?
You would.
I guess I would.
Want some coffee?
Oh yeah.
Two coffees, please.
My treat today.
Thank you.
No, $40 for two coffees?
Not enough?
- Much too much.
- You do it.
The bills all look alike to me.
OK, I'll do the bills.
You have to do the coins.
I'm no good at coins.
Between the two of us, we
almost make a whole person.
Thanks.
So this is it.
This is where I gave
my scintillating
lectures to several hundred
of Michigan's finest.
It's so beautiful.
I was known for my
one on one counsel.
My students meant
a great deal to me.
Mind you, that was when
I still had a heart.
No more?
Like, um, like--
who's that fellow
over the rainbow?
Oh, the Tin Man.
Absolutely empty in here.
Scarecrow.
Just stuffing,
nothing but stuffing.
Hey, Albert, why don't you
come to Minneapolis with me?
Are you out of your mind?
Natch.
I got Alzheimer's, remember?
You could come, though.
You wouldn't get lost.
We can stay in the same room.
You should do it.
It's a chance to
make a difference.
Listen, if we can
find the airport,
we can have a swell time.
We can't go to Minneapolis
that weekend because they got
me on the rotation schedule.
What, you can't
get two days off?
No, I tried.
Some of the guys are
still on winter vacation--
It's OK, I'm
going with Albert.
- That's ridiculous.
- Why?
It's just for two days.
I think it'll be really
fun for both of us.
He's even worse off
than you are, isn't he?
Well, how would you know?
You've never even met him.
Because you're the one
that told us all about him.
Dad, this is a
lot more important
than some guy's vacation.
Get off the schedule and go.
Stay out of it.
It's got nothing to do with you.
The doctors arranged
for the whole thing.
We're going to be picked
up at the airport.
We'll be driven all over town.
We'll be brought
back to the airport.
We'll be supervised the whole
time like good little kids.
Mom, that's not what he meant.
Give me a little
credit, will you?
The answer is no.
Did anyone hear
me ask a question?
I don't think so.
Thank you, Mrs. McGowin.
Room 502.
Oh, there isn't
any number on here.
I know, it's a
safety precaution.
That way if you lose it, no
one knows what room it goes to.
Not even us.
Would you mind just writing the
number in there for me please?
And on his too?
Thank you.
I thought you said
we'd stay together.
We are, but I
couldn't tell her that.
What are you doing?
It's going to
be too difficult.
What do you mean?
What are all these?
The notes for my
speech tomorrow.
You're not going to
give a lecture, Albert.
Nobody wants you
to give a speech.
You have no right to do that.
I wasn't I going to read them.
Damn right, you weren't.
Look, all you have to do is
just speak from your heart.
I have no heart.
I told you, it was
the first thing to go.
Of course you have a heart.
Think of your students.
Think of those students you took
out of that enormous classroom
and helped.
Diane, I want silence.
Yes, professor.
I'm not speaking to your
little gathering tomorrow.
It's just not going to happen.
Albert?
Excuse me, sir, have
you seen Doctor Marelli?
He's about six feet tall
and he's wearing pajamas?
No ma'am, I
haven't seen anyone.
No one's been down here
in quite some time.
Thank you.
This is a lovely hotel, but
you have to go so far to pee.
One of the hardest
things for me right now
is that I can't
communicate with my family
at all, especially my husband.
You know, I try to tell him
what's going on with me and he
just--
it's like he doesn't believe me.
He just-- he doesn't hear me.
Aren't you worried about what
your husband is going to do,
if he's going to stay with
you and take care of you
when you can't even
pick up a spoon anymore?
I mean, how is he
going to do that when
you can't get through to him?
We can't be sure
anybody's going to do it.
And my sister has been
taking care of me.
And she's been wonderful.
But the other day she got
irritated and she said,
you told me that before.
And I knew from
that moment on, she
was not going to stick around.
Why didn't he talk?
Nobody has to talk.
I have a heart, Diane.
I know.
In the beginning,
I was adrift,
in limbo, just nothingness.
And then you.
And then I came alive again.
That's when it all
began, when I met you.
For me, too, that's
when it happened.
Yes?
Yes.
That's it.
That's good.
I love what you
said this afternoon.
What did I say?
You don't know remember?
Not a word.
Tell me.
All the right things.
You said all the right things.
You know, we could--
we could work off
into the sunset
but we'd never
find our way back.
Jack?
What?
Oh hi.
Hi.
You're back early.
No, I'm right on time.
You didn't call.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, we were
worried about you.
Oh.
So how'd it go?
It was wonderful, a lot
of really interesting people
to care about?
How'd your friend make out?
Just fine.
He was fine.
So you're glad you went, huh?
Yeah, I'm really glad.
Yeah, there was-- there was
this interesting discussion.
Everyone's talking about
who was going to take care
of them, you know, when they--
later when they
couldn't do it anymore.
And so I was
thinking, you know, we
should talk about
that because you know,
someone's going to
have to brush my hair,
feed me, brush my teeth,
wipe the drool off my chin.
So who do you think
is going to do that?
Well you know,
maybe we can get
a part time nurse or a
medical student or somebody
like that, huh?
Yeah, well, I was
thinking more you know, a--
about you.
I was thinking, are you
going to be there, you know,
to hold me when I
forget how to breathe?
What are you laying all this
on my now for, for God's sake,
you just came through the door.
Well, I'd really like to know.
I need to know.
But you're doing
great, aren't you?
Well, things are changing.
I haven't been honest with you.
I-- uh, I had to quit my job.
- What?
I haven't been going to work.
Since when?
Since awhile.
I don't know.
I wrote it down.
Oh, well, why didn't you
tell me, for God's sakes?
I'm not the enemy, kid.
So-- so are you--
are you going to--
are you going to
take care of me?
I'll try, OK?
I'll try.
Christ, I put the dog out and
I haven't fed him all day.
[music playing]
Hi, it's so cold.
What are you doing outside?
Oh, are you having a bad day?
I had one yesterday.
Boy, I got lost and I was home.
I couldn't find my own room.
This going to be one of
your nonstop talking days?
No.
I just want to say one thing.
I'm really glad we
went to Minneapolis.
I wanted to thank you
for coming with me.
You may not remember that
you did, but you did.
And I'm grateful.
So, you want to talk
about the university?
The Civil War?
- No.
No.
No?
You want to tell me
who was Alban Berg was?
How about that?
I remembered the name.
Well, we could go for a walk.
I'd love to see some trees.
You want to go to the arboretum?
You won't remember
how to get there.
I do, right now I do.
[music playing]
See, I found it.
Lucky for us they keep
all this alive right
in the middle of the city.
Lucky for us.
Did I ever tell you about
my trees around the house
I grew up in?
Did I ever tell you about
the attic I used to play in?
No, I don't know.
Maybe.
I don't care.
I don't want to hear.
- Oh but come one.
It's really important
to talk to each other,
especially when one
of us is feeling down.
Because you always
have to be the boss.
You're always the
boss, every time.
- What are you talking about?
- You pick the music in the car.
You pick everything.
- You never complain.
You pick where we go.
You pick the days.
I don't-- I don't
like Elvis Presley.
I like, uh--
- Who, Al?
Who do you like?
Tell me.
Tell me all the names.
Tell me all the names of all
the great composers, if you're
so much better than I am.
Shut up.
Bossy, bossy, bossy.
Moller.
I like Moller.
Diane, come back.
[bell ringing]
Albert?
Albert.
Oh, Albert.
Oh, you're so cold.
I'm sorry.
[doorbell rings]
Hi how's he doing?
I was hoping maybe I could take
him for a walk or something?
He's not doing very well.
Really?
Could I-- could I
come in for a minute?
We usually manage to
cheer each other up.
No, Diane, he's
not at home anymore.
Where-- where-- where--
where is he?
Had a severe episode
and we had to put him--
In a hospital?
A facility.
You took him away?
It's a very good
care facility.
No.
We don't need that.
He-- he could-- he could
just come right out of it.
No, Diane.
He's not going to
come out of it.
He had absolutely
no idea who I was.
One day, just one day.
You know?
Tomorrow he could be just fine.
Listen, Miss-- what's your name?
Linda.
Linda, maybe-- maybe
if you can't take
care of him anymore
maybe he could
come live at my house with me.
He's better with me.
No, that's not possible.
Why not?
Don't you love him?
Of course I love him.
You knew this was
going to happen.
We knew it would happen.
We just didn't know when.
I've done the best I could.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about your friend.
Albert.
His name is Albert.
You'll meet other people.
It's not the end of the world.
It's the end of my world.
Albert's gone and
I'm right behind him.
I'm losing a little more
of myself every day.
Pretty soon I won't even exist.
Come on, don't talk like that.
I'll ask Sean to check in
on you later, all right?
No, don't ask him.
Don't ask him anything.
Yeah, I could take care of it.
Just make sure I get
all the paperwork, OK?
Who is that?
Uh, I got to go now.
So I'll see you later.
Bye bye.
That was the night
shift foreman.
I had to check in.
Liar.
I'm not lying.
It was Paula, wasn't it?
What?
I know you've been
talking to Paula.
Sure, I told you I was talking
to her about finding someone
to come in a couple of times a
week and help out around here,
keep an eye on things.
Things, keep an eye on things.
Stop it, Diane.
This ain't funny.
I know the plan.
What plan?
- You and Paula.
- Oh boy.
You're planning to put me
in a facility, aren't you?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
A facility.
Before I get to be
a problem for you.
Don't be ridiculous.
Because I could tell you
right now, I'm not going.
And I can tell you that
nobody is going to force
you to go anywhere, sweetheart.
But I got to go to work now.
Sure you do.
You're such a liar.
Please.
This is getting old.
I'm onto you.
I can't take the
fighting anymore.
You're such a liar.
You're not going to work.
Well, this is the truth.
I'm out of here.
Liar!
I don't know you, lady.
Get out of my house!
Anybody home?
Yeah, Trace, it's dad.
I just got in.
Look, mom's car is not here.
Is she over there?
Nah.
Yeah, that's all right.
Yeah, you're right.
She probably told
me and I forgot.
All right, thanks, love.
Bye bye.
I called Albert's
house but his sister
told me they hadn't seen or
heard from her since yesterday.
Do you know if Diane
had a key to her office?
Well, I didn't think so.
No, Jenny didn't know either.
I called the police.
They won't touch it.
It's too early.
I say it's too soon.
Yeah.
No, it's all right.
Yeah, I will when I hear.
Thank you, Paula.
Mom.
Must have been so hard for you.
Why didn't you tell me?
We didn't have those
roller blade, things.
We had these.
I used to ride like the wind.
There goes Diane,
they used to say.
She's going to
crack her head open.
I remember her.
I remember this girl.
She was fearless and loud.
She had a big mouth, even then.
I led all the sit-ins.
You hear that, Albert?
I never was the silent type.
JACK: Diane?
Diane, where are you?
Hey, Scampy.
How are you doing, kid?
There you are.
Well, it's been awhile.
Come on, I'll help you down.
- No.
- It's me, Jack.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not afraid.
I've been here a long
time, maybe a week.
No, just overnight
Really?
Just one night but I missed
you like it was a week.
Come on.
Let's go home, kid.
You can't just try.
It's not enough.
I know.
I'm going to take care of you.
Whatever happens,
I'll be there for you.
I promise.
Hey, come on.
You got to trust me, see.
Because I heard you.
And now I know what you
meant about being safe.
You did.
You heard me.
Uh huh.
Jack.
I'm not going to lose myself.
I remembered who I am.
No, whatever happens
to my mind or my body,
who I am isn't going to go away.
I'm not going to disappear.
Still Diane.
Diane with
Alzheimer's, but Diane.
I'll never forget you and
what you meant in my life.
And even when you don't
know me, I'll know you.
I promise.
[music playing]