(Multicom jingle)
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] For untold
ages we mined the pure rock,
life blood of our world.
With it, the guild magicians
created the matrix,
a tool so powerful it
fulfilled all of our dreams.
All power has a price.
Ours was a seething shadow,
a living force called The Dark Mist.
In desperation, the totalitarian guilders
built the great seal, and
with their ancient rites
banished The Dark Mist
from the world of light.
Books of prophecy were written
so that none would forget.
The Lord Protector watched
over these words and,
for a time, the world was at peace.
But peace lasts as long as youth.
Houses of kindred color
formed battling for control.
(swords clanging)
Destroying knowledge so
that none could use it,
to seize power.
(marching)
Little of the old world was left
and most had forgotten
what had gone before.
Save one.
Rennick, last of the Lord Protectors.
Rennick dedicated himself
to the scraps that remained,
dark whispers of prophecy.
So haunted, he left love behind
and shut himself away from the world.
(beam striking)
- [Quadrant Shadow] You are called.
Fulfill your destiny.
As you read, so shall you lead.
End times are upon you.
The Dark Mist is rising.
Come.
Assemble, chosen one.
A reader does not fear the words he reads.
So fickle, the chosen.
When you're ready, I shall return.
Peace be by you.
- [Narrator] Thus Rennick sought Pentakis,
once a Lord Protector himself,
now leader of the powerful guild, Magus.
- Here's to many turns, Lord Protector.
We were not aware of any
request for an audience.
- We're on the brink
of end times, Watachi.
I do not need an invitation.
- That was not my meaning, Rennick.
Here lies our way.
- Since when?
- We've made changes.
- I see.
- You have not been announced.
- Fine, announce me!
Pentakis?
(Pentakis laughs)
- Forgive this intrusion, guild mage.
- Rennick, you old scavenger, welcome.
Watachi, take Feltrays.
(creature squawks)
Come in.
Come in, rest your bones.
Rennick, I would like you to meet Priamus,
our most promising adapt.
Priamus, this is Rennick,
otherwise known as the
fabled Lord Protector.
- It is time to gather the Chosen!
- Rennick, please.
- The warning is less than
10 beats and simply sounded.
- [Rennick] The law of probabilities!
The talents required of each
of the Chosen would obviously
be sought in the best candidate
of the current frame of time.
Well, the best in their field would
most likely be well-known.
- You have read very well.
- Very clever, yearling.
You've answered something
that was not asked.
- But, Pentakis, he is right.
It's the only way it fits.
A stone breaker, sealmaker,
obviously a guilder.
Spirit watcher, herbalist.
Something about a homeless warrior.
Look, what's this?
Ponflection will know him.
He who is star shaven with twine.
A power case.
- Storage device.
- A pure rock crystal of proper tone
would work as a storage device.
The Star of Jasper could
be the needed item.
- That will be enough!
- Jasper could be the key.
Pentakis, we must begin immediately.
- I will have no part
in your fool's quest.
(dramatic music)
- What?
- My place is here.
The Dark Mist must be stopped,
but the riddle is not the only answer.
- It is the only answer.
The realm needs you.
- Touching, but hardly accurate.
- But the need of pure rock for closure.
- Priamus.
You are excused.
- Why do you refuse to accept your duty?
- My duty leads me elsewhere.
- I should have expected this from the man
who could cut off the
hand of his own brother.
- Strong words from a bond breaker!
- You're right, I don't need you.
I will bring this before the Great Hall.
Brindey will hear of this.
- Don't leave out, Lady Diamond.
(laughs)
Lord Protector.
- Self preservation we
agree to comprehend!
- You dare disrespect my house?
- My lady Diamond, so
kind of you to join us.
- You tread on sifting sands, Burgandy.
By what authority do
you deny my house entry?
- Small oversight, Lady Diamond.
Only the lower houses were to be barred.
- I trust all was
resolved to your pleasure.
- Words speak to this house.
- What's the meaning
of this, Lady Diamond?
- We are not joined.
We were met at the gate.
He brings us tidings of prophecy.
- The short of it is this.
The Dark Mist is about to break free and
that will pretty much be the
end of all life as we know it.
- Dark Mist, end times?
You speak of bed tales told
to wet the sheet of yearlings.
- It is true!
The Guild has violated their oath.
We must assemble the Chosen.
- We have seen the words of
prophecy, Lord Protector,
but they do not support your rantings.
- What are you talking about?
- The reader has studied
from the Cabal of Valdur
and disagrees with you, my lord.
- As does most of the realm, it seems.
(laughing)
- Show me these words.
(clapping)
- Bring the reader!
- Lord Protector.
- Rise, Mariana.
- Turns have been very kind to you.
- Your words are fair.
- Yes, he's quite the
silver-tongued suitor
when he wants something.
- What words do you hold?
- Most is as you say, Lord Protector.
The signs point to a
coming crisis of import.
- Please, Mariana, we do
not have time for ceremony.
Are the end times upon us?
- From the words I have been given.
- A reader shall not fear what she reads.
Yes or no?
- No, a reader shall not fear.
The signs are not as you say.
The fault must lie in your
definitions of key phrases.
- Mariana!
- There, you see.
The reader has spoken.
- We are done.
- We are not done!
What is this you read?
- Please, Lord Protector.
- You all defy the prophecy!
- You have fulfilled your
duty, Lord Protector.
We choose to follow another path.
- There is no other path!
- Don't, Rennick!
(glass breaking)
(woman screaming)
- Are you part of these
lies, too, my lady?
- Take him!
- Guards!
(growling)
- Call off your men!
(weapons clanging)
- It's an assassination attempt!
(man groans)
(panther growling)
- I don't need your help!
- Yes, doing so well on your own.
- Duck!
(weapons clanging)
Here, catch!
- Kill him!
- Rennick, over here.
- Can't you all stop one man?
(groaning)
(fabric ripping)
(groans)
(playful music)
- Speak a word and your dead.
- What is it you're doing?
- Shh, be quiet.
They'll tire of looking
and I'll be on my way.
(man groans)
(cow moos)
- Uh, they seem to be quite determined.
- You don't wanna push me here.
I'm already three steps past
too far with blood on my sword.
Have I made my point?
(laughs)
(slapping)
- You there!
What's so funny?
- It's a private joke.
- Well, I for one could
certainly use a good laugh.
- Yeah, why don't you tell us?
- Now.
- What, and have to explain it 10 times?
Now, you lads look like men of a keen eye.
May I offer you some of my choice items?
This little bauble, for instance,
this comes from the furthest
reaches of the Third Wood.
Hey, you over there, clear off!
- There he is!
(sighs)
- Ponflection, you know me.
Upon reflection you will know him.
- You can go away now.
- Quite a powerful talent
for a simple merchant.
Who are you?
- I'm three steps passed too
far so don't you push me.
Now go save the world.
- I think you owe me some
answers, Mr. Malthon, is it?
What do you know of the prophecy?
- I owe you nothing and I just
helped you if you'll recall.
Hey!
Will you watch where you're going?
- Malthon.
Malthon.
- [Malthon] What are you staring at?
- Malthon, is it?
You know, I once read a tale
of a great spell weaver,
best in the land,
that is until his own brother,
Pentakis, cut off his hand.
Nohtlam was his name.
He managed to escape and
hasn't been seen since.
(laughs)
Come to think of it, a wagon like this
would make a very good disguise.
- Are you finished?
- Couldn't you have come
up with something better
than to have your own
name spelled backwards?
- I'm sure I could if my name was Nohtlam.
But as you can see I have two hands.
- Yes, but you know of the riddle.
- What, that makes me some
kind of rogue techno wizard?
- Where did you find this?
- Um, I'm a trader, I trade.
- Is this really the True Cabal?
- If that's what it
says, that's what it is.
- You know where to find
this, were there any more?
Can you take me there?
- In the Lost City of Valdur,
maybe, you have to look.
No, go find it yourself.
Now, did I miss anything?
- You've read all those then?
- Of course.
- Well, then you know!
If you've read the books, you know!
- Really, and where do
you see that written?
- What is it with everyone?
- Keep your voice down.
- Why should I?
The world is coming to an end!
I would love to at stay home
with slippers and cream, too,
but I have no choice.
- You don't want me.
- I will not let you walk away.
- No, no, no!
God, no!
No, no.
You will not interfere.
- Sorry.
- No, stay away!
Oh, no.
Goddammit, no, no!
(choking)
No!
Alright, alright, I'll help.
(panting)
- I said I was sorry.
- Right.
Look.
Do you happen to have a plan?
- Yes.
I go to appeal to the Lower Houses.
- There are no Lower Houses.
Opal and his scavengers
have all but wiped them out.
- Then I'll go to the clans.
- Forget it.
This is your show, Lord Protector.
Whether you want it or not.
As you read so shall you lead.
Remember that?
Don't ask.
Alright, look.
I know where you can find a fighter.
I will help you that
far and then I am done.
Is that clear?
Good.
We should move on.
Hop in the back.
(singing in foreign language)
- You're just full of
surprises, aren't you?
- Do you no longer practice the art?
You're going to need it.
(cow grunting)
(singing in foreign language)
(zooming)
(swords clanging)
- This is a waste of time,
it can't be the place.
- The man you are looking for is
known to favor the atmosphere here.
(glass breaking)
- We are looking for a hero.
- No, you are looking for a fighter.
(crowd cheers)
(crowd applauds)
- [Crowd] Boo!
- My turn.
- [Crowd] Yay!
(glass breaking)
- You silly cretins
wouldn't recognize real art
if it reared up and bit ya!
Not a bit of originality.
No style!
- What do you mean?
- Terrible form.
- Him?
(swords clanging)
- C-minor.
(clanging)
No, C-minor, are you deaf?
Ah.
(clanging)
(upbeat music)
Ah, Harold of Burgandy.
I bid you,
go back to your master and give him this.
(smashing)
Head up.
Chest.
(smashing)
(clanging)
- What?
(woman groans)
(crowd cheers)
- When we who eat are hungry.
When we who drink are dry.
(clanging)
When we who blow are frozen.
Our answer to nefarious Opal
and his lot will be the same.
(groaning)
(crashing)
We give you back defiance for defiance.
Menace for menace.
Blow for blow.
Ha!
(swords clanging)
Woo hoo hoo!
Ole!
(swords clanging)
Ya!
(groaning)
- Ya!
(swords clanging)
(shouting)
- Ha!
(men screaming)
(crowd cheers)
(crowd applauds)
Toast to the pig.
Toast to the victor!
(crowd cheers)
(crowd applauds)
Bow.
- [Man] Bravo, bravo!
- And now I wish to retire.
Would you be so kind as to remove
your fingers from my jacket.
- Whoa, easy friend.
- Or I will remove them from your hand.
- We're just trying to help.
- Ah.
Well, gentlemen.
Are you a merchant?
- I travel.
- Ah.
A poor merchant.
- Can I buy you a drink, master?
- You may call me Dunnigan.
And the price of this courtesy?
- A few words of conversation.
- I can tell you're the long-winded type.
Better make it a bottle.
- Ah, yes, here we are.
(instrumental music)
(wine splashing)
(mugs clashing)
- No.
- No?
Wait, did you just say no?
I don't believe this.
- Nothing against you, my friend.
I'm honored that you consider
me one of the Chosen,
but I am already sworn to a quest
by the balls of my father.
- You brought us to him?
- This place was your idea.
- I am Dunnigan Bragg, the last living
heir of the clan of the blade.
- Makers of the legendary dressine, yes!
But you can't make it anymore, can you?
- Do not test my honor!
- Your family's honor couldn't be saved
by a hoard of Darginian virgins.
- An insult!
- Temper, temper.
- Stop it, both of you!
- I have not lost my ardor.
I suffer from an absence of material.
It's a rare, golden flower.
Furnished from our rarest world.
It is my quest to find it.
Or die in the attempt.
- I am loathe to bring this up,
but Rennick will be
traveling to many dismal
out of the way places on his quest.
You might just find your weed.
- You are an extremely irksome presence.
- And you are a drunk.
You'd be better off without him, Rennick.
- It shall be an honor
to assist you, Lord.
(crashing)
- Thank you so much for your support.
(cow grunting)
- There, I've helped him!
Have a nice quest.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
- Are you done?
(cow grunting)
- I'll help you to the edge
of town and that's final.
- Right, whatever you say.
Tell me, what's with you and the glove?
- It's.
Don't ask!
(dramatic music)
Wagon, wagon, get him to the wagon.
- Hold, merchant.
Is this your wagon?
- This is the Lord Protector.
Now let us through.
- Take him!
- I probably should have told you
I had a bit of a run in with Pentakis.
- Guys, to the fight!
Charge!
(swords clanging)
(groaning)
- Dunnigan, we're out of here, now!
(swords clanging)
Brace for it!
(ground rumbling)
Come on!
(panting)
- You know, I shall flee no further.
You shame me, Lord Protector.
- That was some shield you
wove back there, Malthon.
- It wasn't me.
I said it wasn't me.
- Would anyone care for a drink?
- Look, Malthon.
Do you know a quick way outta here?
(laughs)
- Anywhere we go now there
are at least 27 gates,
five causeways, and 15 tunnels
between us and the outer walls.
- All heavily-guarded, no doubt.
- No doubt.
- I smell a fight, cheers!
- Well, we're awfully popular
for a bunch of loaners.
- Look, don't draw your swords.
Maybe we can bargain with them.
- Charge.
- Right.
- Hold!
- Well, Rennick, I see you found
some nice friends to play with.
I've come to help you.
- My lady of the House of Diamond.
The tales of your beauty
are as hollow lies
when confronted by your presence.
Blade Master Dunnigan at your service.
- I am honored.
Look, Rennick, manners.
Excellent work, Austin.
All are dismissed.
(clapping)
- Bravo.
You might as well call
them all right back here.
We don't need your help.
- Really?
I can go wherever I choose, can you?
- My lady has made an excellent point.
- She is not part of this prophecy.
She has no place here!
- Do you dare to walk away from me again?
- Oh, perhaps I should just
leap from the nearest window!
- We accept your aid.
- No, we don't.
- Yes, we do.
- Then it's settled.
- Rennick can be so stubborn sometimes.
- I've even thought of the
perfect disguises for you.
- Just to the city gates
and then you must go back to safety.
- We'll see.
(grumbling)
Bearers, up!
- One!
Two!
Three!
(grunting)
- There, I'm done.
- Yes, far enough.
Now, take your shopping and go.
- Such a way with words.
No.
(Lady Diamond singing)
- Someone should tell her
we're trying to remain hidden.
- Oh, now it's we, aye?
You tell her.
- Cowards, the both of you.
Your pardon, my lady.
- [Lady Diamond] Is that
you, Dunnigan, dear?
- At your service.
I regret that the pleasure
of your song, alas,
endangers the wellbeing of our persons.
- Oh, that's a good one!
(dramatic music)
(fire sizzles)
I don't believe I allowed myself
to be roped into this bloody.
- An excellent time for an
herbal scouting exhibition.
- So.
What's with old grumpy glove?
- Says his name is
Malthon, he's a merchant.
Plus other talents.
First I thought he was Nohtlam.
- (chuckles) The rogue?
Rennick, he has two hands, both very real.
- Yes, I know, I know, but.
There's something not straight about him.
I just can't put my finger on it.
He's the equal of any guilder I know.
Maybe even better than
your friend, Pentakis.
- I didn't come here to argue.
Believe it or not, I've come to help!
- All I've heard from you is argument.
- That's because you've
forgotten how to listen.
- I know how to listen!
It is the rest of the
realm that has gone deaf!
- Rennick, in case you haven't
noticed things have changed!
Your self-imposed exile has made you blind
to the very world that
you are trying to save!
- I don't know why I even bother.
Your apathy has sealed our doom.
- You're simply adorable when
you're being melodramatic.
All is not doomed.
There's others that might help.
- I have enough riddles to deal with.
What others?
- [Malthon] Perhaps she could tell us.
- Mariana?
- We found her snooping
alongside the road.
- What we?
- Hear me, Lord Protector.
I come by firth oath, fealty to the lord.
- Malthon, let her go!
- Fealty to the lord.
Here, warm yourself by the fire.
- How did you find me?
- Long has my mind
held the key waiting for
the leader of the Chosen.
- [Rennick] I am no leader.
- It has always been
for a protector to lead.
There is more I have to tell.
After your departure from the Great Hall,
Pentakis branded you rogue,
claiming you had stolen his property
and kidnapped his son, Priamus.
- Priamus?
Priamus is his son?
- He hunts for you,
demanding your hands in
payment for your crime.
- How original.
- [Mariana] You must move quickly.
When you get to Val--
- We are not visiting the lost cities.
We travel to Third Wood.
- But your fighter?
- Dunnigan Bragg, at your service.
- Yes, we have a fighter.
We need a hero.
Do you know of Ravelle?
- But, Birdwood, our
influence is thin in Outland.
- I smell a fight!
- Light!
(muffled shouting)
Outsiders!
(screaming)
Dunnigan, no!
You gotta get outta here!
- There's more!
- Not now.
Mathlon, back up Dunnigan.
- Send me to wait on Dunnigan?
- You sure you wanna continue?
The risk could be great.
- Travel safely, friend.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Those are my things.
- They don't want us, they want stuff.
(smashing)
- Then why not give them your stuff?
- Oh, but you have so much.
Ah!
- No!
- I'm about to teach these
ruffians proper sword technique!
- Use your talents, Rennick.
We need it now!
(static whizzing)
- [Lady Diamond] No, no, hey, hey, hey!
That's mine.
- Do it!
- [Lady Diamond] Give it to me!
Give it back!
It's mine!
Come on.
It's mine.
No, don't, no, no!
- Dunnigan, we're pulling out!
Dunnigan, leave it!
- [Lady Diamond] No, no,
no, put me down, Dunnigan!
- Follow me!
To a safe place.
(water splashing)
(savages hooting)
(dramatic music)
- Malthon, what exactly
are you looking for?
- An access tunnel.
In ancient times, they
were used to carry water.
Now, they're all but forgotten.
- Except by you.
How fortunate.
(chanting)
- Ah.
Quickly, my head is killing me.
You know, I wouldn't
want somebody's blade arm
to be severed.
(chanting)
- Light.
- Are you sure these tunnels aren't used?
- Absolutely.
I travel these ways all the time.
- I don't like tunnels.
- Get used to it.
Besides, this way no one can track us.
(animal squawking)
(crickets chirping)
(chanting)
Whoa.
Oh, the ancient signals work.
Oh.
- I have him.
I need official--
- Move aside.
No!
Don't go in!
Watachi, did you get his location?
- No, I'm--
- Find them!
- I regret I was--
- Do you hear me?
Find them.
(thrilling music)
- [Narrator] With papers in hand,
they reached the border of the Outland.
From there, they would
pass into Third Wood,
a fearful place of magic and mystery
in search of Ravelle, the healer.
(eagle calling)
As for my Priamus, it
was then he discovered
how far-reaching
Pentakis's grip had become.
The mark of Pentakis served
as Priamus's safe passage.
They searched, and as
time passed hope waned,
tempers flared.
(wolf howling)
(dramatic music)
Only Malthon could hear
the voice of the beast.
And thus they were led into
the dark heart of Third Wood.
- At last, welcome!
I've heard you coming for
the last turn of sand.
I'm Ravelle, come in please to my home.
Be warm and eat.
- Our many thanks to you.
I carry the title Lord Protect--
- No need for formal talk now.
Come in, please.
We'll get to know each
other by a warm fire.
(door creaking)
Pendil, that's enough.
You'll eat me out of house and home.
Zesty, my compliments, hostess.
Are you going to eat that, wagon man?
- How can you eat this swill?
(banging)
- You be nice.
- Brisk ale, anyone,
to top off the evening?
- Legendary!
- Now, tell me why you journeyed
so far to talk of prophecies.
- The riddle points to you
as a member of this quest.
We are the last hope of
defeating the Dark Mist.
- I don't understand.
I'm just a simple herbalist.
- Herbs?
My lady, hostess, do you mind
if I go through your bins?
I'm looking for the root
of a rare golden flower--
- They're back there.
Help yourself.
You want me to go with you
because of some dandy tale?
That's ridiculous.
- I know it seems strange
to have all of our lives
affected by something so remote,
but I've made my decision.
The same as everyone else I guess.
(crashing)
(glass shattering)
(metal objects clanging)
- Well, I'm not picking him up.
- Rest here tonight.
I'll give you my answer in the morning.
- Yeah.
A little sleep.
(dramatic music)
- [Pentakis] They are with you now?
- All but your son.
- [Pentakis] Don't concern
yourself with Priamus.
You'll find my son, he has
gone ahead to the caves.
Show me the talisman.
Ah, so that is the key.
- Rennick says we'll face the Dark Mist.
You didn't mention that, Pentakis.
Why?
- Ravelle, you are a trained assassin.
Why would a hint of danger bother you?
- Because I wasn't paid to die.
What's to keep your Mist spawn
from eliminating me, as well?
- You should not fear magic
for magic will protect you.
Catch.
It shall identify you as belonging to me.
Report when you make final contact.
- You tell me the target now and
we'll be done with them tonight.
- No!
I need them, for now.
Do I need to employ someone else?
- I don't break my contracts.
- See that you don't.
- Put on the amulet, Ravelle.
I'm with you always.
(scoffs)
(dramatic music)
(clears throat)
- May I be of some assistance?
- You should be sleeping.
- I'm a late sleeper.
Pretty handy when cutthroats are about.
- And what do you mean by that?
- Oh, I often sleep in
disreputable places.
No offense to you, of course.
- None taken.
I just like my guests to be comfortable.
I'm so sorry I woke you.
- You are too kind.
I thought I heard voices.
- I talk to myself.
- So many lovely girls
suffer from that same malady.
- Comes from living alone.
- Alone, lonely, wild woman of the wood.
I know all about reminiscing.
Can't bear to think of
such an honest woman
as yourself feeling that way.
From now on, I shall be
your constant companion.
- I haven't said I'm going.
- Oh, I think it's safe to say your going
and I will be with you always.
- Oh, how clumsy of me.
Are you alright?
- No harm done, mistress.
Accidents will happen.
See you in the morning, Ravelle.
- [Narrator] Dunnigan was right.
Ravelle joined the Chosen.
Rennick led them to an ancient
place of gathering forces
where manmade tunnels joined
with rock from a lost age.
The crystal caves, now
known as a place of evil,
a place to be feared.
- People go in there and
they don't come out again.
- I hate tunnels and
now I don't like caves.
I'll wait out here.
- We all go.
(chanting)
Light.
Alright.
We'll have to split up
into teams to search, uh.
- Move away from there, yearling!
- Malthon, come see what I found.
Techno spawn spy!
Sent no doubt by my thrice-damned brother.
Move away.
- No, see, I understand how it works.
And if we can decipher the correct--
(chanting)
(dramatic music)
(groaning)
(chanting)
(electricity whizzing)
- Malthon!
Stop!
You'll bring the whole place down!
Malthon, enough!
- He is in league with the Guild.
- I know him.
Priamus, if you stop we can talk.
(electricity whizzing)
(groaning)
You alright?
- Just a little shaken up.
- But still delightfully whole.
- Alright, would somebody
tell me what is going on?
Priamus, what are you doing here?
- He's been following us since day one.
I felt him the whole time.
- So that was you?
Oh, I should have known.
- Pentakis claims I've kidnapped you.
- Oh, it was a reasonable
assumption on his part
as I did not share with
him my plan of departure.
- Reasonable?
He wants my hands!
- Well, I'm sorry if my arrival
came at an inopportune time
but if I've read aright you need me.
- Can we just kill him?
- Where's Diamond?
- My lady, Diamond?
- I'm here.
(electricity whizzing)
- [Quadrant Shadow] Welcome to the Chosen.
The repair team is now complete.
- Repair team?
- [Quadrant Shadow] Leader, approach.
- I think i means you.
You are well chosen, but
your gathering has been slow.
Only five lights remain to mend the
promise in Shadow Valley.
Remember, access to the
Tulcarion seal is the key.
- Wait, is that it?
- [Quadrant Shadow] End time is now.
Chosen, heal the brink.
Peace be by you.
- I need a drink.
- Quiet, quiet, I need to think.
Dunnigan, fighter.
Ravelle, healer.
Priamus, mage.
- Not bloody likely.
- Lady Diamond must be
part of it, too, Rennick.
- As what, a storage device?
- Drop dead.
- So, Priamus.
Eh, it seems like you're meant to be here.
- Does that mean we don't
get to kill the Guild spawn?
- Right now we have to figure out how
to find the Shadow Valley.
- We can access the matrix.
- Absolutely not!
- Quiet, Malthon, what
are you talking about?
- Well, the matrix stands before you.
It reflects the energy currents that float
through our world.
This is our greatest discovery.
See, Pentakis learned
of it using the books
that you gave him, Rennick.
- But what does all of that mean?
- We can use the matrix as a doorway
to wherever we need to go.
- Wait, you say you can use it?
Pentakis has trained you as techno-mage?
- I was made for it.
All my genetic codes
were chosen by Pentakis
to yield a mind that could
comprehend the ancient ways.
- Pentakis grew you?
- Well, technically he is my father.
Is that not how it is done?
Uh, if you do not wish
to access the matrix,
another alternative would
be to construct a portal.
- Where do you come up with these ideas?
A construct would be unstable at best.
- I merely state our present options.
- Activate the matrix.
- Of course.
(dramatic music)
(buzzing)
There, now.
Input, Shadow Valley.
(beeping)
- Oh, you've gotta be kidding.
- Is this where the big
fight is supposed to happen?
On the other side of the world?
- We'll be there in moments.
Proper access codes.
(electric shorting)
- What's the matter?
- Oh, I don't know.
This is not right.
Look out!
- Rennick, how nice of you to call.
- Well, well, Pentakis.
I now have proof of your crimes.
Genetic manipulation, the
matrix, crimes for which--
- Careful, Lord Protector, he--
- We are talking!
Such manners.
You learned that insolence from your
short time with Rennick.
Who else is there?
- Oh, Lady Diamond!
- [Rennick] Diamond!
(screaming)
- What ever gave you the
idea you could be a leader?
The Bragg clan?
Poor choice.
- What about me, my brother?
I am one of the Chosen.
- Traitor!
- Rennick, raise the bond.
- Rogue!
Priamus, I created you,
you cannot deny me this.
Give me the location of the seal.
- Don't tell him.
- The Shadow Valley.
- Goodbye, my son.
(laughs)
(ground rumbling)
- Cave in!
- Everybody out!
- My things!
- I think we go that way?
- You think?
- A Groton walk has
more brains than you do.
- Now just try it, little man.
- Put it away, Malthon.
Put it away.
(grunting)
- I must beg your pardon, hostess.
- Just stay away from me!
You, too!
- This is just great.
Dunnigan, keep an eye on things.
- Pentakis.
(creature squawking)
Pentakis, are you there?
- I can barely here you?
Where are you?
- We're in some kind of manmade tunnel.
I'm not sure, but we're heading
for Lady Diamond's southern stronghold.
- We're trying to get a fix on you.
Ravelle, it's time to earn your keep.
Eliminate Dunnigan.
Ravelle!
(creature squawking)
Oh, blast that woman.
Watachi!
- I could not get a fix on them, master.
- No need to worry, Watachi.
She said they were in some
tunnels going to Diamond's.
(laughs)
Oh, very clever, my brother, very clever.
They're in the ancient tunnels.
We will just flood them all.
Here.
(laughs)
And here.
Whoosh!
- Dunnigan.
You startled me.
- I Know you're up to something
and I will find out what it is.
I had no idea your feelings
for me were so strong, my lady.
- I should kill you right now.
Right now.
- I'm sure we'd make
the crossing together.
- Ah!
You, no!
You!
Let me finish, please.
(whimpering)
(sobbing)
Nohtlam.
Yes.
A long time ago.
(laughs)
Uh, I prefer Malthon now.
- Alright, then, Malthon.
I think it is time for that explanation.
Tell the tale.
(sighs)
- This hand.
This hand was a gift.
A gift from the Dark Mist.
Pentakis and I have
fought this battle before.
He won and took my hand in the process.
I went to his secret pool,
a place where the Dark
Mist had penetrated.
(steam blowing)
No!
The Dark Mist sensed my emotions.
It knew what I wanted and it wanted me.
(electricity whizzing)
(screaming)
It talks to me, Rennick.
It wants something.
I don't know how much is me
and how much is it anymore.
I could kill all of you.
Not me, but this thing.
- The hand is part of you, Malthon.
From what I've read of the Dark Mist,
it shadows the needs of the host.
If you kill one of us it is
because you harbor that desire.
It is you.
Take it.
- Wait.
We have to get out of here now.
This is a trap.
Pentakis has found us.
- Priamus, glad to see
you're still with us.
Everybody, we are out of here, now!
- He can't be moved, Rennick.
- We have to.
- He can't, he's hurt!
- The tunnel is going to flood.
- Flood?
I thought you said it was safe?
- Dunnigan, I really don't have time
to debate this right now.
- Doors.
- Wait, he's trying to say something.
- Seal doors.
- Rennick, the doors.
Priamus says seal the doors.
- Doors.
(waves crashing)
(Water flowing)
- (together) What doors?
(waves crashing)
- Panel.
Use the panel.
- It's here!
- Do something, lads!
- Come on!
- Malthon, now!
- That's it, I don't know what else to do.
- Run!
(door slamming)
(sighs)
I hate tunnels.
- [Narrator] With the aid
of Ravelle and her potions,
Priamus quickly regained his strength.
They traveled the tunnels and emerged
near Lady Diamond's stronghold
filled with new hope.
(dramatic music)
(sand blowing)
(fly buzzing)
- The clans gave their word
that this would not happen.
This is the work of Pentakis.
He's killed them all, destroyed my house!
- With new pure rock, we fail.
That is why he destroyed it all.
- You see those?
Solid pure rock.
We don't let him win.
- Malthon, can you
levitate those out of here?
- I suppose we can.
You realize, of course, it
will leave us almost powerless?
Do you really wanna build a portal
if you're gonna be too
drained to walk through it?
- I thrillingly await
your superior suggestion.
How long to build the portal?
- Less than a pass if
we all work together.
Malthon, I could use an extra hand.
- Let's get to it.
- You go on then.
I'll take care of the dead.
(rock sliding)
(groaning)
- You did.
Well.
(crickets chirping)
- Goodbye, my friend.
(fire crackling)
- I smell a fight.
(dramatic music)
(warriors giving battle cry)
- Get to the portal.
Hey, night, die!
Hey, night!
- Portal activated.
(whip cracking)
(soldiers shouting)
- [Rennick] Malthon, hold the portal.
(swords clanging)
- Watch it!
- I'm sorry.
(groaning)
(maniacal laughter)
- Quadrant Shadow, Dash Valley.
- [Quadrant Shadow] Enter access code.
(shouting)
(swords clanging)
(groaning)
(screaming)
(panting)
- That's twice.
- Thanks.
- Couldn't bare the thought of a knife
marring that beautiful back of yours.
(shouting)
(groaning)
- Are you alright?
- Only a flesh wound.
Let's get back to the others.
- Quadrant Shadow, Dash Valley.
- [Quadrant Shadow] Enter access code.
- Why isn't it open?
- It says we require an access code.
- Here, use this!
- Centurion!
- Access granted!
Portal open.
Time allowed for passage 20 turns.
17.
- On the other side.
- 16.
- Come on.
- Please move a little faster.
I cannot guarantee the
integrity of this construct!
Let's go, Dunnigan.
- 12, 11.
- Please hurry.
- [Quadrant Shadow] 10, 9.
(whip cracking)
- Dunnigan!
- [Quadrant Shadow]
Attention, portal closing.
In three, two, one.
(groaning)
- Oh my god.
(panting)
Oh.
(birds chirping)
(groaning)
- You will not be fighting for a while.
- Tell that to the Dark Mist.
- Sometimes in life you
don't have a choice!
- You always have a choice, my lady.
- I believe you dropped this.
- Never really liked it anyway.
(electricity whizzing)
(banging)
- A wise choice.
- For you, for saving my life.
(laughs)
- I believe it is I that should
be giving you the flowers.
It's your herb, you silly man.
The one you've been looking
for to make your dressine.
- Aye.
(laughs)
(groans)
- We better get outta sight.
We leave at dusk.
Make what preparations you.
You can.
(birds chirping)
(fire crackling)
We'll wait another click
or so and then we go.
- A few turns of sand one way or the other
will make little difference.
- You don't have to wait, Rennick.
He's not coming back.
- What did you say to him?
- Don't you understand?
His arm is worthless!
He can't fight!
He left so that we would
stand a better chance.
- I know how he feels.
- Drink this.
It'll help ease the pain.
- I have something infinitely better!
Dressine, that which
gives heart to the hunter,
courage to the worthy,
and beauty to all women.
Drink.
- Dunnigan, what?
- Go on then, drink!
(magical tingling)
- That stuff has some kick.
You do your family proud,
brew master Dunnigan.
- It is superior.
Is there more?
- Plenty for all.
If the lady would oblige.
- It's good to have you back, Dunnigan.
All of you.
I'm no good at speeches, I.
I think you all know what we face.
To friends.
And companions.
It's time we finish this quest.
- [Dunnigan] Okay.
- My Lord Protector, if you'd be so kind.
(door creaking)
(dramatic music)
- Stay your hand.
Allow me to clear the way.
(swords clanging)
(grunting)
(groaning)
- Their made of Dark mist.
- Not much of a defense if you ask me.
Come on then, move across.
(swords clanging)
(shouting)
- Well, it seems the Dark Mist knights
are multiplying exponentially.
- Move across, yearling!
(shouting)
(swords clanging)
- Come on.
Give me your hand.
- Hurry, Malthon!
- Thanks, Malthon.
- Run!
(Lady Diamond shouting)
(warrior shouting)
- I had him.
- I know.
(shouting)
- Dunnigan!
- At last, a worthy challenge.
You travel on, I'll catch up later.
- I won't leave you.
- I can't tell you how touched I am,
but the others need an
assassin of your caliber.
- You knew?
- Can we possibly take this up later?
- You are the most impossible man I have
ever met and I hate you!
- What's that?
I love you, too!
(shouting)
- It's not working.
Pentakis must have altered the codes.
- Step aside.
(electricity blasting)
Knock knock.
(panting)
- Pentakis.
- You are here.
Welcome to end times.
- The final seal.
Pentakis, brother, you know what the
Dark Mist will do if you free it.
- It will do my bidding!
Brother, it is a distinct
pleasure to see you again.
We have so very much to talk about.
Pain.
- No, Father!
The massive Dark Mist bound by
the seal is far too powerful.
You cannot control it.
- I made you too well
and you talk too much.
Air!
(choking)
- Pentakis!
He's a yearling!
- I can make a new one.
Lady Diamond, the most
precious prize of all.
Isn't she beautiful, Rennick?
- Don't you touch her.
- Oh, I will do much more than that.
You will be my conduit to remove the seal.
- Over my dead body.
- Yes, well.
If you insist!
- No!
(groaning)
- God!
- Now the conduit is in place.
I could do with a little more power!
(electricity whizzing)
I have fulfilled the prophecy!
(groaning)
Let the Dark Mist rise!
(electricity whizzing)
(screaming)
- Rennick, stay with me.
- He's killing her!
- The seal.
We have to stop it before
it builds up more power!
(groaning)
- Rennick!
- Where the fuck is the crystal?
More!
Give it everything you got!
(shouting)
(exploding)
- Don't let it pull you in!
- [Priamus] Need a hand?
(shouting)
(laughing)
- Diamond, Diamond!
Oh.
What am I gonna do with you?
- Well, technically the quest is over.
I'm in Seranna, Rennick,
you figure it out.
- Thank you, Priamus.
- You're welcome, uncle.
- [Dunnigan] Would
anyone care for a drink?
- Dunnigan.
Well, go do it.
- Always.
- [Narrator] And thus the Lord
Protector solved the Riddle
of the Chosen and led them to victory,
victory that ensured life
to their world, for a time,
but that is another tale.
(upbeat music)
(thrilling music)
(Multicom jingle)