[film camera flicker]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[soft haunting piano music]
[man softly grunting]
[car seat softly rubbing]
No.
Douglas-
- I'm trying, I'm,
I'm trying...
I don't want you to think
this is about you at all.
Has nothing to do about you.
Don't think about it's
about you for a second.
It's not about you.
It's kinda hard not to when...
What can I do about it?
I don't know, maybe that's
one you can figure out.
[soft haunting piano music]
You open up,
I'll grab the bags.
That's way too much.
I got it.
Just give me the
chips at least, come on.
You can have the chips,
or just take your purse or I'm
not gonna carry it anymore.
Okay.
[soft haunting piano music]
Hey, Vee, where's my suitcase?
[Veronica] I brought
it downstairs, babe.
I had to get ready.
Okay.
[Veronica] Dan's
gonna be here soon,
I wanted to get changed.
Okay.
[Veronica] You want
me to bring it up?
No, I'm good, thank you.
[soft piano music]
- Yay.
- Hi
So Donna found
that photo of us.
I thought we lost it.
Which one?
The one from the
trip before last.
I was, I thought it was gone.
Just found it behind the futon.
Oh.
If I was gonna
lift, was gonna lift
and I'm gonna finish
that script on this trip,
I can just feel it.
Hope so.
Is it too late just to,
just to have Dan go
back to Orange County?
You wanted him to come.
I didn't say yes.
Yeah, you didn't
say no either.
And no decision is a decision.
You don't want Pia
and Dan to come up,
then you should said something.
I said nothing about Pia.
Oh, let me get that for you.
That came off too adamant.
You're the only girl
for me, you know that.
Yeah, sure.
[car softly honks]
Veronica!
- Pia, ready?
- Are we doing this again?
- Veronica!
[Veronica] Veronica!
Veronica!
[soft piano music]
Stop the press, hello.
Jessica Rabbit, hey.
Oh my god, you are a dream.
[Veronica softly laughs]
- Look at you.
- Hello, Douglas.
Smell nice.
Pia.
- Hi!
- Hey!
- Hey.
- Hi, sweetie, how are you?
[Pia] Good, you?
Come here, you douchebag,
come here, missed you.
Hey, babe, babe,
what I tell you?
Bitch-in-love hug.
Whoa, whoa, I'm kidding.
So what are you doing,
you gonna invite us in?
This guy all of a
sudden gets a hot wife
and he's got no manners.
Was gonna help
you with the bag.
She's fine, look at
her, she's hot, look.
This is for you.
We know you don't
know shit about wine.
Dan.
He doesn't, so we
picked this out for you.
Who says I don't
know shit about wine?
I know this wine.
"Who says I don't
know shit about,"
no one has to say it, Dougie.
This guy, you so cute, come
on, show me the house, come on!
[cicadas softly buzzing]
Stop.
You can look, we know
you need to watch this.
See what's happening here.
Give him the neck.
- [softly kissing]
- Hey, baby, we can-
- Okay, okay, you're awesome.
To you, this has been amazing.
Yeah.
Dougie, you've found
a great one, cheers.
You're beautifully
dressed, as always.
She is, well, I just
got one question though.
Doug, when are you
gonna do something
about that shit
around your mouth?
[Pia] Dan.
What, babe, what?
It's getting out of hand,
you said so in the car.
[Pia] No, I didn't.
Well, I happen to like it.
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
Doesn't bother you trying to
find his lips through
all that shit?
Nah, she likes the bush.
She does?
Yeah.
Everyone likes a little
bush nowadays, right?
It's like a
picnic, you have to
go through some
bush to get there.
He should shave the bush-
- No, bad boy.
- It's better to go through.
What's goin' on?
Everyone likes a
little bush, huh, babe?
- Stop it.
- Actually, there's nothing,
she's clean as a.
I love you.
Hey, Dougie, you remember
the Wasserman account
- You remember that-
- Boo!
- What, what, what?
- Yeah, no, we said no.
- We said no-
- Oh, come on, no.
- No.
- Are you serious?
We had one rule.
What's the rule?
[Douglas] You're
such a dick, dude.
You tell me what the rule was.
No talking shop.
- Are you serious about this?
- Or just no talking, period.
No talking?
Geez, listen, Dougie, are
you sure you wanna hear this?
You're a dick.
Am I gonna tell
the story or not?
- Carry on.
- Yes!
Okay, this one Wasserman
account, right?
I've been trying to
land this account
for I don't know how long,
it was Dougie's lead,
he couldn't land it, easy
150 grand a month, easy.
Dougie couldn't land it because
of Tim fucking McNealy, that
prick, remember that guy?
He worked at a different
copier place and he's a dick.
Yeah, well, yeah, but I
thought I was telling the story.
Veer, I'm telling
the story, right?
- Yes, go, go on.
- Baby, babe,
- can I finish the story?
- You have the floor.
Oh my gosh, keep going.
Thank you, so,
right, after you left,
Rob passed it around people's
desks, didn't happen.
Landed on my desk, like
a turd, what do I do?
What do I do, babe?
I know the story, keep going.
Yeah, I go pay
Wasserman a visit, right,
every time I get there,
the jerk-off gatekeeper
says he's got no time.
Every time, no time.
So I wait a couple weeks, and
then, I do the unthinkable.
Can I get a drum roll, please?
I pull out the clipboard.
[Veronica] What's
with the clipboard?
Dougie, you wanna tell
'em or should I tell 'em?
[Douglas softly mumbling]
Should I tell 'em?
Let me tell 'em, let
me tell, okay, okay.
One day, Doug's in some office,
some schmuck's office,
I don't know who.
These people, maintenance
people, walking through,
holding a clipboard,
nobody says nothing, nada.
They just let 'em walk right by.
Dougie here gets the smart idea,
he goes into Office Depot,
Office Depot, or was it...
Office Max.
Office Max, nobody stops
the guy with the clipboard,
or a Mexican with
the leaf blower.
- Oh, what?
- I can say that joke,
because, listen, I can say
that joke, I'm half Mexican.
You guys can't, you
will be canceled,
I'm just stating facts.
What about a white
guy with a leaf blower?
Yes, this also works.
Anyways, I got the clipboard,
I go right past that jerk-off.
I'm in Wasserman's office
and he walks in five
minutes later, right?
- No way.
- Way.
And we're doing the damn thing,
three yeses, I'm in,
this guy won't commit.
Whatever I do, he
will not commit.
Had to give him
everything, everything.
Almost had to let
Pia fuck him here.
I was thinking I had to do it,
and I almost thought I
was gonna do it, but,
I kid, I kid, baby.
- Aw!
- Yeah.
I would never let
him do that, well-
- It's okay, maybe
I wanna do it.
Whoa, pause, babe.
[soft ominous music building]
Dougie knows though,
I don't lose.
Dan Mackie never loses, never.
So, I get this bright idea,
my bulb goes off, I head
down to the corner store,
I grab a deck of cards.
Next meeting, I walk
in with five cards,
Ace, King, Queen,
Jack, 10, all hearts.
You know what that is,
tell 'em what it is.
I don't know.
You know, it's a
royal flush, say royal-
- A flush.
It's a royal flush, whatever,
she's foreign, it's cool.
You can call on any of my guys,
anytime with this hand,
now make it happen.
But each time he calls, I take
one card,
and when I finally
have five cards,
I get to go all in and ask him
for one favor and
he's gotta do it.
We shook on it.
It was a deal,
Dougie, you remember.
So, [softly chuckling]
he used his last
card on Wednesday.
Me, I asked for my
favor yesterday.
I asked for his business.
And this morning,
well, this morning,
I closed that motherfucker!
[Pia speaking French]
Fuck you,
Timmy Fucking McNealy
and that's how you do it.
Can I get an amen?
[Pia speaking French]
Can I get an amen, amen?
[Veronica] Amen.
[Pia speaks French]
I'm sorry, right?
Come on, that's a power move.
Was that a Kanye move?
I'm like Kanye.
That's, congratulations,
that's huge.
Yeah?
You sound so enthused.
I, no, I don't mean,
I mean, congrats.
Congrats, that's huge?
Tell me you miss it, Dougie.
You miss it, right?
You, don't flip me
off, you miss it.
The rush you get, the
feeling of watching
you eat another
cocksucker's lunch, right?
I don't want any
cocksuckers around.
I don't know, maybe this
writing thing fills
that need, I don't know.
If I have a need to
be filled, it does.
So is that a yes?
I don't know, man.
Baby, are you seeing this?
Who does he look like?
[Pia] Stop it.
You know else had that look?
Gary did.
Yeah, it's that look,
man, it's that hunger.
If you don't do
something about it,
it's gonna eat
you alive, Dougie.
Dan.
What, I'm just, look, all
I'm saying is Doug and me,
we're like vampires.
Eat another man's lunch,
it's like blood to us.
Dan.
All right, all right,
all right, all right.
All right, just,
I'm done.
Anyways, I need another
drink because I am thirsty.
But seriously though,
can you get me a drink?
Something stiff?
Okay-
I got it,
- I got it.
- Was it too much?
Okay.
I'm gonna get the
vampire's blood.
[Dan] Sorry about that.
That was stupid.
So, how's America's
favorite tart with a heart?
You know I hate
when you call me that.
What do you care for?
Dan.
She doesn't like that.
Okay, all right, all
right, I'm sorry, but okay,
you gotta admit my
favorite character,
Kendall James, is a steel-jawed
cunt, let me finish,
hiding behind that so gorgeous
and immaculate,
wonderfully deceptive
pretty case of whoever he was.
Isn't it fun being
someone else for a living?
No, it was.
Yeah.
No, it, it was.
I stepped down a few months ago.
Stepped down?
Qu'est-ce que
c'est stepped down?
You mean,
you quit?
[Veronica] Yes.
Oh, Dougie. [softly chuckling]
Your meal ticket here
just got punched, brother.
Looks like you need
to get a real job.
Can always come back with
me, or copier sales, huh?
Why did you step down?
15 years on the show
started to get stale.
She's all out of love,
and so lost without you.
Besides, Douglas and
I are looking forward
to a normal life,
normal schedule,
spending more time together.
And Douglas has been
working on his writing.
You hear that, Dougie?
You, you want a normal life?
I have a normal life.
That's not what I
asked you, playboy.
I said do you,
[ominous music building]
you want a normal life?
I have a normal life, I
like it very much, thank you.
That's cute.
Who the hell wants
a normal life?
Normal people?
[softly chuckling] Okay.
Okay, now I get it, I get it.
Yeah, I tried being normal once.
It was the worst 30
seconds of my fucking life.
Normal is for people
without courage.
I don't know, Dan.
My dad used to say,
"You become the price you
paid to get what you want."
So, just make sure
you really want it.
No matter what it is, even
if it's a normal life.
From the mouth of a babe.
I don't think
that's an expression.
Well, I'm saying-
- For Dan, it is.
[ominous music softly building]
Oh my god.
See?
Was it me, or was it 1000
times more obnoxious than usual?
- Yeah.
You weren't like that, right?
I suppose we all were.
Even when we weren't, you know?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I know you guys
hadn't seen each other
since the funeral
and everything,
and I thought it might help
with your writer's block.
Maybe it would, you know?
If I hit it to so much
Dan, it might, you know?
It's just so much
Dan, but, it might.
Yeah.
No.
You're so much
better than him.
I love you.
[soft piano music]
Just two more days.
[soft blues jazz]
Rob has been asking
a lot about you lately.
You know, just figuring
out [softly mumbles]
- Thank-
- Hey, let's stop.
Who's selling who
here, all right?
I don't lose, all right?
You're coming back
to work for me.
That's it, it's a
done deal, all right?
Winning and shaving, huh?
Go hand in hand.
You do it everyday,
or you look like shit.
That's just, it's just the way.
It's just the way
the world works, man.
Gary knew it.
Fucking Gary.
Pauline said so.
You still talk to his wife?
Yeah.
Gary.
"How the heaven are you?"
That's what Gary used
to say when he'd walk
into a room, "How
the heaven are you?"
Dumb fuckers say hell,
he thought it was corny.
What I wouldn't give to like
hear it again, you know?
[Dan softly humming in sleep]
[dishes loudly clattering]
[faucet loudly running]
[cookware loudly clanging]
[softly uttering gibberish]
[softly drumming hands]
[loudly drumming hands]
Hey, hey, hey, hey, wait, wait.
Hey, listen, Veronica, Veronica,
she's a good girl, man,
you're lucky you found her.
I am.
Me too.
Whatever that means.
Hey, boop. [softly laughs]
Hey, man, listen, seriously,
you, you're a good friend.
Yeah, I love you too.
Hey, you're a good
friend, right, and,
we're brothers, we're brothers.
Sorry about your wife, man.
[dramatic music pounding]
[ominous music]
What'd you say?
Dan, what'd you say, Dan?
Dan! Dan?
[ominous music loudly building]
[soft ominous music]
[haunting piano music]
[ominous music loudly building]
[soft ominous music]
[dramatic music loudly pounds]
What you doing?
[ominous music]
Come to bed, baby.
[soft haunting piano music]
Vero?
[dramatic music loudly pounding]
[soft ominous music]
Did I wake you?
It's been so long since
you've held me like that.
I miss it.
Are you feeling okay?
Yeah.
You're not letting what
he said get to you, are you?
He's the kinda guy
who shits on you
and says, "Lucky you," 'cause
he's got soap and water.
You're great here.
You're gonna get
the script done.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Okay.
Sure.
Just one more day.
Now go take a shower, you
smell like pickled ass.
Thanks.
[shower running
drowns out singing]
♪ Don't walk away ♪
[softly humming]
Oh, yeah.
Vero?
Vero, can you get me a towel?
Our shower's acting up again.
Vee, can I get a towel?
[door loudly clatters]
Oh! Sorry.
It's okay, do you
still need a towel?
Yeah, I didn't
know it was you.
How could you have?
Morning.
Vero?
Oh, she went to the
general store with Dan
to get some eggs, I think.
Eggs?
I coulda swore we picked
some eggs on the way up.
[Pia] Do you want some coffee?
I just made a fresh pot.
Sure.
How long did they leave?
A little while ago.
Here you go.
Thank you.
So, that movie idea,
what is it about?
The what?
Oh, the script, yeah.
To make a long story less long,
it's about a robbery and a love
story that comes out of it.
Between two of the hostages?
No, no, no, no, between the
robber and one of the hostages
but I guess you can kind of
say that he's a hostage too
because the robber's
holding them at gunpoint,
and the cops are holding the
robber at gunpoint, so, yeah.
Anyway, it just got
a bit too contrived.
[Pia] What?
The script.
No, what part got contrived?
Oh, the love story,
I guess, and the,
the whole thing, really.
But mainly the love story.
Every time I tried it,
I just had to like-
- Force it.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, you know what they say,
love is like fart.
If you have to force
it, it's probably shit.
Life is very complicated.
Yeah.
Love shouldn't be.
No.
Okay, so we're
starting at the money,
the woman, and getting away.
What does he really want?
What do you mean?
Douglas, this is a love story.
He can only have one
want, one want and what.
Well, no, no, he has to get
both the woman and the money.
Otherwise it's not a
happy Hollywood ending.
Happy Hollywood ending depends
where you stop the
story, Douglas.
And the story only starts
when you know what
he really wants.
What he really wants
will drive the story.
Yeah, that's actually,
that's really good
advice, I must say.
It must be, if you must say.
Did you write yourself?
No, I just know what I want.
Hey, do you mind reading my,
my script when I'm done?
[door softly clatters] Okay.
[Douglas softly whistling]
[ominous music loudly building]
[Dan] Whoa! Whoa!
[Dan softly laughing]
You're so strong,
oh my god, hey, hey.
[dramatic pounding
drowns out Veronica]
Let me ask you, let me ask
you, are you a Kenny G fan?
Yes.
You like Kenny G?
I love Kenny G.
Are you serious?
[Veronica] Yes!
Oh my god, Douglas, you
sandbagging son of a bitch.
You're holding out on me, huh?
I see, you're trying to keep
all the good shit to yourself.
You're amazing. [Veronica
loudly giggling]
Oh my God.
Your face right
now, it's like you,
tickled his O-ring mid stroke.
You okay?
Okay, well this has
been a good talk.
I will talk to you guys later.
See ya.
Douglas, what was that?
Is this about last night?
[ominous music softly building]
I don't see any eggs, Vee.
She said you're going to
the store to get some eggs.
You guys having too
much fun to get eggs?
The store was closed,
the hours must've changed-
- Must've, mm-hm.
You know what, let's go down
there together right now,
me and you, we'll see
if they have eggs.
- Okay, maybe you need-
- I want eggs, I really want-
- A little space or something-
- Some eggs right now.
To do whatever it is you
need to do to normalize but,
I don't know what to say to you.
[car softly honking]
[Douglas] Hey.
You startled me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm going to the general
store, do you want a ride?
[Pia] No.
Eggs.
They didn't come
back with any eggs.
So I'm gonna go get some eggs.
If you...
Open.
Oh, shit, I'm sorry,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- No.
- Shit,
I'm sorry, yeah, perfect.
I'm sorry, I'm just really
in my head right now.
[radio softly clicks]
[soft moody guitar music]
Learn to love the quiet.
It has so much to show you.
[birds softly chirping]
Only keep the important one.
Speak only good?
Speak no evil.
Sure.
They have a,
there's a fair in the
square every fall.
I won that the first time we
came up here, me and Veer.
We used to come up here
as a place to escape everything.
Now it just seems like
we come up here to hide.
But yeah, I guess I did, I
did keep the important one.
Speak no evil.
Only good.
Only good, when I can.
Let's go.
- [women softly chattering]
- There's no way, yeah.
[Woman] Yeah, and you
didn't know about it?
[2nd Woman] No.
[Woman] Oh, yeah.
[2nd Woman] My husband
[women softly chattering]
[Woman] Oh, I'm glad
he let you come here.
[Woman 2] Yes, yesterday
was beautiful anyway.
- Aw, thank you.
- So I can't wait
to see you again.
- Oh, you too.
- Thank you so much.
Nice to see you, bye.
Nice to see you too, bye.
Hi. Dee Dee.
Douglas.
And friend?
This is Pia.
Can I call you friend?
I don't know, can you?
Pia.
Dee Dee.
Close friend, she and
her husband are her for,
I don't know, just to get
away from the city for a bit.
Oh, how are you liking it?
[speaking French]
Great.
That's French.
Oh, well, what can
I do for you two?
Just gonna get some supplies.
Hey, Vero was here earlier,
she said you guys
were closed, that,
you change your store hours?
I was here a
couple minutes late,
but the store has
the same hours.
- [soft ominous music]
- Okay.
Okay.
Yeah.
We're just gonna
go get the shit
that we're supposed to get.
All right, you go ahead, hon.
[Pia speaks French]
That's a nice shirt, I like it.
Thanks.
[soft ominous music]
Do you mind if I
stop for a second?
[speaking French]
For me, it's wheat
bread, prosciutto,
and a two-minute egg.
[speaking French]
I can live without
the prosciutto today.
[speaking French]
How well do you know Dan?
How well should I?
You married him.
You should know him the best.
Then that's how
much I know him.
Is that enough?
For me it is.
The trouble you're feeling,
is about Veronica?
Yeah.
Is it something she's done?
Or something you
think she has done?
I don't know anymore.
When do you?
Two things we should
never get angry with,
things we can change, and
the things we cannot change.
That doesn't make any sense.
[Pia softly laughs]
What if it wasn't us that
needs to know them well?
Oh, your egg, um-
- Two-minute egg.
Not a word of this
to Veronica, okay?
Ooh, a secret.
[ominous music loudly building]
- [music drowns out Dan]
- No.
[Veronica softly giggles]
- Oh, hey, guys.
- Hi.
Hey, babe.
You good?
Yeah.
[Douglas and Dan softly chuckle]
All right, come on.
I normalized, so, yay.
Okay.
Look, look, but I, look, I'm,
I'm sorry, dammit, okay?
I'm sorry.
Look, I don't know
what I'm doing here.
I'm not the jealous
type, you know that.
"I, I, I."
You really wanna
show me you care?
Think about me first, for once.
[ominous music
softly distorting]
All right, so I'm
thinking about brownies,
you guys want some brownies?
Yeah.
[Dan] All right,
babe, you're gonna cook
some brownies for us?
[Pia] Yeah, sure.
[Dan] Okay, come
on, get over here.
She's hot, she's gonna
make some brownies.
I like this.
Oh, thank you.
"I, I, I."
You really wanna
show me you care?
Think about me first.
- Danish?
- Danish, yeah.
She says danish,
I don't understand.
Yeah, but it's good,
it's a one-day trip,
wine-tasting, it's fun,
it's up in Santa Ynez.
Babe, Santa Ynez?
I don't know, baby.
Spain.
[ominous music building
and distorting]
[Veronica] "I, I, I."
Think about me first.
I swear to god,
listen, listen, listen.
So, you remember this?
Gary comes and he kicks
open the goddam door,
and he's holding
his cheeks together,
he's like, "Where's the
shitter, where's the shitter?"
He's gonna shit
all over himself,
- I promise you.
- No.
Stop the press.
Holy shit.
From a bearded clam to a
Brazilian-waxed beaver, whew!
Your puss just keeps getting
prettier and prettier, baby.
Come on in and sit
down, come on, come on,
sit down, the new man, huh?
I saved ya some, oh my
god, Hollywood, Hollywood!
Hey, man, welcome back.
You lookin' gorgeous,
Tom Cruise, I like it.
You guys throw a great party.
You must excuse me, I think
I've had too much of this.
There he is, there he
is, Hollywood, Hollywood!
Did I put it down or
did I put it down?
You put it down.
What?
No, man, I love
you, I love ya.
I'm gonna go take a piss.
- Dan.
- Thanks.
- What?
- TMI.
Listen, what I coulda said
is I'm gonna take a dump,
- but we just ate.
- Oh, wow.
I'm not gonna be weird.
I'll be back, you guys.
[Veronica] Sorry, your lips,
your lipstick, I'm
loving that shade.
It seems hydrating but not wet,
and your lips look so full.
It's not a lipstick,
it's a gloss.
Oh, what brand?
[phone softly vibrating]
Oh, I'm sorry, I
have to take this.
Hello, this is Veronica.
It is a lipstick, I think.
Really?
Now we have two secrets.
The owner put that chair there
like six months ago, it's new.
Yeah?
Yeah, they made it to
look old, but it's new.
I like the, um-
- Oh.
Thanks.
Been a long time.
- Yeah?
- It feels good.
Great.
It looks better though, right?
Why'd you shave it?
I never told Dan I didn't
like it, by the way.
- No?
- No.
It looks good.
Not better, but good.
[soft music]
I think I should go.
But do you though?
Yeah.
Veronica.
[Dan] Veronica!
Veronica, Veronica!
Here's the one I
was telling you about.
No, I couldn't.
Yes, you could,
and you should.
It's gonna look
much better on you.
Yeah?
Yeah, your skin tone and
the warmth of it, definitely.
Okay.
Oh, may I?
It's okay, it's okay.
Perfect, come, I have so
much more to show you.
Thanks for getting Dan
to come up, by the way.
I don't know if I said that
with everything going
on, it's just...
He misses you guys,
even if he won't say so.
I miss him too.
And you.
How have things been
since the funeral?
Hard sometimes, he feels
guilty, like it's his fault.
[Pia speaking foreign language]
What?
Beautiful, more
beautiful than when,
when Lance tried to kill
you at the Hollywood sign.
Oh, on the show.
That episode was over 10
years ago, so I doubt that...
Oh my god.
Hey, I'm making mix.
Dougie, hey!
What's that?
This is a, it's
called liquid courage.
Little potion I'm making.
You want?
Yeah.
Okay.
You, you just go wait for me,
I'll be out in a
second, all right?
Yo, you think I'm
gonna roofie you?
Listen, if I wanted to fuck you,
I'd want you to
see it coming, man.
Every inch, balls deep, leaving
my DNA all over your walls.
Yeah, just go out, I'll
be out in a second.
I call this A Goddam Shame.
Why?
I don't know, that's what
it's fucking called, man.
Spiced rum, mezcal, spiced
Clamato, it's genius.
Hey, what's the difference
between a baby and a trampoline?
I take off my cleats to
jump on a trampoline.
[Dan loudly laughs]
Come on, bro, come on.
There was a time, man,
you woulda pissed
yourself at that joke.
So, what do you think about Rob?
Dan, I'm not going back.
I know, I know, I know, but
just, come on, just humor me.
Better than you.
[Dan loudly laughs]
He's better than me?
Fuck you, man.
The day I take shit from this
job's the day I walk away.
But seriously, man,
like as a manager.
As a manager, he's adequate.
He's a better salesman
than a manager.
I don't know,
it's kind of like
that script you
wrote about us, bro.
Dan, I've already told
you, it wasn't about you.
It was fiction.
Fiction my diction, man.
That's not even a sentence.
Anyways, look, it
doesn't matter, anyways.
So hey, you remember, you
remember the circle, right?
Yeah.
Okay, so we're in the
circle and we're talking
about this pipeline and this
guy and Rob starts Jonning on
about a fucking
job he's working.
Get the fuck outta here.
No, I'm serious, and this
guy doesn't talk about shit
unless he's closing a deal
and he knows he closed it.
But there Rob was,
out of character,
sweating like a blind bull
dyke in a fish market.
Apparently the office
manager was a chink.
- No, no, no.
- Mm-hm, mm-hm.
And you know what they say,
chink's a jinx, Dougie.
Those slanty-eyed,
abacus-loving fucks.
They see right through
us, guys like you and me,
see right through us.
I'm talking about Rob,
never needed advice
in the history of motherfucking
advice, until he did.
Kinda like you, man.
So I'm gonna tell
you what I told him.
Bail.
They can see you coming, buddy.
Doesn't matter by
hook or by crook,
you ain't gonna get what you
want, not the way you want it.
[soft ominous music]
Hey, what do you do when
I look you in the eyes
and I tell you that
I can see you coming?
[ominous music loudly building]
[Dan loudly laughs]
Your face right now, man.
Like someone took
a shit in your hat.
Oh anyways, the deal
Rob was working,
he lost a shirt, we all did.
But...
Some fucking guy caught up
with him in the parking lot
and he just beat the fuck out
of him, like fucked him up.
His eyes hanging out
of his fucking head,
his nose smashed in, man,
blood everywhere, fuck.
Was crazy, man.
But I guess, you know,
that's the price you pay
for what you want, right?
What did that douchebag,
Pakowski, say?
"Find what you love
and let it kill you."
Doug, whatever it is you're
chasing, I hope you love it.
Cheers to you, motherfucker.
It's A Goddam Shame.
May I?
Do you like yourself,
who you are today?
Kinda have to, wouldn't I?
I mean there's...
Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
What if you spent
your entire life
running away from who you were
only to realize that you
were running towards it?
I'm not the same person I was.
No?
[soft ominous music]
So the truth is not
that Dan ate your lunch
and now you want to eat me?
He shoved his cock so
deep into her, you know?
The surprise in her face.
He loved it,
watching her
discover every thick,
veiny inch until
he exploded in her.
And she came too.
So many times.
More than with anyone else.
More than with you.
[ominous music loudly building]
She loved it.
In fact, she liked
it so much that...
She only thinks of him
when she's with you.
And here you are, trying
so hard to make her come.
But she only comes when she's
with you thinking of him.
[ominous music
loudly intensifying]
What's going on?
Dammit, Pia.
Would it matter if I said
it doesn't mean anything?
No?
I mean, it's just, have you
seen the cock on that guy?
[softly laughs] You
have, haven't you?
Then you know
after him,
you're not enough.
The new you is the old you
with a sensitive
stomach and no fangs.
He can still bite if
you want to, I know it.
Just fucking do it.
Do it.
[soft tranquil vocal music]
[loudly descending
into haunting vocals]
Dan!
You're so good!
Mwah! Wow.
That's all it takes
to get your wife
to scream my name, Dougie?
I wish Pia were that easy.
Babe, what?
All right, well, I know this
is a dangerous proposition but,
Dougie, do you wanna
chose the wine?
- Sure.
- Okay, stop.
I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking
chicken, white wine,
but that's poor
critical thinking.
This is roasted
chicken, it's dark meat.
So pairs red with the red.
It pairs good with the red.
Come on, chop, chop,
hurry up, buddy.
Okay.
Why don't you bring them both?
[Douglas] Okay.
So, we're going
to the canyons.
- Pinot grigio, please.
- I think it'd be cool
if you came with us.
I would love to go.
Oh, top me off,
buddy, thank you.
- Babe.
- Thank you.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Sorry about that.
It's okay, it's okay.
He was a dunce in class.
So Dougie, what's this
strip you're writing?
Script.
Script?
You said strip, it's script.
- Did I say that?
- Yeah.
Well, you know
what I mean, right?
All right, so Vero tells
me that it's about a heist.
[Dan softly laughing]
I thought you were supposed
to write what you know, man.
What the fuck do you
know about a robbery?
I guess about the same as you.
There he is.
Okay.
All right, well,
you know, it's funny 'cause
Veronica tells me
that you're in a jam
and you're stuck and
you can't get out of it.
I just, you don't wanna flap
your gums about it, it's fine.
I'm just, see what shakes
loose, just say so.
[Douglas] So.
[Pia] Dan, stop it now.
- All right.
- Dan-
- No, no, no, no.
[Pia whispering in French]
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, this guy's
- rockin' is granny panties.
- He doesn't wanna
- talk about it.
- Listen, Doug knows,
Dougie knows me.
If he wants to tell
me to fuck off,
just tell me to fuck off.
It's okay.
I can, let him talk, Pia.
So Dan, what is my jam?
And how can I fix it?
- Should I?
- Yeah.
Look, I'm just
here to help, buddy.
If you don't wanna
talk, you don't talk,
I just wanna help, right, Vero?
Yeah, he really does.
Dan wants to help me?
- [Douglas softly laughing]
- Yeah, I'm just,
I'm just here to
help you out, buddy.
[Douglas loudly cackling]
Dan wants to help me!
That's so awesome.
I love it, I love it, I love it.
[Douglas loudly cackling]
I'm so lucky. [softly mumbling]
Dan wants to help me.
Dan can't even help himself.
[Dan] Whoa, whoa, whoa, stop.
No, finish, Dan can't do what?
Help yourself.
[Dan] What can't I do?
The first thing they
teach you in Sales 101-
- Yes, it's three yeses-
- I'm fucking talking to you!
[Veronica] Douglas.
Sorry, yes, it's
the three yeses.
The last thing they
teach to a fucking retard
who doesn't grasp the basic
rudimentary, fundamental
nuances of sales is, guess what,
those same three goddam
yeses, and you know why?
Because it doesn't
take intelligence.
It doesn't take skills.
It doesn't take creativity.
It doesn't take a
fucking functional brain.
All you have to do is
think of three things.
Three, three little things
that can make someone say yes.
And you get them in the
habit of saying yes.
Like for example, is
Dan a fucking idiot?
Yes.
Is Dan a
piece-of-shit-motherfucking-lowe
fucking-cocksucker liar?
Yes.
Is Dan the worst salesman
in the history of
motherfucking history?
Well, you guys probably
don't know the answer
to this question but
I'm gonna lead you
in the right direction, okay?
Follow me, the
Wasserman account.
I had that lead first, right?
We can agree on that.
- That's right.
- I took a run at it
and nothing clicked, so
then I left the company
and did Rob give it to you, Dan?
Fuck no.
Rob wouldn't give you a fucking
lead with fucking shit, man.
You fucking choke on fucking
water, you fucking simp!
[ominous music softly building]
No, Rob gave it
to, remember Rubin?
And then he gave it to,
I think it was Scott.
And then every
motherfucking hand
in that motherfucking company
touched that motherfucker.
So then, Rob give it to Dan.
What could go wrong?
I mean, I've already, I don't
have any expectations here.
So you got your
fucking hands on it.
And you fucking hack.
You took my shit,
my tools to get in
and you're luckier than a
fucking dog with two dicks.
You're lucky because
Wasserman came in when he did.
Look at me.
You got shit on.
That's all you did,
you got shit on,
you got lucky and you
didn't fuck it up, Dan!
Congratulations, Dan.
That's, I think, the truth.
If I'm not mistaken, we're
all friends here, so.
Yeah, I guess,
- I guess we are friends, yeah.
- Yeah,
so is Dan the worst
fucking salesman
in the history of fucking
salesman salesman sales,
are you a bad fucking salesman?
Yes, you are.
I stomach you
because I like Pia.
And for the life of
me, I can't figure out
what the fuck she sees in you.
Are you a hostage?
Tell me right now.
Blink twice for yes and once
for no, just fucking blink.
I mean, literally, what do
you fucking see in this guy?
Motherfucker said red.
I'm so sorry.
Well, you said it yourself.
He's 1000 times more obnoxious.
So he had it coming?
You think what he
did makes you even?
Fuck even.
Just one more day, right?
I know he can
be a lot sometimes
but he's a good friend.
He is?
A good friend?
He drove all the
way out here for you
to be here for you,
can't you see that?
Drop the act, Vero.
[soft haunting piano music]
What's that?
Why is the picture
under the dresser again?
What the hell?
I'm gonna take it that
wasn't lost, right?
No.
You wanna talk about it?
I don't.
Normally, I'm an open
book, but I just,
I can't do this right now.
Obviously not.
You know, but this is us.
This is what we wanted.
It's the us you wanted.
And there's nothing
wrong with that
but have you ever really
looked at that picture?
How happy do I look?
Or do I look like someone
who's life is about to be over?
Do you know what kind of jobs
aging soap actresses get?
Not the ones that are hot moms
but the ones they just age?
Trick question,
they don't get any.
In that weekend,
the network randomly decided
to make me the mother
of a 16-year-old.
So?
I don't want to
be anyone's mother.
I'm Kendall fucking James.
You're not.
I am.
And overnight I'm 16 years older
with a life I never wanted.
And you made me celebrate it.
When I look at that picture
I see the beginning of us.
I don't see this.
All this.
That guy downstairs,
I just...
You didn't like what I did for
a living and I quit my job.
You didn't like who
I was as a person.
And I became this.
You don't like the
way I make love.
I'm not even in my
own skin anymore.
Why aren't I enough?
Because I want more.
Like Dan?
Yeah.
Like Dan.
I told you I didn't
wanna talk about this.
[soft haunting music]
Sorry.
Oh, it's fine.
Didn't know you were
here, I would have-
- You'd have stayed
in the bedroom?
[both softly chuckle] Thirsty?
[soft muffled jazz on stereo]
I read your
script a little bit.
Oh, yeah?
What'd you think?
It's who you are today.
You weren't in the same when
you wrote the other one.
It reads like it.
Is that good or bad?
It's honest.
May I?
Oh, please.
Hmm, it's good.
What, the script or the?
Okay, so, what
does Jacques want?
The money, the girl,
or to get away?
Well, one doesn't work
without the other, so.
That's not true.
If that's really what he wants,
he's in a pickle.
What, it's not
the way to say it?
No, it is, it's, go on.
Okay, so the
police surrounds him
and he's got the money.
But if he takes it,
he loses the girl
because she doesn't
like stealing.
But in your setup he needs
the money, always has.
Yes.
And there, the
girl comes along
and he really wants
her bad, infatuation?
It's more than
infatuation, I think.
And the police threatens
to take both possibilities away.
That's the gist, yeah.
Okay, so for me, it's clear.
He needs to pick one.
Stability, desire, or freedom.
How? You can't.
Why are you so
afraid to choose?
It's only the choice he's
making him in that moment.
Okay, let me help you choose.
Let's try stability.
Why stability?
Because the cost of stability
is diminished
opportunity to grow.
Says who?
Sheryl Sandberg, for one.
Who's Sheryl-
- Just choose
opportunity to grow.
I'm just afraid I'm gonna
make the wrong choice.
There is no wrong
choice, if it's honest.
[soft music]
Excuse me.
♪ Oh my dear please
would you be mine ♪
♪ We could do what
love is all about ♪
♪ Oh my dear please
hold my hand ♪
♪ This is all I want,
this is all I need ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh-ooh ooh,
ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh-ooh
ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ooh
ooh ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-Ooh ♪
♪ Oh my dear please
walk with me ♪
♪ Until the sun
rises back again ♪
♪ Oh my dear please
take forever ♪
♪ Time will tell what
love is all about ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh-ooh ooh,
ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh-ooh
ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh-ooh ooh,
ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh [record
loudly clicks] ♪
[soft ominous music]
What are you doing, Douglas?
Making a choice.
It's not wrong if
it's honest, right?
You want this too, right?
What just happened?
You are who you were today.
The same little guy with a,
with a sensitive
stomach and dull fangs?
You said it, not me.
[soft haunting piano music]
[haunting music softly building]
[soft dramatic orchestral music]
[birds softly chirping]
You guys up?
He's still sleeping.
I'm gonna go for a run.
You wanna join?
God no, I don't run
unless I'm being chased.
I don't think he will
be up for breakfast.
Copy that.
Surprised you're up.
Yeah, me too.
Did you make coffee?
I did.
Oh, oh, you got it?
- Yep.
- Thank you.
Hey, you seen Pia?
She went for a run.
Dougie?
No.
He came to bed last
night though, right?
Hey,
Are you guys okay?
Not sure.
[soft ominous music]
Hey. [Douglas
loudly breathing]
I've been coming up
here for all these years
and I've never seen this
before, it's crazy, huh?
I think I know how it
ends now, my story.
Yeah?
- Yeah.
- You've written it?
No.
So how do you know?
Things don't always go
the way we want, Douglas.
Yeah, I'm picking
up this subtexty vibe
that I'm hoping is
just that, a vibe.
[Pia softly mumbles in French]
Hey wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait wait.
I mean, can we both agree
that I'm walking
off a cliff here?
Like Wile E. Coyote and I'm
looking down at the same time?
No one asked you
to do that, Douglas.
He's, that advice!
I mean, you came on...
I'm sorry, I'm, I'm scared, Pia.
Like I don't, I'm afraid
to do anything about this.
About, about
anything in general.
So I do nothing, I
don't do anything.
I just, that's probably
why I don't do anything.
I just, I just
don't do anything.
You know, life has a way of
kicking your fucking teeth
down your throat,
you know what I mean?
You don't know which way
is up or down or sideways.
So you don't do nothing.
You just sit there,
you don't do nothing.
You get to feel okay though,
that whatever life gives you,
you just, you just accept it.
I mean, I haven't been doing,
haven't been doing,
I've been doing nothing
since I left Barossa
since I met Veronica.
But then you, you showed me.
I didn't.
You showed me.
It was about the
story, Douglas.
It was about me.
The first time in a very,
very, very long time,
I am going to take
control of my life
and I'm gonna let,
I'm gonna hold the reigns
and I'm choosing
what happens to me.
What happens next.
Yeah?
So tell me, what happened next?
You, I don't care
about stability.
I don't care if we
get away with it.
Fuck Dan, fuck Veronica.
Whatever happens happens.
As long as you're
with me, I just,
I don't care what happens next.
I don't.
You're my wanton want.
[Dan] Dougie!
[Veronica] Douglas!
[soft ominous music]
Stop pursuing, Douglas.
Us, or this, or you?
Don't you want this?
You know you want this.
[Pia speaking French]
[ominous music building]
[Pia softly screams]
Shut up.
[Pia loudly screaming]
What the fuck?
[Veronica loudly screams]
Fucker, what the
fuck is wrong with you?
You said you haven't
been coming, brother.
And don't you dare fucking
look at me like that.
You let that
fucking shit in you!
Let him stick his shitty
fucking dick in you!
What the fuck are
you talking about?
He told me, he told me.
He told me that when he
was on the couch, drunk.
"I'm such a good
friend, Douglas.
"I'm sorry for
fucking your wife,"
like you're still
fucking Pauline.
What do you want, man?
I'm not fucking your wife!
[Pia] But you're
still fucking Gary's?
Pia, Pia, Pia, wait-
- Sorry.
- Pia, Pia?
It's true.
You are right, I
am not Kendall James,
because this, all of this would
have never happened to her.
I mean, if it did...
But Dan said that-
- I don't give a
fuck what Dan said!
I didn't deserve this!
You are a fucking child!
Was it worth it?
All this?
Look at me.
Say it.
- Say, "Yes, she was worth it."
- Absolutely.
Every goddam second.
Thank you.
I wish you the worst.
The absolute worst.
[car softly starting up]
[car softly driving away]
It's just, okay,
what if I get to Lebec?
How about to Grapevine?
What if I make it
to Bakersfield?
So if I get to Bakersfield,
you can get me?
No?
You know, there's a
bus in a couple days.
Just forget about it and I
cannot thank you for this.
All right, be well.
[soft haunting piano music]
Hey, it's me again.
I'll just take the loan
ride, yeah, I'll pay for it.
Okay, great, thanks.
A minute?
I'll be downstairs, okay, bye.
What's worse than a
pile of dead babies?
The live one at the bottom
trying to eat its way out.
[loudly cackling]
How the heaven are you, Dougie?
I'm not Dougie.
And you're not you.
And yet, here we are.
You're not real.
Come on, when has
that ever stopped us
in this crazy
tapestry of, you know.
Hey, where in Orion's
Belt did I have that last?
At the backroom, before you...
[soft music]
Why'd you do it?
Why does anybody do anything?
'Cause it's time.
'Cause it needs doing.
When the show's over,
they turn on the lights.
May I?
Yeah.
Just hang on.
You're good, brother.
[soft piano music]
[soft uplifting piano music]
[lightly knocking at door]
Pia.
Pia, I'm so sorry-
- Finish that sentence
and I'm out of here.
Did you like what I-
- Did you care?
Of course I, yeah.
No, I...
Dan has the same pitiful
look when he looks at me.
The shame of knowing
that I know who you are.
That makes my pussy
dry, Douglas.
I just wanna see
if you're real.
- Am I?
- Yeah
[speaking French]
A sensitive stomach
and dull fangs?
[speaking French]
I can't fix the man
you've become, Douglas.
Only you can.
[speaking French]
"I'm sorry, Pia."
Yeah, you're sorry?
[speaking French]
You didn't happen
to me, Douglas.
I happened to you.
[speaking French]
Yeah.
Sensitive stomach
and dull fangs.
[speaking in French]
I don't understand
a word you just said.
If you stop the story here,
you have your happy
Hollywood ending, Douglas.
[soft music]
[soft piano music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ Oh my dear please
would you be mine ♪
♪ We could do what
love is all about ♪
♪ Oh my dear please
hold my hand ♪
♪ This is all I want,
this is all I need ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh-ooh ooh,
ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh-ooh
ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ooh
ooh ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-Ooh ♪
♪ Oh my dear please
walk with me ♪
♪ Until the sun
rises back again ♪
♪ Oh my dear please
take forever ♪
♪ Time will tell what
love is all about ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh-ooh ooh,
ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh-ooh
ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ooh ooh
ooh ooh, ooh-ooh ooh ♪