Joe, hello?
Joe, the door.
It's just another one
of those guys.
What guys?
Eh, guys working for
the big companies.
Want to buy the house,
rip it apart,
tear it down
like all the others.
Forcing good people out.
Goodbye, neighborhood.
Goodbye to your roses.
We can always
get more flowers.
That's not the point, Alice.
It's pure greed.
I'm in the business.
I see it from the inside.
We don't have to stay here.
We could sell up
and go live by the ocean,
like you've been
going on about forever.
The sound of waves--
wouldn't you like to hear that?
What I'd like to hear is
that pounding on my door stop.
I'm telling you,
they don't quit,
I'm gonna go get my gun
and clear up any confusion.
You stay away from
that old thing.
That's just gonna backfire,
and it's gonna hurt you
more than it hurts them.
At least put me
out of my misery.
Maybe you should
go talk to them?
Alice, it won't let up.
Okay, if you won't, I will.
Don't... don't you dare.
You do not go near that door.
-You're forbidding me?
-Don't you see?
They want,
they want one of us to break,
and they know it's usually
the wife that goes first.
Okay, you win.
Aces, champ.
Are you gonna at least water
my roses like you promised me?
In a minute.
I love you.
That's why I stick around.
A-Alice?
Alice?
Dad?
Zoe.
Yeah.
Didn't you hear me out there?
-I've been pounding on the door.
-Yeah, of course I heard you,
but you ob-obviously,
you-you got your keys.
Why aren't you
answering your phone?
-I didn't hear it.
-Is it charged?
I don't know.
It's around here somewhere.
Right.
Hey, Zo, Zo, no, please,
please do not do that.
We need to let some air in here.
There's plenty of air.
Why are you wearing a sweater?
It's hot out.
Well, I'm comfortable.
Okay.
Dad, I'm officially worried.
Do you ever leave this room?
Are you eating?
Are you sleeping?
You'd be surprised
how little of both you need.
And, yes, I leave the room.
I go outside to water.
Did you call out for Mom
when I came in?
No.
No, of course not.
Don't be an idiot.
Dad, you're hurting.
I knew that expensive college
education would pay off one day.
You can't stay in here forever.
You need to let it go, grieve.
I grieve.
You waltz in here
every now and then,
you tell me how to dress,
you tell me what to eat.
Why don't you let go, huh?
Stop picking on me.
Okay.
Have you figured out what you're
gonna do with her ashes yet?
I got some ideas.
I'll let you know
when one of them feels right.
You can't let her
stay in there forever.
Why not?
If that's what I choose.
People-people hold on
to ashes all the time.
-She wouldn't want that.
-She's gone.
The dead are dead.
Whatever I do is for me.
And me.
Yeah.
Yes, and you. I'm-I'm sorry.
Zoe... I get it.
Don't worry.
I'll figure it out.
I just need time.
I wish you would
let Frank come by and do...
Don't, don't, don't.
Okay, if not him,
then someone, just...
I'm telling you, that man steps
one foot inside my door,
I-I don't know what Ill do.
You're gonna what?
You're gonna beat up our pastor?
I sat there out of respect
to your mother.
Every Sunday, I listened to him,
I listened to the guy
before him,
week after week, years of it.
Suit and tie, even when jeans
became okay in church.
Now I don't have to,
end of story.
Wow.
I was...
I was married to your mother
for 43 years,
eight months and 12 days.
Clock stopped ticking.
Wasn't my plan, but here we are,
and I do not need you and Frank
or anybody else tag-teaming
to tell me that I'm hurting.
I'm hurting, I know!
I'm hurting! I get it!
But I'll get over it, just like
I did with your brother.
-I got over it.
-No, you haven't.
Well, you want,
I could start drinking.
How'd that work out for you?
Huh? Get you over the hump
when Danny bolted and left you
and Adam hanging? Huh?
I'm s-sorry. Zoe, I didn't
mean that, not like that.
I did not mean that.
-Yeah, you did.
-You're so--
Come on, Zo,
why are we doing this?
Is it--
Would you just come here?
I don't even recognize you.
I don't, Dad.
I'm confused by this.
I'm scared.
Well, don't be.
I'm working my way through it.
Would you-- how 'bout just come
and give me a hug? I need a hug.
You have people out there
depending on you.
And you have a guy out there
who's ready to sue you
because you left his house
half-finished
and his family is stuck
in a motel.
Jason and the guys
are gonna finish it.
It's just a couple of toilets,
a di-- I think it's a dishwasher
and, uh, we turn on the water!
That's what
I'm talking about, Dad.
Jason and the guys
quit two weeks ago
'cause they like to get paid!
Where are you?
Fine. I'll do it myself.
What moron cannot
connect a toilet?!
You know your bank called me
looking for you?
They did.
About your mortgage payments.
Give me a break!
My wife died!
And there is more of this
vomiting out of your mailbox.
I assume you've blown off
every bill you've received
in the last three months,
not to mention
the condolence cards
people have sent
-to show you they love you.
-So I missed my Hallmark moment.
You're...
Dad, this is
really freaking me out!
None of this is like you.
That's what worries me.
You did exactly
what I asked you not to.
-What?
-17 times.
What are you talking about?
He mentioned God by name
17 times in a 30-minute service.
You throw in every "Jesus this,"
"Jesus that,"
that's well over 30.
That's one mention a minute.
You actually counted?
I asked for one thing, Zoe,
one thing only.
"Please do not turn her service
into a religious thing."
She was Christian.
She's dead.
She's gone.
That day was for me.
It was also for me.
I am Christian.
I tell you what,
I'll make you a deal right now.
You stop jumping from
one fix to the next.
You start to believe that, I
tell you, you believe anything,
maybe I'll believe it, too.
-It had meaning for me.
-Meaning?
You want meaning?
Go out there and find out
who killed your mother.
Cops sure as heck
aren't doing it.
Three months, Zoe.
You find the scum
who ran her over
and left her in the street
lying there for dead!
No, I can't do this.
-Not today, Dad!
-That's right!
Fire gets hot, what does she do?
She runs off!
That's what sane people do
so they don't get burned!
If you don't want help,
that's fine.
Fine, Dad. But I am not
gonna go down with you.
I can't. I'm not going to.
Well, grab that little chain
around your neck, honey.
Keep on praying.
I hope it works for you.
You are such a...
I got to water the roses.
And get some air.
Hey.
Hey, wh-- shoo!
How'd...
How'd you get in here?
Shoo! Shoo!
Go!
I'm warning you.
Huh? I'm warning you.
You better get out of here.
Fine, have it your way.
Shoo.
Hey! Hey!
I'm not going anywhere!
What?
This house back here?!
This house, my house?!
Not for sale!
Whatever you say, boss.
I'm not your boss;
I'm your enemy!
Not for sale!
Guy's a whack-job.
Stay out!
Ah, he's a nutcase.
How'd you get in here?
Hey. Hey!
Hey! How did you...
What, you think
I'm playing around here, huh?
Huh?
Oh, now you're
making fun of me? Huh?
Go on. Come on.
Get out of here. Shoo.
Just get...
Come on, you ugly mutt, get--
Sh-Shoo.
Just get-get out of here.
I mean it.
Go!
Wrong.
Come on. Let's go.
Go! Go!
All right.
But I can tell you this,
the nights get pretty messy
around here.
It's when the ghosts come out.
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, you're a tough guy.
All right.
You've been warned.
Move it to the left.
Oh, thank you.
Ah.
Hold on. Hold-hold on.
Don't...
Don't you pee on my floor!
Here we go. Here we go.
Out you go. Come on. Come on.
Hey, hey!
No, not there, not there!
You get-get away from those!
Get away!
You don't ever go near these.
You got it? Ever.
You stay away.
Yeah, finish up
whatever you're doing there
and just get out of here.
Just go.
I got no business with you,
you got none with me.
Are you done?
All right. Go on.
What is with you?
Can you smell that?
Do you know what I have here?
I sure do.
Bring 'em on!
Just one!
That belly of yours
isn't getting any smaller.
You want me to eat just one,
but you tease me
with a plate full.
Where's the logic in that?
Restraint.
I'm teaching you restraint.
You got me
to restrain my language.
Doesn't that count
for something?
It does.
And I appreciate it.
Believe me, I got
a storage locker full of F-bombs
just busting to see
some daylight.
If I could take this
and squeeze it into a lifetime,
I'd die a happy man.
Fat and happy.
You know, I was just thinking
about that time up on the lake.
You know?
We were just down on that dock,
ah, just looking up
at that night sky,
the moon, the stars.
Yeah, wondering
where it all goes.
You and me, hmm?
Sitting there
in our own little world.
Could've just reached
right up there, grabbed them,
the stars.
You remember that?
I do.
I fell in love with you
that night.
Is that where you are right now?
In the stars?
-What do you want?
-Hi.
Are you, uh, are you
the homeowner?
What do you think?
-Great.
-Oh, hey.
Hey, little guy, how are you?
Oh, you're friendly, aren't you?
Does he belong to you?
No. But you like him so much,
why don't you turn around
and take him with you?
I'm not interested.
Okay. Uh, well, I don't suppose
your wife's around?
Why would you ask that?
Oh, I'm sorry,
I just thought that I...
Hey, kid, I know
why you're here.
You see a "for sale" sign
out there?
Huh? I don't.
I do, however,
see a "no trespassing"
and "private property" sign,
and what part of that
gave you the bright idea
to come knocking on my door?
All right, I'm sorry.
Uh, obviously, y-you know,
you're not interested.
Yeah, I just told you that.
And there's no wife here
to cave in.
I know your tricks.
Cool.
I-I'm gone.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Yeah.
Take the dog.
Nope, I'm good.
Thank you, though.
What?
Oh. Hey!
Hey, hey, hey.
You know what?
That was bad.
That was way out of line.
Woke up on the wrong side of bed
this morning.
Come on back, let me hear
what you got to say.
Nah, man, I-I don't want
to bother you. It's...
You already did that.
You offering good money?
I could be interested.
Uh, we-we are--
we're competitive.
Well, competitive works for me.
Dog here thinks you're okay.
Come on back.
Let's hear what you got.
Yeah, hey, sorry about the mess.
My wife just died. Recently.
Oh, um, um, listen, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry to hear that. I-I...
So what are you,
what are you gonna do?
Just buy it, tear it down?
Is that your plan?
Uh, listen, uh, you know,
maybe-maybe this isn't
-the best time right now.
-No, no, no.
Oh, actually,
it's a perfect time.
Come on. Close the door. Sit.
Sit!
So what do you got?
Oh, uh, right.
Um...
Ah, hey. Look at that.
Ah, let's see what you got here.
What do you have here?
Norman Olsen.
Ah, Norman.
You don't hear that name
a lot anymore.
Yeah.
You look more like a Chad to me.
Huh.
So, Chad, what kind of numbers
are we looking at here, huh?
For my place.
Now, I know
it's just land to you,
but it means a lot more to me.
Uh, yeah. No, right.
Um, well, I-I suppose I should--
well, I have to ask you
a few questions first.
-Sure.
-Um...
Uh, do you, do you own the house
or-or do you have a,
do you have a mortgage?
What difference does that make?
I know what I owe.
You tell me what I get from you,
I do the math.
All right.
All right, yeah.
All right, I got ya.
Yeah, okay.
Uh, all right, next,
um, uh, let's see.
Are there any liens
on the house?
-Nope.
-No.
Uh, any other names
on the title?
No, just me.
My wife is gone now.
Yeah, right. Um...
Yeah, and again,
I'm-I'm sorry about that.
Uh, okay, uh, what about
the-the lot, square footage?
Say just approximately.
7,227 square feet,
11 and 3/4 inches.
Let's round it off to 28.
Wow.
Uh, that's-- Okay.
-All right, look, kid.
-Hmm?
Just give me your number.
Your slick brochure,
your fancy shirt
with your muscles popping
out of it, doesn't impress me.
Life is all about
the numbers, right?
Yeah.
You're right. Yeah, yeah.
No, I got you. I got you.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, all right, but, um,
-I got to do some crunching.
-Yeah. You go ahead.
Coffee just kicked in.
Got to do
a little crunching myself.
Well, uh,
take your time.
Um, I'll just hang out
here with, uh--
-Wh-What's your dogs name?
-Uh...
Dog.
That-that's his name?
Yeah, why not?
After all, a name is
just a name, right?
In reality, we are who we are,
right, Norman? Chad?
Norman? Chad-Norman-Chad?
Um, Dog's fine.
Give me that number, Norman.
Love of my life.
I'm sure that...
Then bang, just like that,
she's gone.
Three months, seven days, and--
what do you know?--
just a couple hours ago.
Hmm.
And now here we are,
here you are, to take my home.
I-I what?
Is that just a coincidence,
Norman?
Uh, I don't, I don't understand.
No.
Yeah, I don't think you do.
Please.
I-I've got a kid, all right?
Me, too.
Little girl in those photos?
She used to have a mother.
Yeah, kids lose their parents
all the time
to life's unfortunate events,
and sometimes, well,
parents even lose their kids.
I-I think that you might have me
mixed up with somebody else.
Did you or did you not come here
with the sole purpose
to take this house, my home?
I mean, yes, I did.
I mean, but sort of.
Conveniently available,
sort of, don't you think?
-Now with my wife gone.
-I-I don't underst...
-You kill her?
-What?
Did you kill my wife?
Look, I-I have no idea what
you're talking about right now.
Oh, I think you do,
you or the people you work for.
You killed her, you made it
look like an accident.
We know what happened.
Don't we?
And why.
Please, sir.
-Please what?
-Please, please don't-don't do
whatever it is that you're
thinking about doing right now.
What is it you think
I'm thinking about doing?
Uh, I-- look, all I did was
I just came here to see
if you wanted to sell
your house, that's it.
Oh, fair enough.
So what do you think now?
You think I want
to sell my house, Norman?
No, probably not.
Your-your wife just passed away.
She didn't just pass away.
She was killed.
So what do you think, Dog?
Should we just finish this guy?
Finish him
and be done with it, hmm?
Hmm?
What?
What-what is he,
what is he saying?
I don't know.
You speak dog?
You tell me.
Um, I-I think that he's,
I think he said that you should
let me go and that I'll forget
that this ever happened
and I will never, ever, ever
bother you ever again.
Is that right?
We should just let him go, hmm?
Really?
I think maybe you're right.
I think he also said, I find out
that you or the people
you work for,
you killed my wife,
you killed my Alice,
I will not hesitate
to shoot you on sight.
You let them know I'm onto you.
The whole thing.
Uh, yeah, fair-fair enough.
This will not be forgotten.
I don't forgive and forget.
I-I hear you.
I hear you loud and clear.
All right, go on.
Go on.
Take your little brochure.
Hey, you never gave me
that number.
What this place might be worth.
Uh, I'm really sorry
about your wife.
Good answer.
That might be the
dumbest thing you've ever done.
Not now, Alice.
-Consequences.
-The air had to be cleared.
A message had to be sent.
And this is how you do it?
Yes, this is how I do it.
And where has that gotten you?
Here. Right here.
My house. My home.
My little piece of it all that
they can't get their hands on!
Mine!
I'm telling you, Alice, they
take everything if you let them.
You got to fight back.
You got to send a message!
If you say so.
You're being hard on Zoe.
She's hurting and she needs you.
-She looks up to you.
-I know.
She loves you.
I know.
I'll... I-Ill patch things up.
And get rid of that gun.
Promise me.
I promise. I promise.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
But what's done is done.
At least they know
to leave me alone now,
give me five minutes of peace.
Come on, guys.
All right.
Watch your head.
Thank you.
Hey. I'm sorry.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
It's-its just
a big misunderstanding.
-Thanks for coming in, Miss...?
-Bigler.
- It's her maiden name, my name.
- Zoe.
-Zoe's fine.
-She was married, but her deadbeat husband ran off
-on her and their kid on his fifth birthday.
-Okay.
-Actual day. What a world, right?
-Okay, Dad.
It is.
All right, Zoe.
Um, I'm Detective Rollins.
If you don't mind, Id like
to jump right into this.
Yeah, that's fine.
Does your father own a gun?
N-No, not that I'm aware of.
-Dad?
-Of course I don't.
You know how your mother felt
about guns.
-This is absurd.
-Mm.
Well, I've got
a signed affidavit here
as part of a complaint
that he pulled a gun out
on a Norman Olsen, who had
visited his house earlier today.
I'm sorry, who?
Another guy trying
to buy the house.
I'm telling you, Zo,
they won't let up.
-Sorry, you had a gun?
-No. No.
That's what I've been
trying to tell them.
I don't own a gun.
This guy, this Norman kid,
he's making it all up.
It's-its just another trick
to get me out.
First your mother, now this.
Okay, let's not do that in here.
Wait, what do you mean,
trick to get you out?
My dad thinks somebody
wants his house for the land.
'Cause its an older home...
-It's strong and sturdy.
-Like you, right?
Neither of us are
going anywhere soon.
My mother had an accident
recently on her bike...
No. No, no, no.
She was murdered.
-Now I know why.
-Dad...
She was.
But you wouldn't know anything
about that, would you?
Because nobody around here seems
to be doing anything about it.
I-I told the cops
who came around after.
It was no accident.
Uh, she was killed.
To try to get me to cave in,
get all emotional
and just move out.
And you think
this Norman Olsen
-had something to do with it?
-Him, somebody he works for.
It's all one big circle.
They're all in it together,
buying up the world,
turning it into something
that I couldn't recognize
to save my life.
And that's why
you pulled out a gun on him?
What part of "I don't own a gun"
do you not understand?
-And don't you try to trick me.
-Dad...
No. No.
I've done nothing wrong.
It's my word against
this Norman kid.
Search me.
Search my house.
No gun, period.
It's all made up.
So you mean we can do that?
Search your house?
Yeah. Sure.
Here, go ahead. Here, I got...
Knock yourself out.
How's Adam?
-He's fine. He misses you.
-Thanks.
I miss him, too.
Maybe you could
bring him around.
Not now.
Just tell him
I was thinking about him.
I will.
Hey, did I tell you
I got a little dog?
-What?
-Just showed up one day. Won't leave me alone.
Uh, won't leave, period.
Did you try
to find his owner?
Adam's gonna love him.
Dog-- that's what
I'm calling him.
-That's creative.
-It works.
Dad... I'm serious.
When we get through this,
I really need you
to talk to someone.
To anybody.
I don't know what to do.
I'm scared. I don't know
what's going on with you.
You understand that?
Okay. I-I need somebody
to help me understand this.
I-I get it, Zo.
Make it happen.
I'll be there.
I promise. Whoever.
Thank you.
-Yeah, sure, thanks.
-We'll get this all straightened out.
I just want it to be done.
-Hey, how you doing, Norman?
-Dad, stop...
I'm-I'm sorry about
any misunderstanding.
Mr. Bigler?
So?
He's dropping the charges.
Oh, he changed his tune, did he?
That was quick.
So this ends here, unless
you give me a reason otherwise.
So let's keep it in check, okay?
Don't let me regret
letting you off the hook
for whatever happened today.
He won't.
Mr. Bigler?
What part of the...
You got my word.
I won't be a problem.
Promise me.
Swear to me
you don't have a gun.
I already got rid of it.
It's not gonna be a problem.
Oh, my...
I want you
to talk with Frank.
Here it goes.
You just said I make it happen,
you'll be there.
-You said whoever.
-To talk to somebody,
work my way through this,
not get the magic wand of God
waved over me and try
to turn me into something
I'm never gonna become, Zoe.
He's a good listener,
that's all.
I talk to Frank,
that makes you happy?
This is so far beyond
what makes me happy.
Fine.
Fine. Bring him over.
No big deal.
We'll clear the air.
I promise.
I... I'll talk,
he listens, we make peace.
After that,
maybe I can see Adam?
Get him and Dog together.
That would make me happy.
You have a deal.
What? What?
What? Quit it.
Huh? What?
What?
You see that?
I told you, they don't give up.
And now they got me
right where they want me.
I can't even defend myself.
Oh, now I got you to take care
of me, is that right?
You might want to brush up
on that bark of yours
I've never heard.
Yeah, sure. Why not?
Over here, over here!
Yeah, come on through.
How come I never
hear you bark, anyway?
You do know how to bark,
don't you?
You're a dog.
That's how dogs talk. They bark.
"How you doing today, Mr. Dog?"
"Oh, that's nice to hear."
"How are the wife and kids?"
"Oh, that's good."
"Oh, it's very nice of you
to ask. I'm doing just fine."
Hey. What are you looking at?
H-Hey, get back! Get back!
You better be finished
with your business.
What did I tell you?
Here I am, I give you
some slack, I make friendly,
and suddenly you turn on me?
Ah, so now you're
a smart guy, huh?
All right.
Is that it?
Is that what you're
looking for, Columbo?
Bad dog! Bad dog.
Dad?
You do not go near that,
do you understand?
-You stay-- Hey, Dog.
-Dad?
You do not go near it.
Do you understand me?
Dad?
Hey. I thought I heard you.
-Dad.
-I was just about to water the flowers.
Oh. Is this him?
Is this the dog you found?
Oh, more like he found me.
Aw, come here. You're cute.
He thinks you say that
to all the dogs.
Ha. Not true.
But you could definitely
use a bath.
I don't think
he likes water too much.
I tried to hose him down
once, but...
So you haven't seen
any signs for lost dogs?
-No one's come around?
-Nope.
-Oh. Well, you can't keep him.
-Why not?
'Cause he belongs to somebody.
He has no collar, no leash,
no tags, no nothing.
He shows up at my door; nobody's
come around looking for him.
What am I supposed to do?
I take him to the pound,
you know what they're gonna do.
Yeah.
-Well, Frank's inside.
-Oh.
Right.
Well, that was quick.
-You promised.
-I did.
Let's do this.
-Be nice.
-Nothing but.
I just want to say
right off the bat
that I-I'm sorry
about the service.
I heard from Zoe
that you were disappointed.
And my walking out
in the middle of it
didn't send that message, huh?
Oh, it did, it did.
And, uh, again, I'm sorry.
I was trying to find a balance
between what you'd asked for
and the expectation of others,
Alice's friends.
Okay. Fine.
Let's move on.
Sure.
Still, you must know
that Alice had
deep feelings
regarding her faith.
Look, Alice had faith;
I had doubt.
You'd be surprised
how well the two work together.
Doesn't surprise me at all.
I think that doubt's
an important part
of a healthy faith.
Tell you what.
Let's put all the
religious stuff aside for now.
Would it surprise you
to know that
Alice was concerned about you?
Well, I, uh...
Oh, that's news to me.
Well, she and Zoe...
care about you.
Frank, can you--
Frank, can you do me a favor?
Stop talking like
she's still here.
Yeah. Sure. I'm sorry.
You know, for a guy who's here
to do some listening,
you're starting to do
a lot of the talking.
Okay. You're right.
Tell you what.
Just tell me how you're doing.
Oh. Okay, let's see.
Um, like I said, I'm-I'm good.
I'm-- No, really, I am.
I-I even told Zoe this.
I know it may not look that way,
but I'm working
my way through it.
It just takes time.
Frank, uh, come on.
You must deal with
this grief stuff all the time.
I do.
Oh.
We're good, then.
-We done here?
-Dad.
Well, Frank gets it.
He knows, it's just
gonna take some time.
It-It's nothing more.
Right, but there's plenty
to talk about still.
Look, if you're waiting for me
to fall on the floor
in a heap of snot
and cry out to Jesus to save me,
it's not gonna happen, honey.
-That's not why I'm here.
-Forgive me, Frank, but...
give me a break.
Hey.
You know it, and I know it.
All right, look.
Yes, Alice had her beliefs,
and I supported her.
But it doesn't mean
it works that way for everyone.
And it certainly
doesn't work that way for me.
And frankly, Frank...
I don't think she was
as concerned about me
as you make it sound.
That was a low blow.
Okay.
But if I may,
what does work for you?
You say you're getting over
Alice's death.
How?
I just take things as they come.
I deal with them when they do.
If nothing else,
I learned that in the ring.
Tomorrow's always another round.
I always counted on that.
You know, Joe,
I think we have more in common
than you might think.
Oh, yeah?
How so?
Take love, for example.
You know love, right?
I know that you loved
Alice deeply.
And faith,
you may call it hope,
that strange force
that drew you into the ring
when every part of your body's
telling you to stay out.
And mercy.
Compassion.
I saw it every Sunday
when you took a seat
next to Alice in church.
Even if you were just
going through the motions,
you were there for her.
Do you recognize
any of those things?
Yeah, of course.
I'm human.
See? We're not so different
after all.
God just uses each one of us
in His own way.
You see that, Zo?
See what he did just there?
He snuck God right in
through the back door.
All right, my turn.
Two times in my life
I tried to reach out to God.
And, I mean
give it my best shot,
despite every part
of my being saying don't.
And you got to understand,
this was because of Alice.
Not for her, but because of her.
Uh, I mean, if God and all that
meant so much to her,
there must be something to it,
something I must be missing.
I loved her that much.
I trusted her that much.
And I respected her.
First time, I'm at work one day.
I get a call out of nowhere,
out of the blue, that,
"Your son is lying in a hospital
bed and he's dying." What?
Anyway, I get over there,
to the hospital
where they got him, and...
I see Alice and I see
a fear in her eyes
like nothing
I've ever seen before.
So I-I figure I-I guess
I should pick up the slack.
I-I should say a prayer that she
can't seem to manage just then.
So I, um...
I beg Him.
I beg God...
"Please, don't take my son."
Hmm? I prayed...
...and I prayed.
And I waited. And I waited.
I begged for mercy.
I begged...
for compassion.
We all know how that turned out.
One day short
of you guys turning 13.
He didn't even have a chance
to be a man.
Second time,
three months ago,
I'm sitting in this room,
right in this chair right here,
and suddenly
there's a knock at the door.
There's a cop. He tells me
there's been an accident.
I heard sirens. I didn't think
anything of it, but...
Anyway, he goes on to tell me,
um, "I'm sorry, sir,
but your wife has
fallen off her bike."
Just like that,
"Fallen off her bike."
So, uh, I rush over
to the hospital--
same hospital where Mike died--
and they tell me,
"It doesn't look good."
What is going on here?
"It doesn't look good"?
What is this, a television show?
Anyway, they...
they take me into the E.R.
They pull back this curtain
where they got her
hid from view,
and then there she is.
Just cut to pieces.
Mangled.
A mess.
43 years by her side,
all that beauty, all that love,
and then there she is,
like that.
And the only thing-- our entire
future and our entire history,
the only thing we got left
is the faint beep
of this little machine
they got above her head,
telling us that
she's still with us.
So I turn to God once again.
Only this time,
I get down on my knees,
like I think you're supposed to,
on this filthy green hospital
tile floor, and I beg Him.
I beg... begged Him.
"Please, let Alice live.
"Please, take me.
"If you're mad at somebody,
be mad at me.
If you want to punish someone,
punish me."
And I'm telling you,
I meant this with all my heart,
everything I was asking.
I even forgave Him about Mike!
And then just like before...
...nothing.
Not a fly flapping its wings.
Nothing.
Then, um...
oh, maybe 60-- not even 60--
30 seconds later,
I... I hear it.
That little beep.
It goes flat,
the sound that death makes,
and I get His answer.
"Sorry, Joe.
Too little, too late."
Twice I tried.
Twice I was denied.
I figure, you reach out
to somebody, anybody,
certainly God, for hope
and mercy and compassion,
and you get nothing back,
anything back, it's just a...
...yeah, a fantasy you make up
to keep from going nuts.
That wall?
That's real.
I know it's there,
it knows I'm here.
Mutual respect.
God never gave me as much.
That's not God, those words.
Oh, yeah? Then who?
Who was it who took my
son in a blink of an eye?
And who has
such a supreme authority,
such an audacity to let
my beau-- my beautiful,
my beautiful wife,
everything I love,
she died lying face down
on the asphalt
when she gave nothing but love
to everyone who came around her.
Who?
Not God.
Well, maybe you're right.
Maybe it's just...
the man in the mirror.
Maybe it's nothing at all.
Either way...
...I, uh,
I'm gonna leave it at that.
You okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Sorry for what?
For letting you down.
Using all those words I...
Joe, by the time
we fell in love,
I knew what I was getting into.
Well, then that's on you.
But you're the one
punching holes in walls.
Back to fists?
Dropping F-bombs
like it's Hiroshima.
Well, that's what you
get for leaving me here alone.
We're never alone.
It's a choice.
I don't know.
It's like you're
a million miles away.
I lose a little piece of you
every day.
Every minute.
The choices you make
have always been yours.
Never needed me for that.
You always helped.
One look in your eyes, and...
...I had all the answers.
Come here.
Come on.
Dog?
Ah, come on, where are you?
Hey. Hey! Can I help you?
Mr. Bigler.
-How you doing, sir?
-I'm doing fine.
What are you doing over there?
I was thinking
I could use a truck.
Well, I think
that's more than you need.
Right. Oh, man.
Personally, I want to live as
far away from work as possible.
Hey, look, I know you didn't
come here to talk about trucks
or where you want to live, so if
you got something on your mind,
I'm kind of
in the middle of things.
No, actually, I think
I may be able to help you.
How so?
You mentioned before that
people were trying to force you
-out of your house here?
-Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So they can just rip it down
and put up whatever they got
planned for the land next door.
And you think maybe your
wife's accident had something
to do with that, getting you
out of this place here?
I'd stake my life on it.
She was killed. They made it
look like an accident.
They figured I'd be so broken up
that I-I wouldn't want
to stick around.
Are you broken up?
Yeah, of course.
What kind of question is that?
But you have no plans
of leaving?
They're gonna have to
carry me out in a bag.
I hear that.
Look, the case is still open.
I was thinking maybe
I'll take a stab at it.
Really?
Yeah, it seems like
the right thing to do.
Well, thank you.
That-that would mean a lot.
But to be fair, the detectives
assigned to this case,
they've done a good job,
they've done their work.
Yeah, well, if in your book,
not figuring out
who killed my wife is
"a good job," I...
They've gone door-to-door
for witnesses,
checked out security cameras,
checked body shops.
They checked your wife's cell
phone recovered at the scene
to see who she was
in contact with during the time.
I-I don't understand.
What does her phone
have to do with anything?
Look, you wanted them to do
their job, look at all angles.
That's part of what we do.
It just seems like
an invasion, that's all.
Uh, so what'd they find when
they looked at these records?
Nothing solid.
But my point is that they've
done a good job, all right?
They've been very thorough.
That doesn't mean
it didn't happen like I said.
It has nothing to do with cell
phones or cell phone records.
Someone killed her
to get this place.
That's what happened.
And I think it's an angle
that needs to be addressed.
Oh, who's this?
Dog.
Bad dog. Bad dog.
Where were you?
Yeah, yeah.
Get in there. Go on.
Get in there.
He's a real pain in the butt,
but I deal with him.
Got one myself.
Only mine's a teenager who wants
the life and luxury of LeBron,
but he's too short and cant
shoot a hoop to save his life.
Look...
I'll tell you how it goes,
all right?
If you can think of anything,
need to talk, that's my cell.
Anytime, all right?
Let's put this thing to bed.
Thank you.
No, I-I mean that.
You know, I could turn him
into a fighter.
-He's got strong hands.
-Don't even think it.
One is enough.
Thanks for letting me
spend some time.
Yeah, it's good,
for both of you.
Ah, for all of us.
You weren't exactly wrong about
me, what you said the other day.
-Zoe, we don't have to do this.
-No, you were right.
I do, and...
I grab for things,
whatever, just to,
I don't know,
make sense of it all.
We all do.
That's human nature.
Somehow we think
it's just us. Me.
Mm-hmm.
I just don't understand
how a man could
-abandon his kid like that.
-Dad...
I'm sorry. You're right.
I won't go there.
You're all I got.
You and Adam.
Dad, I need you to be okay
for me to be okay.
I wish I could just flip
a switch, make it better faster,
but I'm not wired that way.
Definitely not.
Zoe,
you and I, we-we don't see
eye to eye on everything.
You know, a lot of things.
Your mother and I certainly
didn't, that's for sure.
But...
I'm glad for what you found.
It's a safe place.
It's a good place.
I'm happy that its taken away
some of the pain.
Thank you.
Faith.
It's a funny thing, huh?
Fickle and funny
in who it chooses.
Not me.
But your mother
always had my back.
And now that she's gone?
Well, now that she's gone,
I got this guy.
Don't I, Dog?
Keeping me on
the straight and narrow.
Talk about faithful.
I can't get rid of him
if I wanted to.
Who needs a leash?
I hate to say this, but we have
to try to find his owner.
We have to just try.
Hmm?
He's saying,
"Nobody owns nobody."
He's turning you
into a softy.
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
Just a couple of moves,
I promise.
- Strictly self-defense.
- Oh.
Come on, right there.
Boom!
I'm telling you,
my bank was in on it.
Joe, just slow down, all right?
Let's think about this.
Rollins,
please listen carefully.
Look, my wife dies, right?
I don't pay my mortgage
for a couple of months.
Give me a break,
my wife just died!
You should see all these-these--
not just bills but these-these
threats they're sending!
-Threats?
-Yeah, in so many words.
All right, okay. Look.
Listen very carefully.
First thing they got to do is
they got to get me out of here,
so what do they do?
They foreclose on me.
The bank.
They're the real crooks here.
Next, the builder comes in
and buys my house from the bank
at a discounted price.
Bank wins.
Next, the builder tears it down.
They go back to the same bank to
get financing for whatever it is
that they're gonna put up,
some work/live lofts, whatever.
Bank wins again.
Whoever buys this
whatever-it-is,
at the suggestion
of the builder,
goes back to the very same bank
to get their mortgage.
Bank wins again.
That's three times.
Three times. They all win.
They all win because
they're all in on it together.
They all win, everybody but me.
I lose my house, I lose my wife.
Wow.
-You really thought this through.
-I have,
and I can see that
you know what I'm saying here.
Yeah, but killing someone
and covering it up?
Why not?
Go to church on Sunday,
back to work on Monday.
Clean slate.
Of course, the banks will
tell you it's just business.
Okay. I'll take a look into it.
Ah, classic.
Ah, "I'll take a look into it."
Okay, Kojak.
That's a blow-off line
if I've ever heard one.
I just think
you're reaching here, Joe.
I mean, banks don't do that.
That's not the way it works.
Hey, the banks, all of them,
just watch the news!
You know what? Forget it.
I'll deal with it myself.
Joe, I told you that I'll...
Thanks for your help.
-Mr. Bigler?
-Yeah, that's right.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What can I do for you today?
Uh, do you think we could go
somewhere more private?
Yeah, of course.
Come on in.
Hey, come on.
Let's go, Dog.
In there.
Let's just, uh,
cut right to it, hmm?
-You recognize those?
-Mortgage bills. Are they yours?
No, they're his.
Of course they're mine.
Name Alice Bigler
mean anything to you?
My guess is your wife maybe.
Is she also a client here?
She was my wife.
She's gone now.
-She was killed.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
You know anything about that?
What?
Ah, ah. Don't look at him.
-I'm the story here.
-I'm sorry, I don't understand.
I think you do.
Rob?
That's your name? Rob?
Your parents have a crystal ball
or something?
All right.
Rob, uh...
I've been a customer here
for 25 years,
well before the fancy remodel.
I've never seen you
around before.
Probably because I've only been
here a little over three months.
Three months.
Huh, is that right?
Yeah, they-they tend
to shuffle us around.
How convenient.
Three months ago,
you got shuffled.
Mr. Bigler, I have no idea
what's going on here,
and I have no idea
how I can help you
or even what your concern is.
Now, perhaps if...
My wife dies.
I get a stack of bills
from you guys, followed by
twice as many threats
to "pay up, or else."
All because I take
time off to grieve.
Starting to sound familiar, Rob?
Uh, is-is this what you're
referring to as threats?
You tell me.
Well, Mr. Bigler,
these are courtesy letters.
The bank sends these out
whenever a customer is late.
It's a-a friendly reminder,
if you will.
That's how you see it.
I see it differently,
not so friendly.
Are you still behind currently,
on your payments?
Again, you tell me.
Well, looks like
just a couple of months.
Three months.
Three months, to be exact.
Well, we can certainly
take care of that today,
if that's what you want.
Uh, or under the circumstances,
I-I'm certain we could
get an extension.
At the very least,
I-I'd be glad to waive
-some of th-the penalties for...
-Ah, gee.
That's awfully nice of you.
Okay, so if that's
the only problem...
No, the problem is,
the problem is, Rob,
you can't have my house.
I'm not an idiot.
I know your plan here,
and you can't pivot me
with a couple of
meaningless goodwill gestures.
I can assure you,
it is never our goal
to take a home, especially not
after a loss like yours.
Oh, so if I didn't have a loss
like mine, you might think about
-taking my house?
-No, that's not what I meant.
We-we just don't do
that sort of thing.
Give me a break!
You killed her to get my house.
You and whoever it is
that you're working for,
you killed her to get my house,
it didn't work,
and now here I am
to call you on it.
Okay, I think this conversation
is over now.
No, no, Rob.
- Why, Joe?
- This guy!
That's not what I'm asking.
This is for you, Alice.
This is for you.
No, it's for you.
Mr. Bigler...
- Why, Joe?
- You say it.
"I killed her."
You say it, we're done here.
Just say it.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
-Again, Joe, why?
-Say it!
"I killed her"! Say it!
One last time, why?
You got no idea how hard it is
living with somebody who sees
everything so perfect
all the time, especially when
all you can sm-smell is
the rot underneath it all.
Doubt.
In everything you love.
Still, she never quit on me.
Not once.
Joe?
Hey, Alice, sweetie, you got to
answer your phone
when I call you.
Do you have any idea
where my glasses are?
-What?
-My glasses. I can't find them.
I told you before I left,
they're right on the TV cabinet
next to the remote.
Well, I'm standing right here,
they're not here.
They must have walked off
or I need them
worse than I think
because I've looked everywhere.
-They're not here.
-Joe.
I've looked everywhere, Alice.
Well, just use mine.
They're in the kitchen.
And I'll just find yours
when I get back, okay?
-How far away are you?
-Joe.
How far away are you?
I'm just on the road, but...
Well, I need you
to turn around and come back.
I need them.
I need mine, not yours.
I got a pile of work to do.
Yeah, and I've got a ride to do.
Alice, I need you
to turn around and come back.
Joe!
I need you to come back now.
You're a real piece of work
lately, you know that?
Come back now.
-Morning, Joe.
-What now?
You can't just walk into a bank
and blow off steam.
-It blows back.
-Yeah, I was wrong.
I'm gonna go in today
and patch things up.
It's not that easy,
not this time.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, what
are you, what are you doing?
What-what are you...
I warned you.
What-what's going on here?
Placing you under arrest
for aggravated assault.
What?
Are you in on this now, too,
Rollins, huh?
I just wanted to scare him,
make him talk, that's all.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you...
Fine, you won't do your job,
I'll do it for you.
-Whatever.
-You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford
an attorney,
one will be appointed for you.
Yeah, yeah,
we've all seen the TV show.
You know a good lawyer?
This is gonna be recorded.
I-I told you,
I'm gonna apologize to the guy.
Do we need these theatrics?
Come on, turn that thing off.
I have a couple questions.
Uh, this is-- are you--
this is a joke, right?
First, you refuse
your right to have
legal representation present,
is that correct?
-Because I got nothing to hide.
-Yes or no?
Yeah.
Yeah, sure, yeah.
You sure you don't want
to call your daughter?
-Absolutely not.
-All right.
I'm gonna ask you
a few questions
about you and your wife.
-Me?
-Yes, you.
The last person
your wife talked to was you.
On her cell phone,
right before the accident.
-Give or take a minute or two...
-You serious?
...depending on the timeline
we've created
with some of the first folks
on the scene.
-What timeline?
-A witness several blocks away
reported a white truck speeding
through around the same time.
Th-This is insane.
You did call her, correct?
On her cell phone?
-While she was on her bike?
-Yeah, but it was...
You mind sharing
what you discussed?
Are you accusing me
of this now, too?
What happened to her?
What is with you people?
I'm not accusing anyone,
all right?
I'm just finishing up what you
asked me to pursue, that's it.
This isn't what I had in mind.
It was nothing.
I told her I lost my glasses,
asked her if she knew
where they were, she said no.
-End of story.
-Are you sure? That's it?
Yes, that's it.
You have a temper.
First Norman Olsen,
now this guy at the bank.
Unbelievable.
The dent and the scratch
on the front right bumper
of your truck.
If we run a test on that,
what will we find?
You'll find out that I ran into
a post at a hardware store.
Believe me, the post
got the worst of it.
-You report it?
-It was a post.
You were checking me out.
Weren't you?
At my house. My truck.
Snooping around, even then.
And the cracked running light?
Same run-in with the post?
I remember, once in the ring,
back when I was getting started,
I knocked this guy down.
And I felt bad for him.
Can you imagine that, a fighter
feeling bad for the other guy?
So I help him back up to his
feet, show him some compassion.
Anyway, dumb move.
Guy clocks me,
knocks me right out.
I gave you more credit, Rollins.
I was trying to help you, you...
I never learn.
Dumb move.
Now, there's a sight.
What a mess.
Yes.
It is.
Can't see up from down
anymore, Alice.
So look sideways.
There's my girl.
Ah, I miss you.
I'd give everything in this
world to be with you right now.
Wherever that is.
I'm right here.
And from the looks of it,
neither of us
is going anywhere soon.
But again, that's your choice.
Damage I've done.
Ever think it might be time
to give yourself a break?
If I do,
I might lose you forever.
If you don't...
you just might.
Risky.
To forgive and to forget
are two different things.
I know you know that.
You're a miracle.
So are you.
A work in progress.
I'm so sorry for making
such a mess of it all.
For making you turn around
and come home.
Why... why'd I...
why'd I do that?
What for?
I'm-I'm sorry.
Shh.
I forgive you.
Thanks for doing this.
I'll pay you back, of course.
Sell the house,
whatever it takes.
I'm done with all of it,
I promise.
Don't thank me, thank him.
Of course.
Be grateful.
And whatever you do,
don't leave town.
Just like TV.
Thank you.
You are a terrier, right?
That's my best guess.
Look, you're starting
to grow on me, too,
but we got to find out
who owns you.
Time for both of us to move on.
You sure you don't want
to go out with me,
help me put
these things up, hmm?
Starting to think this whole
"man's best friend" thing
ain't for nothing.
And you never bark,
for which I am hugely grateful.
Not a bit confused.
I knew you'd come around.
Come on.
Sorry.
Hey! Hey. Hey, slow down.
Dog!
Oh. Oh.
Sorry. Sorry.
Dog!
Come on.
What?
Ah, slow-- Hey.
Hey! Hey!
All right.
Stop.
You're not doing my knees
any favors, pal.
What? What?
This place over here,
what about it?
Oh.
This is where you live?
You're not messing with me,
are you?
All right.
I guess this is it, then, huh?
What? What?
You want me to take you
over there?
No. These people are gonna be
mad that I kept you for so long.
You go on. Go on.
Fine.
All right, let's...
just get this over with.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on.
Hello?
What?
Hey.
What-what are you doing?
I shouldn't be
snooping around like this.
I'm already in enough trouble.
If this is your house
and you want to stay, stay.
But I'm not snooping around
like this.
What?
You're the one
who took me there.
This is on you
as much as it is me.
Think it through, Joe.
-Somebody's gonna get hurt.
-That's the idea.
I could almost feel you.
You were so close.
What happened?
Loose ends.
Guilt has to be assigned.
This is revenge.
Call it what you want.
They're accusing me, Alice.
And this is how
you set them straight.
Yes. This is how
I set them straight.
This is anger, not truth.
Alice, I love you,
but I'm begging you, not now.
One way or the other,
it all ends tonight.
You do this, Joe,
and you are on your own.
I am gone, forever.
-Alice...
-And you know that.
Alice, I got no more fight left.
The problem is
you never had fight, real fight.
-You punch at shadows...
-Alice, not now!
...make holes in walls...
Would you get the heck out of
here and let me finish this?!
...and the only person
who ever gets beaten up
-over and over again is you.
-Leave!
Wow.
You better say something soon,
'cause this guns
got a mind of its own.
How about we start with a name?
-Nathan Wells.
-Oh.
Oh, good evening, Nathan.
I'm Joe.
You found my dog.
So you belong to this punk?
If it means anything,
I've tried to--
since it happened, I-I've stood
outside your house...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, whoa.
You're also the same guy
that's been
creeping around
my house at night?
It was just an accident.
Whatever you think, I promise
you, it was an accident.
Oh.
Well, you promise me, then...
Huh?
Huh? Go on.
No?
Well, it looks like he switched
teams on you, Nathan.
-King.
-Huh?
His name is King.
I call him Dog,
but King, King kind of works.
Of course, it makes him a royal
pain in the butt.
It was an accident.
You say that once again and,
so help me, I will shoot you
right here on the spot.
Like that's supposed
to make it all right.
"It was an accident."
Please.
We can work this out.
I'll do anything.
Give me one reason,
give me one reason
why I should show you
an ounce of mercy,
when you didn't think twice
about doing the same for my wife
and then you ran off
like a coward.
I was wrong.
Do you know what they told me
after she was gone?
They said that if whoever hit
her called for help one minute,
maybe just one minute sooner,
they might have been able
to save her.
One minute. Ticktock.
My wife-- she's inside.
She's pregnant.
Well, my wife's dead.
I think I got you beat, pal.
What can I do?
We could go to the police.
I'll tell them everything,
I swear to...
Too little, too late.
Join the club.
All right. Here's what
we're gonna do, Nathan.
Anyone ever call you Nate?
No. No, not really.
All right, then, Nate.
One minute from now,
that's 60 seconds,
I'm gonna shoot you dead.
It's a fact.
I'm gonna kill you
because you killed my wife.
One minute from now.
Same amount of time, if you'd
made one simple phone call,
you might have been able
to save her.
You ever hear that expression
"all the time in the world"?
One minute just became
what's left of yours.
No.
-"No," what?
-I don't want to die.
You can't do this.
Nobody wants to die, Nathan,
and, yes, I can.
In 50 seconds.
I'm begging you. Please!
No, no, no, still nothing
coming through.
Uh, it happens.
Why are you doing this?
-40 seconds.
-Please.
My wife is gonna have a baby.
Yeah, that's what you said.
Consequences, right, Alice?
I didn't mean for it to happen.
I was just coming home
from work.
I-I had just gotten laid off,
for real.
Boo-hoo. 30 seconds.
I-I was just coming
down the road, not even fast.
I don't think
I even had a stop sign.
Oh, please, you do not
want to tick me off
more than you already have with
"I don't think
I had a stop sign."
And quite frankly,
I don't buy your whole
"I got laid off" sob story.
It's true, I was.
So I was, I was distracted.
I don't know.
I was thinking about the baby.
How I'm gonna take care of it.
It was just an accident.
-20 seconds.
-Please.
Did you even bother to check
on her after you hit her?
Of course.
It was horrible.
Sh-She wasn't moving.
And still, you just
left her there, huh?
Like roadkill.
Who are you? What kind of man
does something like that?
I panicked.
Yeah, 'cause you got
a baby coming.
Got to be honest with you, kid's
gonna be better off without you.
I thought if-if I go to
somebody, if-if I told someone,
the-the police, everything
would change in an instant.
Nothing would ever be
the same again. And my wife?
It all just happened so fast,
so, yeah,
I panicked and I left.
It was wrong! I was wrong!
And the longer I-I didn't
do anything about it,
the more I couldn't
because it would only
make things worse
because I left.
I'm sorry.
And I tried to go to you.
And I couldn't even do that.
I'm sorry!
All right?
But that's all I got!
Yeah, that's right.
Time's up.
Put down the gun, Joe.
Cutting it kind of close
there, Detective.
I... I think I could've
actually shot him.
You don't want to tell me that.
Put the gun down.
Put the gun down slowly.
Nathan?
I'm sorry.
What did you do, Nathan?
Nathan.
You could've said
something... King.
I am sorry.
Stupid.
-Yeah.
-All of it.
She deserves better than me.
They all deserve better than us.
Look, kid.
I know why you did what you did,
to protect her.
I get that.
I just wish it hadn't been
at the expense of my wife.
We had a son.
He died suddenly.
Man,
I just got sucker punched.
Put me right over the edge.
So I disappeared.
One day, Alice--
That was her name, by the way,
in case you missed that.
She sits me down,
looks at me point-blank,
and says that
if we're gonna survive,
I'm gonna have to make a choice.
I can keep staring down
at my feet or I can...
I can look up at the stars.
That simple.
Course, I, uh, came back
with a joke.
I said, "It's daytime, dummy.
There are no stars."
She shot right back at me,
"Just 'cause you cant
see them right now
doesn't mean they're not up
there, dummy."
I guess this business of life
has always been pretty, um,
"what you see
is what you get" for me.
We come into this world, we work
our way through it, we move on.
Have a couple of laughs
along the way.
You know the truth?
Sad reality?
Her ability to deal with
all this kind of crap
that life throws at you,
all this...
...I knew where it came from.
Always.
And it ju-- it would burn me up.
I'd resent her because
I knew it was connected
to some... goodness...
...that I was, I was
never able to buy into.
And she... she could so easily.
What are you saying?
Heck if I know.
-You should keep him.
-Hmm?
Dog. Or whatever
you want to call him.
At least for now.
It would be one less worry.
You're assuming all this
is gonna blow over for me.
We share blame here.
And I'm the one
who pulled the gun.
An empty gun.
They're not gonna do
anything to you.
Well, if it works out that way,
maybe till you're sorted.
Did you really get fired?
-That day?
-Oh, yeah.
What kind of work you do?
Paint.
You know, houses.
Huh.
So what did you do
to get dumped?
Truth?
Oh, now, now he starts.
I hated the people
I worked with.
I got into a thing with one of
them, one of those know-it-alls.
Only he didn't know anything.
He just walked around all day
motor mouthing.
I know the type.
Sometimes it takes all you got
not to punch them down
just to teach them a lesson.
Yeah.
Might serve you well
to keep that thought
to yourself and, uh,
you'll work your way through it,
you and your wife.
She must've been
an incredible woman, Alice.
She was.
Pure love.
I think maybe I see some of that
in your girl there.
I think...
I think Alice would want me
to say, um...
that I forgive you.
Do you?
I don't know.
It's a work in progress.
Yeah.
How come you're being
so okay about all this?
You think that's
what this is, me being okay?
I'm not okay.
You two gentlemen
simmered down yet?
Yeah. We're simmered.
Good luck, kid.