(slow dramatic music)
(slow guitar music)
(men speaking in foreign language)
(slow dramatic music)
(guns firing)
(slow guitar music)
(men speaking in foreign language)
(gun fires)
(slow dramatic music)
(slow guitar music)
(men speaking in foreign language)
(slow dramatic music)
(slow guitar music)
(gun fires)
- [Commander] All right, keep
your head and necks down.
(gun fires)
Keep them down!
(slow guitar music)
(men speaking in foreign language)
- [Announcer] All right, men, listen up.
The training exercise, small
arms fire, 18:00 hours.
The first section, 18:00 hours.
All sections, all your
ordnance production reports
to Colonel Sperry before
the end of the day.
- Where are the clips?
- Worry later.
- Some more shell casings.
- Whoa there, come on.
There goes the sparks.
(quiet overlapping chattering)
(people speaking in foreign language)
(motorcycle engines revving)
- Go on.
(slow dramatic music)
(people speaking in foreign language)
(women speaking in foreign language)
(women screaming)
(people speaking in foreign language)
- You must be Gonzalez.
(Gonzalez speaking in foreign language)
- You filed a report
against us with the sheriff.
You even approached
the Farm Worker's Union
for help against this evil militia.
- One day, someone will bring justice
to this town, you'll see.
(women crying)
- You got guts.
You have got guts.
I admire your bravery,
Mr. Gonzalez, I truly do.
But I cannot condone this kind
of activity, you understand?
Shoot him.
(Gonzalez speaking in foreign language)
- No, please!
(group speaking in foreign language)
(gun fires)
(women screaming)
- You live life weakly
if you cannot appreciate
the extermination of vermin.
(slow dramatic music)
(woman speaking in foreign language)
(overlapping chattering)
(door creaks)
- [Jose] They will kill us all.
- [Audience Member] Yeah,
you saw them, right?
We all saw them over here, right?
- [Hector] Hola, Pablo.
(overlapping chattering)
- [Woman] Hector, Hector.
(speaking in foreign language)
- [Jose] There were no witnesses, huh?
- [Audience Member] Yeah, witnesses.
- [Jose] Were there witnesses?
- We all saw them over here,
right, didn't you see them?
I saw them.
- Who, who is going to testify?
That's what I thought.
- Well, what can we do?
If we testify, they will kill us.
I don't want to die.
- He's right, remember Monte
Planto and his brother?
They went to the sheriff,
and the very next afternoon,
they were dead.
And now, now Gonzalez.
(overlapping chattering)
And before that, Jorge
Menendez was beaten so badly
that he could not ever walk again.
(overlapping chattering)
- Why don't we go to the
state police or the FBI?
(overlapping chattering)
- Really, amigo, then both
of us will get deported.
The sheriffs only keep us
around as long as we stay out
of trouble and as long as
we do the town's dirty work.
(overlapping chattering)
- Well, what are we going to do?
Are we gonna let them keep
killing us one by one?
(slow music)
- Then we must fight the militia.
- You are crazy, Hector, how?
We got no guns.
- Then we hire other killers.
We fight fire with fire.
(slow guitar music)
(quiet overlapping chattering)
- Like we really know people
who could stand a chance
against the militia.
- For hire. (speaking in foreign language)
You look good up here.
Green beret with trained mercenary team.
Expert skills, can handle any problem.
Contact Lieutenant William Fredrickson.
There's an address in Los
Angeles and no telephone number.
It's going to cost us plenty,
but it may be it's our last hope.
(slow music continues)
- My brother is right.
If everyone chips in all
the money they can afford,
he and I will take the morning train
to Los Angeles to hire this man.
(group speaking in foreign language)
- Yeah.
(train horn honks)
(slow guitar music)
(siren wails)
(overlapping chattering)
(helicopter wings whirring)
- Lieutenant Fredrickson?
- Uh, yeah, uh, have a seat.
Dad?
(toilet flushes)
- Damn.
- Lieutenant Fredrickson?
- You boys in from the deli?
- Senor, is this you?
- Yeah, could be.
Could be.
Sit down, sit down, boys, tell me,
tell me what I can do for
you, what do you want?
- We need you to help us fight a militia.
- There ain't no militias around here.
- No, not here, senor, in Texas.
- How many are there?
- Over 100.
- Shit, is that all?
100, (laughs) they got a lot of firepower?
- Well, yes, senor.
- They have many guns.
- Yeah, sounds like you
boys got a little problem,
doesn't it?
I know all about the militias, I do.
I've been there, boys, I've been there.
They're scary and they get dangerous.
It's expensive, too,
how much money you got?
- Uh, how much is your fee?
- Fee? (stammers)
Anyway, it's more than you can afford.
- You don't know how much we got, senor.
- Don't make no difference.
Carmen will show you the way out.
Good, good luck, boys, yeah.
(slow music)
You boys ever run into somebody out there
that smells like a dill pickle,
you tell him to get his ass in here fast.
Yeah.
- Wait, listen, listen, I have an idea.
There's this guy, his name is McQue.
I've never seen him before,
but I've heard about him
from guys who have come in here
and he's supposed to be tough.
- Where can we find him?
- Well, he works at a motorcycle shop
about a block and a half away.
(Carmen sighs)
Let me see.
First you have to go
over to Margaret's Diner.
It's over on Spring Street.
Here it is, okay, pencil, um.
I don't have my pen,
lipstick, (laughs) okay.
(slow music)
(overlapping chattering)
- [Man In Ball Cap] Two
blocks and make a right.
- Okay, thank you.
- [Chef] Jerked fish on rye.
- This looks like a drop-top Benz.
I can do that, a Dodge
Viper, cherry apple red.
I can do that, how much
you paying? (scoffs)
I can't do that, no, that's INGA,
it's not gonna happen.
- Bueno, here we are.
What do we do now?
We don't even know what
this man looks like.
This is all your idea.
- My idea, no.
Who's the one who said, "Me
and my brother will go to LA"?
- We don't even belong here.
- [Waitress] More coffee here?
- Don't blame me.
- Maybe we should go back to Los Robles.
- Look, how was I supposed
to know this guy Fredrickson
was gonna be some kind
of alcoholic drunk, stupid, crazy nut?
- How can we talk to this McQue
when we can't even recognize him?
- Shut up, Jose. (background
noise drowns out speaker)
(slow dramatic music)
- Listen up and no one gets hurt.
- All right, everybody, put
your hands on the table.
- Put your money and your
jewelry on the table.
Keep your hands in the air.
Put your money and your
jewelry on the table.
(quiet overlapping chattering)
- Hands behind your heads.
All right, don't move.
Get your hands on the back of your head.
- Get down, right now.
Get them up.
- No.
- Hey.
What are you, deaf?
You, what are you, a tough guy, huh?
You think you're a tough guy?
- All the town's money's in those bags.
- Now, you listen to me,
if you don't shut up,
he's gonna hear you, he's gonna kill you,
and if he doesn't kill you, I will.
- I said give up the cash.
Wallet, jewelry, rings,
everything you got.
- I don't mind you taking this stuff,
just leave the sunglasses.
- [Robber] What's so
special about the glasses?
- They're my favorite pair.
- Hey, boys, Johnny Webb
here has got an affection
for his sunglasses.
(gun clicks)
Now you listen to me.
This gun's sticking in your ear,
and all I gotta do is pull the trigger,
and poof, no more tough guy.
- I don't care what you do,
just don't touch the glasses.
(people screaming)
(overlapping chattering)
(gun fires)
(dishes clattering)
(people screaming)
(glass shatters)
(wheels screeching)
- [Jose] I thought that was McQue.
- That's our man, whether
that was McQue or not.
- Come on.
(slow music)
(sirens wailing)
- GI Joe with kung fu grip, want a ride?
- I don't need a ride.
- I think you need a ride.
(slow guitar music)
This is it?
Hey, yo.
Check it out-
(door rattles)
(motorcycle engine revs)
Hmm.
Britt,
Jeremy Britt, I'm a CDM, a can-do man,
and I'd like to talk to you for a minute.
- Do me a favor, Mr. CDM.
Turn around and leave.
(Jeremy laughs)
- That's pretty cold, man.
I give you a ride here, you
shut the door in my face,
and I ain't even said nothing
about your confederate hat.
Can't we just all get along?
Besides, I need some
muscle every now and then.
- You want muscle, join a gym.
What is this, visitor's day?
- Senor McQue, Hector Chavez.
This is my brother, Jose.
- What can I do for you?
- Uh, we saw what you
could do at the restaurant
and we need to speak with you.
- Just one minute, please, senor.
- Go ahead.
- We come from a small
town called Los Robles.
It's in Texas on the Mexican border.
About 20 miles east,
there's this compound.
- It's for the Sons of Texas.
Senor, it's a bunch of
right-wing red necks.
- You've got 45 seconds.
- They hate us because we're Mexican.
They hate anybody who's not white.
They steal from us every month.
They take food, supplies,
anything they want.
They have killed and they have raped.
- The sheriff, he does nothing to help us.
- Why don't you go to the
state police, Texas Rangers?
- Oh, we can't, some of us are illegals.
Some of us have lived there for 30 years.
- So why don't you just fight back?
- Fight, we cannot fight back, senor, no.
No, see, there's over 100
of them and they are devils.
One of us tried to stand
up to them last week
and they murdered him in the street.
- We're not trained fighters, like you,
you and others like you.
(slow orchestral music)
- We are willing to pay, senor.
$14,000.
7,000 now and the balance when
you have completed the job.
You are our only hope, senor.
We cannot go back to
Los Robles empty handed.
We cannot let our people down.
- I feel for your problem.
You're not gonna find a lot of men willing
to risk their lives for $14,000.
Sorry.
I can't help you.
(slow guitar music)
- Damn, let's go.
We were led to believe
that you were someone
who would understand, but
we're not gonna beg, vamos.
- Hector. (speaking in foreign language)
- No, vamos.
(Jose speaking in foreign language)
- [Jose] We cannot listen
to the. (speaking in foreign language)
- What if I told you there was a lot
of money at the compound,
that the town people have heard
that the militia has millions of dollars.
- Oh, si, senor, they
keep it in a big safe.
It's how they pay the
sheriff off every month.
We all know about it.
(Jeremy knocks)
- You hear that?
That would be opportunity knocking.
You get a couple of your boys together,
take care of our friends' problems,
and we're rolling in the
dough, millions, even.
- You want to chase
rainbows, go chase rainbows.
You don't know diddly
squat about this militia.
Now get the hell out of here, all of yous.
- [Hector] Jose, we're leaving.
- Wait, wait, wait, Chavez, whoa, whoa.
Chill, chill, my Spanish brother.
Come here, we can do this.
Let cooler heads prevail.
This is what I got in mind.
(guns firing)
- Sir, I must tell you, the
men are getting restless.
They've been training over a year.
They have yet to see action.
- In peaceful conditions,
a warlike man would turn upon himself.
Nietzsche said that.
That is not going to happen here.
Our battle will soon be upon us.
This country is coming apart at the seams.
You got foreigners everywhere you look.
Washington is scheming
to take away even more
of our liberties.
Hell, we're the best
chance this country's got.
- [Commander] Cease fire.
- [Lamont] Callin, get over here!
- Yes, sir?
- You men know that using
the telephone is prohibited.
- [Men] Yes, sir.
- That call, sir, will cost
you one week in the brig.
- Let's go.
- Find out what you can on him.
I want to know everything there is.
- Yes, sir.
- The rest of you men continue.
- Sons of Texas.
Lamont Sperry, blah blah blah blah blah.
Hmm, McQue, I took my men outside
and had a chat with them,
checked this stuff out,
they're right, look, straight from the net
and CIA email, I download the bio
of the militia leader Lamont Sperry,
former Special Forces commander.
He's supposed to be sitting on millions
in profits from illegal arms deals.
Now, my guess is, the
money's at the compound,
like Hector and Jose said.
- What makes you think that?
- Well, he sure didn't put it in the bank
where the government can get to it.
- So why aren't the feds after it?
- After Waco and Ruby Ridge,
they want to be real sure
before they make a move.
- How reliable is this information?
- [Jeremy] Straight from the
government news releases.
- That gives me a lot of confidence.
- No, no, look, either the
money is at the compound,
or we can track it down from there.
I think it's at the compound.
You get yourself some men together,
I'll get a plane and get us to Texas.
- And how would you manage that?
- I'm a businessman.
A CDM, remember?
- How often do Sperry and
his men come to Los Robles?
- At the end of each month.
- That gives me three weeks.
- How you gonna get these men?
- That's my business.
- How do you know they're
gonna be any good?
- I'll know.
You just leave that little bag here.
The other we'll expect when
I arrive in Los Robles.
- And when will that be?
- 12 days from now.
- But how do we know you
just won't take our money
and not show up?
- You're just gonna have to trust me.
- Well, I'll be back tomorrow.
- Don't bother, just leave
your cellular number.
(slow music)
- MC Que, what's going on?
- What the hell are you doing here?
- I followed you, who you waiting for?
Look, I gotta know what's going on
before I put up the
dough to fly us to Texas.
Better get your ass out the street.
(tires screech)
(Dash laughs)
- [McQue] Good to see you.
- Long time.
- [McQue] So how's everything
on the racing circuit?
- Ah, it sucked.
- [McQue] Yeah?
- About a year ago, I got an accident.
French doctor said I'd
never walk again. (laughs)
What do they know, huh?
- [McQue] They know about
great wine and beautiful women.
- That's one of the things I respect
about McQue, no pretense.
- Yeah, I like that, too.
- I need a driver, interested?
- Government or private?
- Private.
- How much?
- Not much up front,
but it could be a big
payoff on the back end.
- I'm in.
- Let's have some fun.
- Great, Simms is my name.
- [Jeremy] Britt, Jeremy Britt.
- Well, it's a pleasure to meet you.
Let's go for a ride, huh, yeah.
- Where we going?
- For pancakes.
(slow electronic music)
- Hold, hold on, I already
ate, I ain't hungry.
- Coffee.
- I don't drink coffee.
- Skim milk.
- Skim milk?
(car engine revs)
Hey, slow down!
(tires screeching)
Whoa, whoa, what the
hell is going on here?
McQue, Simms, Simms!
- Come on.
- That was great, man, look
at McQue, McQue, McQue.
- [Dash] Come on, better
look out, get out of my way.
- [Patron] You're crazy!
(overlapping chattering)
(motorcycle engine revs)
(Jeremy cries out)
- [Dash] Look out, relax.
- [Jeremy] Don't tell me what-
- [Dash] Whoa!
- Whoa, Simms!
(tires screeching)
(car horn honks)
(Jeremy groans)
Simms, my car, my car,
my car, my car, my car!
(tires screeching)
I, I think you'll be fine.
(overlapping chattering)
- This is your last chance,
it's your last chance
to place your bets, place your bets.
The last chance here,
time is running out, boys.
Place your bets, get
them down, get them down.
Get them down, don't be shy.
Last chance, and that's it,
no more money, my friend.
No more money, we're gonna get it on.
In this corner, all the way
from St. Louis, Missouri,
we've got Mike, the Missouri Mule.
(background noise drowns out speaker)
- Yeah.
(crowd cheers)
(overlapping shouting)
- That's right, folks, and over here,
coming to us all the way from Germany,
we got Mr. Kurt Mayer.
(crowd cheers)
Listen up, listen up, listen up.
We got the same rules as always.
There's not any.
(crowd cheers)
It's the last man standing is the winner.
(slow dramatic music)
Let's go, gentlemen.
- I'm pumped.
(overlapping shouting)
- Let's go, boys.
Let's get it on, let's get it on.
(overlapping shouting)
(crowd cheers)
(Kurt groans)
(overlapping shouting)
(crowd cheers)
- Good job, good job.
Yeah.
(crowd cheers)
$145, and you earned every bit of it.
- [McQue] He deserves more.
- [Kurt] McQue in this house.
- Kurt, how's the (indistinct)?
(both laughing)
- Hey, Pauly, who the hell is this guy?
- Will you leave us alone, please?
How the hell did you find me?
- I made a few phone calls.
What are you doing in a place like this?
- Hell, it's not easy to find a shop
in our line of work.
- Why don't you start your own business?
- Like what?
- [McQue] Protection.
- Depends for whom.
- Hey, he's got a job, be here
next week and don't be late.
- Shut up, pinhead.
How much?
- 2,000 up front, maybe more.
That buys a lot of knockwurst.
- You have just bought yourself
some serious protection.
- [McQue] Come on, let's get out of here.
- Hey, what about me?
We got a contract for three more fights.
- Call my lawyer.
- So McQue, you gotta put
me down with this, man.
I'm not gonna take no for an answer.
- Let me ask you, what
can you do? Can you fight?
- [Jeremy] Uh.
- Can you handle a weapon?
(Jeremy stammers)
Have you ever been in a battle?
- No, I'm an acquisitions man.
I can get my hands on
anything, and I'm smart.
- Well, if you're so smart,
then why would you want
to take a chance on
getting yourself killed?
- I mean, I can't explain
it, but these guys,
Hector and Jose, I care for them, man.
I want to help them.
- You really feel that way?
- I swear to God, scout's honor.
Did you know I was an international scout?
- You know what?
You're full of shit.
(both laughing)
But you put a smile on my face.
You get us the plane, you can ride along.
After that, we'll see.
- So tell me something
about this guy we're going
to pick up, who is he, what does he do?
- He's crazy.
(slow music)
Turn left at the sign.
- Two, four, two, three,
four, five, six, seven.
(quiet overlapping chattering)
- [Jeremy] You gotta be kidding
me, your friend works here?
McQue, she's looking at me.
- [McQue] Don't fall in love.
We'll be out of here in 15 seconds.
- You're not my boyfriend.
- Next time, try flowers, let's go.
- McQue!
Hey, McQue!
(overlapping chattering)
Back up the car, McQue!
- [Woman Guard] Stop, get over here!
- Come back, come here!
- [Woman Guard] Hoffman, get over here!
- Stop him, stop him!
(Latrell cheers)
Stop him.
- [Patient] Oh, let him go.
- Hey, stop!
(overlapping chattering)
- Man, that was beautiful.
McQue, man, to the rescue.
Hey, hey, who's this, this
your chauffer? (laughs)
That was beautiful, Q
man, I loved it, man.
I loved it. (cheers)
I gotta piss, I gotta piss.
- Not yet.
- I am about to urinate in your car
if you don't pull this thing over.
Would you pull the car over?
Come on, come on, come on.
- Thank you for not pissing in my ashtray.
(Latrell cheers)
- Sweet juniper.
I heard you got out of government service.
What you been up to?
- Oh, a little of this, a little of that.
- [Latrell] Well, you don't
take a man like the Q man,
take him out of covert
operations in Panama,
Grenada, end up putting
him behind the desk.
- Oh, I didn't know that.
- Much better, (sighs) much better.
- You still got connections in El Paso?
- Oh, yeah, yeah, I can
get you more armament
than half the countries
in the United Nations.
I mean, if it's still there,
I hadn't been there in years.
I have been a little preocupado. (laughs)
- What can you get your hands on?
- Well, I can... hey,
goddammit, don't touch me!
Got a lot of weapons and
explosives and ammunition and such,
I think they got some civilian
things, some nitroglycerin.
Should ought to be able
to pack a pop still.
Might be dated.
You, uh, you got a good driver?
- Simms.
- Simms?
Simms, 'cause that son of a
bitch tried to kill me once.
Now, is there anybody else,
McQue, I need to know about?
- Remi Sykes.
- Well, now, Remi Sykes, she
can kill me anytime she wants.
I wouldn't mind getting
myself a little bit of that.
(slow orchestral music)
(phone rings)
- Yeah?
- [McQue] We'll all be
meeting at eight o'clock.
- Let's make it 8:15.
- [McQue] No later, Remi.
- Yeah.
- You have the money?
- Yeah, that was great.
- Where's your friend?
(gun fires)
(slow music continues)
- Thank you.
- [Attendant] Thank you, ma'am.
(sirens wailing)
Have a good evening.
- [Jeremy] Britt, Jeremy Britt.
- Remi Sykes.
- Hi.
You're late.
- I thought I had some time to kill.
- Remi, good to see you.
- For sure.
- Hi, you too.
- Kurt Mayer, please, have a seat.
- Deutsche, huh?
(Kurt speaking in foreign language)
(Remi speaking in foreign language)
- [Kurt] Vienna?
- Salzburg.
- Where's Hoffman?
- Doesn't need to be here.
- You got Latrell Hoffman?
Well, that's just perfect, he's wacko.
- He may be a nut, but he's at his best
when his back's up against the wall.
- How do you fit in?
- I arranged for us to get to Texas.
- He's a travel agent.
- I'm a can-do man, anything
you guys need, I can do.
Planning, acquisitions, you name it.
I'm the one who got you the info
on Lamont Sperry and the Sons of Texas.
- When do we leave?
- Tomorrow.
We meet at the airport at 08:00 hours.
Kurt, you and Remi will train
any locals who volunteer.
Simms, you'll drive Hoffman
to pick up the ordnance and explosives.
- Hoffman, oh, great, thank you,
then you're gonna get me
killed the first day. (laughs)
- Better you than us.
(group laughs)
Britt, you'll work with Hector and Jose
to gather all the information
you can on the compound.
I want building plans, photographs,
anything you can get your hands on.
Now, I want to reiterate
what I said before.
This is gonna be like
stepping into a bear trap,
but if we're successful,
there could be enough money
to make it worth the risk.
- Well, now, that's what
we're all in it for,
the money, huh, cheers.
- Hey, I'm down for the cause.
- If anyone wants out,
now's the time to speak up.
- One more beer, please.
(group laughs)
- Okay, hasta manana.
- Yeah.
- Crazy German.
- Remi, from what I hear,
this Los Robles is a dumpy little place.
So if you're too caught up with city life,
you're not gonna be happy.
- I'll be fine, what about him?
You think he's up for it?
- Oh, you don't have to
worry about me, baby doll.
I'm down for anything.
- Don't call me baby doll.
(slow music)
(Remi scoffs)
- You got a way with women.
(slow dramatic music)
(plane propellers whirring)
- [Air Traffic Controller]
Midnight black 122,
you're clear for takeoff.
(plane engine roars)
(slow guitar music)
(men speaking in foreign language)
(couple speaking in foreign language)
(group speaking in foreign language)
(Jose speaking in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
(group speaking in foreign language)
(group cheers)
(group applauds)
- Hey, yeah, forget y'all.
(group cheers)
- Hey, thank you!
(Latrell speaking in foreign language)
Thank you, thank you!
(overlapping chattering)
(group cheers)
(slow dramatic music)
(Latrell speaking in foreign language)
- Yes, senor, you speak English.
(Latrell laughs)
- You do that again without permission,
you'll pull back a stump.
- Is that the truck you promised us?
- Yeah, it's the best I could do.
My friend's plugging a leak.
- Can you call the town meet
tonight, about eight o'clock?
- Yeah, eight o'clock is good.
- Thank you.
There's your truck.
- Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
You don't want me to drive this, do you?
- You want Hoffman to drive?
- Well, come on, hotshot,
gonna take us forever
in this beauty.
- [Dash] Oh, terrific, just terrific.
- No Sauerbraten here.
(Kurt laughs)
(slow dramatic music)
- We couldn't come up with
anything on his background.
He could be a plant, or
maybe he was a true believer.
- In a few minutes, it won't
make a damn bit of difference.
Go get him.
- [Sven] Bring him in.
- Move it.
- All right, everybody, listen up.
Griffin is here to teach you
the power of martial arts.
So pay attention to this
most important lesson.
- You're no patriot, all
you teach is militias
your philosophy of evil.
You got that?
- The great turning point in our lives is
when we gain the courage
to accept our evil
as what is best in us.
Fight!
(overlapping chattering)
- Come on, get up and fight!
- Come on, come on.
(overlapping shouting)
- Come on, get up, let's go!
Come on, get up!
(overlapping shouting)
(slow dramatic music)
- Come on, kick him, take him down!
(overlapping shouting)
(Lamont sighs)
- I want him dropped out
on the old creek road.
Let the son of a bitch rot in the sun.
- And your prayers have been
listened to for a long time,
and God willing, those prayers
are now being answered.
I wish now to introduce
you to Senor McQue.
(Jeremy claps)
Senor?
- It's not easy to live with fear.
You feel powerless,
desperate.
This is your land,
your town.
No one's gonna defend it like you.
We need your help.
- We don't know how to fight.
- That's it.
That's all I need, that impulse.
- But we hired you to fight.
We paid you a lot of money,
half of it in Los Angeles.
- And we'll earn every
penny of that money,
but there's about 100 of
them and only six of us.
Two of my men will be arriving
tomorrow with armament.
We'll find out which of
you can handle weapons
and teach you, give me some volunteers.
(slow music)
- Look, uh, he's right.
It's about action here, we can't
keep looking at each other.
So who's down to help themselves?
- Senor, eh, no offense,
but you don't exactly look
like a fighter yourself.
- I'm not talking about that.
I'm looking for a few volunteers.
(slow music continues)
- [Remi] This is ridiculous.
- Hmm?
- Uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh.
(Latrell spits)
This is not what I do best.
(truck creaks)
(Latrell grunts)
Do you have to do that?
- You know, when I was in
the Clearview State Home,
I used to brush my teeth
four, maybe five times a day,
probably 15 minutes each.
Of course, you know, it's
very, very, very important
to floss, so what I'd
do is on the weekdays,
I would start to floss on the right,
and I'd work my way to the left,
and then on the weekends, I
would floss left, work right.
What day is it, anyway?
- It's the worst day of my life.
- Anyway, you want to know what the moral
of the story is, Simms?
I mean, every picture tells a story,
every story has a moral.
Would you, Mr. Simms,
like to know what the
moral of the story is?
- Enlighten me, would you?
- No tartar. (laughs)
- So,
GSG 9, huh, I'm impressed.
Most elite anti-terrorist
group in the world.
What the hell are you doing here?
- When you turn 32, you can
no longer work in the field.
So I quit on my 32nd birthday.
You spend a lot of time alone?
- Yeah, I usually find
company disappointing.
- Why is that?
- I had a strange childhood,
maybe that had something to do with it.
We moved around a lot when I was a kid,
and I couldn't exactly tell my friends
what my dad did for a living.
So when he died,
I followed in his
footsteps, female cleaner.
(slow music)
- [Dash] Make it snappy.
(truck door slams)
(chain rattles)
(truck engine revs)
(truck door slams)
- The white zone is for
loading and unloading only.
Yeah, I think this is the place.
Come on, hoss.
Let me get that for you.
Looks about right.
Find anything there, hoss?
- I don't believe this.
There's nothing there.
- Yeah, there you go.
(lighter clicks)
Child proof.
Loony proof. (laughs)
- Are you crazy?
- I'm certified crazy by the best doctors
in the whole state of California.
- Give me that, give it to
me, give it to me, give it.
With this much explosives,
you could have blown us sky high, man.
- Yeah, but at least we'd get out
with a blaze of glory (laughs)
I got us in here,
why don't you just go ahead
and load us up? (laughs)
- You need a straight jacket.
(Latrell laughs)
(slow music)
- Hmm?
Thanks.
- Nice try, (indistinct)
but I'm gonna need more.
All I can tell from this stuff is
that the walls surrounding
the compound are
about 20 feet high and
there's one main gate.
- Man, I've tapped FBI
files, CIA files. (sighs)
I think it's time for some Britt tricks.
- [Dash] Let's roll.
- I'm going.
(Dash pants)
Are we having any fun yet?
(ordnance rattles)
- Ow.
(gun fires)
- [Remi] Why are you here?
- With the money, I could start over,
and one day, if I meet the right woman,
maybe settle down and have a family.
- Well, that's not a
future I'd ever considered.
- I'm not driving that,
there's no way, that's suicide.
- You were driving the nitro,
what the hell do you
think McQue hired you for?
You're a good driver, aren't
you, huh, are you good?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- Then we have absolutely
no problem then, do we?
- Except I don't drive things like that.
Look at the tires on that,
you couldn't float them in a river.
Forget it, I ain't driving the nitro.
- Listen, Simms, I know you and me,
we've had our few differences in the past,
but I'm the kind of man
who can let bygones go by.
You know why?
Because I can be extremely objective.
- Yeah.
- You understand?
- Yeah, got it.
(fly buzzes)
(Latrell spits)
- I hate flies.
- Me too.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Easy.
(crate squeaks)
(Latrell laughs)
- [Jeremy] Got it, hot off the
press, plans to the compound.
There's the east gate, the west gate.
I got us the plans, now
you gotta get us in there.
(truck screeches)
- What the hell are we
stopping for this time?
- There's a body on the road.
- Is he breathing?
- Hell, I don't know, kick him.
(Callin moans)
- Yeah, he's alive.
Let's get him in the truck.
I'll help you out.
- [Dash] Thank you.
- I'll get the tarp.
- What? (groans)
Stupid basket case.
In fact, you're way beyond
baskets, you're in the pottery.
- Here, let me get this for you.
You got it?
I got him, I got it.
(truck engine revs)
You know, uh,
if we happen to hit a
chuckhole the wrong way,
if we're blown into,
say, a million pieces,
do you think we'll still meet God,
or will we meet him one piece at a time?
- Just shut up, man.
I am tired of hearing about the home,
I'm tired of hearing about
your brushing, your flossing.
Can't you just talk about
something intelligent?
Because if you can't, just shut up
and don't say nothing at
all, you understand me?
(slow dramatic music)
- [Sven] Sir, the townspeople
have hired some mercenaries.
- Now this time, we're gonna
have to call out the dogs.
Your men wanted action?
- Yes, sir.
- Then it's action they'll get.
Turn them loose.
- Yes, sir.
- I ought to kick your ass
for everything you put me
through, you know that?
- Well, if you want to kiss my ass,
Simms, I can accommodate that.
(Dash sighs)
- You know, you're more dangerous
to us than if you worked for Sperry.
If I didn't have so
much respect for McQue,
I'd break your neck.
- You know, I learned back at the home
that it's not really healthy
to keep all this pent
up aggression inside.
I suggest that you learn
how to release it, hoss.
- That's the first intelligent
thing you said all day.
(Latrell cries out)
- Stop the bullshit.
You can kill each other
when we finish here.
- Come on, let me show you
what I found in the truck.
And you need a straight jacket.
- It's gonna wind up in your back someday.
(slow music)
Take him inside.
- Hey, this ain't over.
- You've got two choices.
Help us with what you know,
or I'll federal express
you back to Sperry.
Think about it for a couple of hours.
Untie him and give him some food.
(door slams)
- [Jeremy] Who's the man, McQue?
- Good job, Mr. CDM, but
this is just the structure.
We need to know what it's like inside.
- Seems like our friend here has something
he wants to say to us.
- I'd like to help.
- You can start by giving
us a reason to trust you.
- Well, for starters, Sperry's got a safe
with a few million dollars
inside, how's that?
- Now how would you know that?
- Because I saw it.
- Well, if you know where it
is, why don't you tell us?
- Well, if you let me in
on some of the action,
I'll show you where it is.
- Can you detail the interior
structure of the compound?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Get to work.
- Hey.
How do I know I can trust you?
- You're just gonna
have to take that risk.
(motorcycle engines revving)
- [Man In Blue Shirt] No, senor, no!
(people screaming)
(slow dramatic music)
(man laughs)
- Just what the hell do you
think you're doing here?
- We thought we'd do a little shopping.
- A little what?
- [Man On Red Motorcycle]
All right, scumbag.
(gun fires)
(man on red motorcycle cries out)
- Just was the hell are you?
You guys don't belong here,
and you are gonna learn a lesson.
We'll be back, and when we do, (laughs)
you're not gonna get off quite so easy.
Okay, out of here.
(motorcycle engines revving)
(slow music)
- [Lamont] It's a damned disgrace!
- [Australian Man] She had a rifle, man,
she was up in the tower.
Look, there was nothing we could do.
I'm telling you, there
was nothing we could do.
Now, she could have killed us all.
- What am I seeing here?
- This low-life (indistinct)
is a disgrace to all of us.
- And what do we do when
someone disgraces us?
- Punish him.
- Then punish him.
Get out of my sight.
- [Announcer] Attention, Lieutenant Smith,
ordnance assembly, please.
Lieutenant Smith,
- I'll kill them all.
Guess I have to take care
of everything myself.
(slow orchestral music)
- [McQue] Well, I didn't plan that out.
- You just happened to get
it like that, huh? (laughs)
- [Lamont] Now, don't you be dealing
from the bottom of the deck to me.
- Why don't you guys get something to eat?
- [Dash] I'll be close.
- [Jeremy] Uh, hold up, I'll go with you.
(slow ominous music)
- Do you like blackjack?
- I like anything where
the odds are in my favor.
What are the stakes?
- Too high for either of us.
- Oh, I don't know, my
pocket's pretty deep.
- Mine aren't.
- Hit me.
Why don't you just quit
while you're ahead?
- I feel lucky today.
- Why don't we just cut to the chase?
You don't belong here,
so why don't you take your little group
and you get out of town?
Because if you are still
here tomorrow afternoon,
this little town
will cease to exist.
- Well, I was thinking of
sticking around 'til the election.
- [Lamont] What election?
- Haven't you heard?
I'm running for mayor.
(Lamont laughs)
- Let me ask you something.
Why the hell do you want to die
for a bunch of taco vendors?
- I got real bored with my day job.
- [Lamont] Don't forget,
tomorrow afternoon.
- Sperry means what he says.
He could wipe this town out in a heartbeat
and never get his hands dirty.
- I know.
Something's been bothering me.
- What's that?
- Why would a nice guy like
Sperry want to kill you?
(slow music)
- I was working undercover,
FBI.
I was trying to build
a case against Sperry.
(slow music continues)
- We move on the compound at 23:00.
If anything goes wrong,
Sperry's gonna come
and level the town.
Britt?
- Yeah?
- Be ready to evacuate the people.
- Where do you want me to take them?
- As far away as possible.
- Hold on, if I'm evacuating,
I'm gonna miss all the action.
- You're not trained for the action.
Callin, you and I will take out the guard
at the front gate and
go around the west side.
Remi, you and Simms
infiltrate the arsenal.
Kurt, place the explosives
along the inside.
- I'm still pissed I'm
not going with you, McQue.
- I just don't want you to get killed.
We ready?
- [Remi] Yeah.
- [Latrell] Ready here.
- [Kurt] Ready here, boss.
- Let's move.
(truck engine revs)
(slow dramatic music)
(Hector speaking in foreign language)
(truck doors slamming)
You all know what to do.
If we do it right,
we'll get in and out
without waking anyone up.
- Yeah, well, they're in
for a little rude awakening
after we're gone, aren't
they, boss? (laughs)
- We'll have 15 minutes
after the charge is set.
That means we're out of
here in 01:00, let's do it.
(slow music)
- [Sam] Callin, what the
hell are you doing here?
- [Callin] Hey, Sam.
- I think I'm more afraid
of you than I am of them.
- [Callin] You should be.
- You sure you got him?
- Does the pope wear gold bowling shoes?
(gun fires)
Got him.
- [Dash] I lost him.
I'll meet you at the south gate.
- [Kurt] Yeah, yeah.
(crickets chirping)
(gun cocks)
- Hey, Britt.
- What?
- You know how old I was
when I first held a gun?
- No.
- About four and a half
hours younger than I am now.
(slow dramatic music)
- Hector.
- Yeah?
- I can't stand it, I know they
need every man they can get,
and I'm sitting here babysitting.
I gotta go, man, give me the keys.
- No, you can't drive my truck,
I have to drive my truck.
- Let's go.
- Hector, what are you doing, man?
(truck door slams)
Wait for me!
(truck engine revs)
Do you think maybe this is a mistake?
(slow music)
- [Man In Bandana] Hey, bitch.
(Remi grunts)
(man in bandana cries out)
- [Remi] Hoffman, where are you?
(slow music)
(machinery beeps)
- Come on.
- Come on, this way.
- [Jose] Where's he going?
- [Hector] I have no idea.
- You're not from around here, are you?
- Well, actually, I'm, uh, I'm
just passing through, hoss.
- Wise guy, huh?
Let's go have a chat with the commander.
Don't even try, hoss.
(gun fires)
- [McQue] Come on.
(alarm wails)
(quiet overlapping chattering)
(gun fires)
- Goddamn.
(overlapping chattering)
(alarm wails)
- Sir, we have intruders
inside the compound.
- Shoot them on sight,
I'm gonna cut him up.
(overlapping shouting)
(alarm wails)
(explosives beeping)
(overlapping shouting)
- [Militiaman] Let's go, come on!
Move it, move it, move it, let's move it!
(overlapping shouting)
(truck tires screeching)
(slow music)
- [Dash] Hey, man, what
happened, what's going on?
- Well, we had a little mishap.
Simms, down!
(gun fires)
Simms, you all right?
- Yeah, you know, straight
jacket, you're all right.
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- No, you goof, I'm trying
to tell you you're okay in my book.
- Yeah, well, I love you, too, honey,
but we'll have to bond later.
(gun clicks)
Come on, let's go.
- Jesus.
(overlapping shouting)
(slow dramatic music)
- [Militiaman] Freeze!
(gun fires)
- [Militiaman] Cover me, cover me!
(overlapping shouting)
(gun fires)
(guns firing)
(motorcycle engine revs)
(explosion rumbles)
(guns firing)
- Get some men to shut off the front gate.
What's on your forehead?
- What are you boys doing?
- Drop the gun.
- Well, it looks like we've
got a Mexican standoff here.
- So you think I'm scared
of you, huh, bitch?
(gun fires)
- Hell, yes, I think you're afraid of me.
(explosives beeping)
(guns firing)
(slow music)
- [Militiaman] Let's go up,
come on, let's go up, now, now!
(door creaks)
(overlapping shouting)
We gotta get out of here, we
gotta get out of here, now!
(gun clicks)
- You should have quit
while you were ahead.
Now I'm the house, I'm dealing the cards,
and this game is over.
(Lamont cries out)
I'm gonna gut you like a fish.
(gun fires)
(Lamont cries out)
- That's for the First Amendment.
(Lamont groans)
(gun fires)
(Lamont cries out)
That's so you never walk on anyone again.
(Lamont moans)
You've got about two minutes
before you're pixie dust.
How fast can you crawl?
(slow music)
(guns firing)
(motorcycle engine revs)
(explosion rumbles)
- Go, go, go, cover, come
on, let's move in, come on!
(guns firing)
(overlapping shouting)
Move it, come on, move it!
- [Militiaman] Shannon, hold on, hold on!
(guns firing)
(Remi cries out)
- Kurt, Remi's down!
- [Kurt] Remi.
- Move, move, straight
jacket, where are you?
Go, go, come on, Kurt!
(guns firing)
Straight jacket, where
are you, straight jacket!
(explosives beeping)
(guns firing)
Come on!
Go!
- [Hector] Jose!
(guns firing)
- Go, come on!
- [Militiaman] I'm out of ammo.
(Lamont groans)
- One more thing.
This is because you're
a lousy card player.
(gun fires)
(explosives beeping)
(slow music)
(guns firing)
- He's dead!
- He's my brother, we can't leave!
(overlapping shouting)
(truck engine revs)
Oh, God, no, Jose!
Jose!
(guns firing)
(Hector speaking in foreign language)
(glass shatters)
(overlapping shouting)
(gun fires)
- Go, go!
- [Latrell] You get your ass up here!
- [McQue] Where Callin?
(explosives beeping)
(explosion rumbles)
(slow music)
- [Jeremy] So when you get back-
- [McQue] Sorry about the money.
- [Jeremy] You need to call me up.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Well, I'll be, go to hell, huh?
- Yo, boss.
(overlapping chattering)
- It's good to know I'm still
a good judge of character.
- The government's still gonna want this.
Unless, of course, it's just a
figment of their imagination.
Mind if I get a lift?
(upbeat music)
- I told you.
- McQue?
I just want to thank you
all for what you did.
Here's the money I promised.
- Rebuild your town, take
care of your brother's family.
- I will, I promise.
(upbeat music)
- Will you help me get
some of these cases?
- Let's get on this bus, huh?
(overlapping chattering)
(Latrell laughs)
- [Dash] Kurt.
- Thank you very much.
- Cheers.
- You want me to fly this thing? (laughs)
(overlapping chattering)
Come on, everybody, let's go home.
Don't worry, I can fly
this thing. (laughs)
(overlapping chattering)
(slow rock music)