[bell tolling]
- WELCOME, EVERYONE, TO NITE TALES.
I AM YOUR HOST, THE TIME KEEPER, FLAVOR FLAV.
[laughing maniacally]
[wolf howling]
[faint crazed laughter]
[creepy music]
♪
[dial tone hums]
[phone dialing]
- HEY, GUYS, COME ON. COME ON.
[line ringing]
IT’S RINGING, GUYS. BE QUIET.
- HELLO? - [low voice] HELLO, MA’AM.
IS THIS MRS. BLACKHEAD?
- NO, THIS IS MRS. WHITEHEAD.
- I’M SORRY. WRONG PIMPLE.
[all giggle]
- LET ME TRY.
- NO TIME FOR AMATEURS.
I’LL SHOW YOU GUYS HOW TO DO A REAL PRANK CALL.
[phone dialing]
[line ringing]
- YEAH?
- [creepy voice] I HAVE YOUR CHILDREN WITH ME.
DO YOU WANT THEM TO LIVE?
- I TOLD Y’ALL KIDS NOT TO DIAL THIS NUMBER AGAIN.
- [normal voice] SO WHAT, RAT FACE?
- THAT’S IT. YOU GUYS ARE IN TROUBLE.
I’M GONNA GO TELL DAD.
- NO, YOU’RE NOT. - STOP IT, STEPHEN.
DON’T TOUCH ME. - MAKE ME.
- SIT DOWN, BRACE FACE. - YEAH, WILLIAM.
- I THINK SOMEONE’S COMING.
[line beeping faintly]
[phone beeps]
[soft music playing distantly]
♪
[laughter]
- ALL RIGHT, I GOT IT. THEY’RE TAKEN CARE OF.
- ARE YOU SURE? - YEAH.
- WHAT? THE KIDS ARE ASLEEP. IS THAT WHAT YOU’RE ASKING ME?
- [laughs] YEAH.
[phone ringing]
- [sighs]
HELLO?
- [low breathing] - HELLO?
- YOU KIDS LIKE PLAYING THEM GAMES ON THE PHONE?
- IT WASN’T ME. IT WAS JUST A JOKE.
I NEVER PLAY THOSE STUPID GAMES.
- WELL, I HAVE A FUNNY FOR YOU.
KNOCK, KNOCK.
- WHO’S THERE?
[screams]
[yelps]
[all screaming]
- OH, MY GOD!
- [labored breathing]
[ax scraping]
- NO!
[blows landing]
- [strangled screaming]
- MOM!
[screaming and crying]
[sirens wailing]
- MOM?
MOM, GET UP. PLEASE, MOM, GET UP.
PLEASE, MOM.
PLEASE, MOM, GET UP.
- [whimpering] NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
[police radio chatter]
- DAMN.
DON’T LOOK LIKE ROBBERY WAS THE MOTIVE.
- RIGHT.
- NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE IT.
NO FINGERPRINTS. NO HAIR.
- NOT A TRACE OF EVIDENCE EXCEPT FOR A BOOT PRINT.
THERE HAS TO BE SOMETHING IN HERE.
HE DIDN’T JUST DISAPPEAR.
OR MAYBE WE LOOKING FOR A GHOST.
- I’VE NEVER SEEN A GHOST WITH ONE BOOT.
FIND SOMETHING...
NOW.
[rock music playing]
- ♪ DON’T SEE ANYTHING ♪
♪ BUT A WOMAN AND A LONELY MAN
♪ ALL MY PLEASURES
♪ PHONY TREASURES IN FRONT OF ME ♪
♪ TRANSFER ME TO ALL...
- YOU LITTLE SLUT BAG.
[chuckles]
AH, HELLO.
AHH. OH, SHIT. [phone ringing]
YOU WANNA GIVE ME SOME OF THAT?
YEAH, PUT IT BETWEEN YOUR TITS.
OH, SHIT, YEAH.
UM, YEAH. FUCK, YEAH.
[phone ringing]
FUCK.
CAN YOU TAKE A HINT, COCKSUCKER?
NO ONE’S FUCKING HOME.
- [slowly] HELLO?
- OH, JESUS CHRIST. HELLO?
- AHH. SO YOU KNOW ME.
- WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHO IS THIS? - YOU ALREADY KNOW.
- YEAH? WELL, REMIND ME, YOU DICK SMACK.
- JESUS CHRIST, AND I CAN SEE WHAT YOU’RE DOING.
[music clicks off]
[breathing heavily]
- WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU?
- I’M EVERYWHERE.
- WHY ARE YOU WATCHING ME?
- BECAUSE I LIKE TO WATCH THE PEOPLE I’M GOING TO KILL.
- LEAVE ME ALONE. LEAVE ME ALONE, YOU FUCK.
I GOT A FUCKING GUN, BITCH.
- SO DO I.
BUT I DON’T THINK I’LL USE IT TONIGHT,
BECAUSE I’M GOING TO GUT YOU, LIKE A PIG.
[breathing heavily]
YOU’RE GETTING WARMER.
[cat meows]
- FUCK. - 75, BIATCH.
- GET A LIFE, YOU FUCKING IDIOTS.
[upbeat music playing]
- WHO’S THE KING OF 75?
[all cheering]
- OH, THAT SHIT WAS TIGHT, SON.
- WHEN YOU GONNA START PLAYING, MAN, SO I CAN TAKE YOUR MONEY?
- I AIN’T NEVER PLAYING THAT GAME AGAIN, MAN.
[makes playful noise] HEY!
YOU DO NOT KNOW KARATE.
- TRY ME.
- [laughs] GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
MONEY, MONEY, MONEY, MONEY.
YES. YES, YES.
- SO, MARCUS, DO YOU ACCEPT ANY OTHER FORMS OF PAYMENT?
- YOU KNOW I DO, BABY. JEFFERSONS, LINCOLNS.
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN PAY ME IN PESOS
JUST AS LONG AS YOU TELL ME WHERE I CAN SPEND THEM.
- HOW ’BOUT I LET YOU TAKE ME OUT TO DINNER WITH IT?
- HOW ’BOUT YOU DON’T?
WHY ARE YOU ALWAYS FLIRTING WITH ME, JODY?
YOU KNOW YOUR PARENTS WOULD FLIP IF THEY KNEW YOU LIKED A NEGRO.
- MY PARENTS LOVE N-- - AH, AH, AH, AH.
YOU BETTER NOT. - MARCUS...
- BESIDES, IF I GAVE YOU A PIECE OF THIS CHOCOLATE THUNDER,
YOU’D GO CRAZY: STALKING ME,
HIDING BEHIND BUSHES, WATCHING ME.
GIRL, I’D HAVE TO TRANSFER SCHOOLS.
MM! HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
WHY I ALWAYS GOT TO COME LOOKING FOR YOU
WHEN YOU GOT MY MONEY?
- COME ON, MAN, I ALMOST HAD THAT ONE, DAWG.
- YEAH, BUT ALMOST ONLY COUNTS IN HORSESHOES--OH, YEAH,
AND LIKE THAT TIME WHEN YOU ALMOST GOT ROXY HERE PREGNANT.
- FUCK YOU, MARCUS.
YOU ALWAYS GOT SOMETHING SMART TO SAY.
- THIS IS TRUE, AND...
- ARE YOU GONNA LET HIM TALK TO ME LIKE THAT?
- COME ON, MAN, LET’S PLAY AGAIN, DOUBLE OR NOTHING.
- I INVENTED THE GAME OF 75.
I NEVER LOSE,
SO PAY ME MY MONEY SO WE CAN GET THE PARTY BACK STARTED.
- YOU DONE FIGURED OUT A WAY TO CHEAT, EH?
YEAH, SEE, YOU PROBABLY BE CALLING
ALL THE PEOPLE YOU KNOW AND SHIT.
THEM OL’ RANDOM-ASS NUMBERS SEEM REAL FAMILIAR TO YOU,
DON’T THEY? - YEP.
- DO WE HAVE TO GO THROUGH THIS EVERY NIGHT?
DID THE RULES OF THE GAME CHANGE?
- NAH, BABY, THE RULES AIN’T CHANGED.
- YOU CALL SOMEBODY.
YOU KEEP THEM ON THE PHONE FOR 75 SECONDS.
IF YOU DON’T, YOU LOSE.
AND YOU LOST.
- [sighs] - OH, UH-UH.
YOU KNOW, GOD DON’T LIKE UGLY.
- WELL, HE MUST HATE YOUR MAMA. - OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU BETTER STOP TALKING ABOUT MY MAMA.
- HEY, HOLD ON, BABY.
YOU HAVE BEEN TAKING THEM PILLS, RIGHT?
- OOH, WAIT AND SEE THE NEXT TIME
YOU EVEN GET TO SMELL THIS, OKAY?
- AH, GOD, I’M GETTING THERE. OH, F--
[grunts]
GOD, YOU’RE A LITTLE BITCH. MM!
[soft click]
THAT’S IT, YEAH.
OOH, GRAB MY BALLS.
YEAH.
OH, YOU’RE A DIRTY LITTLE GIRL, AREN’T YOU?
MM! YEAH, WORK IT. AH, YEAH.
THERE YOU GO. THAT’S A GIRL. MM-HMM.
[grunts]
OH, YOU DIRTY LITTLE SLUT.
YEAH. WHO’S YOUR DADDY, BITCH?
OH, YOU’RE NAUGHTY. MM-HMM.
OH, I’M ABOUT THERE. I’M ABOUT TO COME.
OH, I’M ABOUT TO COME. AH, JUST LIKE THAT.
YEAH, WHERE DO YOU WANT IT? YEAH.
OHH, BITCH.
[electronic beeping]
AH, FUCK. [keyboard clicking]
FUCK.
AH, SHIT.
- ♪ WOULD YOU LIKE TO RIDE?
♪
♪ RIDE
- ♪ SO WHY DON’T YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS ♪
♪ GET WITH ME AND MY FRIENDS - ♪ MY FRIENDS
- ♪ WOULD YOU LIKE TO RIDE?
- ♪ I DON’T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED, IT’S JUST LIKE, HEH ♪
- ♪ SO WHY DON’T YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS ♪
♪ GET WITH ME AND MY FRIENDS, MY FRIENDS? ♪
- ♪ I HAD THAT LITTLE-ASS NISSAN AT YOUR CRIB SHOWIN’ UP ♪
- YES, MOM.
YES. MOM, I KNOW.
- KARINA, HEY.
- MOM, GUESS WHAT.
I THINK I GOT AN "A" ON MY FINAL TODAY.
- OH, REALLY?
- YES, MOM.
MOM, NOTHING’S GONNA HAPPEN.
THAT HAPPENED TWO CITIES OVER.
I’LL BE FINE, MOM. THE CAMPUS IS PERFECTLY SAFE.
OKAY. OKAY. ALL RIGHT ALREADY, MOMMY.
I GOT TO GO. I GOT TO GO. I LOVE YOU.
[kissing sound] BYE.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- CONGRATULATIONS FOR WHAT?
- WHAT? YOUR FINAL EXAM.
- I OVERHEARD YOU SAYING YOU GOT AN "A."
- YOU’RE SO NOSY.
IT’S NOT A BIG DEAL.
- YEAH, IT’S A BIG DEAL TO ME.
- YEAH? WHY IS THAT?
- BEAUTIFUL, SEXY, AND INTELLIGENT.
WHAT ELSE COULD A MAN WANT?
- HOW ’BOUT THE UGLY, FAT, DUMB CHICK
THAT HE CHEATED ON HER WITH LAST SEMESTER?
- COME ON, KARINA...
SHE WASN’T THAT FAT.
IS THIS THING ON, HUH?
THAT WAS A JOKE.
LOOK, KARINA, I KNOW I MADE A BIG MISTAKE,
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT... I’M SORRY.
YOU KNOW I GIVE AN EXTREMELY EXCLUSIVE
END-OF-FINALS PARTY EVERY SEMESTER,
AND I JUST THOUGHT YOU MIGHT LIKE TO COME.
- I DON’T THINK IT’S A GOOD IDEA.
- HEY, BRANDON. - DON’T "HEY, BRANDON" HIM.
- I OUGHT TO BASIC INSTINCT YOUR ASS.
- WHAT’D I EVER DO TO YOU?
- YOU’RE LUCKY YOU AIN’T DO SHIT TO ME,
’CAUSE I WOULD BASIC INSTINCT YOUR ASS.
- [feigns laughter] SO, KARINA, COME ON.
WHAT’S IT GONNA BE? - I DON’T KNOW, BRANDON. I--
- UH-UH. WHAT IS WHAT GONNA BE?
- BRANDON IS TRYING TO GET ME TO GO TO HIS PARTY TONIGHT.
- OH, REALLY? MM-HMM.
YOU MEAN THAT EXTRA-EXCLUSIVE PARTY?
- PARTY... GIRLS, HUDDLE.
- COME ON, FINALS ARE OVER, AND YOU GOT TO GET AWAY.
- I AIN’T GOT SHIT ELSE TO DO. WE’RE GOING.
- WE GOING.
WE GOING. - WE’RE GOING.
- WHAT’S UP, TWO-TIMER?
- HEARD YOU LIKE TO LIVE A DOUBLE LIFE, SON.
GOT A LITTLE DOWN, HUH, KID?
[women and Shawn laugh]
- HE KNOWS KARATE?
- I OUGHT TO BUST YOUR ASS, HOMEY.
- [snickering]
- MAN, YOU’RE NOT GONNA BUST A GRAPE.
ME, ON THE OTHER HAND-- I USED TO BEAT UP FOOLS FOR FUN,
AND I’M FEELING LIKE I NEED TO ENTERTAIN MYSELF.
- OH, MARCUS, THERE’LL BE ENTERTAINMENT...
AT BRANDON’S PARTY, RIGHT, BRANDON?
- [mouths words] - OH, YOU HAVING A PARTY, HOMEY?
- YEAH, BUT IT’S KIND OF, YOU KNOW, EXCLUSIVE.
- SO WHAT? WE CAN’T COME?
- SORRY, FELLAS.
- IF I GO, THE CREW GOES.
- IF SHE GOES, THE CREW GOES.
- SO BE READY ABOUT WHAT? 5:00?
- 5:00-ISH SOUNDS COOL. THANKS, MAN.
- KARINA, MAKE SURE "THE CREW" IS READY,
OR THEY’LL BE PLAYING GRAB ASS IN THE DORM TONIGHT.
[clicks tongue]
- LITTLE PUNK ASS.
- STRETCH YOUR HAND UP LIKE THAT.
- HE IS PRETTY CUTE. - YEAH.
- 10-0-30, WOULD YOU ASK Z-1-10 TO MONITOR
WHEN HE’S AVAILABLE?
- CAN YOU HOLD ON A MINUTE?
HOLD ON A SECOND. I’M GONNA HAVE TO CALL YOU BACK.
DAMN IT, CRITON, MY OFFICE HAS A DOOR ON IT FOR A REASON.
- DO YOU REMEMBER THIS?
[man screams] [metal clangs]
- JOHN, IT’S BEEN TEN YEARS.
AS FAR AS I’M CONCERNED, THE WHALEY CASE IS OVER.
I SUGGEST YOU LEAVE IT.
- COME ON, DAVID.
THERE’S A CONNECTION. I KNOW YOU CAN SEE THAT.
- WHAT I SEE IS THE MISTAKE THAT I MADE
WHEN I SENT A SUIT OVER TO THE WHALEY HOUSE TEN YEARS AGO.
- SAME KIND OF WEAPON.
SAME CIRCUMSTANCES.
THE GUY GOT A CALL JUST BEFORE HE DIED.
- JOHN, THE WHALEY CASE IS ONE OF MANY UNSOLVED MURDERS--
IT’S NOT THE FIRST, AND IT DEFINITELY WON’T BE THE LAST.
- LET ME DIG A LITTLE.
- DON’T WASTE MY TIME WITH UNSOLVED MURDERS
FROM TEN YEARS AGO
WHEN I’VE GOT THE PRESS DIGGING DOWN MY THROAT
OVER BODIES THAT ARE TURNING UP IN THE STREET TODAY.
[sighs]
I’D LIKE TO SOLVE THIS CASE...
BUT I CAN’T.
AND JUST LEAVE IT ALONE.
GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
- I THINK I GOT A 4.0 AGAIN THIS SEMESTER,
SO IT WAS WORTH IT.
- WOW, THAT’S REALLY GREAT.
OKAY, SO JODY JUST GOT AN A-PLUS IN CHEMISTRY.
♪ THAT’S RIGHT, UH-HUH ♪
♪ A-PLUS, THAT’S RIGHT, THAT’S RIGHT ♪
- ALL THE TIME YOU SPENT AT PROFESSOR GORDON’S OFFICE,
YOU SHOULD GET MORE THAN THAT.
[laughter]
- I’M HIS AIDE, SHAWN.
- YEAH, AND I JUST GOT SIGNED TO G-G-G-G-UNIT.
[eerie music]
♪
- OH, YEAH, AND I’M SURE HE APPRECIATES IT
WHEN YOU LIGHTEN HIS LOAD.
- [laughs]
- I’M GOING TO THE BATHROOM. - MM-HMM.
[indistinct chatter]
- YOU WANT ALWAYS EVERYTHING, GIRL.
- I WANT EVERYTHING ALWAYS.
- BOO. - OH!
KAREEM! DON’T DO THAT.
- DO WHAT? KISS YOU, BABY, HMM?
- SNEAK UP ON ME LIKE SOME DAMN STALKER.
- AS LONG AS YOU DON’T PLAN ON LEAVING ME,
YOU’RE FINE, ’CAUSE WE GONNA GO TOGETHER.
OR WE GONNA GO TOGETHER.
- [laughs] BABY, YOU CRAZY.
[headphone music playing faintly]
- [singing indistinctly]
[door taps softly]
[door clicks shut]
- YO...
WHAT YOU DOING IN HERE, MAN, CHANGING YOUR PAD?
HOLD ON, SON, AND LET A BROTHER PEE IN PEACE.
[scoffs]
[urinal flushes]
MAN, IS EVERYBODY WAITING IN THE CAR?
- YEAH. GONNA WASH YOUR HANDS? - NO.
- EW. NASTY.
- DO YOU THINK HE DESERVES ANOTHER CHANCE?
- [sighs] GIRL, ONCE A CHEAT, ALWAYS A CHEAT.
- WELL, I THINK IF YOU REALLY LOVE SOMEONE,
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO FORGIVE THEM.
- FORGIVE, MAYBE. FORGET, NEVER.
- WHOO!
- ♪ BOYS, YOU KNOW YOU LIKE...
- [humming] ♪ PARTY, PARTY, PARTY
♪ BOYS, BOYS, BOYS
HAVE YOU DECIDED WHAT YOU’RE GONNA WEAR, KAREEM?
’CAUSE CHECK THIS FABULOUS BELT.
I LOOK SO HOT.
MM, READY FOR THE BOYS.
[chuckles]
- ♪ BOYS, BOYS
- NAH, THAT AIN’T IT.
- DUDE, DO WE HAVE TO GO THROUGH THIS EVERY TIME WE GO SOMEWHERE?
- PATIENCE, MAN. YOU KNOW I GOT TO LOOK GOOD.
JUST GOT ONE MORE THING TO TRY ON.
[all chatting]
- OKAY, READY? MAKE SURE WE ALL LOOK CUTE.
- CHEESE GRITS ON THREE. COME ON.
- READY? - READY.
- BEANS AND GRAVY.
- CHEESE GRITS. - BEANS AND GRAVY.
- HURRY UP.
[honks horn] - COME ON, CREW.
- COME ON. LET’S GO.
- EXCUSE ME. - RELAX, RELAX.
- I WANNA SEE. - SO CUTE.
- RELAX. - LOOK AT ALL OF US.
- GO, GO, GO, GO.
- OKAY. - HURRY UP.
- COME ON, MAN. DON’T START THAT BULLSHIT.
- NAH, THAT AIN’T IT. THAT AIN’T IT.
HOLD UP. HOLD UP. - GRAB MY MP3 PLAYER.
- AND GET SOME TOILET PAPER.
[horn honks]
[indistinctly yelling]
- HURRY UP.
- MAN, LET’S GO.
[all cheering]
- LET’S GO.
[engine turns]
[rock music playing]
- HEY, PARTNER. - CLOSE THE DOOR.
- WHAT’S UP? - TAKE ANOTHER LOOK AT THIS.
[metal clangs]
- [screams]
- COME ON, JOHN.
- I PIECED TOGETHER EVERY BIT OF INFORMATION I COULD FIND.
- YOU’VE BEEN CONDUCTING YOUR OWN INVESTIGATION?
AND WHAT DID THE CHIEF HAVE TO SAY ABOUT THIS?
- I CAN USE AN EXTRA HAND.
THE WHALEY KIDS-- WHERE DO YOU THINK THEY ARE NOW?
- ALL OVER.
SOME WERE PLACED WITH RELATIVES.
OTHERS BOUNCED AROUND FOSTER HOMES.
- ANY NAME CHANGES?
- YEAH.
MOST OF THEM ARE LEGALLY ADOPTED.
ALL RIGHT, LET’S GO LOOK FOR THOSE RECORDS,
BUT THAT’S AS FAR AS I GO.
[upbeat pop music playing]
♪
- CAN YOU PULL OVER SOMEWHERE? I’VE GOT TO PEE.
PLEASE.
- GUYS, ARE THOSE SHEEP?
[sheep baaing]
- LET’S HURRY THIS UP AND GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
ding!
HELLO? IS ANYBODY HOME?
- I BET YOU IF WE START STEALING SOME OF THEIR SHIT,
THEY’LL COME OUT.
[loud banging] - SHIT!
- [exhales] - YOU GUYS ARE ALL DEAD.
[girls chuckle]
- THIS IS SOME BULLSHIT.
I’M FITTIN’ WAIT IN THE CAR.
[door bangs]
ding, ding, ding!
- [yelps] - STOP RINGING MY DAMN BELL.
NOW WHAT CAN I GET FOR YOU?
- MY FRIEND HAS TO USE THE RESTROOM.
- AND YOU WANT THE KEYS.
- PLEASE.
- EW. - WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
- THANK YOU. - BUT NO, THANK YOU.
I’LL WAIT. - SUIT YOURSELF.
NOT ANOTHER FOR MILES.
- HAVE FUN. - EW.
- YOU SURE DO HAVE A PRETTY MOUTH.
- THANK YOU?
[insect buzzes] - [groans]
OOH.
SHIT.
[door creaks]
[coughs] OH, HELL, NO.
OUF.
- [groans] - NOT ANOTHER FOR MILES.
[door creaks]
- KARINA?
JODY?
BABY, IS THAT YOU?
DON’T BE FUCKING AROUND, MARCUS.
[footstep scuffs]
- [yelps]
[shrieking]
- I’M JUST PLAYING WITH YOU, BABY.
- FUCK.
- WHY AM I NOT GETTING A SIGNAL? GOD.
[phone beeps negatively]
- IN THIS DISTURBING NEWS OUT OF PENHURST COUNTY,
THE BODY OF SCHOOL BUS DRIVER CHUCK NEWTON
WAS DISCOVERED EARLY THIS MORNING
IN HIS RURAL HOME OUTSIDE DALESBORO.
WHILE POLICE ARE NOT RELEASING ANY SPECIFICS,
NEWTON WAS REPORTEDLY MURDERED WITH A LARGE WEAPON
THOUGHT TO BE AN AX.
NEWTON IS BELIEVED TO BE A SURVIVOR
OF THE INFAMOUS WHALEY MURDERS.
ANYONE WITH INFORMATION ON THE CASE SHOULD CONTACT
THE PENHURST COUNTY SHERIFF’S OFFICE IMMEDIATELY.
AND NOW HERE’S JANE WILSON WITH THE WEATHER FORECAST.
- THANKS, STU.
WELL, IF YOU HAVEN’T GET BEGUN TO FEEL THE CHILL IN THE AIR,
JUST WAIT.
TONIGHT IS EXPECTED TO BRING
THE COOLEST WEATHER OF THE WINTER SEASON.
- [hoots]
- COME ON, BABY. IT WAS JUST A JOKE.
- CAN WE JUST GO?
[all yelp]
- BE CAREFUL.
LIKE THEY JUST SAID IN THE NEWS,
IT’S GONNA GET COLD.
[labored breathing]
- MARCUS... [engine turns]
DRIVE.
[loud, crackling boom]
- [softly] ENOUGH ALREADY.
- IT’S ALL YOURS.
- LET’S GO.
- I’M SORRY, BUT THE FILES DON’T LEAVE THE ROOM.
- HOW DO YOU EXPECT US TO DO OUR WORK--
- HEY. WE’LL FIGURE IT OUT.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP, MA’AM.
- SHIT.
[whistling softly]
- CHUCK NEWTON, WHERE ARE YOU?
[clock ticking]
I THINK I MAY HAVE FOUND OUR VICTIM.
JASON CHARLES ANTHONY.
ADOPTED BY KAREN AND ROBERT NEWTON.
- YOU WERE RIGHT.
- HOW DO WE FIND THE KIDS THAT ARE STILL ALIVE?
THAT’S WHAT I WANT TO KNOW.
[melancholy piano and string music]
♪
- WE’RE HERE.
- I HATE THE COPS.
- I’M SORRY, BUT I DON’T THINK WE VIOLATED ANY LAWS, OFFICER.
YOU ARE A REAL OFFICER, RIGHT?
[police radio chatter]
- [screams]
- LICENSE AND REGISTRATION, PLEASE.
[latch clicks]
- [clears throat]
BRANDON O’CONNELL’S THE NAME.
- AS IN THE SON OF MITCH O’CONNELL?
- OH-HO, HE’S SMART TOO.
YEAH, MY DAD OWNS THIS PLACE, ALONG WITH, HMM, HALF THIS TOWN.
AND THANKS TO MY FATHER’S CONTRIBUTIONS, "OSSIFER,"
YOU GET TO DRIVE AROUND IN THAT NICE CAR YOU GOT THERE.
- WELL, I’M SORRY.
I DIDN’T KNOW IT WAS YOU, MR. O’CONNELL,
BUT WE’RE MAKING OUR LAST ROUND FOR THE EVENING,
AND WE’D SURE HATE TO SEE YOU GUYS HAVE ANY PROBLEMS.
- IS THAT ALL... OFFICER?
- THAT’S ALL.
CARRY ON.
[imitates radio static] - CARRY ON, ASSHOLE.
- MAN, YOU’RE GONNA GET A NIGGER LOCKED UP!
[engine turns]
- DAMN.
- OH, SHIT, SON.
- GOD, LOOK AT THAT. - SHIT.
- THAT’S IT?
- IT’S HUGE.
[people chatting]
[upbeat hip-hop music]
♪
- OH, MY GOD.
- DANG.
SHIT.
- DAMN. - THIS IS HOT.
- HEY, MAN, WHAT’S UP WITH ALL THESE DAMN CAMERAS?
- MY DAD’S A TELEVISION PRODUCER.
YEAH, HE HAD THIS IDEA FOR A REALITY TV SHOW
WHERE ALL THESE KIDS LIVE IN ONE HOUSE
WITH CAMERAS EVERYWHERE,
BUT A RIVAL NETWORK BEAT HIM TO THE PUNCH.
NO BIG DEAL, YOU KNOW.
- AIN’T NO PARTY LIKE AN L.G. PARTY...
[mumbling happily]
HEY, "B."
HOPE YOU DON’T MIND. I KIND OF GOT THE PARTY STARTED.
- YOU KNOW I DON’T.
- I’M SORRY. WHERE ARE MY MANNERS?
[belching]
[chuckles]
DR. GORDON’S CHEMISTRY 386. JODY WALTERS, RIGHT?
- YEAH, THAT’S ME. WHO ARE YOU?
- CRAZY CAL.
- CRAZY CAL, HUH?
- CALUCIUS DUPREE, BUT YOU CAN CALL ME CAL.
I DID THE PRESENTATION ON HOW TO CHEMICALLY REDUCE
THE EFFECTS OF A NIGHT OF HEAVY DRINKING.
- YEAH, RIGHT. LIKE THAT REALLY WORKS.
- BEERS TEN, HANGOVER ZERO.
HERE, BEFORE YOU START DRINKING, SWALLOW ONE OF THESE BABIES.
IN CASE OF AN EMERGENCY, BREAK...
[sniffing]
AND USE.
- MAN, THIS NIGGER CRAZY. - DID HE JUST--
- I THINK I’M GOING TO BE SICK.
- CAL, CAL, CAL, BEFORE YOU, UH, SCARE ALL OF OUR GUESTS AWAY,
WHY DON’T WE-- - TOUR, TOUR, TOUR.
- YEAH, A TOUR.
WHY DON’T YOU SHOW THESE GUYS AROUND?
- TOUR? - MM-HMM.
- LET’S GO. WHOO-HOO.
THIS IS MY FAVORITE:
THE CONFESSIONAL BOOTH.
NOW, WHATEVER HAPPENS IN THE CONFESSIONAL BOOTH,
STAYS IN THE CONFESSIONAL BOOTH.
- YEAH. - YEAH.
[grunting and moaning]
- [shouts indistinctly]
[laughs] IS THAT YOUR BABY?
[laughs] THIS IS THE POOL HOUSE.
OR SHOULD I SAY SMOOZE HOUSE?
OH, WHUP THAT SHIT! - DAMN!
- WHUP THAT SHIT! - DAMN!
- LIKE $500 AN HOUR TO DO STUFF.
THIS IS THE CONTROL ROOM.
- OH, WHAT ARE THESE FOR?
- YOU CAN SEE EVERYTHING. OH, MY GOD.
- THOSE ARE THE MONITORS.
THERE’S A CAMERA IN EVERY ROOM, BY THE POOL, IN THE GUESTHOUSE.
THIS IS THE ONLY ROOM WITHOUT ONE.
CAN’T MISS A THING ON A REALITY TV SHOW.
- SPIN IT UP, MAN.
[water splashes]
- MAN, YOU KNOW I DON’T DRINK.
- IT’S A GOOD TIME TO START.
- YO, THERE SHE IS.
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE.
- WHO? - GO TALK TO HER.
- WHO, SON?
- LISA, THE GIRL OF YOUR DREAMS SINCE FRESHMAN YEAR.
- LISA.
- [softly] HERE SHE COMES, HERE SHE COMES.
- MARCUS, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- HEY.
YOU HAVING A GOOD TIME?
- SWEETIE, YOU DIDN’T JUST TAKE ONE OF THOSE PILLS?
- MM-MM. - YEAH, SHE DID.
- OH, YOU DID. - YEAH, I DID.
BUT, YOU GUYS, IT’S PERFECTLY SAFE; I SWEAR.
I KNOW CAL SEEMS A LITTLE BIT CRAZY,
BUT HE GOT AN "A" IN CHEMISTRY.
- SO DO YOU,
AND YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT A PERIODIC TABLE IS.
- GUYS, I THINK HE’S REALLY CUTE.
- OH, HONEY, YOU THINK EVERYBODY IS SO CUTE.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
SAY WHAT YOU WANT, OKAY,
BUT YOU GET ONE SHOT IN THIS LIFETIME,
SO GO BIG, OR GO HOME.
- IT’S A LITTLE MORE COMPLICATED THAN THAT FOR SOME OF US.
- WOMAN, YOU’VE GOT TO LIGHTEN UP.
IT’S JUST SEX.
IT’S NOT LIKE IT’S ROCKET SCIENCE OR NOTHING.
- YOU KNOW WHAT, KARINA? I AGREE WITH HER THERE.
YOU HAVE BEEN WAY TOO UPTIGHT LATELY.
MAYBE YOU OUGHT TO LET BRANDON TAKE THAT ROCKET TO THE MOON.
- I THOUGHT YOU GUYS DIDN’T LIKE BRANDON.
- GIRL, I’M DRUNK. - [laughs]
- MISS EASTON?
MELISSA EASTON?
- WE HAVE A SOCIAL.
I CAN RUN IT FOR HER CURRENT EMPLOYER.
- PEOPLE WHO HAVE JOBS DON’T LIVE IN TRAILERS, HASTINGS.
- THANKS FOR THE TIP.
WE DON’T HAVE A WARRANT.
SIR!
CRITON!
SIR! TURN AROUND WITH YOUR HANDS IN THE AIR.
JESUS.
- GUESS WE FOUND MELISSA.
LET ME CALL IT IN.
- ALL CLEAR IN THERE?
- I GUESS.
THERE’S FOUR MORE.
- YEAH. - WHERE ARE THEY?
- TWO ARE IN BRENTMORE UNIVERSITY.
ONE’S IN FARLEY.
- AND THE LAST ONE?
- NO LOCATION ON HIM.
HIS FOSTER PARENTS REPORTED HIM MISSING THREE YEARS AGO.
[sighs]
- WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
- LET’S GO TO BRENTMORE.
[together] DRINK, DRINK, DRINK, DRINK, DRINK, DRINK, DRINK!
[all cheering]
- OKAY, OKAY, OKAY. I GOT ONE. YOU GUYS READY?
HOLLYWOOD SLUTS. AND I’LL GO FIRST.
COLIN FERRELL--ASSHOLE. GO.
- TARA REID. YOU.
- ERIC BENET.
- CARMEN ELECTRA.
- WAIT, HOLD ON. DENNIS RODMAN. DENNIS RODMAN.
[together] DRINK, DRINK, DRINK, DRINK, DRINK, DRINK, DRINK!
- I GOT ONE, I GOT ONE, I GOT ONE, I GOT ONE.
STUPID FUCKING GAMES. I’LL START.
QUESTIONS.
[all oohing]
- I INVITE YOU TO MY HOUSE. YOU DON’T LIKE MY PARTY.
YOU DON’T LIKE THE GAME I CHOSE.
LET ME GUESS: YOU GOT A BETTER FUCKING IDEA, HUH?
- AS A MATTER OF FACT, I DO.
75. HERE ARE THE RULES.
FIRST AND FOREMOST, ALWAYS-- AND I REPEAT--
ALWAYS DIAL STAR 67 BEFORE MAKING A CALL.
IF YOU DON’T, THAT WILL ALLOW THE WEIRDO/ASSHOLE
ON THE OTHER END OF THE LINE TO CALL YOUR DUMB ASS BACK.
YOU HAVE 75 SECONDS.
THAT’S 1 MINUTE AND 15 SECONDS
TO COMPLETELY TRICK THE PERSON ON THE OTHER END OF THE LINE
INTO BELIEVING WHAT YOU’RE PITCHING
IS ABSOLUTELY REAL.
IF THEY HANG UP, YOU LOSE.
IF THEY LAUGH, YOU LOSE.
OR IF THEY SIMPLY NOT BUYING
THE BULLSHIT THAT YOU’RE PITCHING, YOU LOSE.
- SO WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
WE JUST DIAL A RANDOM NUMBER IN THIS AREA?
- NAH, CALL YOUR MAMA. [all chuckle]
- OF COURSE WE DIAL A RANDOM NUMBER.
THAT’S THE POINT OF A PRANK CALL.
A’IGHT, NOW, WHO WANTS TO GO FIRST?
- ME. LET ME GO FIRST.
- RULE NUMBER ONE:
ALWAYS DIAL STAR 67 BEFORE MAKING A CALL.
AND YOU, BIMBO BARBIE, HAVE LOST YOUR TURN.
- AW, COME HERE. - [baby talk]
- AW.
- A’IGHT, WHO’S NEXT? - I’LL GO NEXT.
- ALL RIGHT. - THANK YOU.
STAR 67, HUH?
[line ringing]
- HELLO?
- HEY, LADY, I FOUND YOUR DOG DEAD IN THE STREET.
- OH, MY GOD.
- I GOT HIS FURRY LITTLE BODY RIGHT HERE NEXT TO ME.
- [breathily] I’M SORRY.
I ACCIDENTALLY HUNG UP THE PHONE WHEN I ROLLED OVER ON MY BACK.
- UM, I THINK MAYBE YOU--
- [exhales] OKAY.
I’M ON MY BACK NOW, ROY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO TOUCH NEXT?
- HEY, SUGAR, IS YOUR HUSBAND HOME?
- NO, HE’S NOT. MAY I ASK WHO’S CALLING?
- WELL, I’D RATHER NOT SAY RIGHT NOW,
BUT DO HAVE TO GET SOMETHING OFF MY CHEST--
- [crying] I DID IT. DO YOU HEAR ME?
I FUCKING DID IT.
- WHAT? WHY DID YOU CALL ME?
AND WHO IS THIS? WHAT THE HELL DID YOU DO?
- I KILLED HIM, YOU BASTARD, JUST LIKE YOU TOLD ME TO.
- OH, MY NIPPLES ARE SO HARD.
[breathing heavily]
OH, ROY.
OH, I WISH YOU WERE HERE.
I’M ALMOST THERE, ROY. JUST A LITTLE BIT MORE.
- OH, MY GOD. - JUST A LITTLE BIT MORE.
- WELL, LET’S JUST SAY YOUR HUSBAND IS A SWITCH-HITTER,
AND HE’S BATTING 1.000 FROM BOTH SIDES.
- LADY, YOU’RE CRAZY AS HELL.
YOU’VE GOT THE WRONG GODDAMN NUMBER.
I’M CALLING THE MOTHERFUCKING POLICE.
- [crying] I’VE GOT TO GO, AND I LOVE YOU.
BUT NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS...
[normal voice] ALWAYS REMEMBER, 75, MOTHERFUCKER.
- 75, YOU PERVERT.
- 75! [laughing]
[all chuckling]
- ALL RIGHT.
- LET ME SHOW YOU HOW IT’S DONE, SON.
- MAN, YOU KNOW YOU DON’T WANNA PLAY, MAN.
- STEP ASIDE.
LET A PLAYER SHOW YOU HOW THE PLAYERS PLAY, ALL RIGHT?
- OH, I GOT IT. - ALL RIGHT.
[clears throat]
[beeps seven times]
[line ringing]
- HELLO?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- JUST...WORKING.
- YEAH, I KNOW ’CAUSE I’M WATCHING YOU.
- OOH. THAT MAKES ME SCARED.
- YEAH, WELL, IT SHOULD, ’CAUSE I’M COMING TO KILL YOU.
- [chuckles softly]
WELL, SINCE YOU’RE WATCHING ME AND YOU’RE A KILLER...
[woman whimpering] YOU SHOULD REALLY ENJOY THIS.
[whirring] - DON’T DO THIS.
[shrieking] NO!
[silence]
[phone ringing]
- DON’T TELL ME YOUR DUMB ASS DIDN’T PRESS STAR 67
BEFORE YOU CALLED THAT WEIRD MOTHERFUCKER, MAN.
- I DID.
- THEN WHY THE FUCK IS THE PHONE RINGING?
- MAYBE IT’S JUST SOMEONE CALLING.
- WELL, JUST ANSWER IT.
- HELLO?
- WE GET DISCONNECTED,
OR DID YOU JUST NOT LIKE MY WORK?
[whirring]
- [screams]
- [grunting]
- [screaming]
[sounds of torture]
I KNOW I’M A LITTLE ROUGH AROUND THE EDGES,
BUT I’LL GET BETTER AS THE NIGHT GOES ON.
- THIS IS AWESOME.
IT’S LIKE SOMEONE’S FUCKING 75-ING US.
- MAN, THIS SHIT AIN’T FUNNY!
STUPID ASS.
HE’S A STUPID MOTHERFUCKER.
MAYBE WE SHOULD’VE LEFT YOUR STUPID ASS AT THE HOUSE.
- KAREEM, CHILL OUT. COME ON.
- YEAH, MAN. BE EASY, DAWG.
YOU’RE DOING A LITTLE TOO MUCH.
- FUCK YOU.
- SCOTT.
[phone ringing]
- WHAT? - I WASN’T FINISHED.
- MAN, FUCK YOU. - NO, FUCK YOU!
YOU CALLED ME, REMEMBER?
- LOOK, MAN, YOU THINK I’M JOKING OR SOMETHING?
YOU THINK THIS SOME KIND OF FUCKING GAME?
- NOT ANYMORE.
I CARED ENOUGH TO INVITE YOU INTO MY HOME.
I SHARED MY WORK WITH YOU. - [whimpering]
- THIS IS FAR FROM A GAME.
- LOOK, YOU SICK FUCK, YOU CALL BACK HERE ONE MORE TIME,
I PROMISE YOU, I WILL HUNT YOU DOWN
AND BREAK EVERY FUCKING BONE IN YOUR BODY.
- NOT IF I FIND YOU FIRST.
[line beeping]
- THAT GUY WAS PROBABLY JUST SOME FREAK, YOU KNOW?
- YEAH, MAN.
IT’S PROBABLY NOTHING.
- I THINK WE SHOULD CALL THE POLICE.
- NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THE NEAREST POLICE STATION IS OVER 45 MINUTES AWAY.
BESIDES, NO ONE KNOWS WHERE THIS HOUSE IS ANYWAY.
- RIGHT.
- NO ONE KNOWS WE’RE FUCKING UP HERE EITHER.
- THIS SOME BULLSHIT, MAN.
- YEAH, I MEAN, MAYBE BRANDON’S RIGHT, MAN.
MAYBE HE’S JUST SOME RANDOM FREAK.
- BABY, RELAX. I THINK YOU’RE OVERREACTING.
AND YOU WERE A LITTLE HARD ON YOUR BOY.
- FUCK HIM. HE’S MARCUS’ BOY.
- [sighs] COME ON, BABY. LET’S GO UPSTAIRS.
- WHY AREN’T WE PARTYING?
HIT THE MUSIC, WHITE BOY!
[all cheering]
[sultry hip-hop music playing]
♪
- OOH. MMM.
YEAH. [inhales]
OOH, YOU BITCH.
[giggles]
[soft piano music]
♪
- WHAT’S THAT? - A CONDOM.
- NO, I KNOW WHAT IT IS, BUT WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- WELL, IT MEANS THAT YOU BETTER STAY AWAY
FROM THOSE FAT GIRLS.
IF I GIVE ROXY THE OKAY,
THIS LITTLE DUDE RIGHT HERE WILL BECOME HIS BODY BAG.
- THAT’S NOT FUNNY.
- IS THIS THING ON?
- OKAY, OKAY. THAT’S FUNNY.
- THIS AIN’T EVEN THE RIGHT KIND.
YOU KNOW I NEED MAGNUMS. I’M PACKIN’.
- I KNOW, PAPA, I KNOW.
BUT IF YOU WANNA PACK THAT INSIDE OF ME,
YOU GOT TO PACK IT INSIDE OF THIS.
HOW ’BOUT YOU JUST LET ME STICK THE HEAD IN?
HOW ’BOUT YOU JUST STICK THE TONGUE IN?
- HOW ’BOUT WE JUST FORGET IT?
- [squealing and laughing]
[phone ringing]
[mellow R&B music]
♪
- OH.
- [muffled] WHAT’S IN MY MOUTH?
- [laughs] - WHAT’S THAT?
WHAT IS THAT?
[gasps]
- OH, BABY. IT’S BEAUTIFUL.
- WHAT CAN I SAY?
- [moaning]
[phone ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
- HELLO? - PIZZA. I NEED THE ADDRESS.
- YEAH, HOLD ON A SECOND.
HEY, WHAT’S THE ADDRESS?
- UH, 5100 MISSION ROAD.
- IT’S, UM, 5100 MISSION ROAD.
- 5100 MISSION ROAD?
- YOU CAN’T MISS IT.
IT’S, LIKE, THE ONLY HOUSE UP HERE.
[line beeps] - WHO WAS THAT?
WHO THE FUCK WAS THAT?
AND WHY THE HELL IS YOU ON THE PHONE,
ANSWERING THE DAMN PHONE,
GIVING OUT DIRECTIONS TO SOMEBODY UP HERE?
WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG WITH YOU PEOPLE, MAN?
- HEY. - WHAT?
- WHAT’S GOING ON HERE, MAN? - WHO THE FUCK WAS THAT?
- HEY, HO, WHOA, WAIT, HEY, HEY.
WHAT’S GOING ON?
- MAN, SHE OVER HERE ANSWERING THE DAMN PHONE,
GIVING OUT THE DAMN DIRECTIONS TO SOMEBODY.
MAN, WE’VE BEEN WATCHING THAT PHONE RING ALL NIGHT.
- HEY, WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM? IT WAS THE PIZZA MAN.
- PIZZA MAN?
- PROBABLY WAS THAT WEIRD MOTHERFUCKER FROM EARLIER, MAN.
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
FROM HERE ON OUT, NO ONE ANSWERS THE PHONE.
ALL RIGHT?
NO ONE.
- AND THAT BROTHER IS HIS ONLY NEXT OF KIN.
NO FORWARDING. - JESUS.
AND THE LAST KNOWN ADDRESS? - [speaks indistinctly]
- JESUS. - GOT THAT?
- YEAH, I GOT IT. THANKS.
GREAT.
LOOKS LIKE OUR THIRD KID LEFT FARLEY A MONTH AGO.
WE’VE GOT SOME ADDRESS IN HOBB COUNTY, AND NOW THIS.
- [sighs] SHIT.
[helicopter whirring]
- HEY, GUYS. GLAD YOU MADE IT.
- WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
- IT’S A SINGLE HOMICIDE.
UH, IT’S PRETTY UGLY IN THERE.
JUST A HEADS-UP.
- CAN’T WAIT TO SEE.
[camera shutter clicking]
[doorbell rings]
- OOH, THE DOORBELL.
- YOU BETTER BE CAREFUL.
IT MIGHT BE THE BOOGEYMAN.
- WELL, SHOULDN’T I MAKE IT ROMANTIC
IF I’M ABOUT TO DIE?
LET ME SET THE MOOD FOR MY DEATH.
[chuckles]
[all chuckling]
- [speaks indistinctly]
- WHAT IF THERE IS SOME PSYCHO DICK AT THE DOOR?
- [scoffs] SHE’LL BE FINE.
IT’S PROBABLY JUST SOME RANDOM DRUNK CHICK THAT GOT LOCKED OUT.
AND THERE’S NOBODY WAY UP HERE BUT US.
- AND THE PSYCHO PIZZA KILLER.
[high-pitched screeching sound]
- REAL FUNNY, DICKHEADS. - I KNOW.
- I’M GONNA GO CHECK ON HER.
- NO, COME ON, BABY. COME BACK.
COME ON, BABY. WAIT.
- SO, LIKE, HOW MUCH--
[glass shatters]
[soft footstep]
[foreboding music]
♪
- BECKY?
[shrieking]
BECKY’S DEAD.
- [both laugh] - AND THE OSCAR GOES TO...
- [sobbing]
- BECKY’S DEAD! [feigns sobbing]
- OH, MAN. NOT FUNNY, JULIE!
[squelching sound]
- [screaming]
- DID YOU HEAR SOMETHING?
- [scoffs] DID YOU SAY SOMETHING?
- I’M SERIOUS. I THINK I HEARD SOMETHING.
- DON’T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- I THINK WE SHOULD GO INSIDE.
- WHY, WHEN WE’RE HAVING SO MUCH FUN OUTSIDE?
[bone crunching]
- [yells]
[glass shattering, objects clatter]
[blows landing]
[door creaks]
- [breathes shakily]
[tense, building music]
- COME ON, DON’T YOU THINK THAT’S ENOUGH FOREPLAY?
- AND WHAT’S IN THAT LITTLE HEAD OF YOURS?
- [chuckles]
HEAD.
- YOU WANT TO SEE HOW LONG I HOLD MY BREATH?
- TELL THE TITANIC I SAID HELLO. - [chuckles]
- OHH.
OH, FUCK.
- HOW WAS THAT?
- THAT WAS PERFECT.
[water gurgling]
[sighs]
OH, YEAH.
AH.
- OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
[screams]
[faint screams]
- KAREEM?
- [shushes]
- [muffled scream]
- YOU HEAR SOMETHING?
- BABY, THIS IS WEED, NOT CRACK.
WHAT’S WRONG WITH YOU?
- THIS DON’T FEEL RIGHT, MAN.
I MEAN, IT’S LIKE WE WAY OUT HERE IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE,
AWAY FROM EVERYBODY AND EVERY DAMN THING.
- I THINK THIS WEED IS MAKING YOU PARANOID.
- GIVE ME MY WEED BACK, THEN.
SHIT.
UH-UH, WE GOT TO GO. WE GOT TO GO.
I TOLD YOU THERE WAS SOME SHIT HAPPENING.
I TOLD YOU I DIDN’T FEEL RIGHT ABOUT THIS.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THERE’S SOME DAMN DEAD PEOPLE OUTSIDE
IN THAT DAMN JACUZZI OUT THERE.
YOU THINK I’M PARANOID? GO LOOK FOR YOURSELF.
- [scoffs]
[sighs]
OKAY, KAREEM, YOU ARE TAKING THIS WHOLE THING WAY TOO FAR.
IF YOU WANT TO GO, WE CAN GO,
BUT YOU AIN’T GOT TO START MAKING UP LIES
ABOUT DEAD PEOPLE IN JACUZZIS.
- OH, HELL-- HELL, NO, MAN.
I KNOW WHAT THE HELL I JUST SAW.
LOOK, GET YOUR SHIT.
WE GETTING THE CREW.
WE GETTING THE FUCK UP OUT OF HERE.
LET’S GO RIGHT NOW.
- OKAY.
- SO ANYWAYS, THREE DAYS AFTER THAT,
THERE’S ANOTHER PARTY.
THAT THING WAS, LIKE, BLUE--
- MARCUS, MAN, OPEN THE DOOR.
- I’M HAVING SEX RIGHT NOW.
COME BACK IN, LIKE, TWO DAYS.
- [giggles]
OOH.
- WHAT NOW?
- WE GOT TO GET THE HELL UP OUT OF HERE, MAN.
THERE’S SOME SHIT GOING DOWN.
- WHAT’S GOING ON?
- HE THINKS HE SEES DEAD PEOPLE IN THE JACUZZI.
- MAN, I KNOW WHAT THE HELL I SAW.
- THAT JACUZZI?
- YEAH.
- THAT ONE RIGHT THERE? - YEAH.
- THE ONE THAT’S EMPTY?
- LOOK, MAN, THAT’S THE ONLY FUCKING JACUZZI OUT THERE.
MAN, I KNOW WHAT THE FUCK I SAW.
MARCUS, THERE’S SOME SHIT GOING DOWN IN THIS HOUSE, MAN.
WE NEED TO ROLL.
- ALL RIGHT.
I’LL GO CHECK IT OUT.
BETTER YET, WE GET THE WHOLE CREW,
AND WE’LL ALL GO CHECK IT OUT.
[sighs]
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
YOU CHECK DOWNSTAIRS.
WE’LL CHECK UP HERE,
AND THEN WE’LL CHECK THE OTHER WING, A’IGHT?
WE’LL FIND THE CREW, AND WE’LL SEE WHAT’S UP.
- YEAH, AND IF YOU SEE ANYTHING, SCREAM.
[snorting laughter]
- SCARY-ASS, MAN.
YOU KNOW YOU DON’T KNOW HOW TO SMOKE NO WEED.
[knocking at door]
- JODY?
[suspenseful music]
♪
IT’S KIND OF SCARY UP IN HERE.
- WHAT?
I’M SCARED.
- [sighs]
LOOK, MY GIRL JODY’S IN ONE OF THESE ROOMS, A’IGHT?
NOW IF WE SPLIT UP, IT’LL BE QUICKER.
YOU CHECK THAT SIDE.
I’LL CHECK THIS SIDE.
- OKAY.
- ALL RIGHT.
JODY?
- JODY?
- [screams]
[laughter]
- [sighs]
- I’M NOT CUT OUT FOR THIS.
- COME ON.
[deep growling sound]
[squishing footsteps]
- EW.
BABE, I JUST STEPPED ON SOMETHING.
- COME ON.
- [screaming]
[gasping]
- MARCUS, THIS BETTER BE REALLY FRICKING GOOD,
BECAUSE I SWEAR TO GOD,
IF NOBODY’S DEAD, I’M GONNA KILL YOU.
- YEAH, I BELIEVE YOU, BRO.
I SEE CRAZY SHIT ALL THE TIME.
THESE FUCKERS NEVER BELIEVE ME.
- OKAY, LET’S GO.
[giggles]
- BEEN HERE TOO LONG ANYWAY.
- YEAH, SO I WAS TELLING YOU,
I SAW THIS FACE IN THE FIREPLACE.
IT WAS, LIKE...
- DAMN.
- WHAT? - WHAT?
- HOLD UP. HOLD UP. HOLD UP.
I FORGOT ANNA.
ANNA?
- ANNA?
- ANNA? - ANNA?
- AN-NUH?
- THIS SHIT IS SERIOUS.
ANNA?
OH, SHIT!
- OH, MY GOD!
- FUCKING SHIT! GET OUT!
- JODY, JODY!
- LET’S GO!
[both yelling in panic]
- [roars] - JODY, JODY, GO!
- [yells]
[blade whistling]
- RUN! RUN!
[screaming]
- [grunts]
- [yelping screams]
[pounding at door]
- OPEN THE DOOR!
- OPEN! OPEN!
[desperate screaming]
- OPEN THE FUCKING DOOR!
[blade clanging]
- [roaring]
[banging stops]
[panting]
- IS THAT DEAD ENOUGH FOR YOU, JODY?
- OH, MY GOD.
WE’RE GONNA DIE.
- NO ONE IS GOING TO DIE.
- HA, YOU MIGHT WANT TO REPHRASE THAT.
NO ONE ELSE IS GONNA DIE,
BECAUSE THERE’S A GIRL OUT THERE
WITH HER FUCKING THROAT CUT WIDE OPEN.
- OH, MY GOD, WE ARE GONNA DIE.
- THERE HAS TO BE AN ANSWER FOR ALL OF THIS.
BRANDON?
- WHO WAS THAT MAN? HUH?
WHAT WAS THAT?
WHAT THE FUCK DID YOU GUYS DO TO MY PARTY?
- BRANDON, CHILL OUT. - NO-NO-NO-NO.
I KNEW I SHOULDN’T HAVE INVITED YOU
AND YOUR FOOD-STAMP GHETTO FUCK-FINANCIAL-AID FRIENDS HERE!
- HEY, FUCK YOU!
- COME AND GET IT! COME AND GET IT!
COME AND GET IT! YOU WANT IT?
- FUCK YOU. - BRANDON, BRANDON!
YOU’RE FUCKING OUT OF LINE, DUDE.
IF IT WASN’T FOR HIM, I’D BE FUCKING DEAD RIGHT NOW.
GIVE ME THE BAT, BRO,
BEFORE I HELP HIM WHUP YOUR ASS.
GIVE ME THE BAT.
GIVE ME THE BAT, A’IGHT?
- IT WAS YOUR GAME.
IT WAS YOUR FUCKING GAME, MARCUS!
[door rattling]
- [screams]
- OPEN THE DOOR. IT’S US.
- LET US IN!
- OPEN THIS DOOR! - MARCUS! JODY!
- SOMEBODY OPEN UP! - HURRY!
OHH!
- OVER HERE.
[door slams]
- IT’S A DAMN BLOODBATH DOWN THERE, MAN.
- OH, EVERYBODY’S DEAD.
- GUYS, WE ARE ALL GONNA FUCKING DIE.
- NO, WE’RE NOT.
- YOU-- OH, THAT’S ONE LUCKY FUCKER.
YOU GOT AWAY.
WHERE ARE YOU STABBED AT?
- HE AIN’T STABBED, MAN.
I ACCIDENTALLY JUST KNOCKED HIS ASS OUT.
YOU MADE US ALL--
[all yelling]
- YOU WANT IT? I’M RIGHT HERE!
- KAREEM, MAN, IT’S NOT HIS FAULT!
- WHOSE FAULT IS IT THEN?
- DOES IT REALLY MATTER WHOSE FAULT IT IS?
THERE’S A FUCKING PSYCHO WITH AN AX IN THIS HOUSE.
HOW ABOUT WE BLAME HIM, THE KILLER?
IF YOU FUCKERS CAN STOP TRYING TO PROVE
WHO’S GOT A BIGGER DICK,
MAYBE WE CAN GET OUT OF HERE ALIVE.
- FUCK.
- YO.
SORRY ABOUT THAT ONE.
- DON’T SWEAT IT.
WE GOT TO DO WHAT WE GOT TO DO, RIGHT?
- SORRY.
TRUCE?
- IT’S BEEN A HALF AN HOUR,
AND WE AIN’T SEEN OR HEARD ANYTHING YET.
- I’M GOING TO GET THE KEYS.
- I’LL GO WITH YOU.
- NO-NO-NO, STAY HERE.
THE KEYS ARE JUST DOWN THE HALL IN MY DAD’S OFFICE.
BE BACK BEFORE YOU KNOW.
PROMISE.
- YEAH, AND IF I GO WITH YOU--
- KARINA.
MY DICK IS BIGGER.
I THINK I WIN.
- WE STILL DON’T KNOW IF SHAWN IS ALIVE.
- WAIT, HOLD ON, MAN.
WE AIN’T LEAVING UNTIL WE KNOW FOR SURE.
BRANDON, GO GET THE KEYS FROM YOUR DAD’S OFFICE.
WE GONNA FIND SHAWN,
DEAD OR ALIVE.
- WAIT, WHAT ABOUT US?
- YOU AND SCOTT JUST STAY WITH THE GIRLS.
IF THAT MOTHERFUCKER COME BACK,
SOCK HIS ASS,
JUST LIKE I DID SCOTT.
LET’S GO.
[door creaking]
[soft creaking]
[keys jingling]
- [gasps]
SHIT.
[wood creaking]
[coughing]
[yells] - [screams]
- KARINA.
- [snorts]
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT NEED SOME HELP,
AND FROM THE LOOKS OF IT, I THINK I WAS RIGHT.
NOW GRAB YOUR DAMN KEYS, AND LET’S GO.
- I DON’T HAVE TIME TO TRY EVERY CAR.
I NEED MY KEYS.
[keys jingling]
- [shuddering sighs]
HURRY UP.
- I CAN’T SEE.
- FUCK IT, BRANDON, HURRY.
- GOT IT.
[blade whistles]
- [yells]
- [grunting]
- [growls]
- [screams]
[sobbing]
[yells]
[sobs]
- HEY, THEY SHOULD BE BACK BY NOW, DON’T YOU THINK?
RIGHT?
- I THINK SHE’S RIGHT.
IT’S TAKING WAY TOO LONG.
- NO, THEY’LL BE BACK.
FOR NOW, WE JUST WAIT.
- WAIT FOR WHAT, MAN?
TO GET MY HEAD SPLATTERED ON THE WALL?
- WHAT ELSE ARE WE GONNA DO?
WHAT OTHER CHOICE DO WE HAVE?
- OH, GREAT, WE’RE GONNA DIE. THAT’S IT.
WE’RE DEAD.
- WOULD YOU SHUT THE FUCK UP?
- HEY, EASY ON HER, BRO.
WE’RE NOT GONNA DIE.
I CAN HOT-WIRE A CAR.
THAT’S JUST WHAT I’M GONNA FUCKING DO
TO GET US OUT OF HERE.
- NO, NO, NO, PLEASE, CAL, DON’T, PLEASE.
IF YOU LEAVE THIS ROOM, YOU’LL DIE.
PLEASE.
- [gasping]
- LET’S GO FIND SHAWN AND GET THE HELL UP OUT OF HERE.
[woman screams]
SHIT!
[tense percussive music]
♪
[panting]
SHIT.
- HELP!
HELP!
- DAMN!
- OH, GOD.
- I TRIED TO SAVE HER, BUT I COULDN’T.
I’M SORRY. - MOVE. MOVE.
NO. NO.
COME ON, BABY. GET UP.
WE GOT TO GO.
COME ON, WE GOT TO GO.
WE GOT TO GO, ROXY! WE GOT TO GO!
COME ON, BABY. GET UP.
NO.
[sobbing]
COME ON, BABY. WE GOT TO GO.
WE GOT TO GO, BABY. WE GOT TO GO.
LET ME GO!
DON’T TOUCH ME!
- [whispering] I’M SORRY.
- [sobbing] WE GOT TO GO.
[car engine turning]
- YEAH.
[panting]
ONSTAR.
- ONSTAR ACTIVATED.
- SHIT.
[car horn blares]
[bone crunches]
- ONSTAR, HOW CAN I ASSIST YOU, MR. O’CONNELL?
MR. O’CONNELL?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
MR. O’CONNELL, WE’RE GONNA SEND OUT ASSISTANCE.
- IT’S HIM.
- FUCK THIS SHIT.
- KAREEM!
[grunting]
- FIGHT ME LIKE A MAN, MOTHERFUCKER!
COME ON! COME ON!
FIGHT ME LIKE A MAN!
[gagging]
- [yells]
- [roaring]
[wall crunches]
[gasping]
[moaning]
[groaning]
- [growls]
- [strained groaning]
- [growling]
- [yells]
[wood clattering]
[panting]
- [growling yell]
- [yells]
- [pained groaning]
- GET THE AX! - GET THE AX!
- [growls]
- GET THE AX!
GOD, GET THE FUCKING AX!
GET THE AX!
- GET THE AX!
- [growls]
- HIT HIM!
- HIT THIS FUCKER! - HIT HIM!
[blade whirs]
- WHAT THE FUCK DID YOU DO?
WHAT THE FUCK DID YOU DO?
shick!
[coughing]
SHIT.
FUCK.
[cell phone rings]
- [gasping sobbing]
[door rattling]
[gasping]
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- JODY’S DEAD.
- DAMN.
SCOTT HAS FLIPPED THE FUCK OUT.
- SCOTT IS STILL ALIVE?
- YEAH, BUT HE’S GONE CRAZY.
- WE HAVE TO SAVE HIM.
WE CAN GET TO HIM.
- LISTEN TO ME!
SCOTT JUST KILLED KAREEM, AND HE TRIED TO KILL ME!
IT’S SHAWN.
- WHERE IS HE GOING?
- OH, SHIT.
[door creaking]
- [screams]
[sobbing]
[knife squelches]
- SHAWN!
[body thuds]
- [whimpering]
[wood splintering]
[door creaks]
[door slams]
- SCOTT, MAN.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU, SCOTT?
- YOU AND THE REST OF YOUR FUCKING FRIENDS STEAL MY LIFE,
AND YOU ASK ME WHY?
THAT FUCKING GAME STOLE MY LIFE, MARCUS.
- I’LL SHOW YOU GUYS HOW TO DO A REAL PRANK CALL.
[echoing]
- DO YOU THINK IT’S EASY TO SEE YOUR PARENTS
MURDERED RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU...
- [screams]
- ALL OVER A FUCKING GAME?
[screaming]
OF COURSE, I HAD A FEW ISSUES AFTER THAT,
BUT THEY DIDN’T HAVE TO SEND ME TO FARLEY.
DO YOU KNOW HOW FUCKING CRAZY THOSE PEOPLE ARE UP THERE?
I TRIED TO SAVE HER, BUT I COULDN’T.
I’M SORRY. [echoing]
[phone ringing]
LET A PLAYER SHOW YOU HOW THE PLAYERS PLAY, ALL RIGHT?
- MAN, YOU KNOW I DON’T DRINK.
- I HATE THE COPS. [echoing]
- GRAB MY MP3 PLAYER.
[phone ringing]
HE’S NOT SCOTT.
- WHAT?
- YO, WHAT YOU DOING IN HERE, MAN,
CHANGING YOUR PAD?
THIS IS WEIRD, MAN.
- WHAT?
[sobs] WHAT?
- YOU AND YOUR DUMBASS PRANKS.
AFTER EVERYTHING THAT’S HAPPENED,
YOU STILL THINK THIS IS A FUCKING GAME.
- YOU CAN GET HELP.
- I DON’T NEED ANY HELP.
I GOT HELP EVERY FUCKING DAY
FOR TEN SHIT-FILLED YEARS.
THE ONLY THING THAT’S GONNA HELP
IS TO KILL ALL OF MY PROBLEMS
ONE BY ONE.
[door rattling]
- [gasps]
[door slams]
- THANK YOU.
- [growling softly]
- ARE YOU AFRAID OF HIM?
HE WAS MY BEST FRIEND IN FARLEY.
HE GAVE ME A NEW LIFE
AFTER YOU STOLE MINE.
- [screams]
- [choked moaning]
- I’M SORRY. I HAD TO DO IT.
[body thuds]
NO MORE LOOSE ENDS.
- [whimpers]
- MY BROTHER’S PROBLEM WAS...
HE WAS TOO WEAK,
DOING ALL THAT NIGGER TALK,
GOING ALONG WITH ALL YOU ASSHOLES
AS YOU KEPT PLAYING THAT GAME,
THE SAME FUCKING GAME THAT KILLED MY PARENTS.
DID YOU THINK THAT IF I GOT OUT
AND SAW YOU DOING THE SAME FUCKING THING
THAT IT WOULDN’T FILL ME WITH RAGE?
- MAN, THAT WAS 12 YEARS AGO!
- FUCK YOU!
YOU NEVER FUCKING LEARNED.
YOU STOLE MY LIFE, MARCUS.
NOW I’M GONNA STEAL YOURS.
OOH!
[both growling]
- [yells]
[screaming]
- [groans]
[aggressive yelling]
- [growls]
[metal clattering]
- [screams]
FUCKING BITCH.
[head crunches]
[agonized screaming]
[strained gasping]
- [chuckles lightly]
- [yells]
- DON’T! - STOP!
[gunfire]
[panting]
- LOOKS LIKE WE GOT YOUR MAN.
SHIT.
GOOD WORK, PARTNER.
- [sobbing]
- LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE ONE SURVIVOR.
JESUS, THIS PLACE IS A BLOODY MESS.
- YOU JUST TAKE IT EASY.
- POOR KID.
- DON’T WORRY ABOUT A THING.
WE’LL TAKE CARE OF YOU.
IT’S OVER NOW.
[dial tone beeping]
Captioning byCaptionMax www.captionmax.com
[hard rock music]
♪
- ♪ FALSE HOPE
♪ LOST INTEGRITY
♪ THE FEAR IS MY OWN WAY
♪ TO PACIFY MY GROWING NEED TO SUFFER ♪
♪ I LISTEN TO THE PUMP OF LIFE AS SUCH ♪
♪ I’LL TRY AND BECOME ALL THAT YOU WANT ME TO BE ♪
- ♪ THE WAIT IS OVER
♪ I’M BREAKING DOWN ♪
♪ CAN YOU FEEL THE FIRE?
♪ I WON’T CALM DOWN ♪
♪ I DROPPED DOWN ON THE FLOOR
♪ I’M BREAKING DOWN ♪
♪
- ♪ THE END OF ONE
♪ SO BEGINS A NEW
♪ FORGET THE PAST
♪ FORGET WHAT I’VE BEEN THROUGH ♪
♪ WE ARE THE ONES WHO WANT IT
♪ FACING EVERYTHING
♪ AGAINST THE CURRENT
♪ RISE WITH ME
- ♪ THE WAIT IS OVER
♪ I’M BREAKING DOWN ♪
♪ CAN YOU FEEL THE FIRE?
♪ I WON’T CALM DOWN ♪
♪ I DROPPED DOWN ON THE FLOOR
♪ I’M BREAKING DOWN ♪
- ♪ THE WAIT IS OVER
♪ THE WAIT IS OVER
♪
- ♪ THE WAIT IS OVER
[creepy music]
♪