(ambient music)
(elevator bell chimes)
(door knock)
- [Man in shirt] Hey, Elijah. Come on in.
- Elijah Young, star power bottom.
- [Elijah] What's up, Demetrius?
- Last time I saw you was in L.A.
What was that, three years ago?
- I think about four now.
- Back then I was the star
and you is the star now.
- You're still a star.
- Nah, I'm not saying I'm
retiring, the diapers cost a lot.
- Guys, paper work.
- Wait a second. You're a dad now?
- Yeah, Ricky and I adopted a little girl.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks, man.
- ID and test results.
- Thanks.
- Do you have a copy of his?
- Sure, right here.
- Yeah so I'm a regular Mr. Mom now.
- Do you have a picture?
- A what?
- Of your little girl.
- Oh, of course.
- Oh wow, she's adorable.
- Thanks, man.
- No problem.
Thanks.
I'm having a little
get-together on Saturday.
I mean, you and Ricky are
more than welcome to come
if you guys can get a sitter.
- I mean, I'd be down
but Ricky has baby fever
and we don't do the whole sitter thing.
- I can definitely understand that.
(Elijah and Demetrius moaning)
(rolling train)
(sighs)
You're fucking kidding me.
Seriously?
Seriously, Geo? Are
you fucking kidding me?
It's the first of the month and
you pull a disappearing act.
Look, I know you were probably
waiting until the last minute
to pull it off but I wish
you would have just come
and talked to me, we could
have worked something out.
Look, just call me back when you get this.
Fuck.
- [Rigo] So he's just gone?
- [Elijah] Totally. It's like
he was never even here at all.
Even scrubbed the bathroom clean.
- Well that's something.
What are you typing?
- Nothing much, just
placing an ad on Craigslist.
- That's inviting trouble.
- Yeah, you're probably right.
- [Rigo] But you should
be used to that by now.
- Yeah yeah, whatever.
Rigo, I just don't know what I'm gonna do.
I can't afford this place
by myself and start classes
in the fall, do you know
anyone who's looking?
- Yeah Rashaad, like I know
anyone who would wanna dwell
in the fucking republican boondocks.
Seriously man, how do you do it?
- I dwell anonymously,
thank you very much.
And for your information
my congressman is democrat.
- [Rigo] He's a conservicrat.
- Okay, whatever.
Look, I gotta go. I'm probably
gonna grab some takeout.
See you Saturday?
- I wouldn't miss it.
- Sounds great.
- Hi, Elijah.
- Hey Tak, how's it goin'?
- [Tak] Good.
- [Elijah] My order ready?
- [Tak] Just a few minutes.
- [Elijah] No problem.
- How was your day?
- It was okay, I've had better.
My roommate unexpectedly moved out.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- [Elijah] No problem.
What can you do, right?
- Did you find someone new?
- Nah, I'll probably
start looking tomorrow.
Why? Are you looking for a place?
- Okay, $9.75 please.
- Oh yeah, right.
Here you go, here's a 10.
You can keep the change.
- [Tak] Thank you.
- [Elijah] Yeah no problem.
- [Tak] Thank you my
friend, have a good night.
- Yeah, you too.
- Oh wait, I forgot to
give you your receipt.
- Oh okay, cool.
Thanks, Tak. Good night.
- [Tak] Goodnight, Elijah.
(door knock)
- Hi, Elijah.
- Hey, you're early. Please, come in.
- Sorry, I gave myself
extra time to get lost.
- Don't worry about it, it's fine.
- Shoes off?
- Typically.
A glass of wine?
- Oh, no thank you.
- Takeshi, just say yes
so I'm not drinking alone.
- Okay, yes.
- Excellent.
I've recently developed a
taste for Chilean cabernet.
They're kind of peppery.
Here you go.
- It's very nice.
The only time I ever
had wine was in church
when I was young.
- Church, not temple?
- I was raised Roman Catholic.
- That's kind of unusual, isn't it?
- A little. I grew up in Kirishima.
There's actually a lot of Catholics there.
- Interesting.
Well I'm sure whatever they
were serving you in church
wasn't half as good as this.
- No, this is quite good.
- Ready to see the room?
- Yep.
- This way.
Well there's not much closet space but,
there's more in the hall.
- Oh no, this is more than sufficient.
- Great.
Well before we talk about
rent, we should probably
discuss lifestyles.
- Lifestyles?
- [Elijah] As in, I'm
gay and I don't hide it.
- I know.
My co-workers all think
you're very flamboyant.
- Oh, really?
- [Takeshi] You dress very sexy.
- Well I didn't think I
was being that obvious but,
good to know.
- Is it a problem for
you if I'm not like that?
- Are you asking if it's a
problem that you're not gay?
- [Takeshi] Yes.
- Of course not.
Come on, let me show you
the rest of the apartment.
I go out of town a lot for work,
so I'm looking for somebody
I can really trust.
- What do you do?
- I'm in the adult entertainment industry.
I'm sorry. I meant to put these away.
It's just a few proofs
the photographer sent me
for my website.
- [Takeshi] Those are
very erotic photographs.
- You think so?
- You're a model?
- Something like.
- Oh, adult entertainment.
- Yeah, but I'm not about the party life.
I prefer home to be a quiet place.
- I understand.
- I'm actually having a small
get-together on Saturday.
Just a few friends, nothing major.
So trust me, you're more
than welcome to have
your girlfriend come over.
- I don't have a girlfriend.
- I'm sure that will change.
So, when's the lease
at your other place up?
- There's no lease.
When I quit my job, they
won't let me live with the
other employees.
- You're quitting your job?
- Now that I have my graduate degree,
I want to start working in my field,
information technology.
- Cool. Interesting.
So wait, you and your co-workers,
you all live in the same house?
- [Takeshi] Yes.
- Like servant's quarters?
- Kind of. It's very dirty and nasty.
I can't wait to leave.
- [Elijah] That's terrible.
- You have such a beautiful home.
I would really love to live here.
- Thanks.
Well the rent's about 1,600 a month.
Since I have the larger
room, I say about 650,
half utilities.
- I can only afford 350 per month.
- You're serious?
- You look upset.
- Takeshi, that's low like, really low.
You can't even rent a closet
on Long Island for 350.
- It's gonna take time
for me to find a job.
I have saved enough money
to pay 350 for five months.
As soon as I get a job I can
start paying the full rent
and half the utilities.
- I understand but I'm sorry,
that just doesn't work for me.
(phone bleeps)
Excuse me, I have to take this.
It's for business.
- [Takeshi] I will be a
very good roommate, Elijah.
I will share in the
cooking, I am very clean.
I see you in the restaurant
and I think you're a good man.
- That's sweet of you to say, Takeshi
but this is about money.
Business.
I'd love to help but,
I'm sorry, I just can't.
- [Takeshi] I understand.
- I'm sorry for wasting your time.
Let me show you to the door.
Wait, you haven't even finished your wine.
- That's all right.
I appreciate your hospitality.
- Wait, you're an I.T. guy, right?
- [Takeshi] Yes.
- That means you know
about building websites.
Designing them, I mean.
- In Japan I studied graphic
and multimedia design.
- [Elijah] Are you any good?
- Very.
- Well it just so happens I'm
looking for a website built.
What do you think about a trade?
I'll charge partial in
rent, in exchange you get my
website up and running.
- I would love that.
- I mean, it has to be
first class, flawless.
- It will be the very best.
- Well I think you have
yourself a deal, Mr. Takeshi.
How do you say cheers in Japanese?
- Kanpai.
- So does this mean I
will be working in the
adult entertainment industry?
- (chuckles) Yeah, I guess it does.
- Oh.
How exciting.
- Come on, man. Seriously,
you're killing me.
When would you like to move in?
- Tomorrow?
- Tomorrow it is.
(opera music)
- [Rigo] Wait, so he has no job
and can't pay the full rent?
Yeah, he's perfect.
- He's sweet, and he knows how to cook.
Besides, he's agreed to do my website.
- Rashaad, you know how
Japanese people love curry?
That shit can really stink up the place.
- You're right, I didn't think about that.
- [Rigo] The smell permeates everything.
- I guess we'll just
have to see how it goes
and take it from there.
- [Voiceover] Turn right
at the next street.
- New client?
- New location.
The guy's never invited
me to his home before.
It's usually a hotel.
- (chuckles) His wife must be away.
(phone bleeps)
- Are you on Grinder?
- [Rigo] Maybe. Don't judge me.
- Okay whatever, Rigo.
Look, I'm just about there.
I'm gonna have to call you later, okay?
- [Rigo] Bye.
- Later.
(jazz music)
- [Elijah] Your collection of
classical music is impressive.
- Thanks.
- [Elijah] But there's no opera.
- My father was a power orchestra fanatic.
I guess I inherited his
distaste for lyrics.
- I've always thought the
human voice was more expressive
than any musical instrument.
- I have no problem with the human voice.
I just don't like words set to music.
- Interesting distinction.
So you don't think words are musical?
- Not at all.
Words have a musicality.
Even a character of their own.
I just think that words
and music spoil each other.
They cancel each other out.
- I see you have the
State of Queer anthology.
My friend, well my ex,
he has a few stories in here.
- [Man] So do I actually.
- [Elijah] You write?
Oh, you do.
So why are you in construction?
- Drywall pays the bills.
Writing is more of a hobby.
- Thanks.
- Cheers.
- You must be pretty good.
Hobbyists don't usually get published.
- What's your ex's name?
- Rigo. Rigoberto Gomez.
- Really?
His stories are among
the best. Very militant.
- He sees himself as a bitter pill.
The critics call him strident.
- Is he that angry?
- No, not really.
He's elevated the act of
ranting into an art form.
He's actually pretty funny though.
A constant stream of commentary.
- [Man] Oh, I can see that.
- So you into jazz too?
- A little bit. Feel
improvisational tonight.
- Improvisations aren't scripted.
"I'm a married man from Puerto Rico
"who frequently comes to
Long Island on business."
- Help yourself to some cheese.
The Gorgonzola is amazing.
- "I'm a hung, verbal top
who enjoys drilling the fight
"out of twink power bottoms.
"And I love a submissive
boy in a jockstrap."
- I know what my Daddy
Search profile says.
- What's up with this, Bryson?
- It's just a scenario.
So is this, but our
dialogue is improvised.
- What's this scenario?
- A man invites another man
into his home for dinner.
- That's omitting a lot.
- What details need to be filled in?
- A lot, I mean, you're fit, attractive.
You're not my typical clientele.
You have a photo of yourself
hugged up with another guy
so you're obviously not in the closet.
- Definitely not.
- Yet, you pretend to
be a married businessman
from out of town.
- I play the role that works best for me.
- I guess we both have that in common.
- Do you find reality less interesting?
- Perplexing.
So what made you decide
to draw back the curtains?
- I hadn't had a date in years.
Aside from my family,
you're the first person
I invited to my home in a long time.
- [Elijah] Why me?
- You're intelligent, a
good conversationalist.
- And paid, so no judgements here.
- [Bryson] I'm sure you see
more than your share of freaks.
- Are you a freak?
- I was in an abusive
relationship so you might say
I was damaged by the experience.
- That's not hard to understand.
At least not from me.
Certainly doesn't make you a freak.
- I wasn't the victim,
Elijah. I was the abuser.
- So what are you making?
- A mofongo, it's a Puerto Rican dish.
My mother's recipe.
- I'm sure it'll be great.
(Elijah moaning)
(ambient music)
(birds chirping)
Wow.
Very fancy.
- All I had was some toast, maybe eggs
but I have to leave for work soon.
- This is sweet. Thank you.
- I like performing the role
of the affectionate mate.
- I don't think it's
performing a role, Bryson.
It's who you are.
It was the perfect date and
you're ending it perfectly.
- Had it been a real
date, I would have learned
as much about you as you did about me.
- I kinda got the
impression I was a stand-in
for someone else.
- Maybe, I was hoping you would
shine through my projections.
- I told you a lot about myself.
- You dropped enough
hints to make me believe
we were having a real conversation.
For the most part, you were
playing at being Elijah Young.
- Playing at being?
Sounds like words from a book.
- Sorry.
- Stolen words from a man who
doesn't need to pay for it.
But does anyway.
- The Long Island gay community is small,
and my past is public record.
- An exile, that I understand.
- [Bryson] Really?
- Let's just say my life is...
complicated.
- Do tell.
No peaking behind the curtain?
Not even a little?
- That's not up for sale.
(door knock)
Oh, go away.
(groans)
(door knock)
- Hi, Elijah.
- Do you have a lot to move in?
- No no, just some clothes and a futon.
- Think you can handle it yourself?
I didn't get much sleep last night.
- That's fine, my friend.
I'll be very quiet.
- Great well, make yourself at home.
I should be up in a few hours.
- Hey, Kayla.
Of course you don't.
Really?
Oh well I've got something to tell you.
I've got something to tell you, listen!
Me and Stefan, we broke up.
Yes, again. I know I know I know.
Well, he cheated.
Yes with Christina.
That's who he cheated with.
It's like I want to take
him back but then again
I don't want to.
Really? You think so?
I was thinking about us going
to counselling or something.
Yeah really, but you know.
I don't know, I think it could work.
What do you think?
'Cause I need some type
of friendly advice.
Last time? We've been through
this like five times already.
(dark ambient music)
What are you lookin' at?
(Elijah groaning)
- Welcome to the dorm.
Somethin' smells good.
- I was hoping you like curry.
- I've only had it a few times.
Chicken or beef?
- Chicken.
(Elijah chuckles)
What's so funny?
- Nothing, don't worry about it.
Um, I'll grab a bottle of chardonnay.
(phone bleeps)
(Bryson chuckles)
I really like how Macho
Fuckers done their website.
There's like an easy simplicity to it.
But you see here...
I like how Breed It Raw
displays their models.
Think we could do something like this?
- Sure, you just have
to choose the criteria.
- By names, alphabetically by first
since most models only use one.
Then by whether they're tops or bottoms
and then by ethnicity.
- Tops or...
- Bottoms.
Sorry, gay stuff.
Uh, tops fuck, bottoms get fucked.
- Oh. Which are you?
- Total bottom.
The chicken curry is incredible, Takeshi.
- I'm glad you like it.
Are you on these sites?
- Of course.
- Oh.
Elijah Young, a hot
twink from New York City.
He's hot to death.
Just look at that tight meaty
ass any tops wanna beat.
Elijah loves the hole dug out
and he effortlessly gives
ultra-hung tops a run for their money.
Is Rashaad Jackson your real name?
- You saw the mail?
- Yes.
Wow, you've done a lot of videos!
Are you famous?
- Too famous.
Sometimes I feel like my
life isn't my own anymore.
- What do you mean?
- [Elijah] Just people, I mean.
Complete strangers think they know me.
Some even think they own a piece of me.
- How?
- Sometimes I would go to
clubs and guys would corner me
in the bathrooms as if I owed them sex
just because they bought
a DVD or had a membership
to one of the sites.
- [Takeshi] Really?
- Oh yeah.
There was this one time,
and this is really weird.
I was at a Taco Bell in
Manhattan, so this guys comes up
to my table and he's like,
"You keep eating like that and
"you're gonna get fat and I'm
not gonna buy your videos."
- That's very rude.
- The rudeness I can tolerate.
It's when they become
physical that's the problem.
I've been jumped one too many times.
- Gay bashers?
Out here?
- No, drunk gay guys outside the clubs.
Trying to force me to drop my pants.
- Oh my god.
That's crazy.
- Yeah, I just realized I
had to move out of the city.
- If you don't mind me asking,
why do you still do it?
- Porn?
- [Takeshi] Yeah, if it's
causing you so many problems.
- Honestly, it's like this, Tak.
I enjoy exploring my sexuality.
Plus the internet is forever.
Even if I stop tomorrow,
my videos are everywhere.
I'm one of the highest paid
bottoms in urban bareback porn
right now, I'm making the most of it.
- It must be very tough
to have a relationship.
- Yeah.
It is, very tough.
But you have to understand,
most guys just wanna fuck me.
I'm a fantasy to me, not a person.
So with that, I've put
dating on the back-burner.
- Do you think there's a
difference between Elijah
and Rashaad?
- No one's ever asked me a
question like that before.
- Well?
- Rashaad is soft, sensitive even.
A naive kid who moved to
New York from North Carolina
with hopes of becoming an actor.
- And Elijah Young?
- Driven. Determined.
A bit cold, maybe. Detached.
But with swag. (chuckles)
- Do you still want to
pursue an acting career?
- Given what I do now,
I think that particular
career path is closed off.
But I'm standing to be chef though.
Probably leave New York and
Elijah Young in the past.
So you have to teach me how to make
authentic Japanese dishes.
- Yes I will.
- I wasn't the victim,
Elijah, I was the abuser.
I was hoping you would shine
through my projections.
No peaking behind the
curtain? Not even a little?
(Elijah moaning)
- Shit.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah.
(moaning)
Shit.
(muffled laughter from outside)
(door knock)
Takeshi?
- Hey.
- What are you doin'?
- Uh, I...
- I wouldn't have pegged
you as the voyeur type.
- I'm not really.
- It's cool, man.
I've actually watched Mr.
Casanova myself a few times.
- [Takeshi] Casanova?
- My nickname for our neighbor.
Damn. Look at them go at it.
Now I see why you're springing a chub.
- What?
- Pitching the tent?
Hold on. Think I got something.
- What are you doing?
- Here, take this.
Got them when I went
to see Tosca at the Met
with my friend Rigo.
Total nosebleed seats but
it was totally worth it.
Do you like opera?
- [Takeshi] I really haven't
listened to enough of it
to have an opinion.
- [Elijah] Shit. Look at that guy.
Man, he's got game.
Different chick every night.
- [Takeshi] Do you admire that?
- [Elijah] Sure, who wouldn't?
- But you have sex all the time.
- It's not about getting laid, Takeshi.
It's about power.
Take him for instance.
He's hot, not the best
looking guy in the world.
Pretty decent apartment, nice
car but he's not wealthy.
What he's got is attitude.
- Do you act like that when you're Elijah?
- [Elijah] Nah. Not really.
But I'm a trained actor.
I can be him anytime I want.
- Why do you think he's arrogant?
- [Elijah] Damn.
- What?
- Look like the show's over, my friend.
I'll leave you to rub one out.
- Elijah, why do you think he's arrogant?
- Shit man, I'm sorry.
I guess you have to have
the strength of arrogance
to be able to pull a hottie
like that back to your place.
Without paying for it, that is.
- You're mixing up the coupons
from Shishis with these.
- I'm sorry, man.
Look, I'm not gonna pretend to know a guy
just by looking through his
window for a few minutes.
Now that would be arrogant.
None of us are made of
just one thing, Takeshi.
We're all made of many ingredients
in different proportions.
Orson Welles once said,
"Acting is like sculpture.
"It's not what you add to
yourself that makes character,
"it's what you flick away."
- So if you're playing
someone who's shy and afraid?
- Strip away the
confidence, the certainty.
What's left?
The doubt. The fear.
Just fills in the void.
- I am shy and afraid.
- Are you kidding me?
I only had to come here
from North Carolina
to start a new life.
You had to board a plane
and fly across the planet.
That took major balls.
You don't give yourself
nearly enough credit.
- Rashaad.
- Yeah?
- Thank you for being my friend.
(Elijah chuckles)
- Don't mention it.
Night, Tak.
- Goodnight.
- Real talk.
How's everything going
with the new roommate?
- So far so good.
He made chicken curry the other night.
- [Rigo] Told you so!
- It was delicious so don't be an asshole.
- You think this is actually
going to work out, don't you?
- Well you know, I hope so.
I think so.
He's sweet.
- [Rigo] And?
- I don't know, he's been
here for years now but,
he's a little isolated.
- What do you mean?
- I found his Facebook.
- Great, you've turned
into a cyber-stalker.
- I am not stalking, I was just...
curious.
- [Rigo] Okay, so what did you find?
- Fiction, mostly.
He has these wall posts
that dates back like,
two years or so.
They're all about his
daily commute in Manhattan.
Bitching about people in the subway.
I.T. related problems at work.
He even has this one
photo of some blonde chick
he says is his girlfriend.
But it's all fiction though. Lies.
Everything.
- It's just his idealized self.
The life he imagined
when he first came here.
Kinda reminds me of someone.
- Who?
- You.
- Oh, yeah. Right.
- Don't you remember what
your Facebook wall was like
when we first met?
All the auditions you were going on.
How close your were to getting an agent.
Your selfies were a trip.
- Well technically I
was going on auditions.
- It was mostly bullshit!
- You say bullshit, I say embellishment.
We'll leave it at that.
- And like you, he does it
for the people back home.
Now, Rashaad Jackson virtually
ceases to exist online,
whereas Elijah Young has
over 40,000 followers.
- 60,000 now, FYI.
- Well, not one of them are
interested in getting to know
the real you and you're not
even remotely interested
in letting them so...
are you ready yet?
- I believe it's show time.
- [Rigo] Finally.
- [Elijah] So we're having
this whole production weekend,
I think it was for Raw Stallions
or some shit like that.
So like a few of us models,
you know, we're all vibing
chilling at the hotel or whatever
and you know, me and this
one model, we're really like,
kicking it and like
vibing with each other.
But you know, he's a little too feminine,
a little too cunty for him
to fuck me so, you know,
we go to a back room
or whatever, you know,
we start feeling each other
so you know, I don't care,
I'm top and he's sexy as fuck.
So you know, we're starting
to do it or whatever,
you know, we switch
positions, he's now riding me,
just bouncing up and
down on my dick, you know
and I'm loving it at first,
I'm thinking he's starting to
climax and the next thing I know
this spring just shoots out on my chest.
I didn't think nothing of
it at first, so you know,
we're just getting it in, he's
just bouncing and bouncing
and bouncing but the
next thing I know, like,
his dick just shoots
up and the spring just
shoots me in the face and gets in my mouth
and the next thing I know,
it's like piss and I'm like,
"Yo, this man is having a whole
orgasmic piss all over me."
He's moaning to the guys
and thinking nothing of it
and then we finish and he's just like,
"Are you ready to go again?"
- Holy shit!
- [Man with glasses] So I was like, 19,
almost 20-years-old and I was just,
being out, being at the bars, doing stuff.
It was all very new to me and I was like,
going out all the time and you know,
this is before the days of
Grinder and stuff and...
I was like, sleeping with
another guy every weekend night.
Friday, Saturday, Sunday, it
would just be another one.
I was like, you know,
being a total young slut!
And you know, at the time
it was like tops were like,
the rare thing, everyone
seemed to be a bottom.
And so it's like, you could
still be a skinny, nerdy top
and you know, hey you got the equipment,
I'll get the job done.
But I didn't realize how
much I was sleeping around.
I had only been out total at
the bars for like six months.
And...
one night we had the home bar,
it was on the near north side of Chicago,
we were getting together.
It was our home bar, we would
start, have a few drinks
then go off and see a play,
see a movie, see whatever
and I walk in and I'm the first one,
and I'm with four or five of my friends
and I'm the first one, I
open the door and I walk in
and pretty much everyone I had slept with
in the last four, five six months
was around the bar.
(group laughing)
And I'm looking and I'm like,
"Fuck!"
And I stop and it was
like the three stooges.
It's like my friends just piled into me.
Then I turn around they're
still like bumping into me,
I'm talking like, "No, we
can't go here, we gotta go."
"What's wrong? What's wrong?"
Everything is wrong.
I mean, it was like my
whole sexual history
is having a drink!
(group laughing)
Oh my god, it was just way too much.
So we had to go elsewhere.
I didn't go back to that bar for a while.
- [Man in black shirt] So I
had this roommate in college.
Tall, blonde hair, blue eyes.
Gorgeous.
Total homophobe.
Come to find out
that this dude dresses up as
a woman in his spare time.
(group murmurs)
He pulls out a container
full of women's lingerie.
(group laughing)
- Well, how did he explain it?
I mean, what did he say?
- [Man in black shirt] He
just showed me the lingerie.
- And when you found him
was he still homophobic?
(group laughing)
- Did he try modelling it
for you? Did he put it on?
- [Man in black shirt] He
told me he was still straight.
- Okay, did he ever do drag show?
- [Man in black shirt]
With his girlfriend.
- Well that's bonding.
- [Man in black shirt] Yeah, really.
- "Look sweetie, we can
wear the same outfits!"
(group laughing)
- [Takeshi] Um, this is
not something I remember
but something my mother
and my sister told me.
But when I was five or six
there was this neighbor lady,
probably my parents'
friend or whatever but,
whenever my mother have
to leave me alone at home,
she asked this lady to
take of me but then,
later she said, when she came back home,
she found me dressed as a girl.
(group laughing)
This lady enjoyed dressing me as a girl.
Then my mother tell me this story like was
a memory from my childhood.
But with mom, just that's
not very good for the child.
- Did your mom ever like,
ask why was this neighbor lady
dressing you up as a girl?
Did this ever come up?
- [Takeshi] No, she made it a fun story.
(group laughing)
- [Man in blue shirt] So
in colleges, when I decided
I wanted to give older men a try
and I met up with this
guy from Adam for Adam.
I didn't really look at his
pictures before going there
and when I got there he answered the door
and he was this big, huge guy
and if you've ever seen
that show Dinosaurs,
he looked like that only
a giant Ninja Turtle.
And when I get in, he didn't ask for sex
he asked me to give him a
massage and I felt so weird!
It gets to the point
where I'm rubbing his back
and it's really really
gross and it's spotted
and at the end he offered to pay me
and offer to give my number to his friends
to give them massages and
I absolutely made sure
to avoid that guy...
(group laughing)
forever.
(classical music)
- You know, when I was
their age, if I wanted
to get laid I would have
to put on a clean shirt,
go to a bar and socialize.
Now, everyone has their
face buried in a cellphone.
- [Rigo] Is this your first gay party?
- Yes. Everyone has been very nice.
- The crowd is very sedate,
but they all plan on
going out to a club later.
- You too?
- (chuckles) No.
I'm kind of over the club scene.
- I've never been a nightclub.
It seems exciting.
- (chuckles) Do you want to go?
- Probably not tonight.
Elijah say you're his ex.
- Yep, and I'm not the
only one in the room.
(chuckles) No, not him.
That's a client he's deluded
himself into thinking
is boyfriend material.
- You don't think he is?
- I've read his short stories.
There's a lot of dark and sticky
stuff beneath the surface.
Trust me.
That dude's got more issues than Newsweek.
No.
Him.
- [Takeshi] The older man?
Phillip?
- A client-turned-lover-now-friend.
Very familiar pattern.
- Why did they break up?
- Mm, same as me.
Being the boyfriend of a pornstar is...
complicated.
- Did you know Elijah
before he started doing it?
- We were living together at the time.
The first video he ever did was with me.
- Really?
- Yeah, we were living in Brooklyn.
Totally broke.
He was temping during the day.
Got a job dancing at a club at night.
Then he got noticed by the
head of this porn outfit.
- And you did it together?
- Yep.
But they didn't want me though.
They wanted a twink to pair
up with their muscle tops.
But he wouldn't do it
with anybody else, well,
not at first anyway.
So, I became his agent
and sometimes his pimp.
- What do you mean, pimp?
- He had a few pro ads on Adam for Adam
and a few other sites.
I would screen the tricks, set up meets.
He was still auditioning for
parts in off Broadway plays
and little indie films.
And I was desperately
trying to get published.
- If you were so encouraging,
why did you end it?
- Ego. Fragile masculinity.
I felt reduced.
I know they say that sex
isn't the same as lovemaking,
especially on camera but...
- I think I understand.
- He had given up so much, too much.
Just so the electricity bill would be paid
and we wouldn't end up on the streets.
He's so smart, Takeshi, so talented.
The crime of it all though is,
he hasn't even begun to realize his gifts.
- I think Takeshi will be
in need of rescuing soon.
- [Bryson] Why?
- Rigo is brooding like Max von Sydow.
He's more fun when he's
in Denis Leary mode.
- How do you even know
who Max von Sydow is?
- You don't seem to think that much of me.
I have to tell you, it's
a little disappointing.
- Sorry, I didn't mean it like that.
- Sure you didn't.
You were kinda quiet at dinner tonight.
- How many of your friends are exes?
- And I see you've also
forgotten how to talk to people.
Or do you no longer see the
need to be polite with me?
Looks like I'm being summoned.
(phone bleeping)
- All right, everybody.
This is a poem I was thinking
of reading next Thursday
at the open mic, I hope you guys enjoy it.
Bobby was born an American boy.
Baby blues and all.
Even before birth his sex was set.
He was normal as a child, climbed trees
and bled as most boys do the color red.
But inside his closet lay a secret.
A box the color pink, emanating
a perfume of sweet lilies.
Inside this sissy box were
Barbies, lipstick and jewels.
Things a boy should never have,
that is what his dad said.
In middle school he was a monster.
He pulled and poked at all
the girls and ran faster
than all the boys after picking fights
and darkening the other's eye.
Bobby was an all-American
boy but behind closed doors,
Bobby became Brenda and
she was an American girl.
By high school his box became a trunk
and now the color black for
it was easier to conceal
and slide away from Mom's cleaning eye.
Bobby fit in well.
He was still faster than all
the boys but he didn't bother
to grow, not at all.
But one day Dad met
Brenda and Bobby's speed
could do no good to save
him from the black and blues
or the color red.
Brenda had been busted
and all that remained
was a boy, an American and all.
Mom came in shortly,
she didn't look his way.
She went into his closet, took his trunk
and his pink box too, held her hands out
and asked for her rings back.
He trembled as he removed
them, struggling to get past
the swelling then off
she went without a word.
Bobby ran into the bathroom, he used tears
and sit in water to strip his
face of his stolen secret.
He pulled from his body her
tattered remains, placed himself
into a tub and let the
water run past his nose.
Under he lay, hating who
he was and who he wasn't.
Watching everything fade.
And just before he got too deep,
he emerged, alone.
Brenda had been drowned.
And now there was Bobby,
baby blues and all.
At last, an American.
Thank you.
- Wow.
(group applauds)
(door knock)
- Come in.
- Hey, Takeshi.
Just wanted to let you know
we're about to head out.
- Okay, have a good time my friend.
- [Elijah] Are you sure
you don't wanna come?
- Thank you but I'm rather tired.
- Okay well, I guess I'll
probably be staying out
in Manhattan tonight so,
see you in the morning.
- Okay.
- [Elijah] Goodnight.
(door closing)
(Takeshi sighs)
Hey guys, how's it going tonight?
It's your favorite power
bottom here, Elijah Young.
You guys miss me?
Aw, that's sweet.
Thanks beetlebot, thanks papabear.
It's nice to be back with your guys too.
Oh yeah, very busy.
So I went shopping earlier,
bought some very sexy underwear.
You guys want me to model it for you?
Okay.
Oh yeah, my feet are a little dirty.
A group of us was playing
frisbee in the park.
I just hate wearing shoes.
So what do you guys think?
Short enough?
Sexy enough?
How about a strip show?
I'm sure you guys wanna
see the rest, right?
Wanna see me naked?
Hot.
But first, I may need a little help.
I need a hot scenario.
A kinky scenario.
One that's gonna get me extra...
rock hard.
(Takeshi sniffing)
And I thought I was
supposed to be the actor.
- [Takeshi] Shit.
I...
I'm so sorry.
- No, it's fine.
It's fine.
You look nice.
Really nice.
- I never worn trendy clothes.
Even in the stores.
I'd feel too ridiculous
to even try them on.
- And how do you feel wearing them now?
Attractive?
- I look at myself in your mirror and...
- And what?
- I like myself.
But, I also know they're not me.
- Why not?
- It's all surface.
- They're just clothes, Tak.
They're supposed to make you feel good.
- I never thought my
life would be like this.
- You imagined your life
differently in the U.S.?
- I sometimes think about
going back to Japan.
(chuckles)
But on Facebook I told so many falsehoods.
Posted things to make everyone
think that I'm so happy
and successful.
If I went back, they'll
know it was all lies.
- I think I can relate.
If you had any idea what my life was like
back in North Carolina,
the class I'm from.
Tak, my mom's a pediatrician.
My dad's an attorney.
- They didn't approve of you
becoming an actor, did they?
- No.
They didn't.
Even after all these years,
they think eventually I'll just
give it all up and come back home.
- Will you?
- I can't.
You know, the other night
when you had asked me
the difference between Elijah and Rashaad,
I realized something.
Rashaad no longer exists.
You know, New York has its way of...
I don't know.
- Crushing you.
- Exactly.
- In Japan I had a life.
Not what I wanted but...
here, I got nothing.
I'm nobody.
Invisible.
- And do you think...
wearing my clothes makes you visible?
- Look at me.
This is so pathetic.
Look at me, I'm in another man's bedroom
wearing his clothes, I'm insane!
- [Elijah] Come on, just --
- You should be furious with
me for invading your privacy!
- [Elijah] Come on, Tak, just stop.
- I am disgusting.
Pathetic and disgusting!
- Just relax.
- I've, I've never --
- It's fine.
You're not disgusting. You're beautiful.
Beautiful.
(ambient music)
(Takeshi and Elijah moaning)
(opera music)