♪ La la la la la la la la
♪ La la la la la la la la la
♪ The first time I saw you
♪ You were just standing there
♪ First time I saw you
♪ You were beyond compare
♪ Tell me why can't you see
♪ Can't you see what
you're doing to me ♪
♪ It's not an illusion
♪ You seem to have
caught my eye ♪
♪ I couldn't refuse
you, no, no, no ♪
♪ But somehow we're not right
♪ Tell me why can't you see
♪ Can't you see what
you're doing to me ♪
♪ I can't make it
♪ I can't make it,
no, no, no, no ♪
♪ I can't make it
♪ I can't make it,
no, no, no, no ♪
♪ I can't make it
♪ I can't make it,
no, no, no, no ♪
♪ I can't make it, no, no
♪ I can't make it
Could you believe it, you
guys, finally graduated?
Yeah, man.
Did you see my grades?
You're telling me.
I gotta make a speech in front
of the whole class tomorrow
and I don't even know
what I'm gonna say.
That's what happens when
you're a goodie two-shoes
and you wanna be
a valedictorian.
You're just jealous, Eli.
Jealous, I'm
walking with y'all.
Yeah, just barely.
Remember she used
to stay after class
in Mr Wallace's class?
To do the extra credit?
Extra credit, man, that
was a crush right there.
A crush.
I did not have
a crush on Mr Wallace.
Well now that
I think about it,
you can't talk,
remember Christie?
The weirded out
girl that likes you?
Man, quit with that.
Hey, what about that
one girl you liked?
The one with the eye
condition, what was her name?
Oh what was her name?
Left eye Susie?
- Yeah.
- Left eye Susie.
She was always looking
in two different directions.
No, that's not,
that's not funny,
she had a rare eye
condition, she got it fixed.
Yeah, cause she
was staring at you
and all the other
guys around you, huh.
You ain't special.
Hey Blue, what time is it?
Almost noon.
Wait, what?
I gotta go guys.
I'll see you guys later.
By Che.
Ayo, Cheo, what's up, man?
Hey, what's up young Chip.
How are you, Jeff?
Good, just getting ready
for the big day tomorrow.
Okay, what's new, what's new?
Not much, you know,
just school, music.
How's Christina and
the little homie?
Oh you know,
they're good, man.
Just taking up all my
money playing their sports.
Running me amuck, man.
Speaking of money, I
should charge you double
for this haircut, bro, with
that big ol' head of yours.
Wow, that is a
double priced head.
Holy tomato, my god, wow.
So any bites in the music
industry, bro, or what?
No, I haven't heard
anything back yet.
But I'm starting to think that
I need make my own
sound, you know?
Something different
that's just mine.
Yeah man, I don't blame you.
Yeah, I'm done with mix tapes.
I want a DJ sampling my music.
Abuelita always said,
work at something you love
and you'll never have to
work a day in your life.
Sounds like good advice.
Hey bro, can I help you bro?
You get those sideburns
taken off or what bro?
What is your
relationship with the Lord?
Ah man, we don't got
time for that, bro.
Mighty Lord Jesus
Christ says, unless one
is born again, he cannot
see the kingdom of God.
Marvel not, I said unto you,
you must be born again.
Hey bro, no one
wants that here.
This is a place of business,
man, get out of here.
Jesus guy.
The message of the cross
is foolishness to those
who are perishing,
but to us who are being saved,
it is the power of God.
Dude, there's
some bums out there
that need to hear that, bro.
Get out of here with that.
Hey Cheo, whatever you do,
don't be like that fool, man.
He's nuts.
Okay, Jeff, you've
really outdone yourself.
Yeah, man.
I'm gonna be walking
in the auditorium
lookin' firme homes.
Lookin' blessed, homes.
There you go, man.
Ah man, don't worry
about paying me bro.
That's your
graduation gift, bro.
Really?
Yeah, we're good
man, we're good.
- Man.
- You know what I'm saying?
Thanks for the love, yo.
All right man,
good luck out there.
Orale.
All right man, be cool.
My head ain't that big, is it?
Nah.
What up, bro?
Hey, what's up
Cheo, how's it going?
Not much, just got back
from the barber shop.
Big day tomorrow, huh?
Definitely.
You ready?
I don't know,
this beat is tight.
What you know about this song?
Well when Rocky came out,
it really stuck with me.
I was looking all over for it.
Kool and the Gang
released that song
a few years before Rocky,
on Light of the World, now
that's a must have album.
Yeah, I'll check it out.
Hey, is this any good?
Haven't had a chance
to listen to it yet
but let's slap that bad boy on.
Sweet.
Yeah.
He's got himself a nice hook.
This is where
they get it from.
Good call on this one.
So I hear around
the neighborhood
that you wanna get into music.
Yeah, got any advice?
Well, what you know
about Miles Davis?
Who?
Duke Ellington?
James Brown, godfather of soul?
You know.
No, bro.
Ah Cheo, come on kid.
You gotta know the past
before you can help create
the future.
How can you be the
best at what you do
if you're not familiar
with the greats?
You got me there,
you're right, bro.
Hold on, wait
here, I got something
for you, be right back.
Take these records
home for a few days
and learn about some real music.
Really?
Yeah, this here
is gonna take you
to another level.
These are better than
any college music course.
Sweet, thanks Roland,
they're in good
hands, I promise.
Okay, get out of here, I
gotta get some work done.
All right, Roland,
talk to you later.
Hey, Cheo, what's up?
Comin' from school?
Yeah, just got out of class.
You been skippin'?
Man, that counselor, Mr.
McCann, he be trippin' bro.
Straight up cheating
off of credits.
Talkin' about how I
gotta take summer school.
I didn't want to be
there to begin with,
now he wants me to
take summer school?
Chale homes.
Maybe if you weren't skipping,
you'd be graduating tomorrow.
School ain't for
everybody carnal,
we'll be here workin'
the Low Low's for now.
Let me see what records
you picked up, man.
Hey, who is John Col-tran?
I don't know, some jazz guy.
Roland gave me these
records to listen to.
Says I should study up on them.
That same junk that
Beethoven was playing?
Beethoven?
Sad girl, he likes that
Beethoven music that you do.
It's not classical
music, stupid.
That's jazz.
Same junk, right?
Hey, you ain't got no
oldies or soul up in there.
Nah, that's not the
style I'm kinda goin' for.
But hey, I'll see you Chava,
I gotta run, all right.
How come you don't like
to hang out with us anymore?
Big Happy, give Cheo
a sip of your 40.
I'm good.
Hey Sad Girl,
think Cheo might need
a little tenderness.
Bet you know who sang that song.
Odis Redding, bro.
And hey, I'm cool Julie,
I've got a big day tomorrow.
It's Sad Girl, Cheo.
No disrespect Julie.
All right then bro, next time,
hang out for a little bit.
Startin' to think you
don't like us, homes.
Come on bro, we
grew up together.
I'm trying to get to bed
early tonight, all right.
Hey, want one?
Nah, I'm cool.
You always do
straight leg stuff.
Enjoy your classical
music and Col-tran.
Col-tran, Chava, you need
to expand your horizons, man.
I hear you're gonna
graduate tomorrow, baby.
Hi Ms. Mary.
How's it going?
I am so proud of you.
I sure wish Mr. Reuben was
here to see you graduate.
I wish he was here as well,
I remember him telling
me all the stories.
Yeah, yeah.
You got some new records there?
Yeah.
Is that Duke Ellington
you're holding?
Roland said he
was a must have.
Well, make sure
you open your window
when you playing the Duke.
Reuben sure did
love Duke Ellington.
Will do Ms. Mary.
Yo Cheo?
I gotta go, okay,
have a good day.
My brother, my brother.
What up E?
Sup man.
Ay yo, what you got, you
always got the good with you.
Bro, check this out.
So I went down to the shop today
and Roland really hooked us up.
Gave me a couple records to
listen to some new sound,
he says if we really
wanna make it into
this music business,
we gotta know
where the music originated.
Whoa hold up, man, Roland did?
Man that guy never let's
me borrow anything.
Bro, chill out, there's
a first for everything.
Let's go to my crib.
Bro, you stink bro.
Man, dude, your room smells.
Let's see, yo, think fast E.
Man, quit with that,
you're always playin' around.
Yo, you hungry?
We got some nice
juicy tortillas.
Nah man, I'm
good, I already ate.
You know, actually
bring me some juice.
Yo, E.
- Sup man.
- Here you go bro.
- Thanks man.
- Yeah.
Yo this is fresh.
Yeah.
Man this is fresh.
Yes.
Yo bro, that's the breakdown.
Pretty cool.
Yeah that one.
Come on, I need
the headphones too.
Your old headphones?
Just get the headphones.
Man, I told you you should
get new ones already, man.
You wanna buy 'em?
Man, here, listen
to your music.
Ah, check it.
Yo, man we gon'
definitely have a good night
full of something like this.
Bro, I'm telling you,
this is gonna change
the direction of
our lives in music.
All right, let's
see, let's see.
Hey throw the next one on.
You got it?
Yep, play it.
Oh okay, this is a
game changer, boy.
Give me that.
Man what is this?
Yo, Roland gave me this track.
This is the game changer bro,
listen to the arrangements,
something different.
The arrangements, the
pacing and the timing,
something new.
Man, are we listening
to the same track?
We'll never get another
gig if we play this crap.
What are you talking about?
This is art, man,
clean out your ears.
Dude, how we gon'
use stuff like this?
You gotta think
outside the box.
We do pretty well DJing man.
Yeah but, it's
already played out,
I'm trying to do my
own thing, don't you?
What you mean your own thing?
Oh think you're a hot
stuff without me, huh?
Nah, man I'm just saying
I wanna do something new.
Something that gets my
creative juices flowing.
Well if we play
stuff like this,
your fan base is gonna
be people who are like,
people like Ms. Mary, man.
Oh you'll definitely be a
hit at the senior center.
Bro, you're taking
this a little too
personally, man.
I'm just trying
to mix things up.
Well maybe we should
do our own thing.
I do all the scratching
at the gigs anyway.
Hey man, back off.
Hey man.
Eli, whoa, why
you shoving me man,
why you getting so mad?
Yeah bro, you made it
pretty clear you wanna do
your own thing with
your own sound,
you know, I'ma help you out,
I'ma open up this
window, so you can play
this trash so Ms.
Mary can listen to it.
Bro stop being like this.
Nah man, I thought
you were different
but I guess you're on
Cloud 9 since graduation
is tomorrow and you've already
decided to leave me behind
when you're done with Jefferson.
Bro, you're not even,
what is going on?
Nah bro, you've
done lost your mind.
You don't have to
do this old music
to be better than you.
You had no talent
when we started
and this, this ain't gon'
help you out one bit, man.
One bit.
You know I'm out man.
E, yo!
You know what, that
wasn't my intention at all
but you want it to be that way
then fine, E, go ahead,
do your own thing man,
you're done with
this for some reason
so I'll just stand
back and do mine.
In all these years
I've known you and Eli,
never once have I
ever, ever heard
you guys exchange
words like that.
Oh it hurts my heart
to hear you two argue.
You know, Cheo, the
Lord says there's
a friend who sticks
closer than a brother.
And no matter life
throws at you,
you love that boy,
you love that boy
like you do your
own blood brothers.
Yes ma'am, I've gone through
most of my life with him,
I don't know what happened.
I don't think he
was a huge fan of
those records I brought home.
I have a bunch of old
records just sitting
in the garage if you
wanna take them with you.
Really?
Yeah.
Right through that door.
Right on the shelf by the wall.
Right on the top
shelf, sweetheart.
Whoa, you got a great
collection Ms. Mary.
You can take them
with you, sweetheart.
Reuben would be happy that
you're listening to his music.
I have my radio now so I
don't play records anymore.
That was Reuben's thing.
Are you sure?
This is a lot of records.
You could probably make some
good money off of these.
Yeah, but I'd rather
keep them in the family.
Thank you Ms. Mary,
I'll put them to good use.
Oh and one last thing,
you know sometimes in life,
people aren't gonna
like what you like.
And that's okay.
But you have to
embrace the differences
in people.
But don't compromise
your choices
while embracing theirs baby.
Now you go get some rest
for your graduation tomorrow
and have a blessed day.
Will do, Ms. Mary, thank you.
Hey Cheo, Cheo!
Hey can you come down?
Yeah, hold up.
Hey, what up Blue?
Hey.
You okay, Che?
Yeah, I'm all right.
I've had better days.
I also got some new records
from Roland and Ms. Mary.
Yeah, I heard
you down the street
with the East Side Boys
going over records.
I also heard that Sad
Girl's all over you.
You got it for her now,
cause I thought we
made a marriage pact.
Me?
I'm never getting married.
Plus who marries
they're best friend?
Well I'm holding up
my side of the deal.
Oh I finished that poem
that I told you about.
Will you help me go over it?
Wait, what poem?
The one I've been telling
you about for like two weeks.
Dude, what's wrong?
I'm sorry Blue, it's
just that me and Eli
had a huge fall out and I
don't understand what happened.
I brought some records home
and we just got into it.
Yeah, I heard.
Who told you about it?
No one, these
walls are paper thin,
I can hear everything.
Well what else did you hear?
Just that Sad
Girl's all over you
like a cheap suit,
look like you liked it.
She was just looking
at the records I got.
Mhm.
You know what Blue, I
don't know how you do it
but you always make
it seem like you
and I are in a relationship.
I don't have time for
no Sad Girl crush.
What records did you get?
Too many to list.
I actually just got done
listening to a few tracks
and I already feel inspired.
It's crazy.
You know you're really cute
when you talk about music.
Oh gosh.
I'm serious.
I know, that's the problem.
You know, Che, you and
Eli are better friends
than that.
Things will get better,
just give it time.
Yeah.
Can you come out tonight?
I wanna show you something.
What do you wanna show me?
It's a surprise.
Go get your jacket.
I think I can.
Shouldn't be out
too long though,
dinner's gonna be
ready soon, okay?
Okay.
Be back.
Okay so what's up with
these records you got.
Which ones did you get, you
never told me the names?
Well I did get a
couple from Mr. Roland
and from Ms. Mary.
Yeah, yeah, you
said that, but what?
What records, like what bands?
Right, right.
Duke Ellington.
Okay.
Miles Davis.
I recognize that one.
And then, what
was the last one?
I know, I know, what was it?
Where'd you find this?
I want a low rider one day.
How'd you find this?
Will and his friends
did it, cool huh?
This is tight.
Is it a '65 Lincoln Continental?
'64, look at the tail lights.
Okay Blue, I see you
know your low riders.
I'm telling you, we're
rolling in one soon.
All good things come
to those that wait.
And have money.
Remember, these cars
ain't cheap anymore.
Especially when
they're all hooked up.
You don't need hydraulic.
But you want 'em, I guess.
Yo, Cheo.
Sup, dude.
Happy to see you here.
Yo, back off.
You're in good hands here.
She just makes it a little
nicer here, that's all, boy.
All right man, we
were just leaving.
Hey Cheo, tell you brother
Vinicio said what's up.
You need to hang
out with us again.
Us East Side Boys, you
know what I'm saying?
All right man, let's go.
Love watching
you walk away girl.
What you guys do today?
Some new music comps.
Played some games.
Here you go boys.
Thank you mama.
Thank you mom.
Vini, put your phone down.
This again?
Everyone else eats
nice meals every night.
Plus there's never enough.
It's not enough?
Not enough, Vinicio?
I already work two jobs.
Why don't you just
get another job, ma?
Yo, Vinnie, shut up.
Why you always complaining?
If we were white,
we'd have more money
and we'd have better food.
If you don't like it then you
can get out of here Vinicio!
I've had enough.
You should be thankful
I didn't hit you.
You got anything else to say?
I blame dad for
ruining this family.
You never take responsibility
for your actions.
Enough Jorge Emilio.
It's true mama.
Why is it that every
time you guys get into it,
you always have to bring up dad.
Quit defending him Cheo,
he doesn't care about you.
What makes you think that?
He's always happy to see me.
It's a just front
Cheo, he doesn't love you
and he didn't love mom and
he doesn't love any of us.
That's not true.
Oh yeah, then why
hasn't he come visited us
in years and he only
lives two blocks away.
You see what you did,
this is why we
don't bring him up.
He's not a father figure,
he only cares about himself.
He's just nothing but
an abusive piece of...
Sit down!
Well I'm thankful
for what we have.
Thank you Cheo.
Mama, tus frijoles
son los mejores.
I can't get enough of 'em.
We just had it last night.
Cheo, mijo, there's
a package for you,
please get it out
of the doorway.
Who would bring you something?
I don't know.
What does the box say?
Where's it from?
Okinawa, Japan.
Okinawa, Japan?
That's Jetty.
Oh you know how expensive
that postage must've been?
Mom, you're right,
it is from Jetty.
It was him.
Cheo, I'm sending you
this keyboard from Japan.
By the time you
receive this package,
it'll be three
months later for me.
Make your own music,
you have it in you,
and this should
help you get there.
I love you guys and
miss you all so much.
Take care of mom, I'll
be home soon, Jetty.
P.S. happy graduation.
Que regalo, Cheo!
A keyboard, how did he know?
It's definitely
no boxing glove
but hey, it looks expensive.
Man, so what the
hell did Jetty send us?
Don't let your brothers
mess with this gift.
Your brother Jetty worked
very hard to be able
to send this to you.
I will mama.
I'm a free man, Roland.
Hey look at this guy, all
graduatin' and everything.
Good for you kid.
Could've kept these records
for more than one night.
Yeah, I know.
How'd you like 'em?
Man these were sick.
They changed everything.
I feel like I can
really use these
to make something dope.
And what
stood out most to you?
That's gotta be
a trick question.
Well, Miles gave the
Duke a run for his money
but the Duke dealt
with an entire Big Band
so I gotta give it to the Duke.
Miles?
The Duke?
We're on a first name
basis after one night?
Well, Ms. Mary gave me a bunch
of Mr. Reuben's old records.
Ah, Ms. Mary, of course.
Tell me more.
Well, Miles got this
straight up funk to it's sound,
but James Brown, took that
funk to a whole 'nother level.
I don't know, I guess
I just love it all.
Damn boy, look at you here
with your high school diploma
and your knowledge
for proper tunes.
Welp, I couldn't have
done it without you, Roland.
It ain't everyday
I find someone bit
with the same music bug as me.
Now, go do somethin'
big with it.
That's my plan.
Hey Roland.
Hey what's up, Eli.
Hey so what was up
with those records
you let Cheo borrow, you
never let me borrow anything.
How'd you like 'em?
Want me to be honest?
My dad would have liked them.
But it wasn't my cup of tea.
You gotta expand
your mind, boy.
So where do you think most
of the sounds come from,
from today?
I don't know, man, artists
make them up, I guess.
Oh no, no, no.
See, you should've
listened closely
to those records that
I sent home with Cheo,
you'd understand it
would've been in the vinyl.
Man, that music,
that music was wack.
There ain't nothin'
there for me.
Yeah, whatever kid.
Hey man?
No hard feelings or what.
Come on man, don't
worry about that.
You know we're still homies.
I got your back.
Trying to roll out?
Let's go.
Let's go, man.
All right Rol, see you later.
All right, peace out kid.
Hey man, let's go get Blue
and get something to eat.
What?
So what man, you
love her yet or what?
You're trippin' bro.
We're just close
friends, it's Blue.
Yeah man but
does she know that?
You know what,
just call her over.
I will.
But hey, now that
I think about it,
I've never met someone
as creative as her.
Especially when it comes
to writing and music.
Plus Blue is way
out of your league.
Bro I could recruit
her for my team anyway.
What you talkin' about you?
She wants a hero, not a zero.
So what are you
calling me a zero now?
Dude, relax, I'm just
messing with you, man.
But anyway, about
the graduation party,
you coming over or what?
Yeah man, if
I'm still invited.
You were never uninvited.
Plus we got a couple
hours to kill.
All right man, let's do this.
Let's grab a quick bite to eat,
we'll pick up Blue
and then I'll drop you
off back at the crib.
I've gotta go to the store
to hit up some things
for the party, you know.
Good job Cheo, I love you.
Sup man.
Sup E.
Finally did it.
We heading to the top.
Bro this is the beginning
of our lives in music.
Speaking of music,
check this keyboard
I got from Jetty, it's sick.
Dude?
Yo, can we just get this
party started or what?
All right everybody,
just wanted to thank
you all for making
it out to my graduation.
I see a couple of
graduates out there.
Just wanna let you guys know
that this is a new beginning,
not just for me
but for all of us.
Hey play some
of that Col-tran.
Come over here, Chava.
All right everybody,
settle down.
I got one quick announcement,
this, my boy Chava,
we grew up together
and today is his graduation too.
Get that big 'ol head over here.
It's a degree in
body shop repairs
and rehab of the tightest
low riders in Daly City,
I hereby declare you a graduate
of the school of hard knocks
with a degree in life studies,
give it up to my boy Chava.
Now let's really get
this party started.
Here, listen to this.
See this sound
is like so bomb,
it needs to be on
the radio today.
You know,
appreciate you're
my biggest fan.
Well, my only fan.
Your encouragement
really keeps me going.
Hey Cheo, come here.
I'll be right back.
Why are you listening
to this lame stuff?
What are you doing later?
Later, isn't it already late?
Yeah but there's
always a later.
So why they call you Sad Girl?
Should call you
Bad Girl instead.
But I ain't bad, I'm sad.
Who says you can't be both?
How'd you get so
sad all of a sudden?
You were always
happy growing up.
That was before
guys took advantage
of me and broke my heart.
Who broke your heart?
No matter.
Don't seem sad to me, Julie.
I told you to stop
with that Julie stuff.
Hey, let's go to the liquor
store and get some drinks.
I got Blue and the boys here,
just kick back and chill.
Okay, show me your room then.
Let me go check on everybody
just make sure
everyone is cool, okay?
Don't keep me
waiting too long.
Chale.
You okay?
Yeah I'm fine.
Yo E, can you take Blue home?
I live next door.
Eli, can you walk
her home or what?
Yeah, man, anything
for you, right.
Mr. Big shot.
All right E.
Bro, you good?
It's about time.
What are you waiting for?
Get over here.
Hey, I got you
those frozen burritos.
Che?
Hey, you don't
answer your phone?
I got you those frozen burritos.
Yeah, thanks Blue.
It smells flowery in here.
Are you hungry yet?
You've gotten three
full compositions out.
Yeah, sorry,
let me just finish
this last hook on here,
and then we'll go
get something to eat.
How's patron sound to you?
Sounds good.
Sweet.
This next performer,
I've known for many years,
I've seen and heard
his growth in music,
he has mastered the integration
of today's popular hip hop
sound with the past generation
in ways I've never heard before.
But first, he has
written and composed
a brand new song that
he's gonna preform
for you guys tonight.
With his lead
singer, Julie Torres
and I want you to give it up big
for my man, Cheo Colorado!
♪ Don't like to give
him much credit ♪
♪ Or pay him any mind
♪ But he's somewhere lovin'
♪ All the time
♪ Believe me it's so good
♪ That's got to be an evil
♪ Always sneakin', sneakin'
♪ So you better be careful
♪ Always out there, out there
♪ And they call him the devil
Michael, I'm glad
you were able to make
it out today.
This is the young guy I've
been talking to you about.
I think he has the sound
that you've been looking
for on your roster.
I like it.
How did you find the kid?
I have never heard
anything like that.
Ah, he's a boy from my hood.
He's always had an ear for music
and he's been teaching
himself arranging
and composing.
Introduce me to him
when he finishes his set.
I think I may have found
what I am looking for.
Give it up for him,
give it up for him.
All right, I hope you
guys enjoyed yourself
at Roland Record Summer Series,
my showcase of new and
up and coming artists.
It's been a wonderful
day of music,
wouldn't you agree?
Let's make some noise for
this lead singer, let's go.
♪ You, you think I'm
gonna fall so easily. ♪
♪ Na, na, na
Hi, may I have the
pleasure of introducing you
to the sound of
tomorrow, this is Cheo,
Cheo this is Michael Deville,
owner of Deville records.
Son, you had a very
impressive set here today.
Let me get right to the point.
I want to sign you up.
I think I can use you.
And also I'd like to record
your last composition
on vinyl.
Why thank you so
much Mr. Deville,
it's an honor to meet you.
I really think that this music
is gonna be the new
way for our generation.
Roland was quite
right about you.
You have got ear for
music and arranging.
Do you have any representation?
Do you have a manager, agent?
Um, I kind of just
represent myself.
Roland, he's like
my manager, I guess.
Here's my card.
Give me a call sometime soon,
so that we can
schedule something.
I want to do
everything official.
You bet, Mr. Deville,
thank you so much.
It was nice meeting you, Cheo.
Roland, take care.
All right, we'll be in touch.
Thank you so much,
Roland, thank you.
For everything
you've done for me.
I told you.
I didn't think everything
was gonna come so quick.
Kid, I told you, you
did all the hard work.
All I did was identify talent.
People love working
with true talent.
So, enjoy the rest of your day
and get in contact
with me in the morning.
All right?
Will do, thank
you so much, man.
So you wanna come out or?
Come out where?
We could go and
grab something to eat.
Yeah, when Cheo
comes out, we can go.
No, just me and you.
What, Eli?
Just me and you hang
out somewhere, you know?
You don't want Cheo to come.
Nah, just us, you know.
Yo E, can you pop the trunk?
Is it hella cool in there?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
Hey Eli, can you give Sad
Girl a ride up the block?
Yeah, man.
Sweet.
Hey Blue, can you move over
and make some room, please?
Yeah, whatever.
Did you ever get
this door fixed?
Man I'm broke, just get in.
Hey, thanks for the ride, bro.
I think today went really well.
Yeah man, I'm surprised
they actually liked
your old sound.
Even that old man
from the record label.
All right man,
let's get the trunk.
Hey I thought we were
gonna have a bite and
talk about the concert.
Uh let's take a rain
check on that Blue,
we'll talk about it tomorrow.
Sweet.
Hey Julie, why
don't you sleep with
the guys on your own block, huh,
Cheo's way out of your league.
Whatever scrappa,
I could get any guy
in this neighborhood
or any neighborhood.
You're just jealous.
Cheo's nothing like the
guy's in your neighborhood.
He's actually gonna
get out of here
and make something of himself.
You're just some
trashy distraction.
Why don't you let Cheo
decide what he wants?
'Cause last night it
seemed like he wanted me.
I don't see him inviting
you into his bed.
You don't even know him.
I know him enough to know
he looks good with
his shirt off.
That's more than you
know, isn't it, ninita?
I'll see you tomorrow,
Blue, let's go.
Hood rats these days.
Compositions, compositions.
This is starting
to feel like a job,
this isn't fun anymore,
not with all the pressure.
How are you doing,
mi sentimental?
Isn't obvious?
I feel horrible.
My music sucks, Michael
Deville called last week,
talking about he wants
to meet in five days
to hear some new tracks.
Don't say that,
you're just stuck.
What do they call
it in the music biz?
Writer's block.
But it feels like it's
much more than that.
Here, I'll help you relax.
Am I gonna be all right?
Baby, you know I
wouldn't be wasting
my time with you
unless I thought
you were gonna be
something, right?
So what's up, did you do it?
Yeah, he's all messed
up thanks to you.
And you.
Don't pretend you have nothing
to do with this, all right?
Is he in there writing, though?
He's wired, he could barely
string together a thought.
You got my money?
I'm a little short right now,
I went down to Roland's and I
spent more than I should have.
That's not gonna
work for me, homeboy.
How about I go tell Cheo where
I really get the
good stuff from?
Nah, come here,
come here, come here.
You know, here, just
take it, it's all I got.
Just take it.
That's more like it.
So what's up, you
free tomorrow night?
Yeah, have fun.
Hey what's up man?
How you doin'?
You doin' good or what?
Pretty good right about now.
Are you ready for
your meeting or what?
Come on, let's hear it.
Come on.
No, no, come on, come on.
Come here.
Hey Eli.
Hey, what's up?
Hey just sit down,
listen to some music.
Fix it.
What's going on?
Nothing, he's just about
to get ready for his meeting.
No, Cheo?
Cheo, what's going on?
Nah, it sounds good
man, keep it coming.
It doesn't.
It sounds good.
Are you hearing the
same thing I'm hearing?
This doesn't sound good.
Cheo, your hooks are
completely off beat,
your arrangements don't
even mix together.
Where are your
full compensations?
Just keep on playing man.
You trippin', you
always be trippin'!
I'm trippin'?
Dude, he doesn't
even like your music,
do you hear him?
It sounds good,
he's getting ready
for this meeting.
You got something to say, what?
I just saw you on the
street kissing Sad Girl
and now you're in here,
what are you up to?
You're over here accusing
that he's on drugs,
maybe you're the one on drugs.
Saying that I'm with Sad Girl,
I'm never with Sad
Girl, all right.
I just saw you!
That wasn't me.
Oh really, that's weird
because that person was
wearing your same outfit.
You're tripping, like I said.
Cheo, what is going on?
Okay, are you okay?
I think you need to leave.
What did you do to him?
Just go, you should
just go already, man.
No!
Just go.
You go.
Hey Cheo, just keep
playing that stuff.
Keep doing it man.
Cheo, you just need to
rest and stop playing.
Just get out.
Why should I?
Get out!
You obviously don't
want to protect him
and I actually care
about him, Eli.
Did you not listen
to what he just said?
I don't care
what he just said,
he's obviously on something.
He said get out!
Just get out already!
Leave!
Nah man, just sit down, dude.
You're doing good man,
you're doing good.
Hey man, you need
some of this or what?
Hey, you good?
Hello, Cheo, how
are you doing today?
Doing quite well, Mr. Deville,
thank you for having me.
So I wanted to let you know,
I received your
file this morning.
I listened to it and
let me just cut to the chase,
I'm not impressed.
I didn't send you
anything by mail.
I have my own stuff here, look.
Well I received something,
it had your name on it.
But regardless, I'm not sure if
this is the right
timing of things,
if you understand what I mean.
No, I don't understand.
Well, Cheo, I might
have jumped the gun
a little bit too soon with you.
To be honest, I
don't even remember
what I listened to last month's
Back at the Summer Series.
Please, Mr. Deville, I've
been working really hard
and I'm ready to take
you up on my offer.
I'm not sure what you
received this morning
in the mail but I
promise I have something
you'll be interested in.
Please, if you would,
just listen to this track
and see if you
like what you hear.
Any minute now.
I'm sorry, Cheo.
The deal has been revoked.
We are moving forward
with a new artist.
Welcome, Eli.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Please have a seat.
We listened to your
tape and it's exactly
what the boss wanted to hear
and the direction this
label wants to be in.
So Mr. Eli Cole, we're hopeful
and thought if you could
start off by selling
a million units,
you'd be on track
to lock in a two album deal.
A million units
includes domestic
and foreign sales.
Just so we're clear.
Yeah, we're clear but
what do I receive up front?
It's not as black and white
as it normally would be.
Your sound has potential.
You had a great response
from our focus group
and our firm would like to
build around your sound.
So we're cutting you a
check for 250,000 dollars
with the deal that you product
one album to start with.
All studio expenses
and engineering time
will be covered, of course.
And any remaining profits
from potential units sold
will be added to that 250k.
But just think of this as sort
of an upfront signing bonus,
if you will.
Mr. Cole, Michael
loved your sound.
And he wants to move
forward with you.
We here at Deville Records know
that you have what it
takes to be the best.
Which is why,
we'd like you to
sign a contract.
What do you say Eli?
Do we have a deal?
An opportunity like
this only comes around
once in a lifetime.
I'm in.
Awesome, Eli.
Welcome to the team.
Thank you.
Your family has been
looking for you for months,
I had no way of knowing
what happened to you.
Are you listening to me?
I once knew a girl name Blue
but you seem nice.
Let me take you out of here
and get you clean.
I can take care of you.
You have anything on you,
I could use a bump
right about now.
No, just let me
take you home now.
I don't have a home.
I lost it.
I'm not Cheo.
I can't watch
you die like this.
I love you.
Really?
Yeah.
Crystal Blue.
Can I tell you something?
Yes, anything.
Go on and get
yourself a real man.
Forget about me, you
don't deserve this.
No.
I can't watch you die
like this, I love you.
Cheo, the Lord
says there's a friend
who sticks closer
than a brother.
Foolishness to those
who are perishing,
but to us who are being saved,
it is the power of God.
Lord, if you're real, help me.
Son, son, do you need help?
We don't want anything from you,
we just wanna help.
Men, please help this young man.
Yes, we can.
Take him to the intake room
and get some clean
clothes and dinner.
Yes, let's get you
cleaned up, brother.
Warm food in your belly, get
you a clean bed to sleep in.
All right.
There's some
food here for you.
Lord we thank
you for this meal,
and for the nourishment
of our body.
And Father, we pray Lord,
for those Lord, that
are still in wilderness.
And are lost, that are homeless
and most of all, Father,
that are hungry.
Lord, we know you're
a merciful God,
and we thank you Lord,
in the name of Jesus, amen.
Amen.
Hey bro, I'm
glad you feel safe.
I heard them bringing
you in last night.
So, do you guys do
this every time you eat?
Well yeah, you know,
a little prayer, you know,
it keep us thankful.
By the way, where you from?
I used to live in Daly
City, up on the hill,
near the East Side.
East Side?
You know what,
you look familiar.
Do you have a
brother named Jetty?
Yeah, that's my older brother.
- Oh!
- He's out of the country.
He's actually in
the marine corp.
You know what, I was
there when he enlisted.
Really?
Yeah man, you know what?
He had way more guts than me.
So where am I?
What is this place?
You're at the New Hope Home
and Pastor Donna brought
you in last night.
It's by Christ that she
found you when she did.
Where is this
Jesus, can I meet him?
We're about to
have Bible study.
Today can be the first day
of the rest of your life.
Is Jesus gonna be there?
And what's a Bible study?
Well, he's already there.
And he's waiting for you.
And he's directly
down that hall.
Hello, Cheo, so glad
you could join us today.
Thank you Pastor
Jesus for allowing
me to stay here last night.
You called Pastor Donna Jesus.
I'm Pastor Donna.
Today we'll be
learning about Jesus
and how much he loves us.
No one would love
a failure like me.
People look at the outside
but Jesus looks at your heart.
Can I meet him?
You already have.
He brought you here.
Men, I trust you've all
met our new brother, Cheo.
Cheo will be staying
here for awhile.
- Great to meet you all.
- How you doin?
Welcome.
Hey there brother.
Great to meet you all.
This is a safe place, Cheo.
We've all made decisions
we regret, including me.
But our future doesn't
have to look like our past.
I know it's a lot to take in
but essentially we
have two choices.
We can keep doing things
the way we always have
or we can begin
to fill our hearts
with the immeasurable
love of Jesus.
Fill my heart?
Yes, Cheo, the
choice is yours.
Hi, Pastor Donna,
do you have a moment?
Sure, c'mon.
So I've been doing a lot
of thinking this past year.
I've come to realize
that I've taken
a lot of things in
life for granted.
I'm praying over a situation
and I was hoping you
could impart some wisdom,
on something important.
Of course, Cheo,
what's on your mind?
It's Blue.
I've taken her love for
granted since we were kids.
And she's always
been there for me.
I made right with the Lord
and I now I wanna
make right with her
and ask her to marry me.
Cheo I'm so happy for you.
I've seen how Blue looks at you.
You'll be the missing
puzzle piece to her heart.
You really think so?
Is there something
in particular I can do?
Yes, I was hoping
you could help me find
the perfect engagement
ring for her.
I would love to help you.
I'll tell you what, how about
we go first thing tomorrow
morning, will that work for you?
That's perfect.
Wait, are you sure
that's not too early?
It's not every day
I get to help someone
from our group get married.
Thank you so
much, Pastor Donna.
It means so much to me.
I must be a real slow learner,
here she was right
before my eyes,
this entire time.
Thank you for asking me, Cheo.
We will have a ball picking
out the perfect ring for her.
So yesterday
after Bible study,
I was talking to Pastor Donna.
Okay, what about?
And,
forget it.
Why'd you bring it up if
you weren't gonna tell me?
What'd you talk to her about?
Hey!
You hear that?
What did you talk
to Pastor Donna about?
Not right now,
Blue, come on, look.
You brought it up.
♪ They lean on hope
♪ Lean on, lean on
♪ Lean, lean on
♪ Lean on your own
♪ All your ways
♪ That knowledge
Hold on guys, say
hello to my manito, Che.
Hi Blue, how you doing?
Blessing to see you.
Always good to see you.
All right brother,
how you doing?
Always good.
Vic, how you doing?
Che, we're a little stuck
here, maybe you could help us.
Trying to come up with
a song, we're stuck.
Okay man, I feel
something coming.
May I make a suggestion?
Absolutely, please.
Tony, give me a mambo
beat on the bells.
Mike, on the congas.
Victor, let me hear
rock beat on the drums.
I like that.
Keep doing what you're doing.
Let's see, on my
cue guys, ready.
One, two, three.
♪ Lean on, lean
♪ All your ways,
hang on to him ♪
♪ Hills are red
♪ Your path
♪ Just keep your eyes on him
♪ And I will do my best,
do my best for you ♪
♪ Put all my trust in you
♪ I will do my best,
do my best for you ♪
♪ Put all my trust in you
♪ I will do my best,
do my best for you ♪
♪ Put all my trust in you
♪ I will do my best,
do my best for you ♪
♪ Oh put all my trust in you
♪ I will do my best,
do my best for you ♪
Unless we tag team.
Just kidding.
Hey Blue.
Hey Blue, it's me, Robbie.
We got Archie right here,
you don't remember us?
I guess you just startled me.
Didn't mean to
frighten you, beautiful.
I'm just running
late, so I gotta go.
No, ma, why you in
such a rush, stay.
Cheo's waiting.
Are you scared
of us or something?
I think she's scared
of us, Archie.
I think so too Robbie.
Girl, you look so good.
What perfume are you wearing?
You smell good, girl.
Hey, hey, not too fast, wait!
Okay Blue, okay, you wanna play?
Come here!
No, no, no, no, please.
Watch it.
Archie, Archie, let's
go, let's go, come on!
Come on, Archie!
From looks of it, it was
about 30, 40 minutes ago.
Okay.
No.
Sir, sir, can you
come this way please?
I heard the screaming
and I looked out
through my window and
I saw these two men
and they were brutalizing
this young woman.
Okay, did you get a good
look at the gentlemen?
Yeah, I see those punks
around here all the time.
A couple of losers,
total losers.
Wait, you said all the time?
Yeah.
You wouldn't happen to
know their names, would you?
Oh, um,
one's name is Ronnie and
the other one's name is,
let's see, Archie.
His name is Archie.
Can you remember
anything else?
No, it all happened
way too fast.
Okay, that's fine.
All right so, we're
gonna catch those guys.
If you remember else,
please give us a call.
- Right.
Thank you sir.
You can go ahead,
I'll show you around.
Thank you.
Ma'am, last night a young
girl was found murdered.
Oh Lord.
We believe she
attended your church.
We found this brochure on her.
Also the library card
that was found on her body
stated her name was Blue Tahara.
Oh no.
Did you know her?
Yes, I know her.
She was about to be married
to Cheo, one of our ministers.
I'm sorry, does she have
any family in the area?
I know she has family
here but I don't know.
Cheo will know.
I'm just afraid this is
going to devastate him.
He'll relapse.
Would it be okay if I tell
Cheo what happened to Blue
and call you back later with
the contact information?
Yes, of course.
Here's my card, if
you think of anything,
please, give me a call.
Thank you.
Cheo?
Cheo, I need to
tell you something.
I don't know how to tell you.
The police were just here.
Blue's dead.
They found her in the park.
We're gonna get through this.
I know, I.
Why did this happen?
Hey, what's up Cheo?
You gonna come in and
let me buy you a drink?
Chava's up in here.
I heard about what those
punks did to your old lady.
They'll get theirs when
they get into the pen.
The pen'll take care
of that for you.
We live in a fallen world bro.
Punks about to live the rest
of their lives behind bars.
That's not living, Guillermo.
That's deep Cheo.
But a couple shanks to
the heart and lungs,
would feel good too, you
know what I'm saying.
It was good seeing you bro.
All right, bro.
Chava, can I talk
to you for a moment?
Yeah, I heard about Blue.
Sorry, man.
How are you holding up?
This has got to be one
of the hardest things.
And I thought fighting
addiction was tough.
Don't worry about it, Carnal.
We got your back with
whatever you might need.
There is one thing
you can help me with.
Tomorrow's Blue's funeral.
She loved low-lows.
I was hoping you could
get the horse together.
For you and for Blue,
let me know what time,
we'll be there, okay?
Thank you, bro.
Keep that head up.
This place hasn't
changed one bit.
Cheo, is that you?
Mama, Vinnie, look who I found!
Cheo, mijo, you're back!
I missed you so much,
welcome back home.
Man, I haven't seen
you since the funeral.
Why you so skinny?
Is that a cross
around your neck.
It's for the best,
but I missed you
guys all so much.
So did you bring us anything?
Yeah, me!
You ain't nothin' special.
Never said I was.
You asked if I
brought something and,
bada-bing, here I am.
So mom, are you still
working at the airport?
18 years now, mijo.
Getting ready to
retire, I wanna travel.
Why didn't you stop by?
All that matters
is that you're happy
and you're back home with us.
Thanks mom, and I was actually
at the New Hope Rescue Mission.
Why?
What was at the New
Hope Rescue Mission
that kept you from
coming back home?
Well, you see,
all the bad choices
took me to a dark place
and I wasn't happy.
I was living only for myself
and felt like I
was wasting away.
But I was finally able
to get what I needed.
I was able to find my
peace and joy in life.
He got sucked into
the dad syndrome
instead of focusing on himself
and getting into the
alcohol and women.
Sorry ma.
I will say that,
they took me in,
they fed me, they taught
me how to cook and clean,
and they got me back on track.
Cheo, I'm happy you're home.
I'm glad you found something
that works for you.
Bro, the white man
brain washed you.
They love volunteers.
Or you can call it
some slave labor.
You're just a sucka.
Vinnie, shut up.
Hey George, remember
when they used
to say that Jesus
died for our sins?
Yeah, I remember that.
Well I never understood
what that meant until now.
So are you clean now, Cheo?
Five years, one month,
17 days, to be exact.
I'm so proud of you, Cheo.
Thank you.
By the way, any of you
guys seen Eli lately?
I haven't seen him for years.
I heard that he moved.
Maybe you can go down
and talk to Teresa
and she might tell
you where he's at.
Yeah.
Meanwhile, mama's gonna fix
my chacito his favorite dinner
so we can celebrate.
Vamos!
Hello Ms. Cole?
It's Cheo.
Cheo Colorado.
Cheo Colorado, wow.
I haven't heard that name in
such a long time, come in.
How have you been doing?
Good.
Goodness, come on in.
Don't mind the mess around here.
Don't worry
about it, Ms. Cole.
Come on in, let me get you
something in the kitchen.
So how have you been?
Oh I'm fine honey, I'm just,
I'm just enjoying my
glass of chardonnay,
waiting for Eli
to come visit me.
I'm sorry, is this a bad time?
No, silly, it's fine.
You know, I'm just
waiting on Eli,
he's gonna bring
me by some money.
Have you talked to him?
To be honest, I just
released myself from
a men's home, cleaned myself up.
I had a rough patch and needed
some spiritual guidance.
Well you look good.
You know, it's nice to see
a familiar face around here.
I can remember when you and Eli
were playing music
in your living room
and you kept all of
Peoria street up.
Yeah, those were
the good times.
You know, life can
be so severe, you know,
how things can change over time
and you know, it
can be really hard.
You're telling me.
It's been awhile
and I never expected
I would be out on
my own for so long.
But I guess that's what the
Lord had in store for me.
When Eli got big, it got
really hectic around here.
Between the money, fans, fame,
you know, it got really crazy
but we really needed the money.
Eli got big?
You didn't hear?
He got a record deal.
And they gave him
a big signing bonus
about five years ago.
Really?
I did not know that.
How's it going, man?
It's good to see you, brother.
How you been?
I'm doing much better lately.
After everything with
Blue, I just needed
some space to find
myself and whatnot.
I wasn't expecting
you to be here, man.
It's definitely a surprise,
I can tell you that much.
And Blue, man I miss her.
Yeah, I miss her too.
But I was in the
neighborhood visiting my mom
and I kinda wanted to
visit you and your mom.
You know, catch up.
I'm definitely glad
you're doing great, man.
Hey, you look good.
Hey mom, how you doing?
Hey, how you doing?
I'm just fixing some
drinks for everyone,
Cheo, would you like something?
I'm okay, Ms. Cole, thank you.
Hey mom, before I
forget, here's a check.
Thank you so much.
So, I heard you made it big.
Yeah, something like that man.
You know, I just get focused
and somehow somewhat.
So I got noticed along
the way, that's all.
That's good,
I'm happy for you.
Thanks man.
Hey so how long has it been?
About five years.
Has it been that long?
My god.
What's been going
on with you lately?
Well I'm about to get in the
studio with Deville Records
you know, I'm about
to do my 3rd album.
2nd one wasn't too great,
you know, I gotta
keep going at it
to keep my mom and
I going, you know?
Hey I actually just got
back the UK from a tour.
Nice, me and mom were
actually just talking
about how time flies.
Isn't it crazy?
Right man, one day we're
chilling in your room,
cranking up that music
mix, you know it.
Well everything happens
for a reason, Eli.
Just keep in mine, the
Lord is truly what matters
in life, Blue's here one day
and the next, she's with God.
So what happened
between us, man?
We used to be so tight.
The Lord just had a
different path for us, I guess.
You keep saying the Lord,
as in like, Jesus Christ?
Yeah man.
So what's up, is that
what you've been learning about
these five years
cause you've got
some type of peace
about you now.
I found Christ, I'm a new man.
Well I'm all messed up man,
I've gotta get my act together,
so much is going on right now.
Anything you wanna talk about?
Oh just label pressure,
and this whole money
thing, I guess.
Your mom said you
had a signing bonus.
Something like that, man.
But you know what, there's
so many damn expenses.
And you know, I'm starting
to have my mom slip away
with this drinking thing.
You know what,
think about getting
a call from the cops at 2am
telling you that
your mom is drunk
and out of control at
the Connection Bar.
You know, I'm dealing with
those type of distractions.
That's rough.
Yeah man.
I'll keep you in prayer.
But you do solo
work or group stuff?
I'm doing solo with
some temp musicians
in the studio, if it's not
one thing, it's the other.
Why don't we pray?
You know that's
not my thing man,
you should know that.
Just remember,
it's all because
of Jesus that you're
where you're at.
The gratitude is there bro,
but you know what, I'm
just so damn tired man,
I'm tired.
I wanna just go back to
18 or something, yeah.
Hey Eli, let's play
Cheo one of your singles.
You know, he could
use a good tune
after being out of
society for years.
Mom, mom, not right now.
We're going to grab
something to eat, all right?
I don't mind, let's
hear your stuff.
Don't be stingy Eli,
this is close to my heart now.
Now this tune, this is the one
that Deville Records was
really interested in.
And it rocketed
my son to stardom
and made him famous
and now we're rich.
Sounds familiar.
You got signed by
Deville Records?
Yeah man.
Sounds a little familiar,
that's for sure.
Turn it up, that's the keyboard.
Nah man, we don't
gotta listen to this man,
it's outdated and it's
old if you ask me.
So come on, let's get
those burgers, yeah?
I'm not really that hungry.
I just realized the
time, I gotta get going.
I promised my mom
I'd say bye to her
before she goes to work.
Are you sure, come on,
it'll be my treat, come on.
Yeah man, I didn't
mean to intrude.
Do you mind saying bye
to your mom for me?
Nah man, just stay,
chill with my mom,
you can do the whole
prayer stuff too
if you want to.
It was educational
to say the least.
But good luck with the
career, take care my brother.
Ay yo, Cheo.
Take care of yourself, man.
Mr. Cole, it's so
wonderful to see you,
how have you been?
Good, and yourself?
Oh very good, you
here to see Mr. West?
Yeah, can you call him up?
Yes I will.
You're already in
the conference room?
All right, I'll bring
him right in, thank you.
Eli, good to see
you, come on in.
Did it really take
us 12 voice messages
to get you down here?
Have a seat.
I'm glad you got back
to me when you did.
We, the label, have a few
things we wanna clear up
and discuss with you.
So again, thanks for coming in.
Wait, wait, hold
up, hold up, hold up,
what things?
Well, you got my
messages, right?
About the legal
issues and the hold up
on some of the tracks
on the new album?
So now they're
saying I stole it?
No, no, there's
just some samples
that our people
felt might be better
if we had certain channels
getting the rights to.
Unfortunately these channels
take a little more time
than usual.
Look Eli, you're becoming
a major artist here.
We just wanna make sure
that you're covered
and your work is
totally untouchable.
All right so what's
up, is that it?
No Eli, these legal checks
are just a minor
bump on our end.
To be honest, we'd like
you to submit more work
so that our people
can arrange it
and make a final product.
So you want more?
Yeah, we're
going to need more.
A lot more Eli.
That's what we do here.
We pay you, you produce for us.
It's not hard, is it?
At least it should not be.
It'd be best if
you just give us
as much finished
product as possible
so that you and the
record can get moving
on the next album which is due
by the end of the quarter.
You guys are serious?
The next quarter, no
freakin' way, man.
What's the problem?
The problem is I'm gonna
give you guys everything
so you guys can have some
two bit editor hack my music.
What about we terminate
your contract right here,
right now and stop your
payroll immediately?
How does that sound?
The time, the money
invested in you,
everything is going to waste.
Oh really?
Yes, there is no
way you are going
to meet this tight of deadline.
Especially since
we are seeing both
the quantity and quality
of your work already.
You don't work with us,
we do not work with you.
Simple as that.
No more dodging our calls.
Or I will request,
as per your contract,
this is a business, little man,
if you do not wish
to pick up the phone,
someone else will...
What the hell man?
The sweat and tears
that I put into this?
So not only are you guys
saying that my stuff is late,
you're saying that
my stuff is not good,
this is my art, man.
And I've made you guys
some damn good dough
if I say so myself.
You know what?
My new stuff, yeah my new
stuff's gonna be dope.
It's gonna be?
It has been watered down.
Your work really
speaks for itself.
I am not going to
allow this contract
to be taken advantage of.
I'm not going to
wait any longer.
Deal with nor should I put
any of your shortcomings.
You give me one good reason,
just one, why I
should not terminate
the contract right now.
Eli, we just wanna get
to the bottom of this.
Please sit, please.
We also have here, a
copy of your contract.
Just in case you need to review
your responsibilities.
Good doing business with you.
I knew you would see it my way.
I'm sorry for everything,
can you forgive me?
What if I need you?
Are you using me?
You don't love me,
you don't love me.
Anybody, anybody?
Everything to you is about Cheo,
what about me, huh?
What about me?
You helped Cheo, can you
help me back, please,
Jesus, give me a
rope, forgive me,
I'm sorry, I need
you to help me.
Eli!
He's gone, he's gone!
Eli, Eli stay with me, help!
Father God, you say
when we're at our weakest,
you're at your strongest.
Lord you also say that
you will never leave us
nor forsake us.
Please Lord, please.
I pray that you put a
hedge of angels protecting
and surrounding Eli.
And that the enemy be bound
and cast it back to
where it belongs.
In Jesus's holy and
powerful name, I pray, amen.
Welcome back, Eli.
How are you feeling?
Can you talk?
You know, you almost drowned?
Can you hear me?
Can I listen to your
heart and lungs?
Can you take some
deep breaths for me?
Can you tell me what
happened to you?
No.
Think I fell down.
Well you must have an
angel watching over you
because you survived.
I can see that
you're feeling well.
I'm gonna check on
you tomorrow and try
to get you home soon, okay.
In the meanwhile, you will get
a visit from one of our
mental health physicians.
All right, feel better.
Hey Cheo.
Eli, I'm glad you're
alive and awake.
He heard our prayer.
How you feeling?
I'm feeling good, man.
I got the music you left me.
I'm sorry man, I didn't
mean to burn you like that.
Don't worry about it.
Life always tries to
take us out sometimes.
The music's yours, bro.
Still got that
glow about you, man.
And that peace.
I want that man, I want that.
It's because I found the Lord
at my lowest point of life.
He had a different
path in life for me
than what I had.
But he helped me get
through the loss of Blue.
So is this Jesus
thing for real?
It's as real as it comes.
And look, he saved you,
and here we are.
Hey, get some rest brother.
Hey Cheo.
Man, I know I
already told you this
but I'm sorry man, I'm sorry
for stealing your music.
I knew we were gonna
talk about this one day.
But I didn't know I
was gonna ask you,
can you forgive me, man?
Eli, you mean much more to me
than any music or fame.
God has given me peace and joy.
And he's forgiven me
for all my shortcomings.
How can I not forgive you?
I just wish I was a
better friend to you, man.
How about we leave
the past in the past
and we start thinking
about our future?
I think it's time we
start making music.
And I'm talking your music.
You up for it?
What did you have in mind?
That was clean, bro.
So I think when the
chorus comes around
the second time, that's when
we can have the mini bass solo.
Exactly right,
but after the solo,
let's go straight
back into the slow jam
and into the outro because when
we pull those notes
out, it'll sound dope.
A little more keyboard
work here and there
and it'll be so strong,
you can feel the
power from the song.
Ain't gon' lie man, I have
a good feeling about this one.
Amen.
Hey Jim, pick up the bass.
Maybe a little midi here.
Nice.
No break.
Eli and Cheo, back at it again
with East Side Daly City.
Top of the hill.
When it all comes down to it,
the one thing from
my journey I can say
that stood out, was this.
Life happens in the
blink of an eye.
You asked me what I've learned,
so I'll tell you.
I learned the source
of forgiveness.
The source of love and
the source of peace.
In the end, it wasn't
about my passion for music.
Or my issues with Eli.
No, it was something a
little deeper inside.
Something you can't see.
I know now more than I did then.
You have to be able
to fill your heart
with God's love
because love can't be measured.
Love is the most important
and powerful word there is.
Jesus is love, God is love.
And the Holy Spirit is love.
And always remember who
the source of love is.
♪ I'm a mission
♪ I've got a mission
♪ I'm on a mission
♪ I'm ready to go
♪ I've got a mission
♪ I'm on a mission
♪ Don't ever leave me alone
♪ I knew my life
was full of sin ♪
♪ God was talkin' but
I wasn't listenin' ♪
♪ Then the flame
sparked my heart ♪
♪ Ignited the love in me
♪ You touched my
heart and my soul ♪
♪ Don't ever leave me alone
♪ Don't ever, don't
ever leave me alone ♪