(MultiCom Jingle)
(bright instrumental music)
- [Man] Kitty, come on, let's get ready!
Kitty?
- Fellas?
That's your daddy callin'.
They're done, let's go.
Hot, hot.
Oh, damn-nation!
Fellas, where are ya'?
- Come on, come on.
- Come in, it'll be fun.
The whole family's gonna go.
You'll be all alone if ya' stay here.
- Right ma', bingo.
Ma'...
Sittin' around with those fine families
of Jackson ain't my idea of excitement.
You know, maybe I'll just
head over to the drugstore,
and see who's hangin' around.
- Now, I know we just got here and all,
but this time is different,
we're here to stay.
So, you can take your time
to get to know people, and...
Oh, go slow, Phyllis, not so fast.
- What do you mean by that, Ma'?
- Lewis, here's your shirt!
You know, he got that application
for agriculture college,
ain't that somethin'?
Now, are you coming or not?
- Yeah, let Lewis go on and
dig up dirt if he wants to.
I'm gonna be in the sky somewhere, Momma.
Look, see, just like that.
That's gonna be me one day.
I'm gonna be a pilot.
- Are you comin' with the family or not?
Lewis and everybody's all set to go.
- [Phyllis] Lewis, Lewis, Lewis.
I don't see no crown or diadem
that made him king around here.
- Don't break my pie.
Oh, don't worry, Lyle, we'll get callouses
on those pretty city
hands of yours in no time.
- [Lyle] Great.
- [Betty] Don't say that, Mama,
that's what he's afraid of.
- Would you get my hat?
Now, what are you doin', Boo?
- Maybe my Mardi Gras beads
will grow into a crop, huh Mom?
- Well, maybe they will.
Come on, you'll get your hands all dirty.
Button up that dress.
(serene instrumental music)
- Look at that pretty house.
Who lives there?
- Why, that's Mr. Driggs house.
They're tellin' me the
Driggs family just about
owns the whole town in Jackson.
- Someday we're gonna
have a place like that,
and people will come visit us.
And we'll say, "Come back anytime
"because we'll be right here."
Isn't that right, George?
Oh, yes...
A place like that.
(mid-tempo country folk music)
(laughing)
(clapping)
- [Man] Sheriff Ashford's
got somethin' important
to talk to y'all about.
(clapping)
- Folks, got a lot to be proud of here
in the town of Jackson,
where we truly cherish the
values and traditions...
That make American the
great country it is.
John Jackson founded this
town many years ago...
With a few dollars and a dream.
The dream of buidlin' a good, safe place
to raise your kids up.
Mr. Radley here is gonna take that dream
into the very near future.
- That's right!
- When he picks a spot,
he's gonna start buildin'
what they're callin' suburbs.
Hopefully, right before Christmas,
and that's gonna be quite
a Christmas present for you
in our fine town of Jackson, thank you.
(clapping)
- Outstanding, outstanding!
Sheriff, that was terrific!
- Excuse me, anybody
taken this spot over here?
(mid-tempo country music)
(laughing)
Come on, now, kids, play nice!
That girl is stubborn as
hell and bold as brass.
- [George] She takes after her mom.
- It's about time she
started lookin' around
for a good husband to take care of.
I dont know what she's thinking.
She said some crazy thing
today about flyin' an airplane.
- We gonna have us a home now.
Nobody runnin' us off.
- Can't got callin' us
fruit tramps anymore.
- That's right.
(slow country music)
May I have this dance?
- Well, I'd be honored, sir.
(slow country music)
- Sorry, folks...
Hate to inform you, but this
here's private property.
You're gonna have to be movin' on.
Goes for you too, Sam.
You know better than that.
- Excuse me, Sheriff, I don't
understand what you mean.
- No mixin' with the colors ma'am,
that's what I mean.
Now, my job is to make sure
everyone knows their place,
and now it's time for
you to move on, ma'am.
- Sheriff, Mr. Driggs
owns the land we live on,
we rent it from 'em, we
got a two year lease.
Now, he has a paper that says that.
Well, tell me, Sheriff, does
anybody have a piece of paper
that says they own us?
- Little boy, you wanna last around here,
you better understand
who you're talkin' to.
- Oh, I understand who I'm talkin' to.
- Please, I don't want no trouble.
I don't want no trouble.
Nice meetin' you, Sheriff.
Why don't you come out and
have supper with us sometime?
- Thank you, thank you,
but I don't think so.
Come on, Billy.
- [George] Man makes the law down here.
- Good for you, Lewis.
- [Phyllis] That man
thinks he pees champagne.
- [Lewis] Yeah, and he
sweats cream and sugar.
- Now, we're just outsiders is all.
People ain't got a chance
to get to know us yet.
(tranquil instrumental music)
- [Woman] No, honey, I told
you I'm not gettin' those.
(soft instrumental music)
- [Girl] How about this one, Momma?
- [George] Afternoon, Mr. Cooper.
- George.
- Ah, can you advance us $5
worth of cornmeal, please, sir?
- Alright.
Your total owed is $63.
- Yes, sir.
- And that don't count
the seed and fertilizer
that we had in advance.
- I know, I know.
- Y'all gettin' ready to
start harvestin' out there?
- That's right, that's right,
and in a few weeks we'll
clear that bill up,
and we sure appreciate your help.
- [Kathryn] Afternoon, Sheriff.
- Good afternoon, Sheriff.
Good afternoon.
Well, how you doin', Sheriff, good?
We doin' just fine, thank you.
We gonna be harvestin' soon,
then my momma says we're
gonna get ourselves a house...
- Phyllis, let's go, come on.
- Trash.
- You can say what you want to,
and do what you want to, but I can't!
- It isn't that, it's just us Messengers
don't tell people our business, come on.
Let's go.
(engine stuttering)
- I'll sure be happy when we see
the last of that Yankee trash.
- Well, as long as there is
land around here for rent,
you ain't gonna see the last of them.
But I here Radley's got his
eye on the land they rent.
- Well, you heard right,
I'm just waitin' now.
Good oranges.
(crying)
- [Man] Come on y'all, get out of there.
- Monsters, Ma'.
Monsters, Ma'!
- Monsters, where at?
No, no, I don't see no monsters,
except for the monsters right here
are the monsters!
(giggling)
♪ Ladies fishing for a dream ♪
♪ Fishing in a pond ♪
♪ Her line is silver moon and is ♪
♪ Her beads of silver star ♪
♪ Sail baby sail ♪
♪ Out upon that sea ♪
♪ Only don't forget ♪
(humming)
(insects chirping)
Goodnight, ladies.
(slow trumpet music)
- Thank you.
(distant laughing)
- [Lyle] Don't talk to me
like that, you're my wife.
- [Betty] Hey, come on
inside, Momma's waitin'.
- [Lyle] I dont care, we married now.
(laughing)
- I'm gonna have a little drink.
- [Betty] Oh, come on, love.
- [Lyle] Just let me have one drink, okay.
- Come on, you've had enough to drink.
- I'll decide when I've
had enough to drink.
- Honey, come on inside.
- Don't like 'em much, do you, Ma'?
- I like 'em fine.
- I don't trust him.
- He's family now, Phyllis,
don't be talkin' against family.
(scoffs)
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- Come on, Lyle, what
have you got to lose?
- Right now, nothin',
and I aim to change that.
- Damn it, Lyle, you come
back here and talk it out now!
(slow trumpet music)
(slow instrumental music)
- [Kathryn] What'd you write, June?
- Had me a beautiful,
exciting, and wonderful year.
- Surprise!
- [Kathryn] Happy Birthday, honey!
- Thank you!
- Happy Birthday, honey.
- [Kathryn] Well, doesn't anybody
want birthday cake but me?
- Me!
- [Phyllis] I do!
- Come on, make a wish.
- Okay...
Hmm...
Alright.
(knocking)
- Oh, Mr. Cooper.
Why don't you come on in
and have some cake with us?
- No, thank you...
Ma'am, ah, George?
Could you step out here,
I'd like to talk to ya'.
- Alright.
Yes, sir.
- George, I'm sorry, but I gotta collect
that money you owe on your account.
- I see, ah...
Well, Mr. Cooper, we don't
the $63 right now, but...
- It ain't $63.
See, here, it says $232.76.
But I didn't sign for this.
Mr. Cooper, we was in your
store just the other day,
and that's the last time I...
- Last night, Lyle Nathan walked in,
and said you needed more supplies,
and said you sent him over
there to pick up the stuff.
Well, he said wrong because I dont know
nothin' about that now.
Well, since it's a family debt,
we'll stand good for it.
- I need the money now,
it's just much too high.
- Well, Mr. Cooper, if you
can just give us three weeks.
Now, that crops gonna come in,
and we'll have ya' money.
How's that sound?
- How's that sound?
Like you can't pay your
bill is what I'm hearin'.
Well, let's just go talk
to Lyle Nathan right now,
and get this thing straightened out.
(knocking)
- Betty, hon, you in there?
Honey, get Lyle out here.
Where is Lyle?
- He's gone.
- [Kathryn] He's what?
- He's ran off.
(crying)
- What in the hell?
- [Kathryn] Where's he
gone, Betty, what happened?
- [Betty] I dont know!
- Lyle Nathan's run off,
and how do I know you ain't gonna follow?
How do I know that he ain't waitin'
for you out there somewhere?
I want my money by the end of the week!
- Well, Mr. Cooper, why would we run off
with these crops comin'
in in just a few weeks?
Now, we'll get you your
money, don't, Mr.Cooper!
Look, we'll see what we can sell!
- [Betty] Ma', I'm so sorry.
- Betty, it isn't your fault.
It would've broke my heart
if you had gone with him.
You tried the best you could,
but sometimes life has a
way of handin' you things
that you don't expect.
- He used to say that people
acted like we're trash.
He used to say the
Messengers are just a bunch
of dreamers suckin' on their teeth.
- Don't you let that
boy make you feel small.
Don't let anybody make you feel small.
Baby, I know how much
you're hurt right now.
It'll take awhile, but
everything's gonna be okay.
I promise you.
Your hair's gotten so long.
Why don't we cut you some bangs tomorrow,
that way you can see
what's coming next time.
- Night, Ma'.
- Good riddance is what I say.
I saw it comin' a mile off.
- I bet you did.
- So, you still want me to find a good man
like Lyle to take care of me, Ma'.
- We got a lot of talkin' to do.
We'll talk in the morning, Phyllis.
- Yeah, sure we will.
You'll just be fussin' over Lewis,
and starin' at that stupid
picture of that stupid farm!
Nobody listens to me around here, Ma',
I got places I wanna go
and things I wanna do.
Damn, I sure wish I lived in the city,
because I hate it here, I hate it here!
And all you do is fuss...
- Phyllis, if you are so unhappy here,
then why don't you just
head on to the city?
You're a great big girl now,
you can do what you want to.
Go on.
- [Phyllis] Maybe I will.
- You hate this, and you hate that,
you are just plain hateful.
And that'll get you nowhere fast.
So, go on, then.
- And goin' nowhere fast seems
to be the style around here.
- [Ashford] Get your money, Cooper?
- No.
- They robbin' you alright.
They're all in it together.
- Them tent farmers are like animals.
They sleep together like a pack of dogs.
- They said they'd have the
money by the end of the week.
- They said, they said?
What guts at work, a bunch of transients.
A bunch of transients!
Just a pickin' fruit,
movin' from place to place.
I ant accept that, Cooper.
You can't change a leopard's spots.
I got a job to do now.
Besides, we gotta start breakin' ground
on that land soon enough.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
- Well, that's it, we're
never gonna make $232.
It's all in the land, and
half of that ain't ours.
This is from Betty.
- George Messenger!
This is the Sheriff, I'd
like to have a word with you!
(buzzing)
- Yes, sir, Sheriff.
(cocking)
Mighty, Sheriff.
Now, I told you we were
gonna pay you that money.
- [Ashford] You're under
arrest for obtaining property
under false pretenses at the Cooper store.
Come on, boys.
- No, no, wait.
No, look, we ain't don't
anything wrong, now hey!
We just can't pay the grocery bill!
- Sir, he didn't do nothin'!
(screaming)
- Don't do that!
- Get your hands off us!
- Betty, get back in the house!
(pensive instrumental music)
(shrieking)
(screaming)
(pensive instrumental music)
- [Girls] Monsters, Ma'!
- [Kathryn] Monsters, where at?
- [Officer] Hey, Messenger, catch.
- [Woman] You want me to help you?
Here.
- Thanks.
- A couple, George and Kathryn Messenger
are now held in Santa Rosa
County Jail in Jackson.
They bought under false pretenses
$700 worth of merchandise:
including a large refrigerator, radio,
22 Automatic rifle, and a tractor?
- That's not true, that's lies.
Oh my God, they put them
lies in the newspaper.
- Mr. Messenger, did not resist arrest,
but his wife resisted,
kicking, biting, and scratching
so that the three officers
were forced to use
main strength to get
her into the police car.
(laughing)
- Alright, that's true.
- [Woman] And there's more.
Three juveniles have been trans...
(screeching)
(honking)
- What?
(screaming)
What?
- [Woman] Three juveniles
have been transported
to Fair Crest Youth Home
for state supervision.
- Fair Crest, what kind of place is that?
My little girls never spent a day
in their life without me in Georgia.
- It's a foster home for kids.
The state of Florida
takes care of the children
when they lock up the folks.
- I would like you all to say
hello to our new arrivals.
- Hello.
- Now, who would like to explain
the rules to the new girls?
Emily?
- There's dogs.
- Why don't you show our new
guests what you mean by that?
Well, come on, Emily, be
a good girl, and show 'em.
Ha!
(growling)
(barking)
(screeching)
(banging)
- Shh, shh!
Look!
Now, you can write to your kids,
and let 'em know you're okay.
And you can make sure that they are too.
And you can follow it in the papers too.
Okay?
You can't read, can you.
- Not too good.
- I mean, look, it's okay.
I'll help you.
- Thanks.
- Juney May.
You always wanted your own bed, right.
Now, you don't have to share.
- You lookin' for trouble, darlin', huh?
- Here, this is from Elsa, the cook.
- Thank you.
- She's alright, you can always
count on her to help out.
Look, you stay away from Old Man Virgil.
You don't want him to
fancy you, that's for sure.
Do you know where your folks is?
Did they run off?
That's okay, I dont know
where my folks is neither.
- [Officer] Alright, time to go.
Just the boy.
- Watch your step, son.
- G, good girl, okay.
Truth.
- T...
R...
(pensive instrumental music)
- Sheriff!
- Oh, here comes trouble.
- What can I do for ya', boy?
- Someone stole our crop.
Now, what are you gonna do about that?
- Well, I'll start an
investigation right away.
Of course then again, those crops was owed
on some bills, seems to me.
- Them crops were worth
a lot more than a bill.
Now, you know that, a lot more!
That's my mother's shawl.
That's my mother's shawl!
Where did you get that?
You stole it, you stole it!
- You're mistaken, boy.
- You stole it!
- I want you out of Jackson in one hour,
or I'm gonna arrest you for vacancy.
Better get his butt out of here.
- [Billy] Get out.
♪ Jingle all the way ♪
♪ Oh what fun it is to ride ♪
♪ In a one horse open sleigh hey ♪
♪ Jingle bells jingle
bells jingle all the way ♪
♪ Oh what fun it is to ride ♪
♪ In a one horse open sleigh ♪
- Don't be scared, come here.
Yes, good.
Here you go, here you go.
Good doggy.
♪ Joyful and triumphant ♪
♪ Oh come ye oh come ye to Bethlehem ♪
♪ Come and behold him ♪
♪ Born the king of angels ♪
♪ Oh come let us adore him ♪
♪ Christ the Lord ♪
(gavel pounding)
- You two are charged
with attaining property
under false pretenses.
A felonious action against
the state of Florida.
Mr. Cooper.
- George and Kathryn
Messenger obtained $232.76
worth of merchandise and they couldn't pay
when the time had come.
I've got the receipt right here.
They claimed they could cover
the bill with their crops,
but they could not.
(pensive instrumental music)
- Is there anything you
wish to say in your defense?
- We never seen them supplies, now.
My son-in-law bought that stuff.
(pensive instrumental music)
- We need to set down clear
what is right and wrong.
The Messengers here did wrong.
(pensive instrumental music)
- The jury finds the Messengers guilty
of obtaining property
under false pretense.
George and Kathryn Messengers
you have been found guilty
of a felonious action against the peace
and dignity of the state of Florida.
It is therefore the judgment of this court
and the sentence of the law
that you each be confined
to hard labor in the state
prison in the state of Florida...
For and during a period of seven years.
(pensive instrumental music)
- [Girls] Monsters, Ma'!
- [Kathryn] Monsters, where at?
(pensive instrumental music)
(slamming)
- Hmm...
What a shame to cut such beautiful hair.
Mm-mm-mm.
Well...
That's the rules.
- Can you help me, please?
Can you help me about my kids?
- Your children are at the wards
of the state of Florida now.
Don't worry, they'll be put
up for adoption right away.
They'll be taken care of.
(whistling)
(slow blues music)
- Howdy, I'd like to pass through, please.
(whistling)
- Don't walk so fast,
we ain't goin' nowhere,
except back where we started.
- Not me, I'm gettin' out
of here, you watch and see.
- I'd like to see my client, named Logan.
(whistling)
- Lo!
Step out!
(whistling)
- Hi, Ms. Logan.
- Who's that?
- Her lawyer.
Her family hired him to get her an appeal.
- [Kathryn] I guess her people
got money to pay him, huh.
- Yeah, she say they
have a care dealership.
I seen him do charity
cases a couple of times.
He brings a good magazine though.
- You think he'd help me about my kids?
- The boss man hates his guts.
You be careful.
- Water guard?
- Hands!
Hands, hands!
- [Kathryn] Mister, can
I talk to you a minute.
I'm Kathryn Messenger, I
just need to talk to you.
(screaming)
- Proceed on lie.
To take it under control!
Back in line!
- Shh, shh, shh!
(shrieking)
Now, shoosh, come on, be a good girl, now.
Don't give me no trouble, be a good girl.
Oh..
(shrieking)
(screaming)
Damn!
(suspenseful instrumental music)
- Come here, boys, come
on, come on, doggies.
Come on, doggies, come here.
Good boy, good boy, come here.
Good boy.
(screaming)
Oh, my God!
Get off of me!
(screaming)
- Calm down, honey, those
dogs aren't gonna bite you.
Now, there, you are not to say anything.
Now, you go pack your bags.
You're gonna get your wish.
You're leavin' Fair Crest.
- Please don't go.
- Honey, I ain't got no choice.
Every night, once you go to sleep,
I'll have my arms around you.
- Every, every night?
You won't forget?
- Never.
- [Virgil] Time to go!
- You listen to me, come here!
Don't you ever let anyone make
you feel small, you got that?
Especially that old man,
Virgil, you stay away from him.
You understand me?
Okay.
- [Virgil] Phyllis, right now!
- Okay, be big girls now.
Here, you have this.
Take care of each other.
(solemn instrumental music)
Come on, go back to bed, it's alright.
I'm comin' back for you.
(solemn instrumental music)
(slow blues music)
(whistling)
- Honey, you okay?
You're runnin' on low gear these days.
- They got my kids.
My girl, Phyllis, we had been fightin'
the night we was picked up.
I didn't treat her fair.
- She won't hold it against ya'.
- [Lawyer] Logan.
- Logan, step out!
(slow blues music)
(whistling)
- Washroom, guard.
- [Guard] Step out.
(slow blues music)
- Excuse me, sir.
Look, they took my kids, I just wanna know
they're alright, that's all.
Can you help me?
I'm Messenger, Kathryn Messenger...
- Ma'am, you better go back.
(shrieking)
- You got hearin' problems,
don't you, Messenger?
Don't you!
I warned you.
- And Sands, I told you
to follow the rules,
now get outta here, leave!
- Messenger, I warned you.
- This ain't right.
- Did I hear you say somethin'?
- I sure hope I didn't
hear you say nothin'!
- It ain't oughta be like this!
Give me somethin' real to do!
This is ain't right!
- I'm warnin' you!
Matron, box!
Get up!
(wary instrumental music)
(whistling)
(pensive instrumental music)
Your hearin' improve, Messenger?
I didn't get that!
I guess your hearin'
is not fixed yet, huh?
Well...
I guess you need another five days, huh?
- [Kathryn] Wait, wait...
- Alright, now...
Who are you?
- [Kathryn] 634, sir.
- That's right.
Why are you here?
- [Kathryn] Broke the law, sir.
(gasping)
- Whose fault was that?
- [Kathryn] (crying) Mine, sir.
- How much time left?
- [Kathryn] Six years, sir.
- Hmm, and who owns you
for the next six years?
- [Kathryn] You do, sir.
- Well...
Let's get you cleaned up a little bit.
We got a little reward for you, Messenger.
Just what you asked for.
(footsteps)
- Messenger, I'm gonna
give you some good advice.
You keep goin' after your kids,
they are gonna grow up with the smell
of jailbird Momma on 'em.
Folks can sniff that out a mile away.
And they're gonna straight down the tubes,
but you leave your kids alone,
they might end up with new folks,
folks who can take care of 'em real good.
Better than you ever could.
See, without you, your children may stand
a chance in this life.
You already done the best
thing you ever could for 'em...
By gettin' yourself locked up in here.
You see what I mean.
- Sir, I'd like to...
I'd to finish here now.
- Alright, now, that's
the kind of attitude
we like to see here.
I think we are goin' to get along
real fine from here on out.
(slow instrumental music)
(pensive instrumental music)
(shattering)
(coughing)
(slow instrumental music)
- Mrs. Messenger?
Mrs. Messenger?
No, no, no, it's alright, it's alright,
it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, you're safe now.
(slow instrumental music)
- Safe?
Why?
Are you an angel?
- I'm Bill Sandstrom...
I took the liberty of
lookin' into your case.
Now, I'm gonna try and
get you out of here.
And I ain't no angel and no
devil neither, just a lawyer.
- We didn't mean to break the law.
We didn't mean to, we didn't know we was.
(crying)
We didn't mean to!
- Mrs. Messenger, you have
not committed any crime,
you're innocent, you hear?
Now, listen to me, and this is our deal...
You and me, we're gonna
overcome this thing,
and we ain't given up
because you are innocent.
- Right.
- You damn straight, that's right.
(ringing)
(knocking)
Hello, Judge.
- Mornin', Bill.
- Lord, it's hot, ain't it?
Alright, the Messenger case...
You see, George and Kathryn Messenger
have been convicted of a
crime that does not exist.
Obtainin' property under false pretenses.
Now, these folks had
a grocery bill of $232
that they could not pay
until their crops came in.
False pretenses refers to
the false solicitation,
which if I'm right is not the cause,
not the running up of a grocery bill.
Now, you know and I know
that nobody in this country
can be jailed for debt.
Lewis...
They were wrongly convicted.
I demand their immediate release.
(slow instrumental music)
- Habeas corpus granted.
(pensive instrumental music)
(laughs)
- I dont know how to thank you.
If it wasn't for you...
- Look, Kitty...
I'll tell ya' how ya' can
thank me, now listen carefully.
Don't you ever lose faith again.
I know what it's like to lose faith.
They've done a terrible thing to you,
and the fact is, you
won't ever forget that.
But from now on, you've got to hold
your head up no matter what.
That's it.
(laughing)
That's it, now.
And you keep it right there, alright?
- Alright.
Mr. Sandstrom, I'll try my best.
- Alright...
Alright.
Now...
Here's the addresses of your children.
My office tracked 'em down.
And here's a post card that
just come to you from your kids.
Now, I'm gonna send all
your stuff onto Sweet Ridge.
And here's $50 from the state.
Guess they figured
that's all they owed you.
Now, where you headed?
Fair Crest Youth Home.
- Gosh...
Oh, boy, I gotta go.
- Hey...
You are an angel.
(slow blues music)
"Dear Ma' and Pa, we're
in Sweet Ridge saving up
"to hire you a lawyer.
"Don't forget about us,
love Betty and Lewis."
- My Kathryn Messenger...
Ain't that somethin'.
Read it again.
- "Dear Ma' and Pa, we're in Sweet Ridge
"saving up to hire you...
Oh, George.
(slow piano music)
Come here.
(sentimental instrumental music)
Hey, Mama...
How you doin'?
I missed ya'.
(sentimental instrumental music)
- Somethin' different about you, darlin'.
Somethin' around the eyes.
Somethin' happen to you back here?
- I'm alright, George.
I love you.
Everything's gonna be alright.
We'll go get our kids back,
and then we'll go home.
(slow instrumental music)
(crying)
- Mornin', Ma'am.
- [Woman] Hello.
- We're here to pick up our children.
- [Woman] And who are you?
- George and Kathryn Messenger,
our daughters are here,
June, Annette, and Phyllis.
- Just a minute.
- Do I look alright?
- Oh, you look beautiful.
- [Kathryn] You look awful
handsome yourself, sir.
- [George] Awe, thank you, ma'am.
- I'll be needin' to take
a look at the court order.
- Court order?
- Your parental rights have been severed.
You must now be approved by
the child welfare department
in order to be reinstated
as parents of the children.
Your children have already
been put up for adoption.
- They what?
We were found innocent.
- Where's my girls?
I wanna talk to my girls.
- I can't do nothin' for ya'
till you come back with a court order.
Besides, the big girl,
she ain't even here.
- She ain't here!
- She's been transferred to the residence
for delinquent girls in Ocala.
- She no delinquent girl!
What happened?
June!
- Now, Kitty, Kitty, this
ain't gonna do no good.
- But who does that man think he is
tellin' us about our own kids!
♪ Two times one is two ♪
♪ Two times two is four ♪
♪ Two times ♪
Come on, now.
(distant singing)
♪ Two times six is twelve ♪
♪ Two times seven is 14 ♪
♪ Two times eight is 16 ♪
♪ Two times nine is 18 ♪
- June!
- [Virgil] Hey, get away from there!
♪ Three times one is... ♪
- Momma!
(screaming)
- [Kathryn] Are you okay?
- Momma, Momma!
- Ahh!
(screaming)
- Georgie!
- [Virgil] If you ever, ever
wanna see your kids again,
you better play by the rules!
(pensive instrumental music)
- I wanna go to Ocala, and
make sure Phyllis is safe.
- I'll be back later.
- It wasn't my fault, Ma', I swear.
- No, of course it wasn't, honey.
- I...
(shuddering)
I can't stand seein' you
in a place like this.
(slow piano music)
- Look at ya', all grown up.
(sorrowful instrumental music)
Phyllis, what happened?
What happened at Fair Crest?
- It wasn't my fault, Ma', I
swear, I didn't do nothin'.
I didn't do nothin'.
- It's alright, baby.
It's alright, I believe you...
- No, no, you don't!
- Baby...
(slow instrumental music)
- We love you.
Now, you just hold on a little bit,
we're gonna get you outta here.
- Don't say that, don't say that!
You know it ain't true!
You can't get me out because you can't!
You can't, I'm sorry, Momma!
(yelling)
(sorrowful instrumental music)
- [George] All gone, everything.
- Why George?
Why?
(pensive instrumental music)
- [June] Maybe my Mardi
Gras beads will grow
into a crop, huh, Momma.
I wanna see it when the crops come in.
(pensive instrumental music)
Maybe my Mardi Gras beads will
grow into a crop, huh, Momma.
(echoing)
- [George] Kitty, get up, now.
Kitty, quit that.
- No!
- Kitty...
(crying)
Kitty...
- Hey!
What are y'all doin' back here, anyhow?
You Messengers don't belong here,
stinkin' up our town.
Now get.
Or I'll arrest you for trespassing.
- Kitty, no, Kitty, no, Kitty, Kitty!
Now...
That ain't gonna help.
That ain't gonna help the kids us gettin'
throwed back in jail again.
We gotta go get the kids.
Now...
Let's go get the kids.
- Well, that's done with.
- No, sir, Sheriff.
No, it's far from done with.
(slow blues music)
♪ Well you took my coat ♪
♪ Took my hat ♪
♪ That's alright baby you
know I won't be comin' back ♪
♪ No no ♪
(slow blues music)
♪ I'm gonna move ♪
♪ I'm gonna move baby ♪
♪ Gonna move away from you ♪
♪ Ain't no time to holler ♪
♪ No time to cry ♪
♪ Let me tell you baby ♪
♪ It's bye bye bye ♪
♪ I'm gonna move ♪
♪ I'm gonna move move
move I'm gonna move ♪
♪ I'm gonna move baby ♪
♪ I'm gonna move away from you ♪
(slow blues music)
Don't, I believe your father turned
into a liar in that jail house.
(laughing)
- We got a letter from the girls for you.
Want me to read it for ya'?
- No...
I can.
- What she talkin' about?
(laughing)
- "Dear Ma', remember Ma' when
you'd be out in the field.
"Sometimes, and me, and Annette would come
"and think with you?
If some...
- Body.
- "Body, somebody, ever gave me a wish.
"I'd wish us all together.
"They say we have to go to new...
"Families at Christmas.
"We're sorry for what we did wrong.
"We promise to be good.
"Please...
"Come get us, we'll
make Christmas for real.
"Love June & Annette."
Would you look at how Boo made her name?
- [Lewis] Momma, we're gonna
have to get you a library card.
- Library card?
(laughing)
- Now, we gonna get an application
from them child welfare people?
And we're all gonna have to work,
and we're gonna save enough
to get these youngin' back.
- I love you, Pappa.
- I love you, baby.
- We'll get 'em back, Momma.
- What do you think of me, huh?
- You did great.
- What do you think of me?
(laughs)
(knocking)
- Hello, I'm Mrs. Karsten
from Child Welfare,
I'm here about your application.
- [George] Come on in.
I work the night shift,
you see, and I was, ah...
Well, shoot, I wish I'd
have known you was comin'.
Kitty, my wife, she'd of wanted
to be here to talk to ya'.
Everybody else is out.
My wife, she's workin' the
lunch shift at the Five & Dime.
She'll be back this afternoon though.
Maybe you could wait.
- Oh...
(chuckles)
- No, I reckon not.
Have you had lunch?
I can heat you up some real nice
turtle soup from last night.
- No.
- Well, everybody else is out workin'.
We all work.
- We like to make these visits as casual
and relaxed as possible, that's
why we arrive unannounced.
- Mm-hmm.
- So, who is everybody?
- Well, there's Kitty,
my wife, like I said.
And Lewis, my son, and Betty, my big girl.
- And all of y'all live here?
In such a small place?
- Now, I'm sorry you have to
see us livin' like this...
But this here is just temporary.
Until we can save up enough
to get our little girls back.
- I see.
- She was here?
What'd she say?
- [George] Not much.
- What'd you say?
- Well, I offered her some
lunch, some turtle soup.
- You offered her turtle soup?
Good lord, George, did you tell her about
our jobs, and plans and all?
- Well, of course I did.
- [Kathryn] So, what'd she say?
- Not much.
- Not much?
Well, what'd you say?
Is that all you said?
You offered her soup and that was it?
That was it?
- Dammit, Kitty, I told her the truth.
Now, what was I supposed to tell her?
That we're savin' up to buy a farm?
That we got $300 already saved up?
And if we keep at it,
maybe, maybe, maybe, no.
No.
I told her we wanted our
girls back is what I told her.
- Did you tell her how much we love 'em?
- [George] I told her we wanted
the girls back, that's it.
(slamming)
- Ma'!
It's here.
- The State of Florida
Child Welfare Department.
- You need me to read it for ya', Ma'?
- Dear Mr. & Mrs. Messenger...
The State of Florida has
considered your request,
your request has been denied.
- [Lewis] What!
- Denied?
(heavy breathing)
- [Kathryn] I have business here.
- We're closed.
- I have official business here!
Explain this to me.
- I'm sorry, we're closed now.
You're gonna have to come back tomorrow.
- No, you explain this to me right now,
or you won't be seein'
tomorrow, God help me.
- It says you have been denied adoption.
- I know that, why?
Why?
- Your children were interviewed
by perspective adoptive parents.
It looks as if they've
found new homes for them.
It was the decision of the state
that this was the best thing for them.
They will be moved December 23rd.
- Alright, how much do you want?
- I beg your pardon.
- This is what I have.
This is what we have
saved, is that enough?
- Look, lady, I'm sorry...
- Is that enough?
Is that enough, how much?
- Lady, I'm sorry, but the
decision has been made.
Not by me, but by the state of Florida.
It's for their own good.
- No, no, who the hell
is the State of Florida?
- Pete, Pete!
- Now, you name the price!
How much for my kids?
They're my kids!
They're my kids, they're my children!
Get your hands off me!
- Go!
- I got a right to an answer!
I got a right to an answer.
- [Guard] Don't you come back!
- What are you lookin' at?
- Go on!
- What are you lookin'
at, the poor white trash?
Well, go ahead, take a look!
Just take a look, and you tell me then!
Then you tell me then!
(crying)
- [Guard] Go on, I'll have you arrested!
- [Kathryn] They're my blood!
- Get on out of here!
(screaming)
Go, go on!
(yelling)
(crying)
Oh, no good.
Girls, I'm sorry.
(crying)
Denied.
(slow instrumental music)
- You about ready to come home?
- George, listen to me...
Back at prison...
They got to me...
And I gave up.
I just wanted it over.
I tried to kill myself.
- Well...
I reckon the good Lord wasn't
finished with you yet, was he?
You looky here, we gon'...
Somehow or another, we gon'
find a way to move on from here.
We have to.
We just...
We're just gonna find a way
to make it right together.
- My Georgie...
How could I have ever
wanted to quit on you?
On the family...
I'm ashamed, I'm sorry, I'm...
I'll make it up to you.
- Shh, shh, shh.
- Oh, yes, I wanna go home.
We got work to do.
- Yeah.
- We got work to do.
- Yeah, yeah.
(mid-tempo piano music)
(ringing)
(conversing)
- Excuse me...
Ah, excuse me, gentlemen!
Florida took my kids away,
and nobody will listen to me!
And I need one of you to write my story,
so that people will read it.
Now, I have been reading the law.
And I have a letter from my daughter.
Hey...
(knocking)
Hey!
(whistling)
My mother's talkin' here!
- My children are in trouble.
And nobody'll listen to me,
and I need one of you to help me out.
- Somebody get rid of this cornball.
- I want equal justice under the law.
(laughing)
- Equal justice under
the law means I'm free
to tell you to get out of here.
(laughing)
- And I can leave on my own.
- [Man] Well, then why don't you do so?
(laughing)
- Thank you.
Come on, Betty.
- [Man] Leave her behind.
(laughing)
- Excuse me, ma'am.
Ma'am, excuse me...
I think you left this behind there.
- Please help me.
- No, this ain't my
beat, I do international.
- You read my letter, didn't ya'?
You know what I'm saying
is true, don't ya'?
- I dont know nothin' to
be true about you lady.
I dont know you.
- Oh, yes you do.
You know me...
You know my kind.
Look at me.
Now, you can turn around and walk away,
and pretend you don't, but we know better.
Please help me.
(slow instrumental music)
- Alright, look, I can't
promise you anything, alright.
Come see me in my office tomorrow.
We'll talk about it, okay.
- Tomorrow?
- Tomorrow.
(slow instrumental music)
(laughing)
- Morning, son.
- You scared me to death.
- Listen, I was wondering
if maybe you could do
one more thing for me.
- [Man] One more thing?
I haven't done the first thing yet.
Now what?
- I have to apply for a
court hearing, it's...
A petition for an appeal
to the juvenile court.
And I wonder if you could just explain
some things for me I've been readin'.
- Sure, why not, I'm not busy or anything.
Shoot.
- Well, I...
Sorry...
- It's okay.
- I've been readin' the Constitution,
and I think that it's the law
that the court is supposed to follow.
And I want this down in my appeal.
- Watch the monkey, please.
- I have to send for an
original, three copies,
a T1080 Notice of Motion form.
Color coded with a docket number,
and date of decision,
whatever the hell that is.
- Mrs. Messenger, you haven't been goin'
to law school, have ya'?
- Shoot, I never did have
school after the first grade.
My people was migrants,
you know, fruit tramps.
Anyhow, now I've been learning.
And, well, a woman helped me out at...
And...
I go to the library.
Anyway, could you explain
them things to me?
I figure that I can send my petition
right before your newspaper article.
That way maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe
when they read your story,
they'll accept my petition.
- You know, when you walked
into that press room I thought
there goes one hard headed
woman, here comes trouble.
And I was right.
- Yes, sir.
- Look, I can't promise you that
they're gonna run what I write,
but I will do the best that
I can, okay, I really will.
- I know you will.
- I know you know.
- Thank you.
- Hey, lady, you're Kathryn Messenger.
- Good lord, why?
- Quite a picture, lady.
- Look, Ma'!
- Oh, heavens.
- Oh, it's you!
- Let's see it.
Would you look at that?
That's about, that's me.
- Good luck to ya'.
- Thanks so much, thank you.
♪ Well you took my coat took my hat ♪
♪ That's alright baby you
know I won't be comin' back ♪
♪ I'm gonna move ♪
- [Man] Now, there it is.
- This one right here?
- Discriminatory, look it up.
♪ I'm gonna move baby ♪
♪ Gonna move away from you ♪
♪ Ain't no time to holler ♪
♪ No time to cry ♪
- It's time to go tell
people our business.
- I'm right behind you.
- You should give this woman a chance.
No one in this town has got the nerve
to stand up to Sheriff Ashford.
You might as well let her
be the first one to try.
(slow blues music)
Chicken?
- What?
- Would you like some more chicken, dear?
(slow blues music)
- Mornin', Judge.
- [Judge] Mornin', Sheriff.
- Sarah Louise.
- Good mornin'.
- Judge, can I have a little
word with you a minute?
- Sure, Joe, ah, excuse me, darlin'.
- Of course.
- Sarah Louise, your cookin'
sure smells good, honey.
- Thank you, Sheriff.
- [Ashford] You look like you've been
puttin' on a little weight.
Next time we go fishin', you
might just sink the boat.
(chuckles)
Now, Wyatt, I assume you ain't gonna let
this Messenger business go any further.
- Joe, we got a problem.
And it's all down here in black and white.
- I got a problem too,
that's doin' the job I was elected to do.
- Joe, it ain't gonna
go away by ignorin' it!
- I got a job to do!
And that's preservin'
law and order, so do you.
Now you watch yourself.
Take it easy on those potatoes.
You don't wanna go sinkin' the boat.
- [Kathryn] I can't do this, George.
- [George] We're on our
way to get the kids.
- [Kathryn] On our way to Jackson Court,
where they locked us
up in the first place.
I'm scared.
Plain ol' scared.
(pensive instrumental music)
(baby crying)
- [Officer] The State of Florida
versus Kathryn Messenger.
- Mrs. Messenger, you may
address the court now.
- Mr. Justice Black, Ray
Oliver, 333 US 257273,
identifies these rights as
essential for a fair trial.
The person's right to reasonable notice
of a charge against him and
an opportunity to be heard.
- Will that be all, Mrs. Messenger?
- Who are you?
- I'm Will Leroux, Your Honour.
- He's a newspaper reporter, Your Honor,
he's been writing some articles.
- A newspaper man has no business here.
He's gonna have to leave the courtroom.
Go on, get.
- No, he has every right to be here.
Every right.
The freedom of the press.
You, you have no right
to tell him to leave.
You have no right!
(gavel pounding)
- [George] Just calm down.
- I'm sorry, Judge.
- Proceed, Mrs. Messenger.
- On November 29, 1951,
the authorities of the State of Florida
removed from the house we
rented on the land we worked,
Phyllis Messenger, then age 15...
June Marie Messenger, then age 10...
Annette Messenger, then age...
I tried to teach my kids
that what a person is worth
isn't just how much money they have,
but what they believe in.
And if they are truthful and fair.
Maybe I wasn't always fair my own self.
Maybe I dreamed for the wrong things.
But now, you tell me since
when it's a crime to be poor.
Is it a crime in this
country to go hungry?
country to have a house?
Because that is what my
children have learned from you,
and I have read the constitution
of the United States,
and I have read the
Declaration of Independence.
What if getting ahead isn't
just houses, and new cars,
and more of everything
than the next one's got?
What if it's bein' allowed to show
your children how much you love them?
And through bad times, and hard times...
You continue to try to teach them about
fairness and honesty...
And what if that is getting ahead?
We're not criminals, we're just poor.
And we didn't pay a bill,
and for that they took our girls away.
But they're all we have.
Maybe they're all we'll ever have.
- [Judge] Mrs. Messenger,
I grant your petition.
(slow instrumental music)
- Girls...
It's me.
It's your Momma.
- Momma?
(sentimental instrumental music)
Papa...
Pa?
(sentimental instrumental music)
- Hi, Momma.
Where is everybody?
- At the house, waitin' on us.
(sentimental instrumental music)
Merry Christmas, Phyllis, welcome home.
- Merry Christmas, Momma.
(sentimental instrumental music)
- Good to see ya', buddy.
(laughing)
- Merry Christmas, honey.
(slow instrumental music)
(laughing)
(MultiCom Jingle)