(illuminating music)
(dreadful music)
(cars whooshing)
- [Michael] Good morning, Los Angeles.
Michael Horn on CRN Radio.
Another gorgeous day here in the southland
as long as you don't
mind rolling blackouts
and frequent tremblers.
Now I admit we can't do
much about these tremors.
We do live on one of the most active
fault lines in the world,
but the blackouts, that's another matter.
Why can't these energy
companies get their act together
and generate enough electricity?
That's our topic for today.
The lines are open.
Call me on CRN.
Hi, you're on the air.
- [Raymond] Hi, Mike, this is Raymond.
- Hey, Raymond.
- Calling from the city.
- How you doing?
- I couldn't agree more.
- [Raymond] My wife and I had
to eat dinner by candlelight
for three nights in a row.
Now come on!
(Michael laughs)
- [Michael] Hey, here we go again.
Hang on, everyone, it's
another rollercoaster.
Boy, it's a big one this time.
Wherever you are, listeners,
I hope you got something to hold on to
because the ground's shaking so hard.
Oh my god, the building's
starting to sway, whoa!
(horns honking)
(sirens blaring)
Boy, that was something!
Hey, Paul in the newsroom,
we need to find out from the
seismographic lab at Cal Tech
just how big that one was.
(unfriendly music)
(suspenseful music)
- The real deal, bro.
- Yeah.
Well, why don't you keep
your real deal shut?
- Whatever, man.
- Now listen to me.
We believe in what we're
doing here, all right,
and if you're not in line with us,
why don't you leave?
- Hey, it's cool, man.
- Is it?
- Yeah, I'm cool.
I'm cool.
- We got 14 minutes, come on.
(soft suspenseful music)
(moves into tense music)
Get back.
(zapping)
That's the real deal, bro.
- So this is the enemy's lair.
- Just the front gates.
(guard whistling)
(hidden music)
- Abbott.
- Yeah?
- We got a problem.
- What is it?
- Call Mr. Clemens.
- Oh, that guy scares me.
(tense music)
(typing)
(crashing)
(Sara gasps)
- What are you doing?
- God!
- Leaving my mark.
- Your mark?
- It's symbolism, bro.
The lab represents a...
- Oh my god!
McCullough's geological report.
- It looks like calculus.
- Stress equations.
(crazed music)
(malicious music)
- Um, Mr. Clemens, I...
- Where are your men?
- Um, they're up on 12th, sir.
- Get them out.
- Leron?
Uh, Mr. Clemens is here.
He wants you out now.
- When we get 12, shut down the elevators.
And when your men get down
here, go home, all of you.
We have multiple LBs on 12.
I want you two to go with
Zendon up the stairs.
You two are with me.
Front to back, gentlemen.
- Come on, come on, Sara!
- No, I still have three files to go!
- Hey, we're losing time!
(computer whirring)
(typing)
(elevator dings)
(ticking)
- What was that?
- I'm out.
- I have to finish!
Oh no.
(frantic music)
(heavy breathing)
- Come on, come on, Sara!
- No, I'm not done!
- This is all we get!
Come on, Sara!
Gotta go now, Sara!
Come on!
(heavy breathing)
(typing)
- Oh god, no!
(rushing techno music)
(mysterious music)
(thudding)
(man cries out)
(gunshot fires)
(glass shattering)
(Joel cries out)
(body thuds)
(Sara gasps)
Oh god!
(suspenseful music)
(smashing)
(grunting)
(sharp breathing)
(strange music)
(sniffling)
(sobbing) Okay, okay.
(determined music)
(sharp breathing)
(door creaks)
(gunshots firing)
(Sara sobbing)
(tense music)
(sharp breathing)
(gunshots firing)
(Sara sobbing)
(Joel screams)
(gunshots firing)
(spraying)
(Joel screams)
(emotional music)
(Sara sobbing)
- Who are you?
You know, I can't help you
if you won't talk to me.
(Sara sobbing)
- I, I'm Sara.
Sara Rose.
Please, please don't kill me.
- This was an awful, awful mistake, Sara.
(Sara sobbing)
No one was supposed to get hurt.
Now we're gonna need your help
to explain to the police
exactly what happened here.
(Sara sobbing)
Are, are you with a, an organization?
- (sobbing) We're with
the World Survival Group.
- What were you looking for?
- (sobbing) When the police arrive,
I'll tell them everything.
- World Survival Group.
Well that seems like one thing
that none of you are any good at,
survival.
(Sara sobbing)
Get the cleaning team out here.
(gunshot fires)
(vacuum whirring)
- [Man Inside] Yeah?
- [Man Outside] Hey, man.
I'm a friend of Twin Peaks.
- [Man Inside] 2C.
(paper shuffling)
- [Man Outside] She said
if I, if I mentioned...
- [Man Inside] What's your name, man?
- [Nash] Nash.
(gun clicks)
- Try anything,
I'll kill you.
(eerie music)
I wouldn't normally let you in, man,
but that's my Alma mater.
- [Nash] Really?
- What the whore pig say?
- If I want the good stuff,
I gotta seek the truth.
- The truth.
- Who is this cracker
from around the way, slim?
- He good.
- Him good?
- Yeah.
- What make him good?
Round the way cracker
never come here, never.
- What?
- What do you want, my boy?
- Rock, man.
I wanna buy some.
- Him wanna buy some rock, slim.
(laughs)
You like smoke crack, eh, white boy?
Ah.
Maybe me don't want to sell you no crack.
- Maybe I'll take my two Cs
and go back down the
street to Lester's place.
- Go back down street Lester place, eh?
You say.
You know, you either crazy or stupid.
- Probably both.
- Probably.
You see, because, uh,
me just spoke Lester no more
than, uh, 10 minutes ago.
And he's all out.
Now,
me gonna ask one more time.
Saltine cracker.
What do you want?
(knocking)
Slim, get the door.
You, get in the backroom.
(scary music)
More on time than a Timex.
- Damn right, and we keep on ticking.
How's business?
- Business is business.
You know.
Steady, man.
(camera clicks)
(woman moans)
- Price has gone up.
- [Man With Hat] What?
- The thin blue line needs
to get a little thicker.
(man with hat laughs)
- No more money, man.
(woman moaning)
Just customer.
No need get worried.
(mattress squeaking)
- What the fuck?
- Almost done.
- [Man In Black] Looks like somebody's
been eavesdropping on us.
Little old for a college boy, ain't you?
- I got left back.
(punching)
(grunting)
(tires squealing)
(brakes squeaking)
(chattering on police radio)
- [Cop] Here we go, second floor!
(gun clicks)
(punching)
(grunting)
- White boy little tougher
than he looks, slim.
(electric buzzing)
Got better electric
service in Jamaica, man.
(laughs)
(cops shouting over each other)
(crazy music)
- Easy!
- You set us up!
(gunshots firing)
(grunting)
(wild music)
(woman screams)
(gunshots firing)
(glass shattering)
(man screams)
(woman screams)
(defeated music)
(rumbling)
(clanking)
(cracking)
(crashing)
(Matt screaming)
(smashing)
(sparks zapping)
(crashing)
(car horns honking)
(sirens whirring)
- [Susan] That's not the point.
- The story speaks for itself.
- The story is the earthquake.
- But my story is...
- Your story is shit.
We're burying it.
You'll be lucky to make page 40.
- What?
- You don't deserve to be a byliner, Nash.
You've got the passion,
but you're not focused in the right place.
You're focused on you.
And stop that!
You're wasting your life.
Lose this fascination with danger
and grow up.
I think you should consider
finding another job.
- I can't believe this!
- Well, believe it.
You know, you might've had a story here,
but once again, you put yourself into it.
Report the story, don't be the story.
- But you always say write what you know.
- Goodbye.
- Whoa, Breech, come on,
just give me something to work on.
- There's a soft one you can have.
- What is it?
- Some environmentalists
have been hitting on us
to do a story on the energy crisis,
deregulations, brownouts,
the whole nine yards.
- I'll take it.
- The important thing is that...
(rumbling)
- This is interesting.
You were saying?
- Pay a visit to the World Survival Group.
- And they are?
- Militants.
A lunatic fringe of the
greens in this country.
They think that the energy crisis
was a contrivance of big business.
- What's my angle?
- Besides keeping your job,
get a good story,
without getting shot.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah, can I talk to whoever's in charge?
- There's not really one person in charge.
We're anarchist in structure.
Travis!
- Travis Gentry.
- Matt Nash.
- Rita.
- So, uh, what can we do for you, man?
- I'm with the Examiner.
- Yeah, you look like a reporter.
- How's that?
- No piercings.
- None that you can see.
- I've been after you guys for months.
It takes three people disappearing
to get any interest from the media.
- What do you mean?
- Didn't your editor tell you?
- No.
- See, no one takes us seriously.
Not police, not the press.
Three of our members are missing.
Disappeared the night they
broke into Saturn Energy.
- They broke in?
- Something tells me
you're not fazed by that.
- I'm a reporter, I break
into every place I go.
(rumbling)
You were saying?
- Sara Rose, Todd Stafford, Joel Burns.
We filed missing person reports,
but, uh, cops won't do much.
- You know for a fact they got inside?
- Building security says,
well, other than the earthquake,
that they saw nothing unusual that night.
- Why Saturn Energy?
- Saturn Energy built an
experimental research facility
that's not subject to
environmental impact laws.
- You ever been inside?
- No, nobody gets inside that place, man.
It's impenetrable.
- Where is it?
- [Travis] The middle of nowhere.
(serious music)
- Hola.
(intense music)
Gracias.
(veiled music)
Can I get my change?
- Yeah, right.
(active music)
- Hold it!
- We have a breech.
(speaking in a foreign language)
(alarms blasting)
(dog barking)
- [Woman On Loudspeaker]
Attention, security breech.
Sector seven.
All available personnel please respond.
(speaking in a foreign language)
(thrilling music)
(punching)
(grunting)
(speaking in a foreign language)
(dog barking)
(tense music)
(moves into suspenseful music)
(yelling in foreign language)
(typing)
(computer beeps)
- Okay, listen up.
Tonight we start the OTS.
Finally we get to put
our technology to work.
(people applauding)
We're going to 25% power, people.
Systems checks.
- Surge protectors, go.
Call lines, go.
(hushed music)
- [DC] Sir.
Do we know who he was?
- My men are working on it.
- And the L.A. office?
- It's clean.
- What about the police?
- There's no interest.
Besides, they'd need a warrant,
and that isn't gonna happen.
- Okay, Dr. McCullough, go right ahead.
(shouting in a foreign language)
You can go.
- There is the issue of the email.
- Take care of it.
(ominous music)
- Yes, sir.
(foreboding music)
Off limits, McCullough.
- But I'm a...
- You're just a geologist.
Tonight's a special test.
Only class four personnel allowed.
Doctor's orders.
- I have to talk to Gabriella.
- Not tonight.
She's extremely busy.
- Ready when you are, doctor.
- Power up.
Coolant go.
(vigorous rock music)
(siren wailing)
- [Technician] 5% power.
10.
- 15.
(siren wailing)
- Release coolant in sector three.
(questing rock music)
(camera clicking)
25% power, holding steady.
- Put L.A. on standby.
- Go to standby.
- [Technician] Standby confirmed.
- L.A. on standby.
(puzzled music)
- [Dr. Eisley] Cut their
power at the target site.
- Cut their power.
(serious music)
Still holding steady at 25%.
- Switch to our source at the target site.
- Activate our source.
- [Technician] Activating.
(machines whirring)
(electric buzzing)
(people applauding)
- Magnificent!
Now hold that number for three minutes.
- Yes, sir.
Hold the level.
- I knew we'd do it. (laughs)
(empty music)
- Hey!
(dogs barking)
(frenzied techno music)
- Hey!
(dogs barking)
Who are you?
What are you doing out here?
- I'm just passing through.
(dog growls)
(dog barks)
(Matt screams)
- Ow ow ow!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
(dogs barking)
Ow.
Aw, come on, no.
You don't have to do that.
(dogs barking)
- Anymore jokes?
- A priest, a monk, and
a rabbi walk into a bar.
(dogs barking)
- Get down from there or
you'll be shot for trespassing.
- What's going on?
- Why didn't you tell
me you were a reporter?
- You didn't ask!
- Reporter, trespassing.
- Matt Nash.
I know you.
You're that nut that got
shot in the crack house.
- Whatever it takes.
And you are?
- Gabriella St. John.
Would you get off my car?
(dogs barking)
- What are you doing here?
- I'm just looking for a story.
- This is a research facility.
There's no story here.
- Yeah, right.
(car beeps)
Nice to meet you.
(expressive brass music)
- Nice place.
You a regular?
- They've been watching me.
It's, uh, it's safer here.
- What did I say about being paranoid?
- You said, "Russ, don't worry about it."
I'd never accept a position I'll be in.
- Uh, it's very late, Russ.
- I've started to put
my report back together.
I've been able to reconstruct
the first quarter,
and I'll have the rest of it soon.
(ominous music)
- You have a problem.
- I'm telling you, it's conclusive.
- Look at yourself.
You have got to slow down.
You're working too much.
You never sleep.
- These equations...
- Look, I'm gonna be blunt.
Your problem is you.
It's not your ex-wife,
it's not Saturn Energy,
and it's not our research.
Please, get some help.
- What about the report?
It's evidence.
The heat these tests are
producing is 10 times hotter
than anything we've produced before!
You know what that means?
We're causing these earthquakes.
I'm sure of it.
- It says there might be an anomaly.
There is no evidence of anything.
You're a scientist, Russ.
Start acting like one.
(expressive brass music)
- You got a room I could rent?
- 20 pesos.
- Can I help you?
- LAPD.
- What can I do for you?
- Looks like you got this
place running pretty smoothly.
- Yeah.
- Ever go out for the police task?
- (laughs) Twice.
- Four times.
- Really?
- (laughs) Yeah.
- (laughs) Wow.
- Were you on duty last Sunday night?
- Yes, sir, yeah.
- Notice anything unusual,
having trouble in the building?
- No, mm-mm.
- Can I look at your logbook?
- Uh, well, I...
- You got something to hide?
(Abbott laughs)
- It's, uh...
- What were the repairs for?
- Uh, sprinklers.
We had a small problem up on 12.
- Mind if I look around?
- You know, I'll have
to get you an escort.
Uh, you know, rules.
(Leron whistling)
(weird music)
- New carpet?
- Yes, it is.
(rumbling)
Don't worry.
This building's safe.
- Right.
Okay, I've seen enough for tonight.
(sirens whirring in the distance)
(crashing)
(tires squealing)
(wild music)
(car horns honking)
(tires squealing)
(crashing)
(exploding)
(tires squealing)
(glass shattering)
- [Bystander] Go, go!
(tires squealing)
(crashing)
(exploding)
(tires squealing)
(crashing)
(exploding)
(tires squealing)
(car horn honking)
(crashing)
(glass shattering)
(suspenseful music)
(gunshots firing)
(glass shattering)
(woman whimpers)
(woman screams)
(gunshot fires)
(sirens wailing)
- What happened to you?
- I cut myself shaving.
Is Gentry around?
- Not today.
Big fundraiser up north.
- Can you give me his number?
- I can give you his cellphone.
- That's all I need.
Any word on the missing members?
- Excuse me?
- Your friends.
- Oh, no.
It's weird.
I mean, they're never gone this long.
- Do they usually disappear?
- They hide out.
Sara never likes it.
That's what Todd always does,
lay low after a job.
What a jerk.
- Do you know them very well?
- Sara's my best friend.
She even sent me an
email from the building.
How cool is that?
- From Saturn Energy?
- Yeah.
I couldn't read it though,
all sorts of numbers and equations.
I gave it to Gentry.
He knows that stuff.
- Do you have a copy of it?
- No, he told me to erase it.
- Can you give me Sara's address?
- You thinking about going to her place?
- Maybe.
- Can I trust you?
- Don't I look trustworthy?
- Hang on.
- How can you guys afford
all this expensive equipment
if everyone's just a volunteer?
- Gentry got it for us.
Here you go.
- Thanks for your help.
- Um, do you have a business
card in case I want, uh,
need to call you sometime?
Thank you.
(exciting music)
- Gentry?
Matt Nash, Examiner.
- [Travis] Mr. Nash, how are you?
- Why didn't you tell
me about Sara's email?
- [Travis] I'll be in Mexico tomorrow.
Let's meet there.
(serious music)
- Need some help?
- I think we got off on the wrong foot.
Can we start over?
I'm Matt.
- You were trespassing, Matt.
- And I learned my lesson.
- How many more lessons are
you gonna need to learn?
- As many as it takes.
- For what?
- To find out what's going on in there.
- Look, I told you, there's no story here.
Please leave me alone.
- Three members of the
World Survival Group
went into Saturn Energy
in Los Angeles last week.
They've been missing ever since.
I go looking into it,
obviously there's something
they don't want me to find out.
- And what do you think that is?
- Truth.
- The truth is, there's nothing going on.
There's no story here.
(mysterious music)
- Miss St. John.
Well thank you for coming by.
Good evening.
We were just discussing the tests
and the wonderful results
you two have been achieving.
- I spoke with Russ McCullough,
and he showed me a report,
and even though it wasn't
conclusive, I felt...
- I know that report.
I've seen it.
And what you have to understand is that
McCullough's theory isn't new.
I respect him, but
well, there's no definitive proof.
- I understand, but his numbers are big,
and it wouldn't hurt to halt the test
and wait for him to finish.
- Lately Russ has been,
well he's been troubled.
I guess you should know this.
We've tried to get him into a program,
but he didn't go.
- But I think it's important we...
- The best thing for us right
now is to continue as planned.
- I was being shot at.
- Well maybe those cops
you got killed had friends.
- Something more to that place...
- Nash.
- And there's something
going on at that facility.
- Yes, research.
Now leave it alone.
- But when I went there...
- No, Nash, there is no
drama in the energy story.
Don't create it.
- I thought drama sells newspapers.
- Real drama.
- This is real, Breech.
Ow.
- Fine.
Fine.
But a few bandages prove nothing.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Nash.
I'm sorry about the...
(church bells ringing)
- Quiet place to meet.
The email.
- What does it mean?
- Not much, it's incomplete.
Some geological stress equations,
a section of faults,
latitude regarding agitation.
- Earthquakes?
- Maybe.
Only Darren Claxton knows for sure.
- Darren Claxton?
- Darren Claxton is Saturn Energy.
- You're saying I need to go
inside that research facility.
- I'm saying if you want
truth, that's where it is.
- Okay, so what's in the case?
- Special equipment you'll need.
The crime finder.
It's a 500 milowatt,
air-cooled argon ion laser.
Decibel wavelength, surrounded
by linical mirror tube.
Just aim the light, flip
the control switch on it.
Open the door to a whole new world.
- [Matt] What will I see?
- Anything that'll furess.
Fingerprints, hair fibers,
drug residue, blood evidence.
- Who are you really?
- Just a volunteer.
- With some very special friends?
- When you fight for a cause
you tend to meet a lot
of interesting people.
- Sure do.
(dramatic music)
(gunshots firing)
- [Shooter] Split up!
(frenzied techno music)
(gunshots firing)
(ceramic shattering)
(woman screams)
- [Man] Oh!
(thrilling techno music)
(gunshots firing)
(guard cries out)
(body thudding)
(people shouting)
- Get over there!
(punching)
(thudding)
(gunshots firing)
(galloping techno music)
(people screaming)
(gunshots firing)
Hey!
(crazy techno music)
(gunshots firing)
(guard grunts)
(body thuds)
(guard coughing)
- [Guard] No, no!
(gunshot fires)
(dreadful techno music)
(speaking in a foreign language)
- It's a seed.
Eventually it grows.
- Not without water.
- McCullough showed her the report.
He has to be dealt with.
- Fine.
- And Gabriella St. John?
I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking,
"Do I want to be known as
the man who orchestrated
"an affordable and
unlimited supply of energy
"that propelled mankind
"into the future?
(creepy music)
"Or do I want to be known as the man who
"quit when he got scared?"
We all get scared, Mr. Claxton,
but it's the ones who face their fears
who win in the end.
And the winners write the history books.
And, uh, in yours they'll just say
it was part of the scientific process.
The email
went to a Rita Chetavich.
It's being taken care of as well.
- Still waiting for
that energy story, Nash.
- I need someone from research
to dig up everything they
can on Darren Claxton.
- The former secretary of energy?
- Yeah, DC from D.C.
- Why do you need information on Claxton?
- Looks like the man who's known
for getting things done inside the beltway
is now getting something
done inside Saturn Energy.
- Now that would make
for interesting reading.
Claxton in bed with the energy companies
that he used to regulate?
You know, when Claxton was in office,
he waged a virtual war
against the oil corporations,
accusing them of fixing gas prices.
(rumbling)
These things are getting scary.
- I kind of like them.
- You have one more.
Use it wisely.
(phone beeping)
- Gabby, uh, I did it.
I, I restored the whole report.
You have to read it.
Um, I don't know,
maybe we should meet at the bar again.
I...
(suspicious music)
I think someone's watching me.
(sneaky music)
Uh, okay, listen, call me
as soon as you get this.
(bartender laughs)
(woman laughs)
(suspicious music)
(shouting in a foreign language)
(exploding)
- [Technician] 50% power and holding.
- How long have you known
about Russ's report?
- I thought we were done with that.
- He said someone was after him.
- He's paranoid.
- But if his numbers are correct...
- Please!
Enough.
60% power.
- Go to 60%.
- [Technician] Going to 60.
- We're getting heat in the fixtures.
- [Dr. Eisley] Is it acceptable?
- So far, yes.
- Increase the coolant component by six.
- Increase coolant by six.
We have 60% power and it's steady.
- [Technician] L.A. on standby.
- Cut their power at the target site.
- Cut their power.
- Let there be darkness.
(shadowy music)
- 60% power, still holding.
- Switch to our source at the target site.
- Activate our source.
(uncertain music)
(people applauding)
- Looks like we're in business.
Say goodbye to fossil fuels.
(camera clicks)
(cat meows)
- I've got a weapon!
I'll bust your head open!
- Whoa.
I'm sure you would.
- Who are you?
- I'm a friend of Sara's.
- Name?
- Todd.
- Todd Stafford.
Man, why didn't you say so?
You guys have to tell me
the next time you run off like that.
How does she expect me to feed the cat
if you don't tell anyone you're leaving?
- Yeah, right, sorry, I...
She'll, um...
We'll, we'll be back in a couple of days.
- You're better looking
than Sara described you.
What are you doing here?
- I'm here to get her checkbook.
How crazy is that?
- Pretty crazy, since
she doesn't have one!
She calls banks
(muffled screaming)
(smashing)
- My camera!
(muffled screaming)
(smashing)
- Who are you?
- Matt Nash, Examiner.
Relax a second, please.
I'm an investigative reporter.
The picture's a little old.
- Fine, you're a reporter.
That doesn't explain
what you're doing here.
- Sara, Todd, and Joel are missing,
and I'm just trying to
find out what happened.
- What do you mean what happened?
They always disappear for a day or so.
I pick up her mail and feed the cat.
Not very good at the
investigative part, are you?
- Apparently not.
- (laughs) What are you good at?
(phone rings)
That's my phone.
- You better answer it.
- I guess I should.
(phone ringing)
(foreboding music)
(door opening)
- Back to feed the...
(punching)
(grunting)
(crashing)
(gunshot fires)
(grunting)
(punching)
(thrilling techno music)
(smashing)
(man cries out)
(metallic whooshing)
(thuds)
(man cries out)
(glass shattering)
- [Man] Hey girl.
- Hey.
Konichiwa.
- Rita Chetavich?
- Yeah.
- We'd like to talk to you.
- [Rita] Who are you?
- It's about Sara Rose.
- Is she okay?
- Can we step outside?
- I don't think so.
What are you doing?
- Hey, he's got a gun!
(gunshot fires)
(people screaming)
Get down!
(gunshots firing)
(people screaming)
(cars crashing)
(Rita whimpering)
(tires squealing)
(cars crashing)
(crazy techno music)
(car horn honking)
(tires squealing)
(cars crashing)
(alarms whirring)
(driver shouts)
- Yeah.
Same one as the other two.
(phone rings)
Yeah?
- Matt!
It's me, Rita!
From WSG!
- Rita?
- They're trying to kill me!
(tires squealing)
I came to the Fiji Bar,
and they tried to grab me!
(Rita sobbing)
(phone breaking up)
- Wait wait, wait a second.
No, say it again.
(tires squealing)
- They're right behind me!
Hello?
- Rita, I can't hear you!
- I'm driving!
Help!
- What?
- Hello?
Hello?
(phone breaking up)
Matt!
- Rita!
- Matt, hello?
(crashing)
(people screaming)
- Rita!
(crashing)
(tires squealing)
(man screams)
(people screaming)
(crashing)
(electricity buzzing)
(exploding)
(crashing)
(people screaming)
(sparks zapping)
(dramatic music)
(car horns honking)
(crashing)
(people screaming)
(frenzied music)
(tires squealing)
(car horns honking)
(crashing)
(tires squealing)
(Rita screams)
(crashing)
(exploding)
(electricity buzzing)
(phone ringing)
Rita?
- [Travis] I see you're all right.
- Who's this?
- [Travis] Travis Gentry.
- Oh, I thought you were...
- [Travis] It's time to
take your energy story
to the public.
(phone rings)
(speaking in a foreign language)
- [Matt] Hello?
- Mr. Nash?
- [Matt] Who is this?
- It's Gabriella St. John.
- [Matt] Gabriella, are you okay?
- I want to talk.
- Not the case.
- [DC] Well then what is the case?
- It was an accident.
- There are witnesses.
- You want me to, uh...
- What do you think this is?
This is a business.
We do not have shootouts in public places.
We are not outlaws.
- Aren't we?
(somber music)
- Los Angeles and Orange County
experienced an earthquake
measuring nearly 6.0 on the Richter scale.
Seismologists at Cal Tech say
the epicenter of the
earthquake was located
in the San Fernando Valley.
Although damage control began
almost immediately after the quake,
FEMA has not yet released an
official number of fatalities.
The hardest hit areas
(knocking on door)
are Downtown Los Angeles.
- [Matt] Hi.
- Hi.
- Come on in.
(sirens wailing)
- Earthquake?
- Something like that.
Have a seat.
I'd offer you a drink, but
my glasses are all broken.
- Russ McCullough is dead.
They blew up a bar, and he was in it.
- He is?
- Research, Saturn Energy.
He told me that they were after him.
He told me.
He told me, and I didn't believe him.
- Who's after him, Saturn Energy?
- He had a report about the tests,
but, uh, I don't know.
- What tests?
- We're developing a new energy source,
hot fusion.
Hydrogen deterium and tritium gases
energized through seven million ampheres
through a system of high
magnetic fields and lasers.
- Heh.
- The work we are doing
out there is so important.
The clean energy we are
producing could change the world.
- What does the report say?
- Byproduct heat from our test
is directed straight into the earth.
That's normal.
But the test had numbers.
They pointed to a previously
undetected hairline fault
under the research facility.
The heat could be going into it.
- Causing the earthquakes.
- We've only been running at
a fraction of what we can do.
If Russ is right, a full-powered
test could trigger a quake
that could kill millions of people.
- That's enough for me.
- It's not conclusive.
Russ had just finished
rebuilding his report.
Now there's no proof.
- Maybe there is.
(strange music)
(glass breaking)
- What's that?
(ominous music)
(punching)
(grunting)
(man shouts)
(thudding)
(grunting)
(active music)
Nash!
(uncertain music)
(labored breathing)
You lost the disc?
That could've been our proof.
- If we shut down the
test, we won't need proof.
- I need it.
- Okay, I'll show it to you.
(Gabriella clears her throat)
- May I help you?
- Yes, I'm up from the, uh,
company's Mexico facility.
I have some last-minute research
before the test tonight.
- Kind of late, huh?
- Tell me about it. (laughs)
(Abbott laughs)
- Uh, you have your ID?
- Oh.
- Thank you.
(beeps)
Okay.
All right, I'll have to,
uh, give you an escort.
- Oh, that's okay, I know where I'm going.
- Uh, Miss, uh, St. John.
Uh, company policy.
- Yeah, sure.
(elevator dings)
- Now, um, you have your key, right?
- Uh, no.
They didn't give me one.
- Oh, they always do that.
All right, listen, hang on
here and I'll go get a key.
(mysterious music)
- Nash, I slipped the guard.
We have to move fast.
(sneaky music)
(guard whistling)
(elevator dings)
- Hello?
Miss St. John?
(suspicious music)
Leron.
Leron!
- This should be it.
- This should be what?
- Your proof.
(beeping)
(machine whirring)
(haunting music)
- What is it?
(surprised music)
- Blood.
- Uh, Mr. Zendon, we...
(determined rock music)
- And this is what's left?
- Unfortunately.
This enough to convince you?
Good, now we need...
(Gabriella gasps)
(men grunting)
(punching)
(wild techno music)
(gunshot fires)
- Nash?
(dreadful music)
(sharp breathing)
(Zendon grunts)
(body thuds)
(energetic techno music)
- Hey, hey, stop!
Stop!
(tentative music)
(workers chattering)
- It's dead.
- [Man With Hat] For now.
- You bought at least another decade.
- [Man With Hat] Here.
We have some work for you in the gulf.
You leave tomorrow.
(perplexed music)
(phone beeping)
I want you to raise the price of our crew
to another 10% on the spot market.
Very good.
- New car, Miss St. John?
- Just a loaner.
Mine's in the shop.
- Would you pull over the side, please?
- Why?
- [Guard] We are supposed to
hold you here at the gate.
- Whose orders?
- Mr. Clemens.
- But, but that's ridiculous.
I'm part of the test team.
- Who is he?
(dogs barking)
(shouts in foreign language)
(tires squealing)
- She called ahead.
She's on her way.
- We're going up to full power tonight.
Gabriella has to be here.
It's everything she's worked for.
- I'm sorry, Dr. Eisley,
but you're going to have
to carry on without her.
- [Matt] Pretty nifty backdoor, huh?
- Oh my god.
- What?
- This is a coolant tunnel.
- Is that bad?
- Very.
- Release maximum coolant.
All sectors, go to 30%.
(typing)
- Coolant released.
(alarm wailing)
- What is it?
- If we don't shut the coolant off,
we're gonna drown in here.
(siren wailing)
(beeping)
- 50%.
There's a drop in the coolant.
Where did that come from?
- Doctor, we're getting
massive heat in the fixtures.
Without that coolant, the
system will destroy itself.
- We have to lower it.
- Go to 70%.
- But Doctor!
- 70%!
(typing)
(beeping)
(suspenseful music)
What's the coolant reading?
- Still dropping.
- It's in the red.
- 80%!
(electricity buzzing)
- I think Eisley will listen to me.
It's DC I'm worried about.
- I'll deal with mister beltway.
You just get in there and stop the test.
- The control room is this way.
DC's office is up there.
(electricity buzzing)
- I said 80!
- But Doctor, we can't.
- Stop the tests.
- [Dr. Eisley] Gabriella!
- This facility is on
a fault line, Doctor.
We are causing these earthquakes.
- No, no, those stress
equations are anomalies.
80%.
- The report is conclusive.
- Russ is not well, I told you that.
- Russ is dead.
They've killed him.
- I'm working on a new story,
a byline,
and you're the subject.
- Can I ask what it's about?
- I think I'll open with the
three murders at Saturn Energy.
- Sensationalism.
Of course that's what you're good at,
even if the story's not true.
- It's all true.
- Oh is that right?
Can I ask what your proof is?
- I saw it with my own eyes.
There was blood all over the place.
- That's terrible,
but go to the police with that, tell them!
90%, 90%!
- Don't do this, Doctor.
Please.
Doctor!
- Well Mr. Nash, it seems you've got us.
I guess the fact that you broke in here
and threatened us with a gun
doesn't diminish the
credibility of your proof.
- That's a chance I'm willing to take.
- You know, Mr. Nash,
you and I
are a lot more alike than you know.
(electricity buzzing)
- It's peaking.
- We're gonna break apart!
(rumbling)
(electricity buzzing)
(exploding)
(grunting)
(gunshot fires)
(crashing)
(workers screaming)
(alarm buzzing)
(exploding)
(crashing)
(people screaming)
(men grunting)
(exploding)
(punching)
(grunting)
(people screaming)
(crashing)
(alarm beeping)
(grunts)
(glass shattering)
(body thudding)
(crashing)
(exploding)
(woman screams)
(people screaming)
(crashing)
(dramatic music)
(exploding)
(zapping)
(crashing)
- Oh no!
(woman screams)
(crashing)
(exploding)
(woman screams)
(crashing)
(exploding)
(man groans)
(crashing)
(people shouting)
- [Dr. Eisley] Gabriella, get out of here.
- No, I can get it.
I can get it.
(crashing)
- Gabriella!
Please go!
- I'm so sorry.
- Don't be.
Our science was right.
My method was wrong.
Go.
Finish our research.
- Miss St. John!
(crashing)
(suspenseful music)
I'm gonna kill her!
(crashing)
(malevolent music)
(gunshots firing)
(exploding)
(scary music)
(grunting)
(punching)
(Matt cries out)
(frenzied music)
(Matt choking)
(gunshot fires)
(gurgling)
(body thuds)
(sirens wailing)
(speaking in a foreign language)
(gunshot fires)
(car horn honking)
(speaking in a foreign language)
- Are you okay?
- I could use a band-aid or two.
- I am so sorry about everything.
- Did Eisley make it?
- I was right about you.
- You were?
- I knew you'd be trouble.
You know, when you run this story,
you're gonna destroy Dr.
Eisley's name and hard work
and my ability to carry it on.
- You were right about another thing.
There's no story here.
(thrilling techno music)
(frenzied techno music)
(mysterious music)