[seagulls squawking]
[ambient music playing]
We'll need the identification
of the body.
Get somebody on that, Charlie.
Not the best day
in the world for it.
Not exactly of our choosing.
Uh, it's just that everyone
in Strathcroy
had been up all night
at the big dance.
What? Including the deceased?
More than likely, I'd say.
-Everyone.
-Oh, everyone?
Is that a fact now?
[man 1] How long's the body
been in the water?
[man 2] No more
than a couple of hours.
[man 1] What did you think?
Accident, was it?
[man 2] Too early to say.
[ambient music playing]
[police radio chatter]
[horse snorts]
[goats bleating]
[ambient music playing]
[Edmund panting]
[beeps]
[Virginia] Henry.
Henry, what's it to be,
muesli or porridge?
[Edie] Good morning, Mrs. Aird.
You'll catch your death
without a coat.
Oh, nonsense, Edie.
It's a beautiful day.
Do-- you should let me do
your shopping for you.
Oh, Edie, don't fuss.
The weather's much to good
to waste.
[dramatic music playing]
[laughter]
[boy] Oh, no.
[dramatic music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
-[Violet] Good morning.
-[Isobel] Hi.
How are you?
Violet Aird.
Visitors from America.
-Oh. How do you do?
-How do you do?
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you too.
-Smile please.
-Hello. Oh.
-We're going to Gleneagles.
-Are you?
Well, I hope the weather
lasts for you.
Excuse me, Isobel.
Oh.
[woman] That's great.
That's good.
-Bye.
-Goodbye.
-[woman] Bye.
-Bye.
[woman] Do you
and Lord Balmerino
actually own the village?
[Isobel] Oh, not anymore.
The estate is mostly
rented out now.
The moor has gone to a
grouse-shooting syndicate
run by Edmund Aird.
You've just met his mother.
[man] Any connection
with Aird Electronics?
Yes. It's his firm.
You might meet his wife.
She's from your part
of the world.
[ambient music playing]
All right. I'm off.
Midday flight.
[Virginia] Okay.
Well, take care.
-I love you.
-You too.
Do you mind taking Henry
to Edie's house?
No, if he's ready.
[Virginia] Great.
-Henry.
-Henry, come on.
Bye, sweetie. Mwah.
Have a great day.
-Have a good journey.
-Thanks.
Come on.
[Henry] Bye.
Love you, baby.
[Henry] See you this afternoon.
Here. Henry, get me the office,
will you?
[phone ringing]
Hello, Balnaird.
Hi, mommy.
Well, hello, Henry.
-[Henry] You okay?
-Yes. I'm doing very well.
-How are you?
-[Henry] I'm fine.
-I love you, mommy.
-You have a great day.
I love you, sweetie.
-[Henry] Bye, mommy.
-[chuckles] Bye.
Morning, Vi.
Hello, Archie.
Oh, feeding the 5,000?
Uh, well, the tourist season
is upon us already.
Oh, indeed. I just met them.
What would my father
have thought, eh?
Lord Balmerino running errands?
What's the world coming to?
He'd probably have said,
"My son's a bloating idiot."
Bye, Vi.
-Vi.
-Oh.
Oh, let me drop you home.
No. I'm fine, Verena.
Nonsense. This shopping's
far too heavy.
Actually, I have a favor
to ask you.
Oh? Well, what's it this time?
Library petition,
off-road horses?
Agnes and I are planning a dance
for Katy's 21st.
A really big one,
with a proper band
for the reels
and highland fling.
A disco for Katy's
London friends.
A marquee.
[Violet] Heavens.
When is this to be?
September, I thought, the 16th.
The day after my birthday.
So the dance can be
your birthday party as well.
Oh, I always have a picnic
up by the loch.
Hmm, personally,
I always find the loch
rather gloomy, don't you?
Well, I find it beautiful.
The loch's very special.
I'm inviting everyone.
The Blaires,
the Ferguson Crombies,
the Melbournes,
Lord and Lady McCliston, I hope.
Then there's you, of course.
[Violet] I thought
you had a favor to ask me.
Yes.
I want to send an invitation
to Archie's sister.
Pandora? But...
[dramatic music playing]
But she was long
before your time, surely.
Yes. We are newcomers after all.
We've only lived here 10 years.
Look.
Vi, my dear, I wouldn't dream
of asking personal questions,
but, well, Pandora's name
comes up from time to time,
and there's this stiffening.
I assume there's some
ancient scandal
but nobody will say anything.
You Scots are so frightfully
well-behaved, aren't you?
In public, anyway.
Oh, are we?
Biscuit, Verena?
You're doing it now.
Look, this is
a little awkward.
It seems that Lord
and Lady McCliston
met Pandora at some gallery
in Monte Carlo
and took quite a shine to her.
Well, I've rather given them
the impression that--
Pandora's coming to the dance.
[Verena] They'll definitely
be expecting to see her.
And I rather hope that you...
Certainly not.
She hasn't been here
for nearly 20 years.
I really don't think
this is a very good idea,
Verena.
Yes. Well...
Alexa's still living
it out in London, is she?
[upbeat music playing]
[Martin] Hi.
Can we join you?
My name is Martin.
-Oh.
-Hi.
I'm a designer,
fabrics and textiles.
-Really?
-Yes.
Hope you didn't design that tie.
[laughs]
[upbeat music playing]
[mellow music playing]
[woman] Come on, Alexa.
We're going on.
[indistinct chatter]
[woman] Hurry up, Alexa.
There's a stack of logs
to split.
I best get on with it.
I hate it when the change over
is on the same day.
It's such a rush.
And the silver needs cleaning.
I'm good at that.
I'll give you a hand later.
Won't be long.
[doorbell buzzes]
[Neil] Hi, Alexa.
Uh, remember me?
From the nightclub.
Hmm, no.
[door closes]
[doorbell buzzes]
[Alexa] Oh, great.
-[Isobel] Darling, tea.
-Yes.
I'll, um... I'll put it down.
[Archie] Leave it, darling.
I'll do it.
Oh, it's all right.
It's really not that heavy.
Here you are, Neil.
Thank you.
I recognize this face.
[Alexa] Possibly.
It's my father.
Aird? Edmund Aird?
Yeah.
Of Aird Electronics, yeah?
Yes. I don't usually
tell people.
[Neil] Oh. I'm impressed.
And, uh, this must be
your mother.
No, no, no, no.
That's my stepmother.
My-- my mother died
when I was really young.
I'm sorry.
-Um...
-Well...
Look, um, thanks for the drink.
Um, I better get going.
Not at all.
Thanks very much for bringing
my address book around.
I'm sorry I was so rude
on the doorstep.
That's all right.
Not the first time
I had a front door
slammed in my face,
nor the last, I should think.
-Goodbye.
-Um...
I was just gonna get myself
something to eat.
You could stay for some supper,
if you like.
Well, uh, thank you.
Yeah. I'd like that very much.
[cheerful music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Here we are. Just in time.
I think that's
your bus over there.
Just a moment.
It's been lovely having you.
-Thank you so much.
-I do hope you come back.
It's so nice.
[indistinct chatter]
-Oh.
-Oh. Hello, dear.
Isobel?
Verena.
The new brochures.
Ah. Rather good.
-Don't you think?
-Yes.
"Stay as a guest
in a private house.
Experience the hospitality
and grandeur
of Scotland's loveliest homes.
Meet as friends,
the ancient families
who live in them."
We're not
an ancient family, Verena.
Ancient enough,
as soon as they hear
Archie's a lord.
Archie's grandfather
had a factory.
No need to go into that, dear.
Ladies and gentleman,
this is Lady Balmerino,
-[man] How do you do?
-your hostess for the next week.
Why don't you all
have another cup of tea?
And I'll tell Lady Balmerino
about the slight change of plan.
Now, Isobel, the thing is,
your two chaps
have had really rather...
-[phone ringing]
-Oh, excuse me.
Verena Steynton.
-[man] Uh, Mrs. Steynton?
-Yes?
-It's about your marquee.
-Oh, yes.
Now, we shall want
your largest marquee.
September the 16th.
Oh, good.
Next Wednesday at 11:00.
Excellent.
Goodbye.
I've been meaning to tell you,
we're giving a dance
for Katy's 21st.
Everyone's coming.
Lord and Lady McCliston.
I hope you and Archie,
of course.
And Lucilla must come.
Well, I don't know about
Lucilla.
She's still wandering
about Europe.
She may not be back
before the end of the summer.
I think you have to be
a little firm, Isobel.
Katy had odd ideas too,
but I told her
the year in Switzerland
and the secretarial course
came first.
She could do anything
after that.
They're children, dear.
Oh, yes.
And I'm thinking
of inviting Pandora.
Pandora?
I don't think
that's a very good idea.
What on Earth's the problem?
Everyone behaves as though
she was some sort
of social outcast.
Nonsense.
She and Archie were very close.
So tell me,
what's all the fuss about?
You knew her.
How would you describe Pandora?
[Isobel] Pandora was...
the most beautiful creature
I've ever seen.
Full of life, high spirits,
dazzling.
Sounds like
the perfect party creature.
Good.
-[Edmund] Mr. Samada.
-[Mr. Samada] Hello.
[Edmund] It's Edmund Aird.
Good morning, Mr. Aird.
Listen, as my colleague
explained to you when you met,
we both have a deal
awaiting signature in Malaysia,
but we need a more positive
reaction from your people.
[Mr. Samada] Well, we have been
very flexible in that point.
Now, we both have the figures.
I think we should settle this
without delay.
I can be in Kuala Lumpur
on, uh...
Friday.
-On Friday.
-Okay. Well,
I believe I can bring
new proposals to the table.
Good then.
Good on Friday.
I'll see you then, yes.
-Goodbye.
-[Mr. Samada] Bye.
George, I'm flying out
to meet Samada.
I've told them
they have to improve the deal.
[George] I've been leaning
on them as hard as I dared.
Yes, I know that.
The point is, so do they.
Malaysians like to speak
to the boss.
It makes a difference.
[George] If you say so.
Jane, the conifer investments,
can you get out all the
correspondence on that?
And make fresh copies
of everything,
including the accountant's
breakdowns.
And, uh, mark one to the
attention of Lord Balmerino.
Oh, and get on
to Temple Hall School.
I want to speak
to the headmaster at home.
Tell him it's urgent.
Edmund.
Look, I understand you stepping
in on the Malaysian deal.
I couldn't swing it
and you saved the day
and I'm grateful to you for it.
But the supercomputer
is my special field.
I've been in it
from the beginning.
Well, we had to ride fast.
Do you realize
how many millions are riding
on this particular set
of signatures?
Yes. I prepared the figures,
if you recall.
I should have taken
the Malaysian meeting.
Look, I'm late
for a meeting, George.
We'll settle it later.
That's exactly the problem.
You're never here.
Edmund, you can't take on
everything yourself.
The company needs you here.
I happen to own
this company, George.
I'm fully aware what it does
and does not need.
Thank you.
Daddy, what's a supercomputer?
Well, that's, uh-- that's
rather difficult to explain.
But, basically, they all compute
at an unbelievable rate.
But even that is
all old hat now.
It's all Pentium technology now.
Pentium? Oh, I learned
about that in school.
Good.
Here, put that in the car,
would you?
You know, he really
coming along very well.
I'm not sure he's getting
enough stimulation
at his local school.
When I get back, we'll look
into that whole question
of boarding school again.
[Virginia] But you know
how I feel about that.
[Edmund] Yeah, but think
about the boarding schools...
[Virginia] Edmund.
[Edmund] Boarding school.
Boarding school.
[computer beeping]
Wow.
[Henry] I don't really
have to go
to boarding school, do I?
[Virginia] Try not to worry
about it now.
I'll talk to your dad
when he gets home.
[Henry] If dad bought you
a supercomputer,
you could ask it to do
millions of things.
It sort of breaks down
the questions into little bits,
and all the bits get put back
together at the same time.
It's magic.
[Violet] Henry,
it sounds very clever.
I'm going to come up and see
your computer in a moment,
but I just want to have a word
with your mother.
[Henry] Okay.
-[Violet] Virginia.
-Yeah?
Are you all right?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
You know, with Edmund gone
all the time.
He mentioned, uh,
boarding school
for Henry again.
I guess we have to have
a proper discussion.
Discussion? With my son?
Oh, dear.
Would you like me to try and...
No, no, no. I can handle it.
It's just that,
even after all this time, I--
sometimes, I still feel...
I feel like an outsider.
[dramatic music playing]
[Isobel] You're about to see
another of Strathcroy's
favorite lost causes.
Although it seems help is at
hand from the grouse syndicate.
The village church.
Archie's grandfather built it,
but it's about to fall down,
-I fear.
-[woman] Oh, dear.
Oh, there's no need to worry.
I don't think it's likely
to collapse this very minute.
[car engine rumbles]
[Archie] Hello, Virginia.
-[Virginia] How are you?
-Hmm. Fine, thanks.
-Is Edmund home?
-No, he's not.
He's away on business.
Kuala Lumpur of all places.
Oh. Well, I wonder if you could
give him a message for me?
I've had a letter
from the grouse syndicate.
What letter?
Well, they're offering to cover
the cost of the church rewiring.
-[Virginia] Really?
-How marvelous.
Yeah. That's great.
Well, no, I'm not
entirely happy about it.
In fact, I mean,
the grouse syndicate
is a commercial activity.
We have to ask ourselves
what they want in return.
Well, I'm afraid
you'll have to talk to Edmund
-when he gets back.
-No. Uh, I mean,
I really rather had enough
of the grouse syndicate
behaving as if
they own the place.
Which, in a way, they...
Which, in a way, they do.
Point taken, Vi.
Um, anyway, would you thank
Edmund for his offer?
I wouldn't like him
to think me rude.
Well, I'll mention it to him.
Although, I don't know
what he'll say.
Thanks. Well, I'll see you soon.
Vi, can I give you a lift?
Oh, I think I'll walk.
Thanks.
Right. Oh, right. Well,
is Edie not with you today?
[Violet] Poor Edie has got
rather a lot in her mind
at the moment.
Remember her cousin, Lottie?
[Archie] Oh, heavens, yes.
That awful woman used to
work here for a while.
Used to snoop around
hiding behind doors,
just smashing the crockery.
That's the one.
Dotty Lottie,
we used to call her.
I must say she gave me
the shivers.
I had visions of her rushing in
with a carving knife.
[Virginia] Oh.
Lottie, that's getting
on everyone's nerves a bit.
Could you not stop it, now?
I like the sound it makes.
[Archie] Nice to see you,
Virginia.
-[Virginia] Bye-bye.
-Bye.
-Archie.
-Something on your mind, Vi?
You ever hear from Pandora?
Occasionally.
The odd postcard, you know.
Verena Steynton's planning
to invite her to the dance.
What? She can't do that.
If she does, who'll tell Edmund?
Well, she won't come so there's
no point in discussing it.
Archie, it's been 20 years.
You were so close once.
Can you honestly say
you don't want to see her?
Verena said something to me
which actually made sense.
She said, "You Scots
are so horribly well-behaved."
Don't you think
there's something to be said
for actually blowing up
once in a while?
No. Lord, no.
Heat without illumination
is not very useful.
Bye, Vi.
[dramatic music playing]
[grunts]
[Virginia] Go on out.
I'll feed you later.
[Edmund] Hello? I'm back.
Hello. You're early.
-Mm.
I don't wanna get butter
on you.
Hmm. Hey, that looks good.
Where's Henry?
Not back yet.
Good. I wanna talk to you.
I didn't come directly home.
I went down to Temple Hall
to see the headmaster.
-Why?
-Oh, to talk things over
and get things settled.
What things?
Temple Hall can take Henry
in September.
As a boarder?
[scoffs] Well, he could
hardly attend as a day boy.
I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
-What?
-You had no right
to go there without me.
Henry is my child
as much as he is yours.
And you go sneaking off
behind my back
without even a word?
I did not sneak off
and I'm telling you now.
Well, now it is completely done.
Look, Henry goes back to
the village school in two weeks.
He's getting on
really well there.
He's made great friends.
Edmund, did you
even think about that?
Listen, the place came up
at the very last moment,
so I decided...
You decided?
Why do you always make
the decisions?
Oh, because I always have,
I suppose.
Look, you have always known
that I don't want Henry
to go away to school.
Not yet.
He's too young.
-I went.
-Oh, yes.
I know you went when
you were eight years old,
but why should he?
It's barbaric.
It's crazy to send little kids
away from home.
Look, he can go to Strathcroy
until he's 12,
then he can go away
to boarding school.
But not yet, no.
[Edmund] But why mock
him out as an oddity?
I know that American kids
seem to...
[Virginia] This has nothing
to do with being American.
This is what any normal mother
feels about her child.
It is you who's on
the wrong track, Edmund,
but you could never even admit
that possibility, could you?
You're just
thinking of yourself.
No. I am thinking of Henry.
Henry's just eight years old.
He's barely had
a good nursery.
He needs his home.
He needs us.
[Edmund] Of course,
it'll be hard on Henry.
It's hard on all of them.
It's competitive and tough.
And the sooner they
realize that, the better.
In my view, Henry's far
too dependent on you.
-[Virginia] I'm his mother.
-Yes,
and you're behaving
like a spoiled child,
and maybe that's my fault.
I think it's time
you damn well grew up!
Bull shit!
[door slams]
[dramatic music playing]
[thunder rumbles]
[Isobel] Quickly, everybody.
Get inside. That's it.
[indistinct chatter]
[Archie] Now, you said
you'd like to see
the countryside
at another time of year.
Well, this is how it looks
in September.
[woman] You know, Archie,
you could put all this on video
and make your life
a whole lot easier.
[dramatic music playing]
Good gracious.
Well, this isn't just
old family stuff.
I'd forgotten
it was on this roll.
[Violet] Who's that?
[Archie] Ah. Well, now.
That's my sister, Pandora.
[man] Reservations.
Can I help you?
Yes.
I'd like to book a flight.
Your first flight to London
in the morning.
[man] Passenger's name, please?
Name is Aird.
Virginia Aird.
[man] Will you be paying
by credit card?
Yeah.
[dramatic music playing]
[Archie groaning]
[explosions]
[Archie screams]
[Isobel] It's all right.
It's all right. Shh.
It's just a nightmare.
Shh, shh.
It's all right.
It's all right. Shh.
Oh.
Come on, Lottie.
Let's get you to bed.
Come on. Come on.
Don't forget, your cousin, Edie,
is coming to take
you home tomorrow.
[dramatic music playing]
Come on, Edie.
You're getting so fat.
No wonder
that you can't keep up.
[bird caws]
[suspenseful music playing]
What do you keep
that rubbish for?
Edmund Aird.
I wouldn't sleep easy in my bed
if I were him.
And Pandora,
the wicked bitch.
What are you talking
about, Lottie?
I know what I know.
That woman's no better
than the murderers.
-Mr. Cocklin.
-[Mr. Cocklin] Hello?
We will not go into unfortunate
matter of the misprint.
That is behind us.
But this...
[Mr. Cocklin]
What's that, madame?
You have printed the invitations
on the wrong side of the card.
Are you awake?
[Neil] No.
-Oh.
-You are now.
[Neil] I'm gonna get you
for that.
Look what I got.
[Neil] What's that?
An invitation to a ball.
[Neil] Great.
You gonna go?
Hmm, No, I don't think so.
Why not?
Because I don't want to go
without you.
You haven't told them
about me, have you?
-You little ratter.
-Maybe not. Maybe not.
They couldn't cope with it.
Well, you're not trying,
are you?
I know that.
What's-- what's the problem?
[sighs] It's just...
They wouldn't approve of me,
would they?
I don't believe this.
It's... it's just there would be
a full-scale inquisition,
that's all.
Would you come?
Tribal dances
on the grass moors?
I'd rather shoot
myself in the foot.
Lovely.
Letter from Lucilla.
[Isobel] Oh, good.
I hope there would be.
And the stiff one,
hand-delivered,
looks like a summons
for the queen.
That must be Verena's invitation
-to the dance.
-Then two more of the same.
One for Lucilla and another
for Pandora, to be forwarded.
I told Verena
it was not a good idea.
Open Lucilla's letter
That's much more important.
"Darling, mom and dad...
just to let you know I'm fine
and having a great time.
I'm traveling with an
Australian boy called Jeff,
a sheep farmer farming
around Europe.
Might nip down to the Riviera
to see if Pandora's still there.
I'm bit short of cash.
Any chance of a loan?"
And there's a bit about a
Matisse exhibition she went to.
Well, farming around Europe.
-[sighs] Sheep farmer.
-Hmm.
Might be worst, I suppose.
I wish she'd come home.
Who?
Lucilla.
Oh, yes. Of course.
Well, I'll get a
check off to her.
[dramatic music playing]
[Pandora] Don't you
understand, Archie?
I'm having a baby.
I can't believe
you won't help me.
[Archie] Did you ever think
of anyone apart from yourself?
-[Alexa] Virginia. Hi.
-Hi.
Here.
[Alexa] Excellent.
Oh, let me help you.
Come in. Come in.
I didn't even know
you were in London.
A spur of the moment thing.
I decided to do
-a bit of shopping.
-A bit?
You got half of
Knightsbridge in here.
[laughs]
Oh, wow. This is gorgeous.
Yeah.
How's Fa?
He's fine.
I thought you'd given up?
Oh, I have, I have.
This is temporary.
I've been a bit frazzled lately.
You all right?
Yeah. Sure.
[phone rings]
Oh, sorry.
Hello?
Oh, hi. Um...
yeah, uh, look, Friday night,
I'm really not sure
what I'm doing at the moment.
I didn't mean to pry.
So, um, when did he move in?
A couple of weeks ago.
Is it serious?
I hope so.
Well, you better tell Edmund
before somebody else does.
Men can be trouble gossips.
Actually, I was gonna ask.
Could you tell pa and gran?
Would it be really
difficult for you?
No. Vi takes
everything in stride.
And as for your father,
at the moment,
I don't really care
what he thinks.
I knew there was
something wrong.
Here I've been banging on
about my love life.
Oh, it's all right.
We've just come across
a cold war situation
at the moment.
Oh, God. That isn't why
you're here, is it?
No. I'm here because
I wanted to cheer myself up
by taking it out
on his credit card.
It'll sort itself out.
Edmund's made up his mind.
And when pa makes up his mind,
it's like talking
to a brick wall.
He'd be more human
if just once in his life
he really screwed up
and had to admit he was wrong.
Let's have some of this wine,
shall we?
Edmund, anything wrong?
Hmm.
Just thought I'd drop by,
have a chat.
Well, I'm sorry you didn't feel
you could accept
our offer of help.
Forgive me, Edmund, but your
colleagues are businessmen,
not a charity.
What's in it for them?
You are an absonant bastard,
Archie. It isn't the Syndicate.
Do you think they give a damn
about what happens
in the village,
all they're concerned about
is the grouse shooting.
The church rewiring was my idea.
I was thinking of you.
I talked to them into it.
Good PR I said.
And you made me look stupid.
-Well, I'm very sorry.
-Well, you should be.
You are hardly in a position
to be so choosy
over the offer of a gift.
Well, now,
that's an interesting thought,
the role of gifts.
A Trojan horse can come
in many shapes.
You were always
a stubborn bastard, Archie.
I didn't think you were a fool.
I'll be on my way.
Edmund, I'm sorry,
I'm being unfair.
If the offer still stands...
[sighs]
It does.
Oh, and...
I meant to give you this.
Take a look at it.
I value your opinion.
Heart of a plantation.
Well, now, one of those
get-rich-quick schemes
for absentee landlords, is it?
There you go again,
jumping into conclusions.
The tax loophole
was closed years ago.
This could be
real local benefit.
Will you at least read it?
Oh, I'll read it.
Good heavens.
What was Edmund doing here?
-And what's that?
-Looks harmless, doesn't it?
But I think it's a Trojan horse.
[Alexa] Oh, right. That's the
new Recluso film, isn't it?
Did you like it?
Neil. I didn't hear you.
Virginia, Neil Keeling.
So this is Neil.
-Hello, Virginia.
-Hello.
My stepmother.
You're welcome
to the dance though.
No, 'cause I'm gonna
hate it out there.
'Cause of all those
wide open spaces,
and the gale-force winds,
and men in skirts.
You know, I can't cope
with that.
Long prayers and lots of Scots.
The sun has been known
to shine, hasn't it?
Barkley Square please.
I'm gonna get my hair done.
-Bye, sweetie.
-Take care. Pamper yourself.
-Thanks.
-You will come though?
Only if you save me a tango.
-Uh... I promise.
-You heard her.
She promised.
You heard that, didn't you?
-Evening, Mrs. Ishak.
-Hello.
Listen, I'm in a bit of a hurry.
I need a bunch of flowers.
You know, the sort of thing
my wife likes.
Of course.
-[Lottie] Mr. Aird.
-Hmm.
I've seen you
around the village,
but you're always
in such a hurry.
Never had a chance
to have a chin-wag.
Yes.
Remember me?
Lottie Carstairs.
I used to work for old
Lady Balmerino for a while.
Yes. Uh, yes, of course,
I remember you.
I was there when Lord Balmerino
was getting married.
Well, that, uh--
that was all a long time ago.
What times they were, eh?
You're still married
to Caroline,
and Pandora buzzing about
like a bee after honey,
and then running off.
But then she was always
a bit of a bad penny.
You and I know that.
Don't worry, Mr. Aird,
you more than anyone--
Sorry, Mr. Aird,
I couldn't find any paper.
[bell chimes]
Oh. That's all right.
Just put it on the account,
will you?
I think...
Oh, it's a wee bit
chilly tonight, Henry.
Would you put a match
to the fire.
[suspenseful music playing]
Henry? What is it?
Do you think Edie
is going to be all right?
I don't think Edie
is in actual danger.
[sighs]
Lottie.
[suspenseful music playing]
-[glass breaks]
-[screams]
Just slipped out of my fingers.
I'll be at boarding school
on my birthday.
Won't be the same without you.
[sighs]
I don't want to go.
Mommy doesn't want me
to go either.
She'll miss you.
They both will.
They've been quarreling.
I know.
How do you know?
I may be old, darling,
but I'm not stupid.
And your father is my son.
And I'd like to shake
him sometimes.
[airplane engine rumbles]
[tires screeches]
Did you get a dress
for the dance?
Yeah.
And I got my hair done.
Yeah, I noticed.
I like it.
Did you see Alexa?
Yes.
Promise you won't go
all Victorian on me.
I have some news for you.
She met a guy
and she's crazy about him.
She wasn't sure
how you were gonna take it,
so she gave me the job
of telling you.
He's some sort of
financial whiz kid.
Venture capitalist,
I think what she said.
Ha. Definitely a charmer.
[Edmund] Oh, you mean
a ladies' man?
[Virginia] I guess you
could put it that way.
[Edmund] Alexa's innocent.
Now, she's met up
with some city slicker.
-I don't want her to get hurt
-Nor do I.
But don't you think she's old
enough to take her own risks.
Well, she's hardly
in the position to judge.
Prince Charming can come in
pretty funny packaging.
I mean, my parents weren't
exactly over the moon
about some Brit with a kid
on his hands.
I'm much too old for you, huh?
[sighs]
You took on a lot.
I loved you.
That was the miracle.
Thank you.
Edmund...
I know this is tough on you,
but you have to let go.
All I want is to do
the right thing.
Edmund...
I have something to say.
I think that you're making
a big mistake about Henry.
He's far too young
to be sent away.
But I don't want...
[dramatic music playing]
[sighs]
...this to go on between us.
I've missed you...
and I do love you.
[exhales]
I shouldn't have settled
the matter without...
-consulting you.
-No.
You shouldn't have.
[dramatic music playing]
Truce?
On one condition,
the day that Henry
has to go to Temple Hall,
you take him.
I can't face him.
I'll take him.
I promise.
[dramatic music playing]
Here.
Thank you.
Oh...
coming home present.
Oh.
Put them on for me.
[dramatic music playing]
[switch clicks]
[man] Move a bit
to your left, Gary.
[Gary] That's enough?
[man] All right. That's fine.
Just...
[dramatic music playing]
[Archie] Edmund.
[Edmund] Oh, hello, Archie.
Have you had the chance
to read my--
No. I've not read
your presentation.
I see little point in doing so.
What was all that guff
about valuing my opinion,
since you've obviously
gone ahead with your dreadful
carnival scheme
without my valued opinion.
[Edmund] Well,
if that's way you feel--
Well, at least,
I know where we stand.
[slams phone]
[tires screeches]
Mommy, you're back.
Hello. Hmm.
Hmm. How are you?
-I'm all right.
-Hmm. I've missed you.
[chuckles]
Keep it. Cheers.
[classical music playing]
[laughter]
Alexa, I'm so sorry, darling.
-I'm late--
-[Jasmine] Neil? It's fine.
-Jasmine?
-Oh, what a surprise?
Haven't seen you
since you went off to New York.
[Neil] Well, no.
I've been, uh...
busy.
Hey, whoa. Hey,
these catalog numbers or prices?
And since when have you
been interested in art?
Hmm, I'm not really.
Alexa is the patron here.
[Alexa] Hi.
Right. That explains it.
All right. When you see
anything you like,
-just give me a wave.
-[Alexa] This one is beautiful.
Really exquisite.
Oh. I've got the man
who painted it over here.
Follow me.
Barry?
Alexa, meet Barry Miller.
-Hi. Alexa Aird.
-[Barry] Hi. How are you?
-I'm a big fan of your work.
-Oh.
I'll show you a piece
you might like.
-Over here.
-Jasmine?
-Yes?
-Can you keep a secret?
I don't know.
What have you got in mind?
[indistinct chatter]
[car engine rumbling]
[birds chirping]
-Oh, I think that's Archie.
-Oh, it is.
Hello, Archie.
Lord Balmerino,
I was looking for you.
You'll have
to excuse me, Lottie.
I'm rather busy.
[car engine starts]
I'd have looked after the baby.
I wanted to.
They wouldn't listen.
Lottie?
I think it's time
we went home, Lottie.
No. I wanna talk...
-to Lord Balmerino.
-Lottie, dear,
I really think that you should
go home with Edie now.
But why do you come and have
a cup of tea with me one day.
Can we go to Edenborough?
I could do with a bit of life.
Go shopping.
Very well.
We'll arrange an outing.
-Don't forget.
-No, I won't forget.
-Of course, I won't forget.
-[Lottie giggles]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Archie] Oh, Pandora,
don't be such a fool.
He doesn't love you.
And the last thing
he wants is your baby.
[Lottie] Mr. Archie...
I know what to do.
I can help.
[Pandora] I hate you, Archie.
I hate you. I hate you.
I hate you, Archie.
Argh.
-Isobel.
-Come in.
My dear, I'm having
a nervous breakdown.
I know why Napoleon lost
the Battle of Waterloo.
You simply cannot rely
on anyone.
Has Lucilla replied yet?
She has not.
Nor Pandora, I might add.
You can't rely on Pandora
to reply to anything.
But I did have a favor
to ask you.
Could you be a darling
and have a stray man
to stay for the party.
-Of course.
-Oh.
-Who is it?
-Oh, some American.
Katy met him at a dinner
in London.
His wife just died,
and he's over here
for a bit of a holiday.
Poor man.
She thought it would
cheer him up,
but I'm full to the rafters.
-Oh, of course, we will.
-Oh, you're an angel.
-What's his name?
-Yes.
What is his name?
Plucka-- no. Tucker. That's it.
Conrad Tucker.
He's sounds rather sad.
Anyway, I must fly.
No tea?
My dear, I have to put
the band and the pipers,
and something called
a portable disco.
I suppose it'll be some ghastly
young skinhead with spots.
[Isobel] Oh.
I was 15...
when my mother put me
into service.
A half day off a week we had.
No way...
you could meet a young man.
Go to the cinema
or a dance hall.
I'd have liked to have joined
the police force.
Had some fun.
But I didn't know
how to go about it.
Lottie, I think you said you
needed to do some shopping.
I need a yard
of boiling knicker elastic.
The haberdashery will have it.
Well, I really don't know
if they sell...
Oh, dear.
[phone ringing]
Croy.
-Surprise.
-Who is that?
Dad it's me.
Lucilla.
-Where are you?
-I'm in London.
I'm at the Dorchester
of all places.
We'll be with you
tomorrow evening, all of us.
-Come on.
-Get off me, you pig.
Hello?
No, no, no. Not you.
Dad, that was Jeff.
You remember, I wrote about him.
Is there any chance of getting
to Scotland this year?
Shh. Yes. Ugh.
Look, Dad, I've got to go.
Okay. Yes.
Hey, we've got a real surprise
for you.
We'll be coming up with Pandora.
So Lucilla thought
she'd see if Pandora
was still at the same address.
And that was it. She was.
And she invited them to stay.
Then announced that she
would come to the dance,
if they drove back with her.
Why didn't she let us know?
The Dorchester?
Lucilla's never stayed
in a proper hotel in her life.
Couldn't she have chosen
something a little less grand?
[Archie] Well, I don't suppose
Pandora knows
anywhere less grand.
Well, sure beats a sleeping bag.
Jeff, are you really sure
we've got everything...
-Here you go.
-...this time?
Straight in there.
Thanks a lot.
Do you want a hand?
-[man] There you are, sir.
-Yup. There you go.
Thanks very much. Okay.
[door creaks open]
[dramatic music playing]
[Pandora] Dearest Archie,
I can't bear to think
of that last time I saw you.
All those dreadful things
we both said.
That's what you call it,
a problem?
Don't you understand, Archie?
I am having a baby.
I can't believe
you won't help me.
[Archie]
Did you ever think of anyone,
apart from yourself?
[Pandora] Yes.
I'm thinking of Edmund.
I can make him happy.
And you can't stop me.
[dramatic music playing]
[Pandora] I just wanted
to let you know,
the little problem...
no longer exists.
So you can all
breathe again.
The family name is untainted,
and I'm perfectly all right.
Don't worry, darling.
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
-[Isobel] Hello, Vi.
Oh, Isobel.
[Isobel] I think you better
be sitting down for this.
I am sitting down.
Just had the most exhausting day
blabbering with Lottie.
[Isobel] Pandora's coming home
for the dance.
What?
It's true.
Archie said
she'd never come back.
Well, she is.
[sighs]
How extraordinary.
What made her decide
to come now?
Oh, Vi...
I do hope there's not
gonna be trouble.
[car engine rumbles]
[car horn honks]
[Archie] Edmund...
Isobel is giving a lunch party
on Sunday.
She very much hopes you both
would like to come.
Henry too of course.
Forgive me if this
sounds rude, Archie.
But, uh, we all know
where we stand.
You think I'm a shit?
I think you're a fool.
This is not a good basis
for a lunch party.
[Archie] Oh, I thought you
might have heard this,
to be a guest of honor...
Pandora.
Here?
[car door slams]
Why?
Verena invited her to the dance.
She's accepted.
[sighs]
And we're all gonna
have lunch together?
Well, this is grotesque.
Well, you have to meet sometime.
Do we?
[dramatic music playing]
[Henry chuckles]
[Virginia] Give it more
of a spiral this time.
-Yeah, that's good.
-[Henry] Come on. Pass. Pass.
[Henry] Okay. [chuckles]
-Hi.
-[Edmund] Hi.
Mm. I missed you today.
-Hiya.
-You too.
Missed you.
-Wanna have a cup of tea?
-[Edmund] Sure.
That's not American
football, is it?
-[Henry] Yes, it is.
-Yeah.
Whatever happened
to good old rugby?
[Henry] It's much better.
[Edmund] Come on. Here.
Here. Come on. Catch.
[Henry] Hey, come here.
Come here.
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
We have an invitation
for Sunday.
Family lunch at Croy.
I thought you and Archie
we're having a row.
Yes. It's a bit bizarre
but there it is.
The thing is...
Archie's sister has come home.
Oh, that's fantastic.
I'm dying to meet her.
Look, um...
Look, I don't want you to take
this the wrong way, but...
Pandora may not be, uh...
entirely friendly.
It's all in the past now,
but, uh, there were...
-What family feuds?
-[sighs]
Well, some people
harbor grudges, and...
I don't want you to get upset.
Don't worry about me.
After all, I'm an outsider,
aren't I?
Oh, it'll be great to meet her.
[dramatic music playing]
[birds chirping]
[car horn honking]
[dramatic music playing]
[birds chirping]
Pandora?
Where are the horses?
We sold them...
ages ago.
[sighs]
Stables are empty.
The parkland is all plowed over.
It's just fields.
Local farmers rents.
And I wrote about that.
[sighs]
Hello, Pandora.
[dramatic music playing]
Sold the horses.
Why are you wearing a fur coat?
I'm mink, you mean, why not?
It's September.
Oh, I can't stand the cold.
This is a savage country,
ghastly climate.
[dramatic music playing]
Welcome home.
Archie.
[dramatic music playing]
Oh.
[chuckles]
I'm so happy to see you.
And to be back is so wonderful.
-I can't believe...
-Wonderful.
[Archie] Ah, there they are.
Oh, Pandora, it's wonderful
to have you back.
[Archie] Hmm, darling.
And you must be Jeff.
-Good day. Good to meet you.
-Hello. Welcome to Croy.
Thank you very much.
Archie, they've been
absolutely angelic,
did particularly
all the driving.
Oh, we have to.
We wanted to get here.
He always drives like a maniac.
These children have no respect
for their betters.
I don't want any more
bad news today.
-Sold the horses.
-Come along.
I'll show you all
to your rooms.
Yes. Come on.
Let's go and have a drink.
Yeah. Great.
I'd love one.
[indistinct chatter]
[dramatic music playing]
Isobel, wait for me.
-Should I take your coat?
-Yes.
Oh, God.
[sighs]
[dramatic music playing]
I've missed this so much.
The Americans have all gone,
so I have given you
the panic room.
Isobel, could I see my old room?
Oh, yes, of course.
I don't think--
It's been years
since we've used it.
Can I sleep here?
But it hasn't been
redecorated or anything.
It's so tattered
and the bed needs airing.
Where are my things, Isobel?
My records?
Oh, it's all safe,
boxed away in the attic.
[dramatic music playing]
[Pandora] I've dreamt
of this for years.
That gray and purple and green.
I've laid the table
in the dining room.
All the best China, crystal.
I thought we'd have a really
grand family dinner.
Isobel...
what I'd love is--
is supper in the kitchen,
like we used to.
Oh. Yes, of course,
if that's what you really want.
I tried to teach the locals
the Highland fling.
They always stated I looked like
the Pasodoble.
-[laughter]
-It was hopeless.
Hey, what about those three
buskers in Santa Fe?
Oh, darling.
They were so lonely.
No one paid any attention.
So Pandora invites them
to join us.
-Well, they were too charming.
-[Lucilla] You liked them.
-I thought they were great.
-Were they great.
-They really were great.
-[indistinct chatter]
[laughter]
[suspenseful music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[laughter]
[Archie laughs]
[indistinct chatter]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Isobel] Why don't take
your glass to--
Done.
So, I can't wait.
Tell me everything.
[sighs]
You know the Airds are coming
to lunch on Sunday.
Is that all right?
Perfectly all right.
What's Edmund's new wife like?
[sighs]
Not exactly...
you. It's been 10 years.
She's warm...
generous.
She's been wonderful to Alexa.
Warm, generous?
She sounds blissful.
Well, you'll meet them all
at the dance anyway.
Have you bought
a new dress yet?
Oh, no. I can't afford it.
But, darling,
you have to have a new dress.
Don't be so silly.
Are things that bad?
Yes, actually.
[dramatic music playing]
What is it, Isobel?
It's everything.
It's Archie losing his leg.
It's having to be nice to people
because they're paying
to sleep in your spare bedrooms.
Archie finds life difficult.
He seems to think
he's let us down.
He's lost his zest for living.
I sometimes think
he wishes he hadn't survived
the Falklands War.
Is there anything wrong
between the two of you?
No.
He always waits until he's sure
that I've gone to sleep
before he comes to bed.
[Pandora] And are you always?
No, but I pretend to be.
It's easier that way.
No demands.
Hmm. No sex you mean?
[sighs]
He's locked away
inside himself.
And when he finally
does get to sleep...
he has nightmares.
-[Pandora] Come now.
-[crying]
[dramatic music playing]
[Pandora] You all right?
Thank you.
[wind blowing]
I hear you're sleeping badly.
You must be worn out
with all that driving.
No.
Archie...
sometimes...
you have to allow people
to know things.
You have to let them
into your life.
Why?
To give them the chance
to help you.
No one can help.
So it's best to put up
the shutters and say nothing.
I think so.
[wind blowing]
Hmm, what a wonderful smell.
Yes. Tobacco plants from seeds.
It's Isobel's latest triumph.
Hmm.
Did you ever receive
the letter I send you after I...
ran off like a mad thing?
Yes.
You never replied.
I stationed in Germany,
if you remember.
By the time it reached me,
you were in America.
It was too late.
You shouldn't
have done it, Pan.
You're not gonna take
the high moral tone with me now,
are you, Archie?
Would you walk me back
to the house?
[dramatic music playing]
Now then,
this lunch on Sunday--
Ooh. I think it's gonna be
fascinating...
in a ghastly kind of way.
I haven't made up my mind.
Shall I behave well...
or shall I be naughty...
hmm?
[dramatic music playing]
[stomping]
[suspenseful music playing]
[sighs]
[dramatic music playing]
Hi.
Lucilla, where did you
spring from?
Jeff and I just went down
to the gate to walk off
that fantastic dinner.
Pandora went to bed.
She looked exhausted.
Oh, she'll be fine
in the morning.
Awfully thin, ain't she?
Well, she's so hyper, dad.
She burns everything up.
Champagne, zapping around
the mountain bends,
and suddenly she crashed out
in the back of the car
wrapped up in that mink.
I know, Dad. I know
I'm not allowed to say so,
but this is really great.
Don't think she's on something,
do you?
Oh, dad.
No, I just thought that
you'd probably know more
about these things than I do.
Hmm, you think I'm part
of the drug culture, do you?
Well, she's...
I think she sort of, changed
in some way or something.
Did you meet
any of her friends?
Yeah. There was one guy.
I think he was called Carlo.
He is quite good looking.
Yeah, I got the feeling they
knew each other pretty well.
Do you think he might be--
Well, I mean, it's not exactly
your usual Latin love,
if that's what you mean?
-You think she's happy though?
-Yeah. Why not?
Lovely house, pool,
loads of loot.
No, but...
I mean, you know...
Dad, she's really happy
to be here, right?
Come on.
Don't start your worrying.
-God bless you, darling.
-Uh-hmm.
-Bye.
-[Lucilla] Goodnight.
[piano music playing]
[water splashes]
[chuckling]
[priest] To everything,
there is a season,
and a time to every purpose
under heaven.
A time to be born...
and a time to die.
A time to plant...
and a time to pluck up
that which is planted.
A time to kill...
and a time to heal.
A to break down...
and a time to build up.
[dramatic music playing]
[birds chirping]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Henry] Come on, dad.
[car engine starts]
[indistinct chatter]
[birds chirping]
[dramatic music playing]
-[Henry] Sasha.
-[Virginia] Henry, come here.
Sasha, come here.
He's an ancestor, then,
is she?
-[Henry] Oh, Mom.
-[indistinct chatter]
[dramatic music playing]
Pandora...
dear child.
Vi.
-Archie, lunch is ready.
-Uh, shall we lead on then?
You have met Virginia?
Edmund's wife.
It's nice to meet you.
Virginia, lovely to meet you.
This is Henry.
Is it indeed?
And how old are you, Henry?
I'm eight.
Ah, the best possible age to be.
I thought seven was better.
Heavens.
Nostalgia already.
-Let's go have lunch.
-[Henry] Okay.
Pandora.
[sighs]
Lovely to see you, Edmund.
How are you?
Extremely well.
You look...
absolutely wonderful.
Oh, please don't go over
the usual clichs.
I always know I'm looking
ghastly when people tell me...
I look wonderful.
I was merely gonna comment
on the elegance of your outfit
and how good it looks.
Not even lip service
to flattery.
Must be looking worse
than I thought.
[Violet] Oh, Archie.
Where would you like us to sit?
[Archie] Uh, why don't you come
and sit here?
And Pandora...
We'll plant ourselves here.
-Honey.
-Okay.
[indistinct chatter]
Well, I shall sit next to Henry.
-May I?
-Of course.
[indistinct chatter]
So, Henry, tell me,
what do you like to do best?
[dramatic music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
It'll end in tears.
Always did.
[indistinct chatter]
[Archie] Uh, Virginia,
you need to aim just there.
Quite impressed with what
you have in mind.
-[Archie] Great put.
-Oh. [chuckles]
[Henry] Come on, Sasha. Come on.
Here's the stick.
Go fetch, girl.
Come on, Sasha. Come on.
Come on.
Nice child, your Henry.
[Edmund] Yes. He's a good boy.
I try to imagine, sometimes,
what it would be like
to have a child?
Pandora, don't do this.
What?
I went through hell.
Oh, did you, sweetie?
What a shame.
What I'm trying to say
is that--
What you're trying to say is "Go
away, you embarrassing woman.
Don't mess up my nice,
tidy life again,"
-isn't that right?
-You know, it's not.
What are you trying to say,
Edmund?
Do tell.
I'd like to get to know
the new improved Edmund.
[sighs]
Why did you come back?
Reasons?
This Verena Steynton party.
No. I can't believe that.
Well, maybe...
I just wanted to see how well
you'd all settled down.
Shake you up a bit. Hmm.
-Are you happy?
-Don't be silly.
Are you?
Are you happy, Edmund?
[dramatic music playing]
[sighs]
Are you?
After Caroline was killed...
You knew about that?
Yeah.
Archie wrote me.
Drunk driving he said.
I began several letters
but I didn't finish them.
I'm sorry.
Well, I decided that keeping
busy was the only thing.
Fill every second
of the day with work.
It was good for the firm.
Bad for the soul, I'm afraid.
Luckily, Virginia came along.
I can't imagine life
without her.
Does that answer your question?
[chuckling]
I hope your board members
are more impressed
by your eloquence, Edmund dear.
-Hmm?
-I think it's time for tea.
Pandora?
Tea?
Edmund, would you get me
a cup of tea?
I can't move.
It's been a beautiful day,
Isobel. Thank you.
It's lovely to see Archie
looking so happy.
Yes.
And Pandora, so... at home.
Makes one wonder.
Well, this isn't getting
the tea made.
Vi, come. Come sit.
Here I am.
Oh. [chuckles]
-[sighs]
-You always look so happy.
That's the way I remember you.
Archie was frantic, you know,
when you went off.
He tried to find you.
The next thing we knew,
you were in America.
I supposed I was lucky in a way.
If it happened today,
the tabloids
would be full of it.
"School girl seduces
married millionaire."
Shock, horror.
Why Pandora?
Hmm...
thought it was, glamorous,
grownup.
I was bored, I expect.
Boredom can be dangerous.
When children are bored,
they sometimes...
smash up their toys.
Well, you don't want
to listen to me chatting on.
You want to catch up
with everyone's news.
After all, you won't be
staying long, will you, Pandora?
Just till the dance, I suppose.
Well, I knew the prodigal son
got the fatted calf
but I didn't know
they went on to say,
"You'll just be staying
till the end of the feast then."
I haven't really decided
what I'm going to do...
yet.
Well...
I want my tea.
Oh, dear.
[Lucilla] Wow. Good one.
Very good.
Oh, careful. Careful. Oh, no.
Lucilla, would you take
Pandora her tea?
-We have to go.
-Sure.
We're going?
Uh-hmm.
Henry.
Hey, how about a walk?
Had a walk this morning.
Hey, what's with this?
I thought you were done
with that.
Can't take it to school
with you.
I know that.
[door slams]
There's eight of us.
I'm the eldest
and the best looking.
Then there's Olive,
she's the married one.
Laurette...
Henry all right?
He's dreading it.
It was interesting
meeting Pandora.
Was she like you remembered her?
[sighs]
Well, it's all more than...
20 years ago.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Pandora] I told you not
to call me here.
[man] I'm not checking
up on you,
I just want to know why?
Why?
-[man] Yes, why?
-You know it's dangerous.
-Look, I can handle it.
[man] Can you? Really?
-What the hell do you expect--
-I have things to settle here.
[man] Pandora, I know you're
concerned, but you--
Don't call me again.
-[man] But--
-Don't call me again.
[man] As you wish.
[dramatic music playing]
[indistinct chatter]