[Japanese pop song
playing in the distance]
playing loudly over speakers]
[man] You sure you don't wanna use
the variable scope for this?
No. I've got a lock
on vector and trajectory.
You ever hear that saying,
"Listen to your elders"?
Big phrase, especially here in Japan.
So you're an elder now?
"Elder" doesn't necessarily mean old.
It just means older.
As in smarter, wiser.
But hey, I'm serious.
We blow this chance, it's seven years...
Seven years of hard work down the drain.
Ah, so you do listen to me.
V…
I haven't missed once in 12 years.
Not gonna miss.
All right. Let's dance.
Oh, one last thing.
See? And you say
I only think about the work.
[bottle fizzes]
[Kate] Hi, uh…
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] No.
[in English] Well, never mind, then.
- Here, catch!
- [all grunting]
[tense music playing]
[woman over radio]
Seasonal, single male mark.
[Kate] Copy. Holding at yellow.
[woman over radio] Target visible.
Seasonal, the window is open.
You're green.
I've got a protocol breach.
[woman] I repeat, you are green.
Code five on-site. Code five.
[woman] Overridden. Take the shot.
Hold on. There's a kid here.
[woman] The window is closing.
I repeat, take the shot, Seasonal.
Please reconfirm.
[woman] I repeat, take the shot.
[gun cocks]
Seasonal, the window is closing.
[suspenseful music playing]
[gunshot echoes]
[speaking Japanese]
[Japanese hip-hop song playing]
[music continues faintly over headphones]
[indistinct conversation]
[Kate] I've thought
about this a long time.
I wanna talk retirement.
[Varrick] What happened in Osaka
shouldn't have.
It was wrong.
- [thunder rumbles]
- [rain pattering]
Nobody knew she'd be there.
We had one rule, V.
One simple rule. No kids.
I know.
I mean, this ain't your first rodeo.
You know there's collateral damage.
You know that.
I can't shake it.
Trust me, I've tried.
Almost to the head of the snake.
Look, I promised
I'd finish the job, and I will.
And then I'm out.
I want a life, V.
You know, I never had one.
A real, regular life.
What does that mean?
I mean, what… Family? Kids?
- Picket fence? Dogs? Suburbs?
- I don't know.
Something like that.
Two trips to Walmart, you'll be back.
- [thunder rumbling]
- [slow pensive music playing]
[sighs]
[inhales deeply]
[exhales deeply]
[inhales]
[crowd chattering indistinctly]
[man] It must be killing you.
You haven't even touched your Merlot.
It's Margaux.
I'm sorry, that was a total pick-up line.
Fuck it. I mean, listen.
The worst way
to start a conversation is a "Hey."
It's boring, it's dull. It's for horses.
So anything but that.
I'm Stephen.
- Hey.
- [snorts and laughs]
[both breathing heavily]
[softly] Shibuya-ku Sendagaya 4-7-11.
Shibuya-ku Sendagaya 4-7-11.
[cell phone vibrating]
Time to leave.
[scoffs]
[Kate] Seasonal, on-site.
[woman over radio] Copy.
Stage mark. Northwest corner.
[slow suspenseful music playing]
Sector and trajectory?
[woman] Main entrance, two black sedans.
Single.
Contact.
Primary win…
[grunts and coughs]
[woman] Seasonal, repeat.
Window on primary?
[woman] Ten seconds, max.
Seasonal, report.
Holding on yellow.
[woman] Target visible. You are green.
[man grunts]
[bodyguards yelling indistinctly]
[woman] Window is closed.
Seasonal, report.
- New point.
- [woman] Negative. You are red.
- [woman] The window is closed.
[dramatic tense music plays]
[car engine revving]
[tires screeching]
[grunts]
- [man yells]
- [Kate gasping]
- [gasping]
- [man yelling]
[groaning]
[coughs]
[man speaking Japanese]
Hey.
[women screaming]
[engine starts and revs]
[Japanese rock song playing over speakers]
[man speaking Japanese]
[police sirens wailing]
[in English] Stop, stop. For fuck's sake.
[rock music continues]
[Varrick] Now you start
the rest of your life
- What's your name?
- Kate.
Kate. I'm Varrick.
I'm your handler now.
That makes me your mother,
your father, your best friend,
and your therapist.
Left. That all you got? Left.
Good.
[footsteps echoing]
[doctor] It's good. You're awake.
You've been out almost a day.
[whispers in Japanese]
[in English] Have you had any recent
exposure to radioactive materials?
No.
The reason I ask is you appear to be
suffering from accelerated ARS.
Acute radiation syndrome.
Lethal.
Caused by subjection
to potent radiation in…
Extremely short amount of time.
Which substance?
We looked for the usuals.
Iodine-131, thallium, but uh…
It appears to be more specific.
Polonium-210?
204.
[inhales sharply]
We'll take the Margaux to go.
Please do not try to…
How much time do I have?
A day, maybe.
- But we will make it painless for you.
- [scoffs]
Shit.
It's possible that...
[doctor] I'll get a nurse.
[breathing heavily]
[inhales sharply]
[speaking Japanese]
- [female nurse speaking]
- [male nurse speaking]
[Sano speaking]
Five liters of blood in the body,
heart pumps two a minute.
Gun's on your femoral. You do the math.
I need something to keep me going.
I want stimulants.
These. Load them in the shots, go.
Give me five.
- Come on.
- Okay.
I don't have all the time in the world.
What are you trying to do?
[woman speaking Japanese on radio]
[whispering] Shibuya-ku Sendagaya.
Shibuya-ku Sendagaya.
[Stephen speaking indistinctly]
- [woman] …take a shower.
- [Stephen] We should just have fun!
- [Stephen] It's the last night. Come on!
- I know.
But I still have stuff to do.
- Oh, my God! [gasps]
- [Stephen groaning]
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] Why'd you poison me?
What are you talking about? Poison?
[hesitates] I didn't know it was…
They told me it was just a roofie,
so they could lift the room.
Who? Who told you?
Even if I knew, I'd be dead if I tell you.
- Aw, she'll be dead if you don't.
- Wait.
Don't.
[Stephen sighs]
Sato.
Kazuo Sato. He manages a Yakuza club.
Which clan?
Kijima.
Fuck, it's a Kijima clan.
[woman] They've owned us for years.
Sato said that
if he did this one last thing,
that he would set us free.
We could actually start over now.
A different life.
Please.
[spits, coughs]
These might fit you.
Can I get you something?
Anything?
Boom Boom Lemon?
You got any?
Oh, um…
No, sorry.
I'm Kanako.
And it seems we're the same.
Collateral damage.
I'm Kate.
And they're gonna know I was here.
Who?
Everyone.
[tense music playing]
Poisoned by who?
[Kate] That's what I'm trying
to figure out.
There must be some antidote.
For polonium-204?
Who was the mark, V?
Kate, you know, uh…
V?
Who was the mark?
You won't get any more
questions from me after today.
A man named Kijima.
I recognized him from Osaka.
Who is he?
Grand honcho
of the biggest family in Tokyo.
Your mark in Osaka
was Kijima's younger brother, Kentaro.
- [gunshot]
- [blood splatters]
[sighs] I won't lie, it's been a shitshow
for us as it's been for you, and…
[clears throat] Kijima, apparently,
who hasn't been able to let it go.
This was revenge for Osaka?
Some people have this extraordinary
attachment to their siblings,
as if genetics make a family and…
Anyway, all that honor shit,
Kijima's been on a tear against the…
[Kate sniffles]
How do I get to him?
Kijima doesn't surface.
Not after Osaka.
Last night was a very rare opportunity.
What about Sato? Kazuo Sato. Ring a bell?
I know that some of his guys hang out
at a place called the Black Lizard.
That's a start.
[Japanese rock song playing]
[song continues over speakers]
[man 1 speaking Japanese]
[dramatic Japanese
traditional music playing]
[performer yells]
[performers yelling]
[Sato speaking]
[yakuza speaking]
[in English] Go.
You Sato?
Kazuo Sato?
[in English] Who are you? What...
Did you poison me?
You don't tell me, I kill you.
I think you're lying, I kill you.
Did you poison me?
[wounded yakuza wheezing]
Yeah.
- Why?
- [wounded yakuza groans]
Hey!
Why'd you poison me?
[Sato] I only follow orders.
- From Kijima?
- [yakuza lieutenant speaking Japanese]
[in English] Please.
Where is Kijima?
How do I get to him?
Nobody knows.
[gunshot]
- All right. Same question, same deal.
- [men shouting in distance]
- [in English] You killed him! He is the...
- He is dead. You worry about you.
You crazy! I don't know!
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] I'm gonna ask one more time.
Where is Kijima?
Last chance.
- Please. I don't know...
- [gun clicks]
[all yelling]
[all grunting]
[bone cracks]
[woman screaming]
[gunshot]
[panting]
Shit!
[all grunting]
[yakuza yelling in Japanese]
[all grunting and yelling]
[women screaming]
[yells]
[yakuza screaming]
[panting]
[spits and coughs]
Ani. Ani-chan would know.
[speaking Japanese]
- [autoinjector hisses]
- [grunts]
Ani?
[Japanese punk rock band playing]
[singing in Japanese]
[music fades out]
[gunshot echoes]
[screaming]
[punk rock song fades back in]
[defibrillator charging]
[electricity buzzing]
[Ani speaking Japanese]
[in English] Hey, stop!
What the fuck are you doing?
Let go of me!
Hey! Stop!
[Ani grunting]
Come on. Ow!
- Get up.
- Kuso!
[in English] You slapped me!
Stop, or I'll… Fuck.
[punk rock song continues]
- [gunshot]
- [song stops]
[Ani breathing heavily] Okay, okay, okay.
Next one goes in there.
I'm sorry.
You're gonna call Kijima for me.
What?
Kijima. Call him.
I can't. I don't have his number.
Oh, you don't have his number? Really?
Kijima, yeah, I don't have his number!
- How do you reach him?
- Okay, who are you?
How do you get in touch with him?
I don't know, I just call ano baka Renji.
- Renji?
- [speaking Japanese]
[in English]
The only person that talks to him.
Okay. Call Renji.
[panting]
[grunts]
[man] Hai, Shinzo.
[speaking Japanese]
[Shinzo speaking Japanese]
[Ani speaking]
[cat meows]
- [Renji] Ani?
- [speaking Japanese]
[in English] I got the kid.
If Kijima wants to see her again,
he can meet me at the center
of Murakawa marketplace in one hour.
- A second more and she dies.
- [Renji in English] Who is this?
[in English] You're crazy.
You wanna get Kijima?
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] You think you can…
You can't get to him this way.
He doesn't give a shit about me.
No one does.
Come on.
[Renji speaking Japanese]
Huh?
[all speaking]
[sucks teeth]
[indistinct announcement over PA]
[in English] And you know,
for your information,
I haven't talked
or seen my uncle in, like, a year.
Shit.
Ew, what the fuck?
Oh, my God, what is wrong with you?
Sit down.
I said, sit down!
Yeah, no way. You're all gross and sick.
And you know what?
Fuck you, cancer bitch.
[Japanese pop song playing]
[Ani] Hey, I have to go to the bathroom.
Me, too. Come on.
[Ani] Ouch.
[speaking Japanese]
[Kate panting]
[in English] Hey.
You got any Boom Boom Lemon?
[store clerk speaking Japanese]
[locks clicking]
[Ani] Well, this sucks.
[grunts]
Ugh! I can barely breathe in here.
- [tooth clatters]
- [spits]
[toilet flushes]
[stall door opens]
- No way.
- [Kate groans]
So many scars and blood. It's so…
It's gross, I know.
- No, no, no.
- [panting]
I think it's awesome.
[scissors snip]
[sniffles]
Ow!
What the fuck are you doing, bitch?
[yells]
This will keep you safe. Trust me.
[slow suspenseful music playing]
[vendor speaking Japanese]
[vendor] Hai.
- [vendor] Dozo.
- Arrigato.
[speaking Japanese]
[men shouting in Japanese]
[in English] Where is Ani-chan?
I don't see Kijima.
Let me see the child first.
Either Kijima walks out right now,
or I leave
and you never see the kid alive again.
[crowd screaming]
- [gunshots]
- [man groans]
[gunshot]
- [can clatters]
- [gunshot]
[crowd screaming]
[both grunting]
[screaming]
[Shinzo speaking Japanese]
[men yelling in Japanese]
[panting]
[both yelling]
[both grunting]
[yelling]
[gunshots]
[gunshots in distance]
[grunts]
[guns firing rapidly]
[both grunt]
[groaning]
[panting]
[Shinzo speaking Japanese]
[grunting]
[gunshot]
[dramatic music playing]
[man yelling in Japanese]
[bullets ricocheting]
[gun clicking]
- Boo!
- [gasps and yelps]
[men laughing]
[banging on door]
[in English] Stupid shit! [panting]
Ani.
Shinzo.
[groaning]
[retching, coughing]
[Ani speaking Japanese]
- [pleading in Japanese]
- [Shinzo speaking]
- [gunshots]
- [Ani screaming]
[yelling]
[in English] Oh, my God.
[police sirens approaching]
[dispatcher shouting in the distance]
- [Kate] You better get out of here.
- Wait!
[Ani] Hey.
Hey. Where are we going?
Stop following me. Stop.
[Ani] You're just gonna leave me, then?
[Kate] Kijima didn't show.
You're useless to me now.
Did you see what just happened?
My own family wants me gone.
Where the fuck will I go?
[Kate] Not my problem. [coughs]
I'll be dead before the night's over.
Hey, that makes two of us.
Why did you save me, then, huh?
You're making me regret it!
[Ani] You… you're a… No!
You can't abandon me.
I know Kijima killed my dad,
and he will kill me.
What did I do wrong, huh?
I haven't done anything to anybody,
but they still treat me like shit!
[gun clicks]
[all laughing]
[Ani crying] Everybody, all the time,
just throwing me around,
like I'm some piece of garbage.
Shut up!
You don't know what you're talking about.
You just yap, yap, yap.
Just "fuck this, fuck that."
You don't know anything! You're a kid!
[Kate breathing heavily]
[Kate groans]
[syringe clatters]
Medicine. Dropped it.
- What's wrong with you?
- [autoinjector hisses]
[groans]
[sighs]
[panting]
I'm dying.
Kijima did this, right?
Are you gonna go kill him?
You're a badass killer motherfucker.
You'll need me, you know. Like…
Just look at you. You…
You won't make it an hour
without my help, okay?
And I can do everything, okay?
I know who, where, when, whatever.
- I can help you get him, get my uncle.
- Okay.
And I'm really good
at shortcuts and maps and…
What?
I said okay.
Okay.
Um…
You can't walk around like this.
[vending machine dispenses]
[Kate groans] Sold out.
Boom Boom Lemon?
[chuckles] Artificial shit.
You know what? This is stupid. Let's go.
Yeah, clean clothes are stupid.
"Everything I should wear
should be just covered in blood."
Aw, it's so cute on you.
Come on.
You're so cool.
But you're also a Terminator, bitch.
Oh, my God.
[imitates gunshot, exclaims] "I die."
[Ani chuckles]
Seriously, we're…
We're actually pretty much the same.
It's scary.
Who has a line into Kijima?
Only Renji. I told you.
His main advisor.
That was my dad's job.
But he got shot.
Kijima did it, I'm sure.
And Renji was there, too.
How do I find Renji?
Um, probably with his aijin.
His what?
His boyfriend, Jojima.
- Tell me where.
- Mmm.
It's this fucking cool penthouse,
top of the tower.
- The entire floor is theirs.
- Security?
I mean, two in the lobby, at least.
- Service entrance?
- Yeah.
The back, by the kitchen.
We could just shoot our ways in.
And risk Renji escaping?
No. I have to get to him
before he knows what's wrong.
We'll be fast, okay? Bang, bang! Brrap!
[imitates gunshots] "You're dead..."
Stop. Speak less, open your ears.
We're gonna distract them.
You're going to distract them.
How?
By being you. Just, you know, louder.
Okay, cool. So…
Can I have a gun?
No.
[waiter speaking Japanese]
[speaking Japanese]
[door buzzes]
[characters on TV speaking]
[men grunting on TV]
[chuckling]
Ani-chan?
[Jojima speaking]
[gun cocks]
[Kate in English] Where's Renji?
What do you want from Renji-san?
It's not your concern.
[chuckling]
Of course it is my concern.
Your concern is to stay whole
until I leave here.
Renji?
You may do to me what you must.
But I will not be
disclosing his whereabouts.
Shut the blinds.
- Shit, there's one remote for everything.
- [loud pop song starts playing]
[both grunting]
Shit, shit.
[exhales]
[exclaims]
[yelling]
[both grunting]
[Jojima screams]
[screams]
Stop, Jojima!
Back off!
[speaking Japanese]
[Jojima grunting]
Konoyaro! Stop it!
You motherfucker!
Stop it!
- [gunshot]
- [Kate gasps]
Fuck. I'm sorry. Fuck. [breathing heavily]
[panting]
[speaking Japanese]
[gasping]
[coughs]
- [groans]
- [in English] There's blood on my…
There's blood…
There's blood on my face. There's blood.
[gasps and shudders]
Hey.
Hey, hey.
Come on. Come here.
- No. No, stop it. Stop it! Stop!
- Hey. Look at me.
- [sobbing and babbling]
- [shushing]
[Kate] Look only at me, okay?
Look only at me and breathe.
- [whimpers]
- Breathe.
Breathe.
Okay? You're gonna live through this.
Okay?
All right? You're doing great.
Come here.
Hey, maybe we should
check this house, huh?
Maybe there's some, uh…
- Clues?
- Clues. Yeah.
[glass shards crunching underfoot]
[sighs]
Bingo.
- Hey, I think I know where Renji is.
- Yeah?
Check this out.
Cellular tracking.
I can see exactly where Renji is
and where he will be.
That's very good.
"Useless."
[driver speaking Japanese]
Ani?
- Bang!
- [gunshot]
[blows air]
- [grunts]
- [gunshots continue]
[gunshot]
[in English] Hey, Renji.
I gotta be honest,
I'm having a rough night.
I really need to see your boss Kijima.
[speaking Japanese]
Speak English, motherfucker.
English, I said.
[scoffs]
[speaking Japanese]
[groans] Wakatta. Wakatta.
Fuzakenna.
[in English] Family killed my father.
Family tried to kill me.
All of you asshole hyenas
getting fat off of my dad's carcass!
[speaking Japanese]
[Kate in English] Look.
Just give him to me,
and you'll live. Okay?
[Renji] I do not know.
When he disappears like this,
he says, "To be amongst family."
I don't know what it means.
I know where he is.
[Kate panting]
Your phone.
[line ringing]
[Kate] I found him. I found Kijima.
I'm gonna finish it, V.
Hey, I promised you, didn't I?
Kate, tell me where you are,
I'll come to you right now.
Let me help you.
Don't. I'll already be dead anyway.
You can find my body
near a house in Hottazaka.
In the hills.
[sighs]
Goodbye, V.
Kate?
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] Does that hurt?
When you do that.
No more questions.
I don't know anything about you.
Don't need to.
Do you wanna know about me?
I know enough.
But I'm the last person
you'll get to know.
You don't wanna know me?
That's sad, Kate.
I think that's really…
It's sad.
My mom's a gaijin, too.
That's why I've never met her.
Never even seen a picture.
They won't… I…
I don't know what she looks like.
She was like you, I bet.
Tall and… pretty.
No shit from no dudes.
Just doing what she wants all the time.
Total killer babe.
[softly] Killer babe.
[slow sentimental music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
It's the old family house.
No one really knows about it.
Where they all grew up.
The elders and shit.
My dad, too.
Go on.
I'll finish this.
What? You'll finish it?
Hey, look at you.
You can't stand, and you can't see.
Okay? You're gonna die.
Yeah, after I kill him.
- I'm here now. I'm coming with you.
- No, you're not.
Why not? I go where you go.
Because you're a fucking kid.
Go be one.
I never could.
Hey, Ani…
You're young.
You have time to forget.
Be someone less angry.
Take control of your own life.
[voice breaking] Go.
[slow somber music playing]
[ominous music plays]
[groans]
[heart beating rapidly]
- [grunts]
- [autoinjector hissing]
[heartbeat stabilizes]
[dramatic music playing]
[Kijima speaking Japanese]
[in English] Look at me.
[speaking Japanese]
[in English, chuckling] Yeah. I'm dying.
[in English] Kentaro, your brother…
[speaking Japanese]
Renji.
[car approaching]
[in English] Hi.
Get lost.
Yeah.
You know, I thought
I had the coolest bracelets.
I realize now,
you have the coolest bracelet.
I have a gun, you know.
[chuckling] Well, good for you.
Your parents raised you right.
Yeah, you don't know
shit about my parents,
so just fuck off.
Well, I know it couldn't
have been easy to lose 'em.
You know,
I lost someone that I love a lot.
And you know her.
Kate?
Maybe my best friend.
And, uh…
I'm very worried about her.
[scoffs] "Friends."
I didn't know Kate had any stupid friends.
Well, she's got you, doesn't she?
But you're right.
She and I
aren't really friends, more family.
[Kijima speaking Japanese]
[in English]
No, but Varrick, he's… he's…
[speaking Japanese]
[Kate gasps and chokes]
[in English] Have you ever wondered
about Kate's obsession with your family?
You mean my uncle?
Yeah, sure. Him, too.
Sorry.
I know you've been through a lot.
What do you mean?
Kate ever share with you what she did
in Osaka when she first met you?
[speaking Japanese]
[gagging and struggling to breathe]
[in English] I have to finish this.
I'm dying. I have to finish…
I have to finish something.
[in English]
Death is the time for the beginnings.
[speaking Japanese]
- [gun cocks]
- [tense music plays]
[gunshot]
[in English] No, no, no.
No, Ani. Ani, no…
[Ani] You lied to me!
[stammering] I killed someone for you.
- Ani...
- You killed my whole family.
You… You bitch!
No, please.
Shoot me if you want,
but don't get in that car, okay?
Look at me. I'm begging you.
You're stronger than I am.
You don't have to end up here...
Shut the fuck up!
I have nothing left, okay?
It's what they do.
You and me, we're collateral...
[Ani screams]
[shuddering]
[gasping]
[engine starts]
[Ani sniffling]
Now what?
Now…
You start the rest of your life.
[ominous music playing]
[Varrick] You start the rest of your life.
I know how much you must be
hurting right now, losing your parents.
But it's gonna be okay.
- [screaming]
- [Ani screaming]
[woman over radio]
I repeat, take the shot.
- [men laughing]
- [young Kate] The gun was empty.
It's empty!
I know.
Shoot 'em in the stomach,
they die slow, in agony.
And they know it's personal.
Let's go.
- [Ani whimpering]
- Breathe.
Breathe.
[Varrick] Are you gonna
let that pain overwhelm you?
- Control you?
- [groans]
[Ani] This is so cool.
Maybe you can embrace it.
- And let it empower you.
- [gasping]
[dramatic music playing]
[Kijima speaking Japanese]
[dramatic music continues]
[autoinjector hisses]
Renji?
[in English] What is she doing here?
She's the future. Mine at least.
Ani, sit.
You went after my girl
without my permission.
I could fucking kill you right now.
And destroy your own operation?
My issue is not with my operation.
It's with you taking it on yourself.
You ordered her termination.
"If she's leaving, I will terminate her."
Your words exactly.
"If."
I said "if."
Key word, "if."
She was coming back.
I just had to work it.
I was working it.
She would have changed her mind.
I would have changed my mind.
Polonium-204?
Fuck you!
[Renji] Your girl had to die.
That was always the deal, Varrick-san.
After Kentaro's death,
all eyes were on me.
I panicked.
I moved too quickly, and I'm sorry.
[chuckling]
Yeah.
You know what? You blundered, I blundered.
Let's, uh…
Maybe we do our best
to put this behind us.
In the name of being human.
I prefer self-interest.
I trust it more.
I can't say I can trust you going forward.
[scoffs]
Trust was not a part of the deal.
Neither is friendship.
Welcome to the Yakuza, Varrick-san.
[suspenseful music playing]
[speaking Japanese]
[Kate sighs]
[slow pensive music playing]
[in English] Not tonight.
[bottle fizzes]
[gasps softly]
Boom Boom Lemon?
[slow pensive music continues]
[exhales]
[sniffles]
Let's go get Ani.
[upbeat Japanese pop song playing]
[gunfire]
[tense music playing]
[man grunts]
[guard over radio] Alpha-six,
camera two is down.
I repeat, camera two is down.
[guard 2] Four to Alpha-six.
[guard 3] So what do we do?
Well, we, uh, call up the teams,
form a barricade around the crystal box.
Bring up the kid.
And, uh, you know,
we'll hole up in there. Move!
Which teams, sir?
All of 'em!
[elevator chimes]
[guard] Go, go, go!
[chuckles]
Uh-oh.
Asshole.
- [man over radio] Bring up the girl.
- Copy that.
Let's go. Move!
Hey! Easy, cowboy.
[tense music playing]
[rapid gunfire]
[Kate's gun clicking]
[both grunting]
[guns clicking]
[panting]
[man] Fuck!
[Kate groans]
[grunts]
[sighs]
Okay, Renji. You ain't coming with.
You take care of Kijima.
You guys, stay with him.
You guys, come with me. Good luck.
[gunshot]
[speaking Japanese]
[grunts]
Eh?
[Renji grunts]
[gasping]
[exhales deeply]
[metal clicks]
[guards grunting]
- [bullet piercing flesh]
- [screams]
[Kate grunting]
[muffled gunshots]
[gunshots continue]
[yelling]
[groaning]
[dramatic music playing]
[Varrick] Bravo, Kate.
Never doubted you.
Ani…
[whimpers] I'm sor...
Ani, I'm sorry.
[voice breaking]
I'd do anything…
To undo it, to take it all back.
[Varrick] Can't go back, sadly.
[Kate] Please.
Be nice, right now,
for both of us, wouldn't it?
Ani, I'd give anything to take it back.
I'd take it all back. I'm so sorry.
[Varrick] But guess we gotta just accept
who we are now.
And you know, Kate, that we are…
Tools.
Well, I was gonna say
"indispensable parts of a system."
That you created and controlled.
[Varrick] A necessary system, Kate.
One that cannot accommodate dissent.
I promise you
it is not what you think it is.
It turns out nothing ever was.
[footsteps approaching]
And I'm not looking away anymore.
Oh.
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] I see. In the 25th hour,
you suddenly grew a conscience.
Don't do this, Varrick.
[Varrick] Don't you do this, Kate.
My entire fucking life,
I never loved anyone, except you.
Come on, V.
We both know you only love yourself.
Life had such…
Big things waiting for you.
My life wasn't mine.
Till now.
[tense music rises]
[Kate groaning]
It's okay. It's okay. Go on. Okay.
[Ani crying]
Great shot.
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
[Varrick exhales]
[groans]
[Ani] I got you.
[panting]
[Kate struggling to breathe]
Hey, hey.
Yeah. It's okay.
I know you.
No, no, no. [sobbing]
[slow mournful music playing]
[heartbeat slowing]
- It's okay.
- [exhales]
[heartbeat stops]
[Japanese pop song playing]