Thank you.
- Martin.
- Hm?
- I'm gonna die.
- No, ya aren't.
Yes, I am.
What's wrong with me doctor?
Well, I can't give you a
definite answer Mrs. Hightower,
in medicine we're
never 100% sure.
Now, when the pain gets too
bad take one of these.
But, try not to take
more than two in any given day.
I'm gonna die, ain't I.
Well, we're all going
to die, Mrs. Hightower.
Look, perhaps I should have
a chat with your husband.
Doctor, I got three more like this at home.
I gotta know,
I gotta make plans.
Seen him.
Well?
- He says I'm right about dying.
- He's cracked.
He ain't cracked, he's got a
paper with ribbons on the wall.
What about that doctor
told the Henleys their...
little Jimmy had the ague, turned out
to be the diphtheria? Doctors... all cracked.
- He's an Army doctor, he knows.
- He's cracked.
- I got this thing growing inside of me.
- I don't want to hear about it!
Ya gotta to hear about it.
- No.
- Yep.
It's in me, and it just
keeps gettin' bigger
till there's no room for
the other stuff to do what
it has to do, and in time,
my body's just gonna stop.
- How much time?
- Two months, maybe a little more.
We gotta make plans, Martin.
No.
No plans.
Whatever happens, it happens, but I
don't want to think about it.
And I don't want to talk about it.
You better get yourself into bed today.
Give me that.
I was gonna make soap and
vinegar and vanilla pudding...
I... I'll do all of it,
you just tell me how, come on.
Well, what about the pharmacy?
Well, I'll do it myself...
Oh! Oh! Oh!
- What are ya doing?
- Just tidyin' up a bit?
I'm really... I'm feeling much better.
Martin, what are ya gonna
do when I'm gone?
We gotta talk, I gotta know.
I'll get by.
How? You can't manage a farm and
four young children yourself.
There went the today.
Come here.
If it's God's will, and you go,
then I'll just worry about it then.
Be too late then,
we gotta start worrying now.
What are ya going to do
with the children?
Ya can't tend to 'em, what
are ya going to do?
I don't know.
Jessica is old enough to tend
to herself, maybe Nathan.
Maybe they could stay with
me and we send Margaret
and Jack off to Emma's in
Cleveland, at least for few years.
Your sister's got six of
her own and poor as rat.
Well, maybe she could
just manage Margaret
and we'll take Jack
and we'll send him to
your brother Daniel in
Baltimore. I don't know.
You expect me
to die knowin' my
family's scattered all
across the continent.
You can't separate my babies.
I'll come back and
haunt you, I swear it.
Maybe I'll be just sell the
durn farm and I'll go back
to Bucks County open up a
harness shop with my father.
I'll have the kids with me all
day long and have kin to help me.
Martin Hightower...
we came across 2000 miles of
purgatory to claim this land.
We've been working 18 hours a
day to make somethin' of it.
Ain't worth buffalo
cookies now but someday...
This farm is their inheritance...
don't you dare sell it.
Don't you dare.
Well, what do ya want me to do?
Start worrying about it.
Don't you think I hadn't been?
Martin? I know we gotta do, we
gotta find you another wife.
I don't want no other wife.
Yeah, but after I'm dead,
you're gonna need another wife.
It's the only way, now put that down
and think, who we're going to get?
Now looky here, Mrs. Hightower,
if there ever comes a time where you are...
what you said, maybe I'll
put my mind to it then,
but if you'll excuse me,
I don't intend holding a discussion
with my first wife about
the selection of my second.
It can't wait till after,
it'll be too late, everything will fall
apart around here, we got to start now.
We got to have someone ready to step
in my shoes the minute I'm gone.
Now you just stop this,
Amy, this here conversation's ungodly.
God? Are you saying
God don't want you and
the children have a life
together on this farm.
God wants to disperse this family,
is that what you're saying?
I don't know what the heck I'm saying.
But there are 10 men for every one woman
on these plains from Texas to Dakota.
Now where are you going to find one,
wants to tend a farm and four
kids what aren't even our own?
All the more reason
to start looking now.
- Mr. Van Der Meer?
- Yes.
I'm Amy Hightower from across the creek,
I was wondering if I could have a talk.
Come in, sit, my wife Merka.
Pleased to meet you,
I'll get some coffee.
No trouble, please.
I have a sickness,
gonna die reasonable soon.
Ain't the fever.
Well, that's too bad,
I'm sorry to hear that.
My husband and I have four
children, eldest seven.
After I go he's going to
need a wife real quick.
I hear ya have a daughter, Caroline.
I assume that's her.
Oh, no, that's Hester,
she's just big,
she's only 11. That's Caroline.
Well, anyway, I was
wondering if you'd let my
husband take her to wife
when the time comes.
Oh... I see.
We're homesteaders, got
a fine piece of land,
20 acres corn planted this year.
We got six cows, ox,
pigs and hens, got a nice size soddy.
And an oak sideboard we
brought from Maryland.
We got a cotton
mattress, a goose feather quilt
and a Calico store
bought frock she'd have.
Might just need some takin' in.
Martin's a real gentle, wholesome man.
He'd make her a fine husband.
Miss Hightower,
you seem like a fine woman
and I wish I could help
you out with your situation,
but they...
they're already five offers
of matrimony on line
for Caroline ahead of you.
The mill owner over there at
Bellevue, he offered my $600 for her,
he's an old man,
but he's a good Christian.
And that smith over there,
he's got a handsome young
son that's gonna inherit that
whole business one day soon.
Mrs. Hightower, I know the kind
of life a soddy woman lives.
I just want something
better for my Caroline.
I'm sorry.
Yea, though I walk through the Valley of
the Shadow of Death, I will fear no evil.
Thy rod and thy staff comfort me. I will
dwell in the house of the Lord forever.
He was a good farmer, a good husband,
a good father, a good man.
We know you'll take him gentle
into to your bosom Lord,
and we pray you'll send comfort and
grace to those he left behind.
Dust thou art and under
dust thou shall return.
Excuse me. I ask your forgiveness
for intruding on your grief.
But I happen to be riddin'
passed and witnessed the proceedings.
I just had the feeling it
was fate brought me here.
Please, can I talk to
you for a moment, please?
All right.
- I see you've just been widowed.
- Yeah.
You're going to need a
father for your children.
And it just so happens in a short time,
my husband's going to be a widower in
need of a mother for our children.
So I'd like to ask
you on his behalf
if you consider
marrying up with him.
I understand and I appreciate it,
unfortunately, it comes a little late...
I'm already spoken for.
Oh... well...
I wish you both the best.
Whoa!
Excuse me, I was looking
for the widow Donohue.
You found her.
Oh, I'm sorry. I must have been
laboring under some misunderstanding.
Sorry for disturbing you.
Good day.
Hey! You looking for the widow Hattie
Donahue or the widow Isabel Donahue?
- They're coming, Ma.
- Nathan.
Alrighty. Now, you good now, and don't
you speak lest you're asked something.
Martin!
Please, come in.
This is Miss Hattie Donahue
and Miss Isabel Donahue.
This is my husband Martin Hightower.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
And these are our children,
Jessica, Nathan, and Jack...
and baby Margaret over
there in the crib.
The Lord never saw fit
to make me a mother.
But they all seem... healthy.
They are, and
good natured, all of 'em.
Well, shall we sit down?
Ladies...
My wife has made a chokeberry pie and I
hope you'll stay and refresh yourselves.
But Miss Donahue, I aren't gonna marry
you and that's the finish of it.
I thank you for the visit.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
one of my hogs is ailin'.
I'm sorry, Amy, I just couldn't
take that woman t'wife.
But we agreed,
ya have to get married again.
I know, but not her.
Why in damnation not, she's a
strong, moral, healthy woman.
- She don't give me the tingles.
- What?
She don't give me tingles.
A man oughtn't have to bed a
woman don't give him the tingles.
Then don't bed 'er.
Ya don't have to if you don't want to,
ya could still marry her.
It's a man's duty to bed his wife,
a man don't bed his wife is not a man.
There ain't nobody else,
I've looked for miles around.
Well, we'll just look...
further afield then.
Criminy!
Do I give you the tingles.
Every time I look at ya.
Every blessin' time.
Excuse me, do you have any single
women livin' in these parts?
Do you know of any single
Naw, not in this town.
- What can I get ya?
- A lemonade?
Sarsaparilla?
- Sarsaparilla, take a seat.
- Thank you.
You alright?
I was so sure in a town this size
there'd be some marriageable women.
I have to locate one
and there ain't any.
That's true, soon as one shows
up or a young'n grows up,
men swarm around like flies.
I bet there ain't an unwed
female between 14 and 114...
aside from the
ladies on the line.
Ladies on the line,
who are they?
Well, you know...
they live in cribs down
by the edge of town.
- And they're unattached?
- So to speak.
They're working women,
if you get my drift.
Working at what?
Oh.
Oh...
Thank you.
What do you want?
I was wonderin' if I could
talk to you a moment.
I'm busy!
Can't you see the door is closed!
Sorry, Pat darlin',
now where was I?
Oh!
Oh, I... I'm sorry.
- Yeah!
- Could I have a moment of your time.
My time's valuable.
No, come on in.
- My name is Amy Hightower, you're Pearl?
- Yeah.
What's your last name?
I don't need one.
Well, how long have you
lived in Cedar Springs?
Well, too long.
Are you married?
Yeah, I'm married my work,
what do you want lady?
I want you to
marry up with my
husband and tend to my
children after I die.
Which is gonna be soon.
All right.
You haven't even asked
me where we're goin',
what sort of life it is.
Haven't even asked me
what my husband's like.
Does he kill people in their sleep.
- No.
- Then I reckon I can handle him.
Do you like children?
Some, some not, same as with people.
Well, I gotta warn ya, life is pretty hard and wearing.
Wait, wait, wait.
You haven't second thoughts, lady?
- Well...
- We can just call the whole thing off.
Well, I guess I'm just kind of worried.
I mean, here I am entrusting you
with my home, my man, my children.
I don't know nothin'
about you except...
Except I'm a whore?
Well, let me tell you a
little bit about myself.
Goodbye!
I ain't just a whore, I'm a
good whore, a damned good whore.
The house I worked at
New Orleans,  men made
reservations for my time,
days in advance.
In California, them miners, they paid
up to $500 for half an hour of my time.
Of course a cup of coffee
was eighty dollars.
But anyway...
in there, that rat trap,
I got by,
surrounded by girls half my age.
Ya know that ain't easy,
but I'm good... good.
A good whore, just like I'll be
a good mother and a good wife.
So am I going with you or not?
'Cause I'm going somewhere, I'm packed.
Is California pretty?
Hi, Ma!
Whoa!
Were you a good boy?
Are you here for daddy?
- Daddy, Ma, and she... a lady's here.
- Sh, sh, Nathan.
- But Daddy...
- Now, Jessica... sh, sh, sh, sh, sh.
- You need to be goin' outside now.
- C'mon.
There was an old mule her name was A-Fool.
We've been singin'.
She'd been crying all day but now we've
been having some fun, we've been singin'.
- Haven't we? There ya go.
- Come here you.
Pearl, this is my husband Martin Hightower.
Martin, Pearl.
He do for you?
He'll do.
She do for you?
I want ya to know none
of those weren't my idea.
None of it, no fashion.
But my wife had arguments and
I didn't have answers for them.
She do for you or not?
She'll do.
Ain't ya gonna tell him?
I'm debatin' the necessity of it.
- She's a whore.
- What?
She's a whore.
She's a what?
- She's a whore.
- A whore?
Ya didn't tell me that.
- I'm tellin' ya now.
- Well, what did you bring a whore for?
It's all they had?
I searched from one end of that
town to the other, it's all they had.
I never agreed to marry no whore.
Would you rather marry the Widow
Donohue, 'cause I'll go get her?
Just make up your mind,
the whore or the Widow Donahue,
one or the other,
it's your only choice.
The whore.
Martin!
Martin, come here.
Look.
Look, look, and look.
I'm runnin' out of time,
Martin, I can feel it.
I'll take the whore.
Well, how's she gonna get backed to...
Cedar Springs?
Pearl ain't going back, she's stayin'.
Stayin'?
Pearl ain't never lived on a farm or had no
children to mind, I got a lot to teach her.
Besides, once I get down to dyin'
could take a long time,
gonna need some help around here.
It ain't godly all of
us living together here.
She can stay in the shed.
You can build her bunk?
I'll make her some curtains.
No, Amy... her and me and
you and you and her and...
It's the only sensible way.
Sensible, but it ain't godly.
Nice chattin' with you.
So for ear ache,
Nathan gets them all the time,
just mix a little tobacco juice, then
you boil it up, pour it in the ear warm.
And you'll notice I always leave
cobwebs in the corner, stops the bleedin'.
And for croup, I...
Oh!
Excuse me?
Can you get that, that's a good one?
What is this?
Apple droppin's,
makes good fuel.
- You bring 'em in the house?
- Gotta bring 'em in to use 'em.
We store 'em outside, they're all
dried out, hard to smell it all.
Come winter, you'll be
real grateful for 'em.
Sure I'll rush right out and kiss
the first buffalo's ass I spy.
Well, Abe Lincoln should forgot
about the slaves and freed you.
Oh! My soup!
- All right.
- I slept on worse.
I'll bet.
Sorry, uncalled for.
That's all right, never knew you
could put a whole sentence together.
What's that?
Just stuff someone gave me once.
Can I try?
Maybe sometime when you have a little
more skin showing through that mud.
I know why you're here.
Wish I did, kid.
How old do they have to be before
they start changing themselves?
No, I'll do it.
Here! Here! Look, watch this!
You all right, Jack?
Nathan put a grasshopper down my pants!
Stop that, Nathan,
tell your brother you're sorry.
And tell that grasshopper you're sorry, too.
Pearl, what are thinkin' about?
About all those nights I
was laying with some...
sweaty... unshaven...
foul breath drunks,
huffing and puffing on top of me.
Never realized how lucky I was.
- Pearl?
- Yeah.
- We're in.
- Hear you.
Just some water.
- Smells good.
- Got it from Europe.
I like to look my best for the pigs.
I was gonna prepare the jerky for the
smokin', thought you might want to see how.
I can hardly wait.
Here, try some.
It's so soft.
I make my own complexion salve from white
wax and sweet oil and rose petals.
Ain't the same as store bought.
That's so dear.
Oh!
They're beautiful Black Deer, thank you.
There for you, Jack,
aren't they beautiful?
Yes, Black Deer,
I'm sure my friend would like some, too.
- Bye!
- Goodbye!
I wonder what he thinks about us.
Well, he thinks we're plumb strange.
He's got my vote.
Listen you!
Since you got here you ain't stopped
snipin' at the way we
do and the way we are.
I haven't even started yet.
Oh, what? If you hate it here so much,
why don't you just pack up and leave?
Because what the hell are
you gonna do if I do?
Even if I am stupid enough
to take on this mess?
Oh, well, don't you worry about me,
I'm sure that's there's another old
whore right out pack it in somewhere.
Oh, god, I'm sorry, Pearl,
don't leave, please.
I ain't leavin', don't worry, deal's a deal.
When I was 12 my daddy
sent me to a whorehouse,
I didn't have a lot of choice in the matter.
But there was times down the road,
I had some put by, I coulda got out.
I know where this is done me.
And I was young and pretty,
I could have found a man, raise kids.
I had a choice.
I made it, now I gotta live with it.
Hey, if I can manage to
hate what you got here,
just a little bit,
makes that easier to do.
I try to get in an hour during the
day and then an hour after supper.
This here's a good primer to start them
out on and then this one's for history.
And here's the book of English
poems by some English fellas
and it's might hard but
like some of the words.
Pearl...
Listen,
I never had much need for reading,
so I'm not going to be able to help 'em.
- Can't your husband teach 'em?
- No.
Martin pretends to read the Bible
but he only knows it by heart.
But it... it.. it doesn't matter,
they're building the school house,
hope to hire a teacher by February.
It's only 6 miles,
Jessica and Nathan can attend there.
Good.
Look, I... might be able to teach 'em
a few songs, I'm good at that.
Ask me what 35% of something is.
Go on!
Well, what's 35% of 600?
Two hundred and ten.
Figure it, go on!
Ask me something else, tougher, real tough.
Four thousand nine
hundred and eighty.
One thousand seven
hundred and forty three.
That's a wonder, how did you do that?
The house I worked at
in... in... New Orleans,
the Court Rouge, whatever I
earn took 65%, I took 35%.
So I got real good at the calculatin'.
Pick her up under the arms,
she won't slip or anything.
- Right on your shoulder, right there.
- Ain't exactly ugly are they?
No they ain't.
Think maybe you'd like
to have one, still could?
One got started in there once, had to
get it stopped by the local barber.
He did a bit too good of a job.
Ain't no way another baby'll
get started in there.
Pearl made the pie, ain't it good?
Uh-huh.
- Well, tell her it's good.
- I just did.
No ya didn't, ya told me.
She picked the berries, rolled the dough,
did the whole thing by herself.
First pie she made her whole life.
Now, you tell her it's good.
I already did.
Silver tongued devil ain't he?
You sure?
I've been feelin'
real fine these last few days.
If it hurts you, you tell
me straight away, alright?
Okay.
Oh! Ow!
It's pressin' inside me, I just can't.
- ..._..._ ..._...
- No, ya don't.
How come we used to do
it near every night?
A man wants it but he don't need it.
- Martin.
- Huh.
If you and Pearl wanna...
have at it... it's fine with me.
Have at what?
Do it, you know?
What?
You know...
Holy... what are you...
woman are you out of your mind?
Soon as I die, you're going to
be doing it anyway, why wait?
What kind of man do
you think you married?
You're good man, but you're a man.
You're entitled to the comforts of a woman's
body and I can't give it to ya no more.
Well, that's fine, we'll just call her right
in here and you can sit right over there
and you can watch us have at it and give
her instructions on the whole damn thing.
I just wanted ya to know...
I just want you to know that if I
hear another word about this,
I'll call a whole arrangement off
and send her packin'.
Understand.
I understand.
Consider it of ya to figure it though.
35% of $100 is $35, 35% of $200
is $70, 35% of $300 is $105.
- You get the milk for Jack?
- What?
- Did you get Jack's milk?
- Milk? Uh... yeah.
All right.
- Beautiful day.
- What?
I'm just commenting on the
beautifulness of the day.
- Oh.
- Ya hear that?
It's a jay, that's what it is, a jay.
- Ya don't say?
- Ya like birds?
Nothin' specific against 'em.
Now me,
I... I always loved birds ever
since I was I was...
I was tiny and I did their calls.
I can do all kinds of...
do all kinds of owls.
Ya know, I can...
this here's a screech owl.
This is... this here's a...
a flammulated owl.
This is a... a...
great horned owl.
Real impressive.
Let go of 'em.
Amy says to go ahead and do it.
I don't imagine it's gonna be too easy
doin' birdcalls without your teeth.
Well, you're a... you're whore, aren't ya?
No, I ain't a whore, I was a whore,
but now I'm a fiancé, you got that?
Dad! Dad! It's ma!
She's having a stomach attack.
What?
Ma just plopped down on the
floor, her stomach's hurtin'.
- It's bad, never hit inside someone's house.
- Easy!
Give her some laudanum.
I gave her some laudanum.
- Give her some more.
- It's too soon.
- Just get it!
Now!
Good night, Mommie.
Look here, honey,
Pearl's brought you something to eat.
It's a little hot, but don't ya wanna
try a little bit, just a...
I can't.
Well, just try it, one little taste,
don't want to hurt Pearl's
feelin's now, do ya?
- One more.
- I just can't.
All right.
Ya want...
ya want Jessy to read to ya or somethin',
Ya know she reads better me now
and Mr. Honaker give us this
Atlantic Monthly it's only a
year old, he let us borrow it.
No, just let me sleep, okay?
All right.
Go to sleep.
I...
No kissing.
Why not?
Kissing's special, anybody
can do this, animals do this.
People's the only creatures that can
kiss... it oughta mean somethin'.
- Very interestin'.
- The rest is all right.
You better go, she'll
wake up, she'll miss you.
Naw, it's all her idea,
it's what she wanted.
Sometimes what a woman says she wants
is a long walk from what she really wants.
Well, I think I'm gonna I tell her about it,
I think she's just gonna be real
happy that you and me are getting along.
- Tell her.
- Uh-huh.
- I don't think so.
- Well, I'm gonna.
Oh, yeah, and uh... uh...
this here was... uh...
real nice.
- You gonna tell her that, too?
- Of course.
Well, hold on,
I don't think I want to miss this.
Morning.
Mornin'.
Amy... uh...
Pearl and I did like you said and uh...
we uh... well, Pearl was
afraid, you wouldn't be glad
and I told Pearl that you'd be
glad and so... well... you're glad.
Aren't ya?
Of course I am.
Why don't you go start the stove.
Oh, Jessica's done doin' that.
- No, I wanna talk to Pearl.
- Oh, all right.
I'll just uh...
Pearl... come here.
- Was he all right?
- What?
Was he, you know, satisfying
to you, was he all right.
You've been married to the man 10 years
anybody knows that it ought to be you.
Well, course he's always been fine for me,
but... he's the only man I've ever known.
And you with your
broader experience
might judge him differently
based on more stringent standards.
- You phrased that real nice.
- Thank you.
Well, based on my... stringent
standards, he stood up real good.
- I'm pleased.
- The pleasure was all mine.
Just before he... exploded,
did he shout anything?
Well, I was kinda busy myself but,
uh... I... I think... glory, glory?
- That's it.
- Every time?
Every time, every time.
Don't it... hurt you... thinking
about me with him... like that.
Yeah... it does...
but not as much as the
thought of you leavin'.
Water! I got water! Water!
- Yea!
- Yes, sir! Yes, sir!
I'm gonna get you wet!
Water!
There ya go, Hon.
Family, this here is Royal Spencer,
he owns the farm 30 miles over
to Riverdale... from church.
You wants some... somethin'
to eat or something, Royal?
- Uh, no thank you.
- Maybe some coffee.
- Coffee?
- Comin' right up.
Coffee.
My wife just had a baby,
it's our first son.
Uh-huh.
We're having a shivaree
a week from Saturday and
I'd like to invite you and the Mrs.
Oh, well, Mrs. Hightower,
you see, is over
here in bed, this is our
friend is Miss Hickson, and,
as you might notice my wife
is doin' none too well.
- She...
- She's dying.
- Now, hush now, Nathan!
- You and Pearl go.
- No, Amy.
- She never stops workin'.
and does everything I used
to and has nurse me as well.
They oughta do 'er good.
- Amy...
- Don't argue with me, just do it.
You'll be fine.
Well, wadaya think?
Beautiful... maybe a tad too
beautiful for the folks around here.
Yeah, that's what I figured,
it's the only party dress I still got.
Well, maybe we can let out mine around
here and it would fit you just fine.
Oh, I don't know, it's one thing
borrowin' a woman's husband,
a party dress is a
whole other thing.
- All right?
- Well, maybe a few more buttons... I think.
Martin!
You need some water, Jessica'll fetch it for
ya and Jack and Nathan will start the fire.
Nathan's pretty good with the...
with the matches now, and...
We'll be fine, I'm feeling better.
- Wait a second.
- What?
Offer her your arm.
- Why?
- Just... offer her your arm.
You make a fine looking couple.
Afternoon, good to see ya,
come on in.
Food's over here, the dance has just
started, you go enjoy yourself.
Excuse me, may I?
My name is Jake Masterson,
I'm Royal's kin.
Woulda asked you t'dance earlier
but figured you was the Mrs.
to that feller that come in here.
And Royal tells me you're just
staying with him and his wife.
Um-hum.
Ya know, you're the prettiest woman here.
The fact is, you're the prettiest woman
I've seen since I got here six months ago.
I guess you're probably the
prettiest woman I ever seen.
- I guess what I'm trying to say is...
- I'm pretty.
Yep.
I was wonderin' if I might be able to come
by and call on ya some evenin' and, uh...
with the possible eye on the
venture of matrimony.
Excuse me, thank you.
- What did he want?
- To marry me.
- What did ya say?
- Didn't have a chance to answer.
Excuse me.
You've danced with her already and
now she's dancin' with who brung 'er.
- I just want to finish our conversation.
- Your conversation is finished.
Do that again and you're gonna regret it.
Well, I'll take that chance.
I coulda knocked his block
off, he was just lucky, he's a
little faster and stronger, a little
more skilled than I was, I suppose.
Yeah, he was fortunate in that regard.
Let's understand somethin',
I'm not sure property.
We have a business arrangement,
a provisional business arrangement.
And if certain eventualities should
come to pass and I become... your wife,
then you'll be entitled to certain
expectations in regard to my behavior.
Until then, I'm gonna do
what I want with who I want.
What in the hell are you
talking about doing
a business arrangement after
how we've been together?
That don't count for nothin'.
In deference to
your wife's wishes,
I've simply been servicing
certain of your biological needs.
It's all that easy.
Whoa!
Then how come when I
saw in that man's arms,
it felt like someone was
banging a stake in my gut?
Whoa there! Whoa!
How'd you get here?
Jessica helped me over, you can bring
the rest of my things in the morning.
What happened to you?
Oh, don't mind that.
What are you doin'?
I want Pearl to move into
the house with you.
- No, Amy!
- I can't do that.
- That's your home.
- It ain't gonna be long now.
It'd pleasure me considerable to
see all of ya livin' like a family.
- Considerable.
- No, absolutely not.
Makes no sense my being in the house.
I keep you awake all night, and I can't
rest with the children playing.
Well, I'll just march right on
over there and I'll keep 'em still.
I don't imagine the next
while being too pretty.
I'd rather the children didn't
have to see and hear everything,
Please, it's what I want.
...of three hundred dollars
is a hundred and five dollars.
- 35 percent of four hundred dollars is...
- What?
- A hundred and forty dollars!
- Yes!
It's been three days since
she's kept anything down.
It's okay, honey, come on in.
It's okay.
We don't have to do this now.
We shouldn't do this now.
Yes we do, got to do it now,
got to do it proper.
- You want me to stay?
- Course.
Gotta have witnesses.
Oh, honey... right?
The last will...
and... testament of...
How do you spell "testament"?
I don't remember.
Just do it how it sounds, it'll be fine.
Amy Marigold Hightower.
I didn't know ya had a middle name.
- I never liked it much.
- I think it's pretty.
To my beautiful... daughter Jessica,
I leave my...
jade pin that was my grandma Reba's.
And... to Nathan I leave
my volume of poetry.
And to Jack...
to Jack I leave my daddy's silver tie pin.
And... to my precious baby Margaret,
my photograph in my diary
so she may know me a little bit.
And to my adoring friend Pearl...
all my dresses she can find use for.
In particular...
but you can leave that one out...
my wedding dress.
And to my loving husband, Martin...
my share of the claim and all
the rest of my worldly goods.
Did ya get that, honey?
Most of it, I reckon.
Let me sign it.
I need you to sign, here.
Jessy, come here, you go in and see to the
children's supper, it's in the stove.
- Can I have a piece of bacon?
- Sure, go ahead..
G'mornin'.
Just had a hand for some Johnny cakes,
come and get it while it's hot.
Come on.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Oh, why don't you let me do that?
You go help Martin with the shoeing.
You shouldn't overdo it,
why don't you go lie down?
I don't ever want to... lie down again.
I just want to run and jump
and dance and eat like a pig.
I feel so good.
I guess God wasn't ready for me yet.
Maybe hell was so crowded nowadays,
they're using Nebraska for the overflow.
It feels so good, it feels so good.
Go to her, Martin.
You're her husband.
You belong in her bed, not mine.
- You love her don't you?
- I'll always love 'er.
I was merely substitutin'
for her during her indisposition.
I thought it might be permanent.
Isn't that so?
Go on!
Ya know, it just ain't right, first she says
me to you, and now you send me to her and...
I feel like some great big
old Indian rubber ball.
It's all right... go on.
It's just real confusin' bein' a man.
Where do you think you're goin'?
Stage Coach Station.
- No you ain't.
- Yes, I am.
I got no place back there
now, you know that's so.
Just like that, just up and go? Whoa!
I was hoping to avoid
this very conversation.
Well, it ain't fair, we had an arrangement.
Yeah, that's right, we did, and you didn't
keep up your end, you didn't go belly up.
You just can't trust some people.
We woulda lost the farm if it weren't for
all you've done, and we owe you so much.
Not as much as you think,
I took $20 and the egg money.
These last months, I didn't
exactly get nothing from 'em.
In fact, if you just give me a ride
to the station, it might be near quick.
- So where are you going?
- Oh, maybe Oregon.
- Got lots of lumber camps up there.
- What are ya gonna do?
- No, Pearl!
- It's what I do best.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
But if I'd wanted a husband, I wouldn't
have any trouble around these parts.
Put a skirt on a warthog,
somebody'd marry it.
I guess a husband and a family just
ain't what I want, that's all.
- Why not?
- Who knows?
I do, within your heart, you already
have a husband and family, it's mine.
Whoa!
You ain't leavin',
we're gonna work something out.
This farm is your home, you belong here.
- What about your husband?
- We'll work something out there, too.
It makes such perfect
sense, there's way too
much work for all of
us to do around here.
So it'll be like this...
I'll do the housework
and  Pearl'll help you
in the field one day,
and the next day we switch.
That way you'll always have a helper
and life will be easier for everyone.
Sounds practical.
Now, Pearl's insisted on
moving back in the shed.
But I figured with all
of us working, you'll have
time to put that addition
on we were talking about
and Pearl have our
own room right in here.
- I'll get started on it right after planting.
- Good.
And there's one other thing, since Pearl
and me gonna be sharing all the chores,
the cooking the cleaning,
the laundry, the child rearing,
I think it's only fair  that
we should share everything...
including... your attentions.
What exactly you proposin'?
Well, you have a deep
feeling for me, don't you?
You're my wife, Amy.
And you have a deep feeling
for Pearl, too, right?
Well, yeah.
We both have similar feelings for you.
So I don't see any reason why all these
feelings shouldn't be accommodated.
You don't?
Well, what about God?
Why are you always bringing
him into it, he won't mind?
King Solomon was God's Anointed
and he had 1000 wives.
And those Mormons, they're Christians
and they have as many wives as they want.
Well, I ain't no king
and I ain't no Mormon.
So how was you plannin' on doing it?
Is it like the housework, she
gets me Monday, Wednesday, Friday,
you get me Tuesday,
Thursday, Saturday?
Or maybe you was plannin' on us all
bouncing around  in bed all at once.
Well, sorry Martin. I just thought
you might like the idea.
I didn't say I didn't like it,
Amy, I said it aren't right.
And it is right for Pearl to leave here,
no place to go when we promised
her this would be her home?
Well, no it aren't,
but she can stay here without...
No she can't!
A woman has needs, too, just like a man.
- She does?
- Yes.
And it's more than that,
Pearl has a very
special attachment to you.
You've been with me,
you've been with Pearl.
Yeah, but whilst I was with you,
I was just with you,
and whilst I was with Pearl,
I was just with Pearl,
I didn't go switching back
and forth, night to night.
What if it wasn't switching
back and forth, night to night?
What if it was... say, half... half a
year with her and half a year with me?
Well, that might make a difference
seems a little more... dignified.
Yep, it might make a difference to me.
I think that can be arranged,
what do you think, Pearl?
Who gets winter?
We'll draw a straw.
I think we managed
that right well.
Let's seal it with the kiss.
Come on.
Well...
ya know, we might not have
to wait exactly... half a year.
I think... three months might work fine.
Or maybe one...
one month might do.
Or...
tell you what...
one week might do fine...
long as it wasn't... ya know...
- Back and forth, night to night?
- Right!
At first anyways.
Pretty cold night.
- Pearl must be freezing in that shed.
- I hope she's alright.
Ain't it pretty?
I'll get your candy for ya.
Here it is, here it is!
Here ya go.
How do you know you're gonna like this?
You never tasted molasses candy before,
how do you know?
You know! Yeah!
You're gonna get better,
just like last time, I promise ya.
I hope so.
I better put this little one to bed.
Pearl.
Ya know, a little while
ago you helped me out back,
- you know what I was thinkin'?
- What?
Right when I was doing it,
I was thinking this here's my last pee.
Oh... Amy.
I haven't really appreciated it before.
I'm gonna miss it.
It's a real good thing.
You ever notice?
No... well...
try t'pay it more heed in the future.
Ya know, you had bad spells before.
Nathan... he's got a real good head...
they build that high school up
in Holdrege, you make him go.
Jessica, she's just got
to know your love her,
ya gotta to tell her
every day, or she forgets.
Then Jack, he'll try to see what
he can get away with, but...
just let him know what the
limits are and he'll accept 'em.
Then Margaret...
a little early the tell,
but... I think she's gonna be a beauty.
Still ain't no reason to spoil her.
- Spoil her a little.
- Yeah, okay.
Any tips on how to handle your husband?
Oh... well...
Someday years from now
you and him are going to
be having some argument about
something or another, and...
he'll make some nasty reference
to your life before you came here.
Of course he'll feel rotten about it and
be all contrite and beg you to forgive him.
You will forgive him, won't you?
Sure I will...
right after I knock him right
upside the head with the iron pot.
Is that all right?
Well, the pot's a might extreme, but...
the philosophy's good.
You gotta get some rest.
Pearl.
A while ago, I was talking to my maker,
and I was real angry with him.
And I was asking him, "Why?
Why do you want to take me so soon?"
I realized...
it's the only way he could figure
it out to get me to meet you.
It shut me up real good.
Lord, thou hast been our
dwelling place in all generations.
Before the mountains
were brought forth,
for even thou hast formed the earth in the
world, from everlasting to everlasting.
Thou art with God, the Lord
shall preserve thee from all evil,
yea, it is even He that shall keep thy soul.
The Lord shall preserve thy going out
and thy coming in,
from this time forth, for forevermore.
Do you take this man to be
your lawfully wedded husband,
to have and to hold,
to love and to cherish,
in sickness and in health,
until death do you part?
I do.
And do you Edwin Jerome Beasley
take Jessica Anne Hightower
to have and to hold,
to love and to cherish,
in sickness and in health,
till death do you part?
Today, by the power vested
in me by this church,
and by the State of Nebraska,
I pronounce you husband and wife.
My word!
You'd think it was our wedding night.
I'm a very fortunate man.