[instrumental music]
[audience cheering]
[man whistling]
[camera clicks]
[dramatic music]
[crowd whistling]
[music continues]
[indistinct chatter]
[instrumental music]
[sighs]
[woman] So he takes my design,
slaps the company logo on it
and submits it anonymously.
And I'm supposed to be cool
with that
because I'm a team player.
Oh, hey, uh, the couple
that bought Harold's house
moved in today.
Wow!
Thanks for the emotional support
there, Trev.
I am supporting you,
just quietly.
By changing the subject?
By not disagreeing with you.
- Do the new neighbors have kids?
- I don't know, kiddo. Maybe.
I'm supposed to just suck it up
is what you're saying?
It kinda seems like you're
putting words in my mouth.
Mom, can I be excused?
- Am I wrong?
- Mom?
[clears throat] Look,
everybody knows it's your work.
So just, I don't know,
b-boost the firm,
not the individual.
I guess, I-I understand
the mentality is all.
What is it
about being unemployed
that turns everybody
into a communist?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It's a joke, Trev.
- Lighten up.
- Can I be excused?
I'm the one who needs
to lighten up. Copy that.
Yes, honey, you can be excused.
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't take it out on you.
I should just put my head down
and do the work.
Anyway, forget it.
What about the new neighbors?
Nothing. They seemed nice.
I didn't know
the house was for sale.
The old man's
only been dead for two weeks.
It's a hot market.
Gotta move fast.
[mellow music]
[car engine starts]
-[tires screeching]
- Oh! Oh! [sighs]
[chuckles] I don't know
where my head's at this morning.
That's what you have me for.
Don't forget to pick up Clio
after practice.
I'm on it.
Great.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
Hey, excuse me!
I am sure
it's something super simple.
I've just been pressing the same
buttons over and over again
for the last half hour.
[chuckles]
- Oh-oh!
-[laughs] Yeah.
-[woman] Oh, my God. Awesome.
- Yeah.
- All right. Okay.
-[woman] Cool.
Well, um, just... Sorry.
- Uh, just...
- Mm-hmm.
Let me know if you need help
with anything else.
Um, I noticed you around
during the day.
- Do you work from home or...
-[machine whirring]
- Uh... [chuckles] Yeah.
-[laughs]
- Yeah, mostly, um... yeah.
- Doing what?
I, uh, do some consulting
and music,
but right now
I'm kind of in between gigs.
And your wife? Wife, right?
Yes. Yeah, wife. Renee.
She works
at an architectural firm.
Cool. She's an architect.
Architectural designer.
Isn't that, like,
kinda the same thing?
[laughs] Uh, apparently no.
No, not according to her.
Yeah. [clears throat]
Hey, actually, you know what?
Uh, the two of you
should come by
sometime this week
for, like, drinks and dinner,
and then we can let you in
on the deep, dark secrets
of the neighborhood.
Cool, I'd love that.
- Yes, I'll figure something out.
- Okay. Thanks.
[Trevor] Nope!
All right, you got this,
slugger. Come on.
[Trevor whistling]
[crowd cheering]
[Trevor] Make him pay, kiddo.
You got this.
-[Trevor] Swing!
-[Clio grunts]
[crowd cheering]
Yeah! That's my girl!
Let's go! Let's go!
Safe!
Yeah!
[Clio grunts] What'd you say...
[screaming] Come on, Pat,
dig it!
Okay!
-[grunting]
- Ow.
Look, I don't care
what he said to you.
Okay? I really don't.
Okay, I give up.
What did he say?
[indistinct whispering]
What?
Okay. Good job.
We're not gonna tell mom,
but I'm glad you hit him.
-[giggles]
- You did great.
No fights, okay?
You mean, like, with Clio
or you mean, like, you and me?
All fights.
Well, I'm down.
Well, I don't know about Clio.
- That girl's a warrior.
- Yeah.
- Where did she get that from?
- I don't know.
Hm. Where could she
get that from?
- Xena.
-[chuckles]
You know, I think
we should have
the neighbors over for dinner.
Uh, yeah.
- No?
- No. Ye-yes. Yeah.
Um, I actually, already
mentioned it to Kaylie, so...
- Kaylie?
- Yeah.
I think that's her name.
Great.
Did, uh, did you and Kaylie
set a date?
No.
Just, you know,
mentioned it in passing.
Like, "Hey, you and your husband
should come over
for dinner sometime."
Nothing specific.
Yeah, o-okay. Yeah, sure.
We should do that.
[chuckles] Okay.
What was the husband's name?
Uh, it's Ray, I think.
[Ray] Then they told me I can
paint the house any color I want
as long as it's Boston Brick
or Wedgewood Gray.
[Trevor] Oh, welcome
to our homeowner's association.
- Your home is beautiful.
- Mm.
Like a museum.
My great-grandfather built it.
It's been in the family
ever since.
- Yeah.
- Ooh, Ray?
Ah, what the hell?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- I'm not driving, right?
So Kaylie says
you're in the music business.
Yes, yeah, I've, uh, I've done
some session work off and on,
but, ah, with the way
the music business is right now,
it's, it's more off than on.
[Renee] He's amazing.
If Stevie Ray Vaughan
and Andres Segovia
had a love child...
You should hear him play.
- I wo... I'd like that.
-[Ray] Wait, Andres who?
Hey, Clio,
what's your favorite animal?
[virtual assistant]
Boo the Space Hamster.
-[Clio laughs]
- Oh, my God.
You guys have
one of those smart thingies.
Yeah, well, as soon as she
found out that there was one
with her name,
she insisted on it.
Although, it can get
a little messed up at times.
Hey, Clio, do you know
that you're beautiful?
[virtual assistant]
Life is beautiful.
No, seriously. I mean it.
You are such a beautiful
little girl.
You're like a princess.
Tsk. Oh, she doesn't really do
the princess thing.
We don't really believe
in gender stereotypes.
Uh-huh, but every girl wants
to be a princess, don't they?
I guess.
Ever thought about
being in a beauty pageant?
Oh, my gosh, you remind me
so much of me at your age.
It's crazy. I can't get over it.
My dad was a pageant judge.
- No way!
- I was.
- Wow!
- Whoa!
- Where the hell did that go?
- Oh, gosh. Here.
- Let me top you off.
-[Ray] Sure.
[Trevor] Yeah.
[Ray] Pour away.
[Renee] So did any of you
see the news?
Apparently,
the riots in Cleveland
are the worst since Ferguson.
Ah, that's right,
yeah, it's like
a dozen people killed so far.
God gave us
so many incredible blessings,
but also the responsibility
to look after those
less fortunate than ourselves.
It's like, if we could just
love one another
and look past our differences,
we could end hate
in our lifetime.
Wow, that is so true
and just... beautiful.
Hm.
Seriously?
What's that?
I better get dessert.
- Can I help?
- No.
No, I'm, I'm good. Yeah.
It's okay.
- Well, this has been great.
- Yes.
Thank you so much for having us.
- Of course. Yeah.
- This is amazing.
[sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
[Trevor] They make it.
[Ray] Yeah.
-[Ray] Oh, that looks delicious.
- Ice-cream!
-[Ray] Nice job.
- Yeah.
So you and Ray...
how did you two meet?
- I'm sorry?
- How did you get together?
- When was your OMG moment?
- She thinks we're...
Um... [chuckles]
Oh, my gosh, no. Uh...
Ray is...
He's my-my big brother.
I've known him my whole life.
Believe me,
no OMG moments so far.
-[chuckles]
-[Renee] I though you said...
Oh, no, I...
I don't think I said either way.
[Kaylie] Oh, no, no,
I-I can totally understand
why you two thought that,
but, no.
Ray and I, we, we've been living
together for about a year.
We were living with my mother
until she passed away,
and we inherited some money
and we just kinda
wanted to make a change.
- And get out of there, you know?
-[Trevor] It's really cool.
Uh, not about your mom,
obviously, but...
- Right. Thank you.
- Thanks. Yeah.
We've both been going through
some changes
and we wanted to stick together
for the time being.
We're the only family
we have left
and family is everything.
- Yeah.
- Right, princess?
- Right.
- Mm-hmm.
- Cheers to family.
- Yeah.
-[Ray] To family.
[mellow music]
[birds chirping]
[Renee] So I'm gonna be
late tonight.
We have a big deadline at work,
and yours truly has to do
all the heavy lifting,
anonymously.
- Again.
- Ow!
But happy anonymous.
Well, don't you worry about us
because I am gonna whip up
another fantastic meal of
dead skin and rodent droppings.
Sorry to miss that.
Clio, can you add frozen dinners
to the grocery list?
[virtual assistant] What type of
frozen dinners would you like?
- Pizza!
- What?
[virtual assistant]
Adding frozen pizza.
Speaking of dinner,
the birthday boy needs to think
about where he wants to go for
his birthday dinner next week.
Oh, it's my birthday already
again?
Every year around this time.
Yeah. No birthday. No!
[sighs]
Did you do your homework?
Yeah?
- Hey, what was that?
- What?
Well, I mean, it's the first
time I've ever seen you
go around the puddle
and not through it.
- No.
- Hm.
Is my little tomboy
turning into a little lady?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Are you, are you a little lady?
- No.
Oh, that was very lady-like.
That was...
Oh, are you pushing me? Huh?
♪ Inside my little shell
♪ All my demons love me
♪ And we know each other well
♪ Don't get too close to me
♪ That's what I...
- Hey.
- Hi.
Ah, so this is how you stay
in such good shape?
[chuckles] Yeah,
turns out, my morning latte
has more calories
than two glazed donuts.
It is a cruel, cruel world.
- Tell me about it.
- Yeah.
Well, gotta run.
Right. Yes.
I should get back to it.
Yup. Awesome.
♪ I never feel alone
♪ Don't get too close to me
[grunts]
♪ I warned you
♪ Ah ah-ah-ah
♪ Whoa-oh-oh
♪ Ah ah-ah-ah...
- Hey.
- Mm. Hey.
- How's it coming?
- It's coming.
Why did you add
the clerestory windows?
Uh, more light, more privacy.
It really is quite, uh...
- It's quite brilliant.
- Thanks, John.
When you're done, I'll run it by
the client, see what she thinks.
But, uh, also finish modeling
the other version, okay?
Just in case.
Goodnight.
♪ Don't get too close to me
[guitar music]
[clears throat]
♪ Well I'm tired of the way
you look at me ♪
♪ When I speak my mind
♪ I'm tired of the words
that you put in my mouth ♪
♪ Happens all the time
♪ I ain't looking
for someone... ♪
[laughs, mumbles]
- Hi.
Don't stop on my account,
please.
Uh, yeah.
I don't, I don't usually sing,
I just play, but, uh...
- You want a beer?
- Yes, thank you.
- There you go.
- Sounds great.
- Keep playing.
- Okay. Ah!
- Go on.
- Okay.
[clears throat]
♪ I ain't lookin'
for someone to save me ♪
♪ I ain't waitin'
on a flash of light ♪
♪ I've lived too damn long
to apologize now ♪
♪ I just wanna have fun
tonight all right ♪
- Amazing.
- Thank you.
Oh!
So sorry if Raymond and I
gave you the wrong impression
about our... relationship.
Yeah, that was a,
a bit of a game changer.
He's my brother
and I love him to death,
but he can't really be alone
right now.
How so?
Just got out of rehab,
among other things.
Oh, I plied him with, like,
a gallon of wine last night.
- Oh, my gosh, don't feel bad.
- Oh.
He's an awful human being
when he's sober.
I hate to say it, but that's,
that's the God's honest truth.
Well, listen,
it's none of my business
and-and probably out of line,
but it sounds like
maybe you guys
could use some help.
Yeah, I've tried. He says
he's done with all that.
And I have my own issues
with the profession, you know?
Yeah.
But, hey,
we, we hardly know each other.
That's so not, not your problem.
Thank you for the beer
and the serenade.
Yeah, it's my pleasure.
- Kaylie, wait!
-[gasps] Oh, my goodness!
Hi, sweetheart. Why aren't you
inside doing your homework?
-'Cause you're here.
- Well...
I was just about to leave,
but not before... this.
[squeals] Do you like it?
[gasps] It's just
the beginner's crown.
I'm sure there will be more.
Okay, okay. Go inside.
Bye!
-[sighs]
- You didn't have to do that.
Oh, it's just my way of saying
thank you for an amazing dinner.
I hope she likes it.
Well, if she doesn't wear it,
I will.
[laughs] It will look good
on you.
- Mm.
- Bye.
Bye.
[guitar music]
[Ray] What's that?
Oh, God. This again?
Come on. Not today.
[Kaylie] Get your life together.
[Ray] Get what life together?
I don't have anything
to get together!
[indistinct yelling]
[Trevor] We had fried chicken
because I make what she likes,
and what she likes
is fried chicken.
Yes, tomorrow I will make
an entire plate
of fresh vegetables.
See how that goes over.
Mm-hmm.
I love you.
- Bye.
-[knocking on door]
- Hey.
- Hey. [sniffles]
I, uh, I didn't know
where else to go, so...
Yeah, no. Uh, come in.
[dog barking in distance]
Do you want something to drink?
Is, uh, scotch okay?
- Sure. Yeah.
- Okay.
So what happened?
He's just...
He, he loses it over
the tiniest things, you know?
There's a reason
people self-medicate.
Uh, what was it
that got him so upset?
You.
What?
He, he thinks I'm sweet on you.
That's...
Yeah, I told him he's crazy,
he...
- Mm.
- He didn't really like that.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I don't...
I don't think
crazy people usually
like being called crazy, so...
I'm sorry,
am I making you uncomfortable?
No, no, just that...
- Uh...
- I should go.
No, wait, uh...
You don't have to
if-if you don't want to.
Okay.
What are you,
what are you doin'?
- Ah. Ow!
- Do you want me to stop?
- Kaylie, I...
- Oops.
-[pant unzips]
- I forgot something. Panties.
Hey, do not...
Don't do this. Mm.
- Mm...
- Don't do what?
I-I can't do this.
Don't worry.
I'll be as quiet as a mouse.
Mm-hmm. Hey. Hey, I can't,
I can't, I can't do this.
Okay, I'm not this guy. I can't.
♪ I've waited too damn long
♪ To apologize now
♪ I just wanna
have fun tonight ♪
-[door shuts]
-[gasps]
[grunts]
- Uh...
- Hey.
- Huh?
- What just happened?
- Love the bed-head. [chuckles]
- Oh.
I'm sorry, what happened?
I got home so late last night,
so there was no point
in coming to bed.
I killed the alarm
so you could sleep in.
- What about...
- We are good.
Clio has had her breakfast,
she's upstairs
getting ready for school.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be.
It's nice to be mommy
every now and again.
- I could use the practice.
- Hm.
You okay?
[clears throat]
- Yeah.
- You sure?
Positive.
Okay.
-[engine starts]
- Oh, hey.
[sighs] Oh, thanks. I am
really gonna need this today.
[sighs] Have a good day.
[Renee] Mwah!
[guitar music]
[door opens]
[moans]
[vehicle approaching]
- Hi, daddy.
- Hey, kiddo.
Come here.
- What was that for?
- Hm.
What, is it illegal
to give your daughter a hug?
- No.
- No?
[cell phone vibrating]
Who's that?
It's nobody.
- So tell me.
- Hm.
What is on the tap for today?
- Geometry.
- Geometry?
- Ooh.
- But first, I need chocolate.
'Cause it helps me think.
- Yeah?
-[Clio] Yeah.
Okay. I think
there's some in the pantry.
[Clio] Yay!
- This is hard.
- It's supposed to be hard.
Clio, how do you calculate
the area of a trapezoid?
[virtual assistant]
The area of the trapezoid
is equal
to half of its height
times the sum of the lengths
of the two parallel sides.
Hey, little lady,
I'm pretty sure that's cheating.
- I don't think so.
- Hm?
- Clio, how do calculate the...
- Oh.
[virtual assistant] I'm sorry,
can you repeat that?
Clio, don't answer.
[virtual assistant]
Okay, Trevor.
Kaylie Drake left you
a voice note.
-Would you like to hear it?
- Yes!
[Trevor] No!
[virtual assistant]
"I just wanted to tell you
what a fantastic time I had
last night, Trevor."
- What did you and Kaylie do?
- Nothing.
I just, uh, I played her
one of my songs, is all.
Hey, Clio, you can go ahead
and erase that message.
[virtual assistant]
Message deleted, Trevor.
You, homework. And by yourself.
[woman] You had it all,
remember?
[sighs] Shame, in the end
you just couldn't seal the deal.
You let
all those small, pathetic men
walk right over you
like a doormat.
Don't worry, hon. You'll always
be my little sweetheart.
[screams]
[knocking on door]
- Hi.
- Hey.
We need to talk.
Come on in.
Oh, sorry for all the mess.
We're still unpacking.
I'm afraid, all I can offer you
is instant coffee.
Oh, thank you. Hey, look.
There's, uh, there's something
I need you to understand.
I don't have a clue where
half this stuff is gonna go.
It's a little overwhelming,
to be honest.
Hey, listen, about last night...
It can never happen again.
- Okay. [chuckles]
- I-I mean it.
O-okay, bye.
Well, it was a mistake.
O-obviously, it was my mistake.
Well, then you can just tell
your wifey and be done with it.
Hey, is everything good
between you two?
Things seem a little,
well, I don't know, strained.
I have a pretty good nose
for that sort of thing.
I was kind of hoping
we can leave her out of this.
That's kind of hard to do,
considering...
Considering what?
I mean, Kaylie, we...
We didn't even, uh,
go all the way.
Oh. "All the way?"
I feel like I'm at summer camp.
You were inside me,
babe-asaurus.
Accidentally left this thing
running last night.
How stupid is that?
Maybe I'll accidentally release
a sex tape.
[Trevor moaning on phone]
Uh-uh! Blip.
[cell phone beeps]
In the cloud.
Okay, look, whatever it is
that you're thinking about doing
or w-whatever this is, just...
It's over. Do you understand?
I mean, i-it never even was.
One and done. Got ya.
Wow, y-you, on the outside
you are a very beautiful woman,
but on the inside, you're s...
Now I'm beautiful
on the inside, too.
- What do you want from me?
- I don't know. An apology?
Okay. Fine, then I'm sorry.
Okay?
- I'm sorry for whatev...
- Not feelin' it, Trev.
Is this about money?
Trevor, you have no money.
I'd be taking it from your wife,
and I have nothing against her.
Besides, I would never wanna
do anythin'
to that wonderful, little girl
who I absolutely adore.
No, it needs to be
more personal.
Needs to come directly from you.
[gasps] I know.
A finger.
It's like how the Japanese
gangsters apologize, right?
- You can't be serious.
- Come on.
It's not like
I'm asking you for your arm
or your balls or anything.
Just one little finger.
You can even make it
the pinky finger if you want,
which isn't even really
a finger.
When you stop to think about it,
it's more like half a finger.
I'm not listening to this.
Seems like a pretty small price
to pay
for the woman you claim to love.
There's even a tribe in Africa
that cuts off a finger
when they get engaged.
How romantic is that?
I think 24 hours should be
sufficient, don't you?
Let's make the cut-off
at 5 p.m. tomorrow.
So to speak.
[mellow music]
[Kaylie laughs]
[Clio] You are funny.
[Clio chuckles]
[Kaylie] Turn around.
Let me see your hair.
[indistinct chatter]
-[Kaylie] Oh, my...
- Hey, Clio!
Hi, daddy! [chuckles]
You know what Kaylie and Ray
call themselves?
- Raylie.
-[both laughing]
Time to get inside, kiddo.
- Don't forget...
- Now.
Inside.
[door opens]
- She's here!
-[Renee laughs]
Hey.
Ah, what did I miss?
I'm sorry. I lost track of time.
Ooh, something smells good.
Mm.
You're angry.
I should've called. I'm sorry.
No, it's fine. You're busy, so...
No, it's not. You cooked.
The least I could do
is be home on time to eat it.
Oh, it's good.
It's really good.
I petted a skunk today.
Really? You don't smell
like you petted a skunk.
[Clio] It wasn't
that kind of skunk.
What other kinds of skunk
are there?
[Clio] The kind
that doesn't smell.
Hey, we don't talk
with our mouth full.
Well, he must've had
his scent glands removed.
[Clio] Yeah. You have to do it
when they're babies, though.
So I got a call from Kaylie
asking if I wanted
to have coffee tomorrow.
Great.
- You done?
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
No more late-nights.
I promise.
Unless it's more than that.
You'd tell me if it was,
wouldn't you?
Yeah.
"Yeah," what? [chuckles]
Yeah, I would tell you
if it's more.
[mellow music]
[screaming]
- Trevor?
- Hm?
[cheering]
[grunts]
[crowd cheering]
What's going on, kiddo?
I guess I just don't feel much
like playing anymore.
What? You love the game.
I know, but...
- But what?
- It's not feminine.
"It's not feminine?"
Okay. Hey, it's all right.
It's okay.
[laptop keys clacking]
[dramatic music]
[instrumental music]
[guitar music]
[sniffles]
[blowing raspberry]
[intense music]
Ugh, gross!
[cell phone beeps]
[message alert]
[clicks]
[instrumental music on laptop]
♪ They they go like that
and I was like... ♪
[clicks]
♪ I'm tired of the words
that you put in my mouth ♪
♪ Happens all the time...
[chuckling]
-Hello.
-[Kaylie] Hi.
I'm sorry,
am I making you uncomfortable?
No, it's just that...
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Look.
That's you and that's our house!
What have I said about using
the Internet
without our permission?
But it was Kaylie.
I don't care. Rules are rules.
Go to your room.
[intense music]
[music continues]
It was an accident.
[breathing heavily]
[garbage disposal whirring]
[garbage disposal turns off]
[Kaylie] Let's make the cut-off
at 5 p.m.
Clio?
Hey, Clio, where are you?
[virtual assistant]
Right here, Trevor,
metaphysically speaking.
[clanking]
Ouch.
Hey, Clio?
Clio!
[birds chirping]
[knocking on door]
Hello?
[instrumental music on stereo]
[music continues]
[grunting]
-[groans]
-[laughing]
I have a right
to defend my home.
Unfortunately, that doesn't
give me a legal right
to kill an unarmed intruder.
You know that sucks.
You can get murder, too, just
for protecting what's yours.
[sighs] Not that
I'm bitter or nothin'.
[coughing]
You're all right.
- Just breathe.
- My daughter.
What about her?
Where is she?
You have to ask my sis.
[Ray whistling]
Hey.
I heard you're thinking about
chopping off a finger.
Bit of practical advice.
The best way is to smash
your funny bone really hard.
Like this.
[Ray groans]
[laughs]
Uh...
Your hand goes completely numb
for about ten seconds
and that should give you
enough time to get the job done.
If you're quick about it.
You see,
the trick is not to hesitate.
[instrumental music on stereo]
♪ Ooh yeah
[door opens]
♪ Look away
♪ Yeah
Hi, daddy.
♪ Look away
You go home
and you wash that off now.
- But...
- Now! All of it!
Hey, come here.
I'm not mad at you, kiddo. Okay?
But Kaylie needs to know
what she did was wrong.
But we thought you'd like it.
Clio wanted to give you a big
surprise for your birthday.
Come on, let's go.
I'll meet you down there.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You still don't get it, do you?
Let me throw you a lifeline,
cutie.
Remember a certain
Miss Whittier Beauty Pageant?
Six years ago?
There was a contestant,
a pretty blonde
and a pageant judge who said
some really awful things
about her.
Bing!
You were blonde then.
[chuckles] So typical.
You change your hair and a dude
doesn't even recognize you
anymore.
So all of this, uh,
all of this is what?
Because you were offended?
Oh, all this?
All of this is for telling
the other judges
I tried to seduce you.
Yeah, you did, Kaylie.
You did try to seduce me.
We both know,
if I wanted to seduce you,
you'd be seduced.
Not much debate about that
anymore, is there, Trev?
Okay, you know what?
I'm sorry. Okay?
I'm sorry for whatever it is
that you think I did
or, or said. I'm, I'm sorry.
You think that's enough
for ruining my life?
I don't really understand
how one minor-league pageant...
[grunts]
One pageant?
My whole life was pageants,
Trevor.
I had to dress up in slutwear
and come on to middle-aged men
ever since I was five years old,
just so that I can bring home
these shiny little trophies
so that my mother
would love me.
Every pageant I entered...
I won.
Not because I cheated,
because I was better.
I was smarter,
sexier.
I deserved to win.
I deserved it.
And then comes Whittier.
And from there,
it's a straight shot
on to Miss California,
then Miss USA,
then Miss Universe.
That was my future, Trevor.
That was my destiny.
And you killed that.
You single-handedly killed it.
All because you thought
I was coming on to you?
Some basement-dwelling cockroach
who only got the gig
because mommy
was the pageant director
and you needed
a quick 300 bucks?
That pageant
meant nothing to you.
It meant everything to me.
Everything.
I never forgot you, Trevor.
And then there was that night
at Filly's...
[upbeat music]
[Trevor] It was just
a bachelor party.
Yes, it was.
You were so hammered,
you hardly saw me.
But I saw you.
Yucking it up with your buddies.
And that's when I think
it really...
it really clicked for me.
You were happy.
Tell your brother to move,
Kaylie.
No.
See, this is where
karma steps in.
I happen to see your neighbor's
name listed in the obits, right?
And a little light went off
in my head.
It's like,
"Kaylie Drake, this is it.
This is your moment."
[intense music]
What do you want from me?
Just a finger.
Something you give up in return
for what you took,
which was my future...
which was... my happiness.
You're insane.
- Fair's fair, lover boy.
- Please.
Tell your brother
to get out of my way.
Bye, Trev.
[water splattering]
[Trevor grunting]
[engine revving]
Hey, birthday boy.
I got you a little surprise!
[Trevor] Oh-oh.
I mean, it's not so little
and not so much of a surprise,
but... I hope you like it.
Yeah. Wow.
- What's the matter? You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
You look awful. Are you sick?
No, I just, I, I had
a little accident is all.
- You had an accident?
- Mm-hmm.
It's stupid,
I was, I was just chopping...
- Chopping?
- Yeah, uh, no.
I just, I wasn't paying
attention to what I was doing.
- It's fine.
- Come on, show me.
- It looks so much worse...
- Come on.
Let me see.
[gasps] Oh, my God.
- It's fine. It's not that bad.
- Come on.
- No.
- It-it, it is decidedly bad.
Come on. We need to get you
to the hospital.
I don't, I don't want to go
- We're going. Come on, let's go.
- I said no!
I'm so sorry.
I just... [clears throat]
If it doesn't stop bleeding
in, like, an hour, I'll go.
I promise.
Okay.
[mellow music]
Oh.
- Mm...
-[Trevor groans]
Somebody has an owie.
Okay. So that's it.
All this, it's-it's over.
Well, I mean, let's not
get ahead of ourselves.
What is that supposed to mean?
I'm just saying, what you did,
it was a sacrifice and all,
but not as big a sacrifice
as I thought you were making.
I mean, you could've
at least told me
instead of me
having to find out from Ray.
[stammers] Told you what?
I-I did exactly what you said.
- Look in the damn envelope.
- Oh, I know you did.
But that's... [chuckles]
that's not the point, Trevor.
The point is, you aren't really
gonna suffer much for this.
Are you? Mm.
Not much at all
when you think about it.
Not like I have
for all these years.
That's for sure.
Django Reinhardt, Jerry Garcia,
that dude from Black Sabbath...
What do all those guys
have in common, hm,
besides being epic guitarists?
We had an understanding.
Well, apparently, we only had
a partial understanding, Trevor.
You tricked me.
How was I supposed to know
you can still be a guitar god
with missing fingers?
Fair's fair, sweetie.
But don't worry, I will think
of something to even things out.
You're not gonna do anything...
because I'm not gonna let you.
Well, okay, then.
Guess I'll just have to start
thinking outside my box.
[crickets chirping]
[Trevor] Listen, I just,
I felt trapped
and I didn't see
another way out.
Are you listening to yourself?
Do you know how you sound
to a rational person?
Yeah, I do.
I just, I-I panicked, so...
I mean, to-to take a knife...
It wasn't a knife,
it was bolt cutters.
- I, I used bolt cutters.
- God!
I couldn't lose you.
I know this is gonna sound
horrible, but...
I'm kind of relieved.
At least
I don't have to wonder anymore.
- About Kaylie?
- Not just about Kaylie.
It's been going on
a lot longer than Kaylie.
Something changed with us
after Clio was born.
I mean, I don't know
if it was... parenthood
or work
or continental drift.
I just think every relationship
has growing pains.
No. It was more than that.
I honestly thought
you were gonna leave me.
I would never leave you.
Well, I see that now.
[both laughing]
Uh, yeah, I mean...
Maybe I should've done this
a long time ago.
I need you to know something.
If this is about John,
I really don't wanna hear it.
Great.
How long has that been going on?
A couple of months.
It was just once.
I don't, I don't know
if I was trying to hurt you...
or hurt myself.
I just needed to feel something.
Anything.
But afterward,
I just felt empty.
And that was it.
The next day I told him
it was a big mistake
and it would never happen again.
So all those late-nights were...
Because he wasn't there.
It was the only time
I could be alone.
And still,
he had his way with me.
He's taken all my designs
and doesn't give me credit
for anything.
I mean,
I guess that's my punishment
for taking what was going to be
a promising affair
and turning it
into a lousy one-night stand.
- You could've quit.
- Could I?
Yeah, you could've gone
to another firm.
With what?
I don't have a portfolio.
I don't have my name
on anything.
The second
I put myself out there,
he's gonna tear me down so fast
that no one would hire me.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything.
Me, too.
[intense music]
[birds chirping]
[man] What do you do?
[Trevor] Musician, mostly.
But that's not gonna be
happening anytime soon.
So I figured I'd get off
the couch, make myself useful.
So you don't have any real
construction experience?
Ah, I worked
with Habitat For Humanity
after college for a little bit.
Yeah? How'd that go?
Pay sucked. [chuckles] Yeah.
Well, look, I've just got
general labor stuff.
Uh, unloading, cleaning up.
- I can start you at 17 bucks.
- Yeah, that'd be great.
I just, I need to be done
in time to get my daughter
after she's off school,
if that's okay.
Yeah.
- Sign here and here.
- Yeah.
So you're good
with power tools, huh?
[chuckles] Long story.
So I'm thinking
of going back to school.
Maybe take the NCARB exam
this fall.
That's amazing.
Wow, our own board-certified
architect in the house.
Well,
I still have to pass the exam.
They say it's even harder
than the bar.
You'll nail it. I have no doubt.
Well, that's one of us.
Well, for what it's worth,
and trust me,
it's not worth much,
your husband got a job today.
[Renee] What? That's great!
Well, tell us about it.
Uh, it's construction.
Entry-level.
But it should count towards
my union days.
And, and who knows?
Maybe one day I will even build
one of those fancy houses
you design.
Well, what do you think
about that?
Your dad and I building a home
for some lucky family like ours.
[eerie music]
[Trevor panting]
[Renee] What's wrong, honey?
I hate parsnip.
[Trevor clears throat]
Am I ever going to see
Kaylie again?
[Renee] I don't know.
Not right now.
[Clio] Why not?
She's not a good person, kiddo.
Because she made you
cut off your finger?
Finish your stew.
[Trevor] What else
has she told her?
- That-that lying, manipulative...
- Trevor...
She's not gonna stop until she
turns our daughter against us.
- You know that, right?
- That's not gonna happen.
- Mm...
- Clio's a smart girl.
We're not gonna let her
get brainwashed
by some bitter,
has-been trash queen.
No, no.
Do not underestimate her, Renee.
I already
made that mistake once.
I didn't know you use this gym.
I know! It's crazy, right?
[sighs]
Well, since we're here,
I think you and I should have
a little chat.
Argh! My God!
Ow! What?
Uh, oh, not much.
I'm just being stalked is all.
What? Well, you're hot.
I'd stalk you, too,
if I wasn't your brother.
She threatened me.
Hey, what are you doing?
[Ray] Ow!
What is this?
- Do...
- What are you doing?
[Kaylie] Ugh...
[Ray] Oh, that's...
[Ray mumbles]
You're supposed to meet
with your PO this afternoon.
- Remember?
- Oh, PO.
I don't care.
I'll go back to prison.
I got friends there.
The food's good in prison.
They're not your friends,
Ray-Ray.
What?
You have no friends, remember?
- I have friends.
- I'm all you got.
- Yeah.
- And you're all I got.
We look out for each other.
Nobody else does that
and nobody ever will.
- Mm.
- Okay?
- Inside prison or out.
- Okay.
Just keep it together
for a few hours.
- Yeah.
- That's all I ask.
Okay.
Then I can tell you
all about my crappy day.
- Can you just don't do that?
-[toilet flushes]
[engine rumbling]
-[Renee grunts]
-[Clio chuckles]
You know you can tell us
anything.
Anything at all.
- We love you so much.
- Love you, too, mommy.
Mm...
All right.
[groans] These bones
weren't made for heavy lifting.
[groans]
Well, where does it hurt?
Everywhere.
Oh. That feels good.
[mellow music]
I feel better.
So do I.
[both chuckling]
[dramatic music]
[wind howling]
- Trevor, Trevor.
- Hm?
[knocking on door]
[Trevor] Hello?
Hello?
It's Trevor and Renee.
We're just looking for Clio.
- Oh, my God!
- What?
They haven't even unpacked yet.
Ray, I'm coming upstairs.
Don't do anything crazy.
The beds are stripped.
They're gone.
[music continues]
Trevor?
[footsteps approaching]
- What?
-[panting] The box.
It's empty.
They're all empty.
They don't live here.
The boxes, the truck...
It was all for show.
- No, it's not. It's not...
- They don't live here.
It's not possible.
They bought the house.
Did they? How do we know that?
The house
isn't even on the market yet.
Oh, my...
Oh, my... [sobbing]
She was here.
Clio was here.
[sobbing]
They left this so we would know.
[sobbing] No!
[sobbing]
- Hey, it's okay.
-[sobbing]
It's okay.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[dog barking in distance]
What are they doing
in the backyard?
It's just procedure, ma'am.
Are they looking for a body?
- Is that what they're doing?
- Renee, don't.
I wanna know what they're doing.
They're looking for anything
that might help
in the investigation.
Buried... in the backyard.
[Trevor] Look,
I-I spoke to Gary.
He's the president of our HOA,
and he said that the house
is still in probate, and it has
been ever since Harold Jenkins,
the previous owner died
last November.
Gary said he just assumed
that they were relatives
of Harold's or something.
[man] Nothing on a Kaylie Drake.
[sighs]
Try, uh, Kaylie Ann Clevender.
It was her name back then
in the pageanting days.
Did you call in an Amber Alert?
Your daughter's information was
entered into the NCIC system,
but we still need an accurate
description of the vehicle.
It was yellow. A compact.
Can you tell me what kind?
I don't know. I...
I-I didn't look at it closely.
This her?
Yeah, that's her.
We got ourselves a looker.
We got an address.
Our girl likes to keep moving.
Eleven known places of residence
in five states.
Always with her brother
until he upped and moved
to Washington State Pen.
Down the hall
from the Hillside Strangler.
Okay. So then, what do we do?
I mean, what's our next move?
Just sit tight for now,
we'll be in touch
the second we know anything.
Okay.
[woman] Ninety-seven percent
of all abducted kids
are found alive and well,
Mrs. Gustafson.
Those are
some pretty decent numbers.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[dramatic music]
[Renee] I'm trying to speak
to Detective Dobbs.
Uh, the other person had...
No. No. The other person...
The other person...
They transferred me to you,
so...
Hi. Yes. Yes. Yes.
I'm trying to speak
to Detective Dobbs.
No, you,
you are not putting me...
Okay. Yeah, hi. I'm trying
to speak to Detective Dobbs.
The, the other person
had me on hold.
No. The other...
[mellow music]
[music continues]
[sniffles]
Hey, Clio?
[virtual assistant]
Yes, Trevor?
Tell me about my daughter.
What would you like to know,
Trevor?
I don't know. Um...
Tell me what her smile's like.
I'm sure it's nice.
Where is she?
Clio, where is my daughter?
Your daughter
went to live with Kaylie.
She will miss you and Renee
very much.
How do you know that?
Clio made a note.
May 13th, 11:42 p.m.
Where did they go?
I don't have
that information, Trevor,
but I can play the voice note
if you'd like.
Yeah. Yeah, play it.
[Clio] Kaylie says
I'll get to go on fun trips
and wear
the prettiest clothes ever.
You'll both understand because
you only want me to be happy.
Kaylie says someday soon you'll be really, really proud of me.
And then all the sad stuff
will go away
and you and mommy
will never argue again.
[Clio] Daddy?
Come on, we're gonna be late.
[Renee] What do you mean,
"No police?"
Look, they have this
all figured out,
and, and whatever it is...
[sighs] they're the ones
that are in control,
so we have to do what they say.
But the police are trained
for this kind of thing.
Baby, the police would need
an entire army
to storm that theater.
Ray needs a bullet.
Don't talk that way.
Listen to me.
I know what he's capable of.
This is wrong.
This is all wrong.
We have to believe that.
Otherwise none of this matters.
If we do what they say,
she stays safe.
How do we know that?
Because she doesn't wanna
hurt Clio.
She wants to hurt me.
Look, I don't know
what you're planning,
but this is not the way.
This is not
how we get our daughter back.
There is no other way.
This is it.
I promise you,
I'm gonna get her back.
I promise.
I'm coming with you.
Hey, take a seat.
Oh, can you, uh, shut the door?
Thanks.
[sniffles]
Come on, guys.
Show's about to start.
[Trevor] Where's she?
Where's Clio?
She's fine.
So let's keep it that way.
Sit.
Good boy.
Hey, I think you guys
are really gonna dig this.
It's gonna be great.
[instrumental music]
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
I am your host,
Morris Galinsky.
- That's pronounced Gavinsky.
-[laughing]
[Morris] Is this thing working?
All right.
Morrie and Kaylie go way back.
He's worked, like,
all of her pageants.
I mean, he's a little gone
in the head these days,
but he's a great guy,
he's the best.
[Morris] I've had bigger houses
in my life,
but a gig is a gig
and I will work 'em all.
Okay, everybody!
Now, you all ready
for a great evening?
"Our judge tonight
will be
an accomplished guitarist
and past judge
of Miss Whittier, 2011,
Trevor Gustafson!"
Let's hear it for Trevor!
Come on, everybody.
Stand up there, Trevor.
Dude, don't be a dick. Come on.
[Morris] Where are you?
[Ray] Here he is.
He's right here.
Hey, you with the musket!
- Is that real?
- Sure is, Morrie.
You talk about a tough crowd,
here they come armed already.
So without further ado
and until we next say adieu,
here she is,
our loveliest of lovelies!
-[Ray] Yeah!
- Our one and only...
Well, come on, sweetheart.
-[Renee] Oh, God!
-[Ray applauding]
- Yes! Let's, let's bring her on!
-[Ray howling]
-[Morris] Come on!
-[gasps]
Well, hello to you.
Tell us a little bit
about yourself, Clio.
I'm seven years old,
and I love dancing,
chocolate cake
and wearing pretty dresses.
What have they done to her?
They grow up fast, don't they?
- Uh! Don't do it.
- Trev-Trevor, Trevor, don't.
Come on. Sit down.
But especially, I love my family
and I love my school
and friends.
[Morris] Maybe you have
a message for us all?
God gave us
so many incredible blessings,
but also the responsibility
to look after those
less fortunate than ourselves.
If we could all love one another
and look past our differences,
we could end hate
in our lifetimes.
So true.
[Morris] That was wonderful,
honey!
Seven years old
and she's already
got my vote for president!
-[Ray laughing]
- Well, here it is.
The moment
you've all been waiting for!
I know I have!
[music stops]
Kaylie, I stuck around
like I promised,
but that was worth a hell
of a lot more than a C-note.
I know. I'm sorry, we can't
afford you for longer than that.
You've still got it, baby.
- Okay.
- Thank you so much.
Listen, tell your friends
about me, love.
I will.
What a lovely, little,
unspoiled beauty.
Just like you way back when,
remember?
Kinda like getting a do-over,
isn't it?
Trouble is,
at the end of the day,
she'll be a star
and you'll still be you.
♪ Well I'm tired of the way
you look at me ♪
♪ When I speak my mind
♪ I'm tired of the words
that you put in my mouth ♪
♪ Happens all the time
♪ I ain't lookin'
for someone to save me ♪
♪ I ain't waitin'
on a flash of light ♪
♪ I lived too damn long
to apologize now ♪
♪ I just wanna have fun
tonight ♪
♪ Right
♪ Right...
[instrumental music]
- Please make it stop.
- Ah. Wow!
Look at her go.
- Clio!
- She worked hard on this.
Don't be rude. Sit down!
♪ Look away
♪ I ain't waitin'
for someone to save me ♪
on a flash of light ♪
♪ I lived too damn long
to apologize now ♪
♪ I just wanna have fun
tonight ♪
♪ I ain't lookin'
for someone to save me ♪
♪ I ain't waitin'
on a flash of light ♪
♪ I lived too damn long
to apologize now ♪
♪ I just wanna have fun
tonight ♪
♪ Right
[Kaylie applauding]
Whoo-hoo! How amazing was that?
That was just incredible!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I can't hear you!
Come on, guys,
don't make her feel bad.
[Kaylie] Come on.
Yeah!
And now for the highlight
of our evening,
the crowning
of Little Miss Adorable!
And it all comes down
to our judge.
He picks the winner.
And his decision, as always,
is final.
And what does the winner
receive, you might ask?
Well, our little sweetheart
gets an all-expenses paid
ten-year apprenticeship
with yours truly,
expert pageant coach,
Kaylie Drake,
who usually bills her services
out at up to $90 an hour.
Of course, you can't get
this kind of intensive
one-on-one training at home.
No, not with
all the distractions
of friends and family.
So should Ms. Gustafson win,
her parents won't see her again
until her 18th birthday
when she qualifies
for her first adult pageant.
What happens if she doesn't win?
Great question, Ray.
I would hate to think of
the lives that would be ruined,
starting with this
poor little thing right here.
But I'm afraid,
this time around,
it would be our judge,
Mr. Gustafson,
who has the most to lose.
But I wouldn't worry about that.
That's how confident I am
in our little starlet.
We await the judge's decision.
But not too long.
This dump rents by the hour.
Give her the prize.
- Huh?
- Give her the prize.
- She's the winner.
- Hey! [laughing]
Ladies and gentlemen,
put your hands together
for Clio!
Yay!
[Kaylie] Here you go, sweetie.
And, uh...
Where is it? [gasps]
I present to you
Little Miss Adorable,
Clio Kaylie Gustafson!
Whoo-hoo! [chuckles]
[Kaylie applauding]
Okay, let's go. Come on.
-[Renee] Clio!
- Stop.
Clio! Now's your chance! Run!
[Renee] Clio, run, baby,
as fast as you can!
Come on, sweetie,
everything's gonna be okay.
Daddy's just a tidbit emotional.
- You can fly, kiddo!
- Last chance!
[Renee] Trevor...
Ah...
You got me on a good day.
Sit your asses back down.
Let's get on with this.
Why are you letting her do this?
She's my little sis.
I'd die for that girl.
I probably will one day.
So... here's how
it's gonna go down.
You two are gonna sit there
and we're gonna be on our way.
So see you
in about ten years or so.
So long.
[Ray whistling]
[door opens]
Trevor!
[Trevor] Clio!
Clio, your mom and dad
are gonna be so proud of you.
You'll do all the things
I only dreamed of doing
when I was your age.
You understand what a big
opportunity this is, right?
Millions of kids, millions,
and only one gets to be crowned
Miss America.
- All good.
- Bueno relleno.
[Ray] Why you talking Spanish?
[Kaylie] Don't ask questions.
[grunting]
Come on!
My lady.
Ray promises next time he's
gonna fix us up with a Beemer.
Sure thing. I'm gonna
put a order in tomorrow.
[intense music]
You okay, honey?
You're sweating.
Oh, you must be starving.
I know I am. I'm ravenous.
Ray, let's stop
for a froggy burger
and a cookie butter shake, okay?
Yeah, we can do that
in Bakersfield.
Sounds good!
Baby, what's wrong?
I don't feel well.
I-it's okay, it's just nerves.
We all get 'em on pageant days.
It's completely normal.
Okay, Ray, maybe you should
pull over. She's gonna be sick.
- What?
- Baby, it's okay. Shh!
She's gonna be sick.
Can you pull over?
Yeah.
[Clio groaning]
Come on. No, no, no.
Not on me, sweetie.
Take it
from the queen of bulimia.
You'll feel much better
after you...
Ray!
I got it.
[Renee] Trevor!
[intense music]
Excuse me. Coming through.
Thank you.
Nothing to see here. Thank you.
[grunts]
-[panting]
-[woman] Hey!
What's the rush, Flo-Jo?
Ah, thank God.
Thank you so much, ma'am.
Yeah. She's just, uh...
[panting]
She just gets a bit crazy
sometimes.
Don't you, sweetheart?
- Yeah?
- He your daddy?
-[Clio] No.
- Oh, sure, sunshine. Yeah.
-[footsteps approaching]
- That's her mommy back there.
- It's okay, sweetheart.
-[panting] Hi.
- Hi.
- Uh...
I think we might wait for a cop.
Oh. No. No.
No, that's, that's really
not necessary.
- Oh, no. Yeah...
- Uh, Kaylie, why don't you...
No, that's,
that's our daughter. Clio.
Yeah, the doctors say
she's on the spectrum,
but, personally, I think she's
just headstrong like her mommy.
Yeah.
-[Kaylie] Um...
- It's a happy family.
- Yeah.
- I just wanna be sure is all.
- Thank you so, so much.
- Yeah, we appreciate that.
I just know if it was
my daughter, I just... Ow!
Oh, my God!
[intense music]
Trevor.
[grunting]
I don't know what the law says
about killing a defenseless man,
but truth is, I don't care.
You stole my daughter.
Okay. Okay. That...
Yes, that was bad, but you can
have her back, right?
That was always the plan.
Sooner or later...
Not so fast, Miss Thing.
[groans]
[grunting]
If you're gonna do it,
do it right.
[Ray] Where you going? Come on.
Come on, man.
Hey.
I'm sorry, daddy.
I'm sorry, too, kiddo.
[sobbing]
[siren wailing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[Kaylie] I don't even care
what happens to me.
I just wanted to help
that poor little girl.
If only you saw
what her life was like,
it just... broke my heart.
And to think
what's gonna happen now...
what would become
of her hopes and dreams...
it just hurts so much.
[sobbing]
See what I did there?
I brought you into my world.
I made it real.
That, gentlemen, is acting.
When I get out,
I'm gonna be an actress.
You may not know this,
but I've done the whole
beauty-pageant thing
since I was five.
Do you know
how many former beauty queens
become A-list stars?
A lot. Vanessa, Michelle,
Halle, Oprah, Sharon...
It's like a natural transition.
And the beauty,
the real beauty of it is...
when it comes to acting...
the crazier, the better.
[giggles]
[instrumental music]
[music continues]