JOEY (VOICEOVER): My name is Joey Chambers,
and I'm from the greater Cleveland area.
The only reason I'm writing in this stupid journal
is because I have no choice.
I guess that's not entirely true.
According to this wilderness counselor,
she says you're free to make choices.
You're just not free of the consequences.
I guess the choice I made a few days ago
was the straw that broke the camel's back.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Keep the change.
I'm in a hurry.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
-Hey, wait.
Get back here!
-This is Road Runner.
I need clearance for landing.
MAN (ON PHONE): You're clear.
Come on in.
-You did a nice job, kid.
Sure you come in clean?
-Don't I always?
-Don't you get cocky.
When you get cocky, you get careless.
I think you ought to lay low for a while,
just stay out of this area.
I'll give you a call in a couple weeks, 'cause I
got a special request-- 750 Beamer.
I'll let you out of here when it's safe.
So you be cool.
-Don't know any other way.
-Yeah, nice mustache.
-Come in here, Joseph.
How was school today?
-It's all right.
-You know who this is?
-Hm, your golfing partner?
-This is Mr. Billingsley.
He does detective work.
He's aware of all your extracurricular activities
at school.
Thanks for coming in, Phil.
I'll give you a call tomorrow.
-Sure thing, Mr. Chambers.
Uh-- look, I'm sorry to have to be the one
to break the news about your son.
-What do you think this is going to do to your mother
when she finds out you're a petty car thief?
Just what she needs to keep her in the rehab clinic.
-Does she have to know?
-Do you have any idea how serious this is?
These characters you're mixed up with-- you
think they're some kind of a junior achievement group?
All you have to do is cross them once.
[SIGHS] What have I done to deserve this?
-Nothing.
-Then why are you trying to ruin me?
I've gotten you everything you ever asked for.
-Yeah, Dad.
You've been very generous.
-Are you being cynical?
-All I'm saying is that you never spent any time with me,
so you just bought me things instead.
-What are you talking about?
-Nothing.
Just nothing.
I mean, you never even came to one swim meet.
-Yeah.
You got busted, and got kicked off the team.
-You never came before I got busted.
-I have done everything I could to keep things afloat,
so that I could buy you things and keep your mother sober.
-Well, you seem to have plenty of time
for your old drinking buddies.
-Maybe I should've spent more time with you.
But where do you get off using that as an excuse
to try to act like a criminal?
-I'm not using it as an excuse.
I mean, you barely know I'm alive, much less talk to me.
-We talk all the time.
-Yeah, you talked, and I listened.
-Hey, if you would have listened,
maybe you wouldn't be in the fix you're in.
-Yeah, right, Dad.
-Hey, what are you doing with the extra money, anyway?
You're sniffing drugs again, aren't you?
-No.
-Don't lie to me.
Your grades are in the toilet.
You're running around with a bunch of losers.
You come in all hours of the night.
Got the sniffles all the time.
Why don't you just tell me the truth?
Then you won't have to be a liar as well a thief.
-Did you turn them in?
[CHUCKLES]
-No, I handed my Mercedes over to them.
Of course, I turned them in.
-Do you have any idea what's gonna
happen to me when they find that out?
-As far as the police are concerned,
you're not implicated.
Besides, where you're going, I guarantee
nobody is going to find you.
JOEY (VOICEOVER): It all started when early one morning,
these two guys who look like the bushwhackers came into my room,
pulled me out of my bed, forced me to go with them.
They practically threw me on the plane.
I was pretty bummed at first, but then I
noticed the chick sitting across from me was pretty hot.
I wondered where she was going.
I somehow hoped she would be going to the same place I was.
Yeah, right.
She didn't look like she was in any kind of trouble.
She looked a little stuck-up anyway.
-Get your clothes.
You're coming with us.
-Who are you guys?
-Take it easy.
Everything's gonna be OK.
Come on.
-What's going on here, man?
All right.
All right!
You guys are behind this?
-We're doing this for your own good.
Nothing else has worked.
-What?
You don't want me around, Ma?
I'll leave then.
I'll just leave then.
-No, no.
It's not that we don't want you around.
It's just that we can't trust you anymore.
We know you're dealing in drugs.
It's got to stop.
-Well, I don't know what you plan on doing with me.
Don't waste your money.
-If we're gonna catch that flight,
you better get some stuff ready for him, will you?
Sit down.
-You must be Joseph Chambers.
-Yeah.
-I'm Eli Hathan.
But you can call me Grey Wolf.
That's the name I was given after my vision quest.
And you must be Chelsea Banks.
Have you met Joseph?
I'm sorry your parents were unable to accompany you.
Jim, could you get their bags?
Follow me.
-So uh, what brings you here?
-Haven't you heard?
All the travel agents say this is the place to be this year.
JOEY (VOICEOVER): There we were-- a bunch of misfits.
I was like in this daze, and I had no idea what was up.
Didn't know where I was or where I was going.
I guess the only thing I had going for me was that girl,
Chelsea, was in the same boat I was.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-OK, everybody out of the car.
[CAR DOORS OPENING AND CLOSING]
-Contrary to what you may think, you're
here at this place and time because you are loved.
You all have something in common-- that's your inability
to live in harmony with those who you should love the most.
You're no longer on your own turf.
Lies, drugs, alcohol, cheating, thievery have no place here.
This is a chance for you to be reborn and to start again.
And this is your starting place.
Shortly, you'll be joined by those who will help direct you
on your new path in the future.
-Wait a sec.
You're just gonna bail on us?
-Yeah, you want to tell us what's going on here?
-What's going on here is no one's
gonna be here to tuck you in tonight.
-Lay off.
-There's a place to stay, right?
I mean, we might not stay in no motel or nothing like that
but--
-Don't worry.
You'll all be well taken care of.
You play by the rules, and soon, you'll
be able to see yourselves face to face.
Then, you'll be ready for the next step.
[ENGINE STARTS]
-I never been in the-- I never been in the wilderness before.
-Relax.
It's not like they're gonna leave us out here stranded.
-Yeah.
Right.
-I don't think, anyway.
[IMITATES ANIMAL]
-Come on.
Pick on somebody your own size.
-Relax, bro.
-Yeah, 'cause you know like, we could
use a little comic relief out here.
Don't you think?
-Well, it wasn't funny.
-Somebody mind telling me what's going on?
I'm out here freezing my ass off,
and this Wolf guy's telling us everything's cool.
-Dude, it's about one thing out here.
It's about mind control, all right?
-That's bullshit.
And who made you the expert, anyway?
-Listen.
I've been in and out of these so-called therapy houses
before, OK?
All they want to do is make useful little robots out of us.
-Well, we're not in a therapy house, now, are we?
We're out in the middle of nowhere.
And if you know so much, how come
you have to keep coming back?
-I won't be coming back.
Watch and see.
The counselors here are trained hypnotists, all right?
And the food-- who knows what kind of chemicals and shit
they're gonna be putting in your bodies.
I mean, you know they can't force us to stay.
Civil liberties and all that shit-- all you have to do
is say they laid a hand on you.
-Well, like Joey says, you're still here.
-Well, that's 'cause you're here.
And you and me, we'll blow out of here
as soon as we find out where the hell we are.
-Do you hear that?
-What?
-Look over there.
-Yeah, right.
INDIAN: Hah!
[HORSE WHINNIES]
-I know where you've been.
It's not a good place to be.
Each of you are on a course to self destruction or otherwise,
you wouldn't be here.
I'd like you to meet your guardian
angels for your journey.
This is Running Doe.
-Hello.
-This is Walking Far.
Joey, are you happy with the direction your life is taking?
-What direction is that?
-Exactly.
-And you're here to save us all, right?
-No.
Just some of you.
-Chelsea, do you know why you're here?
-Because my mother had me kidnapped.
You know, they can do that if you're underage.
-I don't think you understood my question.
-You mean, why did she force me to come here?
Because I ran away.
Because I did drugs.
-What kind of drugs?
-I did some-- some coke and-- and some pot, all right?
-OK.
Benji, what about you?
-Uh-- tried some stuff.
JOEY (VOICEOVER): After these counselors with Indian names
told us we were gonna take a vow of honesty
as if we had a choice to say no, we
were each assigned to a counselor.
I started to wonder if this Webber guy wasn't right.
Maybe they were gonna turn us into robots or something.
-How long do we have to be here?
-As long as it takes.
-So how long is that?
-That all depends on you.
You're In the first phase starting now.
-For me, it's only gonna take about five minutes if that's
how long that we putting up with this shit.
-Oh that reminds me.
The kind of language you use around others
impacts profoundly on you graduating to the next phase.
-No shit.
-You can usually figure on about a day's
delay for every expletive used.
-Expletive?
What the hell is he talking about?
-Not to mention large rocks placed in your pocket
as you hike.
Now, for the first while, you're gonna
experience some discomfort as the various drugs
leave your bodies.
-You can't mean us.
-Oh, Mr. Smythe, yes I do.
-Each of you has been assigned a counselor.
Minnie, you, Chelsea, and Rita will go with me.
Webber, Steven, and Benji, you'll be with Walking Far.
Joseph, you, Mitchell, and Jamal will go with Night Eagle.
-[SCOFFS] Loser.
JAMAL: They trying to kill us off, man.
I should be bagging my Z's right now, instead of up and down,
up and down.
Man, this whole thing is a crock of shit.
Man, see? [SIGHS] I'll run down these hills killing myself.
-Spider, save your strength, all right?
You're gonna kill yourself talking.
-What's he doing?
-Why don't we take a breather?
-Somebody better do something.
I think Minnie's trying to leave.
Minnie, you all right?
-I've gotta find a bush.
Do I have to announce it to the whole world?
-You know the rules-- no more than 100 feet away.
MINNIE: Whatever you say, counselor.
-And I want to hear you count.
Minnie, start counting.
-I better take it from here.
Looks like I'm gonna be shadowing Minnie.
-Chick's starting to come unraveled.
-Just shut up, all right?
She's no different than any of us.
-Yeah well, this one's trying to check out a couple of times,
you know what I mean, chica?
-Well, maybe you should try sometime.
And don't be trying to talk like me, pretty boy,
'cause it doesn't go on you, all right?
[PANTING]
-You see?
That's what happens when you act out of desperation.
No plan, no nothing.
There's no way she's gonna get out of here.
When we make the move, we'll be ready.
-What makes you so sure we're going with you?
-Well, what is the worst thing that could really happen?
No, seriously.
So we get caught.
So what?
What are they gonna do, discipline us?
Send us home?
[LAUGHTER]
-Listen to my man.
He knows of what he speaks.
Hey, if you guys can break out after dinner tonight
when everyone's asleep, I got a little something
that might ease your burdens.
What are you staring at, geek?
-Stop it.
He didn't do anything to you.
-Joey, [WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
-Forget it.
She's a loser, all right?
-What are you talking about?
-What?
You think I was born yesterday?
You've been staring at Goldilocks
ever since we got here.
JOEY: I have not.
-And that's too bad, 'cause if you looked right
underneath your nose, she ain't got nothing I don't got.
[JAMAL LAUGHS]
-Yo, go for it, man.
She's got the hots for your wigwam. [LAUGHS]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[MINNIE PANTING]
-Minnie?
All right if we talk?
It's pretty awesome, isn't it?
Kind of makes you wonder how it came to be.
I know you must be in a lot of pain.
[MINNIE SNIFFLES]
And I thought maybe if we could talk about it, that would help.
-I don't know you.
-I know.
I know you don't, but I'd-- I'd like you to.
I think I know what you're feeling.
-Oh, you do, huh?
Are you a mind reader?
You know what it's like to be 17 and feel
like your life is a black hole?
-Yeah, I think so.
-Yeah, right.
If you know so much, then how come you're here and not back
in the real world?
[SOBS AND SNIFFS]
You want to know why I failed at killing myself?
-Yes.
-Because I wanted to find out if anyone
gave a rat's ass whether I lived or whether I died.
-Look.
Minnie, I know you don't-- you don't know me.
But I care.
[MINNIE SOBS]
You know, Minnie, a few years back
I was part of the suicide pact.
These uh-- these friends of mine and I
started experimenting with drugs.
Gradually, we got sucked in to the point
where life didn't seem that big of a deal.
I mean, we never talked seriously about it
until one night, the three of us got high, and we made a vow.
I chickened out.
They didn't though.
You know, it's been 10 years, and I still
have to live with the fact that I
probably could have stopped it.
What/
-Just don't seem like the type.
-Why?
-You seem so normal.
-You say normal like it's some kind of disease.
I think we just gotta take things one day at a time.
You know?
-You mean to tell me this is it?
Rice and lentils?
Isn't this illegal?
Definitely not getting all my food groups met.
-Well, a lentil is a legume.
And when you mix that with rice, it's a complete protein.
So I think you'll be all right.
Listen, there's a small lake on the side of that cliff there.
That's where we'll be setting up camp for tonight.
If we hurry, we can get there by sundown.
-What about Minnie and-- and Night Eagle.
-They'll have to catch up with us.
OK.
This is where we'll be setting up camp for the night.
Don't get too comfortable.
We have a lot of work to do before our bonfire session
tonight.
-Hey, what about Minnie and Night Eagle?
-They'll be here.
We're gonna be here tonight, and we'll be here tomorrow.
Tomorrow afternoon, a doctor's going to come by and check you
out to see if you've been detoxified.
OK, Webber?
-Yeah, sounds great.
RUNNING DOE: All right, now let's get everything set up.
WALKING FAR: So how do you feel about your mother?
CHELSEA: I hate her.
I hate her for trying to live my life for me.
-So is that why you ran away?
-Yeah.
-Well, do you think your mother loves you?
-I don't know.
-Why do you think she sent you here?
-To straighten me up.
To make me learn how to do things her way.
To make me learn that what's important to me doesn't matter.
-What is important to you?
-Ever since I was four years old,
I dreamed of being a dancer.
But that wasn't in her plan.
-Remember the representative from Interlochen
School I told you about?
-Yes.
-Well, I've been invited to attend
the summer camp this year.
Mother, it's a really great opportunity.
I'm the only one from all the classes,
and I think they're willing to give me a partial scholarship.
Ms. Swanson said that if I--
-Chelsea, we talked about this.
We agreed that your school work comes first.
I got your second term report card.
You're an A student doing C and D work.
You could pull yourself out of this tailspin you're in,
and I'm willing to help you if I can.
But it's gonna take some cooperation on your part.
-So what are you saying?
Are you saying I can't go?
-I'm saying until you get your grades back,
you're not going anywhere.
-But Mom, I promised that I would do better this term.
-That's not good enough.
And there's still the issue of your little drug bust.
-That was a one-time thing.
I promised that that would never happen again.
-Chelsea, that was a week ago.
What about all the other times?
-Fine.
I'll ask dad.
He'll let me go.
-It's easy for him to say yes, but you know very well,
he hasn't got the money.
Why do you think I want you to get into a top college?
So you can take care of yourself like I've had to.
-I can be a professional dancer.
-Of course you can.
Just like all those other beautiful ballerinas
that stand in line at the unemployment line.
-That's what I love about you, Mom--
your great confidence in me.
-Confidence?
That's something you earn.
-No wonder dad left you.
No compassion.
No bend.
-Don't you ever talk to me about what happened with your father
like that.
-Better yet, I'm not gonna talk to you at all.
I hate you.
-Get back in here right now!
[CARS HONKING]
Shut up!
-Well, I guess it's your turn to straighten
me out where mom failed.
-(WHISPERING) Hey, let's go.
-They checked everywhere except the pump.
[LAUGHTER]
-If we get caught, we're gonna be here til Christmas.
-Listen.
I know a place in Oregon.
We'll hang real low.
No one will ever find us.
Strut, I gotta talk to Chelsea for a while.
STRUT: Hook me up.
-Sleep good.
STRUT: No problem.
-I didn't think we'd get any privacy.
-I don't know about this.
-Come here.
What is that?
Joey, the little wimp told you, didn't he?
-Leave her alone.
-She's a big girl.
I think she can take care of herself.
-I'm gonna go back.
-Wait a minute.
You breath a word about this to the counselors,
you're a dead man.
-I could care less about you.
Leave Chelsea alone.
-All right, man.
It's cool.
RITA: You all right?
-Yeah, why?
-What time did you get in?
-I don't know.
You guys were all asleep.
-I was worried.
That's all.
JOEY (VOICEOVER): After surviving the first night,
we're now waiting for some uh, medic types
to come to our camp.
I think the counselors have to know whether everyone is dried
out before they can hike us to death.
-You Little snitch.
-What's your problem, dude?
-No problem.
Just that you stole the stuff from my shoe.
That's all.
-I didn't steal--
-Come on, punk.
-He didn't steal your junk.
I confiscated it.
Poor substitutes for getting high.
Doggone things always make you pay.
JOEY (VOICEOVER): The last couple
weeks have been really tough.
Walking Far has been telling us all about survival
in the desert.
Like we're really ever gonna need
to know these things in the real world.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MITCHELL: I kind of-- I kind of destroyed property.
-Would you like to be more specific?
-No.
No, not really.
-So what happened, man?
Did you break mommy's window or did
you spray graffiti on the detention house wall.
-I burned a guy's house down, all right?
-You torched a dude's house?
[SIGHS]
-My dog got poisoned.
-Do you feel like it was worth it?
-No.
-Why not, Mitch?
-(WHISPERING) They know already.
-Because I found out later he didn't do it.
-Are you only sorry because you found out he was innocent?
-No.
I'm also sorry for unjustifiably releasing pent up hostilities
and striking out, all right?
-It would be if you meant it.
Do you feel like you've paid for your mistakes?
-I do.
But apparently someone else doesn't.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be stuck here
in the middle-- in the middle of wherever we are.
-You know Mitch, if you view it as punishment,
that's probably what it will be.
On the other hand, you could like it.
-Well, you know, I, for one, am having a wonderful time.
-Me too, dude.
-Night Eagle?
-Yeah?
-What lake is this again?
-You've heard of Lake Powell?
-Unbelievable.
-It's awesome.
Let's take a break for a half hour.
-Look at this.
-All right.
What do you say?
-I'm so hot.
What I wouldn't give to cool off down there, bro.
-Man, go ahead and cool off then, man.
-Go on, Strut.
-Yeah, right.
No.
[STRUT YELLS]
[LAUGHTER]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-How's it feel?
-Well it looks like I'm gonna save him.
[CHELSEA YELLS]
CHELSEA: Come on, Minnie!
-What are you waiting for?
Come on!
-Hi.
OK, OK.
Ah-- no.
I can't.
-I need some help with the clothes.
-Yeah.
-Come on, Mitchell.
-Yeah, you can do it, Mitch.
-This is still too high!
JOEY (VOICEOVER): The last while has been really strange.
No TV, no music, no hot showers or sleeping in,
no parties or hanging out with friends.
Sometimes, it's the little things
that you never notice that you miss the most.
Sucks.
I also miss my mom a lot.
And I'm still ticked at my dad for forcing me to come here.
And I am hungry most of the time,
but I'm still not willing to supplement my diet with trees
and cactus and crap like that.
Rattlesnake and lizard don't sound too appetizing either.
But I do have to admit, the ground
doesn't seem quite so hard now.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR SLAMS]
[SOBBING]
-We've come a long way.
The journey's really just begun.
-Well, that sucks.
-You reach one plateau to find a larger mountain ahead.
In three days, you will have completed phase two.
But to reach it, you're gonna have to achieve certain goals.
-All right, congratulations.
You survived.
I mean, you survived the first phase of your wilderness quest.
-I'd hardly call doing what we're forced to do a quest.
-Well, you're looking for something
aren't you, Mr. Chambers?
-Not out here, sir.
-Oh.
Well, it's been my experience that the greatest treasures
in life kind of spring up when you least expect it.
So keep looking.
And one of these times when you go to take a drink out
of a clear spring, you may see your own reflection
and actually like what you see.
-What-- what's that smell?
-Yeah, what's going on, man?
-Take out your cups.
Help yourself.
-What is that?
-This is a hand cart.
-What?
-Some of the Mormon pioneers used these in the 1800s
to carry what possession they had out west,
because they're light.
They don't need a horse or oxen to pull them.
They can make pretty good time with them.
Now, we do as well as they did.
We'll be doing 15, 20 miles a day with these.
-Yeah, right.
Here we go again.
-It was difficult for them.
But they found that if they work together and cooperated,
the trip was a lot easier.
-(PANTING) Boy, are we going uphill?
-It does seem a little bit heavy.
JAMAL: They've gone too far with this shit this time.
Dirty mother--
-Ow!
Watch it!
-Yo, I ain't say it.
I ain't say it.
See?
-I'm trying to push, all right?
-Chill out, chica.
I'm the one that's doing all the work.
-Excuse me.
-Are you gonna help?
-Yeah!
-Why don't you just sit down there, and we'll push you?
-If we were gonna escape, we should have done it
before we had to push these stupid things.
-Stay cool.
It won't be too long now, all right?
[SHEEP BLEATING]
-Hey, nice wheels.
-What's up, bitch?
-Don't pay them any attention.
-In two minutes, they're gonna be out of your life for good.
-Hey, uh-- looks like your right tire's a little low there.
-Pretty tough in that getaway car, aren't you?
-Oh, listen to this guy.
-Come on.
Let's go, man.
-Yeah, let's go.
-You want to extend your vacation here?
You're looking for a sure way.
-Bring it on.
Hey, we're gonna be late for this party.
We better get going.
[SHEEP BLEATS]
-What's going on?
-Fat kid dropped a sheep in the back of your car.
They're gonna pay for this.
MINNIE: She always takes his word over mine.
RUNNING DOE: Have you given her reason not to believe you?
-Yeah.
About the drugs and the shoplifting and stuff,
but not about-- you know, about my step father molesting me.
She thinks I lie about it.
Well, I'm not lying.
-Why don't you just tell the police?
-'Cause I was afraid of what Jack may do to me.
-What's gonna happen when you go home?
-No way am I going back there if he's still there.
-What are you gonna do?
-I don't know.
-You could come to my house, and uh--
live with my grandparents and me if you wanted to.
-Yeah, right.
Just what they need-- another basket case.
-Want to know why I'm pissed-- PO'd?
I'll tell you why.
I just got a scholarship for Fresno State to play football
this fall.
My bit opportunity, right?
Wrong.
Instead of doing workouts with the other members of the team,
I'm out here in the wilderness trying
to-- trying to find myself.
Only by the time I get back, I won't
get jack sh-- I won't get diddly squat.
RUNNING DOE: Why didn't you think about that
before you robbed the liquor store?
-Yeah well, I did my time for that.
-That's true.
But then you turned right around and stole your mother's car.
-Borrowed my mother's car. [SCOFFS]
-Right.
You borrowed your mother's car and then lead the police
on a high-speed chase before you totaled it.
-It wasn't totaled.
RUNNING DOE: What?
-It wasn't totaled!
-$500 for a brand new Camaro with lapsed insurance?
That's not totalled?
-What are you?
With the CIA?
-Come on, Spider.
It's high time you stop lying to yourself.
-OK, you can put the hand carts down now for good.
NIGHT EAGLE: After we cross the Snake River, each of you
will have an opportunity for self discovery.
This will be your vision quest.
You'll be accompanied to a place where you can think
about your lives-- where you're been, where you are now,
and where you're going.
You'll be alone for four days and four nights.
The only provisions you'll be given
will be what's necessary for your survival.
Each of you will be placed on your honor
to remain in the area that you've been assigned.
And someone will be checking on you from time to time
to make sure you're OK.
-You know, you can't force us to do this.
-You're right.
-If you feel you're not ready, you can stay behind with us.
-Then it takes us that much longer to graduate, right?
-Like I said before, it's all up to you.
-Show us the way.
-Yeah.
What's the big deal?
Let's do it.
-Hey, listen, listen.
I'm not sure I can go, sir.
-Why's that?
-I can't even start my own fire.
How can I go?
-Yeah, you can.
-Hey.
Hey, if you want, we'll help you.
I mean, you don't have to worry about it, all right?
-You got a couple hours before we take you out.
-Just focus on it.
Just don't think about nothing else.
-Give it all you got for like 10 seconds.
-Doing good, man.
-Burn!
Yes!
You did it!
-I did it.
I did it.
-See that boat?
That's our ticket out of here.
-What are you talking about?
-That's it.
RUNNING DOE: This is it.
-That part about not having any food,
I mean, that was a joke, right?
-Look around you.
You have a whole garden of epicurean delights.
You just have to get up off your butt.
-Mm-hmm.
-Of course, if you decide not to,
fasting is really great for your system.
-What if it rains?
-If it rains, it rains.
-OK, I have to go.
Don't worry.
Guardian angels will be by every once in a while
to check you out.
-What?
Don't you trust me?
-I'm starting to.
Bye.
-I got it.
OK.
Sleeping bag's under the tree.
Got my water.
And I gotta check the berries in the morning,
make sure they're not poisonous.
And I got it.
I got it.
I'm cool.
I'm Rambo.
-(SOBBING) I hate this.
I hate it.
-Made it this far.
I'm sure to make it three and a half more days.
OK, let's see, sun comes up in 7 hours.
Gives me 6 hours to sleep, hour to uh, get ready.
[HOWLS]
[HOWL ECHOES]
[HOWLING CONTINUES]
-Come in, Running Doe.
OK
RUNNING DOE (ON RADIO): I hear you.
-Better check the camp sites.
Make sure Walking Far checks his.
RUNNING DOE (ON RADIO): Will do.
Over.
-Looks like Strut's missing.
What about Webber?
RUNNING DOE (ON RADIO): He's gone too.
I'll go find out about Chelsea.
-All right. [SIGHS] I'm gonna look
for Joey then head down to the river.
You check on the road, and tell Walking
Far to call the ranger station.
You seen Webber or Strut?
-No, but I heard some screaming.
-Running Doe, do you read me?
RUNNING DOE (ON RADIO): Looks like Chelsea's missing too.
[SIGHS]
-I'll head down to the landing now.
Over.
-I'm going with you.
-I don't think so.
-What's up?
All right.
Where's Chelsea?
-I don't think she's gonna make it, bro.
Sorry.
Her, we better get going, man.
We can't wait around all day. -All right, let's go.
Make the move.
-Hey, it's me!
It's me!
-Come on.
Come on!
-This is gonna be fun.
-Hey, where's the boat?
-We have no idea in the world where this is gonna take us.
-Down river.
-Well, what are we gonna do once we get there?
-Relax, all right?
We're fine.
-Maybe we should have just lasted it out.
We only had another month.
-No.
No way.
No.
-Well, what do you mean no way?
-Strut, tell her.
-I overheard Night Eagle and Running Doe,
and our stay has definitely been extended.
Definitely.
-We think we may have had a couple runaways down here.
-They must be the ones who stole the boat.
They're headed around the bend right there.
-I gotta get to them before they hit white water.
I need to borrow your boat.
They don't know a thing about white water.
-Night Eagle, come on!
-Hey, what about my boat?
-Uh, uh-- thanks a lot.
-You must like it here.
It's like you're begging to stay on.
-Sorry, sir.
I'm just-- just worried about my fellow students.
-All three of them?
-Yeah.
-Put on that life jacket.
Hand me one.
-Got something here.
-Got it.
Hang on.
See them yet?
-I don't see them, no.
-Need to-- need to put on a life vest.
-There they are!
-Joey, when we catch up to Webber,
you might have to take charge of the boat.
-All right.
-Well, if we can hang in there just a little longer, just
after this next bend, there's only one more set of rapids.
-Hold on.
-Hang on.
Hold it!
-Take this, and call Running Doe.
Get to shore when you catch up with the boat.
-All right.
-Take it.
I think we got it made.
-We got it made?
What about Strut?
-He's got to take care of himself, OK?
That's just the way it goes.
Chelsea, what are you doing?
-You may not care about Strut, but I do.
-All right, then go.
You go, all right?
I don't need you in this boat.
You're doing me a big favor here.
CHELSEA: Thank you.
-You belong with those losers anyway.
JOEY: Chelsea, hang on!
JOEY (VOICEOVER): Everyone finished their vision quest
except for Chelsea, Webber, Strut, and me.
Night Eagle has given Chelsea and me extra assignments
to make up for our little river adventure.
Webber is still missing, but they
found the boat on the shore.
So he must be OK.
As for Strut, he was gonna be sent home.
And I don't believe it, but apparently he begged to stay on
and even agreed to do an extra month.
-After the storm comes the rainbow.
It brings with it fresh new life.
Many flowers and blossoms spring forth from the hard rocky soil.
And though the landscape seems barren and hopeless,
the most beautiful flowers make their appearance.
Minnie, you are one of those flowers.
I give you the name Rainbow Blossom.
-Until we are strong enough to survive on our own,
we are dependent upon those who care for us.
So it is with the hawk.
You are agile.
You are swift.
I give you the name of Swift Hawk.
-From a glowing ember we make a fire--
a fire that gives us warmth and gives
light to a world of darkness.
From something small many things are possible.
I give you the name Fire Fox.
-You have come to realize many God-given talents,
and you have determined to develop them.
In planning for your future, you not only hunger
for good, nourishing food, you also
hunger for knowledge and truth.
Therefore, I give you the name of Hungry Bear.
The raven is known for its cunning, wisdom, and magic.
She's special, and she's powerful.
She's not as swift as the hawk or as strong as the bear,
but in what others may perceive as her weakness lies
her strength.
I give you the name of Night Raven.
-A young swan is awkward and gangly.
But as it grows, it becomes graceful and beautiful.
Its spirit dances on the water.
When it takes to its wings, it rises above the earth.
I'll call you Rising Swan.
-Being willing to risk your life for someone else
is the noblest of gestures.
And having the determination and skill
is fortunate for Rising Swan.
I give you the name Brave Otter.
Grey Wolf is here to prepare you to return to your families.
-Well, congratulations again.
You have realized your vision quest.
You've become self sufficient.
And you've seen yourself face to face.
I only hope that you like what you see.
JOEY (VOICEOVER): Night Eagle told us
about some ancient prophet guy who said that the race doesn't
go to the fast ones but to those who endure to the end.
We awakened at sunrise and were told
that we were to run eight miles through the mountains
and that if we made it, we were ready to start our new lives.
-Why did you put me in here though?
Why did you put me in here?
-I'm sorry.
I kicked him out.
I'm sorry.
-Look at you.
Just look at you!
[SOBBING]
-I didn't think you were gonna show.
-Are you kidding me?
We wouldn't miss this for the world.
-I think I'm ready to come home now.