NAME'S JORDY--
JORDY REMBRANDT.
I GREW UP ON THE
SOUTH SIDE OF THE CITY.
THIS IS MY HIGH SCHOOL.
OR SHOULD I SAY "WAS"...
LIKE MOST PUBLIC SCHOOLS
IN ANY CITY
THE CLASSES WERE TOUGH...
[slam... thump]
MORNIN'!
ADMISSION WAS
HIGHLY COMPETITIVE.
AND THERE SEEMED TO BE AN
OVER-EMPHASIS PLACED ON
ATHLETICS.
SO WHEN MY COUNSELOR SUGGESTED
A CHANGE OF VENUE MIGHT IMPROVE
MY CHANCES OF GRADUATING...
YOUR HONOR, WE DO THROW
OURSELVES
AT THE MERCY OF THIS
COURT.
BEARS SEASON TICKETS
YOUR HONOR...
YOU AND THE MISSUS.
IT SOUNDED LIKE
WITH GOOD BEHAVIOR
I COULD STILL GRADUATE
IN JUNE.
TOUGH BREAK
KID.
AH!... OOF!
THIS IS MY NEW SCHOOL.
OINK, OINK... MOO
LIKE MOST PUBLIC SCHOOLS
IN THE COUNTRY,
IT TOO, HAS PROBLEMS...
TODAY IT JUST GOT ONE MORE.
ME.
♪ [bright orchestral] ♪
THEY'RE GONNA PAY.
EASY, ICE.
LAST YEAR
IT WAS A GIANT PINK
JOCK STRAP!
AND THEY SHAVED
THE FRESHMEN CLASS.
WHAT HAPPENED TO SECURITY
THIS YEAR FRESHMEN?
THEY CAN'T DO THAT
TO OUR FRESHMEN.
ONLY WE CAN DO THAT
EVERYBODY HERE
AGREE WITH ICE?  YEAH!
EVERYBODY HERE THINK WE SHOULD
JUST MARCH OVER THERE
AND BASH IN THE WINDSHIELDS
OF THEIR BMWs?
YEAH, YEAH, GREAT!
A MASCOT WITH
GENDER PROBLEMS.
WHAT DID
YOU SAY?
I WAS TALKING
ABOUT YOGI.
HE SEEMS TO BE HAVING
A BAD FUR DAY.
DUDE, DON'T
'DISS THE GRIZZ'.
THAT'S A BIG DEAL
AROUND HERE.
BUT YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY
NOT FROM AROUND HERE.
CAREFUL THERE, COWBOY.
HEY! KNOCK IT OFF YOU
GUYS!
THERE ARE BETTER WAYS
TO GET REVENGE.
LIKE WHAT,
MR. PRESIDENT?
MAKE PEACE.
OUR FIGHT IS NOT
WITH EACH OTHER,
THIS IS A FIGHT
TO DO WHAT'S RIGHT.
I AGREE WITH CROWDER!.
AND THE RIGHT
THING TO DO
IS TO STOMP THEIR
BRAINS OUT.
(yelling)
YEAH...YEAH!
HEY! YOU THINK THIS
IS A BIG JOKE?
YOU'RE THE ONE
DEFENDING THE CARE BEAR.
THAT KINDA MAKES YOU
THE BIG JOKE.
YOU'RE A REAL FUNNY GUY.
I'D KINDA LIKE TO SPREAD
SOME OF THAT HUMOR AROUND--
THE SIDEWALK!
THIS DUDE NEEDS
TO LEARN SOME RESPECT.
HE SURE DOES!
ALL RIGHT COME ON--
APOLOGIZE TO THE BEAR!
[boys yelling]
PROBLEM BOYS?
LAST DAY FOR SENIOR CLASS FLOAT
ENTRIES IS THIS FRIDAY.
STUDENT COUNCIL WOULD ALSO LIKE
TO REMIND ALL STUDENTS
THAT A RESPONSE TO THE VANDALISM
DONE TO OUR SCHOOL
WILL BE HANDLED
THROUGH THE COUNCIL.
VANDALISM IS A CRIMINAL OFFENSE.
LET'S NOT SINK TO THEIR LEVEL
FOLKS. THANK YOU.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU SHOULD SEE THE OTHER GUY.
I'LL BE LOOKING FOR YOU
AFTER SCHOOL.
HE LOOKS
FINE TO ME.
MASSIVE INTERNAL INJURIES.
IT'S UGLY.
WELL... HOPE
YOU FEEL BETTER.
YOU.
JORDAN REMBRANDT.
I'VE GOT YOUR FILE HERE -
MOST OF IT ANYWAY -
THE FAX MACHINE
IS STILL WORKING.
YOU WERE SUSPENDED
FOR FIGHTING.
HE HIT ME FIRST.
YOU WERE SUSPENDED 8
TIMES.
THEY ALL HIT ME FIRST.
2-TIME ALL-STATE
WIDE RECEIVER.
THAT WAS UNTIL LAST MONTH
WHEN YOU PUNCHED YOUR COACH.
YOU PUNCHED YOUR COACH?
HE WAS GONNA HIT ME FIRST.
THE COURT SAYS WE'RE YOUR
LAST CHANCE
YOU MESS UP AGAIN,
AND IT'S BACK TO SUNNY RIDGE
BOYS HOME.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO LEARN
HOW TO GET ALONG WITH OTHERS.
I CAN DO THAT.
I DON'T TOLERATE FIGHTING.
ONE WEEK DETENTION STARTING
TODAY.
AND I WANT YOU SIGNED UP FOR
2 AFTER SCHOOL ACTIVITIES
STARTING MONDAY.
BRING ME
WRITTEN PROOF.
WOULD DETENTION BE CONSIDERED
AN AFTER SCHOOL ACTIVITY?
PHILANTHROPIC CLUBS,
SPORTS ACTIVITIES
I WANT WRITTEN PROOF.
GO-- SEE THE NURSE.
OH--
WELCOME TO MORRIS.
GO GRIZZLIES.
THE AFRICAN TREE FROG
IS ABLE TO ADAPT
TO ITS SURROUNDINGS.
IT DOES THIS AS A NATURAL
DEFENSE AGAINST PREDATORS.
BY BLENDING WITH PLANT LIFE
IN THE BIOSPHERE -
A TECHNIQUE KNOWN AS
"CAMOUFLAGING" -
NATURE PROTECTS
THIS HARMLESS AMPHIBIAN
FROM ITS HOSTILE ENVIRONMENT.
LIGHTS PLEASE.
(Wally)
ANYONE-- LIGHTS!
AHHHHHHHH...!
(screaming)
GET 'EM OFF ME.
THEY'RE SUCKING
OUT MY EYEBALLS!
GET 'EM OFF ME!
AAAHHHHH!
[students chattering]
QUITE HARMLESS, ACTUALLY.
RIBIT!
[students laughing]
♪ [medium-paced
flute & strings] ♪
♪   ♪
(The Dean)
SIGN THE ROLL, TAKE A SEAT.
THANKS--
BROUGHT MY OWN.
NO TALKING.
♪    ♪
[bell rings]
NEED A RIDE HOME?
UH, I CAN WALK.
I MEAN AH...
SURE... WHATEVER.
I DON'T LIKE
SPECIAL TREATMENT.
THAT'S WHY I PARK
OUT HERE IN THE LOT.
BY THE WAY, I'M WALLY.
(Jordy) WHO'S THAT GIRL?
(Wally) THAT'S PAM...
WE'RE SORT OF AN ITEM.
BUT DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
IT'S A SURPRISE.
TO WHO?
PAM.
HEY PAM.
HEY!
THIS IS JORDY.
YUP, I KNOW--
JORDY REMBRANDT.
I CHANGED THE PAPER IN THE FAX
MACHINE THIS MORNING SO...
SO YOU'VE SEEN ALL MY
MERIT SCHOLARSHIP AWARDS.
HEY PAM, COMIN' TO CLC
FRIDAY NIGHT?
WHAT'S THE MOVIE?
OH, IT'S A CLASSIC!
SURE
HEY CHICAGO!
[thump]
ANYTIME YOU WANT TO BUTT HEADS,
SUIT UP.
WE CAN ALWAYS USE A COUPLE EXTRA
TACKLING DUMMIES.
[all laugh]
BRING THEM BOOTS.
LOOKS LIKE YOU HAVE ALL THE
DUMMIES YOU NEED.
ICE!-- IF BRAINS
WERE DYNAMITE
HE WOULDN'T HAVE ENOUGH
TO BLOW HIS NOSE.
WELL, MAYBE I'LL SEE YOU FRIDAY?
YAH. I'LL BRING THE JELLO MOLD.
I'LL DRIVE.
RIGHT.
[grunting]
IF YOU THINK I'M CLOSIN' YOUR
DOOR FOR YOU, YOU CAN FORGET IT.
(Jordy)
I HATE GRAIN.
WHEN I WAS A LITTLE KID I SAW
THIS MOVIE WHERE THE ARMY
WAS PUTTIN' NUCLEAR MISSILES
INSIDE THESE GRAIN SILOS.
EVER SINCE THEN, THE HEARTLAND
HAS SEEMED SORT OF APOCALYPTIC.
DEATH AND DESTRUCTION
COULD BE LURKING
INSIDE ANY ONE
OF THOSE BABIES.
IT'S FOR ROADSIDE
EMERGENCIES...
IT'S A BIBLE.
PEACE WITH GOD?
(chuckles)
WHO CAN BE
AT PEACE WITH GOD?
YOU CAN.
AND I SUPPOSE YOU'RE
AT PEACE WITH GOD?
YEAH. YEAH I AM.
I'LL STICK WITH DEATH
AND DESTRUCTION.
[engine roars]
[engine rumbles]
HOME SWEET HOME?
'TILL MY BROTHER
CHANGES HIS MIND.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR
PARENTS?
THEY'RE ON VACATION...
FROM ME.
HEY, A BUNCH OF US ARE
GETTIN' TOGETHER FRIDAY
NIGHT
TO WATCH A MOVIE.
WHAT'S THE FLICK?
LAWRENCE OF ARABIA.
CAN'T YOU GUYS WATCH ANYTHING
FROM THIS CENTURY?
HEY MIGHT BE A GREAT WAY TO
MEET PEOPLE FROM SCHOOL.
YOU EVER HEARD OF CLC?
ISN'T THAT
A GRUNGE BAND?
NO - CLC -
A CAMPUS LIFE CLUB.
THAT BE CONSIDERED
A PHILANTHROPIC CLUB?
(male narrator on film)
HE WENT TO ETHIOPIA
AND SET UP A SMALL MISSION
FOR CHILDREN
WHERE HE BECAME
LAWRENCE OF ETHIOPIA.
HEY-- YOU MADE IT!
YOU WANT TO START THIS OVER?
IT'S GREAT,
RIGHT UH-HUH.
(Jordy)
WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
(Wally)
LOOKS LIKE EVERYBODY'S HERE NOW.
THIS IS ABOUT IT.
THIS IS
A BIBLE CLUB?
2 GUYS?
AND A BIBLE.
THINGS ARE GOING TO BE
DIFFERENT THIS YEAR.
YA, WE GOT FLYERS.
I'VE GOT ACTIVITIES PLANNED--
A COUPLE
OF CONCERTS,
A BILLY GRAHAM CRUSADE,
MOVIE NIGHT.
GREAT WALLY. LISTEN,
I'VE GOT TO LEAVE,
DO ME A FAVOR...
DON'T WANT TO WATCH...
WE CAN
JUST HANG OUT--
I'LL INTRODUCE YOU
TO EVERYBODY.
THIS IS JIMMY.
THIS IS ZIPPY.
HERE COMES SOMEBODY ELSE.
(Jordy)
HOPE YOU GOT ENOUGH CHAIRS.
SORRY I'M LATE-- HAD TO WALK MY
BIKE HERE,
I GOT A FLAT.
HI.
HEY!
I FEEL LIKE A BURGER.
WANNA COME? YA!
WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS MEETING'S NOT OVER YET!
YOU'RE BUYING, RIGHT?
SURE. OK, SOUNDS COOL.
ALRIGHT, I GUESS WE
COULD END EARLY.
WE'LL TAKE MY CAR.
(Zippy)
WELL, I HAVE TO CALL MY MOTHER.
OK, ZIPPY.
(Wally)
WELCOME TO WESTBURY PARK--
BADGER COUNTRY.
PLEASE KEEP YOUR ARMS
AND LEGS INSIDE
HEY, MAN, WHAT YOU DOIN'
(Wally)
SORRY!
HEY BE CAREFUL WILL YA?
SO THIS IS BADGERLAND?
EXCUSE MOI, I MUST USE THE
BATHROOM!
THE BADGER IS A VERY
VICIOUS ANIMAL
I BETTER GO WITH HER.
HEY MADGE!
HEY WALLY. HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU
GUYS GONNA HAVE?
GIVE US A COUPLE CHILI
FRIES,
4 DOUBLE CHEESEBURGERS,
3 COKES AND A RONDO.
COULD YOU MAKE MINE A
CHOCOLATE SHAKE?
CHOCOLATE SHAKE
HUH? ALRIGHT.
SURE.
THANKS.
SHE TALKED
TO ME.
JIMMIE, SHE'S OUR WAITRESS.
HEY, HOP IN THE FRONT WILL YA?
HEY FRESHMAN...
NICE CAR!
THANKS. YOU TOO.
YOUR CAR I MEAN.
ALLOW ME.
OOH! WHAT A GENTLEMAN.
HOW CUTE.
HE BLUSHED.
HEY! COMIN' THROUGH!
AAAAAHH!!
[splat]
OH MY GOSH, YOU OK?
NICE MOVE MORON!
THAT WAS OUR
DINNER.
IT'S NO
PROBLEM REALLY.
HELP HER UP,
PUNK!
IT'S OK, I'LL GET SOMEBODY
TO CLEAN THIS UP.
THE PUNK WILL CLEAN
IT UP,
WON'T YOU PUNK?
(Wally)
LOOK IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
WE'LL PAY FOR IT.
OH, YOU WILL.
RIGHT AFTER YOU AND YOUR
FRIEND LICK THIS UP.
(Wally)
I SAID WE'D PAY FOR IT.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH
YOU FISH,
YOU GOT A PROBLEM
WITH THAT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
CAN'T YOU TALK
I CAN'T WALK.
WHAT?
I CAN'T WALK!
BIF, MAN-- THE GUY'S
A GIMP. (laughing)
(Jordy)
PUT HIM DOWN!
OOF!
HOW'S WAS I S'POSE TO
KNOW HE WAS A CRIPPLE.
I DIDN'T SEE A SIGN OR NOTHIN'.
C'MON MAN.
LET'S SPLIT.
HEY WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING AT?
YEAH. THAT'S WHAT I
THOUGHT.
HEY BUZZ, CHECK
IT OUT.
A GIMP... A
SHRIMP... AND A
WIMP. (laughing)
[thud... bloof]
[everyone yelling]
AAAAAHHHH!!... [THUD!]
YAAAAAHHHHH!!!!... OOF!
[splat!]
(Pam) YOU OK?
[whoosh]
[whack]
AAAAAH!!... OH!
[everyone yelling]
KNOCK IT OFF!!
GET IN THE
CAR NOW!!
(Pam)
C'MON!
SORRY JORDY.
YOU OKAY?
WHEN DO WE PLAY THOSE
GUYS?
[screech!!]
[smash!!]
(Ice)
WHAT CHANGED YOUR MIND, CHICAGO?
(Jordy)
BIBLE STUDY.
COACH?
REMBRANDT...
START ON DEFENSE.
I'M A WIDE RECEIVER.
OH... PLEASE DON'T
PUNCH ME, REMBRANDT.
LET'S RUN
THE OFFENSE...
YOU TOO!
ALRIGHT, GENTLEMEN!
TODAY WE HAVE TO
MAKE A DECISION.
WHO ARE YOU
GOING TO FOLLOW?
GOING TO PLAY FOR?
NOW, TO PLAY FOR ME, YOU HAVE TO
FOLLOW MY RULES.
REMBRANDT!!
THIS IS A TEAM--
YOU START DOING YOUR OWN THING,
AND YOU'LL FIND YOURSELF HURT,
BENCHED OR BOTH!
YOU GOT IT?
ALL RIGHT TEAM,
EVERYBODY FOLLOW REMBRANDT--
5 LAPS AROUND THE FIELD!
(many voices)
ALRIGHT! C'MON, LET'S GO!
[bird chirps]
HEY, YOU!
HEY!
FOOTBALL, HUH?
YEAH.
WHERE ARE
YOU HEADED?
HOMECOMING COMMITTEE.
I THOUGHT MAYBE WE COULD DO
SOMETHIN'...
HEY YOU GUYS COMING
TO THE MEETING?
AH... THINKING
ABOUT IT.
I THOUGHT WE'D
ALL GRAB SOMETHIN'
AT TOLI'S AFTERWARDS...
CELEBRATE.
YEAH. LET'S GO
BACK TO
BADGERLAND.
WHAT ARE WE
CELEBRATING?
OH, AH, HA, HA, HA!
(Pam)
OK, C'MON STUDENT COUNCIL
COME TO ORDER PLEASE!
WE HAVE 4 ENTRIES
FOR THIS YEAR'S SENIOR
HOMECOMING FLOAT, SO UM...
BARRY, WHY DON'T
WE START WITH YOU.
WELL, WE STILL HAVE THE FLOAT
FROM LAST YEAR.
SHEERAH?
I ENVISION A
30-FOOT AMAZONIAN GODDESS
A HARBINGER ARCHETYPE OF THE
SHE-WOMAN EARTH MOTHER.
RIGHT ON!
OK... I GET MY DAD'S
'58 CONVERTIBLE.
WE PLASTER CHEERLEADERS
ALL OVER IT...
I DRIVE.
YEAH!!
OW, OW, OOOOH!
♪ [suspenseful strings] ♪
[small electric motor whirs]
[whoosh!]
GRRRR!
[cheering & clapping]
(girls)
WALLY, THAT WAS AWESOME!
HOW DID YOU DO IT?
NOW THIS COULD REALLY
BOOST SCHOOL SPIRIT.
I THOUGHT WE WERE
GOING TO TOLI'S.
JUST WANTED YOU A MINUTE
TO MYSELF.
YOU WANT TO
WALK THEN?
I THOUGHT WE COULD
JUST SIT.
TALK.
OKAY.
UM...
WE BETTER GO--
I MEAN, WALLY'S...
WALLY'S A BIG BOY.
LET'S FINISH OUR
CONVERSATION.
♪ [melancholy flute] ♪
[flute & strings]
WHAT'S THE
MATTER?
JORDY, I REALLY
LIKE YOU.
BUT, MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST
TAKE ME HOME.
(sighs)
WAIT!
CHANGE YOUR MIND?
I'VE SET CERTAIN
BOUNDARIES, JORDY.
SO, THIS IS ABOUT
YOUR RELIGION.
NO, I JUST DON'T WANT
TO GET HURT.
IT'S NOT--
IT'S ABOUT THIS
RELATIONSHIP I HAVE...
WITH WALLY?
WITH GOD.
GOD DOESN'T WANT US
TO HAVE ANY FUN?
NO, HE DOES, BUT
HE JUST CARES ABOUT US
SO MUCH THAT
HE DOESN'T WANT TO SEE US
BE HURT
OR, YOU KNOW,
MESS THINGS UP,
AND EITHER DO I.
YOU REALLY BELIEVE
ALL THAT STUFF?
YES. AND, YOU KNOW,
BELIEVING ISN'T SOMETHING
THAT YOU JUST DO
IN YOUR MIND -
IN YOUR HEAD -
I MEAN, HE'S IN MY HEART.
AND IT'S SOMETHING YOU DO
WITH YOUR WHOLE BODY,
AND YOUR HEART, AND YOUR MIND,
AND YOUR EVERYTHING.
AND SOMETIMES THAT'S
REALLY HARD,
BUT, I MEAN, IT'S
A DECISION I'VE MADE,
AND IT'S SOMETHING THAT
I WANT TO LIVE BY.
THAT'S WHY I WON'T
SWIM OUT THAT FAR...
I WANT US TO STAY
CLOSE TO SHORE.
WELL MAYBE YOU BETTER
JUST STAY ON THE
BEACH.
ALL RIGHT DEFENSE,
GET IN THERE.
[tense music,
crowd cheering]
WELL, I HOPE THEY
PULL SOMETHING OUT.
READY... SET...
(male announcer)
FIRST DOWN, BALL IS ON THE...
HUT ONE!
OOF... [grunting]
(announcer)
INTERCEPTED!
BY NUMBER 20, JORDY REMBRANDT.
HE'S AT THE 50,
HE'S AT THE 40,
HE COULD GO ALL THE WAY.
[loud screaming & cheering]
TOUCHDOWN!
♪ [triumphant orchestral
brass & cymbals] ♪
♪    ♪
♪ [fuzz rock guitar] ♪
(Wally)
IS THAT A BEER?
(Pam)
I'M JUST HOLDING IT.
(Wally)
YOU'RE NOT SETTING A VERY GOOD
EXAMPLE HERE.
EXAMPLE, WALLY?
NOBODY EVEN KNOWS WE EXIST.
HEY, CROWDER,
HOW 'BOUT A BREW?
NO THANKS BRO'...
ONE BREW AND
I MIGHT LOSE CONTROL--
START DANCING
ON THE TABLE.
(Ice)
I WANTED YOU
TO GET ME ONE.
OH. HOW ABOUT
A PEPSI?
WOULDN'T WANT YOU TO
VIOLATE YOUR TRAINING RULES.
WHERE'S JORDY?
DISAPPEARED.
♪    ♪
CAN I GET
YOU ANYTHING?
[fuzz rock guitar
& people chattering]
(Wally)
GUESS NOT.
♪    ♪
[zip... zip]
[cheering]
FIRE IN THE HOLE!
[whoosh!]
[cheering]
GREAT JOB, JORDY!
THANKS.
PIZZA TIME!
ARE YOU GOING?
YEAH. LET'S ALL GO.
(Pam) UH, GUYS... WHAT ABOUT US?
WALLY'S STILL WORKING ON
THE THING.
WELL YOU GUYS CAN FOLLOW US
LATER IN WALLY'S CAR.
YEAH, BUT SEE, WE CAME
WITH JORDY.
MICHELLE--
RIDE WITH ME?
JORDY SAID HE'D TAKE ME.
MICHELLE CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A SECOND?
(other students)
WHO'S GOT THE KEYS TO MY TRUCK?
MIKE HAS THEM.
WHAT?
WHAT IS IT?
I WAS JUST WONDERING.
IF YOU WEREN'T ALREADY
GOING TO HOMECOMING,
I WAS THINKING MAYBE WE
COULD...
THAT'S REALLY SWEET ICE
BUT I'VE ALREADY
BEEN ASKED.
SORRY.
JORDY?
RIGHT.
I CAN COME BACK
FOR YOU GUYS.
(sighs) BOYS...
WHY ARE THEY
SO STUPID?
HEY WATCH IT,
THAT'S MY GENDER
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
NOT YOU, WALLY, I DON'T
CONSIDER YOU ONE OF THEM.
OH, THANKS.
SHUT UP. YOU KNOW WHAT I
MEAN.
IT'S JUST NOT FAIR.
WHAT?
THIS WHOLE
CHRISTIAN THING,
YOU KNOW, ALWAYS HAVING
TO BE THIS GOOD LITTLE
GIRL ALL THE TIME.
AND THINGS WOULD BE DIFFERENT
IF YOU WEREN'T?
WHY DO I HAVE TO LIKE HIM?
WHY CAN'T I LIKE SOMEBODY
LIKE YOU?
(Wally)
IT'S EASY DOING WHAT EVERYBODY
ELSE IS DOING.
EVERYONE'S GOTTA SET BOUNDARIES.
BOUNDARIES AREN'T
NECESSARILY BAD.
REMEMBER COLORING BOOKS,
AS A KID?
(Pam)
YEAH. WHAT ABOUT EM?
(Wally)
IN MY FAMILY
WE USED TO HAVE RACES
TO SEE WHO COULD FINISH A
COLORING BOOK FIRST.
I ALWAYS WON.
BUT THERE WAS THIS LITTLE GIRL
WHO LIVED ACROSS THE STREET,
SHE WOULDN'T RACE...
REFUSED! (Pam chuckles)
SHE'D SPEND A WHOLE WEEK
ON ONE PAGE!
(Pam)
SO... MAYBE HER PARENTS WOULDN'T
BUY HER NEW BOOKS?
NO. THAT
WASN'T IT.
SHE WAS TAKING HER TIME
TO MAKE THEM SPECIAL.
AND THEY WERE, BECAUSE
SHE TOOK HER TIME.
I WAS ALL OVER THE PLACE--
WASTIN' TREES
WHILE SHE WAS MAKING ART.
PICTURES THAT WOULD LAST--
KEEPERS.
YOU KNOW WHERE
THAT GIRL IS TODAY?
UH, THERAPY?
NO, SHE'S BUILDING FLOATS
AT MORRIS HIGH.
SHE'S STAYING INSIDE THE LINES,
TAKING HER TIME.
SHE'S MAKING SOMETHING BEAUTIFUL
OUT OF HER LIFE.
SOMETIMES, IT'S REAL
HARD,YOU KNOW.
YEAH... IT'S A FIGHT
TO DO WHAT'S RIGHT.
BUT GOD NEVER TESTS US BEYOND
WHAT WE'RE ABLE TO ENDURE.
WELL. HERE WE ARE...
HERE WE ARE.
WELL... GOODNIGHT.
WAIT, WALLY?
WHAT DID YOU DO WITH
THOSE PICTURES
WHERE YOU WENT OUTSIDE
OF THE LINES?
GOD HAS A WAY OF TAKING
EVEN MY WORST MISTAKES
AND MAKING SOMETHING GOOD
OUT OF THEM.
HIS GRACE IS...
IT'S A NEW COLORING BOOK,
Y'KNOW?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW GREAT YOU ARE?
[splashing of rain,
orchestral music]
I'VE NEVER KISSED
ANYONE BEFORE--
'CEPT MAYBE
THOSE TREE FROGS.
OH...
WELL... GOODNIGHT.
YOU'RE A KEEPER,
WALLY CROWDER...
YOU'RE A KEEPER!
[dog barks]
[barking louder]
[suspenseful music]
[rushing sounds]
[crackling]
IT'S TOAST, MAN!!
(Wags)
THEY JUST BURNED OUR FLOAT.
(Moto)
IT'S TOAST MAN.
IT'S TOAST.
(Wags)
I SAY WE KILL 'EM.
DEATH TO BADGERS!
(all chanting)
KILL, KILL, KILL, KILL!
(Moto)
IT'S TOAST, IT'S TOAST, MAN!!
(all chanting)
KILL, KILL, KILL, KILL!
♪ (heavy strings) ♪
♪    ♪
HEY, NICE GAME.
I STEPPED OUT OF BOUNDS.
HEY WE STILL WON.
LISTEN. SOME OF THE GUYS
ARE GETTING TOGETHER
TONIGHT,
I THOUGHT MAYBE WE
COULD...
UH, I CAN'T.
IT'S CROWDER'S BIRTHDAY.
I GOTTA BE THERE.
WHADDYA STILL HANGING AROUND
THAT LOSER FOR?
WALLY'S A FRIEND.
WELL, WE'RE YOUR TEAMMATES.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE
DEPENDING ON CROWDER
TO BE PUSHING 200 POUNDS OF
BADGER AROUND THE FIELD
SO YOU CAN MAKE A TOUCHDOWN.
WE'RE LAYING A BLOCK
TONIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
[Wally blowing loudly]
I DON'T KNOW WHAT COULD HAVE
HAPPENED TO HIM.
(Jimmy)
HE COULD'VE FORGOT.
SORRY, WALLY.
OR MAYBE HE'S WITH MICHELLE.
I'D FORGET MY OWN BIRTHDAY--
JIMMY...
WE GET THE POINT, ALRIGHT?
HEY. IT'S ONLY A BIRTHDAY.
(Jordy)
WESTBURY PARK?
(Ice)
WE THOUGHT WE'D STOP AND PICK UP
SOMETHING TO EAT.
(Wags)
YEAH, WHAT DOES BADGER TASTE
LIKE ANYWAY?
(Jordy)
OH NO. WAIT, YOU GUYS.
(Ice)
C'MON, IT'S NEVER BEEN DONE.
WON'T OUR FLOAT LOOK GOOD
BEING PULLED BY A LIVE BADGER.
(chuckles)
♪ [drums & heavy strings] ♪
(Jordy)
GOT IT. LET'S GO!
♪    ♪
(Moto)
WE'RE IN!
♪    ♪
[deep breathing]
GOT IT!
LET'S GO.
GRRRRR!
[all screaming,
growls]
IT'S OUT!!
AHH!! IT'S GOT MY FLASHLIGHT.
[screaming]
AAHHH!! IT'S GOT MY SHOE!
(Floater)
DUDES! RUN FOR YOUR LIVES!!
[screaming]
(Moto)
THAT THING'S CRAZY!
(Wags)
WE GOT NOTHIN'!
(Floater)
DUDE, IT SHREDDED YOUR PANTS!
(Wags)
MY PANTS? LOOK AT MY SHOE!
[guys chattering]
GRRRRRR!!
♪    ♪
[music becomes tenser]
(Jordy)
ONE, 2, 3.
[all grunting]
♪     ♪
♪ [intensity builds] ♪
[all yelling]
♪   ♪
[boom... BLAM!!]
[all yelling]
IT'S TOAST GUYS!
[yelling]
YES! YES! AW THAT
WAS BEAUTIFUL MAN!
YES! YEAH!...
YES!!
[crackling]
AWESOME DUDE,
TOTALLY AWESOME!
♪ [jazz clarinet & strings] ♪
♪  ♪
REMBRANDT!
SEE YOU
IN MY OFFICE.
JORDY, THIS
IS OFFICER STAVERMAN
OF THE MORRIS
POLICE FORCE.
I ASKED WALLY
TO BE HERE BECAUSE
HE'S PRESIDENT
OF THE STUDENT GOVERNMENT,
AND THIS DOES INVOLVE
THE ENTIRE STUDENT BODY.
BUT OFFICER STAVERMAN WOULD LIKE
TO ASK YOU A FEW QUESTIONS.
OKAY.
SO, JORDY, CAN YOU TELL US WHERE
YOU WERE LAST NIGHT?
WELL, THERE WAS A PARTY LAST
NIGHT...
BUT I STAYED HOME. STUDYING.
STUDYING.
YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THAT
WESTBURY PARK BOOSTER BUS
THAT BLEW ITSELF UP?
NO, WAS ANYBODY HURT?
SO FAR, SO GOOD.
LOOKS LIKE IT WAS JUST A PRANK
THAT WENT A LITTLE AWRY.
ALTHOUGH I DO UNDERSTAND THAT
THERE IS A BOUNTY OUT.
AM I BEING CHARGED WITH
SOMETHING?
'CAUSE I KNOW MY RIGHTS.
OH, I'M SURE YOU DO.
THE POLICE ARE LOOKING
FOR ANY INFORMATION
THAT MIGHT HELP THEM FIND THE
KID OR KIDS WHO DID THIS.
WHAT MAKES YOU
THINK IT WAS US?
WE DON'T KNOW WHO DID IT JORDY.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY, THERE'S A
WHOLE SCHOOL
FULL OF KIDS OVER AT WESTBURY
PARK WHO THINK THEY DO.
NOW WE'RE JUST TRYING TO END
THIS WHOLE THING
RIGHT HERE AND NOW
BEFORE SOMEBODY DOES GET HURT.
I WISH I
COULD HELP YOU.
BUT I CAN'T.
CAN I GO BACK
TO CLASS NOW?
PICK YOU UP AFTER
PRACTICE JORDY.
[click]
[door creaks]
WE'RE DEPENDING
ON YOU REMBRANDT.
I GOT A SCHOLARSHIP
ON THE LINE.
THEY'RE JUST TRYING
TO SCARE SOMEBODY
INTO POINTING
A FINGER.
MAYBE THEY
SCARED YOU?
NO.
WHAT DOES
CROWDER KNOW?
HE KNOWS I MISSED
HIS PARTY LAST NIGHT.
HE'S GIVING ME A
RIDE HOME AFTER PRACTICE...
NOT A GOOD IDEA.
WALLY'S A FRIEND.
HE'S MY RIDE.
THAT FOOTBALL SCHOLARSHIP
IS MY RIDE.
I'M NOT GOING
TO LET SOME
RELIGIOUS FANATIC
MESS THAT UP.
LIGHT?
THANKS.
HEY, YEAH...
NO OFFENSE JORDY -
BUT WE'RE
ALL CHRISTIANS -
BUT WE'RE COOL.
WE DON'T LET IT
GET IN THE WAY.
(sighs)
ALRIGHT, HERE'S
WHAT WE DO.
WE ORGANIZE
A JOINT TRIP,
ADVERTISE IN
BOTH SCHOOLS.
IT'S CLOSE,
IT'S A NEUTRAL ARENA,
AND IT'S WITHIN
OUR BUDGET.
WALLY, IT'S FREE!
EXACTLY.
A COUPLE OF GUYS
FROM WESTBURY PARK
GO TO MY CHURCH.
I CAN GET
THEIR NAMES.
WE'VE GOT FLYERS.
THIS IS A
PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
TO BE PEACEMAKERS.
WELL THEN, LET'S
GET STARTED.
ALRIGHT,
LET'S PRAY.
DEAR LORD, WE ASK
FOR YOUR STRENGTH
AND YOUR GUIDANCE
IN THE COMING DAYS
AS WE SEEK PEACE
IN THIS CONFLICT...
[bell chimes]
THIS IS A GREAT CAUSE.
IF I COULD JUST LEAVE A
FEW...
IT'S AGAINST SCHOOL POLICY.
WHO'S YOUR BOSS?
FRITZ GOLDMAN.
IS HE AVAILABLE?
HE'S IN A MEETING.
AVAILABLE AT LUNCH?
NO, HE'S BUSY.
I'LL BE BACK AFTER SCHOOL.
DEAN GOLDMAN
IS NOT AVAILABLE.
PLEASE, IT'S A REALLY GOOD
CAUSE.
DO WHAT YOU
HAVE TO DO.
[bell rings]
[engine roars]
[bell ringing]
[engines roaring]
[ominous vocal chorus]
PASS ME.
PASS ME ALREADY!
[screech... clunk]
OWN THE ROAD BUDDY! GO FOR IT!
[roar... screech]
♪ [ominous] ♪
[starter motor whirs]
[smash... crash!]
[motor roars]
[screeching]
♪ [ominous] ♪
[blam, screech, smash]
♪    ♪♪
THIS IS DEAN STAVERMAN.
I HAVE AN IMPORTANT
ANNOUNCEMENT TO MAKE.
GOOD MORNING,
THIS IS DEAN GOLDMAN.
(Dean Staverman)
YESTERDAY AT APPROXIMATELY 6:00
PM,
MORRIS STUDENT BODY PRESIDENT,
WALLY CROWDER,
WAS INVOLVED IN A TERRIBLE CAR
ACCIDENT ON SEAVEY ROAD.
(Dean Goldman)
WE DON'T HAVE ANY INFORMATION AT
THIS TIME,
HOWEVER, THE POLICE HAVE
CONFIRMED...
(Staverman)
...THAT HE WAS TAKEN BY
AMBULANCE
TO ST. FRANCIS HOSPITAL.
HE WAS TRAVELING ALONE
AT THE TIME...
(Goldman)
IT APPEARS THAT NO OTHER
VEHICLES WERE INVOLVED,
AND NO ONE ELSE WAS INJURED.
(Staverman)
OUR THOUGHTS AND PRAYERS
GO OUT TO HIM AND HIS FAMILY.
(Goldman)
A TRAGEDY LIKE THIS
AFFECTS THE ENTIRE SCHOOL.
(Staverman)
THIS IS A VERY SAD DAY FOR ALL
OF US.
THE BEST THING WE CAN DO IS TO
HOLD OUT GOOD THOUGHTS
FOR OUR FRIEND, WALLY CROWDER.
WE HOPE TO GET WORD FROM THE
HOSPITAL SHORTLY
ON HOW HE'S DOING.
THAT'S ALL FOR NOW.
♪ [melodic orchestral] ♪
MRS. CROWDER, YOU CAN
COME IN NOW.
(Pam)
HE'S GOING TO BE OKAY THEN?
(Dr. Allen)
WE'RE JUST KEEPING A CLOSE EYE
ON HIM RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HE'S A GOOD PERSON MY
BOY,
WHY WOULD ANYBODY
WANT TO HURT MY BABY.
(Jake)
WE CAME BY TO EXTEND OUR
APOLOGIES.
WHO'S RESPONSIBLE?
WE DON'T KNOW.
NONE OF US.
ALL OF US.
WE WANT TO PUT AN END
TO THIS THING LIKE HE
DID.
IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND
GIVING HIM THE MESSAGE.
WE PLAN ON BEING THERE.
(Pam)
WALLY TRIED TO DROP OFF SOME
FLYERS...
(Jake)
WE'LL BE THERE AND WE'LL BE
PRAYING.
THAT'S GREAT!
HE'LL REALLY
APPRECIATE THAT!
NOW I'VE GOT A MESSAGE FOR THE
GUYS THAT DID THIS.
WE'D LIKE TO SETTLE THIS ONCE
AND FOR ALL.
ANYBODY THAT'S GOT THE GUTS.
JORDY! THIS HAS
GONE TOO FAR.
3:00. MONDAY.
SAME FIELD
WHERE IT HAPPENED.
ANYBODY THAT'S
GOT THE GUTS.
YOU TELL THEM
I'LL BE THERE.
[BANG!]
(reading)
"DEAR JORDY,
DON'T BECOME SO WELL ADJUSTED
TO YOUR CULTURE
THAT YOU FIT INTO IT
WITHOUT EVEN THINKING.
FIX YOUR ATTENTION ON GOD.
YOU'LL BE CHANGED
FROM THE INSIDE OUT.
WE GOT TO FIGHT TO DO
WHAT'S RIGHT BROTHER,
WALLY."
(Dr. Billy Graham)
THERE'S SO MUCH
DISEASE AND POVERTY
AND WAR AND HATE
AND LONELINESS,
UNEMPLOYMENT, BOREDOM,
SOCIAL INJUSTICE,
RACIAL PROBLEMS,
PSYCHOLOGICAL PROBLEMS, AIDS.
ALL OF THESE THINGS
ARE PUSHING IN ON US.
AT A TIME, IT SEEMS TO ME,
WHEN WE OUGHT TO HAVE
A MARVELOUS WORLD
OF PEACE AND LOVE.
WHAT'S WRONG?
AND YOUNG PEOPLE ARE ASKING
THAT QUESTION:  WHY?
WHAT'S GOING TO BECOME OF US?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THE WORLD?
IS THERE AN ANSWER TO IT ALL?
DOES ANYBODY CARE?
DOES ANYBODY REALLY LOVE YOU?
YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY
IMPORTANT TO GOD.
JUST AS THOUGH YOU WERE THE ONLY
PERSON THAT EVER LIVED.
AND GOD LOVES YOU.
AND HE WANTS TO FORGIVE YOU OF
YOUR FAILURES AND YOUR SINS,
ALL THE WAY BACK TO THE TIME
THAT YOU CAN REMEMBER.
HE'S WILLING TO
FORGIVE YOU TONIGHT.
AND COVER IT UP AS THOUGH
IT HAD NEVER HAPPENED.
GOD DOESN'T JUST SAY, "I LOVE
YA, I FORGIVE YA."
HE DOES SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
HE SENT HIS SON, CHRIST,
TO DIE ON THE CROSS.
AND WHEN CHRIST DIED
ON THAT CROSS,
HE TOOK YOUR SINS AND MY SINS
ON HIMSELF.
AND HE TOOK MY SINS
AND YOUR SINS
AND BURIED THEM
IN THE DEPTHS OF THE SEA.
AND HE FORGETS THEM.
WELL, YOU SAY, "BILLY, I KNOW
THAT JESUS DID ALL THAT FOR US
BECAUSE HE LOVED US.
I KNOW THAT.
BUT WHAT DO WE HAVE TO DO?"
FIRST - YOU HAVE TO
REPENT OF YOUR SINS.
JESUS SAID, "I CAME NOT
TO CALL THE RIGHTEOUS,
BUT SINNERS, TO REPENTANCE."
SOME LITTLE BOY SAID,
"REPENTANCE MEANS BEING
SORRY ENOUGH TO QUIT."
THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD DEFINITION.
AND THEN THE SECOND THING
IS FAITH.
WITHOUT FAITH, IT IS IMPOSSIBLE
TO PLEASE GOD.
YOU SAY, "WELL, WHAT DOES
THAT MEAN?"
IT'S NOT SOMETHING YOU WORK UP.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING YOU DO WITH
YOUR HEAD.
IT'S SOMETHING THAT YOU DO WITH
YOUR BODY.
WITH YOUR HEART.
WITH YOUR EMOTIONS.
WITH EVERYTHING YOU HAVE, YOU
SAY,
"I GIVE MYSELF TO CHRIST."
THE THIRD THING--
YOU MUST OBEY HIM.
YOU MUST LIVE FOR HIM.
AND I'M GOING TO ASK YOU TONIGHT
TO RECEIVE CHRIST
INTO YOUR HEART.
AND LIVE FOR HIM THE BEST YOU
CAN WITH HIS HELP.
I'M GOING TO ASK YOU
TO STAND TO YOUR FEET.
I'M NOT ASKING YOU TO
JOIN ANY ORGANIZATION
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT,
I'M JUST ASKING YOU TO RECEIVE
CHRIST INTO YOUR HEART.
TONIGHT IS A GOOD STARTING PLACE
WITH ALL THESE PEOPLE HERE
AND MANY THOUSANDS
OF PEOPLE PRAYING.
YOU CAN GET STARTED AND SAY,
"LORD, I WANT TO START,
MAYBE AFRESH OR ANEW WITH YOU.
I'VE BEEN SORT OF A FAILURE
UP 'TIL NOW.
I BELIEVE,
BUT I HAVEN'T BELIEVED.
THAT'S WHAT YOU NEED TO DO
TONIGHT, IS TO GET STARTED."
YOU SAY, "BUT I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO PRAY."
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
PRAY LIKE A PREACHER.
YOU JUST TALK TO GOD
AS THOUGH HE WERE YOUR BEST
FRIEND WHICH HE IS.
TELL HIM EVERYTHING.
SAY, "LORD I LOVE YOU.
I... I PRAISE YOU.
I THANK YOU."
AND THEN SAY, "LORD,
I NEED SOME HELP.
PLEASE HELP ME."
PRAY IT IN THE NAME OF JESUS.
AND HE'LL HELP YOU.
HE ANSWERS EVERY PRAYER.
YOU GET THE GAS,
THROW IT UP ON THERE...
VAROOM!!
MAY I HAVE
YOUR ATTENTION PLEASE?
WE'RE GOING TO
KEEP THIS REAL SHORT.
AFTER DISCUSSIONS
WITH THE ADMINISTRATION
AT WESTBURY PARK HIGH SCHOOL,
WE HAVE DECIDED TO CANCEL
THIS YEAR'S HOMECOMING.
[many students]
WHY? WHAT FOR?
QUIET! QUIET!
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH!
SIT DOWN!
I'VE ASKED PAM FOSTER
TO SPEAK TO YOU
ON BEHALF OF
THE STUDENT GOVERNMENT-- PAM.
WALLY CROWDER ASKED ME
TO READ THE FOLLOWING LETTER:
"MY FELLOW GRIZZLIES.
I KNOW THINGS ARE STILL TENSE.
EVERYBODY'S GOTTA
FOLLOW SOMEBODY.
I REALIZE IT ISN'T
GOING TO BE ME.
THEREFORE, I OFFER MY
RESIGNATION AS YOUR PRESIDENT.
[clears her throat]
SECONDLY, I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I FORGIVE THE GUYS
THAT DID THIS.
AND I HOPE YOU WILL TOO.
THE CHOICE IS REALLY YOURS.
CONTINUE THIS CHILDISH FEUD
OR RESOLVE OUR DIFFERENCES
LIKE RESPONSIBLE CITIZENS
AND CHRISTIANS.
THE FUTURE IS IN OUR HANDS.
PEACE, WALLY."
SO WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO, GUYS?
CONTINUE THIS CHILDISH FEUD
OR RESOLVE OUR DIFFERENCES?
CHILDISH FEUD!
(other students)
CHILDISH FEUD! CHILDISH FEUD!
CHILDISH FEUD!
(more join in)
FEUD! FEUD! FEUD! FEUD!
JORDY! JORDY!
JORDY! JORDY!!
JOR-DY! JOR-DY!
JOR-DY! JOR-DY!!
JOR-DY!
JOR-DY! JOR-DY! JOR-DY!!
CAN I SAY SOMETHING, PLEASE?
MOST OF YOU ALREADY KNOW THIS.
I WAS INVOLVED IN
THE INCIDENT AT WESTBURY PARK.
I'M, AH...
I'M RESPONSIBLE
FOR WHAT HAPPENED.
ALRIGHT... YEAH
[much cheering]
(speaking forcefully)
AND WHAT I DID WAS...
WHAT I DID WAS WRONG.
A FRIEND OF MINE WAS ALMOST
KILLED BECAUSE OF ME.
I HAVE SOME UNFINISHED BUSINESS
WITH OUR CROSS-TOWN RIVALS.
ANYBODY THAT'S GOT THE GUTS...
FOLLOW ME.
REMBRANDT!!
♪ [strings-- suspenseful] ♪
HE'S GONNA GET
KILLED.
YEAH... LET'S GO WATCH.
♪    ♪
[angry yelling]
AGAIN, I'M SORRY.
HOMECOMING'S BEEN CANCELED.
THIS MATTER'S GOTTEN
WAY OUT OF CONTROL.
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE...
QUIET, PLEASE!
QUIET, PLEASE!!
GRIZZLIES ON THE MOVE!
THE WHOLE SCHOOL
IS MARCHING ON US.
THEY'RE IN
FISHER'S FIELD!
LET'S GO,
COME ON!
YOU ARE NOT DISMISSED!
[much yelling]
STAY IN YOUR SEATS
UNTIL YOU'RE DISMISSED!
[bell rings]
OKAY. YOU CAN GO.
♪ [throbbing bass, strings] ♪
♪ [throbbing bass, strings &
powerful vocal chorus] ♪
♪    ♪
♪ [trumpet fanfare] ♪
♪ [throbbing bass, strings &
powerful vocal chorus] ♪
♪    ♪
LORD, WE CLAIM
THIS FIELD FOR YOU TODAY.
THIS IS YOUR BATTLE NOT OURS.
WE PRAY FOR A PEACEFUL
RESOLUTION TO THIS CONFLICT.
WE PRAY FOR COMPLETE
RECONCILIATION AND FORGIVENESS.
LORD, WE BELIEVE THAT
YOU ARE IN TOTAL CONTROL.
AND LORD, PLEASE MAKE ME
TOTALLY INVISIBLE.
WE'RE GOING TO
DESTROY YOU GUYS!
(Jordy)
YOU'RE GOING TO DESTROY US?
YOU'RE A DEAD MAN,
REMBRANDT!
YEAH, I AM.
AS OF THIS WEEKEND ACTUALLY.
IT'S PAY BACK TIME.
AND I INTEND TO. EVERY CENT.
YOU TORCHED
OUR BUS!
YEAH, I DID.
YOU'RE ADMITTING IT?
YEAH. AND I APOLOGIZE.
I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO MAKE IT RIGHT.
WE DIDN'T TOAST
YOUR FLOAT MAN.
YEAH, I GOT AN IDEA
ON THAT TOO.
THE KID IN THE CAR
ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. HE'S GOING
TO BE ALL RIGHT.
♪  ♪
SEE YOU ON
ANOTHER FIELD SOMETIME?
DEAL.
♪ [piano & strings] ♪
♪  ♪
[car door slams]
[knocking on door]
HEY.
[gasps]...
I HAD NO IDEA.
I JUST THOUGHT...
(Wally)
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY DIFFERENCE.
HOW'D IT HAPPEN?
MESSING AROUND.
IN A POOL.
I WAS A SWIMMER.
WHEN?
4 YEARS AGO.
YOU NEVER THINK IT CAN
HAPPEN TO YOU.
ANYWAY. WHAT'S UP?
SO... THE GAME'S ON TOMORROW.
I HEARD THAT.
THAT'S GREAT.
I JUST THOUGHT IF YOU FELT UP TO
IT YOU COULD COME BY...
I DON'T. BUT THANKS.
WELL THEN, I JUST CAME BY
TO SAY THANKS.
YOU CAME BY BECAUSE YOU
FELT SORRY FOR ME--
DON'T.
I CAME BY TO TELL YOU
YOU WERE RIGHT.
IT'S BEEN A REAL FIGHT BUT AH...
I THINK I'M DOING
THE RIGHT THING.
FOR ONCE IN MY LIFE.
I WENT AND HEARD
BILLY GRAHAM.
HE SAID IT TOO.
"EVERYBODY'S GOT TO FOLLOW
SOMEBODY," RIGHT?
I CAME BY TO SAY THANKS
FOR BEING AN EXAMPLE
OF WHAT IT IS TO FOLLOW JESUS.
I HOPE THAT SOMEDAY YOU CAN
ACCEPT MY APOLOGY...
FOR EVERYTHING.
I'M DEDICATING THE GAME
TOMORROW, TO YOU.
DID YOU REALLY JORDY?
DID YOU INVITE CHRIST
INTO YOUR HEART?
YEAH. I DID.
THEN DEDICATE
IT TO HIM.
AND YOU RUN
THOSE BADGERS BACK
INTO THE DARK HOLE WHERE
THEY BELONG.
(chuckles)
[grunting]
[cheering]
(announcer)
PASS TO #20-- JORDY REMBRANDT!
NICE CATCH!
NICE HIT!
(announcer)
THAT'S THE BALLGAME!
THANK YOU
GOOD GAME!
PICK UP YOUR TICKETS FOR
HOMECOMING
AND HAVE A GREAT WEEK.
LET'S GIVE A NICE ROUND OF
APPLAUSE FOR THE KIWANIS CLUB
FOR SUPPLYING ALL THE GREAT
UNSALTED PEANUTS.
SEE YA NEXT WEEK!
(Jordy)
ANY SIGN OF HIM?
(Pam)
NO... WE TRIED BUT...
HE'S STILL
PRETTY BANGED UP...
INSIDE.
(Jordy)
I GUESS I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY
TOO.
IT'S NOT ENTIRELY
YOUR FAULT.
YOU'RE A GUY.
Y'KNOW GUYS ARE DUMB.
THANKS PAM.
FOR WHAT?
KEEPING ME
CLOSE TO SHORE.
(Dean Staverman)
AND THE KING AND QUEEN
OF MORRIS HIGH SCHOOL'S
HOMECOMING IS...
I AM PROUD TO PRESENT...
JORDY REMBRANDT
AND MICHELLE STARK!
[applause]
I... I GUESS YOU BETTER GO.
YEAH.
SMILE, DUDE, THIS
ISN'T A FUNERAL.
(Wags)
HEY MAN, LOOK WHO YOU'RE
STANDING NEXT TO.
[applause]
♪ [strings, oboe] ♪
[click]
♪    ♪
NICE SUIT!
THANKS. STRAIGHT
OFF THE RACK.
YA! SHOULD'VE
STAYED THERE.
WELL, HERE'S SOMETHING
I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D BE ABLE TO RETURN--
YOUR FRIENDSHIP.
YOU'VE TAUGHT ME A LOT
WALLY.
NOBODY DESERVES THIS MORE
THAN YOU.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU SAY, WALLY?
THANKS, JORDY.
I'M GENUINELY TOUCHED.
HEY-- I WONDER HOW MUCH THIS
THING IS WORTH MELTED DOWN?
SO, MAY I HAVE THE HONOR?
BY ALL MEANS.
♪ [violins
rising in intensity] ♪
(Jordy)
Y'KNOW, GOD MADE EACH OF US
UNIQUE...
AND WE SPEND OUR WHOLE LIVES
TRYING TO BE LIKE EVERYONE ELSE.
THIS WAS MY HOMECOMING.
FINDING THE LOVE OF GOD AND THE
LOVE OF HIS FOLLOWERS.
TO BE ACCEPTED...
JUST AS I AM.
EVERYBODY'S GOT TO FOLLOW
SOMEBODY.
THE WAY HOME IS SIMPLE.
JESUS SAID IT BEST...
"FOLLOW ME."