Man: THANK YOU FOR THAT
TRAFFIC UPDATE NANCY DENOBE,
FOR MY MONEY, THE SEXIEST
REPORTER IN CENTRAL ARIZONA.
IT'S 6 P.M.,
AND YOU'RE LISTENING TO...
♪ PHOENIX
IN THE AFTERNOON ♪
WE'RE STILL TALKING ABOUT IT,
SO CALL US.
TELL US THE WACKIEST PLACE
YOU'VE EVER MADE LOVE.
CALLER, YOU'RE ON THE AIR.
WomaKarlin, I once made love
on a beach in Mexico.
It was sunrise.
There was no one else around.
SO YOU WERE BY YOURSELF?
No. No.
I was with my boyfriend.
Man: On my surfboard
off The Big Island of Hawaii.
WomaIn a rowboat
on Lake Erie.
Man: The Empire State Building
Gift Shop.
WomaIn the library.
Woman: On my desk at work.
Man: The restroom
of a 747.
Woman: The elevator
of my apartment building.
I LIKE THIS ONE.
For a full 10 minutes,
we kept expecting
the elevator doors to open
and for someone to catch us.
YOU JUST LOVE THOSE
EXOTIC PLACES, DON'T YOU?
YOU ENJOY THE IDEA
OF GETTING CAUGHT, I BET,
OF SUDDENLY BEING EXPOSED.
Oh, it was wicked.
OOH, YOU'RE A NAUGHTY GIRL.
ALL RIGHT. THAT'S IT.
I'M OUTLAWING BEDS.
FROM NOW, PHOENIX, EVERYBODY
MAKES LOVE IN PUBLIC PLACES --
ELEVATORS, POST OFFICES,
LAUNDROMATS, AIRPLANES --
NO MORE INHIBITIONS.
I WANT TO CATCH YOU
MAKING LOVE IN PHONE BOOTHS.
I'M CALLING FOR
A REVOLUTION OF NAUGHTINESS.
TAKE IT ALL TO THE EDGE.
DO YOU HEAR ME, PHOENIX?
TAKE IT TO THE EDGE.
[ WOMAN MOANING ]
YOU'RE INCREDIBLE.
SOMETIMES.
WILL I SEE YOU AGAIN?
VIVIAN...
MAKING LOVE I'M GOOD AT.
RELATIONSHIPS I'M NOT.
WE GOT TO GO.
HA HA.
SCREW YOU.
YOU JUST DID.
ARE YOU FINISHED?
AAH!
OH, MY GOD!
HOLD ON!
PLEASE, GOD!
OKAY! HOLD ON!
I CAN'T!
AAH!
NO! NO! NO!
NO! NO! NO! GOD!
GOD! GOD! GOD!
OH. OH.
OH, WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT HAPPENED?
[ CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING ]
AUDITION TAPE THREE,
TAKE FIVE.
AHEM.
MUSIC YOU CAN LISTEN TO
ALL DAY LONG.
MUSIC FOR THE OFFICE.
MUSIC FOR THE HOME.
AND WE NEVER OFFEND ANYONE.
WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS.
WE'RE CLASSICAL 98.1,
KOZY, LOS ANGELES,
AND I'M JON PRICE
FOR THE ONLY STATION --
[ BEEPING ]
DAMN.
WALDO.
[ SNORING ]
WALDO!
IT'S TIME.
SOOTHING MUSIC.
MIND-NUMBINGLY DULL MUSIC.
MUSIC YOU DON'T NEED
A HEARTBEAT TO ENJOY.
SO WHETHER YOU'RE
IN AN ELEVATOR
OR ATTENDING A FUNERAL
OR JUST STARTING YOUR
NEW PRESCRIPTION OF PROZAC,
LISTEN TO CLASSICAL 98.1.
OKAY. END OF TAKE FIVE.
MOZART'S "REQUIEM."
WHAT A WONDERFUL PIECE OF MUSIC.
COMING UP ON KOZY
CLASSICAL 98.1, LOS ANGELES,
MAHLER'S "KINDERTOTENLIEDER,"
OTHERWISE KNOWN AS
"THE DEAD CHILD'S SYMPHONY."
Man's Voice: Get ready
for an exciting evening
of Gregorian chants
this Monday night...
".7, .7, .5 -- "
OH, FOR CHRIST'S SAKES --
".4 -- 10:00 TO 2:00 A.M."
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
ANY GOD DAMN ARBITRONS.
WE HAVE A QUALITY AUDIENCE,
ONE THAT EXPECTS A CERTAIN
STANDARD OF EXCELLENCE
TO BE MAINTAINED.
COME OFF IT, WALDO.
WE'RE IN DEEP SHIT HERE.
I CAN'T GET A 50-BUCK BILLABLE
FOR A 60-SECOND WITH A .4.
MR. CORREL,
YOU HAVE A MINUTE?
MY AUDITION TAPE --
I WAS WONDERING IF
YOU HAD A CHANCE
TO LISTEN TO IT.
WHERE IS IT?
WHEN DID YOU LEAVE IT?
I GAVE IT TO YOU
LAST WEEK, MR. CORREL.
I THINK YOU SHOULD GIVE HIM
A CHANCE TO BE ON THE AIR.
I HEARD HIS TAPE, AND I THINK
THE BOY IS VERY TALENTED.
WE HAVE A WEEKEND
SUBSTITUTE SLOT OPENING UP.
I WAS HEAD DJ
AT BOSTON UNIVERSITY,
AND I'VE DONE A LOT
OF RADIO AD WORK.
OKAY.
I'LL LOOK FOR YOUR TAPE.
I'LL TRY AND LISTEN TO IT
THIS WEEK,
BUT NO PROMISES, OKAY?
THANK YOU.
HOW DID IT GO?
WALDO MADE
ANOTHER PITCH FOR ME.
THAT'S GREAT.
YEAH.
WHAT'S WRONG?
NOTHING.
LOOK, I KNOW
IT'S FRUSTRATING,
BUT IF YOU JUST
HANG IN THERE,
THINGS WILL START
TO HAPPEN FOR YOU.
WHEN I'M TOO OLD
TO APPRECIATE IT?
ALL I NEED IS A BREAK.
YOU KNOW I'M READY FOR IT.
I DON'T KNOW WHY IT'S
SO HARD TO GET A SHOT.
TELL YOU WHAT,
I KNOW IT'S MY FIRST YEAR
OUT OF LAW SCHOOL,
BUT AS SOON I BECOME
A PARTNER IN A LAW FIRM,
I WILL BUY YOU
YOUR OWN RADIO STATION.
BUY ME MY OWN STATION, HUH?
I HAVE A LITTLE SURPRISE
FOR YOU.
MMM.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT,
AT THE CAR WASH?
OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW IT.
IT'S LOVELY.
ACTUALLY...
THIS IS
FOR BEING THERE FOR ME.
THANK YOU.
THANKS.
[ CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, SOMETHING WENT DOWN
THIS MORNING.
YOU KNOW, THE OWNER'S JAG
WAS HERE YESTERDAY.
THE XJS.
RIGHT.
A REAL BEAUTY.
HEY, HOW'S SHARON DOING?
FINE. UM...
SHE WANTS TO BUY ME
MY OWN RADIO STATION.
YOU ARE LUCKY
TO HAVE A WOMAN LIKE THAT
TO SLEEP WITH EVERY NIGHT.
Man:
COME IN.
JON PRICE, ROGER MORGAN,
ENGINEERING DEPARTMENT,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
I'M RICK HARRIS,
NEW GENERAL MANAGER.
WHAT HAPPENED TO LES?
HE WAS FIRED LAST NIGHT.
I'VE BEEN HIRED TO TURN
THE DISMAL PERFORMANCE
OF KOZY AROUND,
SO, AS OF 10:00 A.M.
TOMORROW MORNING,
THIS WILL NO LONGER BE
CLASSICAL MUSIC STATION.
WE'RE GOING TO TRY
A TALK RADIO FORMAT
FOR A WHILE,
SEE HOW THAT WORKS.
ALSO, WE'RE CHANGING
THE CALL LETTERS OF
THE STATION TO KRZY.
POWER 98.
I DON' THINK
OUR CLASSICAL ANNOUNCERS
CAN HANDLE THAT FORMAT.
I FIRED THE CLASSICAL STAFF
THIS MORNING.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
HARRIS, I PUT TOGETHER --
EXCUSE ME.
NO, NO.
COME, COME, COME.
I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET
OUR NEW 4:00 TO 8:00 P.M.
DRIVE-TIME DJ,
KARLIN PICKETT.
HIS LAST SHOW WAS ON
STATION KPXH IN PHOENIX,
RATED STEADY
IN THE TOP THREE.
I THINK HE HAS POTENTIAL,
SO I BOUGHT OUT HIS CONTRACT
THREE WEEKS AGO.
I'M EXPECTING HIM TO WORK
HIS MAGIC FOR US HERE.
HARRIS, HERE'S THE SEGMENT
IDEAS YOU WANTED.
WELL, I'D LIKE YOU
TO GIVE HIM
A COMPLETE TOUR
OF THE STUDIOS.
OKAY, TIME TO ANSWER
SOME OF OUR PHONE LINES.
THAT IS THE LAST THING
I EXPECTED.
THEY FIRED EVERYBODY.
JUST LIKE THAT.
I'LL NEVER GET A DJ SLOT NOW,
NOT EVEN AS A SUBSTITUTE.
YOU REALLY SOUND SEXY,
YOU KNOW THAT?
Woman: Well, I've been told
my voice --
YOU'RE GETTING ME HORNY HERE
JUST LISTENING TO YOU.
SO THIS IS GOING TO BE
OUR NEW FORMAT.
YEAH.
ARE YOU WEARING
ANY CLOTHES RIGHT NOW?
No. Just some panties.
OOH. LITTLE ONES, RIGHT?
Black bikini.
MM-HMM.
YOU WANT TO HAVE
SOME FUN WITH ME?
Yeah.
GOOD. TAKE THEM OFF.
I can't believe
I'm actually doing this.
Okay, it's off.
ARE YOU NAKED?
Yes, totally.
REALLY, REALLY?
Yeah. Let me close
the shades here.
GREAT. I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WE'VE GOT A NAKED WOMAN
ON THE LINE.
A TOTALLY NAKED WOMAN!
ON OUR RADIO STATION!
OKAY, NOW THAT
I'VE GOT YOU HERE,
YOU KNOW
WHAT I'D REALLY LIKE?
FOR YOU TO TELL ME
YOUR PET NAME
FOR A GUY'S...MMM...PENIS.
HA HA HA HA.
HE DID NOT
JUST SAY THAT.
HE DID.
NO, HE DIDN'T.
What do you mean?
I MEAN LIKE, DICK.
SCHLONG, SALAMI, PECKER.
Tell you what I call it?
SURE.
ARE YOU INTO IT?
NO...NO.
YOU CANNOT BE THAT STUPID.
Karlin: HELLO?
How about six tickets?
SURE, HONEY.
TELL YOU WHAT.
USE THE WORD
IN A SENTENCE.
SOMETHING LIKE,
"I'D LIKE TO SEE
YOUR BIG, LONG SCHLONG."
What? I don't know.
AHH, COME ON, KAREN.
IT'S JUST FOR FUN.
SHE'S GOING TO DO IT.
THINK OF ALL THE GUYS
YOU'LL BE TURNING ON.
BETTER YET,
THINK OF THOSE SIX TICKETS.
SHE'S GOING TO DO IT.
SEXY NOW.
I really want to see
your big, fat, juicy love toy.
OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS WAY BETTER
THAN WALDO. WHOO!
[ Giggling ]
KAREN, YOU HAVE GIVEN ME
THE MOST ENORMOUS WOODY.
HEY, JON PRICE.
I JUST HEARD
YOUR AUDITION TAPE.
MAN, IT'S GREAT.
THE AUDITION TAPE I GAVE LES
BEFORE HE GOT CANNED?
I TOLD HARRIS
I WANT TO KNOW EVERYTHING
ABOUT EVERYBODY
HERE AT THE STATION,
SO HE GOES THROUGH HIS SHIT,
HE COMES UP WITH YOUR TAPE.
I REALLY LIKED IT.
THANKS A LOT.
HOW COME NOBODY
TOLD ME ABOUT YOU?
YOU GOT A FANTASTIC VOICE,
YOU'RE FUNNY AS HELL.
THIS OUGHT TO BE GETTING
YOU YOUR OWN SHOW.
I'M TRYING.
LET'S GO TALK ABOUT IT.
I GOT SOME IDEAS.
LET'S GO HAVE A DRINK.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF MY SHOW?
IS THIS THE STUFF YOU PLAN
ON DOING ALL THE TIME?
YEP.
YOU WANT MY HONEST OPINION?
SURE.
YOU'RE LIKE A HORNY
HIGH SCHOOL KID.
BUT YOU LAUGHED.
I SAW YOU.
VODKA TONIC.
GIVE ME
A CLUB SODA, PLEASE.
HE'LL HAVE
A VODKA TONIC, TOO.
COME ON, JON.
LIVE A LITTLE.
VODKA TONIC.
SEE, JON,
YOU GOT TO SHOCK
RADIO LISTENERS
OUT OF THEIR MUNDANE,
ORDINARY LIVES.
GIVE THEM SOMETHING
TO TALK ABOUT
AROUND THAT COFFEE MACHINE
IN THE MORNING.
YEAH, BUT TALKING
ABOUT GETTING A WOODY...
SURE, IT'S STUPID,
BUT IT'S A MEANS TO AN END.
WE'LL GET
MORE SOPHISTICATED.
YOU'LL SEE.
SALUD.
SO, WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS?
MY PLANS.
YEAH, RIGHT.
I WANT MY OWN SHOW.
BUT FAT CHANCE
OF THAT HAPPENING NOW.
HOW BAD DO YOU WANT IT?
BAD. I'D GIVE
ALMOST ANYTHING FOR IT.
A MAN WHO KNOWS
WHAT HE WANTS.
I'VE TRIED ALMOST EVERYTHING
AT THAT STATION.
I GUESS I SHOULD
FACE REALITY.
THERE'S 1,000 OTHER GUYS
OUT THERE READY TO KILL
FOR A SPOT ON THE RADIO.
WHAT CHANCE DO I HAVE?
YOU JUST WANT A CHANCE
TO PROVE YOURSELF, RIGHT?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
I GOT AN IDEA.
HOW ABOUT YOU CO-DJ
A SHOW OR TWO WITH ME?
WE'LL GIVE IT A SHOT,
SEE HOW IT GOES.
YOU'RE JOKING, RIGHT?
NO. HARRIS OWES ME
SOME FAVORS.
YOU'RE NOT JOKING?
JESUS, THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING.
I'M A MAN
WHO BELIEVES IN IMPULSE.
AND I GOT A GOOD FEELING
ABOUT YOU.
WELL, WAIT A MINUTE,
KARLIN, I'M CONFUSED.
WHY DO YOU NEED MY HELP?
JON, THE SHOW
COULD BE EVEN FUNNIER
IF I HAVE SOMEONE
TO PLAY OFF OF,
AND YOU'VE GOT
A GREAT AUDITION TAPE HERE.
WELL, THANKS.
I GOT BIG THINGS PLANNED, JON,
AND I NEED ONE MORE INGREDIENT
TO MAKE THIS SHOW COOK.
AND MAYBE YOU'RE IT.
THIS SOUNDS TOO GOOD
TO BE TRUE.
IT IS TRUE.
YOU COULD BE EXACTLY
WHAT I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR.
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
WE GIVE IT A SHOT TOMORROW,
SEE HOW IT GOES.
WORST THING THAT CAN HAPPEN?
WE'LL HAVE A GOOD TIME.
ABSOLUTELY.
I'M NOT TURNING DOWN
A CHANCE LIKE THIS.
YOU CRAZY?
YOU GOT ME.
YOU'RE LISTENING
TO JON PRICE.
HI. YOU'RE ON THE AIR
WITH JON PRICE
AND KARLIN PICKETT.
JON PRICE.
YOU'RE ON THE AIR.
HONEY, TURN OFF THE TV.
I'M TELLING YOU, LADY,
I'VE GOT THREE TESTICLES.
A UROLOGIST DISCOVERED IT
LAST YEAR DURING AN EXAM,
RIGHT, JON?
YEAH, SURE.
SEE? HE BELIEVES ME, LADY.
YOU REALLY GOT
THREE OF THEM?
I MEAN, YOU DIDN'T...
I DON'T KNOW...
COUNT ONE OF THEM TWICE
OR ANYTHING?
JON, YOU WANT TO COUNT
FOR YOURSELF?
NO, NO, NO. I'LL TAKE
YOUR WORD FOR IT.
YOU'VE GOT THREE TESTICLES.
Woman: Young man,
don't say that word again.
Certain words should not
be said on public airwaves.
LADY, CHILL OUT.
ALL THESE WORDS
ARE MEDICAL TERMS.
THERE IS NOTHING WRONG
WITH TALKING ABOUT TESTICLES.
IS THAT
SUCH A BAD THING, JON?
OF COURSE NOT.
IT'S FINE.
IT'S MEDICALLY
AND POLITICALLY CORRECT.
AT LEAST I'M NOT TALKING
ABOUT DICKWEED OR TITTIES.
Oh, dear God.
AT LEAST I'M NOT TALKING
ABOUT MASTURBATION
ON THE AIR, EITHER.
ALTHOUGH IT MAY BE APROPOS
FOR THE SUBJECT AT HAND.
You two better not
talk about that on the air.
AND WHY NOT?
It's vile and hedonistic.
HEY, LADY. IF GOD HADN'T
WANTED US TO MASTURBATE,
HE WOULD HAVE MADE
OUR ARMS SHORTER.
EVERYBODY DOES IT.
EVEN THE POPE...PROBABLY.
HELLO?
[ PHONE HANGS UP ]
[ DIAL TONE ]
SHE'S GONE.
IT'S CLOSED-MINDED
ATTITUDES LIKE HERS
THAT MAKE PEOPLE
LIKE ME AND YOU
THINK THERE IS SOMETHING WRONG
WITH SLAMMING THE SALAMI
EVERY NOW AND THEN.
WHEN I WAS A KID
AND I FIRST DID IT,
I THOUGHT,
"GOD, I BROKE IT."
ABSOLUTELY.
I THOUGHT I WAS A FREAK.
NOW I THINK
THAT PEOPLE WHO ENJOY
A LITTLE SELF-STIMULATION
SHOULDN'T FEEL WEIRD
ABOUT THEMSELVES.
I MEAN, IT CAN BE
AN IMPORTANT RELEASE
FOR PENT-UP EMOTIONS.
EXACTLY.
IT'S VERY THERAPEUTIC.
JON, WHEN WAS THE FIRST TIME
YOU POLISHED THE OLD ROCKET?
UM...
WELL, MY MOTHER
ALWAYS WONDERED
WHY I WAS TAKING
SUCH LONG, HOT SHOWERS.
I TOOK A LOT OF THOSE.
I REMEMBER I DISCOVERED
THE ACT ALL BY MYSELF.
NOBODY TOLD ME
ABOUT IT, EITHER.
IT JUST HAPPENED.
BUT YOU ENJOYED IT,
DIDN'T YOU?
WELL, YEAH. IT FELT GREAT.
I HAVE TO ADMIT.
JON, YOU ARE
A GENUINE PERVERT,
AND THAT'S WHY I LOVE YOU.
TIME FOR A BREAK.
SHE WAS FUN.
Man: WE'RE THE AUTO INSURANCE
CONNECTION.
Woman: WHAT IF I'VE BEEN
CONVICTED OF DRUNK DRIVING?
WE ARE FANTASTIC TOGETHER.
I HAVEN'T LAUGHED SO MUCH
SINCE HIGH SCHOOL.
JON, YOU GOT THE GIG.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME?
NO.
THAT IS GREAT, MAN.
WE'RE FANTASTIC TOGETHER.
THAT WAS SO MUCH FUN.
HI.
SORRY I'M LATE.
THE DEPOSITION TOOK
LONGER THAN I THOUGHT,
AND THEN THE PARTNERS
CALLED A MEETING.
SO, DID YOU
HEAR THE SHOW?
YEAH.
WELL, WHAT DID YOU THINK?
REMIND ME NOT TO ENTER
THE BATHROOM
THE NEXT TIME YOU'RE TAKING
A LONG, HOT SHOWER.
I ACTUALLY LAUGHED
THROUGH MOST OF IT.
IT WAS WILD, SHARON.
I HAD THE BEST TIME.
THIS IS GOING
TO BE INCREDIBLE.
WHAT IS THAT?
TO CELEBRATE
YOUR FIRST DAY ON THE AIR.
OH, THAT IS SO SWEET.
I LOVE YOU.
HERE'S TO YOUR SUCCESS.
NO, NO.
HERE'S TO OUR SUCCESS.
WE'RE JOINED BY
OUR NEWEST INTERN, JOY,
WHO'S GOT A FEW WORDS
TO SAY TO HER MOTHER, JULIE.
GO AHEAD, JOY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M DOING THIS, MOM.
WE HAVE FOUR VOLUNTEERS
FROM OUR ENGINEERING STAFF
TO HELP US
WITH A NEW SEGMENT
CALLED "RATE THE BUTTS."
ARE YOU READY, GUYS?
Joy: [ LAUGHING ]
GET SET...
SHOW US YOUR GOODS.
♪ DUH-DE-DUH DUH DUH
DE-DUH! ♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ GASPS ]
All:
[ LAUGHING ]
JOY, NUMBER ONE.
WELL, NUMBER ONE IS...
NOT BAD.
HEAR THAT, NUMBER ONE?
YOU'RE NOT BAD.
HOW ABOUT FLEXING THOSE
BUTT-CHEEK MUSCLES FOR JOY?
THERE YOU GO!
HA HA HA HA.
WAIT A MINUTE.
HE LIKES DOING THAT TOO MUCH.
NUMBER ONE,
DO YOU LIKE GIRLS?
LET ME TRANSLATE.
YES, HE DOES.
GOOD MAN.
OKAY, JOY, NUMBER TWO.
NUMBER TWO --
OW!
UH...VERY FIRM.
HA HA HA HA.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT!
WAY TO GO, NUMBER TWO.
HA HA HA HA.
JOY, NUMBER THREE.
NUMBER THREE
IS A LITTLE...
HAIRY.
YOU'RE A LITTLE HAIRY,
NUMBER THREE.
UM...NOT BAD,
ACTUALLY.
NOT BAD.
YOU'RE IN THE LEAD.
HARRIS JUST GOT
THE NEW OVERNIGHTS.
HE WANTS TO SEE YOU
AND KARLIN AFTER THE SHOW.
NUMBER THREE IS
THE GRAND PRIZE WINNER
THANKS TO JOY.
HARRIS, YOU WANTED
TO SEE US?
GOOD EVENING,
GENTLEMEN.
ARBITRONS CAME IN
AN HOUR AGO.
AND?
LET ME GUESS.
MY SHOW GOT AN EIGHT SHARE.
NO.
IT GOT A 12 SHARE.
ALL RIGHT!
THAT'S GREAT.
APPARENTLY,
THE GENERAL PUBLIC
HAS AN INSATIABLE APPETITE
FOR BAD TASTE
AND SCATOLOGICAL HUMOR.
FRANKLY,
I DON'T LIKE YOUR SHOW.
BUT I LIKE YOUR NUMBERS.
I TELL YOU WHAT,
I'D LIKE TO
TRY TO HEAD OFF
ANY OTHER OFFERS
YOU GUYS MIGHT GET.
I TELL YOU THIS --
I WILL DOUBLE
EACH OF YOUR SALARIES
IF YOU DELIVER TO ME
A 25 SHARE.
A 25 SHARE?
JON AND I
WILL GET YOU YOUR NUMBERS.
BUT WE'RE GOING TO WANT
COMPLETE FREEDOM
TO DO OR SAY
ANYTHING WE'D LIKE
ON THE AIR.
NO...NO.
YEAH. GIVE US
TOTAL FREE REIGN, HARRIS.
OKAY.
YOU GOT IT.
[ SLAPS JON'S KNEE ]
DO WHATEVER YOU HAVE TO DO.
GET ME THE NUMBERS.
BUT ONE WORD OF CAUTION.
I MAY HAVE TO RE-EXERT
SOME CONTROL
IF THE FCC STARTS
FINING THE STATION.
HARRIS...
IF THE FCC STEPS IN,
IT'LL MEAN OUR RATINGS HAVE
REALLY GONE THROUGH THE ROOF.
YEAH.
I'M STILL IN SHOCK.
WE GOT A 12 SHARE.
THAT'S DOUBLE WHAT
THE CLASSICAL FORMAT GOT
ON ITS BEST NIGHT.
AMAZING. FROM BEETHOVEN
TO BUTT CONTESTS IN ONE MONTH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I CAN BELIEVE
THERE ARE SO MANY PEOPLE
LISTENING TO THE SHOW.
I MEAN I LOVE IT.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU, JON?
LET ME EXPLAIN
HOW IT WORKS.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
ME?
I DON'T KNOW.
SUCCESS, YOU KNOW.
TO BE HAPPY.
YOU WANT A COUPLE
OF BEAUTIFUL HOMES,
YOU WANT TO DRIVE
GERMAN ENGINEERING,
BEAUTIFUL WOMEN.
YEAH, SURE. WHAT EVERY
RED-BLOODED AMERICAN WANTS.
I ALREADY GOT
THE WOMAN PART.
YOU DO?
YEAH.
LET ME SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
IT'S MY LITTLE HONEY.
THAT'S SHARON.
ISN'T SHE BEAUTIFUL?
SHE'S NICE.
NICE?
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL, MAN.
BESIDES, THERE'S MORE
TO A PERSON THAN LOOKS.
THERE'S TRUST,
THERE'S LOVE,
THERE'S COMMITMENT.
YOU GOT A POINT, JON.
BUT...
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
WITH HER?
THE BLONDE IN THE BLACK.
COME ON, KARLIN.
LET'S SAY THAT SHARON
WOULD NEVER FIND OUT.
WHAT'S THE POINT?
I KNOW YOU GET
THE URGE, JON.
EVERY GUY DOES.
AT LEAST I ADMIT IT.
WE'D ALL LOVE TO HAVE
EVERY BEAUTIFUL WOMAN WE SEE.
AM I RIGHT?
AND YOU CAN, JON.
BECAUSE OF ME, YOU'RE
GOING TO BE FAMOUS.
GOING TO MAKE MONEY.
NOW, WHAT WOULD YOU DO
WITH HER
IF SHE WAS LYING NAKED
ON YOUR BED?
MMM.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
WITH HER, JON?
OKAY, OKAY.
I'M NOT A SAINT.
HONESTY, JON.
THANK YOU.
WE'D ALL LOVE TO HAVE
A WOMAN GUYS GO CRAZY OVER,
A CAR THAT TURNS HEADS.
EVERYBODY HAS FANTASIZED
ABOUT BEING FAMOUS.
PEOPLE RECOGNIZING YOU,
BEGGING YOU FOR YOUR AUTOGRAPH.
BUT MOST OF ALL, JON,
YOU'D LIKE TO HAVE POWER.
REAL POWER.
POWER TO DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
YEAH.
SEE? I SPEAK THE TRUTH.
I KNOW WHAT PEOPLE WANT.
THAT'S WHY THE SHOW WORKS.
I KNOW WHAT YOU WANT.
THAT'S WHY WE WORK.
IF YOU STICK WITH ME,
YOU'RE GOING TO HIT THE ROOF.
WE'LL GO THROUGH
THE STRATOSPHERE.
BUT YOU GOT TO STICK WITH ME
THROUGH THICK AND THIN.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE SOME
WILD TIMES UP AHEAD, JON.
AND I NEED TO KNOW
I CAN COUNT ON YOU.
CAN I COUNT ON YOU, JON?
YEAH. ABSOLUTELY.
GOOD.
ONE MORE.
HEY, WHEN ARE WE
GOING TO GET
TO GO ON THE AIR
WITH YOU?
DENISE. CYNTHIA.
SO NICE TO SEE YOU LADIES.
IF I DIDN'T KNOW
ANY BETTER,
I'D THINK THAT YOU WERE
PUTTING US ON THE OTHER NIGHT
ABOUT BEING ON YOUR SHOW.
PUTTING YOU ON?
MR. PRICE, WILL YOU TELL
THESE LOVELY LADIES
THAT I WAS JUST
TALKING ABOUT THEM?
YEAH. HE SURE WAS.
HEY.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU JON PRICE?
YEAH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE THE SAME PERSON
I LISTEN TO ON THE RADIO
EVERY NIGHT.
WHY? WHAT DID YOU
EXPECT ME TO BE LIKE?
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE --
I DON'T KNOW.
OLDER.
NOT SO ATTRACTIVE.
IT'S WEIRD.
I LISTEN TO YOUR SHOW
EVERY NIGHT, AND YOUR VOICE --
I KNOW THAT THIS
IS GOING TO SOUND STRANGE,
BUT...IT'S BECOMING
SO FAMILIAR TO ME.
SO COMFORTABLE.
REALLY?
I FEEL LIKE YOUR A FRIEND
WHO'S HOME WITH ME EVERY NIGHT,
KEEPING ME COMPANY.
WHY DON'T YOU COME BACK
WITH ME TO MY PLACE TONIGHT
AND HAVE SOME WINE?
YOU CAN TELL ME
HOW YOU COME UP WITH
ALL THOSE CRAZY THINGS
YOU DO ON THE AIR.
MAYBE YOU CAN EVEN
TUCK ME INTO BED.
AHH, MAN.
I'M KIND OF SEEING
SOMEONE RIGHT NOW.
COME ON. IT'S JUST
A GLASS OF WINE.
ALL WE'LL DO IS TALK.
LOOK, CYNTHIA, I CAN'T.
I'M SORRY,
BUT-BUT I CAN'T.
HERE'S MY NUMBER.
I WANT YOU TO CALL ME
WHEN YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND.
OH...GOD.
[ DIAL TONE ]
[ TELEPHONE DIALING ]
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
HELLO?
Jon. Jon,
did I wake you?
KARLIN,
ARE YOU OKAY?
I COULDN'T SLEEP.
CAN YOU COME OVER?
There's something
I want to talk to you about.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
JUST COME OVER,
ALL RIGHT?
HELLO?
KARLIN?
Karlin:
JON, COME ON IN.
THIS PLACE IS BEAUTIFUL.
HEY, JON,
THANKS FOR COMING.
YOU WANT A DRINK?
SURE YOU DO.
COME ON.
I GOT SOME GREAT
RED WINE HERE.
SO, YOU EVER
MAKE IT WITH CYNTHIA?
HEY, I'M LIVING
WITH SHARON.
SHE WAS SO INTO YOU.
AND YOU CAN HAVE ANY
BEAUTIFUL WOMAN YOU WANT, JON.
YOU'RE BECOMING A CELEBRITY.
YEAH.
SO, WHAT DID YOU
CALL ME HERE FOR?
WELL, YOU KNOW I SAID
ABOUT SOME WILD TIMES UP AHEAD?
WELL, IT CAME TO ME
ABOUT AN HOUR AGO
WHAT WE GOT TO DO.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE SHOW.
WE GOT TO BECOME
MORE OUTRAGEOUS, JON,
OTHERWISE, WE'RE GOING
TO LOSE OUR NUMBERS.
MORE OUTRAGEOUS.
DO YOU THINK THAT'S POSSIBLE?
DRINK UP.
WE'RE GOING TO GO
FOR A RIDE.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU
SOMETHING.
WHAT ARE THOSE?
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY'RE YELLOW.
COME ON.
GRAB THAT DOOR FOR ME,
WILL YOU?
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THE BLUE ONE?
325I?
YOU KNOW IT, HUH?
IT COSTS $50,000.
2.5 LITER IN-LINE
SIX-CYLINDER ENGINE.
DELIVERS 189 HORSEPOWER.
0 TO 60 IN 7 SECONDS.
I EVEN PICKED OUT
MY OWN COLOR.
GIVE ME SAMOA BLUE.
200,000 PEOPLE DOWN THERE
LISTEN TO ME AND YOU
ON THE RADIO EVERY NIGHT.
WE ARE RIGHT ON THE VERGE
OF GETTING WHAT WE WANTED.
I LEARNED A LOT
IN PHOENIX, JON,
AND I'M GOING TO APPLY IT
ALL RIGHT HERE.
WHY DID YOU LEAVE PHOENIX?
YOU WERE DOING WELL THERE.
I HAD OUTGROWN PHOENIX, JON.
JUST LIKE WE'RE GOING
TO OUTGROW LOS ANGELES.
OUTGROW LOS ANGELES?
I'M STARTING TO GET OFFERS
TO SYNDICATE NATIONWIDE.
IF OUR NUMBERS KEEP GROWING,
I'LL BE TAKING OUR SHOW INTO
50 CITIES ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
WE ARE ENTERING A NEW AGE.
OLD TABOOS ARE FALLING AWAY.
PEOPLE ARE NOT AS AFRAID
TO TAP INTO
THE DARK SIDE
OF THEMSELVES.
IN FACT,
THEY ARE FASCINATED
BY DEPRAVITY.
I WANT TO DO
A NEW SEGMENT,
AND CALL IT
"MY BEST CRIME."
PEOPLE CALL US UP
ANONYMOUSLY,
AND THEY TALK ABOUT
A CRIME THEY'VE COMMITTED --
AND WE'RE NOT TALKING
SHOPLIFTING HERE.
I MEAN RAPE, INCEST, MURDER.
ISN'T THAT
A LITTLE HARDCORE?
THE ABSOLUTE CUTTING EDGE.
SURE, WE'LL GET
A LOT OF CRANK CALLS,
BUT WE'LL ALSO GET
A LOT OF REAL CALLS.
JON, THERE'S A WHOLE
CITY OF PERVERSION DOWN THERE,
AND WE CAN PLUG INTO IT,
USE OUR 55,000 WATTS
OF POWER
TO SPREAD IT
TO EVERY SINGLE CORNER.
I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
IT SOUNDS
WAY OVER THE EDGE.
YOU GOT TO ADMIT
IT SOUNDS CRAZY.
IT'LL BE FASCINATING.
WE'LL HAVE PEOPLE
GLUED TO THEIR RADIOS.
WE'LL HAVE THEM ASKING,
WHO'S GOING TO CALL TONIGHT?
WHAT SICK CONFESSION
WILL I HEAR THIS EVENING?
I BET WE GET A 25 SHARE
OUR FIRST MONTH.
AND FROM THERE,
YOU AND I ARE A SIGNATURE
ON A CONTRACT AWAY
FROM GOING COAST-TO-COAST.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
SOMETIMES.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, JON?
YEAH. HELL, YEAH.
LET'S DO IT.
Man: So, I stole this car
when I was in 11th grade.
And me and a couple of friends
went for a ride to Vegas.
FOLKS, IS THIS
THE BEST WE CAN DO?
Well, hey, the car
was a brand-new Cadillac.
We drove all night --
WHAT A LOSER.
STEALS A CAR.
THAT'S HIS CRIME?
BIG DEAL.
IT HAPPENS 1,000 TIMES A WEEK
IN THIS CITY.
FOLKS, THIS IS
AN OPPORTUNITY
TO GET SOMETHING
REALLY BIG OFF YOUR CHEST.
OKAY, I WANT
TO HEAR ABOUT
THE NASTIEST CRIMES
YOU'VE GOTTEN AWAY WITH.
GET DOWN AND DIRTY, PEOPLE.
WE'VE ALL DONE SOMETHING
WE'VE REGRETTED,
EVEN YOURS TRULY,
KARLIN PICKETT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT CONFESSION
ACTUALLY DOES FOR THE SOUL,
BUT IT MAKES
FOR GOOD ENTERTAINMENT,
SO CALL ME.
I AM WAITING ANXIOUSLY
TO HEAR YOUR DARKEST SECRET.
OUR NEXT CALLER
ON DIRECT LINE TWO.
HELLO, CAN YOU PLEASE
TELL US YOUR NAME?
Uh...I'd really
rather not say.
GUY WON'T TELL US
HIS NAME.
OKAY, THIS MUST BE GOOD.
OKAY,
WHAT'S YOUR BEST CRIME?
HELLO?
Yeah, hi.
SPEAK UP.
HAVE YOU GOT A GOOD CRIME?
Well, this is a little hard.
I heard you guys tonight,
and um...
well, I really feel like I need
to tell someone about this.
I kind of met this girl
one night.
She was really cute.
This is a little hard
for me.
She got me really pissed.
I mean, for her,
it was just a one-nighter.
Like she just wanted
to screw me.
So, I think I got
a little bit angry,
and I lost control.
SO YOU BEAT HER UP?
THAT WAS A MISTAKE.
BUT YOU SOUND
LIKE A NICE GUY.
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN, RIGHT?
No, I didn't beat her.
It actually went
a little further than that.
I kind of hurt her bad.
HOW BAD?
I'm not sure
she made it through, actually.
ARE YOU SAYING
THAT YOU KILLED HER?
HELLO?
SIR, NO JOKES NOW.
YOU REALLY THINK
YOU KILLED HER?
Yeah. I know I did.
YOU'RE SAYING
YOU KILLED THIS WOMAN?
Yes.
We were making love
in an abandoned warehouse,
and she...
she fell.
Actually, I kind of
picked her up
and threw her
over the side.
The cops still don't know
that I'm the one who killed her.
I just needed
to talk about this.
Get it off my chest.
Because I don't know.
I might do it again.
And if I do,
I'll call in
and tell you about it.
I really love your show.
It's all
that keeps me going.
I think I better
get off now.
UH, SIR,
PLEASE STAY ON THE LINE.
I'll call back again.
DON'T HANG UP.
HELLO?
WE LOSE HIM?
[ BEEP ]
WHOA.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S TAKE A FEW
DEEP BREATHS, TAKE A BREAK.
LISTENING TO
"THE KARLIN PICKETT SHOW,"
POWER 98.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OH...
Man: IT'S THE CRAZIEST
CAR RADIO SALE...
A MURDERER
ACTUALLY CALLED IN.
I NEVER REALLY BELIEVED
IT WOULD HAPPEN.
TO THINK HE MIGHT
CALL IN AGAIN.
WE'RE INTO
SOME WEIRDNESS NOW.
I GOT TO PEE.
HEY, DO YOU REALLY THINK
THE CALLER WAS FOR REAL?
THE GUY THAT CALLED?
HE DIDN'T KILL ANYBODY.
HOW COULD YOU
POSSIBLY KNOW THAT?
HEY...
WAIT A MINUTE, KARLIN.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
HE WAS A FRIEND OF MINE.
I HAD HIM CALL.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
NO, I'M NOT.
IT WAS A FAKE CALLER?
YEP.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID THAT.
I CAN'T GO ALONG
WITH THIS.
SINCE WHEN HAVE YOU
BECOME MR. ETHICS?
HEY, MAN, WE GOT TO TELL
OUR AUDIENCE ABOUT THE CALLER.
ARE YOU AN IDIOT?
IF THE FCC FINDS OUT --
THE FCC, MY ASS.
LOOK, THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH WHAT WE DID.
NOBODY WAS HURT BY IT.
YOU CAN'T TALK ABOUT THIS,
JON. THE SHOW IS TOO HOT.
YOU FOUL IT UP
AND PEOPLE COULD BE LEAD
TO BELIEVE THIS FAKE CALLER
WAS ALL YOUR IDEA.
TRY GETTING BACK
ON THE AIR AFTER THAT.
YEAH, I GET THE PICTURE.
GOOD.
HEY.
WHAT?
I'LL GO ALONG WITH IT
FOR NOW,
BUT AFTER THIS,
I WANT MY OWN SHOW.
GETTING PRETTY COCKY,
AREN'T YOU, JON?
WHO WERE YOU
BEFORE I PUT YOU ON THE AIR?
YOU WANT ME TO GO ALONG
WITH THE PRANK CALLER,
YOU GET ME MY OWN SHOW.
THAT'S THE BARGAIN.
THAT'S THE BARGAIN?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL GIVE YOU YOUR OWN SHOW.
I'LL MAKE IT A CONDITION
OF MY RENEWAL.
BUT YOU BETTER
WORK WITH ME ON THIS.
DON'T FUCK IT UP.
ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT.
OH, YOU'RE STILL UP?
HI.
I GOT SOME GREAT NEWS.
WHAT?
I'M GETTING MY OWN SHOW.
THE JON PRICE SHOW
WILL BE ON IN A MONTH.
OH, MY GOD. THAT'S GREAT.
IT'S HAPPENING SO FAST.
I CAN DO MY STUFF,
NOT THIS TRASH
KARLIN HAS ME DOING.
WHAT WAS GOING ON
WITH THE SHOW TONIGHT?
THAT WAS JUST A STUNT.
THE GUY WHO CALLED,
HE NEVER KILLED ANYBODY.
HE'S JUST SOME FRIEND
OF KARLIN'S.
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU'RE SAYING
YOU GUYS PLANNED THIS?
NO, NOT ME. KARLIN.
THIS WAS KARLIN'S IDEA?
WHY DID YOU LET HIM
MANIPULATE YOU
INTO GOING ALONG WITH IT?
I WASN'T MANIPULATED.
I DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT IT
UNTIL LATER.
IS THERE ANY ASPIRIN
IN THIS HOUSE?
SO KARLIN IS
LYING TO THE AUDIENCE,
AND YOU'RE GOING
ALONG WITH IT.
YOU THINK I LIKE
WHAT HE'S DOING? I DON'T.
BUT WHAT I LIKE EVEN LESS IS
BEING SOME ANONYMOUS ENGINEER,
BEING BEHIND IN CAR PAYMENTS,
THE RENT, MY STUDENT LOANS.
YOU KNOW WHAT, JON?
WE GOT BY.
WELL, I'M NOT GOING
TO GET BY ANYMORE,
YOU KNOW?
SO WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
A FAKE MURDERER
IS CALLING THE SHOW.
IT'S NOT HURTING ANYBODY.
I CAN LIVE WITH IT,
ESPECIALLY IF KARLIN
GETS ME MY OWN SHOW.
JESUS. LISTEN TO YOU.
YEAH.
LISTEN TO ME, SHARON.
I'M LEARNING I GOT TO DO
WHAT I GOT TO DO
TO GET WHAT I WANT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE HAPPY
WITH WHAT YOU SEE
IN FRONT OF YOU.
YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT I SEE?
I SEE A GUY
WITH A HIT RADIO SHOW.
I SEE SUCCESS.
Harris:
HELLO, EVERYBODY.
COULD I HAVE
YOUR ATTENTION?
Man: SHH!
YEAH, EVERYBODY.
PLEASE, EVERYBODY.
THIS HAS BEEN
AN AMAZING COUPLE WEEKS
SINCE WE STARTED.
I THINK WE ALL KNOW HOW
EXTREMELY UNUSUAL IT IS
FOR A LATE AFTERNOON
DRIVE-TIME SHOW
TO TURN ANY STATION AROUND,
BUT, UH...
I JUST RECEIVED
THE OVERNIGHTS,
AND, UH...
I'M PROUD TO ANNOUNCE
THAT THE "KARLIN PICKETT SHOW"
HERE ON KRZY POWER 98...
HAS JUST RECEIVED
A 37 LAST NIGHT!
[ APPLAUSE ]
HIS HIGHEST RATING EVER
FOR A SINGLE SHOW!
WHAT DID I TELL YOU,
LITTLE BROTHER?
WE ARE HOT.
YEAH. THANKS TO YOU.
HARRIS.
THERE ARE MY TWO
SPECIAL BOYS.
I KNEW WHEN I SIGNED YOU
GREAT THINGS WERE GOING
TO HAPPEN AT THIS STATION.
WHAT'S WITH THE COPS?
IT'S STANDARD PROCEDURE.
ABOUT THE GUY WHO CALLED.
THE GUY WHO SAID
HE KILLED SOMEONE?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE MAKING A COPY
FOR THEM OF LAST NIGHT'S SHOW.
IT WAS A GREAT THING
THIS GUY CALLED.
IT GAVE THE SHOW A BOOST.
IF HE CALLS BACK,
WE COULD DOUBLE OUR RATINGS.
YEAH.
TO CONSOLIDATE OUR GAINS.
YOU KNOW HOW THESE THINGS
TEND TO ERODE.
OH, IT'S AMAZING.
IN THE 20 YEARS
I'VE BEEN IN THIS BUSINESS,
I HAVE NEVER SEEN
BETTER DEMOS DELIVERED FASTER.
EVERYBODY IN THIS TOWN
WITH A RADIO
WAS LISTENING LAST NIGHT.
CONGRATULATIONS, BOYS.
I'M GOING TO CALL UP
BUSINESS AFFAIRS
AND HAVE THEM STRIKE UP
YOUR NEW CONTRACTS RIGHT NOW.
HARRIS, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO WAIT ON THAT.
WHAT?
WE COULD HAVE A LITTLE BUMP
IN THE OLD ROAD.
TELL HIM, JON.
HARRIS, I WANT
MY OWN SHOW.
WHAT?
AND WE'RE NOT TALKING
GRAVEYARD SHIFT, EITHER.
I WANT HIM AS LEAD-IN
TO MY SHOW,
PLUS I WANT HIM
WITH ME FOR AN HOUR.
YOU MEAN BUMPING DeSANTOS?
NO BIG LOSS.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
I'M PAYING DeSANTOS?
$245,000.
DO YOU THINK I'M GOING TO FLUSH
THAT MONEY DOWN THE TOILET?
WE'RE GETTING OFFERS,
HARRIS -- BIG OFFERS.
KROV, KHOK,
UNITED SYNDICATION.
THIS IS NOT
AN OPTION, HARRIS.
THIS A DEAL-BREAKER.
YOU TWO ARE LITTLE SHITS.
YEAH. BUT AT LEAST WE'RE
STILL YOUR LITTLE SHITS.
LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S US.
AND TOMORROW THERE
WILL BE 15 MORE OF THOSE
AROUND THE CITY.
YEAH,
IT'S PRETTY GOOD.
PRETTY GOOD?
TOMORROW YOU'RE GOING TO
BE SIGNING A CONTRACT
FOR YOUR OWN SHOW,
MAKING 10 TIMES THE AMOUNT
OF MONEY YOU HAVE EVER MADE,
AND YOU'RE TELLING ME
THAT'S PRETTY GOOD?
YOU'RE RIGHT, IT'S GREAT.
IT'S...
IT'S FANTASTIC.
DID I KEEP MY PROMISE
TO YOU?
DID I GET YOU THERE?
YOU DID,
BUT WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT
MY STAYING ON YOUR SHOW
FOR AN HOUR?
I TOLD YOU I WANTED
TO BE ON MY OWN.
JON, I NEED YOU ON MY SHOW
JUST A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
WE TALKED ABOUT.
I THINK I'M MISSING SOMETHING
HERE, LIKE A LITTLE GRATITUDE.
LOOK, I WANT TO RIDE THIS BABY
JUST A LITTLE BIT LONGER
AND MAKE SURE THE SHOW'S
IN A SOLID POSITION.
IS THAT TOO MUCH TO ASK?
ALL RIGHT.
THEN I'M ON MY OWN?
YES, JON.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S US.
SHARON, ISN'T IT BEAUTIFUL?
HAVE YOU COMPLETELY
LOST YOUR MIND?
WHAT THE HELL'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN GOTTEN
YOUR FIRST PAYCHECK.
COULD YOU SPEND
WHAT LITTLE MONEY WE HAVE
IN A STUPIDER WAY?
I DON'T NEED THIS.
JON, WAIT.
CYNTHIA...
JON PRICE.
YEAH, I WAS WONDERING
ABOUT YOU, TOO.
I WAS JUST DRIVING AROUND
AND THINKING ABOUT THAT OFFER
TO HAVE SOME WINE AND TALK.
WERE YOU SERIOUS ABOUT THAT?
RIGHT NOW?
UH, YEAH...YEAH, SURE.
OKAY. WHERE AM I GOING?
HI.
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHY I'M HERE.
OH, HI, SHARON.
I'M SORRY I'M SO LATE.
YOU GOT A CALL-IN
FROM CYNTHIA.
CYNTHIA?
SHE SAYS PICK UP THE JACKET
YOU LEFT AT HER PLACE ANYTIME,
PREFERABLY AT NIGHT,
WHEN YOU CAN TUCK HER IN.
SHARON, SHE'S JUST
PLAYING WITH YOU.
IS SHE THE FIRST,
OR HAVE THERE BEEN OTHERS?
SHE'S PROBABLY A FAN.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT, JON?
DON'T LIE TO ME,
BECAUSE I AM NOT AN IDIOT.
I CAN SMELL HER
ALL OVER YOU.
OKAY, UH...
OKAY, CAN WE TALK
ABOUT THIS?
NO. I'M TOO PISSED OFF RIGHT NOW
TO TALK ABOUT ANYTHING.
I'LL HAVE SOMEBODY COME OVER
AND GET THE REST
OF MY THINGS TOMORROW.
OH, OKAY, THAT'S IT?
YOU'RE JUST GOING TO PACK UP
AND LEAVE ME JUST LIKE THAT?
THAT'S RIGHT, I'M PACKING UP,
AND I'M LEAVING.
LOOK AT YOU. YOU DON'T EVEN
DRESS THE SAME ANYMORE.
YOU LOOK LIKE HIM.
YOU LOOK LIKE KARLIN.
IT'S THAT YOU'VE CHANGED.
YOU SOLD YOURSELF OUT
TO GET WHAT YOU WANTED.
MAYBE IT TOOK THIS OTHER WOMAN
TO MAKE ME SEE IT.
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
OKAY, FINE.
I'M NOT GOING TO STOP YOU.
YOU WANT TO END IT THIS WAY,
THEN GO, LEAVE.
I DON'T NEED YOU, SHARON!
I AM SUCH AN IDIOT.
Karlin: Hey, Jon,
how's it going?
YOU GAVE CYNTHIA MY NUMBER,
DIDN'T YOU?
You don't sound too happy.
THAT'S RIGHT, KARLIN.
I DIDN'T APPRECIATE IT.
NEITHER DID SHARON.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE STILL
SEEING EACH OTHER.
YEAH, RIGHT. NOT ANYMORE.
You can have any woman
you want now.
AND BELIEVE ME,
THERE'S A MILLION OF THEM.
JON PRICE,
I'M DETECTIVE WILKINSON.
THIS IS DETECTIVE DURRANO.
IS THERE SOMETHING
I CAN DO FOR YOU?
MIND IF WE ASK YOU
A FEW QUESTIONS
REGARDING THE MAN WHO CALLED
YOUR SHOW LAST WEEK?
THE ONE WHO CLAIMS TO HAVE
COMMITTED A HOMICIDE?
YOU MIND COMING WITH US?
SHOULDN'T TAKE TOO LONG.
COFFEE?
NO, THANKS.
I DON'T BLAME YOU.
EVERYBODY THINKS
THAT COPS DRINK COFFEE.
ME, I LIKE TEA.
DOESN'T GO THROUGH
THE PIPES AS FAST.
YOU WANT SOME TEA?
THAT'S FINE.
YEAH, I WANT TO TELL YOU,
I REALLY LIKE
YOUR SHOW, MAN.
ME AND MY PARTNER,
WE LISTEN TO IT ALL THE TIME.
YOU GUYS DO SOME SICK STUFF.
THAT "RATE THE BUTT" SEQUENCE
KILLED ME.
THANKS.
HERE YOU GO.
JON...
CAN I CALL YOU JON?
YEAH, SURE.
JON, WHAT WAS YOUR IMPRESSION
OF THE GUY WHO CALLED UP,
THE ONE WHO CLAIMED TO KILL
THE WOMAN HE PICKED UP?
YOU THINK
HE'LL CALL BACK?
HE SAID HE WOULD.
MAYBE IT WAS JUST
A CRANK CALL.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I ASKED.
WE KNOW IT WASN'T
A CRANK CALL.
I ASKED YOU IF YOU THOUGHT
HE MIGHT CALL BACK AGAIN.
ARE YOU TELLING ME THAT
THERE REALLY WAS A MURDER?
YEAH, JON.
THE GUY WAS FOR REAL.
YOU SEEM SURPRISED.
YOU MUST HAVE THOUGHT
IT MIGHT BE LEGIT.
YEAH, IT'S JUST
KIND OF A SHOCK
TO THINK HE WAS DESCRIBING
A REAL MURDER.
WE KNOW HE KILLED THIS WOMAN
THREE MONTHS AGO.
VIVIAN PORTER'S HER NAME.
SHE WAS PUSHED OFF
A WAREHOUSE FIRE ESCAPE,
JUST LIKE
THE CALLER DESCRIBED.
SEVEN STORIES,
STRAIGHT DOWN.
OH...
GOD.
OH, JESUS.
WE DON'T HAVE A MOTIVE YET.
NOT A STRONG ONE, ANYWAY.
WE FIGURE IT'S PRETTY MUCH
WHAT HE SAID IT WAS --
A ONE-NIGHT STAND GONE BAD.
AND NOW HE'S GETTING HIS ROCKS
OFF CALLING YOUR SHOW
TELLING THE WORLD
WHAT HE DID.
JON, I'M GOING TO BE
DIRECT WITH YOU.
WE BROUGHT YOU DOWN HERE
TO ASK YOU ONE SIMPLE QUESTION.
YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THE CALLER?
LIKE WHO HE IS,
FOR EXAMPLE?
NO.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH, I'M POSITIVE.
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT WE FIGURED.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK TO
YOUR PARTNER, KARLIN PICKETT.
SEE WHAT HE KNOWS.
WE'RE ALSO GOING TO MONITOR
THE RADIO STATION,
YOUR SHOW ESPECIALLY.
IF THE CREEP CALLS,
WE'D LIKE TO BE THERE.
IT ONLY TAKES 10 SECONDS
TO TRACE A CALL.
FIVE MINUTES TO GET
THE BLACK-AND-WHITES
THE LOCATION OF THE CALL.
SO IF HE CALLS AGAIN,
YOU KEEP HIM TALKING, OKAY?
OKAY.
WE HAVE NOTHING MORE.
THANKS FOR YOUR TIME, JON.
OKAY, THANKS.
HEY, THIS IS
OUR PHONE NUMBER
IN CASE YOU WANT TO
CALL US ABOUT ANYTHING --
A HUNCH, A LEAD, WHATEVER.
OKAY, THANKS.
BOY'S IN A HURRY.
JON.
WHO'S THE GUY
THAT'S CALLED THE SHOW?
WHO IS HE, KARLIN?
HOW COME YOU'RE SO CONCERNED
ABOUT WHO HE IS?
A COUPLE COPS WE'RE
AT MY HOME THIS MORNING.
THEY TOLD ME YOUR FRIEND
REALLY KILLED A WOMAN.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
NO, I'M NOT.
IT ALL HAPPENED EXACTLY
THE WAY HE DESCRIBED IT.
YOU DIDN'T TELL THEM
ANYTHING, DID YOU?
NO, I WANTED TO
TALK TO YOU FIRST.
WE GOT TO TELL THEM
WHO THIS GUY IS.
NO, WE CAN'T DO THAT.
WE HAVE TO.
NO, WE DON'T.
EDDIE --
EDDIE DIDN'T DO THIS.
EDDIE? EDDIE WHAT?
HE'S PROBABLY TAKING CREDIT FOR
SOMETHING HE SAW ON THE NEWS.
I'M GOING TO TELL THE COPS
WHAT'S GOING ON,
THAT YOU KNOW THE CALLER'S
THIS EDDIE GUY.
YOU CAN'T.
WE GOT THE TOP-RATED SHOW.
THAT'S AN INCREDIBLE
ACCOMPLISHMENT.
YOU TELL THEM ABOUT EDDIE,
THEY'LL TAKE US OFF THE AIR.
SCREW THE SHOW.
THIS GUY KILLED A WOMAN.
HE DIDN'T KILL ANYBODY.
LET'S SAY BY SOME COINCIDENCE,
THEY TIE HIM TO A MURDER.
THE COPS WILL MAKE YOU AND ME
ACCOMPLICES TO IT.
THAT MEANS JAIL TIME
FOR BOTH OF US.
I HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH EDDIE.
JON...
YES, YOU DID.
IF YOU WERE
TO PHONE THE COPS,
I WOULD FUCK YOU OVER
ROYALLY.
I AM NOT
SUFFERING THIS ALONE.
I'LL SAY YOU KNEW AS MUCH
ABOUT EDDIE AS I DID.
YOU WANTED WOMEN,
YOU WANTED SUCCESS, WELL...
BE CAREFUL WHAT YOU WISH FOR,
LITTLE BROTHER.
IT ISN'T FREE.
GOODBYE, HONEY.
PLEASANT DREAMS.
I'M IN A GREAT DEAL OF PAIN
RIGHT NOW.
PAIR OF 2's. I'M OUT.
AH, TOO BAD, JON.
I GUESS YOU'RE NOT
THE CARD PLAYER I AM.
YEAH, I GUESS NOT.
CLAIRE, WHAT YOU GOT?
STRAIGHT, 10 HIGH.
STRAIGHT, 10 HIGH!
SUSAN, CAN YOU BEAT IT?
MNH-MNH.
SUSAN'S GOT A...PAIR,
BUT WHAT A PAIR, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE WHAT
BIG BROTHER KARLIN HAS.
FOUR OF A KIND -- JACKS.
LOOKS LIKE MY HAND.
OKAY, SOMETHING HAS GOT TO
COME OFF, LADIES.
ALL RIGHT. WHILE WE'RE WAITING
FOR OUR NEXT CRIMINAL TO CALL,
LET'S GET DOWN
TO BUSINESS HERE.
CALLER NUMBER 1,
WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST?
Man's voice:    WELL,
ARE THEY WEARING BRAS?
YEP, AND NOT MUCH ELSE.
WELL, TAKE THEM OFF!
Karlin: MM...
CALLER NUMBER 2,
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
Man's voice: JON? KARLIN?
YEAH,
WHAT'S YOUR SUGGESTION?
UH, I'M SORRY,
BUT I HAD TO CALL AGAIN.
OKAY, WE'RE LISTENING.
I GUESS YOU KNOW BY NOW
THAT I WASN'T JOKING
ABOUT VIVIAN, WAS I?
I REALLY PUSHED HER OFF
THAT BUILDING.
I'VE GOT TO GET THIS STUFF
OFF MY CHEST, YOU KNOW?
I MET ANOTHER WOMAN
LAST NIGHT.
I MEAN, I ACTUALLY LIKED HER,
YOU KNOW?
I DIDN'T WANT ANYTHING
TO HAPPEN TO HER,
BUT SHE STARTED TO LAUGH AT ME
WHEN WE DID IT.
I'M IN A GREAT DEAL OF PAIN
RIGHT NOW.
THIS WOMAN,
SHE WENT HOME WITH YOU?
YEAH -- NO, NO,
I WENT TO HER HOUSE.
IS SHE OKAY?
NO.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER?
I KILLED HER...
WITH CYANIDE.
GET ME THE LOCATION
OF 555-7620.
OKAY, KEEP TALKING.
TELL US MORE ABOUT IT.
YOU KNOW HER NAME?
YEAH.
YEAH, WE'RE HERE.
WE GOT AN E.S.U.
AND SIX BLACK-AND-WHITES
HEADED FOR THE SOURCE
OF THE CALL.
UM, I'VE SAID TOO MUCH
ALREADY.
I...I REALLY...
I GOT TO GO.
Jon: NO, NO, NO,
TALK TO US.
COME ON,
WE'RE LISTENING.
I'LL CALL AGAIN.
[ DIAL TONE ]
DAMN IT.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
I DON'T KNOW. EDDIE CALLED
ON HIS OWN THIS TIME.
GET HIM TO STOP,
UNDERSTAND?
YOU CAN'T BUY P.R.
LIKE THIS.
I BET WE MAKE IT
TO THE NATIONAL NEWS.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
THIS IS INSANE.
WE GOT THE SYNDICATORS
BY THE BALLS.
IF EDDIE KEEPS CALLING,
THEY'LL BE BEGGING US
TO DO A NATIONWIDE SHOW.
NOW GET WITH THE PROGRAM.
Wilkinson: GENTLEMEN.
WE GOT AN ADDRESS,
BUT IT'S WRONG.
LOOKS LIKE HE'S GOT
A SCRAMBLER ON THE LINE.
AH, WHAT A DRAG.
YEAH, HE'S A SMART ONE.
CALLED IN TO HEADQUARTERS
AND GOT A CONFIRMATION.
ABOUT THE CALLER?
YEAH.
ANOTHER WOMAN WAS KILLED
LAST NIGHT.
THE CORONER'S
MAKING AN AUTOPSY NOW,
BUT THE CALLER PROBABLY KILLED
HER THE WAY HE DESCRIBED.
CYANIDE POISONING THIS TIME.
THE STUFF'S
EASY ENOUGH TO GET,
AND YOU CAN MIX IT
WITH ANYTHING.
YOU'D NEVER KNOW.
EXCEPT THAT IT SMELLS
LIKE BURNT ALMONDS.
JESUS.
THAT'S TWO IN A ROW.
LOOKS LIKE YOU GOT YOURSELVES
A GENUINE SERIAL KILLER
CALLING IN TO YOUR SHOW.
WE GOT TO GET DOWNTOWN.
YOU READY?
YEAH.
THANKS, GUYS.
Wilkinson: YOU TRIED.
WE'LL KEEP MONITORING.
THIS GUY'S REALLY
KILLING PEOPLE.
I HAD NO IDEA THAT IT WOULD
GO THIS FAR, MAN.
YOU'RE IN ON THIS,
AREN'T YOU?
WHO THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
THIS IS A TOTAL FUCKING
SURPRISE TO ME, JON.
LOOK, I KNEW EDDIE
WAS WHACKED,
BUT NEVER LIKE THIS.
THIS SCARES ME.
I GOT TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
EDDIE OWED ME A FAVOR.
I SAVED HIS ASS
FROM A LOAN SHARK ONCE,
BUT I HAD NO IDEA THIS ASSHOLE
MIGHT BE KILLING WOMEN.
WELL, THAT'S IT.
I'M TELLING THE COPS.
YOU CAN'T.
EDDIE MIGHT KILL US IF HE
THINKS WE WENT TO THE COPS.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
LET HIM KEEP KILLING WOMEN?
JON...
YOU LET ME HANDLE THIS
MY OWN WAY, YOU UNDERSTAND?
COPS ARE FUCKING IDIOTS.
THEY WOULDN'T BE COPS.
YOU DON'T TELL THEM NOTHING.
NOW, I'LL GO TO EDDIE.
I'LL GET HIM TO STOP.
YOU LET ME DO IT
MY OWN WAY.
HEY.
TOUGH DAY, HUH?
YEAH.
IT'S ALWAYS DARKEST
BEFORE THE DAWN.
THAT'S WHAT I ALWAYS SAY.
JESUS, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
HE KILLED HER.
THIS BASTARD'S FOLLOWING ME.
CAN I SPEAK WITH
DETECTIVE WILKINSON, PLEASE?
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
YOU'VE GOT A CALL
ON LINE THREE.
I CAN'T TAKE IT.
HE SAYS IT'S IMPORTANT.
TAKE A MESSAGE.
HE SAID TO TELL YOU
EDDIE'S ON THE PHONE.
WHICH LINE?
THREE.
HELLO?
I finally get to
speak to you in person.
Hello?
YEAH, I'M HERE.
I really liked talking
to you on the radio.
It made me feel better.
I left a little souvenir
in your apartment.
Remember Cynthia?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
If I were you, I'd go home
before the police do.
They might
get the wrong idea
when they find Cynthia's
wallet and clothing
not so well hidden
in your bedroom.
[ CLICK ]
[ SIREN ]
[ HELICOPTER WHIRRING ]
SIR, WE JUST BAGGED THIS.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
TAKE A LOOK.
BETSY, IT'S JON.
WHERE'S KARLIN?
I GOT TO TALK TO HIM.
I don't know.
WE'VE BEEN TRYING TO
GET AHOLD OF HIM.
Ah, Christ.
THE COPS WERE HERE.
THERE'S A WARRANT OUT
FOR YOUR ARREST.
I don't understand
what's going on here, Jon.
I'M BEING FRAMED
FOR A MURDER.
WELL, YOU'RE
IN A PILE OF SHIT.
THANKS. I KNOW.
I'VE GOT TO GO.
Wait, hold on, Jon.
[ DING DONG ]
KARLIN!
EDDIE.
EDDIE, EDDIE, EDDIE,
WHERE ARE YOU?
HERE YOU ARE.
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
ENGINEERING.
Roger.
JON,
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
EVERYBODY'S LOOKING
FOR YOU.
ROGER, I WANT YOU
TO DO ME A FAVOR.
SURE,
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
I WANT YOU
TO TAKE AN ADDRESS
THAT'S NEAR THE STATION.
I want you to meet me
at that gas station.
I need you to bring
a few things.
WHAT KIND OF THINGS?
EDDIE?
JON?
KARLIN.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I CAME TO HAVE A LITTLE
CONVERSATION WITH EDDIE.
I WANTED TO FIND OUT
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON.
YEAH. I GUESS WE BOTH
HAVE SOMETHING
TO TALK TO HIM ABOUT.
IS THAT MY GUN?
YEAH.
YOU GOT BALLS, JON.
I DON'T HAVE
MUCH OF A CHOICE.
YOU KNOW EDDIE KILLED
ANOTHER WOMAN LAST NIGHT?
CYNTHIA.
THE WOMAN
FROM THE NIGHTCLUB
THAT WANTED
TO GO HOME WITH YOU?
YEP. HE PLANTED HER CLOTHING
AND HER WALLET IN MY HOUSE.
THE POLICE
THINK I KILLED HER.
THERE'S A WARRANT
OUR FOR MY ARREST.
EDDIE. GODDAMN IT.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO TAKE HIM TO THE COPS.
YEAH, WE DO.
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE HE IS.
WHILE WE'RE WAITING,
DO YOU WANT A DRINK?
SURE.
WHAT HAS HE GOT?
LET ME LOOK.
HE'S GOT SOME BOURBON,
OKAY?
YEAH. WHATEVER.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE YOU GO,
LITTLE BROTHER.
DOES HE HAVE ANY ICE?
WHY DON'T YOU GO LOOK?
IT'S A WILD PLACE, HUH?
HE'S BEEN A SQUATTER HERE
EVER SINCE I MET HIM.
I'M REALLY GLAD
YOU'RE HERE, JON.
OH, YEAH?
ACTUALLY, I THOUGHT
YOU MIGHT BE KIND OF PISSED.
PLEASE.
DRINK OKAY?
YEAH.
BY THE WAY,
THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANT TO CONFESS TO YOU.
THAT IS THAT, UH,
THERE IS NO EDDIE.
I MEAN...
I'M EDDIE.
SEE,
WITH THIS EQUIPMENT HERE,
THIS IS A SOUND PROCESSOR
AND A SYNTHESIZER.
I CHANGE THE MAKEUP
OF MY VOICE.
I BECAME EDDIE.
OH, MY GOD.
YEAH. I GOT ALL
THE REGULAR SUPPLIES.
SEE, HERE'S THE SCRAMBLER,
FOR THROWING OFF
THE POLICE TRACING DEVICES,
AND A DIALING MECHANISM.
I PRERECORDED EDDIE'S VOICE
ON THIS TAPE MACHINE,
AND I SENT IT TO OUR SHOW
BY WAY OF THIS AUTOMATIC TIMER.
ALL I HAD TO DO
WAS STICK TO A SCRIPT.
I MADE IT SOUND
REAL AUTHENTIC,
EVEN FOOLED YOU,
LITTLE BROTHER.
OH. AH.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, JON?
I FEEL A LITTLE DIZZY.
VIVIAN AND CYNTHIA --
GOD, THEY WERE HOT,
ESPECIALLY VIVIAN.
I KILLED THEM BOTH,
YOU KNOW.
[ RETCHING NOISES ]
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO KILL VIVIAN.
WE WERE GETTING IT ON
ONE NIGHT ON THE RAILING
OF THIS FIRE ESCAPE.
OH, GOD. SHE WAS SWEET.
ANYWAY,
WE JUST GOTTEN THROUGH
AND SHE STARTS
TO MEALY-MOUTH ALL THIS,
"I WANT TO SEE
YOU AGAIN,"
YOU KNOW,
RELATIONSHIP JARGON.
I SUPPOSE SHE DIDN'T LIKE
MY RESPONSE
BECAUSE SHE GOES
TO SLAP ME, I STEP BACK,
THE BITCH GOES OVER
THE SIDE OF THE FIRE ESCAPE
AND FALLS SEVEN STORIES
TO THE CONCRETE. SMACK.
IT FREAKED ME OUT,
BUT THAT'S
WHEN I DECIDED
I WOULD USE HER DEATH
TO HELP ME.
I WOULD INVENT A KILLER
WHO WOULD CALL INTO OUR SHOW
AND CONFESS TO THE MURDER.
IT WAS
A GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY.
WHY CYNTHIA?
WHY DID YOU KILL HER?
OUR AUDIENCE DEMANDED IT,
THAT'S WHY.
THEY WANTED
A SERIAL KILLER.
SO I GAVE THEM ONE.
I EVEN GAVE THEM A DEAD
WOMAN HE COULD CALL IN
AND CLAIM TO HAVE KILLED,
BUT THAT WASN'T ENOUGH.
[ RETCHING NOISES ]
DO YOU KNOW THAT OUR RATINGS
WERE AT THEIR HIGHEST
AFTER THAT FIRST CALL
FROM EDDIE?
A 42 SHARE.
BUT ONE WEEK LATER
THEY WERE FALLING OFF.
ALL OUR NUMBERS WERE BAD.
SO THE PEOPLE WANTED MORE,
MORE DEATH.
SO I GAVE IT TO THEM.
I GAVE IT TO THEM,
AND FRANKLY, JON,
KILLING SOMEONE
ISN'T AS HARD AS
IT'S CRACKED UP TO BE,
ESPECIALLY IF IT'S
A GOOD CAREER MOVE.
YOU BASTARD. YOU POISONED ME,
TOO, DIDN'T YOU?
YEAH. JON, THEY'RE GOING
TO FIND YOU HERE DEAD,
AND BECAUSE THE EVIDENCE
I PLANTED AT YOUR HOUSE --
CYNTHIA'S DRESS
AND HER WALLET --
AND BECAUSE OF
ALL THIS EQUIPMENT,
THEY'RE GOING TO THINK
YOU WERE EDDIE.
YOU KILLED CYNTHIA.
NICE AND NEAT, HUH?
AND YOU COMMITTED SUICIDE
BECAUSE YOU JUST COULDN'T
LIVE WITH YOURSELF ANY LONGER.
SO CYANIDE POISONING --
VERY SAD, BUT VERY POETIC.
VICTIMIZER DIES
THE SAME WAY
AS ONE
OF HIS VICTIMS.
THE REAL BEAUTY OF IT IS,
COUPLE DAYS
AFTER YOU'RE DEAD,
I CAN GO BACK AND HAVE
THE MOST TALKED ABOUT
RADIO SHOW
IN THE COUNTRY
ALL TO MYSELF.
I'LL BECOME
A MEDIA KING.
EVEN OPRAH WILL WANT
TO DO A SPECIAL ON ME.
HIS CO-WORKER
WAS A HOMICIDAL MANIAC.
SO YOU JUST HAVE BEEN
USING ME ALL THE TIME.
OH, YEAH. I HAD
IT FIGURED OUT MONTHS AGO
AND YOU WERE JUST
THE RIGHT SUCKER
AT THE RIGHT PLACE
AT THE RIGHT TIME.
I'M SORRY, JON,
BUT I TOLD YOU
I HAD BIG PLANS,
AND NONE OF THEM
INCLUDED YOU.
YOU ARE SUCH
A BASTARD, KARLIN.
YOU MANIPULATED ME
INTO DOING ONE SICK THING
AFTER ANOTHER
UNTIL MY LIFE WAS A WRECK.
YOU DIDN'T DRINK
YOUR BOURBON.
I DIDN'T DRINK
THE BOURBON, KARLIN.
I SMELLED CYANIDE
IN THE BOURBON.
COPS TOLD ME CYANIDE
SMELLS LIKE BURNT ALMONDS.
SO I SWITCHED THE BOURBON
FOR SOME COLA AND WATER
IN THE KITCHEN.
EVEN YOU WERE FOOLED,
LITTLE BROTHER.
SO WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO?
YOU GOING
TO SHOOT ME?
YOU SHOULD HAVE
SHOT ME, JON.
YOU'RE IN SOME
VERY DEEP SHIT NOW.
NO, I'M NOT.
NO ONE CAN TIE ME
INTO ANY OF THIS.
OH, YEAH?
I'M WIRED, KARLIN.
I'M WIRED,
YOU SON OF A BITCH.
THIS PHONE IS BEING
PIPED INTO THE STATION,
AND THEY'RE USING
THEIR 55,000 WATTS OF POWER
TO SPREAD IT TO
EVERY SINGLE CORNER OF TOWN.
THE WHOLE CITY'S
BEEN LISTENING TO YOU.
EVERYTHING YOU'VE BEEN
TELLING ME IS GOING OUT
ON POWER 98.
THAT'S RIGHT, KARLIN.
AREN'T YOU
THE ONE THAT SAID
THERE'S A WHOLE CITY
OF PERVERSION OUT THERE
FULL OF PEOPLE
WHO AREN'T AFRAID
TO TAP INTO
THE DARK SIDE OF THEMSELVES?
OR MAYBE YOU WERE JUST
TALKING ABOUT YOURSELF.
HEY, CAN YOU
BELIEVE THIS STUFF?
TELL ME SOMETHING, KARLIN.
HOW DOES IT FEEL KNOWING
YOU JUST EXPOSED YOURSELF
TO A MILLION PEOPLE?
JESUS.
THEY HAVE GUNS?
QUIET.
CONFESSING IS GOOD
FOR THE SOUL, ISN'T IT, KARLIN?
AND JUST THINK WHAT OUR
NUMBERS WILL BE LIKE TOMORROW.
Detective:
OPEN UP. POLICE!
Detective #2:
THE POLICE! OPEN UP.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
LOOKS LIKE EVERYONE
IS LISTENING
TO THE RADIO TONIGHT.
Detective: WE KNOW
YOU'RE IN THERE!
JON...
DON'T SHOOT ME.
Detective:
OPEN UP, KARLIN!
IT'S MY PLEASURE
TO FUCK YOU OVER.
DON'T MOVE!
Detective #2:
PUT IT DOWN.
FREEZE!
PUT THE GUN DOWN,
KARLIN.
Jon: OW.
AH.
OH, JESUS.
GUN.
WHOA. WHOA.
Paramedic: WATCH YOUR BACKS.
WE'RE COMING THROUGH HERE.
Man #2: WE RAN IN THE SECOND
WE HEARD YOU GUYS ON THE AIR.
YOU DID GOOD, KID,
BUT THANK GOD
WE WERE FOLLOWING KARLIN.
IT KEPT US NEARBY.
SO I THINK HARRISON FORD
OUGHT TO PLAY YOU
IN THE MOVIE
VERSION OF ALL THIS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YEAH.
GET HIM OUT OF HERE.
Woman: MORE COFFEE?
SO YOU HAVEN'T TALKED
TO SHARON YET?
NOPE.
I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT GOING OVER TO HER PLACE,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
HOW SHE'D REACT.
MAYBE IF YOU APOLOGIZE...
GROVEL.
IF YOU GET
ON YOUR HANDS AND KNEES
AND BEG FOR HER FORGIVENESS
LIKE A DOG,
MAYBE SHE'LL COME AROUND.
I MEAN,
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT TO LOSE?
YEAH.
NO, NO. IT'S ON ME.
YOU EARNED IT.
HEY, THANKS.
YOU KNOW, IT'S
JUST NOT THE SAME ANYMORE
WITHOUT YOU
AT THE STATION.
YEAH. WELL, THANKS, ROGER,
BUT I THINK I NEED A BREAK
FROM RADIO FOR A WHILE.
YEAH.
DON'T BLAME YOU.
HEY, GOOD LUCK.
TAKE IT EASY.
HI.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
HOW'S YOUR HAND?
DOCTOR SAYS IT'LL BE FINE
IN A COUPLE WEEKS.
SO HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
GOOD.
I HAVE CALLS TO MAKE.
SHARON, LOOK.
I'M SORRY.
I KNOW WHAT I DID
WAS WRONG,
YOU KNOW, AND...
IT WAS LIKE
I WAS POSSESSED.
NO ONE FORCED YOU
TO DO ANYTHING.
YEAH, I KNOW.
YOU'RE RIGHT, SHARON.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
YOU KNOW, NO ONE FORCED ME.
I WANTED
ALL THE WRONG THINGS --
THINGS THAT IN THE END
DIDN'T WIND UP
MEANING ANYTHING.
YOU DO.
THIS ISN'T GOING TO BE
EASY FOR ME.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I CAN'T PROMISE YOU
ANYTHING.
WE'LL TAKE IT
ONE DAY AT A TIME, OKAY?
ONE DAY AT A TIME.
WANT TO GRAB A BITE?
YEAH.
HI, LOS ANGELES, IT'S ME,
CHUCK GELSON,
ON THE BRAND-NEW POWER 98,
AND I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT ON MY ALL-NEW AFTERNOON
DRIVE-TIME SHOW
THERE WILL BE
NO FORBIDDEN TOPICS.
SO GET READY TO RID YOURSELF
OF HANG-UPS.
GET READY TO BE SET FREE.
SO DON'T BE SCARED.
DON'T BE SHY.
WHAT DO YOU SAY,
CALLER NUMBER ONE?
YOU ARE ON THE AIR.
♪ IN THE SEA OF YOUR HEART
I WAS SWIMMING ♪
♪ YOUR BLUE SOUL
I COULDN'T KICK ♪
♪ GOING UNDER ♪
♪ THAT WAS EASY ♪
♪ BUT COMING UP ♪
♪ NOW THAT'S THE REAL TRICK ♪
♪ OH, I ♪
♪ I BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ IN EVERY SINGLE LITTLE KISS ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ I NEED YOU ♪
♪ WHENEVER I'M DOWN LIKE THIS ♪
♪ COME ON, MAKE ME SMILE
MAKE ME LAUGH ♪
♪ MAKE ME HAPPY ♪
♪ MAKE ME YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ COME SWALLOW ME ♪
♪ LET ME DROWN
WANT TO GO DOWN ♪
♪ WANT TO GO DOWN ♪
♪ IN YOUR SEA OF LOVE ♪
♪ WELL, I LAID IN YOUR MUD
AND YOUR KISSES ♪
♪ AND I'M FOLLOWING
YOUR EVERY MOVE ♪
♪ AND I'M DRIFTING
INTO YOUR DEEPNESS ♪
♪ WITH NOTHING ♪
♪ LEFT TO LOSE ♪
♪ OH, I ♪
♪ I BELIEVE ♪
♪ IN EVERY SINGLE LITTLE KISS ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ I BLEED ♪
♪ WHENEVER I'M DROWNED
LIKE THIS ♪
♪ OH, OH ♪
♪ MAKE ME SMILE
MAKE ME LAUGH ♪
♪ MAKE ME HAPPY ♪
♪ MAKE ME YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ OH, I WANT TO LIVE ♪
♪ I WANT TO DROWN ♪
♪ LET ME GO DOWN ♪
♪ IN YOUR SEA OF LOVE ♪
♪ YEAH, OH ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH ♪
-- CAPTIONS BY VITAC --
BURBANK, PITTSBURGH, WASHINGTON
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
WARNER BROS. INC.