I just don't think I can
give you that promotion.
It's because of
my guts isn't it?
Here at Derbish and
Browns we're looking
for someone with that drive
to succeed deep down inside.
Or outside is fine too so.
Is there anything I can do? I'm
gushing with ideas. I have umm.
Let's see how the day goes.
Final decision won't be until five o'clock
so if you'll just excuse me.
Yes you're excused sorry.
Shelly, can you bring in some cleaner please?
Horace was here.
Yeah, the guts guy.
There he is. How'd it go?
Terrible. Because
I didn't get it.
That's bull!
Hey you guys need to be quiet, people are
trying to add and subtract numbers in here.
You know what Janet is so nice.
She really is.
Yeah she's the best.
Maybe she's thirsty.
Dude great point.
I'll be right back. Hold
down the fort. You got this.
Hey Janet I thought you might be thirsty from
all that number crunching you were doing.
God I'm so so so
sorry. I am so sorry here.
Just kind of rub that around so you want
to form a base and then just sort of go
counterclockwise. We're
going to need some soap.
Who's got soap?!
Why can't you just be normal?
What's going on out here?
Janet spilled water.
So yeah I came in with that
tre, swish. Beat the buzzer man.
Won the game, best
moment of my life.
Aww I was awarded best
whitler in the eighth grade.
Shh.
What the hell is
wrong with this guy?
Do I have something on my face?
That's Horace, don't look directly
at the guts. This is Brody.
Yeah he's super cool and
smells way better than you so.
I can smell him from here.
I don't know if you know this
or not but that's disgusting.
You look like a used band-aid.
You look like a prince.
Why don't you just put
a shirt over that bro?
That's a great idea, which is
why I'm glad I had it, but um
you know the blood soaks through the
fabric and it ruins all my clothes
so what I had to do was cut holes
in my shirt. I cut my ties too.
Watch out!
Is that pee?
He said watch out man.
Yeah that's pee.
Pee pee bro.
Nobody does that to me.
Hey blood brothers man.
I'm sorry okay.
Sorry not gonna cut it bro.
I'm gonna fight you.
After work.
Five o'clock.
In the parking lot.
You're dead.
Wait hey wait I don't
know how to fight.
Wait which parking lot?
There's like three parking lots.
Brody which parking
Hey
Thought you'd be
long gone by now.
No I can't leave until
five. Have you seen him?
Yeah he's right over there.
This is our boy Brody,
Brody this is our boy Janet.
Nice to meet you.
Janet actually likes him?
Maybe he's not that
strong and you can take him.
I really feel like
we're crushing it.
Well
Maybe he's forgotten about it.
Did he just come up with
that dance move right now?
Yeah.
Check these out.
Got them at the state
fair when I was 12.
I'll give you 50 bucks if you
hit him hard enough to hurt him...
...but you know
don't like kill him.
Or.
No don't.
I'll do it for free.
- Hey don't mess with my friend!
- Yeah.
Damn Ronald.
Plastic?
What is going on out here now?
He clocked me so I
clocked him back sir.
I like you.
Have you ever thought
about upper management?
Horace, get back to work.
Whoa that's weird.
Who who put that there?
It was you dipshit.
Thank you.
Janet.
See ya.
Hey Brody.
It's not even five
o'clock yet bro.
Look at me I'm just like you now all my
guts are on the inside. Let's do this bro
Sike.
That's it. You are dead!
Stop!
We need to get back
to number crunching.
No guts, no glo.
Don't you choke cause
I want to kill you myself.
What the hell is
going on out here?
Mr. Browns, I want
that promotion.
I'll give you one thing kid,
you've got