I got you, Sensei. Stay with me.
You're a life saver, Casey Jones.
I learned from the best.
Come on, we're almost there.
Bad doggies!
Impeccable timing, little brother.
Very dramatic.
Help him, Michelangelo. He's hurt bad.
That's it. The resistance failed.
The Krang won.
But... but it isn't over.
We've still got a ninja's
greatest weapon...
hope.
That and a badass mystic warrior.
Mikey, we need a time gateway.
It'll take everything I have.
I know, but this is our last chance.
It's our only chance.
Hm.
- Wait, what's going on? Where is he going?
- Casey, listen.
The Krang first came to our planet
through a mystic doorway.
The key that opened the doorway
looked like this.
Why are you telling me this?
Because Mikey's
about to send you back in time
to the day that the key was stolen.
Wait, he's gonna what?
The people who stole that key
opened the doorway for the Krang.
You have to find it before that happens.
Find the key, stop the Krang.
- But, Sensei...
- Say it!
"Find the key, stop the Krang."
I don't want to lose you.
Casey, it's not about me.
They found us!
Mikey!
Master Michelangelo, no! You're gonna...
Casey...
when you're done saving the world,
do me a favor.
Grab a slice!
Huh?
Where...
I made it?
All right, Casey, here we go.
Find the key, stop the Krang.
♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles ♪
Easy does it, Leo.
You've got this.
Concentrate.
The whole world is counting on you...
to break the pizza box stack record!
One-hundred, twenty-five boxes!
They say it couldn't be done,
but look who's doing it, moi.
That's Spanish for Leo.
Go ahead, my non-lingual friend,
count your unhatched fowl.
My record stands until you reach the top,
which, according to
my calculations of wind speed,
barometric pressure, and dew point,
is highly unlikely. What?
According to my calculations,
as long as you believe in yourself,
you can do anything!
Thanks, little brother.
No one believes in himself more than me.
Leo!
Leo! Leo! Leo! Leo! Leo!
- Yeah! I am Leo!
- Yeah, baby!
There you are.
I've been looking all over for you guys.
Raph, guess who just broke the record?
What? You did? How many did you...
Stop distracting Raph!
We were supposed to be training...
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta. Hold that thought.
Donnie?
You, sir, have bested me.Mazel.
- Ahem?
Leo. Leo.
Leo! Leo!
Stop it!
Leo, we have work to do,
and you dragged him out here for this?
Training, record-breaking.
The choice was clear.
Dang it, Leo.
Everything's not about you.
When are you gonna grow up
and start acting like a hero?
And there it is. Gentlemen...
- What was that? What are you guys doing?
- A little game I invented.
Every time you say "heroes,"
we take a bite of pizza.
I don't say "heroes" that often!
Leo!
So what if I say he... that word a lot.
It's a good word. We need to be that word.
Relax, Raph.
We've got this hero thing wired.
I mean, our ninjocity is off the charts.
We've got some kickin' mystic weapons.
And do I need to remind you who has
four shells and defeated the Shredder?
- Hey.
- Leo!
You just don't get it.
Huh? What is all that... That's me.
Looks like we have a 317-39.4 in progress!
Uh-huh?
Oh, come on!
Has nobody read Donnie's Big Book
of Bad Guy Codes? Nobody?
- Nope.
- Never gonna happen.
We did it!
We got the whatcha-ma-hoosie-doodle!
Of course we did.
Nothing can stop Supervillain Warren Stone
and his conjuring compatriot,
Hypno-Potamus!
There they are! Okay, here's the plan...
Raph, relax. Who needs a plan
when we got crazy cool mystic powers?
Leo!
Come on, swords, it's portal time!
I'll see you guys later
after I save the day! Buh-buh-bye!
Stop! We need to work together!
Wellington Sunday!
It's those pesky Turtles.
License and registration.
Oh, I'm sorry, mate.
I must have left it in my other jacket.
Leo! Ah!
Leo, we're coming.
- Don't worry.
- I got 'em right where I want 'em.
Doesn't look that way to me.
Donnie, Mikey, Maneuver 12.
- On it!
- Ha!
Whip-o-rama!
Prepare to be Donnie'd by my mystic tech!
Oh boy.
Okay, creeps, hand over the stolen thingy!
Oh no.
That's gotta be what they stole!
I got it!
With those clumsy hands?
No, I got this one.
Oh, you portal-chopped him!
"Portal-chopped," I like it.
Maybe my new catchphrase?
Okay, let's see how it fits.
"You've been portal chopped!"
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
I'll be taking this.
The Foot Clan?
Finally, after all these centuries,
this is ours.
Yes, well, of course, thanks to us,
delivered safe and sound.
No problemo, partner.
Hey, just quietly, are we partners?
We are partners, yeah?
Oh man, that thing must be dangerous
if the Foot Clan wants it.
Ya think?
Huh? What?
I clearly said, "I got it."
Everybody heard me say, "I got it."
Yeah, but I got it with style.
But you didn't get it!
You lost it, and now
we've got a Foot Clan situation, Leo.
Huh?
What's it gonna take
for you to be serious, Leo?
And end up with a worry line
between my eyes like you?
No, no, no, I do not want a Raph chasm.
"Chasm"?
You know, valley, gorge, crevasse.
The only reason I have a chasm
is I have to worry about you bozos 24/7.
You just don't get it, Leo.
I'm the oldest here.
I'm responsible for keeping us safe
and making sure we can
handle anything that comes our way.
'Cause if I don't,
you could all end up dead.
Sorry, I missed that.
Can you repeat everything from...
well, everything?
No wonder you always want to train.
You really need the practice.
Let him go, Mikey.
Wait! No!
Boys! Stop this arguing!
But, Dad, Leo keeps...
Buh-buh-buh-buh, buh.
No more.
You are a team. You are brothers.
And most importantly, you are too loud!
I cannot hear my TV show!
Tristan finally proposed to Annabelle,
but did she say yes?
I don't know because of you!
Be the ninjas I taught you to be,
respectful and quiet!
Sorry. Excuse me.
Hey, how am I supposed to find this thing?
Whoa.
So many people.
How am I gonna save them all, Sensei?
I really wish you were here.
Wait, you are!
I just need to find you.
April.
She'll know.
Huh?
Hi, professor. Do you have a sec?
Hmm.
Are you even in this class?
I'm April O'Neil, journalism major.
I write for the
Eastlaird University Daily News.
Maybe I could get some shots of you
at the whiteboard for a story?
Oh! Of course.
So, uh, what... what should I do?
You know, just write something sciencey.
I actually have the perfect equation
for your article.
Now a few where you're
staring thoughtfully at your work.
Oh, I always stare intently
at my equations.
Especially this one.
You know,
I think I should put on my lab coat.
- Look at it!
- Oh! Okay.
You know, I could probably
stare at this equation all day.
This is April O'Neil, investigative
reporter, Eastlaird University Daily News.
For years, this college shot down
rumors that a foreign government
is paying them millions
to develop a super-toxic
herbicidal deforestation bomb.
Those rumors end today because
I'm about to blow the lid off Big Chem.
April O'Neil.
Ooh. This stuff looks nasty.
Hey! Who's there?
Hm?
Evidence, baby.
Oh boy.
Well, it's a good thing video
ain't the only thing I took.
April! Yes!
- Commander O'Neil...
- Catlike reflex!
What's the matter with you,
creeping up on a person in the dark?
What the...
And then I saw that picture
and I brought him here.
Sensei?
Hm?
It's you!
It's all of you! Together!
- I never thought I'd see you again!
- I'm so happy I could hug you!
Who are you,
and why do you have a picture of us?
Yeah, who took this? 'Cause I look great.
What's your favorite pizza?
'Cause I'm ordering right now.
And why are you
wearing genius-built apparel?
That's trademarked!
Grappling hook!
What's going on?
He's trying to escape!
- Want me to knock him out again?
- Let me.
Donnie? Donnie!
Oh, okay.
Wa... Wait, stop!
I'm a friend. Let me explain.
Let's start over.
My name is Casey Jones,
and the reason I have this photo
and your tech
is because you gave it to me,
but not yet, because I'm from...
the future!
This isn't a joke.
Please, if time travel is possible,
future Donnie would have come back
and already given me
all the lottery numbers like we planned.
It's true. I need you to believe me.
Humanity depends on it.
In the future,
an alien race decimated the planet.
We were hunted. We lived in caves.
We ate leaves and rats.
No offense.
None taken. We are delicious.
I know how this sounds,
but Master Leonardo gave me a mission.
I do like how he calls me "Master."
Of course I do.
You are the greatest ninja
the world has ever seen.
You told me to find the key
and stop the Krang.
"Aliens." Pfft.
Sure.
This story just keeps getting better.
Splints?
"The Krang"?
I have heard that name.
Powerful, barbaric creatures
worshiped by the Foot Clan.
Legend says they came from the stars.
Ruthless, unmerciful, with one desire,
to enslave our world
like so many before us.
All seemed lost,
until great mystic warriors
forged a mighty weapon,
a key that was used to lock them
in a prison dimension beyond this realm.
Over the centuries,
the mystic key remained hidden
to protect humankind
and prevent the return of the Krang.
So...
Future boy is really from the future?
Mind...
Someone finds the key! Today!
They steal it and use it
to open a doorway and free the Krang!
That's why I came back, to find it first.
Master Leonardo drew a picture
on the back of that photo.
So to stop the Krang,
all we have to do
is find the key before it's stolen.
- Mm.
- Hm-mm.
Huh.
What?
Yeah, did future handsome,
amazing me tell you what to do
in case that already happened?
'Cause that already happened.
Mm!
Oh no, we're too late!
No, we're not.
'Cause we know who has the key,
the Foot Clan.
Okay, we gotta find them
before they use it,
and this time, we do it together!
Uh, can someone untie me now?
Oh no...
Villain to villain,
your hideout is a bit... lacking.
Might I suggest some velvet, a fireplace,
maybe a fuzzy white cat
with a diamond necklace?
Tonight, we liberate our masters
from their dimensional prison.
With this key,
we shall free them to lay waste
to this world and enslave its people.
Ah, I thought we were just gonna rob
a bank and be, you know, crime buddies.
We shall follow the Krang
as they lead the Foot Clan to glory!
Bored.
You!
- Leo!
- What?
I was waiting for a good spot to jump in,
but they just kept blabbity-blab-ing.
There it is! That's the key.
Get them! Don't let them
interfere with the ceremony!
No!
It started!
He's unlocking the doorway!
We need to get up there right now!
Casey, go. We've got you covered.
Oh no.
Oh.
Oh no! They're here!
Then let's make sure
their visit's short and sweet.
I'm finally free!
The people of this planet
will pay for what they've done to me.
Welcome to Earth.
I hope you don't enjoy your stay!
Oh!
Enough tricks!
Mikey! Donnie! No!
No...
Raph, what happened to our powers?
They... They're gone.
What did they do to us?
Brother, sister, join me.
Time for us to finish remaking
this universe in the image of Krang.
How I've waited for this day.
Indeed.
Brother, widen the portal
and retrieve our ship, the Technodrome.
Once it is here,
this world will kneel before us.
Oh, if you two don't mind,
I haven't killed anything in ages.
No!
Huh?
Retreat!
Retreat? We don't retreat!
Leo, for once, listen to me.
They're too powerful and Dad's hurt.
You don't understand.
If we don't close that doorway,
it's only gonna get worse.
Raph?
I'm not gonna argue with you, Leo!
Donnie, escape pods, now!
You don't have to tell me twice!
Sensei, we need to get that key!
Leo!
Huh?
Raph?
Raph, wait, no.
Wait, Raph! Raph! No, Raph!
Raph! No, Raph!
Escape pods incoming.
Congratulations
on surviving, fam.
Huh?
Oh, I hate that.
Everyone okay? Anybody hurt?
How did we get here?
Donnie pods.
We've never had to use those before.
So, how would everyone
rate their escape experience?
"Very satisfied," "Very, very satisfied,"
"Extremely satisfied"?
- Donnie!
- Sorry. Sorry.
Data collection calms me down.
Splints.
This is terrible! Why did we leave?
In case you didn't notice,
we were getting our butts kicked!
But my mission was to stop them!
Now, the Krang are using that key
to bring in something
that will destroy the world.
We lost.
Oof.
- Where's my other pod?
- Where's Raph?
Ah, did you know this would happen?
Why didn't you tell me?
- What are you talking about?
- Easy!
- Leo, what's going on? Where's Raph?
- Leo, what happened to Raph?
Leonardo?
They...
They got him.
You left Raph?
He left himself.
He used his pod to save me, all because
I went after this stupid thing.
You got it! Nice.
"Nice"? They captured Raph!
He's from the future!
He knew this would happen!
No, I didn't.
This didn't happen in my time.
We changed the past, and you got the key.
That means there's
still a chance to stop them.
- No, we have to save Raph. Come on.
- Leo, wait.
If you won't come, I'll go myself.
- We've lost our mystic powers.
- We don't have a plan!
We don't need a plan.
"I'm the greatest ninja
the world's ever seen," his words.
Shouldn't we talk about this
before we run off all half-cocked,
willy-nilly, pell-mell?
I keep being told
I'm doing this hero thing wrong.
But I got the key, didn't I?
I get results,
so now we're doing it my way.
My son, listen to your team.
This is not about you.
They made it about me
when they took my brother.
Trust me, I got this.
Donnie, you're driving.
What do we do with this?
We can't just bring it with us,
but we can't just leave it behind.
Then we should destroy it.
Splints and I will stay here
and take care of business.
Mm-hmm.
Thanks, Commander O'Neil.
"Commander"? I like the sound of that.
Oh, look at it.
Disgusting.
Try looking in a mirror.
Ugh, it's talking at me.
I'm going to rip out its tongue.
Forgive my sister.
She's got a bit of a temper.
And being in prison for a thousand years
hasn't done her any favors.
You're not human.
What are you?
Let me go, and I'll show you.
Hmm.
You're more powerful
than the people of this planet,
yet you defend them.
- Why?
- It's my duty.
A word used by the weak.
Many planets before yours
have spoken of duty.
They too have been consumed by the Krang.
And now our glorious crusade continues
to restore the natural order of things.
The strong will devour the weak.
Last I checked,
we weren't the ones locked in a
prison dimension for a thousand years.
That's called "trash talk."
A rare misstep.
Once I retrieve the key
from your comrades,
I will bring forth the mighty Technodrome,
and you will witness
the true power of the Krang.
Now, where have they taken my key?
It won't tell you anything.
Let me kill it.
Lady brain face here is right.
I'm not telling you jack.
You don't have to tell me.
I'll look myself.
There it is.
They always do it the hard way.
Our brother and I will secure
a location for the dimensional doorway.
Take these soldiers
and retrieve me my key.
We live to serve.
You will serve me whether you live or not.
What is this thing?
Hold on to your gluteus maximi!
The Turtle Tank, baby!
It's how we roll in the past.
I mean, the present. I mean...
- Ugh! Time travel's confusing.
- They're on the move.
According to the subcutaneous tracker
I put on Raph...
Wait, does that mean
you put trackers on all of us?
"No"?
No, of course I did... n't.
Based on their trajectory,
they're headed...
...to the tallest building in the city.
That's right, Metro Tower.
I heard the story so many times as a kid,
but I never thought...
"And behold,
from their perch atop New York City,
the Krang ripped open the sky itself."
"What came out was terror,
and what rained down upon us
was worse than death."
They told that to kids?
Man, the future is harsh.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
We need to get into Metro Tower
without being spotted.
We'll take the subway tunnels.
Subway tunnels don't offer much
in the way of an escape if we need it.
- Are you sure about this?
- Yeah, maybe we should...
Guys, we're doing it my way. Remember?
Hm?
Prepare the site so we may
bring forth the Technodrome.
Yes, brother.
See? Smooth sailing.
We'll have Raph in no time.
I hope he's okay.
How are we gonna find him
once we get there?
I have a lot of questions
regarding "once we get there."
Relax. We'll do what we always do.
Ninja in, ninja their faces, ninja out.
That's exactly how you freed all those
families from the Krang labor camp.
Yeah, that sounds like me.
In the future,
you guys are beyond amazing.
The mystic powers you're able
to harness are on a whole other level.
Of course! What about my future?
I'm expecting big things for me.
How many Nobel prizes do I have?
Don't tell me. I wanna be surprised.
Donnie, you were the most brilliant,
innovative mind of all time.
I'm shocked, I am.
Go on, continue to meet my expectations.
What do I do in the future?
You are the most powerful mystic warrior
the world has ever known.
With those two hands,
you sent me back in time.
Wow!
Actually,
there is something I should tell you.
Auto brake engaged.
Huh.
Wow.
Think we're in the right place?
Looks like the Metro Tower station
is on the other side of those vines.
Great. Let's hoof it.
Through the disgusting,
drippy slime jungle?
I know. I know. Leo knows best,
but I'm not sharing my hand sanitizer.
Feeling a lack of rush
in this rush hour, right?
I don't know, Leo.
Something feels...
off.
Don't worry. I won't let us die.
I'm a mystic warrior.
"I feel better already,"
he said without a hint of sarcasm.
Look, the stairs.
Sneaking in from below was the right move.
Those slimeballs will never see us coming.
We tried to jackhammer it,
flamethrower it, pour acid on it...
I thought lasers cut everything!
How did that not work?
There's not even a scratch!
Maybe it was your aim.
Maybe your big rat head got in the way!
Mmm, I'll show you, fat rat head.
Okay, deep breaths.
You said some things, I said some things.
Maybe we should just
get back to saving the world.
What's next?
Huh?
This cannot be good.
April O'Neil!
Come back here!
Faster.
Faster!
I knew this was a bad idea.
Leo, there's too many. We should go back.
No, we're gonna get to those stairs.
Leo, we're not gonna make it!
We have to turn back.
We push forward, get Raph, that's final.
Mystic hands!
Donnie! Mikey!
Oh no, Donnie, your soft shell!
You're exposed!
We gotta find shelter!
Oh, oh, keep it down, Vomitello!
Oh. Keep it down, daddy!
Run, insects, but you can't escape!
Don't!
The key, human! Give it to me!
Ah!
What did you do to me?
What did you do to my face?
Ha!
I knew that stuff was nasty! I told y'all!
Yes, yes, you're a genius. Let's go.
Ah!
Donnie, come in.
They found us. Where should we go? Donnie?
We're trapped.
We are trapped
in the subway under Metro Tower.
The tank is running on emergency power
and is covered
in some kind of Krang bio-growth.
- I repeat...
- April, come quick!
We're getting squished!
We're on our way!
But, April, how will we get them out?
I've got an idea.
Yeesh.
Remind me to never get on your bad side.
Casey!
Casey, you okay?
Donnie, Mikey, anybody?
Ah!
What the heck was that?
Some kind of drippy, crazy Krang monster.
No, I mean you!
Why weren't you listening to anybody?
Because I was trying to get us
into the building!
That sure worked out well.
I was doing everything right.
How could it go wrong?
Because you weren't
listening to your team!
You don't have
all the answers all the time!
I'm the greatest ninja
the world's ever seen. You said that.
I was wrong.
What?
You're impulsive, you're arrogant,
and you don't see that every decision
you make could cost someone their life.
You want to know what really happens
to your brothers in the future?
They die.
Everybody dies fighting the Krang.
The world needs Master Leonardo.
And all we got is this guy.
We have an update
on the strange situation at Metro Tower.
All contact has been lost
with those inside the building,
and conflicting reports suggest
something is barricading entrance
for emergency personnel.
Fools.
These creatures should
welcome the power of the Krang.
You on the rooftop!
Stop and surrender immediately!
We've got eyes on the roof top
where the police are confronting...
What is that?
You may begin.
Oh look! Okay! Wait!
Look out!
Mmm.
Look,
I know I'm not the Leo you knew
in the future, and maybe I never will be.
This whole time
I was sure my family needed me,
but the truth is I need them.
If we're gonna survive this,
we have to do it together.
Hull integrity, 4%.
Breach imminent. Good luck.
Whew, good.
We have an imminent amount of time.
"Imminent" means "soon," Mikey.
Don't worry.
I'll save us with my mystic hands.
Ah?
Casey must have been wrong about me.
This is it, Donnie.
We're gonna get crushed!
- Knock-knock!
- April?
Anyone order a rescue?
Boom goes the herbicide!
April!
You saved us!
Uncomfortable with emotion!
Where is Leo? And, uh, Future Boy?
Somewhere in there.
Faster! They're this way.
I can smell them.
She found us! We gotta move now.
Oh man,
is this what the future looks like?
Nope, the future is worse. Much worse.
Donnie, Mikey, do you read me?
Come in, Leo.
Donnie, where are you?
We've extracted from the subway
and are ascending a staircase.
I'm getting a lot of interference,
but if you hold still,
I can triangulate your position
using a complex geo-location algorithm.
- Uh, Donnie?
- Odd numbers, primes, no... almost.
Almost!
Ugh. I never get to use my algorithm.
Man, I am so glad you guys aren't dead.
Ditto.
Okay, before this gets too mushy,
we need to locate Raph.
Can you tell me if he's in the building?
Bet your momma's
subatomic particles I can.
Got him! He's close.
He's almost on top of us.
Wait, he is on top of us.
Raph!
Quick, cut him down, get him out of there.
Huh?
Hang on. We got you. Almost there.
Raph?
Ah.
Surprise.
What did you do to my brother?
Improved him.
Thank you for this.
We will be putting it to good use.
Come, the world awaits destruction.
Tear them apart!
We gotta move.
- Leo, move!
- No!
A shame our brethren
didn't survive the prison dimension.
Then again, their weakness
has no place in my new Krang empire.
Open and bring unto this world
the mighty power of Krang!
Warning! This is a warning!
...appears to be something
falling from the sky...
What?
Oh!
Begin!
What do we do now?
I fear we are lost.
The Krang are too powerful.
Maybe we could
change the future some other way.
Guys, it's time to face facts.
We can't change the future.
Says who?
Says the grandfather paradox,
says physical determinism,
says the space-time continuum.
Look, I didn't want it to be true, but...
...science.
That's it! Donnie's wrong.
The world is ending,
yet the barbs continue.
Don't you remember?
We already did change the future.
Raph never got kidnapped and
turned into a Krang zombie in your time.
- Right, Casey?
- No, he didn't.
- That means we did change the future!
- We're just in a different...
Bifurcated time branch?
Yes, yes, yes, that nerd thing.
You know what that means, right?
We still have hope!
A ninja's greatest weapon.
Hey, I like that!
Look, I'm done
thinking I have all the answers.
I don't know how to beat the Krang,
but I do know our future
isn't written until we write it as a team.
So what do we got?
Maybe...
Maybe we don't have to beat them.
Can't we just send them
back to the prison dimension?
There's an idea! Donnie, what do those
big, beautiful eyebrows have to say?
If we got control of their ship,
we could send it back through the portal.
Yes! Yes! Now we're cooking. Who else?
If someone on the ground
can get to that key...
We can close the doorway.
And then bye-bye Krang forever, baby!
Exactly. What do you say, Donnie?
You ready to fly a space ship?
Literally the greatest question
I have ever been asked.
All right, team, we have a plan.
Let's go save the world.
Wait, but what about Raph?
That big jerk may be
covered in goo and half alien,
but he's still our brother,
and I'm not giving up on him.
I'm not leaving him behind.
There's the key. Let's go.
Like Casey said, let's go!
I wish my tech was working!
Usually, my cardio is jet pack-assisted.
I'm not getting credit
for any of these steps!
Eugh.
Hey, question,
is it too late to join April's team?
Sh.
You two figure out
how to hijack this ship.
I'm gonna find Raph.
So how do we hack this thing?
Best guess, main console?
Unfortunately, it'socupado.
Uh, new plan.
Run!
Surprise. I've come for my brother.
Let me guess.
Duty.
He said doodie.
I see you got yourself an upgrade.
You'll pay for what you have done to me!
This psycho routine is a little thin.
Where's the character development?
Leo's counting on us
to get to that key.
I think I have an idea.
Cover me!
Raph, you're coming with me,
whether you like it or not.
I don't want to fight you,
but I will if I have to.
Oh, you will have to.
Bravo, Mikey!
There's no buttons,
or computers, or anything.
Just a lot of drippy,
ooey-gooey disgustingness.
I don't know how to hack in...
Oh God, I know what I have to do.
What?
No, I don't think I can do this.
What are you talking about?
Oh no!
That's... so gross!
- I can't do it.
- I believe in you!
- No, it's my worst nightmare.
- I know.
I'm doing it! I'm doing it!
Raph, I know you're in there somewhere.
You've gotta snap out of this!
Do you feel what
the power of the Krang can do?
I am saving this weak planet!
I am a gift!
It's not working.
I need more of a connection.
Mikey, take off my battle shell.
No, you're too vulnerable
with just your soft shell.
There's no time, hurry.
Donnie?
Mikey, I am...
a spaceship!
Oh! Ah!
I'm trying to save you, you idiot!
Why do you have to make things so hard?
Ah.
You want to keep coming at me?
Go ahead. I'm done fighting you.
What?
No!
Finally, man and machine
entwixed in perfect bionic synergy!
How dare you desecrate Krang's ship!
Donnie, Mikey!
I don't want to fight anymore.
I was fighting you
because I didn't understand you,
but now I get it.
I always figured you were mad because
you didn't like the way I did things.
But when I see what's happening to you,
and what's happening to them...
I realized it wasn't about me.
You didn't yell because you were mad,
you yelled because you were scared.
It's scary to be responsible
for the lives you protect.
Your team... your family,
but we do it anyway
because that's what it means to be a hero.
If this is it,
I want you to know I finally understand.
And I'm sorry.
Raph, Raph, there you are! Come back!
Your family needs you.
- Leo?
- Yes!
Mikey, Donnie, we can fight this.
Raph's doing it for us,
so we do it for him.
That alien jerk face thinks we're weak
because he hasn't seen what we can do...
when we fight together!
It's pointless to resist Krang.
Give up!
You will be consumed like
everyone else on this pathetic planet!
Fat chance.
We're not like
everyone else on this planet.
We are...
...the Teenage...
- ...Mutant...
- ...Ninja...
...Turtles!
If this isn't the poster shot,
someone's getting fired.
Oh, we are not done yet.
April O'Neil!
That's payback.
Keep her under that building
until I bring it down.
Yeah!
Casey, get out of there!
Commander O'Neil!
Nice shot.
Donnie's almost got the ship to
the other side. I have to get to the key.
See ya.
Come in, Sensei, it's Casey.
Can you hear me?
Come in, Sensei! Can you hear me?
Ya!
Ah!
Okay! Donnie!
Cowabunga!
Flip-o-rama!
Let's roll.
Ka-zoom!
Raph, go.
On it!
Gotcha! Don't worry, Donnie!
This is not a hug. It's a rescue!
Where are we? Staten Island?
Oh, gross.
So how would everyone rate
that rescue experience? Unsatisfied?
Very unsatisfied?
Wish Donnie would have done it? Um-hum?
Donnie.
Leo's still up there.
Casey. Casey, come in.
Sensei, I'm here.
And I've got eyes on the key.
Tell me when you're home free,
and I'll pull the plug.
Casey, listen to me.
When I get to the other side,
you close that door.
What? Sensei, no!
Casey, it's the only way.
He's too strong.
He's not gonna stay on the other side
unless I keep him there.
There has to be another way!
We tried everything, Case.
This is the only way.
Leo, please don't do this! Leo!
You're one to talk, big bro.
Hero moves are totally your style.
Outmatched and alone, yet you persist.
For what?
Honor, redemption?
Sacrifice? All meaningless.
We'll see about that.
Leo, please!
I can't lose you again.
Hey, future me would be real
proud of you. I'm proud of you.
Weak words, weak actions.
I have forever known
what you fail to understand,
strength always prevails!
What you fail to understand
is I missed on purpose.
No, enough of your little tricks.
Casey, close the portal now.
What?
No! Let go of me!
Casey, please.
You've been portal chopped.
You...
You've ruined everything!
And now... my wrath
will be reserved for you alone.
You think you've won,
you wretched little pest?
Wipe that grin off your face!
Mikey, it's over.
Leo never gave up on us.
I'm not giving up on him.
Whoa. Mikey,
whatever you're doing, don't stop!
We're here, Mikey. Together.
Took you guys long enough.
Leo!
Huh?
- Leo?
- Hey.
Eww! Are we in Staten Island?
- Come here!
- Aww!
No pictures.
So this is "grabbing a slice"?
I don't get it.
Wait for it.
Mmm.
So much better than rats!
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey.
Hey, the rest of the world we saved
is pretty great too.
All right, everybody, look up here.
April, you just got a message
from someone named "Cassandra."
Whoa!
Looks like our friend Cassandra
has been busy.
That's my mom!
There goes the space-time continuum.
You did it, little brother.
You really did it.
I'm proud of you.
This wasn't about me.
It was about all of us
doing what needed to be done
because we're heroes.
You said "heroes."
There it is, gentlemen, our home.
What a town.
Beautiful.
And if it needs defending,
we'll always rise to the challenge.
Speaking of which,
you know what challenge I'm gonna rise to?
- Beating that record!
- Yay!
No way! No, okay, fine.
All right, Big Raphie, let's do it!
Raph! Raph! Raph! Raph!
Raph! Raph! Raph! Raph! Raph!
♪ Rise of the
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles ♪
♪ Teenage, rise ♪
♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles ♪
♪ Teenage ♪
♪ Rise ♪
♪ Ninja, ninja, ninja, ninja ♪
♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle ♪
♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja Tur... ♪
♪ Rise of the ♪
♪ Rise ♪
♪ Rise, rise ♪