[MultiCom Jingle]
["You Don't Own Me"
by Leslie Gore]
[car engine whirs]
♪ You don't own me ♪
♪ I'm not just one of
your many toys ♪
♪ You don't own me ♪
♪ Don't say I can't go
with other boys ♪
♪ And don't tell me what to do ♪
♪ Don't tell me what to say ♪
♪ Please, when I got
out with you ♪
♪ Don't put me on
display 'cause ♪
♪ You don't own me ♪
♪ Don't try to change
me in any way ♪
♪ You don't own me ♪
♪ Don't tie me down
'cause I'd never stay ♪
[bottle shatters]
♪ I don't tell you what to say ♪
♪ I don't tell you what to do ♪
♪ So just let me be myself ♪
♪ That's all I ask of you ♪
[bat thuds against flesh]
[nun screams]
[foot whaps against flesh]
[bat thuds against flesh]
[nun screams]
[nurse screams]
[foot bashes against flesh]
[bat thuds against flesh]
[nurse screams]
♪ To say and do
whatever I please ♪
[gas splashes]
[flame roars]
["You Don't Own Me"
by Leslie Gore]
[gun fires]
♪ Don't tell me what to say ♪
[priest groans]
[gun fires]
♪ Don't tell you what to do ♪
♪ I am young and I love
to be young ♪
♪ I am free and I
love to be free ♪
[crickets chirp]
- See you later, have a
good night, guys.
[ominous piano music plays]
[jarring, booming music]
[Mo shrieks]
Jesus, Mo, what the hell
are you doing?
- Ah, the ole
chicken mask trick.
Gets'em every time.
- You scared me half to
death, what is wrong with you?
- It's good to see you too.
Doing a little redecorating?
[car horn blares]
[tires screech]
- My friends are here.
I'm in a raging hurry, okay?
- Alright, I wouldn't
want to keep
your little sorority
sisters waiting.
- I'll catch you in psych
tomorrow, okay?
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
this is like an emergency.
I really need you.
- Oh my God.
Who is that?
- Yo, that's that
weird goth chick.
I heard she's a dyke.
- [laughs] Hey, a little
lesbo action, dude.
I can get into that.
- Yeah. [laughs]
[Boozer growls]
- What the hell is she doing?
We've been waiting for
her ass for like
five minutes.
Come on Riss, the nun's away.
- All I need is a ride.
- A ride, a ride where?
- To the convent, that's
where you're going, isn't it?
Heard you guys were
trying to like,
paint your little letters
on the convent
before the Kappa's
beat you to it.
- Yeah, and?
- I need you to give me
a ride there.
- I just can't take you, Mo.
They won't understand.
- Whatever, Clorissa.
You're always gonna be
struggling to fit in.
They're never gonna accept
you for who you are.
- They're my friends.
They like me for who I am.
- Seeing as how they
like you so much,
I'm sure you wouldn't mind
if I told them about all
of your tattoos,
or the nose ring you
used to wear.
Your one night stand
with Joey Ramone.
- They won't believe you.
- By the way, I was
digging through my closet,
and I came across
this picture of you and
I at the Misfits show.
I'm sure they'd love
to see that,
it's a classic.
Oh did you,
ooh.
- Look, I'm sorry we
don't hang out anymore,
but do you think you can
just blackmail me
into being your friend again?
- Oh, get over yourself,
Clorissa.
I need a ride and that's it.
- And?
- And I wanna see if the
place is really haunted.
- Oh, I thought you gave
that up with like Menudo.
- What your new friends
don't like Menudo?
[car horn blares]
- Would you get it
in gear, Riss?
I'm like getting wrinkles
waiting here for you.
- Hey, hey bring the
lesbo along.
[guys laugh]
- Ooh, lesbo, that's me.
This is great.
[guys laugh]
- Okay, why?
- Because Frijole hasn't got any
since he got booted
from the house.
- Yeah, after
breaking the record
for longest
pledgehood in history.
- Wait, why would you even
try to scam on a dyke?
You know you can't have her.
- I'll turn her around man,
just give me five minutes.
Watch.
- Right dude,
you can't even turn a screw.
- Dude, screw you.
I'll show you
wannabe's what it's
like to be the mack of UCC.
- Frijole, you--
- Watch and learn girl.
All I need is five minutes
alone with her.
- Fine, you wanna go that bad,
jump in,
but I swear to God, if
you say anything.
- Don't worry, Riss, your
secrets are safe with me.
- Guys, this is Mo.
- What's that short
for? Morticia? [laughs]
- Are you a bulimic bitch?
- Excuse me?
- So Kaitlin, how was
cheerleading practice?
- [Kaitlin] Oh, it was fine.
They had us do the same
routine like 99 times.
[ominous music plays]
- [Frijole] Hey, hey, it's that
creaky old bitch's pad, man.
- [Kaitlin] Who?
- The town legend.
Crazy chick who lives
in that house.
- Ew, somebody lives
in that house?
- I guess anything's
better than the loony bin.
- [Clorissa] Whataya mean?
- [Chad] That's
Christine's house.
She made'em shutdown
the convent.
- [Mo] Actually, she
shut it down.
She went crazy and blew
away the nuns.
Made our town famous.
- Has anyone ever seen her?
- No, she shoots at anyone
who steps on her property.
- [Biff] For real?
- Yeah, man, she shoots
at people all the time.
- I bet you I could fuck her.
[Biff laugh]
- Would you stop being
such an asshole
and let's just get
there already.
- I just wanna check and see
if the freak wants to
come with us.
Hey, baby, hey, we're gonna go
visit your friends
tonight, you wanna come?
- Shit, really?
- Girl, just relax.
Come on baby,
we got room for one more.
[car horn blares]
- Let's split.
- Dude, quit being such a
buzzkill, man.
There ain't no one
living in there.
- You know what, I don't care.
I'm just getting like
really bad juju
from this place, okay?
- Alright baby, this is
your last chance.
[car horn blares]
[ominous music plays]
Oh, shit.
[group screams]
- [Biff] Oh shit, man, go.
[tires screech]
[wolf howl]
- [Clorissa] I am not
overreacting,
I don't think this is gonna
be a good Friday night,
getting attacked by
some crazy lady.
- [Biff] Chill out, huh.
[Chad] Riss, you're
such a spaz case.
[chain rattles]
- Yeah.
[group cheers]
[chain snaps]
[gate clanks]
[group cheers]
[owl hoots]
[ominous music plays]
- [Frijole] Holy shit.
- Alright kids, we got
some painting to do.
- You know, this place is
all Amityville and shit.
Like, redrum, redrum. [laughs]
- It's only a movie, nimrod.
- Yeah, hey, hey, I
got a good one for you.
Alright, what kind of
pussy does a priest get?
- None.
- None, get it? [laughs]
- Yeah, same kind you get,
huh Frijole?
[Biff laughs]
- You're right dude, she
wants you bad.
- Yeah, laugh it up homey,
just watch.
I'm gonna get some tonight,
fo sho.
You just give me five minutes.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh, I finished the guys
laundry early,
so they let me come along.
- The guys?
You make it sound like they're
your big buddies or something.
- They are my buddies,
they're gonna let me in
the fraternity.
- Don't you see they're
just using you?
You're a joke to them sweetie,
they're never gonna let you in.
- God, you sound just like mom.
- Hey.
- Can't you except that
they're my friends, too?
- Can't you just accept that
- [groans] Ah.
- Oh, yeah.
- Nice, nice.
- Good one, Chad.
That one went all the
way up my ass.
Good job, pal.
Yeah, you just go on ahead,
I'll catch up.
Be right there.
- Yo, bust it open, pledge.
- I'm sorry, Biff, what?
- I said bust down the
door, now, now, now.
- Yeah, hey, bust it down,
pledge.
- Okay, alright.
Bust it down,
Bust it down, [laughs] okay.
Yeah, [laughs] okay, bro.
Yeah, alright.
Um, okay is there a shovel or
something around I can use?
- A what? A shove?
Move your ass now, bitch.
[Brant bashes against door]
- Hey, hey, can you please
take it easy on him?
- [Frijole] Ah, sorry Riss,
but coddling your
little brother,
ain't gonna make him a Lambda.
- Oh, and body slamming
him into a door will?
- Just one more time,
alright Clorissa?
- Fine, whatever.
- Please, I, ooh.
[Brant bashes through door]
[Biff laughs]
- Good job man.
- My ass is stuck.
- Get out here, you fucking...
Climb inside.
- I think I ruptured my spleen.
- Hey, don't be a pussy, pledge,
climb inside.
- Sounds to me like you're
all a bunch of pussies.
Get out of my way.
- Excuse me?
- I think you heard me
the first time.
- Why don't you stick
it in your ear.
[guys laugh]
[ominous music plays]
[crickets chirp]
[Boozer whimpers ]
- This must be where it
all happened.
- Where what happened?
- The abortion.
[jarring music plays]
- There is no abortion, I mean,
that's just urban legend, right?
- Bullshit.
It was the scandal that
closed this place down.
The last surgery ever
performed here.
[Christine screams]
Christine O'Mally was
16 and pregnant.
Not a pretty
situation back then.
[Christine screams]
Father Ryan and Mother Superior
kidnapped her in the
middle of the night
and brought her here
and strapped her down.
[Christine screams]
[saw blade whirs]
They performed an abortion
right then and there.
No consent necessary.
- Bet they used a wire hanger.
- Ah, gross Kaitlin.
- That's my girl.
- Why would they do that?
I mean abortion's like the
biggest sin in Catholicism.
- Rumor has it the
child was Father Ryan's.
- That's fucked up.
- Did the church
punish Father Ryan?
- Hardly, Christine
busted into mass one day
and blew them away and
then torched'em one by one.
Nuns in flames, I'll bet
it was fucking beautiful.
- So she became like,
some serial nun killer?
- Well she claimed they
were the devil's disciples.
And thus began her 30 year
vacation in the nuthouse.
They say that Father
Ryan and the nuns
still haunt this building.
Seeking revenge.
[ominous music plays]
- Sounds like you saw one
too many episodes of Elvira.
[jarring, booming music plays]
[Frijole yells]
[Kaitlin screams]
- Man.
- Nasty, dude.
Yo, get it the fuck outta here,
pledge.
- But, but, but.
- No, don't but me, move it now.
Get it the fuck outta
here, hear what I said?
Move it, move it, movie
it, now, now, pledge.
That's right.
[Kaitlin yelps]
- Biff.
[Biff laughs]
- This place is gross.
Let's just hurry and paint,
and then we can go
somewhere romantic.
- Ooh, now you're talking,
now you're talking
[ominous music plays]
[mumbled whispering]
- Do you think devil
worshipers really live here?
- It's paint, knucklehead.
[laughs]
- Ah.
- What do you say, we do a
little exploring of our own?
- Don't you think we
should all stay together?
[Kaitlin laughs]
Right, what was I thinking?
- Hey, start that
graffiti pledge.
[Boozer growls]
- Holy, the dog's
trying to hump me.
- You said you wanted some
action, dude. [laughs]
- This isn't funny, he's
really strong.
[Brant thuds against floor]
- Whoa, whoa, boy, easy boy.
Yo, Brant, why don't you ah,
why don't you take Boozer
for a little stroll.
- [Brant] Just let him go here,
the place is already
a shit hole.
- Let me repeat myself, pledge.
Why don't you take
Boozer for a walk.
- But,
Okay.
Come on, Boozer.
- Looks like it's just you,
me and the chronic, baby.
[laughs]
- [laughs] Yeah, lucky me.
[Frijole laughs]
[ominous music plays]
- [Clorissa] I wonder if
people really do
come here to devil worship?
- It's another fucking
stupid legend.
- There's probably
homeless people here too.
- I don't know, I
wouldn't exactly
call this place a shelter.
- I wonder what it would be
like to spend a night here?
- Hmm, do you have a
little hidden dark side?
- Maybe.
[ominous music plays]
[lips smack]
[jarring, high pitch music]
[Clorissa screams]
- What?
What's the matter?
- There was
a nun,
and she was all gross
and fucked up.
- Relax, you're just
seeing shit.
Frijole's weed was probably
laced with a little something.
- But I swear, I saw a
nun standing right there.
- Okay, you're trippin'
on the weed
and Morticia's story.
- But it looked so real.
- Relax, we're supposed
to be having fun.
- Well, I'm not.
- Can we please just bail?
I mean, this place
creeps me out.
- Sexy, Riss.
[lighter clicks]
- You think we can get up
to the bell tower from here?
- Yeah, I think so.
What are you scared?
- No.
So baby, do you know karate?
Cause like that ass is kickin'.
[laughs]
- Please tell me
you're not serious.
- Come on baby, it's
just you're so beautiful,
I'm struggling to find
the right words.
- So why don't you do us both
a favor and quit talking.
- Oh, what, you want me to
be the strong, silent type?
I can do that.
- Wait, just relax stud.
- Come on baby, you
know you want it.
- Get off of me.
- All chicks say that.
- Yeah, I'm sure they do.
- Yeah, but they never mean it.
- Well, I do.
Look, frat boy,
I'm a virgin, and I'm
certainly not losing it
to some player like you.
I'm saving myself for
Marilyn Manson.
- [laughs] So you're a hater.
Well, that explains it baby,
but don't worry, you'll get
nothing buy love from Frijole.
- I thought I told you, relax.
- Whoa, whoa, man.
I'm sensing some
aggression here.
- Yeah, you are, so
fucking quit it.
- You talk about sending
mixed signals, man.
Virgin, my ass.
[police sirens blare]
[Officer Starkey] This
is the police.
You have sixty seconds to vacate
the building with your
- Fuck, holy
- hands above your head,
- shit, man.
- or that's your ass.
- Oh shit.
- Look, I was not here.
Do you hear me?
- No, no, no,
it's probably just the
campus police.
Just be cool, okay.
- No, no, no, no, no, I'm
already on probation, okay?
Please just, just
tell'em I cruised.
- Whoa, whoa man, you
want to lie to the five-o?
- Well, come on, it'll
be our little secret.
Just, all you have to do is
just tell them that I went home.
I, uh,
I could make it
worth your while.
- That sounds good to me, baby.
You just tell me where and when.
- Ah, back here,
um,
say an hour?
- How do I know you'll show?
- I don't know, you wanna
a credit card?
- I'll tell you what,
you give me your panties,
and it's all good.
- M, My panties?
- It's a easy choice, baby doll,
panties or community college.
Panties or community college.
- Yeah, okay, alright, alright.
Jesus Christ, what do
you watch Sixteen Candles
like 8,000 times, you got
it on loop at your house?
- What, yeah.
- Bring your ass out now!
- Yeah, that's what I'm
talking about
motherfucker, woo.
[police dispatch mumbles]
- Well, let me guess.
You all thought
you'd be the ones
to finally desecrate the
bell tower, didn't ya?
- Is that what you thought?
- No, we were just--
- Who said you could talk,
white boy?
- I thought this--
- Shut up.
I don't wanna hear another
word from you, little punk.
[Boozer whimpers]
- You see,
every year
come homecoming game,
another group of
kids tries to be
the one to get past us.
But that never happens.
Does it Starkey?
- Hell no.
- And this year ain't gonna be
no different kids, you got that?
Now are you sure
there's no on else
left inside the building?
- Is there anybody else, huh?
Huh?
Well there better not be,
cause if I so much as
catch a scent
of anybody else in there,
I'm gonna lock your
ass up so tight,
they gonna have to have
a combination
to visit your nuts,
white boy.
[Boozer whimpers]
- So,
if you're sure,
that we're not gonna
find anybody else inside.
- Well there was another girl,
but she bailed and went
home by herself.
[Boozer groans]
- Why the hell
would a young girl
head home alone
in the middle of the night?
- Why, why, why, why, why?
- She said something about,
her dorm had a curfew.
- Well,
tonight is your lucky night,
kids.
If I see any of you little
pricks around here again,
you're going downtown,
you got that?
- What's this?
What is this? What is this?
- I, I don't know who's that is,
man.
- Oh, so now you wanna
lie to me, huh white boy?
Oh, no, let me kill him Ray.
- No, no.
- Let me kill'em.
- No, Starkey, no.
He's not worth it, he's
not worth it.
- Let me kill'em
- No, no, no,
Starkey, no.
It's okay.
- You know how it is, Ray.
You know how I feel about
this, the youth
destroying their lives
with this marijuana substance.
- I know, Starkey, I know.
- You delinquent,
degenerate ass kids,
get the hell outta here.
All of ya, get out.
- Do what he says.
- Before I bust a cap
in your ass.
- For your own good.
[Starkey laughs]
[slap hands]
- Man, they get dumber
every year, don't they/
- Oh man.
Don't you think we outta go
in there and check it out.
And make sure that those
kid weren't lying to us?
- Get in the car, let's
move it along.
- Nah, none of these kids
got enough balls
to stay in there man,
don't worry about it.
- Give me some of that.
- Get along, little piggy.
Nice.
[jarring, high pitch music]
[Mo screams]
- Oh, excuse me, can I get the
shredded cheese on the side?
- Frijole, did you
really see Mo leave?
- All I know is I saw her,
alright.
I saw a whole lot of her.
[group laughs and hollers]
[Frijole laughs]
- Can you not be a pig
for just one minute,
answer my question?
- Don't be a hater, baby.
It's not very flattering.
- Did you see her leave or not?
- Take it easy, baby,
you know I like to avoid
that whole cuddling
afterwards bullshit.
[Biff laughs]
Damn girl,
relax.
She hid so she wouldn't
have to deal with the cops.
- Dude, goth chick's
probably gonna go
all narcoleptic and shit
with the dead.
- That would be necrophiliac.
- Ooh.
- Do you guys
get that we left her
alone there?
- So.
She wanted to stay.
- So she could get
raped or murdered.
- Oh.
- Enough with the drama, babe.
- Can we please go
back and get her?
- Excuse me, are you
smoking crack?
[Biff laughs]
I mean, I don't think
getting arrested
is gonna look good on my
application to fashion school.
- Chad.
- Hmm.
- Are you coming with me?
[glass rattles]
- Wait, Clorissa. [laughs]
Calm down.
- You units, do I have to
handle absolutely everything?
- Kaitlin, don't worry about it.
[Frijole laughs]
- [Kaitlin] Clorissa,
where are you going?
- I have to pee.
- Well I have to pee too, but
I'm not gonna go in there.
Is this the ghetto?
- Oh please, just
don't sit down.
- Fine, but I'm gonna
need like a rabies shot.
- [Kaitlin] So what's the deal,
Clorissa?
Why do you give a shit
about that weird ass chick?
- [Clorissa] Kaitlin, we
left a girl alone
in an abandoned building.
Who knows what's happened?
- [Kaitlin] I think you
are way overreacting.
- [Clorissa] No, I'm not.
That place was freaky
and you know it.
I don't care what you guys do,
I'm going back.
- [Kaitlin] Fine, Riss,
whatever.
Let's just hurry it up, okay?
Now is your little fit
over with or is there more?
- [Clorissa] I'm done.
- [Kaitlin] Thanks.
Good, because you definitely
owe me one for this.
- [Clorissa] Oh God.
- Dude, I wouldn't
mind going back
for another round with
that goth chick.
Dude, she was so fine.
- Dude, I say we charge over
to that 50 kegger at
the Lambda House.
- Yeah, beer.
- We can't go back there, bro.
We can get in a lot of trouble
- Dude, if something
happened to her,
you're name could be ruined.
- Beer.
- We wouldn't want
Chadwick Senior
to hear that his
star quarterback
has gone trespassing,
now would we?
[Brant laughs]
- It's just not worth it.
- Hello, are you guys
listening to me?
50 kegs, man.
Five-zero.
- Wouldn't you feel bad if
something happened to her, man?
- It's not my problem, man.
- You guys suck dick.
- Screw you.
I don't care what
you guys think,
nothing is worth going back for.
- Yeah, well I hate to
tell you this,
but I left my entire
stash there.
- [Biff And Chad] What?
[ominous music plays]
- You guys don't get it,
kegs.
- We're risking way too much
for Clorissa's little
Morticia friend.
- It's Monica, okay Kaitlin?
Monica.
- [Kaitlin] Ooh, want
her address?
- You guys, you guys, you
guys, let's just get the stash
and get out of here.
- And get Mo.
- Right, and get Mo.
- Look you guys, maybe if we
separate we'll find her faster.
- Great, Shag, you go
with Thelma,
I'll go with Daphne.
- Seriously, you guys,
what the fuck?
Chad and I will go look
in that hallway,
come on baby.
- And, ah,
ah, we'll um, check out
the bedrooms.
- Later guys.
- Yeah, late.
[Boozer barks]
Boozer.
Boozer, get back here, boy.
Man, hey Brant, go get my dog,
man.
- Wait, I, I, don't
think we should split up.
- Dude, I got some
business to take care of.
- What are you talking about?
- I got some homies
meeting me here
to pick up a little herb.
- They're meeting you here?
- Yeah, yeah, and they'll
probably bring
a couple of hotties with them,
so maybe I could hook you
up if you go get my dog.
- You mean sex?
- Yeah, dude.
- With a girl?
- Yes, here,
take my keys, go get my dog,
wait there.
They'll come and find you, okay.
Yeah, that's great.
All good, it's all good.
I'll be busy shrooming,
motherfuckers.
[trippy, atmospheric
music plays]
[ominous music plays]
[Mo screams]
- Who the fuck are you?
[door slams open]
- I
have arrived.
- Your virgin, my lord.
- Ah,
good.
So this
must be
our sacrificial lamb.
And such a timely arrival.
- Everything's ready sir.
- Very good, my minion of evil.
So, girls on the left
and boys on the right.
And now comes the time where we
worship my father Lucifer.
[thunder booms]
Sapphira, are you ready
to give you soul
to the fires of darkness?
- Yes, my lord, I am
there for your command.
- Well then, Sapphira,
you know Sapphira I don't know
if I've ever told you
this before,
but you
definitely are the
embodiment of lust.
- A mere extension of
your greatness, Saul.
Lucifer will not be
disappointed.
[Mo screams]
- Please tell me you guys
aren't serious.
- Oh, we're dead serious.
- You white trash losers
don't actually think
you're gonna accomplish anything
by killing me, do you?
- [laughs] Excuse me,
silence infidel,
or if not,
I
shall personally
and with thy own hands,
tear the tongue from your mouth,
for
marking the circle
of biz, biz,
the thirteenth coven.
[Mo laughs]
- The thirteenth coven?
Could you be anymore
gothic pretentious?
- How dare you speak to
the prince of evil
that way, you slut.
- The prince of evil?
You work at fucking Dairy Queen.
- Liar.
- Liar, my ass you served
my cousin and me
a Snacker Wizard last week.
- What the fuck is she
talking about?
- Lies,
lies,
lies.
Silence her, now.
[Mo groans]
Ha, ha, now then,
daughter of darkness,
the time has come to silence
this woman for eternity.
- Dairy Queen, Saul?
- Saphirra,
the time is nigh
for your first step
into darkness.
So,
why don't
you
take
the
dagger of despair,
and you know, plunge it
into thy virginal heart.
Today.
- Son of evil, lord of darkness,
I invoke thee master of
the underworld.
I imprison your
virgin in darkness.
We release her
To the sea below seas
release her against
the 60 demons,
possess her eyes with
the demons of the eyes,
possess her hands with
the demons of the hands,
possess her heart with
the demons of the heart,
we deliver thee o' lord
of the plain,
human corpse with [mumbles],
[thunder booms]
demons tear at her
from every side,
rise,
bitch rise.
[knife thuds into flesh]
[fast paced techno music]
[door slams shut]
[wind rustles]
- Cool. [laughs]
[jarring, booming music]
[fist whaps against flesh]
[knife slashes into flesh]
[tongue splats on floor]
[Sapphira screams]
[techno music plays]
[lockers smash on floor]
[Sapphira whimpers]
[blood plops on Sapphira]
[bloods splashes on Sapphira]
[Sapphira screams]
[water splashes on Sapphira]
[Sapphira growls]
- Was that a scream?
- No.
- Do you think Kaitlin and Biff
were trying to fuck with us?
- They better fucking stop,
we don't need the cops to
come back here.
- You know how she gets
when she's wasted.
[door creaks and slams]
What was that?
- Huh, it was probably nothing.
- No Chad, it was
definitely something.
- Let's just get out of here.
- Hello?
[scream]
Mo?
Is that you?
[door creaks]
- Again, let's just
get outta here.
- Well I think we
should check it out.
- Great, famous last words.
- Oh, come on.
- Riss.
- Oh Jesus,
Chad, you're the man here.
- I'm not afraid.
- Oh, then prove it tough guy.
[ominous music plays]
- See, it was nothing,
I told you.
- Alright, I just wanted
to check it out.
- Great, now can we get
the fuck outta here?
[door smashes]
[Clorissa screams]
[Chad screams]
[demon growls]
[Flesh rips]
[Chad wails]
[demon growls]
[flashlight thuds against flesh]
[flashlight rips through flesh]
[blood splashes]
[demon growls]
[Clorissa screams]
[wood thuds against flesh]
- Get up, come on.
- I'm fine.
[demon growls]
- Shit.
- Hey, what's up guys?
♪ Dream weaver ♪
♪ I believe you can get
me through the night ♪
♪ Oh, dream weaver ♪
♪ I believe we can reach
the morning light ♪
This is some good shit.
[Dream Weaver by Gary Wright]
[squeaks]
- Yo, you, get me down
from here, motherfucker.
[Frijole laughs]
♪ Dream weaver ♪
[hallucination giggles]
♪ I believe you can get
me through the night ♪
♪ Oh dream weaver ♪
Well, well, well,
what do we have here?
I,I always knew you were a
creepy little thing, thing.
Whoa,
whoa, shit.
[Mo growls]
Whoa.
Fucking dominant chick.
[Mo growls]
You look all demonic and shit.
Yeah, no, that's cool.
That's cool.
Alright,
that's cool.
Damn, girl.
What you doing?
Alright, breath.
Do, do, do your thing.
Do what you got to do.
I can do this, and shit.
[Mo snarls]
[Frijole screams]
[fast paced techno music]
- Boozer?
Booz?
[ominous music plays]
Boozer?
[door creaks]
[door slams shut]
Boozer?
Boozer, are you, are
you in there?
He's not in there.
[jarring, booming music]
[Brant screams]
- No, no.
Are you one of them?
Answer me, are you the
spawn of the devil?
- No, I'm a Lambda.
- Does he bare the mark, master?
- Whattaya, ah, hey
whattaya doing?
Stop it.
- His nipple, sire.
[Saul screams]
Is it the mark?
[Brant screams]
- No, no, no, no,
it's just a mole.
He's clean.
- Oh.
- Are you guys alumni,
or something?
What's going on?
- The evil scarf, hurry up,
give me the evil scarf.
- The scarf?
- Oh, I
get it now.
You guys are Frijole's bros,
huh?
Yeah. [laughs]
Hey,
hey,
if you wanna hook up with
some of his dope, you know?
[laughs]
You better have a little
action for the ole Brantster.
You know, action.
Action.
Oh daddy, oh, daddy.
[Saul laughs]
Oh yeah, you know what I mean?
[laughs]
- That's right, Brantster.
We
are Frijole's boys,
and we are here to hook you up.
- Yes
- Yes.
So,
let's hook you up.
- Alright.
- Oh my God.
- Yes.
- Give me the scarf now please.
- I'm so excited.
- I'd like you to stand
right here.
[Brant laughs]
I'm just gonna put this
blindfold on you.
- Blindfold? Okay.
Are the girls in the
car or something?
- Oh yes.
[group laughs]
Alright, now listen
very carefully
to the sound of my voice.
You will sleep now.
[club thuds against flesh]
[Brant screams]
- Fuck.
- Did you hurt him, master?
- Oh my fucking head,
you fucking dick.
- I'm trying to strike
him unconscious.
- Oh my fucking God,
that hurt me.
What was that for?
- I'm sorry, I'm kidding,
I'm kidding.
- What the?
- Come on, come back, okay,
listen, listen to me carefully.
- What are you guys doing?
- Shhh.
Just Listen, listen.
You will sleep now.
[club thuds against flesh]
[Brant screams]
- Fuck
me, you fucking dick.
I'm having no fun, you
fucking dick.
- Wait, wait.
- Just stand still,
make yourself home.
And,
you will
definitely sleep now.
[pole thuds against flesh]
[Brant screams]
- Why did you do that master?
- Cause I want to live.
And I have an idea.
- What?
- Perhaps, with another
virginal sacrifice
we might be able to
reverse the process
and send the demons back.
- But, don't we need a virgin?
- Oh,
well I think we found one.
really.
[ominous music plays]
- We should have set up a
meeting place.
- Great time to think
of that Kaitlin.
- Well gee, I didn't
expect to be
accosted by a slew of
dead bugs, okay, Biff?
- Can we exaggerate a
little more?
- Oh,
you know what, I
don't wanna fight,
okay, it's not gonna
get us anywhere.
[flesh squishes]
Ew.
- What now?
- Oh my god.
[demon growls]
[Kaitlin screams]
[flesh rips from skull]
- Fuck.
[fast paced techno music plays]
[Biff screams]
- It won't budge.
Help.
- Riss.
Am I gonna be okay?
- You look good.
Help!
Help.
- Chad, Riss, they're right
fucking behind me, come on move.
Move it, come on.
[demons growl]
- Oh God, we gotta get
him outta here.
We gotta stop that
bleeding first.
[mumbles]
[hand cracks through wall]
[techno music plays]
Biff, help me.
- Jesus, fucking help her.
- [Corissa] Help me.
- Move, move, move.
[pole cracks against door]
- We gotta get my brother.
- Fucking [mumbles].
- Biff, we gotta get my brother.
[hand smashes through wall]
- I'm not going anywhere,
alright.
They ate my fucking
girlfriend, one of them,
they're not gonna get me.
- Hurry up.
- I'm fucking moving.
[pole crashes through wall]
[Chad growls]
[Clorissa screams]
- Shit.
[pole pops head]
[Clorissa screams]
[techno music plays]
[demons growl]
[Clorissa screams]
- Please, please.
[demons growl]
[crickets chirp]
- I found it, boss.
Ew.
Okay, here you go.
- Let's say, listen, Dickie-Boy,
I just found out from my father,
Lucifer,
that I won't be
performing the ritual.
- Oh, really?
- Something to do about
the lord of darkness
is far past doing
such crude work.
So...
- So who's gonna do it?
Me?
But boss, am I worthy?
- You, yes, he told me.
Your time is now,
sibling of Satan.
- I won't fail you my dark one.
- Where am I?
Hey, I can't see.
- Shh,
just lie still.
- But what's going on?
- Come now, Brantster,
it's the surprise you've
been waiting for.
So, just lay there.
- Oh yeah,
yeah.
- Ah-huh.
[mumbles a spell in gibberish]
Rise,
rise, rise.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Nothing, it's a surprise, shh.
[mumbles a spell in gibberish]
Rise,
rise.
[mumbles a spell in gibberish]
Rise,
rise,
rise.
- No, boss, I can't.
- Hey guys,
um, I don't think
this is for me.
- No, it is for you and
only you can have it.
This is your chance, Dickie-Boy,
prove yourself.
Do it.
- I'm getting tired of this,
guys.
Where's the hot chicks?
- Dammnit, what is
wrong with you?
Do it
or it will be you.
[Brant screams]
[blade thuds against floor]
- Oh my God.
Devil worshipers.
- I'm sorry.
- This is not going well.
[car horn blares]
- Help me officer, help me,
help me.
Don't be scared,
don't be scared.
[gun clicks]
- I cast you out, demon bitch.
[gun fires] [gun fires]
[bullet whizzes by]
[gun fires]
Away with you damn
creatures of the night.
[ominous music plays]
- Christine.
[bashes door]
Hello.
Christine, it's the convent.
People are dying.
You need to help us.
Please.
Christine.
Bitch,
bitch.
[door creaks open]
[demons snarl]
[demons growl]
[ominous music plays]
Hello?
- Stay right there, kid.
I've got a pump action
Winchester leveled
at your chest.
If you don't believe
me, take a step forward.
- Are you her?
Are you Christine?
- If you came to get acquainted,
you came to the wrong house.
You came to talk
about the convent,
start yapping.
- My friends are in trouble.
They're stuck in there.
I think some of'em
maybe be dead.
- Goddamnit.
You kids broke in there,
didn't ya?
Let me guess the rest
of the story.
You and your friends went there
to screw and smoke dope.
When suddenly you
awoke the forces
of evil and they started
killing everybody, right?
- Well,
kind of.
- Yeah, well,
save your sob story
for someone who gives
a rat's ass.
- But don't you see,
you're the only one
who can help us.
- Oh yeah, right.
Every five years or so
you stupid kids
think it'd be great fun
to break into the convent and
see where it all happened.
Then when all hell breaks loose,
you come looking for the
chick who started it.
Well fuck that noise.
I've had it.
Not this time.
I don't need to clean up
after everybody's mess.
- But you have to help me,
my boyfriend, he's one of them,
and my brother's still inside.
- Forget about'em, they're dead.
- How do you know?
- I know.
The demons can only inhabit
recently deceased bodies.
Once they take you over it's
too late, you're already dead.
- But my brother might
still be alive.
- Not unless he's a virgin.
He's not a virgin, is he?
- What does that have to
do with anything?
- Straight answer, is
he a virgin?
- Yeah.
- Oh shit, that is just
fucking great.
He's a virgin, that's perfect.
- So?
- They fucking love virgins.
Goddamn, demons, it' always
something with a virgin.
- What's happening?
- You kids have any idea
what you've done?
- No, what?
- Let me tell ya what really
happened 40 years ago.
[thunder booms]
Sister Camilla was the
first to see it
In the garden was a little girl.
[thunder booms]
Just standing there in the rain.
Sister Camilla thought
she was another orphan.
She was the first one to get it.
The first one to get the demon.
[Sister Camilla screams]
[demon growls]
It wasn't long before it spread.
Sister Joan was next.
[cleaver thuds against flesh]
Then it was Sister Abigail.
[demon growls]
[water splashes]
And on down the line.
Sister Kay.
[Sister Kay screams]
[demons growl]
Sister Marlene.
[demon roars]
Sister O'Donoghue
[nun screams]
Until there was none left.
The place had become the
devil's convent.
[thunder booms]
[ominous music plays]
The next day at school, everyone
knew something was wrong.
[children mumble]
I'd only been there a few weeks.
I was eight months
pregnant and a runaway.
They took me in.
From that day on, they
started acting weird.
Really weird.
[chalk scrapes against board]
[demon roars]
[ruler whaps against flesh]
[paddle thuds against flesh]
[demon hisses]
[demon gurgles]
[vomit splashes]
Then after all of that,
nothing could have prepared
me for what happened next.
- Is that when they performed
the abortion on you?
- That's just the urban legend.
It's not what really happened.
- What did happen?
[thunder booms]
- [Christine] I was
lying in my bed,
my baby started coming.
[ominous music plays]
[demon roars]
[Christine screams]
Stop it.
No.
They wheeled me into the chapel
and started the process.
- [Clorissa] What process?
- [Christine] The process
of taking my baby.
- What did they do with it?
- They were gonna use it
for one of their
fucking sacrifices.
You see, the virgin's
blood is powerful,
but a baby's blood,
way more powerful.
- Why were they going
to sacrifice it?
- His body was gonna be the
host for their new leader.
The son of the devil.
Unfortunately for them,
I had a different plan.
[gun fires]
No one is gonna take my baby.
- That's why you went
in with a shot them, right?
- [Christine] Right.
Although small town legend
[gun fires]
has it that I went crazy
[chamber clicks]
because they made me
have an abortion.
- So your baby, did it live?
- Yeah, he's a civil
engineer in Peoria.
The point of the story is
if these fuckers
get their hands on
another virgin,
they can finally complete
their little ceremony.
- My brother's gonna
be the new Antichrist?
- Afraid so.
- Mom's gonna be pissed.
[ominous music plays]
[demons shriek]
- Hello?
Clorissa?
Guys, is that you?
That's definitely not you.
[techno music plays]
- Hello Brantster.
Now, where were we?
- We were about to jab the
dagger into his heart, my lord.
- Ah, yes, very good my
minion of evil,
except this time, let's
get it right, shall we?
[demons roar]
Now then you keep
holding his body
while I recite the passage,
and then, and only then must you
thrust the ceremonial dagger
into his vengeful heart.
- Yes, dark one.
- Oh my God.
- Stop it.
[Saul mumbles a spell
of gibberish]
- Rise
Rise.
[door crashes]
- Hurry up, they're coming.
[Saul mumbles a spell
in gibberish]
- Rise.
Rise.
Rise,
- Now master, can I kill him?
- No, not yet.
[mumbles a spell in gibberish]
[demon thunders through door]
Now, now, now, you must
kill him now.
[Brant screams]
[demon growls]
[Saul screams]
[Brant screams]
[Brant Screams]
- The time is now, give
me the dagger.
[screams]
[groans]
[knife pops eyeball]
[military drum roll]
[bullets clank]
[chamber clicks]
- So, what are you gonna do?
- What does it look
like I'm doing?
- Are you going in
there by yourself?
- No, I'm gonna be
following you.
- Hey, wait, um, uh,
uh, I mean, shouldn't
we just call,
you know, 911 or something?
- Oh, you wanted my help,
but you're too afraid
to go in there yourself?
- No,
it's-
- It's just nothing.
We got some demons to kill.
[chamber clicks]
- I've never even seen
one of these before.
- You'll figure it out.
[engine roars]
Hop on.
[techno music plays]
[engine thunders]
[demons hiss]
- Where are they taking us?
- Don't you get it?
They're going to sacrifice us.
- Sacrifice?
God, why?
- Because you're a virgin.
- I am, well, how do
they know that?
How do you know that?
- Oh please, you are
just oozing virginity.
And the demons,
well the demons can probably
just smell it on you.
- Well then why are
they taking you?
You mean you're a virgin.
- That's Kevin, left, right,
one, okay?
- Okay.
[engine roars]
- So what's your plan?
- I'm gonna walk in and
blow the shit outta them.
- Ah, what do you need me to do?
- Just stay outta my way.
- Right.
[chamber clicks]
[gun fires]
It's really quiet.
- Yeah, well, that's
never a good sign.
- So, Christine, how do
we kill these things?
[demon shrieks]
[Clorissa screams]
[gun fires]
[blood splashes]
[demon whizzes through air]
[machete scrapes sheath]
[machete slices through neck]
[head thumps on floor]
[techno music plays]
- Any questions?
- Psst, hey Brant?
- Yeah.
- I have an idea.
- What?
- I think we should have sex.
- Ex, excuse me?
- I said, I think we
should have sex.
- Why?
- Well,
if we had sex,
we wouldn't be virgins anymore.
- Um,
no, I think I'd rather not.
- It's our only chance.
- Um,
well,
okay first off,
if we weren't virgins
then they'd just kill us.
- Oh.
That's a good point.
Hey Brant.
- Yeah.
- I'd still like to try.
- We couldn't have sex
even if we wanted to.
We're both tied up.
- Now see look, I almost
got my hands free.
- Oh my,
help.
Help.
- Do you know where
you're going?
- I'm going to the chapel.
Stop asking so many
damn questions.
- What is it?
-Dammit.
What?
- They're right behind us.
[demons roar]
[gun fires]
[machine gun fires]
- Die you motherfuckers
[bullets whizz by]
[Clorissa screams]
[machine gun fires]
[demon snarls]
[gun fires]
[machete slices through neck]
[machine gun fires]
[demons roar]
- [Clorissa] What are you doing?
- Just shut up and shoot.
[machine gun fires]
[shotgun fires]
[demon grunts]
[machine gun fires]
[shotgun fires]
- Christine.
[demon head pops]
[Clorissa screams]
[machine gun fires]
[techno music plays]
[door pops demon head]
[blood splashes]
What are we gonna do?
- I got no idea, kid.
- But where do you think
my brother is?
- Oh, I'm sure they got
him over at the chapel.
- Well, then let's go.
[door rattles]
- Look kid, we're almost
out of bullets,
the chapel's all the way over
on the other side of
the convent.
- Out of bullets?
- Yeah.
- What are we gonna do?
- I'll be right back.
- What?
- Hold'em off 'til I get back.
[wood cracks]
- Oh, okay.
[hand cracks through door]
- Where are you going?
- Don't worry about me dude,
I'm just movin' away.
- Come on, Brant.
Brant.
Oh yes.
This is perfect.
- [screams No.
- You don't have to be afraid.
I'll be very gentle.
- For the last time, no.
I would like to stay a
virgin in that department.
- Don't make this difficult.
- No.
Oh God.
Oh.
Oh, no
[demon roars]
Shit, this sucks, this sucks.
- Our father who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name,
please start this fucking bike,
or we're all gonna
bite the big one.
[engine roars]
Jesus.
- Okay, fuck.
Outta bullets.
Fucking crazy ass, ninja
ass, psychotic fucking bitch.
Okay,
hi guys.
Want this.
Kaitlin.
Shit.
I know karate.
[motorcycle thunders in]
[machete slashes through neck]
[head thuds on the floor]
- Let's go.
[engine roars]
- See, if you had just
gone along with my plan
this wouldn't be happening.
- That's no help to me now,
is it, dude?
[ominous music plays]
[motorcycle booms]
[Brant screams]
[gun fires]
[Dickie-Boy yelps]
[door cracks]
- Clorissa.
[knife thuds against table]
[shotgun fires]
Clorissa, you came back for me.
You're the best sister ever.
- Psst.
Please,
help me too.
[knife slashes into flesh]
[Dickie-Boy screams]
[Dickie-Boy gurgles]
[Dickie-Boy growls ]
- Godddamn it.
- What's happening?
Are we too late?
- Not if I can help it.
[Dickie-Boy growls]
You and your brother
get outta here.
- But, don't you--
- Get outta here,
goddamn it.
Alright you motherfuckers.
This time I'm taking you
to hell myself.
[lighter clicks]
[dramatic music plays]
[demon growls]
[explosion booms]
[flames hiss]
[demons howl]
[lightning cracks]
[birds chirp]
- Hey, look it's Boozer.
Hey,
hey you made it.
[Boozer whimpers]
You like me now.
- Do you have the keys?
- Yeah,
fuck.
- So you wanna go to Denny's?
- No.
- You sure.
- Yeah.
[ominous piano music plays]
- That should help you
sleep tonight.
I can't imagine what
you've been through.
The whole sorority house
is just sick about it.
But on the bright side,
looks like you'll get a 4.0
for this semester. [laughs]
I'm going to let you
get some rest.
Sweet dreams.
[cross scrapes floor]
[Boozer barks]
- What's up, buddy?
Boozer.
[Boozer growls]
[Clorissa screams]
Down Boozer, down.
[Boozer snarls]
[techno music plays]
["Show Me Love" by Coolio]
[MultiCom Jingle]