♪ This is my world ♪
♪  Four walls and a view  ♪
♪ I stare at the ceiling ♪
♪ Chasing these feelings ♪
♪ Around in my head ♪
♪ I'm so confused ♪
♪ Constantly wishing ♪
♪ For what
I've been missing ♪
♪ In my life ♪
♪ I learn to be strong ♪
♪ When the walls
are crumbling ♪
♪ All around my heart ♪
♪ You might say
I feel lost and found ♪
I'm all turned around ♪
♪ This is the first time
that I know who I am ♪
♪ 'Cause now my feet
are on solid ground ♪
♪ Before I didn't know
up from down  ♪
♪ It won't be long
till I find ♪
♪ Where I'm going now ♪
♪ I must confess ♪
♪ I was a mess ♪
♪ I tried not to show it ♪
♪ Didn't want them
to know it ♪
♪ 'Cause everyone has ♪
♪ Their own cross
to bear ♪
♪ And mine is
the waiting ♪
♪ For everything
to fall back ♪
♪♪ [fades]
Do you ever feel like
every time you turn around,
your life is being
flipped upside-down?
That nothing you ever
expect to happen ever does?
My name's Alice,
and welcome to my world.
Hey. Come on, Al.
We need a hand.
Thinking about
your mom?
I feel like we're
leaving her here..
No, it's just the memories
that are here.
You know,
wherever we go,
she'll be with us.
Do we really
have to move?
It's gonna be great.
Before you know it,
Silver Spring will
seem like your home.
Oh, and did I mention
there's a great pizza place
about 5 minutes away?
Great reason, Dad.
Got to give me
credit for trying.
Come on.
We got to go.
Up. Lester.
Bye.
See ya.
Here's my girl.
There's enough in here
for everybody.
Okay?
Thanks.
I got that.
Thank you, honey.
I wish you the best.
All right.
Bye.
Bye, sweetheart.
I love you so much.
Take care.
Take care of yourself.
Floss those teeth.
Here's my lovely.
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
Listen, I want you
to call me
if you need anything
at all, honey.
In fact, I want you
to call me from the road.
Does your daddy
have a phone?
We got it.
Don't take
your shoes off.
You never know what's
on the floor of these things.
Okay? Bye, bye.
[Alice]
Bye, Aunt Sally.
[horn honks]
♪ Shining stars ♪
♪ Shining eyes ♪
♪ No time for tears
♪ No time to cry ♪
♪ Sometimes home is ♪
♪ Hard to leave ♪
♪ Go to where your ♪
♪ True heart leads ♪
♪ Sometimes life
has plans for you ♪
♪ Plans you can't control ♪
♪ And sometimes
you just got to go ♪
♪ Go with the flow ♪
♪ It's a long, long road ♪
♪ Starting over ♪
You must be
the new neighbors.
I'm Sheila Price,
and this is my
daughter, Elizabeth.
Hi! I'm Alice!
You look so...
beautiful.
These clothes?
I just threw these rags
on this morning.
I'm Alice.
Hi.
Ugh.
[Mrs. Pierce]
We figured you might
not have time to eat,
so we brought over dinner--
it's homemade meat loaf.
Meat loaf.
Thanks.
We're actually going out
for pizza tonight.
Uh, n-no problem.
You should keep it, though.
Leftovers come in handy.
But it's still hot.
I'm sure someone
would take it.
Oh, of course.
We'll eat it.
Thank you very much.
I'm Ben McKinley.
Sheila Price.
We really appreciate this.
Looks good.
Just let us know
if you need anything.
Hey, maybe we can get
the girls together sometime.
That would be wonderful.
Bye.
It's not like I try
to do embarrassing things.
They just...
happen to me.
How do I learn
to avoid 'em?
All I have are
Dad and Lester
to teach me.
[belching]
You see my problem?
Mom died when I was 5,
so I pretty much
have to figure out
things on my own.
I just never seem
to get 'em right.
Mmm, not bad.
You should ask her out.
She's married.
Could be divorced.
Never date your
neighbor, okay?
If if doesn't work out,
she lives right next door.
What's the worst
that could happen?
Besides, it's not
like you're, you know,
getting any younger.
I'm 42.
Yeah, that's halfway
to the grave.
Lester!
Got to face
the facts, Al.
Dad's days are numbered.
Might as well try to have
a little happiness
while he still can.
Lester, do you really
expect me to take
dating advice
from someone
that shaved their head
to get a girl
who broke up with him
a week later?
Hey, I like it, okay?
Plus, I'm just
trying to help.
Okay, you want to help?
Take your sister
to the mall tomorrow,
get some school clothes.
Yes!
♪♪
Who's the new girl?
I don't know,
but I hope she's
in my class.
Nice outfit.
You look so cool.
You want to come to
my house after school?
I don't understand why we
can't get your school clothes
at Kmart like we always do.
Because some of us have
a sense of fashion.
Okay, these
are the smallest
ones they have.
These don't fit.
No kidding.
I don't know.
Your body must just
be weird or something.
You're not
helping, Lester!
This is the boys' section.
She should be shopping
in the girls' department.
How was I
supposed to know?
Come on.
Hey, what do boys know
about clothes anyway?
Nothing.
I can hear you.
Oh, my gosh!
Al, still alive?
I'm not coming out.
Not ever.
He's gone.
I can still hear
him breathing.
[chuckles]
That's just
your imagination.
Come on.
Could've been worse.
Could've been you standing
there in your underpants.
Look, I'm sorry
I got dirt on your hand
and didn't want
your mom's meat loaf,
but I don't know
anyone else at
this school,
and I wish
you'd just talk
because I'm
really scared.
Me too.
You are?
Well, then we'll get
through this together,
all right?
All right.
All 6th graders
into the auditorium.
The door's
to your left.
All 6th graders,
the door's
to your left.
This is where we get assigned
our homeroom teachers.
They teach us everything
but math and science.
That's Miss Cole.
She's supposed
to be really nice.
And that's Mr. Weber.
He's cool too.
And that is Mrs. Plotkin.
Everyone says she's mean.
That is so funny.
I have to be
in Miss Cole's class.
I mean, look at her.
She's beautiful
and smart and confident.
She even dresses
the way I wish I could.
There's no way
I would be such a loser
if I could just learn
from her.
Okay, everybody,
please listen.
Each teacher will read
a list of students.
When you hear your name,
please line up in front
of your teacher.
I'll begin.
Gary Anderson,
David Bower,
Stephanie Brooks,
Joshua Gluckman,
Gillian Lambert,
Patrick Loughton,
Alice McKinley,
Judy MacInerney,
Amy Roger,
Brendan Scott,
Brianna Trenton,
Julia Turner,
Michelle Winston,
Charlie Williams,
Hey.
and Leslie Woods.
Don't I know you?
I don't think so.
I'm new.
What-- You're that girl
from the store.
Oh, my gosh!
[books thud]
His name's Patrick,
and he doesn't care at all
that I've seen him
in his underwear.
What am I supposed
to say now?
"Were those
Fruit of the Looms?"
[shudders]
Guys are weird.
Good morning.
I'm Mrs. Plotkin,
and as you all know
by now, I'm considered
the toughest
6th grade teacher.
Well, it's true.
I believe in challenging
my students.
You may not
like it now,
but in 10 years you'll
probably thank me.
Alice.
Is that correct?
I think I'm in
the wrong class.
Wrong class?
No, can't be.
You're on my class list.
Okay, so--
No, I'm supposed to be
in Miss Cole's class.
My dad called weeks ago.
I'm certain
the list is wrong.
The names are generated
through a computer
and chosen randomly,
Alice.
Perhaps your father
misunderstood.
No, I'm really supposed
to be in Miss Cole's room.
That's what he told me.
Perhaps you'd like
to take it up
with Mr. Edgecombe,
the principal.
Yes.
Come on up here.
Get your hall pass.
Come on.
He's right down the hall.
Go, quick.
Go, go.
His office
is right down
the hall that way.
What can I do
for you?
I know names
are chosen randomly,
but my dad said he
really wanted me
to be in Miss Cole's class,
'cause he said that
she's cool and confident,
and he said that she's
the most amazing person ever,
so he really wanted me
to be in her class.
Your dad said that, right?
Okay, when was this?
Last week, um...
because we just moved here.
Well, if you are
new to our school,
you wouldn't know
very much
about any of our teachers,
now, would you?
We found it's best
not to play
musical chairs
with our classrooms.
And I like to believe
that all 3
of our 6th grade teachers
are excellent, Alice.
Now...
I'm sure that if you
put forth the effort,
you'll find that
you and Mrs. Plotkin
will get along just fine.
All right?
[Miss Cole]
Okay. Joke of the day.
What did baby corn say
to mommy corn?
I don't know. What?
"Where's popcorn?"
[all laughing]
I know what
I just did was wrong,
and I should never lie,
but when I look
at Miss Cole,
I can't help myself.
That's awesome.
Okay, Hailey,
your turn.
So, how was
the first day?
Killer.
Guys are cool,
girls are hot,
and I'm already
talking about
starting a band.
Right on.
How about you, Alice?
Well, I got elected
class president
after being there
for 5 minutes.
Wow.
Congratulations.
I'm kidding, Dad.
I have no friends,
and I got the worst teacher
in the whole school.
I just want to go home.
I thought you
wanted pizza.
No, our real home.
Okay.
This is our home now.
I explained to you guys
how important it is for me
to own that
music store, okay?
It was the first day.
I'm sure it'll get better.
I don't know anyone.
I feel like a freak.
Making friends
is the hard part,
but I'm sure that
you will, and soon.
I'm not like Lester.
He already has a band
and a bunch
of groupies.
Yeah, but when
he was your age,
he was very shy.
Mom and I, we decided
he was so immature,
we'd keep him
back a year.
You said I got
the chicken pox
and fell behind
in school.
Well, now you're old enough
to know the truth.
Thanks, Dad.
You just made my day.
That's funny.
Feel better now?
A little.
But Mrs. Plotkin
still stinks.
Oh, look.
Hey, Pamela,
this is Alice.
Patrick is telling
all the guys at school
to watch out for you.
No, that was just
a mistake, that's all.
Okay, I maybe saw
his underwear.
[chuckles]
That's great.
Wait until I tell everyone.
Hey, listen to what
the new girl
has to say about
Patrick...
No, I didn't mean
for you--
[gasps]
[laughing, chattering]
Yeah.
Things are really
looking up.
[Mrs. Plotkin]
I always like
to end the day by
reading a book
to my class.
Every year we start
with my favorite novel,
The Adventures
of Tom Sawyer
by Mark Twain.
There's got to be
another way that I can
get in Miss Cole's class.
"'Tom? Tom?
"'What's gone with
that boy, I wonder.
Tom?'"
"The old lady pulled
her spectacles down
"and looked over them
around the room.
"Then she put them up
and looked under them.
[snoring]
"She seldom or never
looked through them
"for so small a thing
as a boy.
"They were her state pair,
the pride of her heart,
[snoring loudly]
and were built for style,
not service."
Alice!
[children chuckling]
[bell rings]
Okay, kids, don't forget
to read the first chapter
in your American history
book for tomorrow.
Alice, I'd like
to speak with you.
Sit, please.
You know, it's apparent
you don't want to be
in this class.
And quite frankly,
with the behavior
you're carrying on,
I don't particularly
want you in my class.
Sorry.
I'm going to have
to schedule
a meeting
with your parents.
No.
You leave me no choice.
My dad just opened
a new store.
He's really busy.
Well, then,
your mother's gonna have
to come by herself then
if he can't make it.
My mother's...dead.
Oh.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Mrs. Plotkin,
I'm sorry for the way I acted,
and I'll never do it again.
Just please,
don't make me tell my dad.
I don't usually do this,
but I'm gonna give you
another chance.
But don't make me
regret it.
I won't.
Oh, Alice?
Here's something
I thought you might like.
The theatre club is putting on
a musical this season,
and the teacher in charge
is Miss Cole.
Really?
Really.
First meeting's
this Thursday afternoon.
Thanks.
Hey, Al. How you doing?
What do you think of the store?
Cool.
Hey, can I join
theatre club?
It meets at school
2 days a week.
Sure. Yeah.
You'll probably make
some new friends that way.
Okay. Can you
just sign here?
Yeah.
I already
filled it out.
Hey, can I look
at the gift shop
for a minute?
Yeah. Loretta, this
is my daughter, Alice.
Could you help her out?
Sure, Mr. McKinley.
So, you're
Lester's sister.
You know Lester?
I have biology
with him.
He's pretty hot.
That's completely wrong.
I mean, Lester?
Ew!
[exhales]
♪♪ [loud rock]
What is that?
♪ Jenny got a fever ♪
What's going on?
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Whoo! Yeah!
Lester, what
are you doing?
Oh, what's up, Al?
Hey, meet the guys.
This is Matt on the drums,
Caleb on the "key-tar,"
we got Pete on bass,
and this is Joe.
We're the Naked Nomads.
"The Naked Nomads"?
Well, it was kind
of hot down here,
so we decided to take
our shirts off.
And we don't have
any place to play,
so we're really
like nomads.
"Naked Nomads."
What do you think?
I think it's great you found
friends as strange as you.
Hey, don't you have
a dressing room
to barge into?
Well, at least I wasn't
held back 'cause I'm
a social loser.
[guys chuckling]
Hey, out. Now.
All right, guys,
let's play.
Two, three, four!
Oh, no,
you look so cute.
I'm serious.
I don't look good at all.
Hey, Alice.
I didn't know
you wanted to be
in the theatre club.
Oh, sure,
I wouldn't miss it.
Oh, did you act
in your other school?
Well, no,
but there's always
a first time.
I've been taking
voice lessons
all summer
so I'll be ready
for the auditions.
Hi, Patrick.
There's a seat right
here next to me.
Hey, Pamela.
Hey, Elizabeth.
You know Alice,
don't you?
I'm not speaking
to him.
Why not?
"Why not"?
Because I don't talk
to people
who spread vicious rumors
around the entire school
and tell them
I'm a peeping tom,
when it's perfectly obvious
that the whole thing
was a complete accident.
That's...why not.
Well, then, who told
the whole school
what kind of underwear
I have?
That wasn't me!
I think you're
both being silly.
Wow, we certainly have
a good-sized group for
the theatre club this year.
As most of you know
we will be putting together
a school musical this year--
"The Princess and the Frog."
And we've even managed
to rent a local theatre
for the performance,
so this will really be
a special production.
Here. Pass this around.
There will be 2 lead roles,
the Princess
and the Frog Prince,
and I'll be working with them
on an individual basis
for extra rehearsals to work
on the musical numbers.
So the auditions
are next Wednesday,
and I'll see you all then.
So break a leg.
Yea!
I'm going to have
a whole dance
choreographed
for the song.
Are you coming, Alice?
In a minute.
Hi. Miss Cole?
Oh, hi.
Um, my name's Alice.
Alice McKinley.
I just wanted
to let you know
how excited I am to be
in theatre club.
I'm gonna try out
for the Princess role.
Well, that's great.
I wish you the best
of luck.
Oh, um, I'd also like
for you to have this.
Oh.
It's from
my dad's store.
It's for your hair.
It's lovely.
Thank you.
It's in the shape
of musical notes
'cause of the theme
of the musical
and everything.
Of course, of course.
That's great.
Are you trying to
bribe me, Alice?
No, no, I promise.
[chuckles]
I'm only kidding.
Whose class are you
in this year?
Mrs. Plotkin.
Oh. Well,
that's...nice.
Yeah.
Well, hey, you're gonna
have some fun in our club
this year, right?
Yeah.
Well, thank you very much
for the present, Alice.
I'll see you
next week?
Good.
♪♪
[doorbell chimes]
Thank you, Alice.
Whatever would I do
without you?
Probably just be
a loser, Dad.
Hmm.
Alice!
Is this your dad?
He is so handsome!
Not as beautiful
as you, Miss Cole.
Well, it's all due to
the wonderful barrette
that Alice gave me.
Hmm.
You're doing what?
I'm auditioning for
the school musical,
"The Princess and the Frog."
[scoffs]
As what, the lily pad?
Lester.
No, the Princess.
Well, you know, Al,
if you don't get
the lead role,
it's not the end
of the world.
But I want to play the lead.
I mean, look at our family.
You play all sorts
of instruments,
Lester plays...
whatever Lester plays,
and didn't you say
that Mom's a really
good singer?
Yes, but--
So it's in my genes.
Something I can't
even mess up.
I'll be a natural.
Ben McKinley?
Is that you?
Kelly?
I can't believe it.
You remember me?
What are you
doing here?
I live in Silver Spring now.
I have a law practice
in Tacoma Park.
What are you
doing here?
I thought I'd be
hearing your songs
on the radio by now.
No. No, actually,
the band broke up
a few years ago.
But, um, I own this place.
We bought it
a couple weeks ago.
Great place.
Right. Oh, right, yeah.
This is my son, Lester,
and my daughter,
Alice.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Well, you'll all have
to come by sometime
for dinner
with your wife.
My wife passed away
a few years ago.
Oh.
I'm so sorry
to hear that.
Well, um, you and the kids
will have to come by then
for dinner.
We can barbecue.
That'd be great.
Here's my card.
Give me a call sometime
so we can get together.
Yeah, I'll, uh...
I'll do that.
Come on,
I'll walk you out.
Do you know
your dad was
the hottest guy
at Lincoln High?
Every girl in school
wanted to date him.
Hottest guy in school?
Ew!
Hey, Lester.
Oh, hey, uh....
Loretta.
Right, yeah.
I knew that.
I was wondering
if you could
help me move some boxes
up from the storeroom.
Of course.
[chuckles]
♪♪
This is more
than I can take.
What are you
doing here?
Aunt Sally!
[laughing]
Hi.
Well, I just thought
I'd drive over
and see how
you all are doing.
Yeah? From Chicago?
Milt and I were in Virginia
visiting his brother.
What, I need an excuse now
to come and see my family?
How did you get in?
The side door
was open.
Ben, that is very
careless, honey.
With children around?
Yeah, what are
you doing vacuuming?
You don't have to do that.
No offense, hon,
but the place was
in dire need.
I'm not even gonna ask
when the last time was
that you vacuumed.
We all have
pretty busy lives.
Oh, no, I know that, honey.
I'm not blaming you.
My goodness.
I know what an impossible
situation this is for you.
Working a full-time job,
trying to take care of
two children without
any help at all.
Uh, I'm not a child.
Aw. I know you don't
think so, honey.
Sally...
Wait a minute.
You didn't wear
those jeans to school,
did you, honey?
What's wrong with these?
What kind of impression are
you gonna give your teachers
if you dress like
a homeless person?
And Alice,
hasn't anyone shown you
how to use an iron?
Sally...
I appreciate what it is
that you're trying to do
for us, I really do,
and I know
it only comes
from the goodness
of your heart,
but we are quite capable
of taking care of ourselves.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm just trying to
help, that's all.
I know.
And you can help us.
Just, uh, leave that vacuum
there and let's go to dinner.
What do you say?
Oh, well!
All right.
Sure.
I don't know why
Dad stopped her
from vacuuming.
I mean, there's
a whole pile of laundry
she could've done too.
So, want to come over
and make brownies?
My mom can help us.
I'd love to,
but Mrs. Plotkin
loaded us with tons
of homework.
Oh. I feel bad for you.
Me too.
Still coming to
my party on Saturday?
Of course.
Wouldn't miss it.
Hey, girls.
Hey, Pamela.
Want to come over
and make brownies?
Sorry, I can't.
Mother and I are
going shopping
for an outfit
for the auditions,
and then she's
taking me to my
voice lesson.
Wow. You really want
the part, don't you?
Well, I just want
the best person to win.
Me.
No offense, girls.
[off-key]
♪ There-- There's ♪
♪ There's... ♪
♪ There... ♪
What are you doing?
Murdering a cat?
I'm rehearsing!
[chuckles]
You're kidding, right?
Al, you've had
3 piano lessons.
How could you possibly
find the right notes?
Let's see this.
Okay.
♪♪ [humming]
All right,
sing this note.
♪♪ [hums note]
[off-key]
♪ There-- There's ♪
♪♪ [hums note]
You can't hear the difference?
I mean, you're not even close.
You're not helping!
Mom was a good singer.
I can be one too.
[sighs]
Al, come on.
I didn't--
Just forget it!
Sorry.
What is going on?
Oh, Alice.
Just tried to help her
with some singing,
and she got mad at me.
Dad, why didn't you ever
tell her she can't sing?
'Cause I don't
know that for sure.
And neither do you.
The last time we heard her sing
was in the second grade.
And she was awful.
Well, that was
4 years ago.
You know, and kids grow.
When you were 10,
you couldn't even
hit a baseball.
If I tell her she can't sing,
she'll give up on herself
before she even
takes the chance.
Okay. But if
this blows up,
it's on you.
Oh, wow!
[giggles]
Thanks, Alice.
It's fantastic.
Squeeze her arm.
She talks.
Hey, Elizabeth.
Are you ready to party?
I love it!
I got you a present from
Build-A-Bear Workshop too,
except mine sings.
I bet I know whose
voice it is too.
♪ Happy birthday,
Elizabeth ♪
What are you doing?
Oh, I spilled something.
Those are pancakes,
not napkins.
Look, everyone.
Alice is wiping her hands
with moo shu pork.
[all laughing]
It's the most hilarious thing
I've seen in my entire life!
[bell rings]
Good morning.
First up,
hand in your essays.
Pass 'em down.
Oh, no.
I didn't...forget to.
Now yours.
Thank you.
Come on!
[exhales]
I'm dead.
Alice, is there
a problem?
Yes, Mrs. Plotkin.
Where's your paper?
Forgot to do it.
Excuse me.
I didn't hear that.
I forgot to do it.
I see.
Wasn't I very clear
when I gave
this assignment
that there would be
absolutely
no excuses tolerated
for not doing
the assignment?
You did.
And you still chose
not to do it?
I didn't mean to.
I was busy.
I was practicing
for my audition,
and then there was
Elizabeth's birthday...
Alice, you've
left me no choice
but for the next
2 Thursdays,
you will come in here
after class
and focus
and write the paper.
But theatre club meets
on Tuesdays and Thursdays!
Then I guess you're
going to have to miss
a couple of meetings.
I can't miss
the rehearsals,
especially if I'm
gonna be the star.
[students chuckling]
Would you like to go
visit Mr. Edgecombe?
Do it.
I dare you.
Mrs. Plotkin,
you must release
my star immediately!
We need her
in rehearsals!
Well, she can't
because she has to
serve her detention.
[chuckling]
No, no, Mrs. Plotkin.
As the star of our show,
we need Alice.
It's much more important
than your detention.
I'm sorry,
but you've been overruled.
Let's go, girls.
I'll get you yet,
Alice McKinley.
Just you wait,
you little...
So, Alice, would
you like to go see
the principal again?
No, Mrs. Plotkin.
Oh, Alice,
I'm glad you're here.
Listen, I need to give
you some money to order
dinner out tonight.
I'm gonna be
a little late.
You're going out tonight?
Yeah, just dinner
with a friend.
That woman?
Kelly.
Is it, like,
a date?
Kind of.
Okay. I guess
that's okay with me.
You sure?
Mm-hmm.
Great.
Hey, can you sign this?
What is it?
It's a detention slip.
Alice!
It's Mrs. Plotkin.
I was a little late for
a report. That's all.
I thought we agreed that
this theatre club thing
wasn't gonna interfere
with your schoolwork.
It didn't, Dad.
I just forgot.
I think you're gonna have
to forget the theatre club
until the schoolwork
gets in order.
Dad, tomorrow are
the final auditions.
I'll stay up all night
and write this report.
I'll write
an extra hundred words.
I promise. Just--
I'll never do it again.
Please?
150 words.
125.
Deal.
Last time.
Mm-hmm.
Thanks.
♪♪ [piano]
[off-key]
♪ Someday I'll find her ♪
♪ And I will ♪
♪ Hold her tenderly ♪
♪ The sun will shine
in her eyes ♪
♪ And brighten
with every beat ♪
[on-key]
♪ Someday I'll find her ♪
Next up,
Pamela Jones.
♪♪ [piano]
♪ There's a spirit
that lives inside ♪
♪ You can see it
within my smile ♪
♪ Through the rainbow that
shines above in the sky ♪
♪ I know I'm not alone ♪
♪ I just close my eyes ♪
♪ And think of you ♪
♪ I'll show the world
They'll feel it too ♪
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ I feel my wings ♪
♪ Oh, let my free spirit ♪
♪ Soar ♪
♪ I reach up high ♪
♪ And break right through ♪
♪ Oh, I don't see ♪
♪ Any doors ♪
[applause]
That was wonderful,
Pamela.
Thank you.
All right. Next up,
Alice McKinley.
♪♪ [piano]
[off-key]
♪ There's a spirit
that lives inside ♪
♪ You can see it
within my smile ♪
♪ Through the rainbow that
shines above in the sky ♪
♪ I know I'm not alone ♪
[on-key]
♪ I just close my eyes
and think of you ♪
♪ I'll show the world
They'll feel it too ♪
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ I feel my wings ♪
♪ I'll let my free ♪
♪ Spirit soar ♪
♪ I reach up high ♪
♪  And break right through ♪
[off-key]
♪ Oh, I ♪
♪ Don't see any ♪
[on-key]
♪ Doors ♪
[crowd roaring]
Thank you.
[Miss Cole]
Thank you, Alice.
It was very...
nice.
Oh, yes!
You did it!
[exclaims]
Oh, my God.
Alice is Frog #3!
A frog?
What, I'm a frog?
Was I that bad?
Well, no
offense, Alice,
but you were
pretty awful.
I thought
I sounded good.
[chuckles]
Then you'd better
have your hearing checked,
'cause you didn't
sing one note right.
Elizabeth,
was I that bad?
Well,
you were
pretty awful.
No.
Al, can I come in?
I, uh--
I guess
you're still upset
about not
getting the part, huh?
Kids are saying
I'm the worst
singer ever.
Okay. So maybe
you're a little
tone deaf. So what?
Wait. You knew that
I couldn't sing?
Well,
honestly, Alice, um,
in the second grade,
you had a little trouble
carrying a tune.
Why didn't you tell me
that I stink?
Because I thought that
with a little practice,
when you got older
you'd be better.
You've ruined my life!
It's not as bad as it seems.
I mean, in a few days,
no one will remember.
I'll remember for
the rest of my life.
I thought...
You're supposed
to help, Dad.
It's bad enough that
I don't have a mom.
Sometimes I feel like
I don't have a father either.
[exhales]
Hey. You want to
go out to dinner?
Your choice.
Food is not
gonna help, Dad.
Okay.
♪ Here I am ♪
I'll be downstairs
if you need me.
♪ Null and void ♪
♪ And just
an empty shell ♪
♪ Calling out to you ♪
♪ So let me
take your hand ♪
♪ And take me
where you will ♪
♪ And help me understand ♪
♪ 'Cause only you can make ♪
♪ Something out of nothing ♪
♪ Something out of ♪
♪ Me ♪
I know I shouldn't
be mad at my dad,
but why didn't
he tell me?
Now I feel
worse than ever.
I just really wish
my mom was here tonight.
"Tom was a glittering
hero once more;
"the pet of the old,
the envy of the young.
"His name even went
into immortal print,
"for the village paper
magnified him.
"There were some
that believed he would
be president yet,
if he escaped hanging."
[bell rings]
Hey, Alice, did you hear
about your new nickname?
"Ribbit."
[children laughing]
That's so funny!
I thought you might
like to have this.
You did a very good job,
once you remembered
the assignment.
Would've been an "A,"
but you turned it in late.
You know,
everyone has their
own talent, Alice.
And when you set your
mind to it, you have
quite a way with words.
Thanks.
I heard about
the musical,
and I'm sorry you didn't
get the part you wanted.
I'm kind of glad
I have detention.
I'd rather be here than
have to face everyone.
Tell you what.
Since you already
finished your report,
why don't you help me
set up the bulletin board
for the Read-A-Thon?
Okay.
♪ I've dreamt this ♪
♪ I've longed this ♪
♪ I've lived this
over and over again ♪
♪ It's right here ♪
♪ It found me ♪
♪ Surrounding me ♪
♪ Over and over again ♪
♪ I used to wonder why ♪
♪ This fire burns inside ♪
♪ But I no longer try ♪
♪ To hide what ♪
♪ I know was there ♪
♪ All the time ♪
Dad.
What are you doing?
Oh, I was just, uh,
playing a song.
Sounds kind of
girly to me.
[woman chuckles]
I think it sounds great.
Alice, you remember Kelly?
Sure.
Hi, Alice.
Um, I'm gonna
head upstairs.
I have a lot of homework.
Terrific.
I'll be up soon.
[Kelly]
Bye, Alice.
Bye.
Everything all right
with her?
We had a fight
last night, and, um,
I just never
know if I'm doing
the right thing or not.
There is no "right thing"
with an 11-year-old girl.
Oh, Alice,
I wanted to
speak to you.
Since you've finished
all your work,
I figured you could
skip detention today
and go to play
rehearsal, okay?
Thanks, Mrs. Plotkin,
but I'm only Frog #3.
Oh, I know
Miss Cole feels
every part is
very important.
And I thought you
were looking forward
to performing in front
of the whole school.
I didn't really care
about the part.
I just...
I wanted to be with...
Miss Cole?
Well, if so, why,
you could do that.
Really?
Well, I'm sure she's
bogged down
with a lot of work
doing this musical.
Maybe you could help her
after school like you did
for me.
You think so?
It's worth a shot.
Why don't you ask her?
She's over there.
Thanks.
I think I'll do that.
Hi, Miss Cole.
Oh, hi, Alice.
Hi.
I was wondering
if I could maybe
help you decorate,
or if you need any
help with anything.
Sure, sure.
Yeah, I could
use some help.
Okay.
[chattering]
Hey.
You and Dad okay?
I guess.
I think you
should give him a chance.
He's trying the best he can.
What's up with him
and that Kelly lady?
I don't know.
I think he likes her.
Well, he wouldn't
get married, would he?
Who knows?
But you'd better get
used to the idea, Al,
'cause it could happen.
If Dad was gonna
marry someone,
they'd have to be
really, really special.
Thanks.
Hey, Marilyn.
Sorry I forgot
to tell you
I'd be working today,
but maybe we can get
together later.
That's okay.
I'm here to see Lester.
Hey, Lester.
Hey, Marilyn.
What are you doing here?
I was just finishing some
shopping down the street,
and I thought I'd stop by
to see if maybe you wanted
to walk home together.
[whispering]
I'm really busy
right now.
Um, can I call you back,
like, later?
Why are you whispering?
Oh, I don't want
to bother the customers.
Um, I got to go
downstairs, but...
Lester,
why is Marilyn here?
Uh-oh.
I-I don't know.
Are you seeing her?
Kind of.
What's that supposed
to mean?
Yeah, what is that
supposed to mean?
I didn't even know
you guys were friends.
Well, we are.
Yeah, we are.
And we're also friends
with just about every
girl in school.
Who are all going
to know
what a slime ball
you are.
Is there something
I can do?
How about dropping dead?
You want to go to
the movies tonight?
Sure.
I get off at 6.
I'll come by.
Great.
Guess there's a downside
to making friends easily.
Okay.
I'm done, Miss Cole.
That's excellent work, Alice.
I just wish I could
take you home
and have you straighten up
my apartment.
Oh, I'd be happy to.
I'm only kidding.
Well, not about me
being a slob.
I'm a total mess.
Why? You always
look so neat.
Mmm, it's all
an illusion.
You know us girls.
We have our ways, right?
Right.
You know, Alice,
I was just considering
changing a part of the play,
and I think you might be
perfect for the part I need.
Really?
Yeah.
You'll still be a frog,
but I was considering
giving one of the frogs
a larger role.
The Frog Prince's
right-hand man--
or woman, in this case.
It won't be much of a change
from what you're doing now,
but you'll have a great moment
in the first act.
A small dance number.
Would you be up for it?
Definitely.
Great.
Well, then, I'll see you
at rehearsal later
in the week.
I'm really looking
forward to this.
Me too.
[chuckles]
See you then.
Okay, it may not be
the Princess role,
but it's almost as good.
My own dance solo?
Just 'cause I can't sing
doesn't mean I can't be
a star.
6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Down, down, down.
Head, head.
Jump, jump.
Okay, you try it.
Okay.
[bell rings]
Jump, jump.
That's great.
You're really taking
to this dance.
Well, it's a fun part.
Well, you're
perfect for it.
Um, I could help you
carry all this
back to your room
and put it away.
Ah, that would be
great, Alice.
Thanks so much
for offering.
Miss Cole?
I'll bet you like
musicals, don't you?
Of course I do.
That's why I like trying
to find new and unusual ones
for you kids to perform.
Well, did you know
my dad owns a music
store?
Oh.
And he carries
all types of sheet music
for all types of musicals.
Oh, I'll have
to stop by sometime.
Great. Well, here's
the address,
and I usually help
him on Saturdays.
Maybe I'll stop by
this weekend.
Sometimes I'm so brilliant
it's scary.
I can help too,
Miss Cole.
Wow, I have my choice
of helpers today.
Thank you, Pamela.
You don't have
to stay, Pamela.
I'm sure you're
really busy with all
the extra rehearsals.
Oh, it's not a problem.
I like helping Miss Cole.
Thanks so much
for your help, girls.
I could help wash
the boards, if you want.
Hmm. Well, I suppose they
could use a washing.
I'll take you up
on your offer, Alice.
The supply shelves are
looking a little messy.
I could straighten them out.
Well, if you really
want to, Pamela,
but it's not necessary.
You've already done
enough already.
It's okay.
I'd love to help.
I bet you do.
I'm so glad Pamela
offered to help
this afternoon.
Now I have time
to go shopping
with you, Alice.
I'll just text the girls
to meet us at the mall.
♪♪
♪ I'll be looking
till I finally get there ♪
♪ Nothing's standing in
my way this time, I swear ♪
♪ Till then you'll find me
having some fun ♪
[screams]
Really, girls,
if you just want
to head home.
We're very enthusiastic
about our cleaning.
Oh.
Al, what are you
still doing here?
I told you
you could go home
about an hour ago.
The music was out of order,
so I'm just alphabetizing it.
Oh. Well,
you'd better
get going soon.
It's getting dark
out there.
Well, I thought
I'd wait for you.
No, honey, I have plans
tonight, remember?
We talked about it.
With Kelly?
Yeah, we, uh...
we kind of have a date.
You don't...love her,
do you, Dad?
[door bell chimes]
You know, it's, um...
It's not like
in the movies, Al.
You don't fall in love
with somebody overnight.
It usually takes
a while.
If my dating is a problem
for you, though, we can
talk about it.
No, I want you
to date again.
I just want you
to find the right woman,
that's all.
So do I.
Miss Cole!
Alice!
Yes!
Well, I made it.
Yes, yes.
Miss Cole, this is
Ben, my dad.
Hi.
He owns this whole
music store.
He's actually into
all types of music.
He was in a band once.
He was the hottest guy.
He's actually dating
again too.
It's been 6 years since
my mom passed away,
so you don't have to
worry about that either.
Alice?
I think that's a little
more information
than Miss Cole
was looking for.
Miss Cole is interested
in everybody.
She's very social.
Right, Miss Cole?
I guess.
So, was there anything
in particular
that you were looking for?
No, I just thought
I'd browse through
your sheet music.
Great. If you
need anything,
just let me know.
In the meantime,
I'd like a word
with Alice.
Of course.
I should be getting
home soon anyway.
I know you mean well, Alice,
and you're trying to help,
but I think it's best
if I pick my own dates.
Dad, she's perfect.
She likes music,
she's smart,
she's beautiful.
She's 15 years
younger than me.
Age is just a state
of mind, Dad.
You're young at heart,
right? Can you please
just talk to her?
I'm sure you'd like her
a lot more than Kelly.
She's hot.
Al, I am not going out
with Miss Cole.
[knock at door]
[Kelly]
Ben?
Hi.
Am I interrupting?
Uh, no.
No, I think, um,
we're good here.
If he thinks I'm just
giving up like that,
he's crazy.
Thanks for the ride.
The mechanic said
my car would be
fixed yesterday,
so it'll probably be
sometime next week.
[chuckles]
My pleasure.
Besides, I had to
find some way
to thank you for
that great dinner.
That feels...very good.
I can't.
What's wrong?
[Ben]
I...I like you.
I mean, I really do.
It's just, um...
my life's kind of
complicated right now.
Ben, Marie has been
gone for 6 years.
I know.
It's time to move on.
It's just, uh,
I just moved here
and I bought
this store,
and my kids,
especially Alice,
she has a lot
going on right now.
What about yourself?
I'm not sure.
I'm not trying to rush
you into anything.
No, you're great.
It's just, um,
like I said,
it's complicated.
I'm not giving up on you.
Just know that.
Dad, what's with
the dead bird?
It's Thanksgiving.
Again I ask, what's
with the dead bird?
We always go out.
Oh, no. Not this year.
Not with Sally
and Milt coming.
No, we're gonna
have a traditional
Thanksgiving dinner
with a traditional
Thanksgiving turkey.
And traditional
food poisoning?
Elizabeth told me
if the turkey's
not properly cooked,
the bacteria could kill us.
Hear that, Dad?
I'm too young to die.
Me too.
Okay, if you're not gonna
help me cook,
then you go upstairs
and clean it up.
I need it in decent shape
by the time they get here.
Smiley girl, you go
do the laundry.
Yes, you.
Okay, it's just
me and you now.
[groans]
Hello. Ooh!
[disposal whirrs]
Ugh!
[retches]
[grunting]
Ow!
Ah! Hot!
[clattering]
No. No, no.
[footsteps approaching]
Laundry's done.
Need anything else?
Uh, yeah.
You know that big
serving platter
that we have?
I think it's probably
in one of those boxes
we haven't unpacked
downstairs.
You've got to be
kidding me.
Ah, there you are.
[Ben]
Alice! Did you
find the platter?
Uh, I got it!
My teacher just
gave me an "A"
for the last English
report I did.
She said I had
a talent for writing.
I'm also in
the school musical.
It's a small part,
but I have
my own dance number,
so it's really important
to the story.
Oh, honey,
that is very good!
Alice, put your napkin
on your lap, hon.
Ben, put your napkin
on your lap.
Lester,
you too, hon.
And what about you, honey?
How are your grades?
Pretty good.
I'm only failing
3 of my classes.
Lester, stop it.
He's doing fine, Sally.
Well, I hope so.
Junior year is
the most important
one for colleges.
I'm not going to college.
I'm going on tour
with my band.
Or joining
the Merchant Marines.
What did I say?
She knows I'm kidding.
Don't you,
Aunt Sally?
Well, of course I do.
But you are going
to college, aren't you?
It's his decision,
not ours.
But do you think
that's wise?
I think that, uh,
everyone should get
to decide for himself
or herself what
their future should be.
But he hasn't even
turned 18 yet.
I don't think
Marie would want that.
I think I know
better than you
what Marie would want;
I am his father.
And if you can't respect
that, I don't think I can
welcome you in this house.
Well...I do know that.
And I respect that, Ben.
And...I'm sorry.
I worry about
them sometimes,
but just because
I love them so much.
I know.
Um, I'm sorry
I raised my voice, Sally.
It's just, we've
been under a lot
of pressure lately,
and, um, I know
how much you love them,
and I can use all
the help I can get.
Well, thank you.
So what do you say
we talk about
something else?
Milton,
how you been?
Great.
My Merchant Marine
application came through
without a hitch.
What?
[giggling]
I got the tickets!
[Ben]
Marie, move closer
to the play poster.
I want to make sure
we remember
what we were seeing
when we're 90.
I think we'll be
lucky enough
to remember
each other's names,
forget about a musical
we saw 70 years ago.
Just think-- Someday
it could be you
starring in this.
Come on,
sing something.
Well, this your dream--
singing on Broadway.
I meant in a theatre,
not on a street corner.
[Ben]
You're too picky.
Go for it.
♪ Just look for me ♪
♪ And I'll be there ♪
♪ In every smile ♪
♪ With every tear ♪
♪ Just look for me ♪
♪ When you're
in trouble, dear ♪
♪ I'll be right there ♪
♪ When you're walking ♪
♪ On air ♪
♪ Just look for me ♪
♪ And I will be ♪
♪ Watching over you ♪
[Ben]
Yeah!
Ah, you are amazing!
What a voice!
I've spent most of my life
missing my mom.
This is the first time
I've really seen her.
I mean, really
have seen her.
She had this whole other
life I never knew about--
all these hopes and dreams
and things she wanted to do--
just like me.
No!
It's our only time
in New York. Come on, please?
Oh, I feel like
such a tourist!
Oh, all right.
Dad!
What are you
doing up?
Dad...
[Ben]
You're so gorgeous.
I love you.
I was just watching...
Those are not
to be watched.
But they're videos of Mom.
Why didn't you tell me
we had those?
Maybe when you're older.
I'm old enough now!
I want to see Mom!
I don't want to
talk about it, Alice.
Go to bed.
You never want
to talk about it.
Please just go upstairs.
You're not the only one
who lost Mom.
Hey, what's wrong?
Dad got mad at me for
watching the videotapes
of Mom.
Did you know
we had those?
Yeah. We used to watch
them all the time when
you were a baby.
Dad really hasn't
been able to watch
them, though, since...
Don't you want
to see them?
Yeah, but not
if it hurts Dad.
When it comes to Dad,
I can't seem to do
anything right.
It's okay, Al.
We're all trying to do
the best we can.
♪♪ [singing scales]
Hey, Alice,
why did the frog jump off
the 10-story building?
I don't know.
He wanted to learn
how to croak.
Just a little
frog humor to
break the tension.
Thanks, I guess.
♪ Feeling all alone ♪
Okay, everyone.
Listen up, listen up.
Okay.
I am sure we're going
to have a great show,
and I wanted
everyone to know
how happy I am
with all of the hard work
you've put into this.
Okay, we have
a full house out there,
so go give 'em your best
and try not to forget
your lines.
All right? Break a leg!
Okay, places, places.
Places, everyone.
Okay, let's go!
♪♪
♪ Waking up
in the morning sun ♪
♪ Feeling all alone ♪
♪ Looking out at
the distance there ♪
♪ Very far from home ♪
♪ Where's the prince
I've been looking for ♪
♪ Searching for
that happy day ♪
♪ Where's the boy who takes
my true heart away ♪
♪ I will show them ♪
♪ Watch me show them
Watch me show them ♪
♪ Why can't they see ♪
♪ Watch me leaping
Watch me keeping ♪
♪ I think I might just
have to kiss him ♪
♪ Has anybody
ever missed him ♪
♪ Don't they all know
that he's the frog prince? ♪
♪ The only frog prince? ♪
♪ Don't take away,
don't take away the best ♪
♪ Years of our lives ♪
Whoa!
[screams]
[all clamoring]
[audience gasping]
You did that on purpose!
This is all your fault!
I'm sorry!
Now, that's entertainment.
Miss Cole,
I'm so embarrassed!
It was horrible!
I know Alice
did it on purpose!
Miss Cole, I'm sorry!
I was just
dancing and then falling.
I really didn't mean it,
and I'm sorry!
Really, Alice!
Why couldn't you
be more careful?
You've ruined the play!
But I didn't mean to.
Okay, look.
I don't want to
hear any excuses.
We'll finish this play
as best we can, okay?
Do you think you can
do that, Pamela?
Yeah.
Good. Now, go back
out on that stage
and finish this
scene, okay?
I think you're finished
for tonight, Alice.
You can wait back here
or go home.
♪♪
It was an accident,
Alice.
There was no way
you could've stopped it.
Miss Cole and Pamela
think I did it on purpose.
That is ridiculous,
and Pamela and Miss Cole
will realize that
once they've calmed down.
Where's your family?
They're still inside.
I can't believe I just
ruined the whole play!
Now you're just talking
silly, you know that?
They've already got
the castle rebuilt,
and you could
hardly even see
the little tear
in Pamela's dress.
It's a little mistake.
One mistake. That's all.
Nothing.
Mrs. Plotkin, I can't
do anything right.
You know every kid your age
feels the exact same way?
It doesn't seem like it.
Well, that's 'cause
they're busy hiding it.
Just like you're
hiding now.
Well, I can't
hide anymore.
You know, I bet
in a few months
this'll all fade away,
and when you're older
you're gonna get a good
laugh at this memory.
I can't imagine ever
laughing about this.
That's 'cause you
weren't watching it.
It's not funny.
No, I know. I know.
A frog knocking down
a castle-- splat.
No, it wasn't funny
at all.
[stifled chuckle]
The tree could've
fallen on Pamela.
And what is more tragic
than a squished princess?
Well, you made it
for me.
Would you do me a favor
and autograph my program?
Personalize it.
So Mrs. Plotkin was right.
The scenery went back up,
Pamela's dress was fixed,
and the show went on.
Pamela even got
a standing ovation.
Today's the theatre
club party,
and I'm not sure
I should even be going.
And I'm getting
a new puppy out of it.
Really?
Yeah, my parents said...
Hi, Alice.
Hi, Patrick.
This party's for
cast and crew only.
You left
the play early.
Leave her alone, Pamela.
Yeah, cut her some slack.
She didn't mean to do it.
Well, how can you be
so sure?
Alice wouldn't do
something like that.
Patrick, why are
you defending her?
'Cause...
she's cool.
Really, Pamela,
I never meant for
any of that to happen.
I might have been a little
jealous that you got the part--
okay, really jealous--
but I would never ruin
the whole play on purpose.
I suppose it would be
difficult to mess up
that badly on purpose.
I mean, who would want
to humiliate themselves
like that
in front of
all those people?
Thanks.
I think.
Alice,
I owe you an apology.
I overreacted last night
and jumped to conclusions.
I'm sorry.
I hope you'll stay
for the party.
And then afterwards
maybe you can help me
clean up a bit?
I'll give you a ride home
if it's too late to walk.
I'd love to stay
and help,
but I actually have
to go meet someone.
Isn't it funny how
I've been trying to be
friends with Miss Cole
just so she could
be my role model
when my real role model was
standing right before me?
Hi, Mrs. Plotkin.
Oh, hi, Alice.
Theatre club was having
a party, so I thought
I'd bring you some cake.
That is so sweet
of you.
You know,
I was just thinking about
taking a little break myself.
Have a seat.
I just want to thank you
for helping me
the other night.
It really made me
feel better.
Oh, it's my pleasure.
I was wondering if
I could come back
and help you
clean the room
in the afternoons.
Oh, that isn't
necessary, hon.
No, I'd like to, really.
I'm trying to say
it won't be necessary
because...
I'm not returning to school
after winter break.
Well, when are
you coming back?
September,
at the earliest.
I've decided to take
a sabbatical.
You know I've
been working here
over 25 years?
I decided I'd like to spend
a little more time at home.
You can't just leave
in the middle of the year.
Well, I know it's not
great timing, Alice,
but that's the way things
work out sometimes.
But I have been
thinking that
if you would still like
to be in Miss Cole's class,
that I could maybe
get Mr. Edgecombe
to agree to transfer
you there.
Due to the circumstances
and all.
I don't want
to be transferred,
and I think what
you're doing is awful!
Alice...
Alice, come back!
Alice, stop.
Please?
I know you're upset,
and I understand that.
But please let me explain
the real reason why
I'm leaving, okay?
You're not going
on sabbatical?
Well, yes, I am,
but not because
I want to.
My doctor
has recommended it.
Your doctor?
You see, Alice,
I have a problem
with my heart.
One of my valves
isn't right.
So they have to do
an operation to fix it.
Are you gonna be
all right?
Well, I certainly
hope so.
I mean, they'll do
the surgery and treatment
and all sorts of therapy
that'll make me
weak and tired,
but in a few months,
the doctor says
I should be fine.
I'm really sorry.
Me too.
But thank you.
[knocking]
Al?
Go away.
Mrs. Plotkin called.
She's worried
about you.
She told me
what happened.
I'm sorry.
Well, I'm not.
Not anymore.
Don't say that.
Why not?
I may not see her again.
Why should I care?
You don't mean that.
Once someone's gone,
they're gone.
What good does it do
to think about them?
It doesn't make them any better.
It only makes you feel sad.
Alice, stop.
Isn't that why
you never want to watch
the videotapes of Mom?
Isn't that why you want
to date Kelly?
'Cause you never want
to think about Mom!
I think about your mother
every moment of my life.
Alice...
there isn't an hour
that goes by
that I don't wonder,
"What would she do?
What would she think?"
I love her more than
anything in the world,
except maybe
you and Lester.
How come we never
talk about her?
How come I haven't
seen the tapes?
It was wrong of me to keep
that stuff from you guys.
I just...
I wanted us
to grow as a family,
not be stuck in the past.
I think about her
all the time,
even though I can't
remember her.
I know you do.
You probably will
your whole life.
I know I will.
Just because
she isn't here,
it doesn't mean that
she's not with us.
She is with us.
That's what makes
us strong.
What about
Mrs. Plotkin?
The thing about Mrs. Plotkin--
she's still alive.
And, yeah, she's gonna
be gone for a while,
but she'll come back.
When she does,
you can call her,
write her nice letters--
I know she'd like that.
I think I'll do that.
Dad, I love you.
I love you too.
And I think
Kelly's pretty cool.
It'd be okay with me if
you wanted to see her again.
As much as
I like Kelly,
I feel like I got a lot
on my plate right now.
But thank you.
[Mrs. Plotkin]
Alice, come on in.
Look at your house!
With all this leisure
time on my hands,
I don't know what
I'm gonna do once I go
back to the classroom.
So you're
coming back?
Absolutely.
The doctor said that
surgery went well,
and he feels
that in maybe...
by next September
I'll be back
in the classroom.
Wow! That's great!
Yeah.
Oh, I have a little
something for you.
Thanks.
Tom Sawyer.
This is the book
that you read to us
in the classroom.
It is.
You know that was
my book from grade school?
It's the first book I read
that I truly loved.
And, um,
with all the trouble
Tom got into, I thought
it sort of
reminded me of you.
[scoffs]
Well, I couldn't
imagine why.
How many marshmallows?
3, please.
[Alice Narrating]
Two days before Christmas,
Lester and the Nomads
played their very
first gig.
Sure, it was for
the Melody Inn
holiday party,
but Lester was too
excited to care.
That is, until he
found out the band would
be playing for free.
♪ Now I know why ♪
Somehow Lester even got
Loretta and Marilyn
to forgive him.
Don't ask me how.
And Aunt Sally
flew in from Chicago.
She actually wanted
to hear Lester's band...
once I told her
they would be
wearing pants.
♪ Now I know why ♪
As for Dad and me,
the talk we had
went a long way
to explaining
a lot of things.
Look, I know I'll
always miss my mom,
but I have my dad and Lester
and all my friends,
and that's enough for me.
♪ I'm so high when she's ♪
♪ When she's around ♪
♪ Jenny got a fever ♪
[crowd cheering]
Alice, your brother is
so cute and talented.
I think he's amazing.
Yeah, he's so sick.
Uh, that's one
word for him.
That was awesome.
We're gonna take
a quick break.
We'll be right back.
I have to go meet him!
Oh!
Here.
Thanks.
So, doing anything
for vacation?
Well, I'm driving up
for a day to visit
my aunt.
You?
Nothing.
Um, well, maybe
we could hang out
sometime.
Sure.
♪♪
Yes.
♪ Walk down the street ♪
♪ Music playing in my ears ♪
♪ Make a step for my seat ♪
♪ Lock myself away
from my fears ♪
♪ And when the music stops ♪
♪ I can feel my soul
just drop ♪
♪ And I, I just got
to hear it playing ♪
♪ I just want
to hear it saying ♪
♪ I just want to
I just got to rock ♪
♪ I just got to rock
to feel the beat ♪
♪ Well, my head keeps bumping
and my heart keeps thumping ♪
♪ The music sounds
so sweet ♪
♪ I just got to rock ♪
♪ Can't you feel the
thunder of the beat? ♪
♪ Well, my head
keeps bumping ♪
♪ And my heart
keeps thumping ♪
♪ The music sounds
so sweet ♪
♪ I just got to rock
and roll all night ♪
♪ Turn it up to 10
and I say all right ♪
♪ Everybody says no
I say yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
[all cheering]
♪♪
[Man]
Background.
You spit everywhere.
You said
I got chicken pox
and you had to--
I fell behind.
You said I got
chicken pox and...
[Man]
And background.
[crash]
[people laughing]
[Man]
Wait on your right.
[Man #2]
Do you want
second take on that?
Second take,
right away.
Second sticks.
This is our Cousin John.
New marker.
How's my hair?
[Woman]
Is that okay? Okay.
[Man]
Give him a mark.
Here we go. And...
Cut.
Mrs. Plotkin,
we must...
Oh! Okay.
[Man]
Quiet. Live mike.
Set.
Mrs...
[all laughing]
Just you wait.
[cackling]
[coughing]
[all laughing]
Boo.
Ow!
Oh, jeez, she clipped
off my eyelash.
[indistinct whispering]
B mike.
[screaming]
It's just me and you now.
Ow! Hey!
Don't bite me! Hey!
[people chattering]
And... cut.
Closed Captioned By
J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA