[music playing]
[suspenseful music]
[watch ticking]
So how about Hawaii?
Hawaii?
We could go somewhere
more exciting.
Hawaii is exciting.
Hawaii is laying on a beach.
[watch ticking]
Look, can we
discuss this tonight?
All right, everybody back up
right now, against the wall,
move, let's go!
Nobody moves, nobody talks.
Against the wall, let's
move, let's move, let's move.
[glass shattering]
[gun shot]
[scream]
[gun shots]
Nobody else move.
That's 30 seconds, all
right, guys, let's go.
[police sirens]
Stay here.
Give me the ring.
- Shit, let's get out of here.
- Not this one.
It's the cops.
Let's move!
Let's go!
Let's go.
Everybody out.
Give it up!
[grunting]
Come on!
[glass shattering]
[gun shot]
[woman gasping]
Come on, get out!
[gun shots]
[groaning]
You're gonna be all right.
Stay calm.
Somebody get an ambulance!
[police sirens]
All right, look, there's
only one guy in that car.
The other three are on foot.
Move, find them, find them!
All right.
I want two choppers in the air.
I want these scumbags.
Where the hell are
the paramedics?
They're on the way.
Well, well, well, if
it ain't the good doctor.
Trouble just seems to always
have a way of finding you,
don't it?
I don't have time
for this, Lopez.
[tires squealing]
[police sirens]
[suspenseful music]
[gun shots]
[explosion]
[hospital workers shouting]
John, we've got
it taken care of.
You want to come
in, go get scrubbed.
John, I got to got to
ask you some questions.
You got 30 seconds
while I get scrubbed.
There were six guys
with ski masks.
We're pretty sure one
guy's name is Kalin.
That's his brother in there.
I've been trying to run
him down for a long time.
Maybe if you spent a little
less time at this hospital,
you could.
How is she?
She'll be all right.
- And the scumbag?
- He'll live.
Too bad.
[suspenseful music]
We have to get Mark.
They'll take her from the
hospital straight to the joint.
We'll get him.
We'll just wait a few
hours til things calm down.
I want that son of bitch to
put him through the window.
First, we get Mark.
Then we worry about
finding that asshole, OK?
Hi.
Still want to go
someplace exciting?
Hawaii's looking
better and better.
Since we've been going
out, you've been hit,
stabbed, and now shot.
What next?
Scud missle.
Right.
I don't think we should
hide anyone in Iraq.
Am I OK?
Well, you had a great doctor.
Oh, did I?
Mm-hmm.
I have some special
treatment for you right now.
Hey, hey, enough of that.
Hi, you guys.
Hi, Julie.
Does it hurt?
I brought you some
stuff, your PJs,
your toothbrush, and Boo Boo.
[laughter]
Thanks, Brad.
How you doing?
I'm fine really.
Come on, guys.
She needs to rest.
Yeah, so what kind of rest she
was getting when we walked in?
Bye bye.
How is she, really?
The bullet passed
through the shoulder.
She's lost some blood,
but she'll be fine.
Holy tomato, you should
be a fashion model.
Look at that beautiful skin.
You like Chinese food, huh?
Whoa!
[crashing noise]
I never saw anybody
as beautiful as you.
Oh.
I planned that one.
It's like a joke.
You the one that's
really beautiful.
Did you know I taught Bruce Lee?
I was his teacher.
Come on.
I even know to cook
Chinese food [inaudible],,
I see you later.
Did you know that pregnant
women is very beautiful?
I mean, sexy also.
I'll be home at
10:00, I promise.
Bye.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
Looks like you're going to
have to postpone the wedding.
We'll see.
John, look, I know you're
telling everyone she's fine,
but you know as well as I do if
the internal bleeding starts--
She'll be fine.
[suspenseful music]
Call 911.
Everybody out.
Get out.
Go.
Come on.
Everybody out.
Well, well, look
what we got here.
You don't want to move him.
Why not?
Because your friend here--
My brother.
Your brother has
a severe concussion.
He could die.
What are you, a doctor?
Yeah.
Good.
Since you're the one
that messed him up,
looks like you're going
to be the one that comes
with this to take care of him.
Shit, the police!
[gun shots]
[shouting]
All right, drop
it, right there.
This ain't over, man.
You're dead, you hear me?
You're dead.
You killed my brother, man.
You killed my brother.
You're dead.
Come on, scumbag.
LOPEZ: We got four,
including Kalin.
JOHN: There were five.
The other one is six-one,
black hair, ponytail.
We're searching the
place from top to bottom.
I hate to say this,
but you did a good job.
My God!
Lopez!
They-- goddammit, they got her.
Calm down.
Don't tell me to calm down.
We'll handle this, all right?
Yeah, right.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
It's Johnny.
Listen to me.
OK.
We'll get all the guys together.
Don't worry.
We'll find her.
All right.
We'll all meet up at
the hospital 6:00.
LOPEZ: I put a
trace on his phone.
Two cars stake out the house.
I'll be there in a half
hour, 45 minutes tops, OK?
John, here's what
we're going to do.
It's going to take a couple
of hours to process them.
Then they'll take them
down to the lock up.
That's when we find out
where they've taken her.
And what if he won't talk?
I'll make him talk.
[scoffs]
[suspenseful music]
[police radio chatter]
[tires squealing]
[car stuttering]
[train honking]
Oh shit!
[explosion]
Jesus Christ.
What are you trying
to do, kill me?
Hey, I got you out, didn't I?
I want him, man.
I got his girlfriend.
Come on.
[car starting]
[explosion]
[music playing]
[hospital intercom]
Phil.
Hey, what's up, Doc?
What are you in
here for this time?
It's only a couple in
the leg, one in the chest.
Man, that was a bad one.
I heard about
Kalin and Predator.
Predator?
The one who took
your old lady.
Where is he?
He's underground, man.
What does that mean?
Well, you know, when
you got an old building,
and you knock it down,
and you put up a new one.
But underneath it's
still the basement
and shit of that old
building, that's underground.
Which building is it?
Man, there's
hundreds of them all
connected underground with
basements and tunnels, man.
Yeah, but you don't
wanna go down there, man.
Why not?
Man, there's all kind
of weird gangs down there.
John, I have to take him.
All right.
Could you bring him please?
Hey, Doc, I got
some more bad news.
Kalin has escaped
Jesus Christ, Lopez!
Can't you do anything right?
Doctor, you have a phone call.
Hello?
Who is this?
An eye for an eye.
That's the way it is
in the underground.
That's our law.
You killed my brother.
[julie whimpering]
I kill your fiance slowly.
Listen to me.
I ask you, what
could be more fair?
Leave her out of this.
I'm the one you want.
Well, you did cost me
a lot of money today.
Let's say you bring me $250,000.
I'll trade you.
Her for the money, and you.
John, stall for time.
It's going to take
time to raise that much.
Well, I'm calling
your house at noon,
before we start dismembering
your pretty little girl.
Don't do it, Johnny!
I'm trying to use the phone!
Pardon me, your wife
was being a bitch.
You know what she said to
me when she first met me?
What?
[screams]
[laughs]
You son of a bitch!
[dial tone]
John, John, listen to me,
chances are if you meet him,
he'll kill you and
probably Julie, too.
Probably?
When he calls you to
set up the drop off point,
we'll surround the
area with a SWAT team
and then send in a decoy.
OK, whatever you say.
All right.
Any luck?
A lot of people
have heard of Kalin.
They're scared shitless of him.
I heard he's in a place
called the underground.
Yeah, there's an entrance
by the wash on first street.
OK.
I'm going to leave now.
You wait for the guys.
Come as soon as you can.
OK.
[music playing]
No guns down here!
Maybe you should have turned
left, or was it right?
It's easy to get lost down here.
How about a light?
[grunts]
Hey, there's two of them!
[screaming]
Get the other guy!
Where's the other one?
Get out.
Go back where you come from.
I can't.
Get out while you
still have a chance.
Wait, come back.
Did you see somebody
come by here?
[engine revving]
Where are you, gimpy?
I'm gonna come find you.
You better run.
I'm coming to get you, gimpy!
Thanks.
That's two I owe you.
You see that
orange pipe there?
You follow down that
way about 300 yards,
and you see a ladder
built into the wall,
and you go up that ladder,
and you'll be in elevator
maintenance room in city hall.
You can get out from there.
I don't want to get out.
Are you crazy or just stupid?
I'm after that guy
on the motorcycle.
And Kalin.
Stupid and crazy.
Look, Kalin kidnapped--
I don't care.
I just don't give a shit.
JOHN: I can help you.
I'm a doctor, I've got money.
Don't you condescend
me, you son of a bitch.
What do you want?
How about respect?
Do you think you
can give me that?
[shouting]
Son of a bitch.
Making my life miserable.
Let's see how many
balls you got, boy.
[grunting]
[screaming]
[swords slashing]
[screams in pain]
Where are we going?
Straight to Hell.
[suspenseful music]
This must be the place.
Let's check it out.
Oh shit, there's giant
alligators in there.
Come on.
[engine revving]
Oh our friend is in
the underground now.
Apparently, he went through
a fight with the garbage can.
Put out the word,
$50,000 reward
if he's brought to me alive.
Don't kill him.
I want the son of
a bitch to suffer.
Bring that incompetent
piece of shit to me.
[chanting kill him]
[groans]
[crowd cheers]
Does that turn you
on watching, huh?
[screaming]
Is it entertaining?
It's fun.
Oh come on now.
Watch a little bit.
And you'll like it.
[crowd cheers]
[music playing]
How much further?
About another
mile to Pasadena.
You can go from downtown
to Pasadena underground?
Between sewer lines,
old buildings, new subway,
old subway, I go from
here to San Bernardino
and not come up for air.
MAN: Tunes, tunes,
tunes, all night,
all day, all around the clock.
That's the kind
of song that makes
me want to get up and shake my
tail fathers, stretch my booty,
lick my dessert.
Is the Freebird back, the person
who couldn't fit in upstairs,
couldn't fit in downstairs, but
whose voice fits in everywhere.
I'm talking to all
you kiddies out
there right now,
because there's a doctor
do goody good good out there.
He's running around our own
little special playground.
And a Mr. K has an
offering of $50,000
cool cash to anyone of you--
oh I love this word--
bangers out there, who
will bring him in alive
or even slightly alive.
Listen doctor do
good, I'd like to talk
to you for a second baby.
This place stinks.
I wonder who
does their laundry.
Don't look at me.
Shh, listen to that.
MAN: She is in good hands.
Really good hands.
We're running out of time.
MAN: Personally, I'd like to
get my hands on you, doctor.
What is that?
It's the underground radio.
[rat squeaking]
Shadow warriors.
[screaming]
[shouts]
[sticks tapping]
[suspenseful music]
Pair of sevens--
Hey guys.
I seen a place like this
before with big giant spiders.
Come on.
Shut up.
Where's this go?
I don't know, but
it's the only way.
I'm not going.
Come on, let's go.
Looks like it comes out there.
OK, OK.
Come on.
Don't push.
I'm coming.
I'm going.
[music playing]
Tommy, are you OK?
Do you need to take a nap?
[coughing]
Welcome to Reaganomics.
Hola, como estas?
This looks like a
third world country.
Aaron, my man.
How you been hanging?
Especially well.
Who be this?
Johnny.
Welcome to downtown.
Actually, we haven't met.
Yeah, right.
Take no offense.
An excess of spleen
This is my house, and
I didn't invite you.
I'm homeless, not illiterate.
Ernest, I can help
you get out of here.
Don't you patronize me.
I'm gonna help you, but you
get your candy ass some guilt
ridden give a dollar to.
Get that bleeding heart
out of my fucking house!
So what brings thee to
the nether world, my friend?
I'm looking for
someone, Kalin.
I need a gun.
Oh you can't.
They're outlawed down
here, since the truce.
Outlawed?
Of course.
We all have our
territories down here.
We all realize that
if there were guns,
we'd be dead within the week.
Take me with you.
You know, I fought with
Henry at Agincourt.
Henry?
The fifth, of course!
Why, he said to me, once
more into the breach,
dear friends, once more
or wall the hole up
with our English dead.
Aaron, Aaron, this is
no time for war stories.
You know, I told you one day
that I'd deal with Kalin.
Now is the time.
This is for you.
- It's lovely.
Let me come with you.
You know, I fought the
Battle of Gettysburg.
No, no, no.
Aaron, this is gonna
be real bloody.
Hey, just remember
he's got Julie,
and I'd rather not get her in
the middle of your blood bath.
Yeah, well, I'd
rather a lot of things.
Now you just dummy up
and do like I tell you,
and maybe you won't get hurt.
Listen to me.
I don't know what
your problem is.
Personally, I don't give a shit.
We're going to get
Kalin my way or no way.
Hmm.
You've got a little
potential there, boy.
Kalin controls the armory.
We'll get that first.
Then fare the
well, good knight.
May the puissance of thine
arms and the favor of the gods
bring the laurel
crown upon thy helm.
[crowd cheers]
Made it through
the shadow warriors.
Guess what?
They have their old
pal Gimpy with them.
This is getting
better and better.
[crowd cheers]
[shouting]
Looks like Johnny's been here.
Yeah, no kidding.
We're on the right track.
You know, I don't
think I like this place.
I'm sure I don't
like this place.
Here we go again.
[shouting]
What took you so long?
Night rats.
Looks empty.
Oh they're here.
Come on, come on, up.
It's fine.
Come on kids.
Inside.
Hello, kiddies out there.
This is the Freebird.
You're not doing a
very good job tonight.
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
You see doctor do good just blew
right past the shadow warriors.
And now he's got the help of
my own favorite weekend soldier
with that little
wounded leg, GI Joe.
Oh Joe, say it ain't so,
Joe, say it ain't so.
So what we're going to
do for the next hour
is we're going to double
everything, double the danger,
double the pleasure, double
the treasure, double the fun,
because two is always
better than one.
As we pump up the volume
here and we make things
nice and hot, because the person
who brings home doctor do good
is going to get that brass ring.
Now it's time for these
hot, hot, hot tunes.
[music playing]
[shouting]
Maybe they'll set him
free when they get back.
It won't matter.
They'll be long gone by then.
I'm telling you they're
only good for killing,
no point in sparing them.
I won't kill a man
if I don't have to.
This is a war zone, kid.
That's how we do it down here.
You tell the rest of them.
Oh shit!
[shouting]
Not bad for a beginner.
How many of these games
do we have to go through?
This is the last one
before we get to Kalin.
Let's go.
Were you army?
Be all you can be.
Can I ask you something?
Mm-hmm.
Why are you down here?
My place in Malibu
is being remodeled.
Come on, Ernest.
You're healthy, intelligent.
Surely the Army trains you--
To do what?
Jump out of a plane?
Field strip a rifle?
What does that qualify me to do?
You every fill out a
job application, Doctor?
Put your phone number here?
Oh, I don't have one.
Put your address down there.
Gee, I don't have
one of those either.
Thank you.
Next.
Still, I can't believe--
No, you can't believe.
You get in your BMW and
leave your gated community
and drive to your
air conditioned
office in Beverly Hills.
You have no fucking
idea what goes
on out here in the real world.
You don't know a thing about
me, what I do, or where I live.
So don't-- hey!
You don't have a
monopoly on pain.
Yeah, I know you
had it real rough.
[music playing]
Oh no, you don't
want to go down there.
Doctor do good,
oh doctor do good.
Can you hear me out there?
You see, I'm lonely tonight.
I'm feeling a little feisty.
But you're not
alone, because you
got some buddies who came
down from upstairs to help
you in your time of need.
Well, that's good for you.
Yeah.
But it's also good for
our bangers out there.
You listening, bangers?
Because Mr. K has
upped the ante.
Pick what's behind
door number two.
What do you see?
You see five grand a
head for any of doctor
do good's buddies that you
bring to Mr. K. That's right.
The stakes are getting
higher and higher.
You know what, doctor do good,
if you're listening, baby,
you might be good.
But I sure couldn't
make you better.
Oh yeah.
Now what might excite the
bangers is the five grand,
but what excites me is you,
doctor do good, is you.
[music playing]
I think we're a
little bit out numbered.
There's only half
a dozen of them.
Any bright ideas?
Yeah.
Let's fly.
[grunting]
[screaming]
Everyone OK?
We're missing Kwong.
Maybe he got out
on the other side.
Yeah.
Come on.
We got to get moving.
[rats squeaking]
You know, you still
haven't answered my question.
Grandpa died a
hero in World War II.
My old man retired
after 20 years.
All my life I wanted
to be a soldier.
A lifer.
At 17, I volunteered
and did a tour in 'Nam.
I was court marshaled and
sent to prison for 20 years.
What happened?
My commanding officer
was shot in the back.
This was set improperly.
It wasn't set.
When we get out of this,
I'll put you in the hospital
and fix it.
I'm not going up there.
Why not?
I just don't
understand it up there.
President of the United States
regularly breaks the law
and lied to the American people,
and nobody does anything.
Down here, we got good
guys and bad guys.
And it's really easy to
tell which one's which.
Move that stuff out the way
so we can get out of here.
[crowd cheers]
Look, I'm giving you a choice.
You can fight, or you can die.
[shouting]
Fight.
[crowd cheers]
Things are heating
up out there.
Maybe you'd better
go check it out.
[crowd cheers]
[engine revving]
Fred is Kalin's
number two man.
In here.
Let me ask you something.
Why are you doing this?
I still owe Kalin
big time for this.
Come on.
There's more to this than
just revenge for you.
Do you know what beauty is?
Beauty?
Beauty is when any
living thing can do
exactly what they do the best.
The Army didn't teach me much,
but this shit I know about.
What the hell is this?
Yo, it's a freak show.
Show baby.
Hurt me.
What's the matter, cute boy?
Cat got your tongue?
You do like to party, don't you?
Yes, ma'am.
Let's get naked!
Outstanding.
So let's party.
Hey, so where's all the guys?
It's obvious you girls couldn't
survive down here by yourself.
We have a truce
with the other gangs.
They leave us along, so long
as we invite to our parties.
We have some wild parties.
[shouting]
So why are you
called the bad girls?
'Cos when we're
good, we're bad.
And when we're bad,
we're really bad.
Guys, we can't hang here.
We've got to find Johnny.
Yeah, in a bit, right after
this well deserved break.
Take a pill, Brad.
Just relax.
That's it.
[crashing noise]
So, you're the guys
Kalin wants, huh?
Drugged us, bitch!
Woo-wee!
Hey, come here.
[grunting]
Holy guacamole.
Wow.
Look at this leg.
Nice butt.
[grunting]
Why did you stop?
I think I'm in love.
You have a dog?
I'd love your dog, too.
[grunts]
You know, you are
really sexy when you
throw one of those spinning--
[gasping]
Friends of yours?
No, I've never
seen them before.
So you won't mind if
I throw them in the cage
and make them
fight to the death.
I'd mind anyone fighting
to the death except you.
Oh you'll see me all right,
when your boyfriend gets here.
You'll see me.
[spits]
My kind of girl.
[julie whimpering]
That one right
there in the cage now.
We almost there.
Listen.
Kalin's thrown room
is right down there,
but the armory's this way.
You go.
I'll head to Kalin's.
You can't go down
there on your own.
Just go.
[crowd cheers]
Come on, Brad.
[grunting]
Brad!
Get up, Brad.
Get up.
Come on, Brad.
Fight back!
Brad!
Come on, Brad.
Get up.
[grunting]
Yeah, come on!
Come on, Brad, bust him up!
Get off, you big slug!
Get up!
Come on!
[groaning]
[booing]
[chanting kill him]
Kill him.
Shit!
Johnny!
That's enough!
I was wondering when you
were going to show up.
Well, here I am.
Wait.
Let me fight him.
He'd tear you up.
Then you lose an
unworthy second in command.
But please, let me fight him.
All right.
Do it.
Yeah!
Come on.
[crowd cheers]
Get in there.
[shouting]
All right, OK.
[grunting]
Johnny!
Come on!
Come on, come on.
[crowd cheers]
You!
Damn!
Come on, come on.
[gun shots]
[screaming]
Quick, get the
guns, get the guns.
[explosion]
Let's go.
[groaning]
How could you let
him do this to you?
[inaudible]
Wait, wait, hold it.
You get out with Brad.
I can't leave Ernest behind.
- Johnny, no.
- Johnny, that's suicide.
Go on.
I'll meet you there
in the tunnel.
Go, come on.
- Johnny!
Come on.
What are you waiting for?
You.
Well, I'm here.
[beeping]
Come on!
[explosion]
[screaming]
[music playing]
[shouting]
JOHN: Ernest, how the hell
do we get out of here?
Just crawl through the
hole in the wall on the left.
That will take us into
the old mine shaft.
That'll lead us out.
Everybody OK?
We should get out of
here as soon as possible.
So what are we
going to do now?
We lost Kwong.
Hey!
Hi, guys.
Kwong.
We thought you were dead.
No, no I had some
problem in enemy territory.
I brought a friend.
I'll be damned.
You finally got a girl.
Let's get to a telephone
and call the police.
[tires squealing]
You destroyed my underground.
Now, we're going to finish
this, just you and me.
There's nothing
left to finish.
Uh?
We don't fight--
[gun shot]
Son of a bitch.
I'm gonna start picking off
your friends one at a time.
Let's do it.
I lose, nobody lives.
You won't lose.
[suspenseful music]
Come on, Johnny.
Get him, Johnny, yes!
Go, Kalin!
[grunting]
Holy enchilada!
Ha!
Get up!
Come on!
[screaming]
Yeah!
Johnny!
Are you OK?
All right, back up.
[julie whimpering]
[kalin laughing]
Get up, Johnny, come on.
Come on, get up!
Get him, boy, get him.
Yeah, yeah!
[screaming]
Give it to him!
Back off.
[grunting]
All right, Johnny.
Yeah, Johnny, come on.
[screaming]
I love you.
Ernest, I don't
know how we're ever
going to be able to repay you.
We'll think of something.
Come stay with us.
We can help you get
back on your feet.
I am on my feet.
Besides, I don't
like it up here.
Too much sunlight.
[tires squealing]
[grunting]
[suspenseful music]
Come on, come on!
Shoot him!
[screaming]
[explosion]
Where's Ernest?
He went back.
Let's get the
hell out of here.
[explosion]
Hey, dudes and dudettes.
I got some news for you.
Mr. K is taking a
snooze this morning,
and I believe it's permanently.
So our contest is over.
We've been busted.
I would like to have
a word with doctor
do good if he's out there.
Your point has been made.
And it shows us down here that
we can still learn something
from you people upstairs.
And just remember, doctor do
good, if that Juliet of yours
finds another
Romeo, the Freebird
is here, waiting for you.
[music playing]
MALE SINGER: Sit back, relax,
and serve rhymes to the temple.
Ain't no ballad,
no instrumental,
just plain and simple,
my fundamentals,
you know what I'm saying?
Don't dust me if you
want to request me.
Don't try to put me down.
Don't try to repress me.
You can't fool me
frontin' like a fresh.
As I told my back seat,
oh there you go again.
So here I go, a
man with a vision,
you want to hang with me, you
better change your mission.
Better give it up.
Mark my words.
And mistake my body,
I'll hunt you out stupid
like a bottle of Bacardi.
Don't test me.
[woman singing]
MALE SINGER: I got to stay
cool and get it together.
I've been through rougher
times and stormier weather.
Strength of my mind.
Strength of my soul.
Based from a culture
thousands of years ago.
Say you must rip and
husk off the past.
You ain't know jack
on how to talk trash.
Living the easy life,
driving the money car,
not knowing at all
who the hell you really are.
Don't test me.
[woman singing]
MALE SINGER: Hey yeah.
Hey yeah.
It's a long, long way home.
Because I know that part of
you that makes me feel wrong
is getting for me.
Losing battles to your
gentle addictions.
Hey yeah.
These things go two ways.
And I thought if we're together,
we'd be on the same tides.
When I lost my way I
don't believe that I
could trust you to find me.
Hey yeah.
There's a life on the silver
screen with an [inaudible]
playing the role.
And it's a tragedy.
Everybody says so.
Everybody knows about it.
Hey, who's that being
knocking at the door?
It's free disco charity.
Come on, woman.
Give me the goods because
I don't want to be here.
Anymore.
Hey yeah.