(MultiCom Jingle)
(medieval instrumental music)
(swords clanging)
(heroic orchestral music)
- Sir Lancelot, I yield!
Well fought.
- You do me honor, Sir Gawain.
It is King Arthur's good fortune
to count thee among his
best and bravest knights.
- Lady Vivian.
Why comes the Merlin's witch?
- Forget thee not,
she is my guardian mother.
- You are looking well, Lancelot.
- Greetings, my lady.
We are well met.
What brings you to Camelot?
(light orchestral music)
- What does the Merlin wish?
- He commands that I accept the quest
which only I may hazard.
The fate of the realm
depends on my success.
- The Sword of Glamis
has been kept for you
for this very day.
It is a weapon of great power.
(magical whirring)
(sword whooshing)
(soft orchestral music)
To accept this quest, place
this ring on thy finger.
It is from the Merlin.
- Sir Lancelot.
You would honor me to
accompany you on this quest.
Your fellow knight and friend.
- Brave Sir Gawain, my thanks.
The Merlin awaits.
(exciting orchestral music)
(thunder crashing)
(soft orchestral music)
- [Gawain] Was not this village burned?
- Aye, by the command of
the sorcerer Wolvencroft.
But forget thee not, by the Merlin's spell
we travel in a time before Arthur is king.
- Might not the castle fiends
still haunt this place?
- Aye, and the sorcerer Wolvencroft
may yet inhabit the castle Raven's Keep.
Come!
(donkey braying)
(cow mooing)
(thunder crashing)
(chanting in foreign language)
(intense orchestral music)
- You must leave this place!
- Come on, my horse will carry us both.
- No, Lancelot!
You must go and fulfill the quest!
- She'll never forgive you if
you die in battle without me!
- A sad day when a
Knight of the Round Table
cannot fare such as thee.
Now go!
(laughing) Come on, come on!
(flowing orchestral music)
(thunder crashing)
- Wolvencroft!
- Sir Lancelot, welcome to Raven's Keep.
Or, shall I say, welcome to the past.
I presume that meddling
old wizard sent you.
He is the Merlin of Britain,
and I am come at his behest.
I am come for the young
squire that you have stolen.
- (gasps) Could this be the
young squire that you seek?
Well, as you can see, he his quite safe.
But you may not have him.
Stay where you are, sir,
or I shall finish off the boy's life now
and the future will be decided.
- I have seen the future of Britain.
Like thee, I live within that time.
Here all this is but a
shade of things past.
- You fool, you think the
future cannot be changed?
- How can that be
changed which already is?
- Do you not understand who that boy is?
What future power lies
quite truly in his hands?
You know nothing?
Oh, by the gods.
The Merlin has brought
you here in ignorance!
Go back to your time, sir.
(laughing)
Go back to your Merlin.
There will be no shame in it.
If the old wizard wishes a fair encounter,
let him come see me himself.
- I have come to free the
young squire, Wolvencroft,
and so I shall.
(grunting)
Release the boy, and I will let thee live.
The Merlin has so instructed me.
- The Merlin is weak and bent with age.
What use his power if not used?
- Yield the boy, Wolvencroft.
- Consider this, Lancelot.
I can grant thee a future
beyond thy wildest dreams.
Would you wish to be king?
Oh, I could use a swordsman such as you.
Your skills are very noteworthy.
No?
Pity.
(squealing)
(swords clanging)
(intense orchestral music)
- You'll find me a more worthy opponent.
- Another time.
(chanting in foreign language)
Wolvencroft!
Reach, squire!
Reach, boy!
- You are too late. (mumbles)
You have failed.
- Never.
Reach, boy!
Reach, squire!
(thunder crashing)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(soft orchestral music)
- So they've got you on
carousel duty today, eh?
- And it's hard work, let me tell you.
- Well?
The book?
- [Liz] I finished it last night.
- And?
- Wow.
- You like it?
- (laughs) Yeah.
Katherine, it is a terrific book.
I wouldn't change a word of it.
Maybe one or two, but that's it.
- You don't think it's too
hard on the male population?
- Men of Romance: Myth and Reality.
It's a little cynical
from my point of view,
but cynicism sells.
- I don't know, I don't
think it's cynical.
I think I'm just being honest.
- Come on, really?
- What happened to all the chivalrous men?
What happened to men who
cherish us, treasure us?
- I think we killed them
off with radical feminism.
- Well, I still have hope
that there's at least
one somewhere out there.
(magical whooshing)
- Hey, what the...
- I regret that once again
we may not match swords.
(phone ringing)
- Somebody's gotta talk to me.
- Well, of course.
This is precisely the reason
why I don't own one of these things.
- Yeah, well I wish we could go back
to the days with no phones.
- I wish.
- Can you give me just a second?
- Yeah, go ahead.
- [Liz] Yeah.
No, that's fine.
Friday.
Hi, this is Liz.
Right, no, that's when we...
- Are they filming a movie here?
- I don't know, I don't think so.
It's LA.
(mumbling)
No, no, no.
Of course.
- Why swear you allegiance to Wolvencroft?
He has abused the ancient ways,
betrayed his vows of power.
- And you serve the great Merlin,
a toothless old woman.
Here.
Give this to your Merlin.
(horse whinnying)
He will know its meaning.
- Where is the young squire, Blackpool?
- I fear you shall never know.
(magical whooshing)
- No, no, no.
Sorry.
What?
- I just saw a great
looking guy on a horse.
- Where?
- I don't know, he was
just there a second ago.
- Mmm-hmm.
- I'm going crazy, aren't I?
(laughs) Either that or I'm
just hungry, I don't know.
- I think you're hungry.
You're gonna sign this for me, right?
- Of course I will.
- Thank you.
Come on, let's go.
Let's eat.
You know what?
I do think they exist.
- I'm still hoping there's at
least one out there somewhere.
- Oh, a closet romantic?
(hooves clopping)
- Pardon, sir.
Pardon, sir, I require assistance.
- Just a minute.
(soft orchestral music)
Whoa!
- I seek another who
has arrived as I have.
- Nice outfit!
Hey dude, do you need a
permit to ride that horse?
- Sir, the information
I seek is desperate.
- Hey, is this stuff real?
I mean, like authentic?
- [Lancelot] Sir, Wolvencroft is his name.
- Wow, because it's
great, I mean that sword,
I mean, it's incredible, that
sword is really incredible!
- His name is Wolvencroft!
- Hey, you know, beach weather
must play heck with it,
I mean, how do you keep it from
rusting and stuff like that?
- Sir, you must attend me.
A boy's life is in danger.
- Okay, all right, okay, okay, calm down,
take it easy, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Listen, I'm Michael.
Mike to my friends.
You know, come to think of it,
I really don't have so many, so...
I'm glad to meet you, what
did you say your name was?
- I am Sir Lancelot du Lac.
- Yeah, okay, why not, I'll play.
- Sir, there is no time for playing.
A boy's life is in danger.
In this place, where do
the men of power reside?
- Reside?
You know, I'm not really even
sure who the men of power are,
to tell you the truth.
Listen, don't look so surprised.
You know, some people don't keep track
of that kind of thing.
You know, I don't even
like the 20th century!
- What?
What year say you?
- What do you mean?
It's the 20th century.
- Say you that we stand
within the 20th century?
- Yeah.
- Know you of King Arthur
and his Round Table?
- Aye, yeah, I grew up on all that stuff.
You know, King Arthur and Robin Hood
and the Knights of the Round Table,
and damsels in distress,
and all that kind of thing.
- The wizard will have chosen
his time and place carefully.
- Oh, now there's a wizard?
- Aye, Wolvencroft.
He will have positioned
himself with priests and kings.
Where do these men reside?
- Priests and kings?
I have no clue.
You know, but I'll tell
you what, my sister might.
You know what I mean?
She keeps up on all the who's
who in the world and stuff.
- Then perhaps our meeting
was no mere coincidence.
We must not tarry.
- Okay.
Alright, well I'll tell you what,
let's go grab a cup of cappuccino,
then we'll go check with
my sister, all right?
- Pray--
- What?
- What place is this?
- Venice, why?
- Nay, Vinaccia?
Say you so?
- Yeah!
- Be these the famed blue
waters of the Mediterranean?
- Mediterranean?
No, man, this is the Pacific!
It's Venice, you know, it's California.
Where do you think you are?
Come on, let's go.
(eagle screeching)
(tense orchestral music)
- You're certain?
Lancelot is returned?
- Oh, indeed, milord.
I did use the spell as you instructed.
- I have warned you, you may
call me sir, or Mr. Wolf,
but milord is unacceptable.
- My apologies, sir.
- And the newspaper?
The knight has taken it with him?
- Oh yes.
- Then, by the gods, I have the Merlin.
- How so, milord?
Sir.
(electric zapping)
How so, Mr. Wolf?
- When Lancelot discovers that he
has returned to Arthur's court,
he will report to Merlin,
and bring the newspaper.
Will he not?
- Then it is a trap to
bring the Merlin here.
- Quite so.
Then I will have the boy and his wizard,
and here they shall remain.
- And all that is Camelot, will it vanish?
- As a mist in the wind.
(laughing)
Understand?
I have grasped the use of time,
and snatched back history.
They are mine to do with as I wish.
- And without Arthur, the
sword remains in the stone.
There will be centuries of chaos!
- Chaos is my hunting ground.
(birds chirping)
(electronic beeping)
- Everything has changed, and yet,
I see so much that is familiar.
- Here it comes, here it comes.
Lance, come here, look, this is it.
This is it.
- This box.
It can foretell the future?
- No, no, just the present.
(humming)
(horse whinnying)
- Michael Anthony Shelley,
could you please come down here?
- Oh lord, the horse.
She's gonna kill me.
- Should I?
- No, no, no, just stay here.
It's safer.
- [Katherine] Michael?
- Yeah?
- Got a question for you.
- Okay.
- What's that?
- What's what?
- That large thing.
- That?
- Yeah.
- It's a horse.
(electronic beeping)
- Yes, thank you for clarifying that.
I realize it's a horse.
I'm just kind of curious as
to what that horse is doing
in our garden, eating my flowers?
- Uh, it's hungry.
- That's great.
Who does this horse belong to?
- It belongs to our guest.
- We have a guest with a horse?
- [Michael] Uh, well...
- Lady Katherine.
(light instrumental music)
I am Lancelot du Lac.
Of thee Michael has spoken,
but the vision of thee far
surpasses his kindest praise.
- Michael...
- He told you you look great.
- I grieve to have
caused you any distress,
but I humbly request indulgence.
Michael?
- Look, look--
- Michael, if this is a joke,
I'm not in the mood at all.
- Just listen for just a second.
This incredible thing happened to me today
you would never believe.
- [Katherine] I can hardly
wait to hear this one.
- [Michael] You would never believe.
(eagle screeching)
(phone ringing)
- Yes?
Very well, I'll be waiting.
It'll be soon be here, Merlin.
I have your precious Arthur,
and soon, your precious stone.
- Come on, Kat.
What if his story's true?
What if it's possible?
Just think about it, all right?
Just think about it!
What an incredible
adventure this could be,
and we could be part of it.
- You've been designing one
too many computer games, Mike.
Look, I'm just having a little
bit of a hard time with this.
I'm trying to absorb it all.
- Alright, well just this once.
Just this once, for me,
think with your heart,
and don't try to dissect everything.
- I'm gonna give it a shot, all right?
Let me get this straight now.
You are--
- Lancelot of Camelot.
Knight of the Round Table.
And the Merlin--
- The Merlin sent you back to a time
before Arthur was a king
so that you could track
down this other wizard.
- Aye, Wolvencroft.
A most vile fiend.
- Now Wolvencroft, he's the
one who kidnapped the boy.
- And by his hand, here
I am in your 20th century
to find the boy and return
him unto Merlin's care.
- Didn't you say that this Wolvencroft
wore a very distinctive ring?
- A ring in the shape of a wolf's head,
and a dragon claw pendant
clutching a black crystal.
Both are sources of great power.
- Is that how he got here?
- Michael, please, you're
getting a little bit
carried away here, aren't you?
This is impossible.
- And yet, here I am.
And Wolvencroft's theft is
a danger to all of Britain.
What more need you know?
- Okay, how about who is this kid,
and why would Wolvencroft
choose to take him
from a time from your own past,
and why am I asking you silly questions?
- Blackpool charged me,
"Show this to the Merlin."
- Arthur...
Arthur...
- Merlin?
- This was meant for the Merlin.
Wolvencroft shows him what is to be.
Why?
- And check out the date!
- Yeah, but this can't be right, Michael.
The sword is still in the stone.
- I could not find
anything, nothing at all,
on the museum's antiquities expert, okay?
He sets up the whole exhibit,
but he just seems to
pop up out of nowhere.
Kind of like you, Lance.
- This place of the
antiquities, where is it?
If the sword is there, there
shall I find the sorcerer.
- Alright, well hold on,
because it's closed now,
but we should definitely
check it out tomorrow.
Lance, when was this sword
first pulled from the stone?
- On the first day of the new year
when the abbey bells chimed the 12th hour.
- Well that's tomorrow.
First day of the new year.
- Only the rightful King Arthur
may draw the sword from the stone.
I search for a boy.
- A squire.
No name.
- Arthur.
- And didn't the Merlin
send you back to a time
before Arthur was king?
- So you're saying that
this boy is Arthur?
The Arthur?
And that Wolvencroft has changed history?
Come on, that's impossible.
- But it hasn't changed yet, Kat.
It's still only a possibility
if Wolvencroft succeeds.
- Succeeds at what?
- Succeeds in uniting the sword of power
with Arthur of Britain,
in a time far removed from
Merlin's power and protection.
Wolvencroft, thou art a demon.
- The sword that was forged when the world
was yearning with power
to unite a nation and build a legend.
Mine!
I have the sword, I have the boy.
These things the Merlin cannot,
need must not ignore.
- When will he come?
- Soon.
At noon tomorrow.
He has no choice, when
the boy draws the sword
and all that is past is undone.
Then...
Then time will be mine.
And I will decide what is to be.
- Whence comes this vision?
What means it?
- Check this out.
- This gift of conjuring
is truly wondrous.
In my day, only the
Merlin had such a glass
for seeing beyond the here and now.
- Trust me, Merlin's gift is a lot better.
Nowadays everybody's got one of these,
and you can only see what
the guys on the other end
want you to see.
- Aye, but is that not always
the truth with a vision?
The seer may receive
only that which is sent.
The seer may not demand more.
- You started this, why
don't you explain it to him?
- Okay, well, without having
to go through centuries of--
- Can you not see him?
The man I seek.
- Is that Wolvencroft?
- Aye.
The sorcerer himself.
- Look, it's the ring!
It's just as he described it.
- We may lose all if we hesitate.
- Do either of you have a plan?
- Well, we're working on it.
- There's no time to spare.
- Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a second.
You can't go out on the
street with a sword like that.
- I'm prepared, and the
Merlin bad may be quick.
- Well then you're gonna get arrested.
- These are indeed strange times.
- You're just asking
for trouble like that.
- Perhaps it is not seemly for the lady
to be further involved.
- Whoops.
- Please, I'm coming along
so neither of you do anything stupid!
- She's warming up.
(cars honking)
(loud rock music)
- Somebody answer me this.
Unlike my brother, I am a
rational, reasonable human being.
So what am I doing here?
- Following your heart for once.
- What happens if we don't find Arthur?
- A fate too terrible to contemplate.
- I don't know, guys.
It looks like it's closed.
- This is the place of the antiquities?
- You know what, let's drive around back,
see if we can get in
through the loading dock.
- Okay.
Here we are.
This is the back entrance.
- 'Tis no higher than a castle wall.
Wolvencroft.
- Take it easy.
He's not gonna go anywhere.
- Look, I've got an idea.
Why don't I keep him busy
while you look for Arthur?
- Be sure, Katherine.
Wolvencroft is a most dangerous adversary.
- I wrote the book on his type, remember?
- Thy books will be of little avail
should he discover the
true purpose of thy intent.
- I'll be okay.
- Let's give Kat five minutes,
then we'll slip in after her.
Don't worry, she can handle this guy.
- Hello, Wolf.
- Yes?
- How do you do, I'm Katherine Shelley.
- [Wolvencroft] How do you do?
- I was wondering, could I
have a moment alone with you?
- How may I help you, Katherine Shelley?
- We're good to go.
- What?
What say you, good to...
- Uh, by thee hence.
- Aye.
- And I'm researching for a new book idea
on influential men in the 20th century.
- (chuckles) And you've
chosen me, an unknown scholar?
Very interesting, could you explain?
- I was just thinking that with
the historical significance
of your latest exhibition,
and your vast knowledge
of medieval British history,
that you would make a fantastic subject.
- Are you sure you're not
here just to see the exhibit?
- [Katherine] Well, I must
admit that I'm fascinated
by the legend of the sword in the stone.
- Hey, Hercules!
Which way to New Jersey?
- Hey, you're not supposed to be in here!
- Do you know where New Jersey is?
- Yeah, I know where New Jersey is!
- Legend has it that as long
as the sword in the stone
remain on English soil,
they are protected by
an ancient enchantment.
- So you mean to tell me
that this is the first time in history
that they're actually unprotected?
- Yes.
Tantalizing thought, is it not?
- That's a fascinating
ring, is that an antique?
- You might call it a family heirloom.
- Down the door to the left.
- Would you mind showing me?
- Absolutely, right this way.
- [Michael] This way?
- [Worker] Yeah.
- [Michael] Thank you very much.
(light orchestral music)
- Aye, a forest!
Praise the gods!
(squealing)
- It's funny, I've always been
interested in antiquities.
The reason why I want
this exhibition in my book
is because I'm really interested
in British history particularly.
- Enough.
You've convinced me that
you may be a writer,
but why are you here?
- I was sent.
- By whom?
- By Merlin.
- What name did thee speak?
Lancelot.
- Lancelot!
(exciting orchestral music)
Disarm him, but kill him not.
He is needed alive!
- What have thee done with
the young squire Arthur?
- Well, as you can see, he is not here.
I fear that once again you are too late.
Arthur's destiny is but a few hours away.
The course of history is shifting.
- You steal him from
a time that needs him.
- Ah, yes.
And because of that, I
have in my grasp today
power beyond measure, which
only the young squire may unlock
at the appointed time.
- You dare to speak of the
sword in the stone, traitor?
- Go to your Merlin.
Bid him come challenge me face to face.
(roaring)
- For Katherine's freedom,
and your word that we may leave in safety,
I shall return the crystal.
- Done.
- Once again, your twisted
fate has saved you.
Go!
- It does appear that
Lancelot is still with us,
does it not?
- I did use the spell.
- I despise disappointment.
(magical whooshing)
Not very original, I'm afraid.
(sighing)
It'll do for now.
(medieval instrumental music)
(tense instrumental music)
- Hey, what happened?
Didn't you find him?
- Wolvencroft said Arthur wasn't there,
but I think he's lying.
He must be.
- Lies become the bitter truth
if on the morrow Arthur
fulfills his destiny
and draws the sword from the stone.
- Well what happens if
Wolvencroft succeeds,
how can that help him?
Wasn't the sword meant
to be used for good?
- As the blade is double
edged, so cuts the sword.
Either way, for good or evil.
He who controls the
sword controls history.
We have but one day to write
that which shall last forever.
(thunder crashing)
- My dealings with Merlin must
be postponed, but no matter.
In time, in time.
(toad croaking)
All is in place for the morrow.
(bell ringing)
The squire is what?
(magical zapping)
When did this happen?
- Not long past, sir.
- You had Wolvencroft.
You should have forced him
to tell you where Arthur is.
- Blackpool had you, milady.
- Well, I know, but I--
- The chivalric code does not permit
the endangering of a woman.
- A little old-fashioned, but I like it.
- Words of truth are timeless, Katherine.
- Listen, this is all very nice,
but what are we gonna do about the kid?
(soft orchestral music)
- [Wolvencroft] Where
would one such as he go?
- A place familiar, sir.
Away from that which
he does not understand.
Perhaps a garden or a park.
The park, sir.
- Very clever.
Don't come back until you've found him.
Use whatever means you must.
- Aye, milord.
(people chattering)
(dog barking)
(soft medieval music)
(grill sizzling)
- Hey!
Hey, that's our stuff, man.
What are you doing?
- He's jacking our food!
- Look, wiener boy, put the
hot dog down, all right?
Put it down!
Look, spaz, put the hot dog down!
- That's smooth, AJ.
Hey look, just give us our stuff back
and get the hell out of here.
- Go get him, Joe.
Kick his butt!
- Where are you, boy, where are you?
(lively medieval music)
- I have no quarrel with
thee, but by the dragon,
I shall fight thee!
- Yeah?
Bring it on.
- Come on, AJ, just leave him alone.
It's not like he's from around here.
- Look, I don't care what
museum this punk escaped from,
I'm gonna drop him!
- Where...
- Hey, go get him, AJ!
- Shut up, Ricky.
- Give me that!
Yeah!
(fist thudding)
- Hey, hey!
- Do you yield?
- Yield?
Dude, who are you?
- One who shall teach
you a lesson in courtesy!
Do you yield?
- Yeah, I yield.
Uncle.
Uncle!
Nice hook.
My name's AJ.
The guy with the mouth, that's Ricky.
This is Joe.
What's your name?
Name, name?
- Arthur.
I am Arthur.
- Nice to meet you, bro.
Who's hungry?
- [Ricky] I am!
- I'm sure Dutch boy could use a snack.
Want to join us?
- Yes!
- Alright, let's go.
- That was fun.
- Then did Pendragon
find himself surrounded
by the villainous Saxons!
He fought like a lion, and
more than 20 Saxons did die
before the king was slain!
Pierced to the heart with a lance...
(groaning)
(clapping)
- Well played, boy.
Well played.
But now it is time you come with me.
- I have no desire to go with thee.
- Foolish knave.
- Who is this guy, Arthur?
Your parole officer?
- Yeah, what'd you do, break curfew?
He doesn't want to go with you.
Buzz off, buttmunch.
(laughing)
- Brave words.
Fools.
- Leave us, this quarrel is not yours.
- No.
No, it won't be that easy.
Your friends may leave in
safety if you come with me.
- I don't think so.
- I dare not.
Yet your fear must also be great.
You and your creatures
against four weaponless boys?
- Insolent wretch!
I fear no one.
- No?
Prove this.
If you'll not let us
go, then a fair fight.
If you understand the meaning.
- Yeah.
(squealing)
- Your friends will pay for your insults.
(intense orchestral music)
(fists thudding)
- We gotta get the hell out of here, man!
- Your little friends.
Do you wish them to live?
- My life for these three men.
I yield.
- So be it.
- Hey, they're gone!
Dude!
- Time as a toad has
improved Blackpool's wits.
- For this treachery, by
the dragon, thee will pay!
- What happened?
- How did we get--
- Guys, I think this is one of those
if I didn't see it, you
didn't see it situations.
Am I right?
- About what?
- Yeah man, I don't even know
what you're talking about.
- Michael has the gift of many abilities.
And you were clever and
bold today, brave Katherine.
If I may take my leave, my lady,
I wish to think on what
has happened this day.
- Of course.
(owl hooting)
(magical whirring)
- Guardian mother, I know not what to do.
Merlin...
What would you have me do?
I know so little of these times.
For all of this you did not prepare me.
- [Merlin] Lancelot...
- Merlin.
- Rise, Sir Lancelot, I am here.
You are not lost.
You wear the ring that I may find you.
- I cannot find Arthur.
- On the morrow, at the appointed hour,
go to the place of the stone.
There will you find what you seek.
- But these times are not mine.
On the morrow perchance
Arthur shall be rescued,
but what then?
I know nothing of the
magic that brought me here.
- The black crystal
which Wolvencroft wears.
You have seen it.
This is the key.
Speak the words that I shall tell thee.
The black crystal shall return you
and the boy Arthur to Raven's Keep.
Once there, I shall return you to Camelot.
- And the boy?
- He must remain in the past.
He awaits his destiny.
The boy Arthur will go
on to build a kingdom
and a legend for all time.
Knew you the boy's true identity?
- I was not certain until
Wolvencroft confirmed it.
- Yet, your heart remained
true to the quest.
- How could it be otherwise?
- Kneel, noble knight.
Listen, and heed what I tell thee now.
(soft orchestral music)
- Mind if I join you?
- Please.
It is a true marvel.
Here I find myself
centuries from all I know,
and yet, the stars have not changed.
- I don't understand why
Merlin didn't tell you
the boy was Arthur.
You've been risking your life,
and you didn't even know why.
- He's a strange one, the Merlin.
No mere mortal.
Perhaps he feared that
even I might succumb
to the desire for power.
- No, not you.
It just seems dangerous for you to be here
without any preparation.
- No.
But I was not meant to come so far.
Merlin had commanded me stop
Wolvencroft at his castle.
- I see.
So then, you and I would have never met.
- True.
It is indeed my good fortune
that we did, Katherine.
This I suspect the Merlin did influence.
- Merlin?
How?
- How, I cannot say.
His powers are vast and wonderful.
But in some way, he was my guide,
and I have found Michael and you here.
So very near the heart of my quest.
- Maybe you're right,
maybe Merlin did have
something to do with it.
In your time...
Do you have somebody?
A lady, a wife?
- My devotion is to God and king.
But if I were to give my heart freely
to any maiden, brave Katherine,
it would be to one such as thee.
Be safe on the morrow.
Should the plan fail,
protect Michael and thyself.
Promise me this.
- But I--
- Promise.
- I promise.
- Good.
Thou art worthy of the heart of a knight.
Lady Katherine.
(soft medieval music)
(eagle shrieking)
- Come, my boy.
Rise.
Your time to be king draws near.
Try not to lose him this time, Blackpool.
(cars honking)
(light medieval music)
- Remember thy promise, milady.
Be safe this day.
- I will.
- Do not underestimate Wolvencroft,
nor take this quest too lightly.
- Understood, but Kat's
job is to drive us in
and drive us out.
That should keep her pretty safe,
and then it's just left
for me to nab Arthur.
- Aye, but the Wolvencroft is no fool.
He will be well guarded.
That shall be my concern.
That, and acquiring the black crystal.
- Isn't there any other way
to get back to your time
without the crystal?
- It is the way that I have chosen.
We have not much time, we must hurry.
- 15 minutes, let's rock.
(tense instrumental music)
(engine sputtering)
- I can't believe this is not starting.
- [Michael] Just try it again.
- I've tried it three times, Mike.
- [Michael] Try it one more time.
(engine sputtering)
- I see the Merlin's hand in this.
And if I am late, all is lost.
Our ride through the park must be swift.
- Look what you did!
- [Katherine] I didn't do anything!
- Just pop the hood, okay?
Give it another try.
- Nothing!
- Nothing?
- Try it one more time.
(horse whinnying)
- Stop!
Don't you think this is mine to do?
- Yes, sir.
- Haven't I waited long enough?
- [Blackpool] Of course.
(magical zapping)
- I see the Merlin still
enjoys his games, does he?
Well let's see how far he will take it.
- [Blackpool] Why?
- Blackpool...
- Should we not wait, sir?
(bell chiming)
The boy's time comes.
(intense instrumental music)
(tires screeching)
- Come, Arthur.
Come.
Fulfill your destiny.
Draw forth the sword of power.
Draw the sword, and give it to me.
Come, boy.
Do it.
(bell chiming)
Draw the sword, and give it to me!
Now!
Do it!
- Arthur, no!
(heroic instrumental music)
- You have much to lose here, Lancelot!
Hold thy sword.
I could offer thee a kingdom and a crown!
- You have nothing to
offer that I would accept.
- Oh, well then consider this.
Just let the boy draw forth the sword
and Camelot shall be yours.
- Well, you know that if Arthur
were to draw the sword here and now,
there would be no Camelot.
- I have seen the past and the future.
The boy's destiny and your fate are one.
Should Arthur become king in his time?
You will destroy him,
and all that is Camelot.
- Arthur shall be king,
and I will fulfill Merlin's quest!
(sword whooshing)
Michael, the stone!
(magical zapping)
(intense medieval music)
- Michael!
- Long live King Arthur.
(magical whooshing)
- You have not finished with me, Lancelot.
By the dragon, you are not.
- Reach boy, reach squire!
(thunder crashing)
Be you unharmed, my lord?
- Aye.
What has happened, why am I...
I know you.
Do I not?
- Not as such, my lord.
- I have no memory of
this place, yet I know it.
Why?
- Perhaps such answers were
best left for the Merlin.
- Merlin?
- [Lancelot] My lord.
- Come on, come on!
(squealing)
(swords clanging)
(intense orchestral music)
(eagle screeching)
Lancelot!
- Gawain.
- I grow weary of your
interference, knight.
Give me the boy!
- Never be, go find Merlin.
Stop at nothing!
- He will never reach the Merlin.
And now, Sir Lancelot...
How shall I deal with you and your friend?
- I counsel thee, yield thyself and live.
- Arrogance.
Pride run wild.
- At last.
- You have much to learn.
- Very impressive.
Let's see what you do with this.
(squealing)
(swords clanging)
(intense orchestral music)
- Lancelot!
(squealing)
- Gawain!
Be these injuries mortal?
(grunting)
- Fulfill the quest.
The land needs a king.
- By the power of the Merlin,
be thee vanquished!
(magical whooshing)
I shall return for you, my friend.
(soft orchestral music)
(laughing)
(squealing)
- Ho there!
Steady, steady!
(tense instrumental music)
You are my only hope.
Fail me not.
Fear not, I shall not harm thee.
But I pray you, stand back.
The horse has no love of thy kind.
Have no fear, I am nothing but a squire!
Thy master will wish me unharmed.
I wish a bit of luck.
Aye...
Is that your master?
I bid you, prepare!
- Stop him!
Seize him, don't let him go!
- Arthur has bested you after all.
- I could kill you with but a gesture.
Far sweeter...
Will be the revenge of my sword.
(heroic orchestral music)
(swords clanging)
(dramatic orchestral music)
Are you ready to serve
your new master now?
- As you covet history,
so should you fight for it.
(tense orchestral music)
(swords clanging)
- You wouldn't kill a sorcerer.
There are so few of us remaining.
- The Merlin has charged me
deal with thee thus.
(screaming)
Britain shall have her king,
and her legend.
(heroic medieval music)
- This really happened.
- Oh yes, yes it did.
I've always told you,
it's a strange world.
- Yeah, but you never told me exactly
how strange it could be.
- Yeah, but it was fun, wasn't it?
- It was fun.
A lot of fun.
I'm gonna miss him, you know?
- Yep.
- For the first time in my life,
I actually started to believe
that heroes and romance and all
that stuff actually existed.
Not just in my hopeless imagination.
- Oh, Kat.
It's okay.
- He's gone, isn't he?
(soft medieval music)
- I think so.
- For good?
- Maybe.
- (laughs) I'm okay.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- What are you gonna do?
- Just gonna go get something to eat.
- You want to watch some TV?
- No.
- All right.
- Thanks.
(soft orchestral music)
- Fair Katherine,
this glove is for remembrance only.
If you wish it, we shall meet again.
But place the ring upon thy finger,
and I will find thee, my lady.
Thy true servant amore, Lancelot du Lac.
(light medieval music)
(magical ringing)
(hooves clopping)
I told thee I would find thee.
Welcome to Camelot, Lady Katherine.
(bright medieval music)
(MultiCom Jingle)