Hey, who are you?
Do you know what happened?
You mean you didn't see that?
See what?
There was a big flash of
light, everything went bright.
I didn't see anything.
Do you have a TV?
Can we see if there's
anything on the news, please?
Okay.
Come on.
Are you alone?
- Yeah, why?
- Can I get you something to drink?
- Sure, sure.
I'm Sasha, by the way.
- I'm Cole.
- Thanks.
- What are you doing way out here?
- I was with my boyfriend,
and then he was gone, he disappeared.
- I'm sure he's around.
What do you say we go into town?
He probably got lost.
It's pretty easy to do around here.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Sorry about the outhouse.
- Oh, it's all right.
I've been camping before.
- What do you say we call it a night?
I won't try anything, I promise.
- Okay.
- You take the
bed, I'll take the couch.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Can I get you anything?
- Just a glass of water.
- Okay.
- There you are.
- Morning.
Know what you're thinking.
It's the 2000s, and this guy
still gets his water from a creek.
- I wasn't gonna say anything.
- Just like to enjoy the
simpler things in life.
- I wish my life was simple.
- Would you mind?
- Sure.
- So, I was thinking about
what you said last night,
about the flash of light.
What do you think it was?
- Hey, wait!
- Sasha!
Hey.
What was all that about?
- There was a little girl.
- Where?
I'm sorry.
- For what?
- I know you're worried right now.
- First Blake, then this
little girl shows up.
I just don't know what the
hell's going on anymore.
- I don't know about any girl, except you.
But it can't just be the two of us.
Have you read it?
- Parts of it, when I was younger.
- You don't think-
- The rapture?
- Yeah.
- I thought about it,
but everybody's gone.
- I didn't think about that.
I mean, surely we're not the only two
sinning nonbelievers around.
- Blake believes in God.
- Yeah, me, too.
- Then where has everybody gone?
- I don't know.
I'm gonna find out, though.
- Somebody doesn't get out much.
- Yeah, one of the perks of
working at the factory, I guess.
- Yeah.
- I don't really go into
town unless I have to.
- I don't suppose you get
Chinese delivery out here.
Any cell service, any cell signal yet?
- Nah, it doesn't really work up here.
- What happened to you?
I guess we'll save that for another time.
Look, thanks for letting me stay.
I really appreciate it.
You didn't have to.
- Yeah, I did.
It's nice to have someone to talk to,
even for a little while.
But my people skills could
probably use a little work.
- You're like the Tom
Cruise of cabin dwellers.
- Show me the money.
Hey.
- Hey.
Do you mind if I clean up a little bit?
- Yeah, be my guest.
- Do you mind?
- Sure.
I guess I'll see you in the morning.
- Night.
Oh, if you need to, use
the water in the jug,
and, if you have to go-
- I'll take it outside.
- Yeah.
Oh, also, if you want, I
have a shirt you can use.
Just throwing that out there.
- Thanks.
- All right.
Night.
- Hey, can I get that shirt?
- Yeah.
- I saw her photo.
She was beautiful.
You scared me.
I'm Sasha, what's your name?
- Mya.
- Hi, Mya.
What are you doing here?
Do you know what happened?
Can you tell me?
Can I trust Cole?
- Shh.
- Hey, are you still up?
Sorry to bother you.
- It's all right.
- I thought I heard voices.
- Sometimes I talk in my sleep.
- I'm sorry, I didn't
know you were sleeping.
- Oh, it's just late.
- I can't sleep right now.
I don't-
- What is it?
You can tell me.
- I'll let you get some rest.
What are you doing in my house?
- We need to talk, Cole.
- How do you know my name?
- That's unimportant.
Come sit down.
- I'll stand, thanks.
- She's dangerous.
- Sasha?
- Mm hmm.
Her past is clouded in mystery.
- I don't exactly have
the best past, either.
- You need to get rid of
her, before it's too late.
- Get rid of her?
I just met her.
- You know, your father once-
- Whoa, whoa, you knew my father?
- Yes.
But don't trouble yourself
about that right now.
- Do you know where everyone's gone?
- You've been dealt a particularly unique
hand of cards, my friend.
There's nothing I can say to give you
a satisfactory explanation
for what you're going through.
- I just want answers.
- You're gonna have to
figure it out on your own,
and you don't have much time.
- Time for what?
- If you don't get rid of her soon,
everything you know is in
danger of becoming extinct.
- How much time do I have?
- A week, maybe less.
- Hey.
What's your name?
- It's Flynn, but that's not important.
Clock's ticking, Cole.
- Hey, about last-
- Look, I'm-
- Go ahead.
- It's okay.
- Everything's a little off.
I really don't know what's
going on around here.
- You're not the only one.
- See, that's just it.
- What do you mean?
- Do you really think
we're the only ones left?
- I don't know.
I mean, if so, why us?
I don't think I'd be very
good for starting over with.
- I'm not perfect, either.
- You seem all right to me.
I mean, you're female.
- I'm no Eve, but I can give it a shot.
She is the one that tempted Adam.
- You planning on tempting me?
- Got any forbidden fruit laying around?
- I'm sorry.
- What do you mean?
- I couldn't help but notice you're upset.
I'm on my way inside, on my own.
I know it's a little lame,
but if you'd like to-
- Sure.
- Sure what?
- I'll join you.
- Really?
- I'm here, you're here.
Might as well make the most of it.
- Okay.
- I'm Sasha.
- Blake.
What happened back there?
- Asshole.
- Listen, as guys,
we're wired to be dicks.
It's only through proper
training and conditioning
that we can treat women with respect.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- I thought we really had something.
- She was your cousin.
- But we really connected.
- Blood is thicker than water, boys.
At least, that's what they say.
Hit me.
- Saddle up, little doggies,
we's going out on the
open prairie tonight.
- How about you, Chuck,
how's your love life?
- Eh, you know, I do all right.
- All right, huh?
- He's dating my best friend Kate.
- When did this happen?
- You knew?
- We're friends, doofus, and we're girls.
We talk.
- You talk, do you, is that what you do?
And what do you talk about,
other than my scorching good looks.
- Just girl stuff.
- Beer, boobs, and football?
- You guessed it, Mikey.
- Whose boobs?
- Can we please stay
on the matter at hand?
- And what matter is that?
- Kate!
What did she say about me?
- Hit me.
- Oh, did I?
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
- It's all right.
Let's get outta here.
- Yeah.
- If anyone
can hear this message,
you are.
If anyone can hear this message,
you are not alone.
- Why do you keep doing that?
- You startle easily.
- You knew this was the end
of the world, didn't you?
Why didn't you tell me?
- Look, we need to go.
- Where?
Cole's the only one around.
Don't you think it's better
if we stick together?
- Glad to have you back.
- I'm sorry about last night.
- You're free to leave whenever you want.
It's not a prison here.
- I know, it's-
- It's fine.
- It's not like me to just take
off without saying goodbye.
- So, is that was this is?
Maybe we should go our own separate ways,
for a little while.
- What are you doing?
- Losing what's left of my sanity.
- Why do you have all these?
You're not one of those
end of the world type creeps, are you?
- No, actually, I haven't
even read half of these books.
Besides, I don't even own a bomb shelter.
I'm pretty sure that's a requirement.
- Yeah.
- I'll let you know if I find anything.
- You're pathetic.
You've really let yourself go.
You're pathetic.
You have really let
yourself go.
- Mom?
- Don't give me that!
Is this how you wanna spend
the rest of your life,
or what's left of it?
- I don't know what to do.
Things haven't been the same since-
- So you decided to just waste away.
- Well, I don't even
know if there's a world
for me to be part of anymore.
- God!
- I mean, for all I know,
I'm the last man on earth.
- Oh, well, what about
that girl
you've been spending so much time with?
- Sasha.
- Tramp.
- She's not a tramp, she's
just as confused as I am.
- No one will ever be as confused as you.
- I devoted my life to you!
- Whatever
helps you sleep at night.
- This is the end of the world, and you.
You're dead.
What the hell am I missing?
Candace?
Did you do what you need to?
- Yeah.
What if we are the last people on Earth?
- I don't know.
Repopulate?
- You would like that, wouldn't you?
You are totally into me, aren't you?
- I've seen better.
- Oh, better, huh?
Do you see any better around here?
- I don't see anybody around here.
- That's what I thought.
- So where'd you go?
It's all right, you don't have to say it.
- It's just things have
been so strange lately.
- You mean besides the apocalypse?
There's been a lot of other weird stuff
going on around here.
- Weird how?
- Well, I had an argument
with my dead wife,
and I also had a
conversation with my mother,
who is also dead.
- Really.
- I've also been seeing this guy Flynn.
- Who's he?
- What is it?
- Nothing.
- Please, tell me I'm not going crazy.
- Better prep the padded
room, reservation for two.
- Come on.
- No offense, but those clothes
look like they've seen better days.
- They're all I have.
- Still have some of my
wife's clothes in the closet.
- Oh, you don't have to.
- It's okay.
She has no need for them anymore,
so you're welcome to help yourself.
- Thank you.
What do you think?
- You look good.
- Yeah, I know.
- I'm glad you decided to come back.
- Yeah, me, too.
I know it's none of my business,
but why haven't you, you
know, gotten back out there?
- When you meet someone
who just really takes
your breath away.
- Well, what happened, if
you don't mind me asking?
- She was out collecting
water from the creek,
the way she did every morning.
She loves being outdoors.
Something just felt wrong.
So I went out to go check on her.
- I'm so sorry.
- Her ring was laying nearby.
- It's all right.
I'm here, love.
What is it?
- Nothing, it's just
something she used to say.
- Oh.
- What is this?
- Hey, what's that?
- Looks like she was writing a book.
- You should probably respect her privacy.
- I have to read that.
- She wouldn't want you
thumbing through her things.
- Well, why wouldn't she tell me about it?
- Everybody has secrets, Cole.
Some things are better left alone.
- What did I
tell you about the girl?
- Jeez.
- Well?
- Yeah, I know what you said,
it's just-
- You like her.
- There might be something to her.
- Yeah.
She's gorgeous, possibly the
last woman on the planet,
and, you know.
- And what?
- And she reminds you of?
- No.
- You miss her?
- Of course I miss her,
but Sasha's not even-
- There's things you
still don't understand.
- There's a hell of a
lot I don't understand.
Women are just one of those things.
- Cole, there's forces
working against you.
- Why are you even here.
There's no way that you can be real.
- What's reality?
- Why are we talking philosophy?
- If your brain thinks
something is real, it's real.
- My brain tells me there
is no way that you're real.
But here we are, carrying on
like two characters in a bad soap opera.
Are you real or not?
- You decide.
- Flynn?
Flynn?
- My God, are you okay?
- I'll live.
- What happened?
- I thought I saw my
wife's ring in the creek.
- So you dove in?
- No, I slipped.
- Let's get you cleaned up.
Let's get a shower.
That's a new look.
- Well, it's time for a change.
What are we gonna do
with the rest of our day?
- We could just stay in bed.
- You're something
else, you know that?
- Oh, I know.
Blake!
- What's wrong, baby?
- What are you doing here?
- Rocking your world, if I'm not mistaken.
What are you doing with this loser?
- Cole?
- How many guys are you sleeping with?
You know, I never would've
pegged you for a cheater.
- That's not fair!
- No, what's not fair
is you don't whether or
not I'm dead or alive,
and, yet, here you are banging this idiot.
- You disappeared!
- How do you know I just didn't go
down to the pub, get shit-faced,
and end up in the gutter
for a couple of days?
- I don't know what you want me to say.
- No, you know what?
I see where I stand.
- Wait, Blake!
- Did you say something?
- No, I was talking out loud.
- Okay.
Wanna try heading out to the pub?
- Yeah, I'll get dressed.
- All right.
- You think we're gonna
find anything in there?
It's worth a shot.
- At the very least,
we can get some drinks.
- Oh, hell yeah.
- Are you good at pool?
- I can kick your ass.
- I need to hit the head.
Where do you think the bathroom's at?
Follow the signs, okay.
Oh, here we go.
I'll go this way, and you go that way.
Are you seeing this?
- Uh huh.
I was not expecting people.
- Let's mingle.
- Hey, bud.
- Me?
- Come here.
- Thanks.
Do I know you?
- Nah, man, you don't know me,
but maybe you should.
- Okay.
- Drink up.
But I know you.
You're the apocalypse guy.
- So you're not real, either?
- Perception is reality.
Everyone knows that.
- Okay, are you the Riddler or?
- No, man, no, I'm not the Riddler.
I'm Blake.
- Hi, Blake.
- Sasha's Blake.
- Oh.
Well, hey, she's around here.
I'm sure she'd be really happy-
- It's not her I'm interested in.
- Oh.
What can I do for you?
- You can stay the hell away from my girl.
- Look, I didn't know that she was-
- I know what you did.
- Okay.
No offense, but as far as I can tell,
she's the only one who's
real in here, besides me.
Thanks for the drink.
- Keep it real.
- What did I tell you about the girl?
- I know, I know.
- You're not listening.
She's coming.
- Who's your friend?
I'm Sasha.
What the hell is his problem?
- He's a comic.
Find anyone interesting to talk to?
- Just one of my imaginary friends.
- We should probably head back.
- Cole, we might not get
another chance like this.
- Let's go.
- Blake!
How ya feeling?
- How do I look?
- Like shit.
I talked to him, you know.
- And you didn't say anything?
- I didn't know who he was, at first.
He's not real, you know.
- How do we even know what's real anymore?
- What if they're just
distracting us from-
- What, from what we're
supposed to be doing?
- Yeah
- What are we supposed to be doing?
- I'm reading that book.
- What book?
- Candace's book.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Trying to find out
what's so damn important
she didn't want me to know about it.
"They lived in a quaint cabin in the woods
"outside a small Colorado town.
"A soft flowing creek ran
behind their loving home,
"and provided the perfect backdrop
"for what they hoped would one day be home
"to their future children."
Is this about us?
"Sasha knew."
Sasha?
"Sasha knew she could never
tell him what happened.
"He would be crushed.
"Blake had always wanted a child,
"and the loss would devastate him.
"Several years passed,
but she never told him
"about the miscarriage.
"Their love had been the
one constant in their lives,
"and she didn't wanna do
anything to put that in jeopardy.
"Maybe one day they would
know the love of a child,
"but Mya, she was her secret."
What the hell is this?
- I
told you not to read it.
- Why are you in this book?
- We knew you wouldn't understand.
- We?
- I'm leaving.
I can't stand to watch this
train wreck any longer.
- Wait, Sasha!
Sasha!
Sasha, where are you going?
- I shouldn't have come back.
Just leave me alone.
- Dad?
What are you doing here?
- You need to quit worrying
about what other people are doing,
and start thinking about
what you need to do.
- Which is what?
- It's time for you to make a choice.
- What choice?
Dad.
Are you Mya?
My father blamed me.
He climbed into a bottle,
and he never looked back.
What do you want?
Hey!
- Get over yourself.
- Can I help you?
Just here to go through all my shit?
- I'm here on business.
- Well, I'm not buying.
- I want my life back.
You're obviously confused, Cole, as usual.
- Why are you even here?
Do you wanna borrow
some sugar or something?
- You're funny.
Sugar, nah, not sugar.
Blood, maybe.
Maybe pain.
- What are you talking about?
- Was I rambling again?
Maybe there's something in the water.
- Get to the point!
- Take it easy, I come in peace.
- Why don't I believe you?
- 'Cause I'm obviously lying.
We're all lying, Cole.
You're just too dumb to figure it out.
- Then why don't you tell me
what the hell is going on?
- The answers will come, in time.
And Sasha, she'll come back to you.
- I thought she was your girl.
- Things change.
- Look, man, I didn't mean to.
- Woulda, coulda, shoulda.
I'm not here for excuses or apologies.
- Then what the hell do you want?
- Don't make the same mistakes I did.
- What in the hell is
going on around here?
- Let's go stretch your legs.
- I saw my mom.
- She's around.
- I had a daughter.
I've been feeling terrible.
- Well, that's to be expected.
- Really?
- Look, I'm not here to
answer your questions.
- Then why are you here?
- That's not important.
What is important is this.
- What do you know about this?
- There's nothing but trouble in there.
You best get rid of it now
while you still have a chance.
- I had a daughter.
- Heed my warning, son.
That book is dangerous.
It'll only hold you back,
and you're running out of time.
I'm afraid this is farewell.
Good luck, I'll be rooting for you.
- What now?
The hell's your problem?
- You know what they
say, if I can't have her.
- You're not real.
- That real enough for you?
There ain't room enough in the world
for the both of us, friend.
- What the hell do you want?
- Face it, Cole, you're all alone.
- Still reading those books?
- They're actually pretty fascinating.
- This laundry is fascinating.
- You know, one day, we'll have some kids,
and then we can make
them do all the chores.
- Is that why you wanna have kids?
- I wanna have kids because I love you,
and I want some little rascals
to share that love with.
- Good answer.
- What do you say we start trying?
- Now?
What about the laundry?
- It can wait.
I used to think about what I
would do if I ever lost you.
I'm talking to people that can't be real,
sleeping with women who aren't you.
I don't know what I'm doing anymore.
But I gotta do something.
"Blake leaned over to Sasha and whispered
"sweetly into her ear."
What the hell are you trying to tell me?
You're not real.
- Don't you see, farm boy?
- See what?
- You'll never defeat
me 'cause you are me.
- No, no, come on, come on, come on.
You're all I have left.
Candace?
I don't understand.
- Come with me, Cole.
- What's happening?
- There's something in the water.
- What do you mean?
- It's affecting you.
You have to make a choice.
- You or Sasha.
- No, the truth or.
- The lie.
I'm having such a good time with you,
but I know it's not real.
Am I the last man on Earth?
- Is that
what's important to you?
- What about Sasha, the book?
- It was too personal
to use our real names.
- Blake said...
Theater.
I'm sorry.
- What do you mean?
- I couldn't help but notice you're upset.
I'm on my way in, all by myself.
I know it's kinda lame,
but I was wondering-
- Sure.
- Sure what?
- I'll join you.
- Really?
- I'm here, you're here,
might as well make the most of it.
- Okay.
That was the best day of my life.
- Mine, too.
- What about Flynn?
- You don't remember?
Cole?
- Can I help you?
- Boy, you've grown.
- I'm sorry, do I know you?
- Last time I saw you, you were
knee-high to a grasshopper.
My name's Flynn, but that's not important.
I'm an old friend of your father's.
- My father doesn't live here.
- Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry to be
the one to tell you this,
but your dad passed away.
I know you weren't close.
- Do you know what happened?
- He was drinking,
like he often did, you know.
Well, I'm sorry you
had to hear it from me.
I'll be on my way.
- Hey, thanks for letting me know.
- No problem, kid.
See you around.
- That was a hard day.
- Yeah.
Why are all these visions, these people,
trying to keep Sasha, us, us,
why are they trying to keep us apart?
- Part of you would want to keep
the illusion alive forever,
but your body can't take
much more of the poison.
- I'm not ready.
I still have so much...
I still have so much.
- This is Gunter Harrison.
We have regained radio signal.
I repeat, we are back on the air.
If anyone can hear this
message, you are not alone.
There are others.
We are gathering in the
small town of Black Hawk.
We have food and fresh water.
I urge you to leave the
comfort of your homes,
make your way to Black
Hawk as quickly as you can,
and, whatever you do, do
not trust the strangers.
I repeat, do not trust the strangers.