♪♪
(man)
22-F.
23-F.
(indistinct shouting)
♪♪
(indistinct chatter echoing)
(man)
Hey, Winston!
(Winston)
Yeah?
(indistinct chatter)
(man)
All right, ten minutes!
Ten minutes!
(congregation singing)
♪ Melt the clouds
of sin and sadness ♪
♪ Drive the dark of doubt away ♪
♪ Giver of immortal gladness ♪
♪ Fill us
with the light of day ♪
♪ All Thy works with joy
surround Thee ♪
♪ Earth and heaven reflect
Thy rays ♪
♪ Stars and angels sing
around Thee ♪
♪ Center of unbroken praise ♪
♪ Field and forest,
vale and mountain ♪
♪ Blooming meadow,
flashing sea ♪
(singing fading)
♪ Chanting bird
and flowing fountain... ♪♪
(church bells ringing)
Elaine?
Oh.
Here's the letter
I was telling you about.
Oh, right!
Thank you so much
for doing this.
Thank you for the letter.
Sure.
Thanks, Mary Ann.
Bye.
(woman)
Bye! See you next week!
(man)
Yeah, good-bye.
(mouthing silently)
(woman)
Bye now.
♪♪
(Elaine)
Dear Mr. Skyler,
your letter was forwarded to me
by my church.
I was asked to volunteer
to be your pen pal.
I'm not much of a writer,
so you'll have to bear with me.
I don't really know
where to begin,
except to introduce myself.
How do you do?
Don't you wonder
what we will have in common?
Maybe we will become
the best of friends.
(security guard chattering)
I have opened
a post-office box,
and I will check it every day
for your response.
Write soon, please.
People in my life see me
as a patient person,
but I'm as antsy as they come.
Be well and know that God
looks after all his children.
Sincerely, Elaine Hodges.
There you go.
(grunting)
Ah!
(sighing)
I should do us both
a favor.
Die in my sleep.
We a little grumpy
this morning?
One good
myocardial infarction,
get the whole damn thing
over with.
If I go,
will you be all right?
Edna's not here yet,
and I'd like to get
an early start.
Well, to hell with Edna.
Answer me, Daddy.
I gotta go.
(Addison)
I'll be fine!
(door closes)
All right, well,
the juice is in the fridge.
And the coffee's on.
I'll see you tonight.
Hey, Bobby.
Miss Hodges.
Well, what are you
doing walking?
Flat tire.
Oh, well, hey, here.
(whirring)
(Elaine)
There you go.
(Bobby laughing)
Miss Hodges.
What's so funny?
Oh, nothing.
Yellow.
What's yellow?
The classroom
was yellow.
Yes, it was.
I can read books.
No one tried harder
than you, Bobby.
The classroom
was yellow.
Yes, it was.
All right,
chapter four.
Everyone on 32?
Benoit?
Okay...
"Three days later,
Nicky was walking home
"from his tuba lesson.
"It was his birthday.
"He gave a little skip
of excitement.
The day of the party
had finally come."
Are you following along?
"When Nicky got to his
little house, it was all dark."
Sheri.
"His heart was going..."
(all)
"Thump! Thump! Thump!"
"'I'd better act
very surprised,' thought Nicky."
(gasping)
All right, pull up, Sheri.
Come here, pull up
to the table.
(indistinct chatter)
(Charlie)
Dear Elaine,
I'm happy you replied
to my letter.
It is as though
I've reached through the bars
and taken grasp of a hand.
Yours.
Thank you.
Hodges.
Elaine Hodges.
I like the sound of it.
It speaks to me.
Sure.
(Charlie)
There is a reason you and I,
out of all the people
in the world, will be friends.
'Cause I believe
there's a reason for everything.
Most in here don't want
to face that,
but I see it
as a healing thing.
Okay, everybody,
hurry up!
(Charlie)
I kept your letter.
I find that it heartens me
at night
knowing that we have
so much in common already.
Yes, already we hold a curiosity
about each other,
a bridge across a moat
of loneliness.
So what do you look like,
Elaine?
Send me a picture of yourself.
(bell ringing)
I wanna see your face.
I'll bet you're pretty.
I will think of you
until you write again.
Your truly,
Charles S. Skyler.
(camera shutter clicking
and camera beeping)
♪♪
(pounding on door)
(door opens)
(Addison, echoing)
What are you doing here?
Get out of my house!
You must be out
of your mind!
Put that gun away!
You hear me?
(woman shrieking)
There's a gun!
Addison!
(gunshot)
Mommy? Daddy?
(Addison)
God, you're out of your mind!
(gunshot, Addison shouts)
(man speaking indistinctly)
(gun clicking)
(gunshot echoing)
Had my dream again
last night.
Oh, please, you're not
gonna go through that
again, are you?
Sorry.
It's always the same.
It's--
Monotonous.
To you.
I can't stop myself
from dreaming it over and over.
I wish we could talk about it.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
I never know why you say that.
I do wish we could talk
about things.
You'd learn nothing.
How many times
have I said this?
Something snaps
in someone's mind
and blood spills.
It happens.
We were unlucky.
Just plain unlucky.
Now, can we talk
about something else?
Edna's birthday is coming up.
What do you think
we should get her?
I fired her this morning.
(Addison groaning)
Oh, why do I have to put up
with this nonsense?
Hey.
You didn't think I'd leave
just because he fired me,
did you?
I wouldn't blame you
if you did.
See, he knows that I know.
I don't mean to rat
on the man,
but seeing as how he wants
to treat me this way,
I want you to know I found
another liquor bottle.
Hidden.
Where does he get it?
(Edna)
I don't know how
he gets it.
Smuggles it
in there somehow.
All right,
I gotta go.
(Addison)
It's not in
the right position!
What the hell?
All this time you've
been working with me,
you should know where
to put it!
(sighing)
(kids)
♪ Boat's too little,
better build an ark ♪
♪♪
♪ Bring the best of the animals,
two-by-two ♪
♪ Something's telling Noah
what to do... ♪
Keep going around.
(kids)
♪ When the rain starts falling,
I'll take care of you... ♪
Andy!
Go around!
(laughter)
(together)
♪ Noah's Ark... ♪
Gotta go back.
(kids)
♪ Something's telling Noah ♪
♪ Build an ark ♪
♪ Noah's Ark, Noah's Ark... ♪
Honey, look at Andy!
(laughing)
That's cute.
(man)
We're gonna have to
get a shot of that.
(kids)
♪ Bring a male and a female,
big and small ♪
♪ Fat and the skinny
and the short and tall... ♪♪
♪ Noah's Ark... ♪
(humming melody)
(Addison groaning)
Daddy?
(Addison)
Hey... yeah.
(clock chiming)
(groaning)
(grunting loudly)
(Addison groaning)
Oh, I don't want--
Why did I--
(groaning)
Thank you.
Ah...
(Elaine)
Dear Mr. Skyler,
your letter is
surprisingly poetic.
My goodness.
You will be
an interesting pen pal indeed.
I teach the first grade
in our local elementary school,
and I love the enthusiasm
of six-year-olds.
I live with my father
in the same house I was raised.
I take care of him
as he is an invalid
bound to a wheelchair.
Oh, there are moments,
when I look
at a brilliant sunrise,
for instance,
and then I think
of what other kind of life
I might have led...
out there beyond the horizon...
in some exotic place.
But those are silly thoughts.
Enough about me.
Now, you tell me who you are.
Write to me.
I look forward
to your next letter.
Sincerely, Elaine Hodges.
(Charlie)
Dear Elaine,
I'm sorry to hear
about your father,
but with due respect,
I could puke at your letter.
You piss on your freedom,
but it's the only thing
that makes you something.
But choose a door
and open the damn thing.
Did I tell you I'm a cook
in the prison galley?
It is slop, I'm afraid,
but I can't cook what I choose.
One day, I will.
One day.
(Charlie)
Hey.
Hey!
Boy, everything you touch
ends up smelling like an armpit!
Son of a-- oh!
(whimpering)
Oh!
(Charlie)
Tell me about your father
and what he's told you.
He's crippled.
Why is he
in a wheelchair?
And what put him there?
I need to know.
Yours truly,
Charles S. Skyler.
P.S.
Your letter
smells of perfume.
I thank you.
(Addison)
What are you doing here?
Get out of my house!
Are you out of your mind?
(woman)
There's a gun!
Addison!
(Addison)
You shot my wife!
Oh! Aah!
(gun clicking)
(woman)
Oh, my...
(gunshot echoing)
(Elaine)
Dear Charlie,
late at night,
when I was six years old,
an intruder murdered my mother,
crippled my father,
and then committed suicide.
My father
will not discuss it.
If I try and talk about it,
he gets angry.
Sometimes he stops talking to me
altogether for days.
(Addison)
That's it!
(Elaine)
You should not
judge me harshly.
He's my father.
And if a person has no loyalty
to their own family,
then I... I simply just
don't know what else there is.
I live the way I do
because it's what I want.
I'm sorry,
but you've touched a nerve.
There is a door to open.
Let it be your own.
I will join you in prayer
for that day.
Sincerely, Elaine Hodges.
(man)
Have a seat, Charlie.
(door closes)
Okay, Charlie.
Your time's up.
You're out.
But... I think
you're a bad bet.
All you've ever known
is trouble
and the four walls
of your cell.
You'll be back.
(Charlie clears throat)
Yeah, I'm not a threat
to anybody.
All I wanna do is put my life
back together
and get a job.
'Cause I got a skill now.
I could be a fry cook to start
and maybe...
maybe someday work
in a fancy restaurant.
You won't see me again.
See, this time...
I'm out for good.
Somebody cares now.
I'm not alone.
I want to be a part
of that world out there.
And I don't want
to hurt anybody.
I just want to be a part
of that world.
I can taste it.
(phone ringing)
(phone continues ringing)
Hello?
Just a minute.
It's for you!
Gentleman caller.
(Elaine)
Hello?
Elaine, hi.
Hi.
(Addison)
Your pasta
is turning to paste!
We, uh...
didn't get a chance
to, uh, speak at the school.
Weren't the kids cute?
Yeah.
You looked really,
really beautiful.
I've been thinking a lot
about you lately.
If it's true love,
he'll call you back!
(Addison)
Blah, blah, blah.
Mm-hmm?
Talk to him
about your menopause!
That'll shut him up!
(Elaine)
Yeah, I'm... good.
No.
Mm-hmm.
(grunts)
(clock chiming)
(Elaine)
Mm-hmm.
(Timothy)
Do you think...
we could get together?
A cup of coffee
or something?
(grunts)
Elaine!
(groans)
There you go.
Your legs are burnt,
but I doubt they'll blister.
I wish I would die.
Now, now.
Just a foolish,
helpless old man.
Shh, you just rest.
You'll be all right.
I'd be lost
if you weren't here.
I couldn't take care of myself.
You know that.
Daddy...
What did Tim--
uh, why was he calling?
Just to stay in touch.
Oh, well, you'd have never
been happy with him, never.
Well, don't leave.
I'm not going anywhere.
No, I mean now.
Sit, huh?
Stay with me
till I go to sleep, please.
Okay.
(bed whirring)
(Addison groaning)
No.
No, you never would've
been happy with him.
Never, no.
(dog barking in distance)
(indistinct chatter on TV)
I've gotta go now.
Early day for me.
What? What? What?
(slowly)
I've got to go now.
Why?
It's my birthday.
Oh... you wake me up
just for that?
Well, I just thought
you should know I was leaving
in case you decided
to choke yourself to death.
Have you got any money on you?
Oh, if I did,
I wouldn't give any to you.
No, I mean borrow it.
With you, loaning it
is the same as giving it.
I'll pay it right back.
Huh?
10 bucks?
Just as soon as tear it up,
throw it to the wind.
So, go.
Stop making such
a big production out of it.
Hope you don't have
a car accident.
I bet you can't
swallow one whole.
(plate clatters)
"I.O.U."
(Charlie)
Dear Elaine,
by the time
you get this letter,
I will be a free man,
released.
I credit your prayers.
(mimics engine revving)
I've dreamed of my freedom
for so long,
but it's not a life I know.
And it's one I've been denied
so many times before.
They said things
at the prison.
They think I will fail.
My blood runs cold when I hear
their words because...
I'm afraid they're true.
That's why I need you, Elaine.
I'm setting sail
with no compass.
You will be my eyes.
You'll speak the language.
And you need me, Elaine,
in ways that you
don't even know.
The key you hold in your hand
will unlock nothing less
than the truth.
(knocking on window)
(gasps)
Oh...
Hector.
You're very nervous,
Elaine.
Do you want to speak to me
about something?
I got heart palpitations.
They say it's nothing,
but I go to an HMO,
and I don't trust them.
Mm-hmm.
Your father was
a wonderful doctor.
It's too bad he doesn't
practice anymore.
Yeah.
I'm sorry to cut you off.
I'm gonna have to go.
Does he ever think
of coming out of retirement?
Oh, I don't think so.
I gotta go now, Hector.
Okay, well, let me know
if he changes his mind.
Okey-doke.
(clock chiming)
(dishes clattering)
Oh, darn!
I banged into the sideboard,
damn it.
Broke this family heirloom.
Bull.
This vase has been
in the family
for generations.
I gotta fix it
before Elaine comes home.
Came all the way from...
Scandinavia, damn it!
Looks more like
the five-and-dime to me.
You'd be heartbroken,
you would be,
if you knocked over
something like that,
like an elephant tusk
or something
that your great-grandmammy
lugged all the way over
on a slave ship.
I ought to push you
off a cliff.
Come on, Edna,
help me!
And why should I help you?
Get the glue for me.
It's down in the basement.
It's probably on a work bench.
How do you know
what's down there?
My basement,
isn't it?
Huh?
Mm-hmm.
Aye, good girl,
good girl.
(locks clicking)
(Edna)
Let me out of here!
Wait!
(Edna pounding on door)
Rat-faced snake-hearted gimp!
(exhales)
(indistinct chatter on TV)
(meat sizzling)
(bell ringing)
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Say, you like your cook?
Well, he shows up,
works hard.
I got no complaints,
I guess.
(door closes)
How come?
Mm-hmm.
Just curious, I guess.
I'm a chef.
Oh, yeah?
American or, uh, cuisine?
Uh, French.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, you might've heard
of it.
It's called,
uh, "En Prison."
Oh, yeah, I think I heard
of that place, yeah, sure.
Right on.
Whoa! Oh!
Holy cow.
Hey! Fire!
I got it! I got it!
What's going on in here?
I got it!
All right!
(overlapping shouting)
He got out
and he knows where I live.
I closed my post-office box,
and this morning,
that one came
to the house.
It unnerved me.
I don't know what
I was thinking.
What can you expect
from a person like that?
It's okay.
We all make mistakes.
It was nice to hear from you
the other night.
It was nice talking to you.
Look, I'll, uh...
I'll go talk to him.
Thank you.
Anytime.
I don't mean
to overreact.
He seemed
a little crazy and--
I'll take care of it.
You make a handsome family.
It's worked out for me.
Some thing's
I'd never change.
The woman I married
wasn't my first choice.
You know, I, uh, I looked out
my window the other night.
I could swear
I saw you watching us.
Were you?
I need your help.
Let me talk
to your cook.
Sure.
Oh, he's a trained chef,
by the way.
(Charlie groaning)
Elaine and I go back a long way,
and she's had a hard go,
and I'm not gonna
let scum like you
make it any harder for her.
You understand?
You've been warned, Charlie.
(panting and groaning)
What's going on here?
(indistinct chatter)
(Charlie)
There you go, Miss.
(woman)
Thank you.
You're new.
Hey, I started last week.
You cook this?
Was there something wrong
with it?
I wanna shake your hand.
You, sir, are a genius.
I've never seen
anything like--
(stammering)
Who'd have thought...
this cheese?
Explain the...
Well, that's cream cheese.
It's, um, it's herbed.
"Herbed"?
Yeah, it's, um...
it's tarragon,
savory, thyme,
little salt and pepper,
and the tiniest bit of mint.
Yeah, I experimented
with the mint, actually.
This is the best cheese omelet
I've ever eaten in my life.
I appreciate that.
Stick around, sir.
Gourmet.
Nothing less.
(Charlie)
Dear Elaine,
I said I meant you no harm,
but you're hiding from me.
Why?
I've done nothing to hurt you.
We can help each other.
I know it.
We can help each other be free
of everything
that's gone wrong
in the past.
You don't deserve the life
you've been forced to lead.
And I can say the same
about myself.
Though we're so different,
we're kindred.
We're family to each other.
And you'll come
to know that in time.
In time.
So don't cry.
Don't be afraid.
Your friend,
Charles S. Skyler.
Hello?
(Charlie)
I could smell your perfume
from down the hall.
Mr. Skyler.
Mmm.
Your--
The door was open.
So, dear Elaine.
I'm glad you came.
Thought you would.
I don't believe
in locked doors.
You look as pretty
as your picture.
I'm not sure what you thought
you'd accomplish by coming here.
You should never have come
to this town.
You never thought I'd get out.
Right, Elaine?
Well, I understand.
I do.
You wanna hear
something true?
Some die behind bars,
but most get out
one day or another.
It's time and will.
That's the secret.
I volunteered to correspond
with a pen pal.
That was all.
If I misled you
in any way
about my life or my intentions,
I'm sorry, that was wrong.
But you frightened me
coming here.
And that lieutenant?
Is he a friend of yours?
Did you send him
to frighten me?
He enjoys his power.
But he's weak,
you know?
I seen that look
a thousand times
in a guard's eyes,
standing over me.
I liked your letters.
"Dear Charlie.
Dear Charlie,"
and "Sincerely, Elaine."
That's a nice way for people
to talk to each other, isn't it?
It's decent.
Why are you here?
You tell me about it,
that night a long time ago.
What?
The night
your father was shot,
your mama murdered.
Why?
Because it's important.
Cruel things like that,
they shape a person's life.
That's true.
And they say it helps
to talk about things
that hurt the most.
Well, you're hardly the person
I would talk to--
Losing everything so soon,
it's like tying an arm
behind your back
and pushing you off a plank.
How you gonna learn to swim?
It's not fair.
I appreciate your concern.
I'm proud of you though,
Elaine.
You sacrificed.
You kept yourself pure.
I could never
have done that.
Look, Mr. Skyler--
It's Charlie.
Charlie, I don't--
With everything
that happened to you,
with everything you'd given up
and lost...
you never hurt anybody.
Why would I want
to hurt anyone?
Well, you'd be surprised.
Yeah.
See, a guy like me
could learn from you.
I need you more than
I can put into words.
Everything good
that could happen to me
from this point on
depends on you.
Don't say that.
The world and I,
we're at odds.
And they know that
back where I came from.
They know I'm lost.
Lost like a baby just born
with nobody to help it.
These people running this way
and that way...
running in all this open space.
All this light
and choice.
You know, I went to a store
the other day
to buy a bar of soap,
and I stood in the aisle
for half an hour trying
to figure out which bar to buy.
(giggles)
It made my dizzy.
See, you can help it
stop spinning...
No, I can't.
...because it's your world,
and you've got no reason
to be afraid of it.
There's nothing I can do
for you, nothing.
Uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh,
everything you give,
I'll pay you back.
I'll pay you back
and I can set you free!
What are you talking about?
Come on.
There are a lot of ways
to spend life behind bars.
Now, you thought
about leaving him,
about having a life
of your own.
You can say it out loud!
Don't you talk to me
about my father, hmm?
He's helpless.
You don't understand
the situation.
Yeah, do you?
You know what happened
that night?
Lies are every bit
as much a cage as steel bars!
Who are you to talk to me
about these things?
You're in jail, Elaine.
You forget that,
you'll never get out!
I've lived with you forever.
Sometimes I'm not sure
who you are
or what you feel
about things.
I let you know
how I feel about you.
Always tried to protect you
from everything that I thought
might cause you pain,
like fathers do.
I don't think we know how
to talk to each other.
What's gotten into you lately?
You seem to be even worse than--
There's more to what happened
that night...
Don't start.
...than I have been allowed
to know.
Don't run from me!
Who shot you?
Why?
You never stop,
do you?
I need to know!
I mean, if there's something
hidden away, I deserve to know!
But I told you over and over
and over it was a stranger.
Now there's no more to tell.
Then why do you get so angry
when I ask?
Because you're asking me
for something
that I can't give you.
Or won't?
I lost my legs and my wife.
It was senseless.
A lunatic with a gun shot us.
Now, that is all I know.
What was his name?
He was a stranger!
How the hell
would I know his name?
I don't believe
he was a stranger!
Please, do this for me.
Out of my way.
Just say his name.
Am I being held prisoner
in my own house?
Addison!
Are you looking for this?
Who are you?
Oh, I'm a friend.
I don't have any friends!
I didn't say
I was your friend.
I'm a friend of Elaine.
Get off my property.
Go on!
Get the hell off of it!
You're an alcoholic.
Doesn't take a genius
to see it, Addison.
How do you know my name?
What do you want?
Boy, you bring nothing
but misery, old man.
What's the draw?
I'm calling a cop.
What?
A good gig,
old man.
Make life hard for everybody
and they just play along.
If I could get out
of this chair...
You tell me who shot you.
Just what is going on here?
You know, somebody put you
in a wheelchair.
You must know who it was.
That is my business.
And I don't talk about it!
You know,
if you still had your legs,
what do you think the odds are
Elaine would still be hanging
around here,
wasting her life taking care
of a piece of work like you?
You hide behind your legs,
Addison.
Why?
Why would I hide?
I'm not guilty of anything.
Guilt?
No.
I'm talking about punishment,
Addison.
Kill me or get out.
Whatever it is you're gonna do,
just do it!
(Edna)
Addison, I swear,
when I see you...
Don't you ever do that
to me again!
I swear to you,
Addison Hodges,
one day you're gonna
just push me too far!
I'm gonna make you rue the day
that you were born!
I won't be shoved around
by some stupid,
uneducated, no-good punk!
I won't!
What?
What do you mean?
I was just threatened
by a maniac
in my own backyard!
Who?
Your friend!
That's what he said.
He says he's a friend of yours.
What did he say exactly?
Well, I don't know.
He was looming over me.
I was afraid any second he was
gonna crack my skull open!
Who knows what he said?
But he's crazy
and he's going to kill us!
Well, why do you say that?
(stammering)
Well, because
he-he-he-he-he's insane.
'Cause he's--
Because it's random?
No.
No, not this time.
Someone picked us again?
Are you forgetting
the little matter
of you writing
to this bastard?
I'm surprised you didn't
sit out a-- an extra place mat!
You're upset.
Damn right I am.
Man like that
will do anything.
There's no conscience,
no-no-no-no logic.
(stammering)
It's-It's reptilian!
And we are
at the mercy of it!
Why are you looking at me
like that?
Huh?
Why?
(groans)
(horn honking)
(Elaine)
Mary Ann?
(engine turns over)
(tires screeching)
I'm sorry!
You okay?
Tim, I'm sorry.
That was reckless of me.
I'm sorry.
That was a close call.
I wasn't paying attention.
I just-- sorry.
What are you doing
out here?
Um...
I'm sorry.
You all right?
I'm fine.
God, I miss you.
Oh, Tim.
I miss you so much.
Oh...
♪♪
(congregation singing
in distance)
♪ Ocean depth of happy rest ♪
♪ Thou our Father,
Christ our Brother ♪
♪ All who live in love
are Thine ♪
♪ Teach us how to love
each other ♪
♪ Lift us to the joy divine ♪♪
Mary Ann!
Elaine.
I need to talk
to you.
What is it?
You're upset about something.
I saw you the other night.
Wednesday night.
On Main Street, coming out
of the apartment house.
Yes.
Of Charlie Skyler?
You know him.
You were there seeing him.
Yes, that's true.
What is this all about?
What are you doing?
Look, I'm very sorry,
Elaine.
I didn't know
he was going to get out.
The poor boy spent
most of his life in prison.
A boy?
He's a dangerous man.
And you led him to my door.
Elaine, he won't hurt you.
How do you know that?
You can't say that.
But you have no right
to point a finger.
He's not a piece of garbage.
I pity him.
(engine turns over)
(Timothy)
Come on, kids.
It's cold out here.
Come on.
(door opens and closes)
Boy, you miss things
you don't even realize.
Like squeezing a ball of dirt
in your hand.
(sniffs)
That's peperomia?
Used to read books
in the prison library,
and they had one
on horticulture.
Can remember everything
I read.
What do you want?
I told you what I want.
I don't know what this
is all about.
Mary Ann gave me
this letter.
Who is she to you?
Mary Ann Rutherford
married Sanford Rutherford
right here in this town,
27 years ago.
Her maiden name
was Skyler.
Look, I would've found you
someday anyway.
Even before I sent
my first letter,
I knew you lived in this town,
and I knew the name Hodges.
I knew the old man
was shot and crippled.
You torture me!
Just say what you know!
Well, the truth is like
everything else.
Nobody comes to it
unless they're afraid.
Stop it!
Well, what are you
afraid of, Elaine?
Are you afraid of me?
The hold your father
has on you?
Or are you afraid
of the years to come?
Now, that's a fear
that'll rise up in your throat
and choke you every bit
as much as a crazy man.
And when you think
you can't breathe,
you'll do anything.
And even the truth
will seem like a friend.
Now, you ask him
who she is.
You ask him.
I need to talk to you.
So, talk.
Who's this?
Do you recognize her?
Oh, I don't know.
I think she was
a patient of mine.
It's such a long time ago,
I don't--
What's her name?
What?
Where'd you get this?
I want to know everything
about this woman.
Now, how would I know
everything about her?
She was just
a patient of mine.
I don't know, maybe...
well, I think she lived
around here somewhere.
Matter of fact,
I think she died
rather suddenly.
How?
Oh, hemorrhage
or something.
"Or something"?
You watch your attitude,
young lady.
I've had just
about enough of this.
(phone ringing)
Hold on, whoever you are!
I'm here! I'm here!
Hello?
(Elaine)
Tim?
Ah, just a minute.
Kids, okay, that's enough.
Come on, Daddy's
on the phone now, all right?
Just hang on.
Okay, okay, that's it.
Come on, go, go!
(sighs)
This is not a good idea
to call here.
You won't look at me.
Now you don't wanna talk to me?
What have we done?
Uh, I think that my situation
is pretty obvious.
Uh, really?
Not too much is obvious
to me these days.
Are you all right?
No.
I took you to my bed.
Elaine...
That meant something.
Okay.
I'm gonna hang up.
Wait.
Good night, Daddy!
You have a beautiful family.
I know you'd never want
to see them hurting.
I need you to do something
for me.
Do you understand?
(door closes)
This file...
this file was never released
to the press.
The old chief and your father,
they were good friends.
Maybe he was a patient.
Both.
I-I don't know why you're
doing this to yourself.
Yeah, well, you're kind
to worry about me.
I do worry about you.
There are things in there
you shouldn't see.
Not alone.
Oh, my mother!
Who would d-do some--
(stammering)
Just tell me
what it says.
What does it say?
The file doesn't contain
a motive.
And it doesn't
identify the assailant
except to say
that it was a woman.
A woman?
(gun clicks and gunshot)
How can that be?
It was a woman?
(Elaine groaning and grunting)
(Elaine retching)
Honey, you all right?
Yeah, I'm all right.
I'm just-- I'm tired.
I just gotta get dressed.
You're pregnant.
What?
Don't be ridiculous.
You don't wanna lie
about a thing like that.
I think you'd be
a fine mother.
(Elaine sobbing)
Oh, honey.
Come-- oh, I--
Oh, it's o-- oh.
Look, you're not alone.
You remember that.
I'm not so sure
about that, Edna.
This is...
This is so stupid.
It's a gift.
It's something
you can call your own.
Does he know?
My father?
Oh, no, goodness.
Your man?
No.
I haven't found the right moment
to tell him.
She was my mother.
She was insane.
Now, that's too easy.
She and your father
were lovers.
I don't believe you.
Oh, you think you're special,
you should be spared?
From lies.
Well, no more lies, Elaine.
I was ten
when it happened.
We lived in a little house
maybe 15 miles or so from here.
We were poor
and she got sick.
We came to your dad
and he made her well.
And she was pretty.
He liked that.
He was rich, a doctor,
and he used her.
I don't need to hear this.
She knew he lied,
but she grew to love him.
To need him, yearn for him.
Then she was a fool.
Yeah, of course she was!
Your daddy knew that.
Your daddy likes being
with a fool
so he can get
what he wants!
You know that key
I gave you?
She wore it on a chain
that hung around her neck.
It opens up
that little house in back
where he'd practice medicine.
What do you think
of the truth, Elaine?
I can't say it's a blessing.
It's ruined my life.
And again,
the lies ruined yours.
I gotta get out of here.
He's cruel!
He takes from people
and he doesn't give back!
You want me to hate my father
for something that's over!
It's done!
You look at us.
Look at us
and tell me it's done!
It isn't done!
You ache
for something better.
You said so yourself.
It's time.
(horn honking)
♪♪
(Elaine)
Hey!
You bastard!
(grunts)
Hey, what's the matter
with you?
Are you crazy?
You're evil!
Save that crap
for your holy rollers!
Now, get out of my way.
You'll stay where are
if I have to knock you down!
You knew all along!
What?
What'd I know?
What the hell
do you want from me?
I want your confession!
How can you talk like this
to your father?
What gives you the right?
The right?
I gave my life over to you!
Dressed you! Bathed you!
Listened to you!
And now I wanna hear
the truth!
And I want to hear all of it!
All of it, now!
Say it!
Okay, okay!
You win!
It was no stranger.
It was someone I knew.
A woman.
She was on my doorstep,
begging for help,
full of disease!
It's what happens
when you live like a pig.
I shot her full
of antibiotics,
and unfortunately, she lived.
A medical service for which
you would receive payment?
Uh-huh, yeah,
you could say that,
I guess, yes.
You raped her!
Didn't have to.
She loved me.
Yeah.
She wanted me
to leave your mother!
You imagine that?
Huh?
I don't know what the hell
she was thinking,
but that's what she wanted.
Shut up!
It would've been kinder
to have pinned her down
and choked her!
Heh, in retrospect,
that would not have been
such a bad idea.
Oh...
Mea culpa.
(groans)
Eh, you're not
so happy now, are you?
Now that you know.
Oh...
(shivering)
Get hold of yourself.
Life goes on,
trust me.
And nothing
has to change.
Hmm?
No father.
It's going to change.
I'm pregnant.
I'm gonna have a baby.
(sniffles)
Baby?
(chuckling)
You... are going
to have a baby?
(laughing)
Now, who the hell
would want to have a--
Hey... Elaine?
Uh... it's a little
out of my area of expertise,
but, uh... it's no big deal
to terminate a pregnancy.
Particularly
one that's early on.
You've probably got a few weeks
left in your first trimester.
I'll fire up
the old autoclave,
do it myself, and no one
would be the wiser.
What do you say?
(sobbing)
Think it over!
Elaine?
Dang.
(slow breathing)
(slams door)
(Elaine)
I'm late.
I have to go to work.
So go.
(clears throat)
There's someone on their way
over to meet you.
Hector Roose.
Ohh.
Andy give up
the ghost?
Another paid companion?
Patient.
He remembers you
as a fine doctor.
He wants you to diagnose
his heart palpitations.
No kidding.
Huh.
I'm back in business.
(Addison)
Edna!
Edna,
come in here!
(Edna)
I'm coming.
Edna!
(Edna)
Yeees?
Well, why didn't
you answer me?
I want my vest.
Why do you need
your vest?
(Addison)
Never mind
why I want it.
I want my vest!
You going somewhere?
None of
your business.
Where are you going?
I just want my vest.
Got a date?
(key jingling)
(Edna)
If you get stuck
out there,
I'm not gonna
come get you.
So who asked you to?
Anybody that'd let you
practice medicine on 'em
deserves what they get.
(door unlatches)
(door creaking)
(door latches)
(grunts softly)
(grunts)
Damn kids.
Ah.
♪♪
Uhh!
(tire chains rattling)
(clattering)
I'd rather
go to a vet!
(sighs)
Doctor?
Ohh.
Ohh...
Nick, there's a DUI
proceeding east
along Highway 56.
Try him again.
He's off his radio, Del.
I can't reach him.
(sighs)
Lordy.
This is so unpleasant.
(wind whipping)
(metal clattering)
(cranks parking break)
(crying softly)
(shuts car off)
(sobbing)
(lock clanking)
Thanks.
No problem.
(door squeaking)
(door clanks shut)
(woman on radio)
Delbert...
Uh... I'm here. over.
I found the lieutenant.
I'm going
to patch him in.
Uh...
(Tim)
What is it, Delbert?
Lieutenant, uh...
a very, very bad thing
has happened.
♪♪
Elaine, are you
all right?
(Elaine)
I'm just upset.
Elaine...
your father's
been found dead.
What?
I'm sorry.
Ohh!
♪♪
(fire crackling)
(wheelchair approaching)
I don't need
to tell you...
justice and pain,
they go hand in hand.
This must be
so hard for you.
Somehow, you'll
find your way.
Ohh!
Elaine. Elaine, please!
Elaine, stop!
Quiet! Quiet!
Shh! Shh.
You gotta trust me.
(whimpers)
They're gonna be
looking for me.
So there isn't much time.
I just came to say...
finally, my mother
rests in peace.
I wish you'd never come!
You don't
say that to me.
Your whole life is out
ahead of you now.
Finally.
Now, could you say that
if I'd never come?
(sighs)
I'm scared.
I'm scared!
There's nothing worse
than to be scared.
Scared and alone.
I'm not alone.
I'm gonna have a baby.
Look, we shouldn't be
on the floor like this.
Please.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
(whispers)
Stay down.
I know the feeling
of 'em nipping at my heels.
I know they're close.
But... we're free.
Every breath we take
from now on, we're free.
We can help each other.
Make sure nobody's
life slips through a crack
or... falls by the wayside.
I never had a brother
or sister, but...
imagine this is what
they would do for each other.
(Delbert)
Miss Hodges,
are you all right?
It's that cop!
(Delbert)
Miss Hodges?
(whispering)
Just run.
He won't see you.
Just run!
(back door opens)
(door knocker rapping)
Yes?
Miss Hodges, I--
I need to-- I need
to know if you're okay.
I'm fine.
Well... it looked
like someone--
No, I was sitting
by the fire,
and then I went
to get a drink of water.
I'm fine.
Oh, um... I'm sorry.
Uh, well, good night,
Miss Hodges.
Okay, good night.
♪♪
(owl hooting)
For a while, I actually
thought I could turn this
into a-- a bistro.
Well, that would've
been somethin'.
Nothing quite
so heartbreaking
as what could've been.
(receding footsteps)
Not much of a lunch crowd
today, huh?
It's so sad.
How was I to know the guy
was an axe murderer.
He knew his food,
though, I'll tell you.
Why, he had
a roasted eggplant
with raspberry vinegar.
Huh?
Who knew that
ever existed?
Those doors, uh...
shut by themselves,
don't they?
Yeah, well...
they swing shut.
They're spring-loaded.
Why?
Is there something I should
understand here, Delbert?
(Delbert)
Watch.
I'm trying
to be patient.
See, this-- this jamb
isn't set plum.
(door latches)
Gravity gives this door
a mind of its own.
It's always gonna wanna...
slam shut by itself.
So?
So it woulda
slammed shut.
Locked.
There's a broken window
back there.
Yeah, but--
but there's snow and mud
outside the window.
Why wasn't any mud
found on the inside?
Why wasn't it
even wet in there?
Maybe the old man
let him in.
I think whoever did this...
broke that window to make it
look like a forced entry,
then used a key
to come right in.
A key?
Isn't it obvious
who we're lookin' for?
Ah, for cryin' out loud.
After all these years,
she finally realized
that her father
was a lyin' bastard,
and-- and she blew.
Don't you think
I thought of that?
Well?
I just don't think
Elaine Hodges
would smash
her father's head in.
Besides, Charles Skyler
is a bona fide psycho,
and he has a motive, too.
Just because
he's a good cook
doesn't make him
an innocent man.
He had to have a key!
(Tim)
Delbert!
I told you he'd be back.
Hold it right there!
Stop!
Stay with Elaine!
Skyler!
Hyuh!
Uhh!
(grunting)
Don't hurt me!
What the hell were you
doing back there?
I was...
trying to help him!
I was trying
to help him.
Don't you know what happened
to Addison Hodges?
Uhh!
You-- you go on now.
Go on. You're free.
He owes me money.
Some things in life
you just gotta
take a loss on.
Hey... go on!
Get out!
(groans)
(distant dog barking)
(door opens)
I hope you don't mind.
Delbert.
It's cold out there,
and-- and my feet hurt.
May I sit down?
Yes.
(sighs)
It's an act of human kindness
that he keeps me on, really.
He's loyal.
(scoffs)
You must miss your father.
I spend my time wondering
what life will be like
without him.
I still have my mom, but...
if she went, I think
I'd feel like an orphan.
Not that I can't
get along without her,
but it's just that...
Well...
(sighs)
It's-- it's a comfort
to have your parents.
Comfort, safety.
He was all I had.
I don't mean to intrude...
Yes?
Hector Roose made his
appointment through you?
My father is strongest
in the...
was strongest in the morning,
so I suggested Hector
come by early.
Edna told us
that your father
headed out to the guest house
before 8:30.
She had breakfast all ready,
but he didn't want it.
He was thrilled.
He was an excellent doctor,
you know-- he had a fine mind.
Well... his enthusiasm
left him alone
for more than a half an hour.
Are you sure
you told your father
exactly what time
Mr. Roose would be coming?
Yes, I am.
And when the lieutenant
found you by the--
by the highway...
it was almost 10:15.
I didn't notice the time.
Why did you
pull off the road?
I needed to cry.
My father and I had
a huge fight the day before.
I already told you all this.
Yeah. It's-- it's been
hard for you,
that convict and all the things
that-- that he brought to light.
I needed to cry.
I understand.
For how long?
I don't know.
Time just kind of
stood still.
It was probably
half an hour or so--
Well, it must have been
more like an hour, right?
I mean, you...
you left he house
before your father
let himself into his office.
It could have been an hour.
I don't know.
Well, you were
late for work.
You must have
checked your watch.
Delbert, what are you
trying to say?
♪♪
I should probably
check on the lieutenant,
see if everything's
all right.
Oh, one other thing.
Are you sure there's not
another key to the guest house--
(Elaine)
Charlie, no!
I don't know, Elaine.
Like we're damned if we do
and damned if we don't.
And what I'd give
for a clean start.
Just clean.
Don't make
this mistake.
That's what it's
gonna take, Elaine.
For somebody to step
out into the world...
on day one.
Without a memory
to haunt him.
(gun cocks)
Then you take me.
Turn around
and put your hands
behind your back.
No! Don't!
(handcuffs snapping)
(faint police radio chatter)
We've, uh, got him
in the lockup.
We're trying to get him
an attorney now.
Good. He'll need one.
Lieutenant, I just don't--
Shut up, Delbert.
Can I just remind you
that we still don't
have a murder weapon,
for whatever that's worth.
You don't need a murder
weapon to prove a case.
But what it could tell us.
I-- I mean, prints or...
where it was found.
I don't know,
some-- something.
♪♪
(rock crunches in brush)
Aaaah!
♪♪
(door opens)
Elaine...
Tim.
(door shuts)
Elaine...
Tim, Charlie didn't--
We had to let
Charlie go.
He didn't do it.
I know.
Do you know that your father
kept narcotics, painkillers,
in that old office?
Yes, he did.
Cabinet was broken into.
I hadn't
noticed it before.
Probably some drifter,
drug addict.
Came in,
took the opportunity.
You understand what
I'm saying?
Yes, I do.
It's time for you
to move on.
Make a life...
somewhere else.
(whispers)
Tim...
(sighs)
If only one of us had
had more courage.
Don't you wonder what
we could have had together?
(door shuts)
♪♪
(car door shuts,
engine starts)
(birds tweeting)
(Charlie)
Dear Elaine...
they say everything
is relative,
and I think that is true.
I've dwelled at the bottom
of my life and suffered,
and now I find myself
lifted beyond my dreams...
held aloft by a happiness
I never knew possible.
You have left,
and I've stayed.
Our places have reversed,
but our gift is harmony.
You and I, Elaine,
know from where we come.
And for all our pain
and loss,
we're still blessed.
(woman)
Beautifully filleted.
(man)
Beautiful!
(Charlie)
For I believe
the sweet, clean air
and the open space
will for us
never lose its taste.
I think of you often.
Charles S. Skyler.
(Elaine)
Dear Charlie,
it's been more than a year
since my father's death.
Look.
I wish you could
see me now.
(chuckling)
I have a baby son.
And I named him
after you.
(whispering)
Charlie.
I spend all my time
with him.
Maybe someday
I will teach again.
I live near a place
that is so beautiful
it makes me think of God.
I wonder what he sees,
looking down on me.
I hope he will
judge me fairly
in his infinite wisdom...
knowing life
is complicated
and holds many secrets.
Sincerely, Elaine.
♪♪