(dramatic music)
- What's the story with our
whisky production this week?
- Well, whisky we're doing okay.
Got 1,500 cases coming
down with Joe Kennedy.
- Good, good.
How about the beer?
- The beer, not so good.
But we'll have
another brewery up
by the end of the month.
Listen, boss.
Do you really think
you should be going
to this meeting in Hoboken?
I mean, this business
with Dutch Schultz,
it's really starting to heat up.
- Hey, don't worry
about it, huh?
Come on.
(dramatic music)
Max, pull over.
- What's the matter?
- Just stop the car!
- All right, all right.
(dramatic music)
Why don't I go check
out the sights?
- Yeah, you do that.
- [Max] If we miss this train,
we'll be late for the meeting.
(dramatic music)
(girl moans)
(tense music)
(train honks)
- [Conductor] Hoboken!
Hoboken Station, next stop!
(tense music)
- Why is it that my
car is not out here
waiting for me, Max?
- I don't know, boss.
- Why is everyone still
standing around here?
Am I supposed to walk?
- Get Mr. Diamond a car!
- Morning, ladies.
- [Woman] Good morning.
- Looks like you
could use some help.
- Mhm.
- [Woman] Yeah.
- I'm Jack Diamond, and
it would be a pleasure
to help such lovely
ladies as yourselves.
- Thank you.
I told her she was
bringing too much.
- Don't listen to her.
Most of this is
yours anyway, Marge.
(guns firing)
(people screaming)
(tense music)
(man groans)
- Can you believe this, Max?
What's this country coming to?
Can you believe the
balls on this guy
trying to hit us on
the way to the meeting?
- He must've known
exactly when our train
was coming in from upstate.
- Wait 'til Luciano and the
commission hear about this.
Lucky, the commission
sets up this meeting,
and this bastard
tries to kill me
as I'm coming to it!
- Handkerchief.
- [Jack] That ain't
the way it should be.
Tony, Frenchie, am I right?
- [Dutch] I can't stand to
be in the same room with you.
- What a shame.
- It's this guy's fault.
He's trying to move
in on my rackets!
- It's my fault?
Listen to his
huffin' and puffin'.
Come here, come here!
- What are you givin'
me the look for?
You see this?
This is his fault,
I don't even know why I'm
talking to this piece of crap.
- He's the one.
He's hitting my trucks!
- He's trying to
take over my rackets!
- You're a fuckin' liar!
- You callin' me a liar?
- You're damn right
I'm calling you a liar.
Come here!
- [Dutch] Listen,
you Irish mick!
- Cheating bastard!
You ignorant son of a bitch!
- This guy...
- This is a bunch of crap!
(glass breaks)
- Well, let's take it outside.
- Let's go.
- All right, enough!
- I want the offshore!
(glass breaks)
- Gentlemen!
- I want the Garment District!
- Enough!
Gentlemen!
We are going to
restore some dignity
to these proceedings.
Jack, you and Dutch here,
you came to me.
You came to me out of
respect for the commission,
and you came to this meeting
because this meeting is
to our mutual benefit.
Now, you have grievances.
And we are all well
aware of your grievances.
- Thank you, Lucky, thank you.
- So then you tell me,
what do you want to do?
- Thank you.
I want the Garment District.
- [Lucky] Jack?
- I want the trucking.
I want the trucking.
I got all this hooch in Canada,
I want to get it moved.
I want safe passage from my
men from Canada to downtown.
You know what I'm talking about.
- I want the offshore,
'cause this prick
ain't running it right.
You understand?
Really.
- Come here!
Come here!
- Don't you...
- [Lucky] Gentlemen!
- [Jack] Okay, okay.
Legs ain't runnin' for shit.
- All right.
- You got it.
I officially declare
this meeting adjourned.
All right?
- After you.
- You want me to go first?
You want me to go outside first?
- Go right ahead.
- Biggest mistake you ever made.
- Yeah, we'll see about that.
Come on!
- We're leaving.
(tense music)
- Look at this crap!
They're calling it a
full scale mob warrant,
the streets of our nation.
Where do these
newshounds get the gall
to print baloney like this?
- They're just trying
to sell papers, chief.
- Well, that may be.
But I don't like it.
They're doing it at
our expense, see?
They're trying to make the
bureau a laughingstock.
- We just may have an
opportunity here, chief.
Innocent people are being
killed by these gangsters.
Now, when the safety of the
American people is in jeopardy,
who's concerned the most?
- The president, of course.
- Right.
What we have here is a
mandate for the bureau.
You've been trying for years
to get a decent budget from
those tightwads in Congress.
- God damn Volstead Act.
It was all the
Prohibition enforcement
of those assholes at
the Treasury Department.
- We need the newspapers
to stir up public opinion,
then we can nail these gangsters
with your public safety idea.
- Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
- Well, we can identify Dutch
Schultz and Jack Diamond
at the scene of the shootout.
But nobody's gonna
testify against them.
We don't know enough about
their individual operations.
But if we can place one
of our own men in there...
- You mean infiltrate?
One of the gangs?
Hm.
Sounds too risky.
Besides...
Who could we get to pass?
My boys don't look like
gangsters, for Christ's sakes.
- Sir, we've gotta
make a federal case
out of these rackets
to show the president
that we mean business.
You get his attention, and
you'll have your budget.
I know just the man for the job.
(lighthearted jazz music)
- Here you go, bum.
Fetch.
Hey, I got plenty more
where that came from.
You don't thank me or nothin'.
(train honks)
Yeah, looks like we're
coming into the station.
You better watch out
for the yard bulls.
- Hey, kid.
Thanks for the smoke.
- All right.
(man hums)
- Howdy.
How about a cup of coffee?
- Who the hell are you?
- Nobody.
- All right, Nobody.
Have a seat, grab
yourself a cup of coffee.
- Thank you.
- How do we know he ain't
a railway man spying on us?
Where you from anyway?
I ain't never seen you
in these parts before,
what's your name?
- You sure ask a
lot of questions
for a man who just
wants a cup of coffee.
- Leave him be, Earl.
Can't you see he's just a
regular Joe looking for a break?
- Don't mind Earl.
We just have to be
careful, that's all.
All the yard bulls, cops,
and gangsters around.
Can't be too sure who to trust.
Understand?
- I heard that, I
don't want no trouble.
- Good.
Times are tough for everybody.
We can't be fighting
among ourselves.
- Thank you kindly.
- Uh huh.
No problem at all.
Don't taste too
good, but it's hot.
See, we're all
family around here.
Come from different places,
but we got to stick together
if we're gonna survive.
(gun fires)
- All right.
Nobody moves.
- See?
What'd I tell you?
He's with them.
- Shut up, Earl!
Don't prove nothin'.
- Washburn.
What the hell did I tell ya?
- I'm sorry, boss.
We's wanted to leave,
but we got a sick child.
(baby cries)
And she can't travel.
(dramatic music)
- You bastards!
(gun fires)
(woman screams)
- You see that, Roy?
That fool was attacking
an officer of the law.
- Yup, I saw.
Ain't smart to do.
(Red chuckles)
- No, it ain't too smart.
What you lookin' at, boy?
(guns cocking)
(tense music)
(Red chuckles)
Hey, now.
We got us a fightin' boy here.
You a fightin' boy, son?
- I don't want to
have to hurt anybody,
but I'll fight if I have to.
- Well, you're gonna have to.
- Don't be a fool,
they'll kill you.
- Let it go.
You'll wind up a dead man.
(dramatic music)
- That's right, Roy.
Hit him!
Get him, Roy!
(dramatic music)
(man grunts)
You guys get in there!
Come on, get in there!
(dramatic music)
Get in, get in there!
Come on, go on!
Get in there!
(tense music)
Burn the place!
We'll figure out what
to do with him later.
- That's the only man to
stand up to these bastards.
Look at what it gets him.
(fire burns)
(dramatic music)
- Wait in the car.
- What am I, a dog?
- Yeah, you're my pet.
Stay.
No, I should take you in there
and feed you to the convicts.
That's what I should do to you.
Don't turn your back on me.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
(dramatic jazz music)
Red, where are you?
- In here, boss.
- Now what did I tell you?
Are you gonna clean
this mess up or what?
I mean, what am I
paying you for, huh?
I'm paying this whole
God damn lousy town
and I'm fed up!
I don't care that you're cops,
you're all the same.
You step out of line,
I'll deal with you the same
way I deal with everyone.
We understand each other?
- Yeah, I understand.
You hear that, Roy?
You better shape up!
Mr. Diamond here
expects a lot out of ya.
- Hey, Red.
Nice shine.
What happened?
Another fight with the missus?
- No, it was this punk.
- Yeah?
Good job, pal.
- I ain't your pal.
Screw you.
- What'd you say?
- I said screw you.
Screw all of yas.
- Let him out, Red.
- All right, let's
go, tough guy.
- You know who
you're talking to?
You know who he is?
- Your boyfriend?
- So you're a tough guy, huh?
- Tough enough.
- Yeah, well I'm gonna-
- Hold on a second, Charlie.
That ain't fair.
The guy's in chains.
- Yeah, so what?
- 'Cause it ain't fair!
See what the hobo can do
without the chains on.
(melancholic saxophone music)
What's he in for?
- Murder, down at
the railroad yard.
- All the better.
This oughta be good.
Take his chains off.
- [Charlie] You won't me to-
- Don't make me
repeat myself, do it!
All right, I got
five on the hobo.
Come on, who'll match me?
Come on.
- [Man] Right here, right here.
- Let's go, come on.
All right, all right, let's go,
let's have a fight
here, come on.
How much you got, huh?
That's all you got?
Come on.
(men chattering)
This fight's gonna
be a good one.
All right, come on,
come on, come on.
Good, good.
(men yelling)
(Jack laughs)
All right, all right, come on.
Charlie, you're no
good, you're a bum!
(men yelling)
- Charlie, he's a punk
for crying out loud!
Would you put him away?
(men yelling)
- Come on!
Oh, not bad!
Not bad at all.
- Anybody else want any?
- Oh!
All right fellas, come
on, pay up, pay up.
What do you got here, huh?
What'd I tell ya?
All right, there we
go, that's the money.
Hey, put that rod away!
- I'm gonna kill him.
- No you ain't!
Only I say who gets
it, you hear me?
Now go get your face washed.
Get outta here, go on!
You're a good fighter.
What's your name?
- Bone Conn.
- Nice name.
I won't ask you how you got it.
You know, I could use a new man.
- I'm busy.
I'm on my way to the pen.
- Don't worry
about these clowns,
they do what I say.
- What?
You want me to release him?
- [Jack] Yeah, I want
you to release him.
That is, if you want a job.
- Sure.
I'd like to know who
I'm working for though.
- The name's Diamond,
Jack Diamond.
Now I want you to get
some duds, get a shave,
be at my office
tomorrow morning.
I got enough bums
working for me,
I don't need another one.
Come on, baby.
(romantic jazz music)
- Cellar, tell the Dutchman
I got O"Brien out here.
(dramatic music)
- O'Brien.
- Mr. Schultz, I...
- I don't think
this Irish potato
knows the kind of
trouble he's in.
You want to live, don't ya?
Get that hat off.
Give me that.
You know what?
Yeah.
(man laughing)
I hear you've been
buying from Legs.
Come on, come on.
Don't bullshit me.
Whose territory is this?
Whose?
- [O'Brien] It's yours, Dutch.
- That's right.
Get out of here.
Give me a drink.
(lighthearted music)
- Come on, let me in there!
- No chance, beat it.
- How ya feelin' this
morning, Charlie?
- Been better.
- You're too happy.
- Hey, thanks.
Hey, wait a minute.
Don't I know you?
Yeah, you're that
bum from the train.
I don't get it.
- I got a job, I'm
working for Legs Diamond.
- You're working for Legs?
I've been waiting for
him out here all day,
I don't get it!
- Well, if it ain't the boxer.
- Here like you
told me to be, boss.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, I got a job to do.
Who is he?
- Just some kid
looking for work.
- Yeah?
Get lost!
- But Mr. Diamond, Mr. Diamond!
I came all the way from
New York to see you.
I'm your sister's
husband's nephew.
- My sister?
- Yeah.
- That tramp.
Get him outta here.
- Mr. Diamond.
He's with me.
- Yeah, so?
- He's a good kid.
- What am I, a charity ward?
All right, he's in.
Max, give him some heat.
(lighthearted jazz music)
- Tony, I got eight bottles...
- Hey, beat it.
You scram!
- [Man] Sir, Mr. Diamond.
- Now...
What'd I tell you about
not buying my stuff?
- But Dutch says the same thing.
- Son of a bitch!
- Hey, what can I do?
- You do what I say, you got it?
- Yeah, but they'll
burn me down.
- Yeah?
Well, let me show
you what I'll do.
(dramatic music)
Hey, boys.
Maybe I should just
shoot this guy, huh?
Put someone else in charge.
Someone who ain't so
stupid as to take crap
from that jackass,
Dutch Schultz.
(glass breaks)
Get the son of a bitch!
(suspenseful music)
He went in that building,
go in and kill him!
(tense music)
- So now what do we do?
- Don't worry about it,
just get outta here.
- What, are you just
gonna shoot him?
- Go!
- Well, what happened?
I thought I told
you to pop the bum!
(gun fires)
- Take the first
train out of town,
I'm not saying it twice.
- Good.
Now that's the way
to waste a guy,
he emptied his whole clip.
- Maybe he's just a bad shot.
What's the matter, you
couldn't put one in his brain
and be done with it?
- Maybe you want to go up
there and look for yourself.
- Nah, come on.
Let's get a drink.
(catchy band music)
Drinks on the house.
Everybody drink up.
Bone, that was good
today what you did.
You really showed me something.
- It was nothin', boss.
That bum had it coming.
- Excuse me, gentlemen.
I got some business
to attend to.
(slow romantic music)
- Hi.
- Hello.
- You new in town?
- Yeah.
- You're a big talker, huh?
Why don't you ask me to dance?
(slow romantic music)
So, what brings you to town?
- I don't know.
One place is as
good as the next.
- You think so?
Some places have more
opportunities, wouldn't you say?
- If you play your cards right.
You seem to be doing
all right for yourself.
- You mean playing
my cards right?
- [Bone] You're playing
somebody, sister.
- You're sort of
fresh, aren't you?
- Kiki.
Bone.
This is...
- Betty.
Why don't you show the
new guy a good time, huh?
Go on.
(slow romantic music)
Kiki.
Sing for me, baby.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
the lovely Kiki Roberts.
(people clapping)
♪ Tell me you'll hold
me tonight, sweetheart ♪
♪ Tonight is all
I'll ask of you ♪
♪ And if tomorrow
- Hey, Max.
Isn't that Legs's dame?
- Uh huh.
- She sings kinda-
- Great!
- Right.
- Regular nightingale.
♪ In my dreams tonight
♪ Your love will be true
♪ Your heart will
- Who's the new guy?
- I don't know, bud.
But I don't like him.
He's a little too slick.
He ain't some hobo who
just jumped off the train.
♪ Forever, my dear
♪ Forever you will love me so
(Betty laughs)
- Oh!
(dramatic saxophone music)
Thank you.
And I'm really not
this type of girl,
I mean I usually don't
do this type of thing.
(romantic saxophone music)
- Break out the champagne.
I'll be back in two shakes.
Keep the bed warm.
(mysterious music)
(lighthearted music)
- Yeah, I'll call you back.
Sit down, Conn.
Yeah, Smith, get us
some black coffee
and tell Margie to come in here.
You look terrible.
What, you been drinking?
- This guy works
out of a speakeasy.
You want me to come off like
a Sunday school teacher?
- You're an agent of
the federal government.
You oughta follow the book.
- Yeah, well, I would
if there was a book
in this kind of operation.
You ever had an agent this
deep inside the rackets before?
- Your job is to uphold
the honor of the bureau.
- What the devil does that mean?
- You got a report?
(phone rings)
We got a corrupt sheriff.
Actually, the whole department's
on Diamond's payroll.
Hit some clubs, some
gambling, some prostitution.
He seems to run those
just for his own amusement
and not for profit.
- That's all nonsense.
It's the local sheriffs.
What about his bootlegging?
- It's bigger than we thought.
It's a major transportation
and distribution network.
He's even trying to set up an
offshore shipping operation.
For now he runs the
hooch down from Canada
through New York State by truck.
- We can't touch him offshore.
But when he crosses
the Canadian border,
that's a federal rap.
- He's getting hit pretty
hard by Dutch Schultz.
- So?
- So I'm in the middle
of a mob war here.
These guys don't
really trust me.
I got their local
sheriffs staked out
in front of my
flophouse right now.
I'm hired on as a
soldier for now,
and the guy's buying
it right and left.
How far can I go to
protect my cover?
- Margie, will you excuse us?
You were an ace in
the Great War, right?
Patton Ring Squadron.
You were a hero, right?
- That was war.
- Well, this is war too.
So they're killing each other,
it makes our job a lot easier.
When Mr. Hoover
authorizes an operation,
he wants results, and he
wants results quickly.
Now, I picked you because
you're rough around the edges.
And I expect that you
fit in beautifully
with all that vermin.
But if you screw up,
I'm gonna leave your
ass out there hanging.
Hey, cheer up.
It's the 30s.
Mr. Hoover wants company
men, not cowboys.
(lighthearted jazz music)
- Put that away!
- Yo, Bart, I'm gonna
go check this out.
- Hold on, what
have we got here?
A still.
Don't you know that's illegal?
- It's just a little moonshine.
Ain't no harm in that.
A man's got a right!
- Not in Jack Diamond's
neck of the woods.
You got no rights unless
we give them to you.
Legs doesn't want
any competition,
no matter how small
potatoes you are.
(mysterious music)
- Well, well, what
have we got here?
What are you gonna
do, shoot somebody?
- If you hurt my daddy, I was.
- Oh, he's your dad?
- Yes, now would
you get off of me?
Let go of me.
- You gotta promise
not to fight first.
- Yeah, sure, I promise.
- You promised!
(woman chuckles)
- Did not.
- So you're gonna get
out of the shine business
if you know what's good for ya.
(bottles clanging)
- Well, I gotta go.
(lighthearted music)
(mysterious music)
(guns firing)
(men yelling)
- Go down there and
finish anybody left.
Move!
And watch what Mr. Legs
Diamond sent us tonight.
- It's the full load, boss!
- Full load?
You wouldn't lie
to me, would you?
- [Man] No!
- Oh my God.
What a grand night it is!
Yeah.
He's gonna be pissed off.
But better to be pissed
off than pissed on.
Yeah, that son of a bitch.
- Let's go!
(dramatic music)
I want you to round up all
the people we got left.
Let's go hit the
bastard where it hurts.
- Boss, bad play.
We're spread too thin now.
We got guys all the
way up to Canada
with that last shipment.
- I'm not just gonna
lay here and take this.
- I got a few tricks I
learned in the Great War.
We'll hit him, hard.
You and me.
(tense music)
- That's some trick, dynamite.
Dynamite, I know, from dynamite.
(tense music)
(dynamite explodes)
(Jack laughs)
(lighthearted music)
- You think she's
good looking, right?
- Who?
- You know, Suzy from the farm.
- Yeah, kid, she's
a regular cupcake.
(tense music)
Max, can you make these guys?
- Schultz's crew.
I could recognize
those yeggs anywhere.
Good eye, Bone.
Gave us the drop on them.
All right.
I'll split off to the right,
we'll hit 'em from two sides.
Wait for my signal,
and bang 'em hard.
(tense music)
(guns firing)
- Max is a little trigger happy.
Stay here.
- No, no, no, I'll go with you.
- Stay here, I'll
take care of this.
(gun fires)
(man yells)
(guns firing)
You little knucklehead,
what did I tell you?
Come on!
(guns firing)
- I'll go tell the boss
that pretty boy is here.
(romantic music)
(woman moans)
(knocking)
Boss.
- I'm busy!
- Boss, Red is back with
Bone Conn, and Kiki.
- What?
What the hell is she doing here?
- I don't know.
- All right, bring 'em down,
I'll be out in a minute.
- Out in a minute?
(woman moans)
Right.
- Why don't we just enjoy
the view for a second?
- Bone, honey, you going
a little daffy on me?
When did you get so romantic?
- It must be the sea air.
- The boss will see you now.
- Hiya, Charlie.
(dramatic music)
- Kiki.
- [Kiki] Hi, Jack.
- So good to see you.
- Yeah, well, I thought
I'd surprise you.
- You did.
You certainly did.
Excuse us.
I got some business
with the men.
- Yeah, I can see that.
Pig!
- Shut up!
- Jack, let go of me.
- Don't raise your voice to me.
- Let me go.
(romantic music)
- Bone.
Good to see you.
You see what I
gotta put up with?
- Not a good thing, boss.
- Yeah.
That was nice work
on that shipment.
See, Max?
You gotta keep your eyes open.
What were you gonna show me?
- Boss.
Take a look at this.
This is the route
we've been running.
We've lost 300 gallons of
whisky this month alone
to hijackers from Dutch.
Why are we doing it?
- Because I'm giving
you safe passage
through my county, that's why.
- Your safe passage puts us
50 miles from Dutch's turf.
He's got us here,
here, and here.
It's one road,
it's a bottleneck.
- So?
We put on more muscle.
Bang the bastard
into the next state.
- Not the smart play.
Come down here to the
Oley Brothers territory.
It's a straight shot
from Canada to Albany,
down to the city.
Call it the Legs
Diamond Highway.
What's standing in the way?
One hick sheriff.
No offense, Red.
- [Jack] Christ, we can
buy him off for one tenth
what we're paying Red.
- Except the Oley Brothers
are with Schultz now.
- So maybe they ain't
so long for this world.
- Your plan leaves us weak,
it opens up the whole west side.
- Let him have it.
While he's busy solidifying
his new territory
of useless farmland,
you get right into the city.
Let him think he's
won something.
Christ, we can
even give him Red,
we're not gonna
need him anymore.
Lose a battle, win the war.
- I ain't standing
for this shit!
Who does this guy think he is
telling you what
to do, Mr. Diamond?
- Shut up, Red.
Shut up.
Bone.
Let's you and I take a walk.
Bone, I'm looking forward
to a great future with you.
I like what I'm seeing.
You're doing great
things for us.
- [Kiki] You're in the
wrong place, bitch!
Get out of here!
- Excuse me.
Looks like I have a domestic
disturbance on my hands.
That's all I need.
- Take your stuff
and get out of here!
I don't want you
anywhere near him!
Get out of here!
- What the hell's going on here?
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
- Why don't you tell me?
Seems like your
little whore's upset!
- I am not a whore!
Jack, who is this person?
- All right, shut up!
Both of you!
All right, Blanche,
get out of here.
This has got to stop.
- I'll see.
Do you have to fuck
everything that moves?
- You have got some mouth.
I don't like that kind of talk!
- Well, I don't
like sharing you!
With Alice, every other
two-bit tramp in town.
- Now don't you ever
talk about my wife!
- Go ahead.
Hit me again, tough guy.
(dramatic music)
Get off me, pig!
Get off of me!
(intense saxophone music)
(romantic music)
(Kiki moans)
(Kiki chuckles)
Aw, shit!
Shit!
- Yes!
(Kiki moans)
(horses galloping)
(lighthearted jazz music)
Come on, come on!
Come on, you bums!
(horses galloping)
Yes!
Yes, baby!
- You really know how
to pick 'em, boss.
- Hey, that's got
nothing to do with it.
You just gotta know which
jockeys you can pay to tank.
Max.
I want you to get Charlie,
go pick up my winnings,
I want you back here.
- Charlie.
- Are we staying?
- Of course we're staying,
I got three more races fixed.
- You promised me you'd take me
to the picture show today.
- Ah, you're right doll, I did.
Can't go now.
Hey.
Come here.
Huh?
You really want to go to the
picture show that bad, huh?
Is that gonna make you happy?
You get to go to
the picture show?
All right.
Here, Bone.
Take her to the show.
Take her shopping
afterwards, all right?
You like that, right?
Get some nice things
for yourself there.
Whatever you want.
I'll see you at the club.
- Miss Kiki.
(lighthearted jazz music)
(dramatic music)
- [Presenter] And now
the further adventures of
Steel Doctor, Crime Fighter.
In this chapter, a hero meets
his greatest challenge yet.
The case of the lady from-
- Are you crazy coming here?
- I had to see you.
I had to.
- Well, if my pa sees
you, he's gonna kill you.
Why don't you go
meet me in the barn?
Get goin'!
- Swell.
(mysterious music)
(Suzy laughs)
(romantic jazz music)
(Suzy chuckles)
(lighthearted music)
- So if I'm hearing
you correctly,
that's a million
dollars a month, right?
(Jack chuckles)
Bone!
Come on in.
Thank you.
Have a seat.
Care for a cigar?
- Certainly.
- I'm telling you,
I love this country.
You know, I started
off with nothing.
I was just a what,
a punk kid down
the Lower East Side
that could outrun the cops.
And so I got into the business.
What, I just jump on a
truck, grab what I could,
and bam, off like a light!
And now look at me.
And I'm a young guy,
and look what I got.
- Only in America.
- There's always
gonna be somebody
who wants to take
that away from you.
I got money, more women
than I can handle,
but what I don't got
is guys working for me
that got it on the ball.
I need 10 more guys like me.
- Boss.
This is where I come in.
Make me your number two.
Let me handle all
the bootlegging.
It's gonna leave you
free to deal with Luciano
and the bosses in the city.
Make peace with them, run
this like a corporation.
Forget about Schultz,
he's small-time.
You'll bury him in a year.
- This is music to my ears.
Finally, finally, someone who
can grasp the big picture.
- Let me sweat the details.
You'll be bigger
than all these bums.
- Okay.
Okay.
We'll hit the Oley Brothers.
You set it up.
Then we'll see.
- You got it, boss.
(dramatic music)
- [Man] Okay, load
it in, bring it in.
(men chattering)
(mysterious music)
- [Man] We're 5
barrels short, boss.
- What?
- Must've been lost on the road,
you know how it is.
- Know how it is?
Oh, how Irish.
The bride at every wedding,
and the corpse at
every funeral, man.
I give him dames,
I give him jobs,
and some guys have
even been stupid enough
to spit in my face.
But nobody steals
from Dutch Schultz.
You will listen to me.
- [Man] I can't give you
something I don't got.
- We don't leave here until
I get what I paid for.
You got that?
- Fellas, come on.
Can we talk about this?
- Take him down to the shed!
(tense music)
- What's the scoop?
- Got them with
their pants down.
They got a full load of hooch.
Oh, by the way...
Our friend Dutch Schultz
is here, in the flesh.
- Dutch Schultz?
Here?
- Yeah, he's supervising
the operation.
Max, I'm gonna need you
to create a diversion.
- Wait, wait, I gotta
think, I gotta think.
Johnson, give me some grenades.
Now, on the double!
- We've got 'em right
where we want 'em.
- And some dynamite.
Mikey, get us outta here.
(dramatic music)
- Dirty rat bastard!
What are you...
Dutch!
I got a wife and two
kids, come on now.
Please.
Have a heart.
- Are you through?
- [Man] Please, Dutch.
- Hold his head.
- [Man] Please.
(man groans)
(Dutch grunts)
- I think he got the message.
Let's go eat.
(men laughing)
(tense music)
(dynamite explodes)
(men yelling)
- Boss, it's Legs!
(gun fires)
- They caught us with
our pants down, Bo.
Let's get the Thompsons.
(guns firing)
- What's going on?
- [Man] Come on!
(dynamite explodes)
(men yelling)
- Move over there!
Come on!
(guns firing)
- [Man] Get those damn guns!
(dynamite explodes)
(guns firing)
- Come on, move!
- Gimme this.
After him!
(man yells)
- [Man] Kill him!
(dynamite explodes)
(guns firing)
(grenade explodes)
- They got Benny!
Come on, get outta here!
(guns firing)
(grenade explodes)
(man screams)
(tense music)
(Jack chuckles)
(phone rings)
- Diamond residence.
Yes, yes he is, one moment.
Darling?
There's someone on
the phone for you.
- Who is it, lovey?
- It's Charles Luciano.
- Charlie.
- Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack.
Listen to me, Jack.
I've already told Dutch
lay off the heavy stuff,
so now I'm telling you.
This thing between
the two of you,
not good, Jack.
- Yeah, so I'm
expanding a little bit.
This is America, I got a
right to do business here.
He's muscling in
on my territory,
he's threatening my customers.
- That you took from him, Jack.
- Okay, all right.
Charlie, I respect you.
- This is just business,
it's not personal.
You see that you separate
the two, all right?
(dramatic piano music)
- Those two aren't gonna
listen to reason, are they?
- Yeah.
We need the cowboys for
a little while longer,
but they're dinosaurs,
this bang bang muscle stuff.
Almost extinct.
We're gonna run this
outfit like U.S. Steel,
and then those high hat
politicians, the hypocrites,
they won't be able to touch us.
- Yeah, I like that.
- Nobody messes with the outfit.
So they'll come
around, or they won't.
(dramatic piano music)
- That was a brilliant idea.
Well, you know, Bone,
I got a genius for
an organization.
- You don't say?
- Yeah!
Our bootlegging rackets are a
regular money making machine.
They won't ever stop.
- What about our
friend, Mr. Schultz?
- He can throw a monkey
wrench into the machine,
this is true.
But I'll tough him out.
I'll beat him.
Christ, back in the old days,
me and little Augie used to face
some real hard-nosed characters,
a lot tougher than
that yid punk!
- That's right, Boss.
You know what my
real problem is?
Dames.
Hey, women really
queer up my life.
You know, on one hand
I got Kiki, right?
I mean, Bone, you
know what I mean,
I don't gotta tell you.
A woman like that.
And then there's Alice.
Sweet little Alice.
And God knows I love her,
she's made a real home for me,
and she would do
anything for me.
But I tell you, the first twist
that walks by me at the club,
and I'm off skirt chasing.
I mean, I can't help it.
I never could.
(guns firing)
(women screaming)
(glass breaks)
Go grab a Thompson!
(guns firing)
- Get outta here!
(tires screeching)
(dramatic music)
(women sobbing)
- Boss, you're hit.
- Yeah?
Ah, so what?
It's just buckshot, I'll live.
Maybe you haven't heard,
they call me the Clay
Pigeon, I can't be killed.
No one can kill Jack Diamond.
No one!
(dramatic music)
- Jesus Christ.
This place looks like
a slaughterhouse.
- Yeah?
So clean it up.
- Jack, we've got
women, kids shot here.
I gotta get an ambulance.
You know, the state police
are gonna have to
come in on this.
- Hey, flatfoot,
I'm bleeding here.
Can we discuss this later?
- Mr. Diamond.
This is bad.
This is real bad.
I can't cover for you on this.
- God damn it, Red,
round up some hobos
and blame it on them,
do what you have to do!
Max.
Take me back to Alice.
She'll patch me up.
Bone, get over to Kiki's,
tell her I'm all right,
and then I want you
to get on the horn
to Charlie Luciano.
This is getting out of hand.
- You got it, boss.
(dramatic music)
- Be a brave boy.
There we go.
- Sweetheart.
- What?
- You're the only person in
the world who understands me.
- Oh, honey, hush.
Shh.
Mommy's here.
Mommy's here to
take care of you.
(soft jazz music)
- Your mother never
teach you to knock?
- I've been looking
all over for you.
Figured you'd come here,
figured I'd let myself in.
- Oh, you did, did you?
Why don't you tell
me what you want
before I throw you out?
- Dutch Schultz tried
to hit us tonight.
Legs got shot.
- Is he all right?
- He's got thick skin.
- Where is he?
- Max drove him home.
You know, to his real home.
- Is that bitch Alice there?
That's it.
That's the last straw.
I'm through with that bum.
- Why tell me?
- See...
I know you're up to something.
You're a cover.
And I'm thinking,
maybe you and I could
work something together.
See, I know that
Legs is in trouble.
And then I see a guy like you,
and I see he's got
something going on.
And I say to myself,
"Maybe we should
have a little talk."
See...
If we understand each other.
- [Bone] We
understand each other.
(romantic saxophone music)
- How are you gonna
stop the violence?
(reporters yelling)
- My office is working
on the legal issue.
- [Reporter] Come on, Chief,
what's the lowdown here?
- We'll be making a
statement in the morning.
(reporters yelling)
- That's not good enough!
The people just want to know
that they can walk
down the street
without some gangster
cutting them in half
with a Tommy gun.
- [Reporter] Come on, how
about a statement, Chief?
(dramatic music)
- All right boys, rough 'em out.
I want him here.
(dramatic music)
All right.
Let's go, Washburn.
- Why don't you let us be?
We ain't harming no one.
- Yeah?
- How you doin', Frankie?
- Arthur.
- Lucky, Oley.
Come on in.
What do you say?
- Hey, sit down, have a drink.
- I think you know
why we're all here.
- Give me a drink.
- Oh, you know Arthur,
what you did was
very, very foolish.
- It was foolish and
it was unnecessary!
- Hey, wait a minute.
Legs Diamond has been
muscling in on my territory.
Territory that's
rightfully mine,
given to me by you.
The guy drives me crazy.
(Lucky laughs)
- Oh, Dutch, listen,
you've got to calm down,
you're gonna give
yourself apoplexy
and then one of these mornings
I'm liable to wake
up and find you dead.
- Hey, that Irish
potato eating mick
is the one that's
gonna wind up dead.
Oh, hey, sorry Oley,
to make the potato
reference, sir.
- Come on, Dutch, so
what's the problem?
You and he used to be pals,
you grew up together,
this war has got to stop.
- Oh, come on.
He was never a pal of mine,
that silky pant son of a bitch.
- This is bad for business,
everybody's business!
- Very, very bad, Arthur.
Now you listen to me,
I want to explain
something to you.
We can not afford to
be calling attention
to our bootlegging operations.
This outfit has got to be...
Invisible.
You start blasting kids
and women on the street,
and then the cops and the
wasp political leaders,
they've just got to take
some kind of action.
- Ah, well, look.
Just pay them off as
usual, those shyster fucks.
- No amount of money will
buy them off this time.
- No?
- This ain't like
the old days, Dutch.
- No, no, no, he's right.
Besides that,
we're liable to get
the feds sniffing around us,
and then that's really bad news.
This is a whole
different breed, Arthur.
- Do you believe this shit?
You know, it used to be
when a guy wronged you,
you can settle a score.
You know what I mean?
Now what do I gotta do?
You know, roll over
and piss up in the air
and come before the
board of directors?
All right, all right.
But anything that moves
across my territory is mine.
And this is how I keep it...
I don't lay down for nobody!
Get my coat.
Son of a bitch.
(dramatic music)
- Read about it in the log.
- Bone Conn, sir.
- It's about time, Conn.
You know, I oughta
can you right now.
Hey, no smoking.
Look, I don't think you realize
what's going on here, okay?
This is all the
paperwork that Hoover
is making me submit to the
committee about this operation.
Well, I have no information
about this operation.
- You want paperwork?
- What is this,
some sort of a joke?
- No.
It's a map of Leg's
shipping route.
That's all I had to write on.
He's got a warehouse in
Canada full to the gills.
These are details of
the port of crossings.
You could nail the whole
convoy right there.
Set up a roadblock, I'll
lead him right to ya.
(chuckling)
- You are now my idol.
- Stop the car.
- What, what?
- Stop the car!
- What's the matter?
- Why is that hick farmer
still in business here?
- What's wrong?
- Am I the only one
upset about this?
I'm killing myself trying
to control this territory,
these yokels are undercutting
me right under my nose!
- [Max] Yeah, that ain't right.
- Jimmy, go out and
burn this guy down!
- Boss, we gotta get goin'.
- Yeah, you're right.
Just shoot him, that's better.
Go on!
We'll see you back in town.
- Yeah, okay boss.
(dramatic music)
(woman chuckles)
- Today's gambling receipts.
Oh, so I'll take them
up to the office?
You gotta lock up.
- Hey, Bone.
I gotta speak to
you, right away.
- Girls, take a powder.
Bud.
- We were driving
outside of town.
Legs, he sees the moonshine,
and he went crazy.
- He is crazy.
He sees that guy's very
existence as a slap in the face.
- Yeah, right, but he
ordered me to kill him.
I didn't.
I mean, I couldn't.
Look, I know Legs is gonna
be really steamed, but-
- No, he's gonna kill you.
- I'm not cut out for this.
Not like you.
I'm gonna go away with Suzy.
You know, take her
out of this mess.
I love her, Bone.
- All right.
I'll square it with
Legs tomorrow, somehow.
- Thanks, Bone.
I mean...
Thanks.
How do you do it?
- Do what?
- The killing.
(dramatic music)
- This place is such a dump.
- Didn't stop you from coming.
- Yeah, well I didn't tell you
you could plan it either.
- What'd you bring,
a whore up here?
- What other kind of
girl would come up here?
(dramatic music)
- You know the drill, let's go.
- Get your clothes!
- Throw him in a river.
(dramatic music)
- Bone, we got an
old friend of yours.
Get in.
- [Bone] Where you takin' me?
- For a ride.
(dramatic music)
- You recognize this guy, Bone?
O'Brien confessed to me
that you went soft on a hit.
And I ask myself,
"What kind of a mug
doesn't pop a mark
when he's supposed to?"
There's only two
possibilities, boys.
Yellow or a cop.
- Thank you.
Which is it?
- I don't accept the choices.
- You got moxie.
He's going for a ride.
(dramatic music)
- How many more
barrels do we got left?
- Ah, four or five hundred.
- Well, let's get them
loaded on the truck
so I don't got all day.
- Come on, a little faster, eh?
- [Jack] Where the hell is Bone?
- [Max] I don't know,
he hasn't shown up yet.
- [Jack] Of all the
days to show up late,
I gotta get these
barrels of hooch loaded!
- [Max] We're working on it!
- Work on it better, all right?
I want these barrels
on the truck now!
- Jack, I'm moving
them as fast I can,
we're a little shorthanded-
- Legs, Legs!
- What the hell
are you doing here?
We're not loading matzah
balls here, Dutch.
- I come to evict yas.
- Came to evict us?
What are you, a comedian?
(Dutch chuckles)
- Come here.
I got something better for you.
Max, what's O'Brien doing alive?
- I guess you
didn't expect to see
this piece of shit
again, did ya?
- No, actually I didn't.
- Yeah?
- [Jack] Bone, what's going on?
Why didn't you kill him?
- Looks like you got
a cop on your hands.
- You got another
dick in your pocket?
- I knew there was something
funny about this guy.
- Funny?
Nah.
This guy's a God damn G-man.
- Bone, what the hell is this?
What the hell is this?
String him up!
How could you do this?
I gave you everything!
I trusted you!
- Come here, you.
- Yes!
My boys found him
skulking around
that rotten singer's apartment.
Yeah.
He's got the smell
of cheap perfume
and pussy on him.
- Damn it, you son of a bitch!
- Don't beat on your relatives.
You've both be
schtupping the same girl.
- You son of a bitch.
Jesus, Bone.
You and Kiki behind my back.
- I guess you hire
guys that like to fuck,
but they don't like to kill.
Guess you don't got the
balls for it anymore.
The killing, I mean.
- What, you think I
don't got the balls?
- I don't know.
- Hey, Jimmy boy, come
here for a minute, will ya?
Come here!
- [Dutch] I don't
need a newspaper.
- He's another kid who
didn't listen to me.
You...
- Oh, hey.
You want me to do it for you?
Here.
(gun fires)
There's one less Irish pick.
- All right, you must've
tipped off the feds,
they're gonna be all
over our trucking routes.
Get these off the trucks,
loaded on the ship, now!
Now, now, come on!
- Hey, Legs!
You're running out of gunsels.
- I'm running out of
patience with you.
- The offshore is mine!
- Well, I'm sorry about that.
- Oh, no.
Hey.
You're welching on the deal.
- What are you, threatening me?
- Luciano's agreement doesn't-
- Are you threatening me?
- Am I threatening you?
- [Jack] Yeah.
- You got the memory
of a cockroach.
(dramatic music)
- Get the hell outta
here, you punks.
Fuckin' cowards.
Go on!
- Give me the gun.
Thanks, baby.
Come here.
(tense music)
(guns firing)
- Where the hell's
that son of a bitch?
(guns firing)
- Forget about Dutch, boss.
We got the feds to
worry about now.
Let's get you out of here,
there's too much booze around.
They can put us away for good.
(guns firing)
- That Jew is gonna
bring us all down.
We better get to the docks.
(guns firing)
But I'm not leaving two
million dollars worth of hooch
for Dutch to find.
Come on, boys, get going.
(guns firing)
Max, you get to the dock,
make sure we get away safe,
find Charlie.
Make him kill this
piece of garbage.
Have him send him to hell,
but make it slow, huh?
(guns firing)
Come on, let's go!
- You see any Irish prick?
You can't run forever,
this ain't over!
- Where's Conn?
- He hasn't checked in yet, sir.
- Ah, the hell with him.
We'll proceed as planned.
All right, men, move out!
- Aren't you gonna
beg now, tough guy?
- Cut the small
talk, cheese-head,
just get it over with.
- What makes you so tough?
- Just comes natural.
(gun fires)
(dramatic music)
- What's the matter, tough guy?
Got no wise aleck
comment for me?
- Give me a minute,
I'll think of one.
(lighthearted music)
(dramatic music)
- You mind telling
me what's going on?
(propeller spins)
(dramatic music)
(gun fires)
- Son of a bitch!
What am I gonna tell the boss?
- Max.
- What?
- Max, he's turning around.
- Huh?
- I think he's coming back.
- What the hell's
that guy up to?
Duck outta here, Gus.
I'll reload.
(dramatic music)
(guns firing)
(grenade explodes)
- Well, well.
If it ain't the boxer.
Always wondered what
happened to you.
Heard rumors you was
working for Legs Diamond.
- I work for the law.
- What?
A copper?
A stinkin' copper?
I thought we had
something going.
- We do.
What's changed?
- Everything.
How can I have
fallen for a copper?
- Kiki.
I need your help.
- Why should I help you?
I hate you.
- Huh.
Law ain't no friend of ours.
- You fellas are facing
the chair for a murder rap.
- We didn't do
nothing, it's a fix.
- Yeah, well don't I know it.
I'll spring you.
I'll give you a chance
to set it straight
with a federal judge,
a judge that ain't
on Diamond's payroll.
But you got to help me first.
- Sounds to me like
we got ourselves
a new marshal in town.
- That's right, and
I need some deputies.
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
- Hey, you guys wake up!
Shoot him!
(guns firing)
Give me a Thompson, God damn it!
Turn it up!
(guns firing)
(men groaning)
- Hey!
You with the Dutchman?
Huh?
Hey, listen, I'm
not with these guys.
Come on!
We can make a deal.
(mysterious music)
Listen!
You can't kill me.
I'm a law!
Really!
I'm a cop, I can help ya.
(gun fires)
You!
You dumb, stupid nigger.
I should've...
(gun fires)
(lighthearted music)
- Lose the Thompson.
I'm gonna kill you!
Never thought you'd make
it this far, copper.
But now it's lights out time.
I'm gonna blow your head off.
Damn it!
Stinkin' copper!
You're dead!
(dramatic music)
(Jack groans)
Where are you taking me, G-man?
- Where do you think?
Albany County Jail.
- Ha!
And how long do you think
they're gonna keep
me in there for?
Not long at all.
See, I got me the best
lawyers money can buy.
How much do you make a year,
you lousy, stinkin',
civil servant.
What, two, three
thousand dollars a year?
I built an empire worth
10 million dollars!
You can't keep me in jail,
and on what charges?
I wasn't doing anything illegal.
- You were
trafficking in liquor,
that's a violation
of the Volstead Act.
- Yeah, maybe.
But you jumped the gun.
You didn't have a warrant.
You can't use that evidence.
- You murdered Jimmy.
He was just a kid.
- Where's the body?
(Jack chuckles)
- You think you got the
answers to everything,
don't you, Legs?
- I know I do.
- Maybe I should put
a hole in your head.
What's the answer to that?
(Jack chuckles)
- It'll never happen.
Let's face it, you're a sap.
All you believe in
is your fancy laws,
courtrooms, judges.
Me?
I believe in the
law of the street,
the gun, and the blackjack.
- Get out.
- All right.
I'll be seeing ya, G-man.
(Jack chuckles)
Stupid copper.
Hey, Dutch.
- I'll see you in hell, Legs.
But don't wait up for me.
(gun fires)
I've come too far
to miss on this.
(gun fires)
That's enough.
What a shame.
(dramatic music)
(melancholic music)
(woman sobs)
- Well, you couldn't have
messed this up any better.
- How do you figure?
We seized a major
shipment of hooch
and got rid of a public
menace at the same time.
- Well, you tell that
to Hoover, not to me.
I'll probably lose my job.
Hoover wanted to make
the pinch himself.
- Well, that's tough.
I'm sorry to disappoint him.
- Some bigshot
senator attacked him
for never getting
into the field,
never making any arrests.
You know, the tough
part of the job.
- Yeah.
Well, he can keep the job.
- Well, you've got
a plane to catch.
(lighthearted music)
(lighthearted jazz music)