Hi, this is Fred. Sorry I miss your call,
but leave your message after the beep.
- What'up. It's Andy. Going downtown tonight. She comes with.
You know, I haven't seen you for a while.
I do not know where have you been,
but Sahra is going to be there.
Give me a call when you get this message. Bye. See you later.
- What'up. It's Andy. Going downtown tonight. She comes with.
You know, I haven't seen you for a while.
I do not know where have you been,
but Sahra is going to be there.
Give me a call when you get this message. Bye. See you later.
- It's mom.
Just want to double-check about your travel plans and...
- Hi
- Wait a second.
- What's up?
- Hi
- Get out!
GET OUT!
- Shit!
Come in tomorrow, okay?
- Hello
-Ehmm...