This is Los Angeles,
City of Angels and
it's Christmas time, in case
that was
unclear, and our particular
story
concerns a young
man just discovering
his place in the world. It's the
story of
a family who finally
need each other
more than any of
them are willing to admit.
And it's the
tale of the Christmas
spirit made manifest
and the magic that
exists this time of
year if we just look
hard enough and believe.
It's like my dad
always told me: digging
up holes you will
eventually find a
bone.
Yeah, well yeah I heard Ricardo
bring it up at the
quarterly meeting
and you know how he
likes to talk. Yeah
I just didn't think
it would be so soon.
Yeah I was just
hoping that we could
get through this Christmas.
I wanted to
prove to Riley that
there was a little magic left.
Okay, Molly, thanks for
letting me know.
[Music]
Come in.
I sold the company.
So all those hours
for Christmas or to transition
operations into shutting
computer
services down...I'm
out of a job.
Yeah. I always thought it
was cool you worked there.
Hey, don't be worried about
a thing. We're going to get
through this.
I'm already look for
something else and I'm
definitely going
to be taking those
extra shifts for the
next 48 hours and
we're going to do
something really nice
for Christmas.
That's ok, mom, you
know I've never really
been a
fan of Christmas
anyways, so...the magic,
it's dead.
Hey, don't say that!
Well, it's true, Mom, I've
been alone for more holidays
than I've been alive.
You know you've
always had to be the one to work
double-time and I
appreciate everything
you've done for
us, I really do but
Christmas is just
another day.
I don't want you to think
that way.
Sorry, I just really wanted
us to have a special day,
just once.
Don't worry about me, Mom.
I'll go over to Andy's
and on the day we'll
go grab waffles like
every other Saturday.
[laughs]
How did you get to be so
grown up?
Science works wonders.
[Music]
I just don't want you to think
that there's no magic.
Well, I stopped believing in
magic when you beat up that
mall Santa.
Hey, he was awful!
He wouldn't
see you, come on,
Santa's don't take coffee
breaks! We waited in line for
over an hour.
You know well I liked the hot
cocoa
afterwards at the
coffee shop way better.
- Marshmallows.
- Marshmallows make everything
gooder.
Yes they do.
[Music]
Nope. Christmas
spirit is left the
building.
It was never that
good anyways.
Did you read all these books?
[Music]
- Who are you?
- I'm Hope. I'm a Christmas
spirit.
What?
My sisters and I
are Christmas spirits.
Faith, Mercy, Charity.
We we go around and
try to restore
people's belief in the
magic of Christmas.
people like you Riley.
Mom told me not
to eat a full burrito
before going to bed.
Yes, gives you heartburn, or
gas, or sometimes both but
that's not
why I'm here.
No no of course not you said the
Christmas spirit had
left the building,
you said and, I quote,
'the magic is dead'.
Do I look like I've
left the building?
And how about this
magic? Yeah, but
don't wake your
mother.
I need you to
recognize your magical
thoughts. I need you to
find the Christmas spirit.
Right, well aren't you
a Christmas spirit?
Okay, here you are.
Yes, good point, I was thinking a
little more figuratively with
a touch of abstraction...
You know what I'm
saying.
- No, not at all yeah
- I was afraid of that
It's like this: you
need to rediscover
the spirit of Christmas.
And to do that,
you have to give
it to someone else as well.
You mean like giving
gifts and stuff?
I mean I gave change to,
like, one of those
bell ringers downtown.
And I watched the
Charlie Brown
Christmas special every
year
All the knowledge
in these books and
that's the best you
can come up with?
So, you mean, like 'the
sharing and giving
of yourself and finding
fellowship in mankind'?
Much better! The Christmas
spirit isn't the same
thing for everyone.
You're a smart young man,
you'll catch on quick.
What does that mean?
A fortune cookie?
'You will discover the spirit
of Christmas and give it to
someone else.'
You can't be serious.
[Music]
Better? More serious?
Good, on the back of
your fortune is a
series of numbers
there but rules follow
them in order and
then follow the signs.
- What signs?
- A sign. A harbinger, a
mystic
symbol from the comic
cosmos or it could
just be an arrow
in a dirt. I have no
control over what
it will be.
Is this a dream?
Not a dream.
You're welcome.
If you don't want to do it
for yourself, do it
for your mother. She
still believes the
spirit of Christmas
but she needs you to
believe it as well.
To do that you have
to help someone you
don't know find it
too, even if they
don't necessarily
want it at first.
It won't be easy but
the rewards will make
up for it.
No, what if I can't do it? What
if I fail?
You won't know until you make an
effort.
Okay I'll do it
[Music]
I'm going to be at work
until late tonight. You're
going to be at Andy's
overnight, right?
Yeah, yeah. Wow, mom
you're right about the
burrito thing, I had
the craziest dreams
last night
Did you get a job at
the mall?
Umm, yeah. Yeah.
I applied but they
wanted to see if the
costume fit first
in case I shrunk.
You look fine. Hey,
we're gonna be alright.
- We are.
- I know.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Wow. The spirit of
Christmas.
So Riley trusted
hope, the Christmas
Spirit and imagination
and his own spirit
of adventure and
found himself in
Malibu. Sun dappled
stretch picturesque
coastline with the
Sun shines bright
the breezes blow cool
and it almost never,
ever rains! Almost.
Is this a place I need to
bring the Christmas
Spirit to?
Why am I talking to myself?
This is nutts.
'Yes, this is the place.
The Christmas Spirit is
needed here, get to work'.
Alright, I don't know
why these
people need to Christmas spirit,
but ready or not, here I come.
[Music]
This is the home of
Tom and Winnie Sims,
their daughter Allison, and
their
faithful dog Campy.
And while they all
love Christmas and
share some wonderful
memories this
particular holiday, they
needed a little help.
[Music]
This is Tom. He looks
a lot with numbers.
Unfortunately the
company he works for
is, um, what's the nice
name they put on it?
'Restructuring', which is a
wishy-washy way of
saying soon to be out
of work.
Tom isn't normally
so stressed out and
intense but restructuring
will do that to you.
[Music]
And this is Winnie.
She writes books for
kids and kids of all
ages, but she's had
a bit of our writers
block recently and
there's nothing more
disappointing and
being so worried
about being an adult
forget what it's
like to be a kid.
[Music]
This is Allison.
She's got more on her
mind that her folks
losing the
Christmas spirit.
[Music]
And this is Justin,
he's a boy next door.
Unfortunately the
holiday has not made
Allison very patient
with her family,
or with Justin's
inability to read her
mind and this is the
state of the Sims
family just before
they meet Riley and
things get very
interesting.
So how's the web
surfing going?
Great! You know
apparently there is
this website where
you can actually
look at pictures of
your children and
your grandchildren?
Gene, next door,
was telling
me all about it.
Well I'm sorry I
had sent you any
pictures, okay?
It's just that
we've been busy.
Listen, I
feel bad about this
Christmas. I don't know,
time just got away from us
I guess.
Well you could
still come out.
No, I mean, just Tom's so
busy with you know the
sale of the company
and money's tight.
It's not like we'd do
anything special.
Winnie, is there something
you want to tell me?
because you know
you can.
No, no, we're just...busy
Okay don't worry
about it. I mean don't
be so wishy-washy we
don't have to spend
every holiday together.
How's Ali doing?
Oh, um, well you know
we went through the
terrible twos and
then our gawky 12s,
well now it's our
malicious felony 17!
Seem to remember
you at that same age.
Need I remind you?
No, thank you, please
don't.
I know you
delight in telling
everybody though what
you mean about me.
Hang in there, Winnie,
um I'll call you
on Christmas okay?
Okay love you.
Bye.
I love you too, Winnie
Bye-bye.
[Music]
Oh my gosh hold on,
hold on.
Oh my gosh, are you okay?
Come on up we go,
oh look at you, oh dear.
Okay, there you go.
Good as new.
So, are you a friend
of Allison's?
Allison?
I'm Winnie, her mother.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Riley.
So Riley, was
the gate speaker
broken? I have been
meaning to get that
fixed. That gate has never
worked properly.
Yeah, yeah, the the
speaker's broken.
You know, Allison's
upstairs, I'll get her
for you.
No! I I wanted to
surprise her for Christmas.
I wanted to give her a
homework assignment
we've been working on.
Cool. Okay
[Music]
Oh Riley I'm so sorry
about that phone call.
Oh, wow!
I hope you don't
mind I thought it
looked like it needed
a little help.
Yeah we've been a
little preoccupied.
We're not usually here for
Christmas.
Oh, why is that?
Travelling, work, deadlines.
We're not a very holiday
oriented family.
Yeah I know what you mean.
Yeah, it's really too bad.
Well how so?
Oh, well, when I was a kid
Christmas was my favorite
time of year.
I just loved it. It's like,
you know, like we had
stockings that were
just full of toys
and on Christmas Eve
we got to open one
present, and my mom
would take the
simplest things and make
a feast fit for a
king I can't even boil
water. I guess it
skips a generation
Oh, so Allison can cook?
I guess it skips two
generations.
Yeah it all sounds
really nice. So why don't
you do it again?
Why don't you
recreate the family
Christmasses?
Oh I think things just get
complicated when
you get older. Maybe
one day.
So, uh, where's your
bathroom?
Oh it's right
around the corner
[Music]
Okay job well done
Christmas tree is
trimmed and Mom at a
nice memory. Christmas
spirit is solved.
Can I go now? Hope?!
I hope I can go now.
[magical whirring, chimes]
Really?
You tens with your
'InterTubes' and your
'My Faces' seem to
think that everything
can be accessed and
taken care of in the
blink of an eye. Where
is the hard work,
the thoughtful consideration?
the self-reflection a
comes with an honest
awareness and assessment
of your role
in a given situation?
So you’re saying I can't go yet.
Riley, Riley, Riley. Have you
met Winnie husband yet?
Their daughter?
No, but I'm not sure
how me getting
arrested for trespassing
is going to help.
What am I supposed
to do?
I would start out by gaining
an ally.
Winnie seems to be
on the right track.
She just doesn't know
how to go about
reconnecting.
Neither do I!
You'll figure it out!
How? What am I
supposed to do?
You're a smart young
man. You'll figure it out.
It's your journey.
Yeah, journey to the
looney bin.
Riley you were chosen
for a reason.
You are a messenger
of hope in
That's me, in case
you forgot.
Your and the Sims
need to understand
that the true magic of this
season is in
communicating
your joy,
your love and
your forgiveness
to those that mean the most
to you.
And those you don't
even know.
But you're sure
I have to stay, right?
Get back to work, Sparky.
[magical sounds]
Oh boy.
*[instrumental
'We Three Kings']*
Oh Riley, thank
you so much!
You did such a nice job with
this tree.
Oh, you're welcome
Oh, wow, I guess I
better go back to work.
You didn't come here
to save our Christmas.
Allison's upstairs,
I'll get her for you.
Allison!
Uh, no no no.
Miss Sims, what do you do?
For work?
Allison doesn't really talk
to me...that much
about you.
I don't suppose she would.
Are you really interested?
Yes! Yes, very.
Follow me.
It's, ah, right in here.
Oh, all these books!
That's awesome. I love
to read.
Oh yeah? Me too. I
guess that's why I
became a writer.
A writer? That's
really cool, Mrs. Sims.
Oh call me Winnie.
And, yeah. It's cool.
You've got monsters, that's
cool.
Oh yeah, monsters, oh
yeah, I guess that's what
I'm known for.
'The Littlest Werewolf'.
It's a children's book.
'The Littlest Werewolf'?
You wrote this?
Yeah.
I, um, I did the art too,
but I'm not
as good at that.
Are you crazy? This
was like my favorite
book when I was a
kid. I had my mom read
it to me every night!
I forget; it's been ten
years since it's been out!
It's been a hard one to
top. I'm not sure what I'm
going to do next.
Everyone seems to have a
good idea except for me.
I remember every word.
it's crazy, my mom she
did the best werewolf
howl!
Well maybe she read
my other books!
'The Littlest Creature,'
'The Littlest Monster'.
Oh, and
'The Littlest Mummy.'
Oh, yeah, she read those.
But the first one of them is
kind of the best.
Oh yeah, I know.
These weren't as good.
No, I didn't-
No, no. It's just
that the publisher
wanted me to
keep writing them
because the first
one sold so well.
Oh, that's too bad. You
could say I got into reading
because of your books.
Really?
That's so nice to hear.
Yeah you know,
now that I think
about it, it was
the first book I
ever read.
I read it back to my mom.
Makes you creative,
I guess.
Yeah I forget
that reading out
loud can spark
the creative fire.
Yeah, my mom, she'd
read it to me,
I read it to her
and we'd do all the
voices and stuff.
She's really good at like,
computer design and
stuff, and she says
I'm creative and it
made me want to become
a writer one day.
So yeah, I guess it is.
[knocking]
Oh hey, I just wanted
to see if you wanted
a cup of coffee. I
made a fresh pot. But I
see we have company.
Oh this is Riley.
Allison's friend.
Oh, hi Riley. I'm Tom.
Nice to meet you.
His mom read him
'The Littlest Werewolf'
when he was a kid
and now he wants
to be a writer.
Oh! That's...that's
great. Listen, I'm
gonna be working late
again so we should
probably plan on
ordering in. I mean
Oh, Honey, again?
It's almost Christmas.
Sorry, I don't know what
to tell you.
Nice seeing you Riley,
I'll tell Alison
you're here.
Uh, no, please don't do...
Hey Riley, will you do
me a favor?
Yeah, sure.
[knocking]
How's my little girl?
[sigh]
Look, we're gonna order out.
You tell your mother
what you want. I have
to work late again.
Of course you are.
Why don't you just
tell me when something
new happens?
Alli, come on,
this isn't easy on me
either.
The company's shutting
down. I have to go
through their books.
I've heard this song.
Please skip ahead.
[sigh]
It's just weird that I never
get to see you, and
Christmas is
ruined, all so you can
work on some stuff
for a company that's
just going to fire you
after you're
done. Nice one, dad.
Sweetheart, I don't
want it to be like this.
But it is. I don't want
to talk about it.
[sigh]
Fine.
By the way,
your friend Riley is here.
Who?
Your friend
Riley from school
I don't have any
friends from school.
And the moon came full and
bright, and the pack
ran together except
one, try as he might.
The littlest werewolf
was left behind,
the pack thinking
it was a little more
than a growl, but
none of them knew.
He had his own special
howl.
[mimicking howling.
pitifully.]
Come on! Let me help you.
[howling]
[howling in unison]
Ah, Allison! You caught
Riley and me trying to
spark our creativity.
Oh, did I?
Yes, why didn't you
tell me about him?
We're like two peas in
a pod!
Yes, Riley's
quite the pea isn't he?
We all know how I
like my Peas: Mushed.
Listen, do you two
want a soda because
I'll be right back.
And Riley it
was sooo
nice to meet you.
Come back anytime.
I will, Winnie.
Who are you, Riley?
Is that your real name?
Did Zoe put you up to this?
Her stupid
pranks are so stupid.
But this is the worst yet,
making a
chucklehead come
over and embarrass
himself with my mom.
Yeah, yeah she did.
You caught me.
I knew it. What was she
thinking?
Are you filming this?
Are you supposed to give
her the footage?
Yeah, yeah that Zoe,
what a nut!
Give it here.
Ummm...
She is going to be
so sorry. I am so going
to get her back, in
front of the whole school.
What was the end game?
What were you
supposed to do?
I was supposed to
make a fool of myself.
At least that's how
it's ending up.
Huh. Did Zoe have something
on you? Is that it?
Is that why you look like a
slack-jawed narcoleptic panda
right now?
Yeah, that Zoey, she
got me.
I knew it. But this is
going to backfire on
her big time.
How can I use
this? You know what
you're going to do?
Bring joy and happiness
into your life?
Stop being a goofball.
No, you're going to
pretend to be my boyfriend,
and help me drive my
parents crazy.
I am?
Do you want your phone back?
Or do you want me to tell
my mom and dad about
your little prank?
[sigh]
What do I have to do?
You'll stay for dinner.
How are you about
swearing uncontrollably?
Not very.
I don't suppose
you would be.
How about breaking
things?
Break something in here
right now.
You know, I'd rather not.
You are terrible at this
already.
Tell me about it.
Fine. Just follow my
lead when the time comes.
Here we go!
Oh, thank you.
Riley's gonna stay
for dinner.
Oh. Ok.
Um, how do you
feel about Christmas?
[Music]
I hate it.
That's what I thought.
Well, uh, since Allie's busy
would you like a
tour the house?
Sure.
Okay.
Chompy! Chompy!
The only dogs will
hibernate every winter.
[magical chime]
[Music]
Doesn't really seem
like Christmas, does it?
You mean like snow
and sleigh bells
and stuff?
No. More like the feeling.
What's your favorite
Christmas memory?
Um, well my mom
she kind of has
to work a lot and
she's getting laid off this
year so...
Oh, I'm sorry
to hear that.
It's been a tough year
for everyone.
She did almost beat up a
mall Santa once, but I'm
sure that's not
what you're talking
about.
Your mother sounds
like an amazing woman.
She is, she is. I just
kind of feel like I
let her down.
Why?
Well she kind
of feels like you do
about Christmas.
About making it
magic.
Well, I might be
overthinking it 'cause
[mumbling]
I'm seeing a strange
fairy woman.
Excuse me?
Uh, never mind.
How about this? While
you're here, you and
I try to reclaim
a little Christmas
magic for ourselves.
I am definitely going to
need a little help
with Allison though.
Yeah, so I've
noticed.
I'm not so sure my
husband is going
to be open to the
prospect either.
Well, you never know
till you try.
Well said, Riley.
One down, two to go.
I'm sorry?
Uh, what's for dinner?
Good lad.
[magic sounds]
Would you like
something to drink?
Sweetheart, has the
gate been giving you
trouble? I can't get
it open.
Oh, no, but Riley
couldn't get in, he
had to jump the back
fence.
Yeah, 'cause the
gate's not working,
exactly.
Yeah, well these
clickers aren't
working either.
I guess I can go
pop the manual release.
I don't want to,
but I gotta grab
some stuff from the
office.
I thought we'd have
a really nice
meal with our guest,
right Riley?
Yeah, a nice family
dinner is great for
Christmas.
Yeah, well that's all
fine and dandy,
but I have a
bunch of work to do
before the year's
end and I have news
for you. If I can't
get that gate open
there won't be any
dinner.
Oh that's not good.
I'm pretty good with
electronic gizmos,
can I take a look?
Knock yourself out.
Hi, Sweetie.
What is Riley going to
do? I don't think he
should be doing
anything to help
anyone.
Well, at least he's
offering to help.
[distant thunder]
[metallic clattering]
Good one, Riley, I
would have never
thought of pressing
buttons for the gate
opener. You're my hero!
Alright, Allie, Please.
The manual opener's
just over there.
by the hatch
out there in the
downpour. Did I ever
mentioned that I don't
- Yes, honey.
- All the time, Dad.
You don't like the rain?
No, no, I
grew up in Florida.
I worked my way
through school
pushing
water from those
summer rain storms off
the marble entry-way
to the administration
building.
They called him Squeegee.
Ok. Ok.
- 'Squeegee Boy'
- Here.
That's why I moved to Southern
California! It wasn't supposed
to rain.
[mechanical swish]
[groan]
- Oh, honey!
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
Oh!
[Allison laughing]
I'm calling the
repair people!
What? No, no, never
mind! The lever's right
here!
Somewhere...
Yeah, the blind leading
the more blind.
I think Riley did
it on purpose.
He slammed into it
on his motorcycle or
something
You have a motorcycle?
Yeah! Tell her how we'd
ride around on it with no
helmets on.
That's not true, is it?
I, uh...promise to get
a helmet for it. And an
engine, too.
I took the bus here.
Ok, we'll discuss it later.
I'm going to call the
gate people.
I told you
to follow my lead
Yeah, sorry.
Do you want me to tell
them about your giant
fraud? I'm sure the police
can get through
that gate.
No, I'll do better. Really.
Here it is! Oh...
never mind, that wasn't the...
that was the
sprinkler...
Allie, have your mom call
the repair people.
Please honey. Daddy's
getting very moist here.
You betcha, Daddy.
[dialing]
Oh hello, is this, uh,
Spirit Gate Repair?
[female voice, via phone:]
Yes, what can I do for you?
What is your gate
problem?
Our gate won't open.
The clickers don't work.
Have you tried the manual
gate lever?
[chuckling]
Hello?
Oh yes, I'm sorry I'm
getting a cold. Any
luck with the
manually lever?
No, we can't even find it.
Okay let me pull up
your account here, Ms. Sims,
just hold on one second.
Oh yes I see your
problem.
What?
Your gate is a PBX 20.
We've been getting
a lot of
problems with that
model. I would not try
to fix it on your
own. Why, we've been
getting reports of
electrical issues,
small fires, real
Stephen King
type-stuff.
I wouldn't get any water
near the system, either.
What are we supposed
to do? We're trapped
inside our house.
I will send someone
out first thing
tomorrow. But yes, I
will just lie low for
the evening. Talk to
your family, family stuff.
Fine.
[beep]
I'm a little wet and
just so you know, this
isn't the manual
release lever.
[laughing]
Oh, he's my hero.
Oh, go on in!
Oh, it's freezing!
So I guess you're staying
with us tonight Riley.
Is your mom going
to be okay with that?
I'm sure she will be.
I'll call her.
Yeah, uh, Allie, you
wanna get the guestroom
ready please?
So we can have a stranger
over for Christmas but
not Grandma?
He's not a stranger,
he's your friend.
'Cause you're
too busy to care.
Whatever, Allison, you
know we can't afford
a big Christmas this
year.
I understand. You two
are both too wrapped
up in yourselves
to care about grandma
freezing to death in some
cabin in Michigan.
Allie, grandma lives in a
condo next to a golf
course and she said
it was perfectly
fine for her to take
Christmas off this
year given the
circumstance.
Take Christmas off?
Who does that?
Who takes Christmas off?
That's totally stupid.
But I'm glad we're
doing it because
you'd make sure this
Christmas stinks,
anyway.
I'll start dinner.
You wanna go after her?
I'll start dinner?
That was a little
awkward, wasn't it.
Yes.
Okay well I guess I'll go
start dinner.
Hope you like frozen
stuff. We've got a
lot of frozen stuff.
Sure, but I'm actually
pretty good at
making dinner because
my mom has to work
all the time.
Oh okay,
that sounds great
I'll see what you have.
Frozen stuff.
[plastic crinkling]
You know, uh, Allison's
grandmother lost her
husband
two years ago and
they moved to Hawaii
to retire, and first
we thought she'd
stay there or move
back here. But she
decided that she
missed the cold and up
and moved to Michigan
of all places.
Didn't know anyone
there, just had a gut
feeling that she
should start the next
chapter of her life
somewhere new.
Pretty extraordinary
woman, I'd say.
Sounds like it.
Yeah. Hey um, wondering
if you could help me with
something? You've
been friends with
Allison for a while
right?
Sure, minutes upon
minutes. Hours even.
Why does she
hate me so much?
I'm sorry, that's...that's
not fair to ask of you.
No, I, uh, I'm sure she
doesn't hate you,
You did just see
what happened,
didn't ya?
Y'know, man, I didn't
even realize how
important Christmas
was until recently.
Until very, very
recently. Now family...
Family's family.
Yeah.
no matter how small,
no matter how
dysfunctional, if it means
that much to one
person then it's worth
it.
I love my mom and
I wish...I wish she
didn't have to work
on Christmas.
I'm sorry. Got a little
emotional and stuff.
Don't be. You should
say that to your mother.
I'm sure she'd appreciate
it.
I will.
Hey Mom, uh, it's me Riley.
I'm at Andy's and
I know you're at work
and all but I just
wanted to say I love
you and Christmas,
it's going to be
special, no matter when
or where, so...
[beep]
[magical sound]
For someone who said that
the Christmas Spirit's
magic was dead, you sure are
doing a lot of
abracadabra.
Yeah, well, you're
weird.
I won't argue.
Keep going, my lad.
[magical chimes]
[music]
[footsteps]
I was looking for
Allison I thought I
might talk to her.
Well you're welcome to
try. She's in the
living room.
Oh, do you mind me
asking who Justin is?
Oh Justin. He's a
neighborhood
boy. He's quiet but he
seems nice.
Do you know him?
No. No, not yet.
Well, I'd better go help
with dinner. I hope you
like frozen food.
[magical sounds]
Is that your famous
catch-all stew?
Thought I'd give it a try.
It's Christmas after all.
Who are you, and what
have you done with my
husband?
Okay, I deserve that
Oh, Winnie. I've taken
on too much. Allison's
right. I'm working
myself sick for
a company that's
closing and a job I
won't even have. None
of it'll be enough
to pay the mortgage.
I need to find a new job.
We'll be fine. You know,
you'll get a new job
and I'll actually
come up with a story
idea.
Oh, now you are
a great writer. And
however long it takes
you is however long it
takes you.
See? My biggest fan
is always right.
And I'm your biggest
fan, and if we just
focus on that, it we'll
be alright.
[kiss]
Hey, do me a favor.
Do not let me ruin
this Christmas
anymore than I already have,
ok?
We're trapped in
our own house!
You couldn't ruin it
anymore!
This is true!
Why don't you take a
break for tonight, ok?
You know, finish what
you have tomorrow
morning and then
the last part of the day
we'll go Christmas
shopping. And who knows,
maybe Allison will
want to come with us.
You really think so?
No.
Easy. Easy, easy!
There's an art to this.
[laughing]
Now, one to go.
What are you doing
here? Really?
The gate's stuck.
No, not that,
Goofball. Even if
someone did put you
up to this,
no normal person
would have stayed.
Well, apparently I'm not
normal.
You like Christmas?
I'm beginning to
understand
the importance of it.
How being together
is most important
thing to do no
matter what.
My grandma makes
the best sugar cookies.
With cinnamon and
nutmeg. She would
make it wherever we
were we were.
We were even on a cruise
once and she had the captain
open up the kitchen
so she could make it
for us.
Those cookies
are Christmas.
She's not making it
this year, or...?
No...she's going to make it.
Yeah, Riley, you're
right. We're gonna make
this happen!
Um, I didn't say anything.
We're going to make
this happen and
you're going to help
me.
[music]
Let's go, Goofball!
I want to help make dinner!
Me and Riley.
You do?
Yeah. Take a load off.
Are you sure?
We've got it covered.
Ok, then.
Sweetheart...
Let us know if you
need anything.
- So what are we making?
- Stew, apparently.
And trouble.
What's that?
Here you go.
Are you crazy?
This stuff's hot!
Really, no
kidding. Dump 'em
in the stew.
Why?!
Fine.
What does burning
your parents faces
off have to do with
your grandma ?
Well, my dad starts to
sneeze and gets the
hiccups when he eats
spicy food.
And when he's having his fit,
I'm going to help him.
And you're gonna take
his credit card,
pretend to be him, and
buy my grandmother
a plane ticket.
So that's your plan? To
poison your
father so I can commit a felony?
Well you said it
yourself: Christmas is
worth it.
I did not, ok? Christmas
is so not worth prison time.
You said that you
wanted to help the
family come together
for Christmas.
Not like this!
Then how?
Through wishes and dreams
and unicorns with
fluffy pancakes
on their heads.
No, Riley.
Sometimes it takes making
a hard choice,
even when it gets
you in trouble.
What about you? Why don't
you get your mom's
credit card pretend
to be her?
After the eBay
incident, my file
has been flagged.
I'm being tracked
24/7.
You have a file?!
Oh, Riley. Grandma's
cookies!
Can she make a filing tool?
I over-did it, I think.
This is crazy, Allison.
I mean...totally crazy
taste this
stew's gonna
have, Allison!
Are you okay, Riley?
I'm great. Totally fine.
Awesome, Ms. Sims.
Did you put something spicy
in the stew?
- No.
- Yes.
Well, be careful, ok?
'Cause you know how your
dad reacts to spicy food.
He sneezes and hiccups,
and let me tell you
that ain't pretty.
Yeah, we wouldn't dream
of doing anything like
that.
Ok, let us finish up
in here. Dinner will
be ready in 30
minutes.
Ok, perfect.
You would make a
terrible criminal!
Yeah I know,
isn't that a good thing?
[rain]
Dinner's served.
- Oh.
- Oh! Wow!
Here you go, Riley.
Let's get to it!
No...! Ah, I forgot the
biscuits. They're fluffy!
I'm going to go help him.
Be right back.
Can't start without
fluffy biscuits!
Do not mess this up
for me. Now you know
what you're going to do?
Well, your father
slowly suffers a
chili pepper inferno, I
sneak into his office,
steal his credit card,
and then call
your grandma.
You have all my
grandma's information
for the ticket, right?
Good! Now after you
put the card back,
I'll call my grandma
tell her the good news,
and look like the hero.
And you're gone by
tomorrow.
It's foolproof!
No, no it isn't,
actually at all! I'm
sure you thought
this through.
Just grab the biscuits,
Apron Boy.
[sigh]
- Wow!
- Oh, wow!
Okie biscuits. Ok!
Allie.
Thank you.
Smells delicious, guys.
I'm so proud of you.
There you go, Buddy.
Thank you.
Uh, I'd like to say a
couple things...
Um, I'm just really
glad that everything
that happened today
happened so that we
get to share this
wonderful feast
together.
And hail to the chefs!
Yes, here here!
Mmh! Allie and Riley,
good stuff!
Did you put something
spicy?
No, Honey, it's fine!
I can take a little heat.
[holding back a cough]
[flamenco-esque music]
Allison!
What? I told Riley to put a
little bit, and he goes all
crazy!
Then try some!
Both of you!
A bigger bite
than that!
[coughing continues
in background]
[breathing strangely]
My face, my face!
My tongue...
Now go help your
father, keep him
moving, and I will go
make the chocolate
milkshake.
A chocolate shake is
the only thing that
will help him when
he gets like this.
Of course sometimes he
seizes it through
his nose and it can
get a little messy.
I suppose so.
[brief music]
Hope. Hope! I need your
help here.
[magical sound]
Whoah! Don't scare me
like that!
It's a small shower. I
didn't have a choice. I
got my shoes all wet
earlier.
Look, I'm in trouble.
I think you're doing a great
job!
No, it's Allison, she
wants me to get her
grandma here tomorrow
for Christmas from
Michigan.
Well, It sounds lovely.
Her coming here. Not Michigan
so much. I had
a relationship with a tree
sprite from Detroit.
It didn't
work out.
What, really?
No! There's no such thing
as tree sprites. Don't be
so daft.
So what's
the problem with
Grandma visiting?
It's Allison, she wants
me to steal her
dad's credit card and
buy the ticket
illegally.
I see.
I'm all for cutting corners
for the greater good, but
this is not quite the
way to go about it.
That's what I said,
but what am I
supposed to do?
Why didn't they have
grandma come out?
Uh, Winnie said something
about being busy,
Tom said something
about money and
Allison thinks her
parents hate her.
I don't know, they're
kind of wishy-washy
about it.
I see. So there's still
one member
of the family you
haven't spoken to yet.
Grandma?
what am I...what am I
supposed to do?
You going to magically
transport me to Michigan?
Yes.
I'm going to call Charles,
my flying Christmas Dragon.
Oh, you silly fool
Do you or do you not
have her name, address
and phone number
in your pocket?
Ah...yes...
Dial her up on
the phone.
What should I say?
The truth is
generally preferable
Yeah but she's gonna
think I'm crazy.
The truth often is.
[magical chimes]
Let's see...'Grandma'...
[buttons beeping]
[phone ringing]
[beep]
Hello, this is Betty!
Um, Hi, this is
Riley Blackwood.
well hello, Riley
Blackwood, who are you
and why are you
calling me so late?
Um, well...
[Tom wheezing in
the background]
Is that my son-in-law,
Tom?
Yeah, it is, Maam.
Somebody give him something
spicy to eat?
Yeah.
I give my chili an extra
kick sometimes, makes him
turn the most marvelous shade of
vermillion. So, revised
question: Who are you,
and what are you
doing at my daughter's
house?
Um, well it's kind of a
really weird story...
Riley, I've seen and heard a lot
of strange and lovely things
in my lifetime, but
at my age I don't
have time to dilly-dally
so spit it out, Son.
Uh, a Christmas
spirit named Hope
came into my bedroom
and told me to
bring the magic of
Christmas to your
family. And then she
dressed me like an elf.
I'm listening,
Riley go on...
Um, ok...
[uplifting music]
It's so beautiful here,
with you.
I just hope that...
Hey, don't say it.
Let's just stay in our
happy place together, ok?
It's been a long time.
Come on now, have I
been that bad?
I think we've both been
that bad.
[kiss]
Are you trying to
tell me that we should
appreciate the
smaller things in life?
Yes.
Okay.
[in funny voice:]
I'm a shrinking man
that needs love.
Love me, Winnie!
[laughing]
[music]
hey Utah
Hey Goofball, get up and
make me some coffee!
Where are you?
[coffee percolating]
What are you doing?
I woke up early.
I see that. After you
messed up yesterday
I thought
you'd be gone by now.
No, I'm just gonna
make you look bad.
Yeah, back off, Pal.
I'm the only one in
here that makes me
look bad.
I've got to salvage stupid
Christmas somehow.
[dishes clattering]
Good morning!
Do my eyes deceive me?
Is my daughter up and
cleaning?
I made coffee, too
Oh, Winnie, I think
that an alien may have
taken over here.
Are you an alien?
A Christmas alien, hmm?
Hey, that's a good idea.
I've been wanting to do a
Christmas story!
You're the alien, Dad.
Oh, am I? An alien, huh?
- Oh, she's smiling!
- Ah, I saw it too, yes!
Honey, I'm going to write
down that Christmas
alien idea, because
it's really good. I'll be
right back.
Thanks for the inspiration,
everyone!
Now, is this coffee
sabotaged? If I drink
it am I gonna
get peppers or...flying
coffee weasels out
of my nose?
No, coffees
not sabotaged.
I mean, unless
Riley's sabotaged it...
Um, Mom and I are
going to go shopping later,
Would you like to
come? I mean we could
get some frozen
yogurt and...
[mumbling]
comfortable for
them maybe I'll take
Maybe.
'Maybe'. I'll take that. I
just have a bit of work to
finish up before I do,
but I promise, it's just
a little, ok?
[music]
Hey, Honey, have you
been in my office?
I cannot find my pen.
No, sorry.
[Music]
Where's my mouse?
Mr. Sniffles is gone.
So is my pen. The
silver one that
I write with.
Yeah, and the mouse to my
computer and the stress
ball that your mom
gave me that I kept
on my desk.
Where's our stuff?
Good morning.
- Hey...
- Hi...
Did you go into my room
and take something of mine?
Were you in my office
last night?
Yes I was...
Where's his backpack?
It's in the kitchen.
I think they came and
fixed the gate this
morning
'cause it opened right
up, so...
I knew I shouldn't
have trusted you.
Trusted him about what?
Umm...
I might have had
him use Dad's credit card.
What?!
I didn't, I didn't, I swear.
I worked it all out with
Grandma Betty.
You talked to my mother?
Where's our stuff?
Now you stop it, young lady.
Ok? You're in enough
trouble already.
Riley I think it's
best if you go yeah
Yeah, yeah. Um, sorry.
What? He wasn't
my friend!
I was just trying to
have a good Christmas.
Why is that so bad?
Look you're gonna
have to call the
credit card
company to find out
what they did with
it, and then cancel
the card.
Yeah. You'd better check on
yours as well.
Ok.
[magical sounds]
Sorry, I really messed this up.
No, not at all Riley.
You did great.
How can you call that great?
You believed, Riley.
Your selfless and
thoughtful, and you
took a chance on hope
and faith and
something bigger than
yourself!
If that doesn't
prove that you have the
Christmas spirit
in your heart, than I
don't know what
does.
But it all got ruined! I'm
probably gonna go to jail!
No, Riley. You may not
think you now, but
you've given them a
gift one that maybe
they don't appreciate
at the moment but
they will. And I hope you do,
too
You're a special
man, Riley. Don't forget it.
[magical sounds]
[contemplative music]
Well, no one use my card.
Mine either.
Alison, get down here!
I didn't do anything!
No, of course not.
And you never got
banned from the
internet, either.
You're never gonna let me
forget about that.
Actually I'm not.
Alright, alright. Alli...
I need to know what
you had Riley do
with my card.
Stop yelling at m-
I'm not yelling at you!
I just need to know
what Riley did with my
card!
[knocking]
- Are you serious?
- Look, you need to
listen to your father.
Hi, it's your Grandma Betty!
Hi Tommy!
...Hi...
Hello!
What, would somebody like
to take my bag before
the old lady's arm
falls off?
Oh, my baby!
What are you doing here?!
Merry Christmas to you,
too, dear.
Now if you'd all like to
stop
being quite so shouty
with each other we
can get down to
business, okay? First
things first,
where's Riley?
Uh oh.
The look!
Uh, let's sit down
you tell me all
about it, okay?
So you sent the boy off
thinking that he had
literally stolen
your Christmas.
Uh...yeah...?
Is that bad?
Let me read to you from your
Christmas letter this year.
'Tom is working to
ensure the smooth
transition of the
company's assets.
We hope his loyalty will
lead to a new and
exciting opportunity
in the new year.'
Is this a holiday
greeting or a press
release?
'Winnie is
considering several
options for her
next book.' I seem to
recall that sentence
in previous holiday
letters. It's an oldie
but a goodie for
sure. Really, can
you call yourself a
writer? I mean can't
you even pretend
that something
exciting happened this
year? With all the
stories in the world
you got writer's block?
Winnie!
I actually came up with an idea
today.
An Alien Christmas.
Ok. 'Alison is finding school
challenging and is
looking forward to
new challenges.' Really, Alli,
have you
challenged yourself
at all this year?
I was the one who got
you here.
What? No, no, no. You
did nothing of the sort.
I paid my own way
here, honey.
You did?
Yeah.
But Riley...
No, Riley did nothing
except to tell an old
lady that
her family loves her
very much but they
were oblivious to
the notion that she
might want to come and visit and
actually pay her own
way, even if there
wasn't some big crazy
shindig going on.
And then when
Riley told me about
Allison's nefarious
little plan I told
him not to worry, that
I would come here
and set my family
straight. I really was
hoping to meet him.
Yeah, well about
that Riley...
He stole our stuff...
maybe...
Uh huh. Ok,
if you'll excuse me
with all the excitement
and traveling
and everything I'd
like to use the facilities.
Allison, why don't
you bring your
Grandma to her room?
What do you want
Santa to bring you
this year?
Well, if Riley didn't take
our stuff, who did?
What's that?
What?
On Choppy's bed.
- That looks like the stress
ball from your desk.
- It sure does. It is.
Hey, here's the remote
for the guestroom TV.
Chompy must have stolen
these things.
Do you think he has
another place that
he puts his toys?
I don't know. Chompy!
Chompy!
Chompy! Chopmy!
[whistling]
Where is that dog?
What?
He may be our Christmas
thief. Dad found some of
the missing things in his
toy basket.
Chompy's pretty OCD
about his toys.
Exactly. Let's go.
- Chompy!
- Chompy! Chomps!
[festive music]
[music continues]
Chompy! Chompy!
Chompy! Chomps?
Where are you, boy?
Chompy...
[sigh]
Chompy?!
Chompy!
Come here!
[whistling]
Win, anything? Allison?
Tom, the firepit! Chompy
loves to sleep by the firepit!
I found some of his
chew toys there!
[in unison]:
You have to go out in
the rain again.
[muttering]
Stupid dog...
You think our stuff is out
there?
I hope so.
Oh!
[clapping]
Here you go.
And that's for you.
'Chompy: The Dog Who
Stole Christmas.'
Wow, that's good
I'm totally stealing that.
Mom, that was your idea. You
just came up with that.
Oh.
[laughing]
Wow.
- Allison.
- Justin?!
- Hi.
- Um, I just wanted to come over
and say thanks.
Thanks? For what?
That's my scarf! I
mean, your scarf! What?
Yeah, your cousin
brought it over
this morning.
My cousin?
Yeah, Riley?
Riley? Oh right ,
Riley, my cousin.
Yeah, yeah, you know he
brought it over. He
said that you've been
meaning to give it to me.
Yes, I've been meaning
to give it you.
But, you know, I'm sure
you've
probably been busy
helping your parents
with Christmas stuff, and...
What? Yeah, yeah
[coughing, forcefully]
Yeah, yeah, I've been helping
my parents prepare for
Christmas.
Did you know she
liked Justin?
No, but I'm guessing
that she wanted to tell us
except we were a little too
busy.
You're right. Let's not
do that again.
Don't mind them.
Please, don't mind them.
They seem like
they're having a good
time.
But you know,
that’s, uh, that's
really cool that
you like Christmas.
I love Christmas
I love Christmas, too.
You should come
over later with your folks.
My grandma's here and
we're gonna have a big
meal.
We're gonna have a big
Christmas Eve meal, right?
Uh, yes actually, I
was just about to
alert the royal chef
to begin deboning
the pheasant. Figgy
pudding for all.
Well, you know what? My
parents are going to
some like business
dinner thing, so I
think it'll just
be me if that's alright.
Uh, that's fine.
Totally fine.
Well, good.
I'll see you tonight.
Oh, and thank you,
again.
[whistful sigh]
That's Justin.
We know, sweetheart.
He's lived
here as long as we have.
Riley gave him the
scarf that I was going
to give to him.
Uh huh?
Riley is actually
an ok guy.
And?
And you totally misjudged
him.
What? I don't think I caught
that.
Okay, I totally misjudged
him.
What, what I can't hear
what you're saying!
- No, no group hug!
- Yes, group hug!
[inaudible teasing,
laughter]
Ok, ok fine. I am an awful
person and I owe Riley a big
apology.
Well I don't know
how all this came
about, but I'm sure
not complaining.
I know Christmas
magic when I see it.
Chompy! Where have
you been?
Chompy!
[laughing]
Committing felonies in his
sleep apparently.
Well, now before we begin
this big Christmas
meal, there's one
thing we have to do:
Call Riley!
Yes, absolutely. Allie?
What?
Call Riley and invite him over
so we can make up for
everything.
And his mom, too!
How? I don't have
his number.
But he's your friend.
Uh, about that.
I, uh...
Wait, I stole his phone!
That is the only time in
my life I'm happy to hear
those words!
I'm telling you, the kitchen is
closed until I know
Riley's on his way.
Don't worry mom, we're on the
case.
Apparently it's not a
Sims family Christmas without
a little
mystery and daring do,
would it?
Okay we should call
his mom, first. What's?
her name?
Sarah Blackwood.
What? I talked to him.
I listened.
Some people
still do that.
He said his mom was
working through Christmas.
Her company
is closing down.
Ah, there's a lot of
that going around now.
Wow, there is a lot of
that going around!
Look where she works!
Wahoo Toys?
That's where you work.
Yeah, which means
I've been helping to
put her out of a
job faster. And more
efficiently, too. And
look at the extension.
This is computer
services. They've been
working
double-time transferring
data.
Well, then maybe she should
report personally to
the VP of Accounts
for a status update.
No, no, no. I can't
do that.
Uh, good luck eating
your shoes tonight, Hun.
Oh, look, if you
can't pull rank now,
when can you pull
rank?
[sigh]
[beep]
Yes, hi, this is
Tom Sims. Um, can you
connect me with a
Ricardo in computer
services please?
Hi Ricardo, Tom Sims.
Yeah, fine, fine. How
are you doing? Yeah,
yeah, yes they do grow
up fast don't they?
Listen, listen, Ricardo
I need you to get
Sarah Blackwood to
my house tonight.
I'm aware of that, but she,
she has some, uh...
she has vital information
that I need to
reconcile with
accounting. I know it's
Christmas but I want
you to requisition
for a car, and a
nice one, and make sure
that they pick up
her son Riley, too.
He's totally checking with
corporate.
Put your foot down!
I will, shh, shh!
Ricardo, listen to me.
I know you're on the
other line trying
to get authorization
from corporate, but
as far as I can tell
I'm the only person
in corporate working
their butt off on
the holiday so I
would appreciate it if
you ensure that I get...
yes I will.
Six o'clock would be
fine. Yes, thank you
so much.
Merry Christmas to you
Cicardo...
Uh, Ricardo.
Wow, Dad. That was awesome.
Awesome. Awesome Dad.
I could get used to that.
Okay, it's off to the market
I need supplies!
[Music]
Come in! Grandma is just
finishing up dinner.
The best one you'll
ever have.
Hi, Tom Sims,
Wahoo Toys,
VP account services.
Well for the next
eight to ten days.
Anyhow, you must be Sarah.
Yes. Yes I know who you are
This is my beautiful
wife Winnie.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Our neighbor, Justin
Hi, how're you doing?
I believe you met our lovely
daughter, Allison.
So, are we not going
to reconcile the
accounts data?
That just sound so
un-Christmassy, don't
you think?
I say we jump into the
festivities instead.
But before we do, I
just wanted to tell
you that you have a
really great son, and
I'm sorry it took us
all so long to notice.
No worries here.
So, Riley, how how do
you know the Sims?
What exactly are you up to?
That's kind of a long story
Yes it is! And if you
come into the dining
room I'll tell you
all about it.
I wanted to sit
next to Justin.
- You look beautiful.
- Oh, thank you.
- Sarah, welcome Dear.
- Thank you.
Riley, hi, I'm Betty.
Right.
I really enjoyed our
conversation last night
and I'd like to speak to
you again later on so
don't forget, ok?
I won't forget.
Dinner in ten minutes
everybody! I hope
you're hungry!
One sec,
I just want to say
a quick toast. To
family and to friends,
may the Christmas spirit
warm us all.
Cheers!
- Thank you for coming
- Thanks for having me.
Merry Christmas!
Mom, let me help you in
the kitchen.
[thoughtful music]
[footsteps]
Hi. Well, how did you
like your dinner?
Oh, it was the best
I've ever had. Really.
I'm stuffed!
[magical chimes]
Oh, that's good. But I
have some cookies
baking in the oven
right now so I hope
you saved a little
room.
Sounds great.
You know, when we talked
last night you were
honest about Hope,
the Christmas spirit
that you said you saw.
Yeah.
Well I wasn't completely
honest with you.
How's that?
My husband
Lawrence passed away a
few years back and
he was the love of my
life.
I'm sorry to hear
about that
But we never would
have met that weren't
for a
Christmas spirit by
the name of Faith.
Wait, you saw a
Christmas
spirit, too?
I didn't. He did. And
for years he
would tell the
story about how Faith
cajoled him into
going to this holiday
formal where we
met and had our
first dance. And even
though it was a
blizzard and he had to
drive a snowplow, he
made it for the last
dance, and his bow
tie was peeking out
from under his
parka. And, I mean all
those years I just
figured it was his
imaginative way of
telling me that he
loved me. But last
night, Riley, you made
me realize that he'd
been telling the
truth all along. And
it just made me love
him all the more.
So I really have to
thank you, Honey, for
giving me that.
- You're welcome.
- Thank you.
I better go check on
those cookies.
Yes.
Riley? Hey, so I was just
talking with Tom and
Winnie...And it seems
like they want to
start their own toy
company based on
Winnie's books, and a
little birdie told
them that I'm a real
creative asset to
any company and
apparently I have this
world-class werewolf
howl. Ok, I've
only met Tom a
couple times at the
company and you don't
go to school with Allison.
So how did
you get here?
Well, I wanted us to share
something special for
Christmas, and I
wanted a little bit of
magic to believe in.
You're not gonna
tell me are you?
No, I'm not, but I will
write a story about
it one day I promise.
Open it.
'May you both believe
in Hope.
Merry Christmas
Sarah and Riley.'
[music]
[musical chimes]
So you may have
figured out I didn't
actually steal
Christmas. I just helped
Hope work her magic a little
and,
contrary to Tom's
lack of pronoun
precision, I am a
patient Dame who may
love her naps, but I
love my family more!
'Chompy the Dog Who
Stole Christmas' was
whinnies next book
and it was a great
success. Because of
it Tom and Winnie
kept their house. The
Sims toy company
made a Chompy dog
stuffed animal, that
became the first
success for the new
company. I'd like to
think it was because
Sarah made sure it
captured my quiet
dignity, if I do say
so myself. And Reilly?
He went on to write
his own stories.
Stories full of
fantasy and wonder, and
an unshakable belief
in the spirit of Christmas.
[music]
[music continues]
[music ends]