Patrick, it's me.
Are you blind?
Maggie?
Something really horrible
has happened to one of the boys.
Which one?
Well, I don't know which one.
I'm not really sure.
All the colors, they got dark.
Colors?
I had a premonition dream, OK?
Wait a second.
You're waking me up
at five in the morning...
to tell me about
a premonition dream?
Yes, I am.
Look, all right, I'm sorry.
The last time,
I made a big mistake.
I had the wrong kid, OK?
I was absolutely sure
it was Darren.
And it turned out
to be Gideon.
Don't you remember?
Gideon broke his ankle.
This is exactly
what happens, Mag...
when you sleep alone, you know?
You hallucinate.
It has nothing to do
with me sleeping alone.
I like sleeping alone.
Well, then maybe
some little bitty part of you...
doesn't like sleeping alone.
Get serious, please.
Why don't you call all the boys
and conduct an inquiry?
It would make you
feel better.
Look, just let me know
if you have any sexy dreams...
involving
your estranged husband.
Patrick, stop it.
Tits and elbows.
Just stop it.
Will you stop it?!
Have your eyes
really gotten better?
They're perfect.
Isn't that amazing?
It's a sign.
-It's not a sign.
-It's a sign.
It's not a sign, Mag.
Oh, it's Alfred.
Alfred.
I got up early
this morning to work.
Oh, God, Cynthia.
I can't get enough of you.
Why are you doing this?
Couldn't sleep.
Bad dream?
Premonition dream.
Yeah? Which one of us
was bumped off this time?
I don't know.
It got dark towards the end.
That's great. Now you
can worry about all of us.
Not you. You're right here
with me, safe and--
Simon, are these dreadlocks?
Sure are.
Well, I didn't know
you had the kind of hair...
that could do that.
A little Jell-o does it.
Jell-o? I ate Jell-o.
It never did that to my hair.
Mom, you put the Jell-o
in your hair.
You let it dry.
You don't wash it out.
Oh, OK.
How many times have I told you
to clean out this garage?
Twenty or thirty.
Well, it's happening today.
It's Izzy.
It's not Alfred.
Well, don't look, then.
It's not you.
All right.
You win.
Well, Mom, first one back
to the car gets to drive.
Oh, since when do
fourteen-year-olds...
know how to drive?
Since that fourteen-year-old's
older brother taught them how.
Who taught you? When?
Come on, get a move on, Mom.
You take Silvermans'.
Simon.
Nope. His mom.
Oh! They've sure got you out
on some freezing morning.
Say, how are those cute twins?
They're great.
They're at school.
Leave me alone!
Stop!
Get out of here!
Mom?
Watch out!
Daisy! Daisy, come here.
Come here.
Daisy?
Come on, baby.
You keep that monster inside.
There's a leash law, you know.
She already bit my son once.
I want my paper.
You better not leave it there.
The next time, it's going
to be in the street, OK?
You're supposed to bring
it to the front porch.
Bastard.
Language, Mom.
Jesus Christ, he could have
taken a chunk out of you.
He was aimed for the Kill.
I know, those teeth,
they just--
It's the twins.
What?
Mrs. Silverman
mentioned the twins.
It's the twins.
Oh, Mom, how do you know
it wasn't me--
I mean, with the dog?
No, because now it's over.
I'd feel better if it was you.
But I don't feel better.
I feel much worse.
It's the twins.
We know it's not the twins.
We talked to them last night.
What bad things could happen
in a dorm room overnight?
Earthquake, fire,
drugs, accident.
Oh, now there we go.
All real possible, Mom.
Now, look, we know
it's not Gideon...
because nothing bad
ever happens in Utah.
Who taught you that?
I can be as crazy as you.
I'm a mother.
I've earned it.
Forgot about Percival.
Percival.
Hey, all you singers
back home.
This is me and my buddies...
bringing you greetings
from the Sinai.
Hey, Mom, I miss you.
Hey, Dad.
Things are going
pretty well here.
They treat me pretty good.
But there's not
a whole lot to do.
We do get movies
every Sunday--
a lot of Sylvester Stallones
and "Lethal Weapons."
I think they're trying
to tell us something--
trying to make us
into heroes or something.
Dad.
Hey. What the hell
have you done to your head?
What are you doing here?
Hey, look at this number
in the background here--
in the black.
Great thighs.
Patrick.
Pink's better. Better buns.
What's going on with
the boxes in the hallway?
What are you doing here?
Mom, have a heart.
Well, I wasn't real happy
with our phone conversation.
And I'm not sleeping
very well at the office.
Well, then, why don't
you get an apartment?
Will you chill?
Any halfway reasonable man
who's separated from his wife...
rents an apartment.
You're not allowed to
just bop in here now.
I'm not allowed?
Who paid for this place?
Is this my jacket?
Will you stop it?
-It is my jacket!
-No, it isn't!
Give me that!
And will you please turn
down that trashy noise?
I think you're right
about her.
You know, if you were
to suddenly turn soft...
I wouldn't hold it against you.
Patrick, don't. Look...
Simon and I are moving.
Oh, that's smart...
when you got a completely
paid-for house right here.
I want to be closer
to my work.
Work? What work?
We interrupt this
regularly scheduled program...
for a news bulletin.
I told you to turn that--
Forty-three marines
are reported dead...
an unknown number injured...
in an explosion this morning
at the American compound...
of the multinational
peacekeeping force...
in the Sinai desert.
Oh, my God. It's Percival.
Details remain sketchy
at this hour.
But preliminary reports
indicate the blast occurred...
in the early morning hours.
It was of suspicious origin,
the explosion leveling...
the three-story
headquarters building...
where an undisclosed number
of marines were sleeping.
Is that where he is?
What building did
they say it was, Simon?
...with updated information
as it becomes available.
Turn it off.
Didn't they say
it was a noncombat zone?
There was forty-three
killed out of five hundred?
Wait.
The blast apparently collapsed
the Marine building...
which was located on
the southern tip of the Sinai...
near the town
of Sharm El-Sheikh.
More than sixty men
are known dead.
Sixty?
They just said forty-three.
Efforts are underway
to rescue others...
still trapped
beneath the debris.
Reporting live from the Sinai...
we now take you back
to our studios.
We will bring you
the latest update...
as soon as more details
become available.
Now back to
your local programming.
How many men were actually
sleeping in that building?
Why don't you know?
Doesn't the Marine Corps
keep tabs on its few good men?
OK, look, when do you think...
you might
know something definite?
If you don't know...
who can I call
who might know something?
You can't be telling me
there's nothing I can do!
I got a son over there!
It's quite a situation,
isn't it...
when there's nothing
you can do but wait?
Come on, guys.
Crank it up.
We're going to be late
for church.
Hurry upstairs.
Get your shoes on. Come on.
We're running behind.
OK. Reasons you won't
marry me again?
Because you're too young.
That's inconsequential.
I have a note from my mom.
You've seen it.
What?
I called Alfred.
Mom needs him.
What did they say?
Nothing. They had
absolutely nothing to say.
"You'll just have to wait,
sir...
"like all the rest of us.”
I had too many children.
I was asking for trouble.
Oh, knock it off with
the self-pity, will ya?
An explosion happened.
That's all we know.
You're spoiling that cat.
She happens to miss me.
See?
For twenty-five years now...
you have been dunking your tea
bag exactly seven times...
and then throwing it
in the sink.
Who do you think takes
your tea bag from the sink...
and puts it into the garbage?
Where is the garbage?
...estimated that more than...
seventy-five marines
have been killed.
And it's feared
the body count is rising.
Give as much as you can,
brothers and sisters.
Give as much
as you possibly can...
to spread the word of God...
and tell us your want.
We'll make your pledge
work hard.
We'll do our best
to pray over your want.
Every dollar is appreciated,
every fifty-cent piece...
every nickel you send in.
God isn't greedy.
He knows that life is hard,
full of...
Why are we watching this?
Well, it beats the news.
I called Beth O'Neal.
She doesn't have
any information.
If it weren't
for Tim O'Neal...
Percival wouldn't even
be in the Marines.
He'd be sitting here
with us...
trying to find out if
anything's wrong with Tim.
Instead, here we are sitting
trying to find out...
if something's
happened to Percival.
Mother, statistically,
it's very unlikely...
that Percival
has even been hurt.
Alfred, what's
the good of statistics...
if you're
on the wrong end of it?
Well, I called Izzy.
He's picking up the twins
and bringing them home.
Not Gideon.
Don't call him yet.
It'd be too hard for him.
Oh, shit.
What is it, Patrick?
Uh-oh. Dad's blind again.
Patrick, sit down.
For God's sake,
will you sit down?
You don't think I don't
know my way around here?
Did you bring your pills?
Where are they?
Who put all this junk
in here?
Are they in your jacket?
What is she doing?
What's with the boxes?
Mom says we're moving,
just me and her.
You left them here?
You were supposed
to have been moved out.
This is my house!
What about Dad?
He's sleeping in his office.
It's weird,
even for this house.
We're separated!
Will you get
your father's pills?
That's a good point.
Just sit down. Lay down.
Why do you have to be
so stubborn? Sit down.
You should take a shower...
and do something
about your hair.
My hair? What big
fucking tragedy, my hair!
Patrick,
will you just lie down...
and stop pretending
like you're in charge?
Listen!
Ironically,
casualties may be higher...
Because on Sunday morning,
many of the men were asleep.
Sunday is the one day...
most of them did not
have to report for duty.
God's day.
Identification of the bodies
will be made more difficult...
because most of the men
weren't wearing their dog tags.
The Marines will have to rely
on dental records.
Pills, Dad.
...and officer identification
in those cases where...
Do you want me
to talk to her?
No. Let her stew.
This is a zoo!
Mother?
Why don't you...
go upstairs...
and shower?
Everyone will be
coming home soon.
I remember. This is
the Mussorgsky, isn't it?
Where all the movements
are different pictures.
You told me about this once.
I remember you--
this is the great gate at Kiev.
I remember you got down
the encyclopedia.
God, how old--
I must have been six or seven?
You showed me the pictures...
the wrought-iron gates...
and that, I don't know,
that church...
that church
with the gold dome.
1 did that?
And the bells here.
I remember you saying...
that this was the sound
of stars falling...
of star confetti.
And it was the springtime...
and this was the celebration
of the Resurrection.
"You see?" You said...
"There is possibility
of perfect joy."
That's fabulous.
I couldn't have done that.
I mean, you were six.
That meant that Izzy was four.
Percival would have been two...
Gideon just starting to walk.
I was pregnant with the twins.
How could I possibly
have had the time...
to take a book down
and show you this?
I don't know, but you did.
That must have been
Beth O'Neal.
I wasn't
that kind of a mom.
Well, what do you say?
Let's go.
A shower,
a change of clothes.
I don't have to be dressed
to hear bad news.
I know, Mother.
It's just that everyone
will be coming home...
and the neighbors
will probably stop by.
People love a tragedy.
Well, Mother, you don't
have to talk to them...
or deal with them.
I'll handle them.
Oh, sweetie, you don't
have to do that.
Yes, I do.
I do, and I will.
I know.
Oh, Alfred.
Take off your coat.
Hi. Mom?
Hi, Mom.
Where's your laundry?
Mom, we wouldn't bring that
at a time like this.
Have you heard anything yet?
Hey, what's different?
You look terrible.
Yes, he does.
Who's there?
Who's come?
Your father's gone blind again.
Oh! I thought that was over.
No. He walks into this house,
he goes blind.
What does that tell you?
I don't know.
It could be stress.
Hey, I am under stress.
Do you see me going blind?
Come on in here.
Don't listen to her.
Hey. Go see Dad.
Hey, how are you?
Go see Dad.
It's pretty tense
around here, huh?
She's in crisis mode.
Loud music?
Mussorgsky.
Uh-oh. What are
all the boxes for?
I don't know.
Simon says they're moving
without Dad.
Dad's been sleeping
at the office.
She's never gone
this far before.
Alfred, you have to talk to her.
Is she serious this time?
I don't know.
We're all pretending
she's not, though.
Don't spoil the fun.
Typical.
Deny what you don't like.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
I just packed all this.
Looking for something--
something important.
So, come on, Dad.
Guess who?
One of the twins?
Yeah, but which one?
What, is this a test
or something?
Yeah. Feel my face.
What is this, a mustache?
Yeah.
"M" For mustache,
"M" For Merle.
Darren's clean-shaven.
Oh, I see. So if I go
blind permanently...
I can tell the two
of you apart?
Informa--who's this?
You still have
the headache, Dad?
What, everybody's
experimenting...
with their facial hair
or something?
So first the headache,
and then the eyes started?
Yeah.
Did you take your pills?
Yes, I did.
...the Sinai desert.
Wait! Shh! Shh!
...inquiries
from the families...
of the Sinai peacekeeping
contingent...
the Marines have announced...
that they will take
the unprecedented step...
of preparing
a list of survivors.
Spokesmen caution that rescue
efforts are still under way...
and some units continue
to be scattered.
So a definitive list may take
several days to prepare.
For further information,
relatives may call...
Alfred.
Call that.
Damn it!
Oh, Simon, get your cat
out of this house.
I'm busy.
We now return you to your
regularly scheduled...
All right. Darren?
Come on. Merle?
The cat.
Your father
could trip over it.
Get this cat--
-Damn it!
-Mom, relax.
It's not the cat's fault.
Oh, no.
Hey, it's cold out there.
If she doesn't like it,
she can go in the garage.
It's really crowded in there.
Well, if you'd
cleaned it out...
it wouldn't be crowded,
now, would it?
Now what are you doing?
Something.
Simon, that's not an answer.
It's just what we've heard.
They're preparing a list.
Each survivor has to be seen...
by a first sergeant
or an officer...
before they put the name
on the list.
They said it could take days.
What if a marine is wounded?
I guess it takes longer.
What if he's dead?
They send someone...
a chaplain or an officer.
We're in for a long siege.
That's Percival, Dad.
He's throwing passes
out on the front lawn.
He's got his green
football jersey on...
his big old helmet.
Yeah. He just
turned nine, right?
Said he'd die if he couldn't
make the football team.
Break!
Come on!
That's all right.
Come on, line it up!
Shift!
Come on, Percy!
Grid eighteen!
Grid eighteen! Cigar!
Look out!
Percy.
Sweetie.
Mrs. Singer, wait a minute.
We'll get a stretcher.
Wake up.
Wake up, Percy. Come on.
Wake up. You can do it.
Wake up, sweetie.
Come on. Wake up.
What's your name, son?
Percival Singer.
And who is this person
right here?
My...my mother.
Pretty strong lady, too.
She carried you
off that field herself.
She what?
In front of all the guys?
Sure did.
She carried me?!
Like a baby?
And the guys saw?
He's going to be fine.
Now, you keep him flat
for the rest of the day.
But if he sleeps too long...
wake him up
and give me a call.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
How could you?
Why didn't you
just leave me there?
They have stretchers
for things like that.
Didn't you happen
to see the stretcher?
I'm sorry. I just--
I couldn't help it.
That's no answer.
Look, sweetheart.
When a woman
becomes a mother...
there's just this little
part of her that takes hold.
And it grows and grows--
this monster-mother part--
kind of like
those little things...
that are in your cereal box,
when you add water...
they grow to three hundred-times
their original size.
Well, when a woman
becomes a mother...
it just rules her life,
this monster-mother...
three hundred-times-bigger
part.
Make some sense.
I saw you lying there.
I was scared.
I wanted to get you to help.
And I couldn't
hear or see anything else.
But other moms don't do
that weird stuff.
Well, you know, I'm sorry.
But you just have to play
the hand you're dealt.
You're a difficult kid.
I'm a difficult mom.
No! You're worse than that!
You do wrong things!
All right.
Well, this time...
I'm going to do
a right thing.
No more football.
You mean for today, right?
No, I mean forever.
It is too dangerous.
I can't protect you.
Oh, you don't mean it.
Tell me you don't.
I do mean it.
Don't you realize...
You could've been paralyzed?
You could've had a concussion?
You could've broken your neck?
You ruin my life!
What is this, a goddamn morgue?
Mort.
I mean, what the hell
is all this?
Don't start, Mort.
The boxes. Explain the boxes.
Simon and I are
moving to the city.
Alone.
And Patrick, what about him?
Patrick's going
conveniently blind.
But not deliberately, Mag.
I mean,
give the guy a break, huh?
He made a joke
about my getting a real job.
What does he call
your working for me?
It's only part-time...
and it's the same thing
I used to do...
when I was a volunteer,
only how you pay me...
because you like
having me around.
Not true.
You're a pain in the ass.
Do you think I'm going to pass
that civil-service exam?
Piece of cake.
Do you think I'd make
a good social worker?
Sweetheart, it pours out of you.
Well, Patrick laughed at me.
And?
-Hello?
-It wasn't funny.
Yes, Percival Singer
is over there.
No, we haven't
heard anything yet.
What do I say?
So is it like a throbbing pain,
or is it like a vise pain...
or is it like
a hammering pain?
Knock it off, Izzy.
Pain is pain.
It's my turn to have a life.
I always thought
you had a good one.
You should stop smoking.
That is a chicken coop.
Your father made us live
in a chicken coop.
It was a--
it was a henhouse.
No, it was a chicken coop,
and it reeked of chickens.
And there were
little chicken ghosts.
And at night,
I could hear them cackling.
Yeah, well, it was
structurally very sound.
Mom, look at your
two little braids.
You look so young.
I was--l was twenty-three...
and I had two kids
and one on the way.
Simon, turn it off.
The newspapers are calling.
Even the "New York Times."
Well, we should try
to get ahold of Gideon.
Not yet.
You want him to read
about it in the papers?
I'll get the number.
I'll dial.
I'll call. Come on, Dad.
Look, if he hears my voice,
he's gonna know it's bad news.
Gideon, it's me.
Dad.
How are you doing?
Good. How's it going?
There's been an explosion
in the--in the Sinai...
where Percival was stationed...
and we can't get any word
yet on how he is.
Do you want me to come home?
No. You've got
an important meet coming up.
This puts
the conference championship...
in a hell of a perspective, Dad.
Look, until we know
something more...
the best thing you can do
is just to stay where you are.
Besides, Percival's probably OK.
We all have a pretty
good feeling about it.
You'll call me
if anything happens?
Yeah, we'll let you know...
just as soon we find out
something, OK?
-OK.
-All right, buddy.
Why did you tell him that?
What good's it going to do...
for him to come
out here from Utah?
Maybe he wants to.
He'd miss days of training
to sit around here and mope.
Maybe he wants to be
with his family.
He's in training!
He doesn't care about that now!
He's got to care about it.
He's got to concentrate
on what's real.
If you lose that,
you lose--
Lose what? What?
What, damn it?
What do you lose? What?
Can you see, Patrick?
What? What can you see?
What does it look like, Dad?
It looks like you
need a shower, Mag.
I like you better blind.
Move.
Do you still have the headache?
Yeah, still there.
Possibly low blood sugar.
Hell, it's not
low blood sugar, Izzy.
They rejected
the chemical theory...
along with the virus theory
and the brain tumor theory.
Well, there's got to
be a cause, Dad.
Well, all the doctors
at Johns Hopkins...
couldn't come up with one.
So where does that leave me?
Uninformed
and periodically blind.
That doesn't mean you
have to give up looking.
What exactly would you
like me to do, lzzy?
I don't know.
I mean, I should know,
but I don't.
Lunch.
Pass the bottle opener.
Mrs. Anderson
baked us a cake, huh?
She's Simon's high-school
teacher or whatever.
So how about my mustache?
It looks pretty good.
It looks like long Velcro.
What is that?
Go like this. You have
something on your lip.
It's because it's blond.
I'm going to dye it.
Should I dye it?
It looks like tail hairs
on arat's a...
On a rat's ah?
Ass. Like a rat's ass.
Peanut butter.
You look like a rat's ass.
I get it. I get it.
Anyway, dye it green.
Red. If you dye it red,
it will look like...
Sweetie, don't do that.
It's disgusting.
I get the picture.
Let's talk
about something...
Anyway, dye it green.
Dye it green.
Oh, my God!
Simon, Jesus Christ.
Come here.
Hey, Ma, you better
have that disinfected.
Boil the finger or something.
Yeah, it's horribly unclean.
How does the song go--
the Irish one you used to sing?
Johnny McEldoo and McGee and me
And a couple or two or three
Went on a spree one day
We had a bob or two,
and we knew what to do
And beer and whiskey flew
Drop the other shoe.
Do you know
what happens to a person...
when he's crushed to death?
What, are
you going to give us...
a complete description, or
what?
Oh, I'm sorry, Patrick.
I didn't--
I'm sorry if I can't
push past the pain...
the way you can this time.
The pain?
Push past the pain.
Isn't that what you
always told the boys?
Just push past the pain,
and they always did.
Past the shin splints
and the bone spurs...
and the muscle spasms
and the...
It wouldn't hurt you to do
a little running yourself, Mag.
Get your mind off things.
I don't want to get
my mind off things.
You tortured your boys.
All these years
yelling at them--
trying to
make them like you.
All right, Mom.
It's a little overboard.
All right, leave.
Go ahead.
Why don't you just split
if it's too much for you?
Yeah, it is too much for me.
You torture yourself.
Good, Mom.
Dad, where you going?
For a stroll.
What are you doing?
Coming with you.
Give it a rest, Izzy.
You going to ring the doorbell?
We've reached
the insane asylum stage.
You know, those "ripoffs” were
the one thing I invented...
that your mom thought
was halfway useful.
I guess that's because
they kept Percival...
and Gideon from
getting overheated.
What about the hand-warmer
you made for Alfred...
when he was playing
the piano?
And the iridescent
pajamas for the twins...
so Mom could tell them
apart in the dark?
Strokes of genius.
How come you never
invented anything for me?
I don't remember you
around much, Izzy.
Could you stop
making all that noise?
It's distracting.
I was there.
You just didn't notice me
a whole hell of a lot...
because you were always running
with Percival and Gideon.
Well, you could have
come along.
Right. I was the one who always
got a "D" in gym, remember?
Dad, I was thinking.
Maybe these eye attacks
are related to stress.
Yeah? Well,
if that was the case...
I probably
would have gone blind...
a week after I met your mother.
Well, no. No, Grandma.
Grandma, we haven't heard
anything yet.
Yes, it's hard.
It's...it's awful.
You know, I didn't
really want Alfred.
I was eighteen.
I just wanted to have fun.
But, of course, when he came...
he was the world's only baby,
so sweet and so cute.
And then along came Gideon...
Percival,
and all the other guys...
and that was it for me.
Yep. It's hard.
How did you manage to
become a psychologist...
have two kids, get a divorce,
snare Alfred...
still make a great meat loaf?
By the way, you might
want to just try...
a little bit of this,
all right?
I'd say Alfred did
the major share of the snaring.
I was very leery.
He's so...
Young.
Yes, he is that.
And neat.
That, too.
And responsible.
That, three.
I robbed him of his life.
It's my fault he grew up
without any passion.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I'd say somewhere
along the line...
he found plenty of passion.
Really?
A marine
out on perimeter duty...
was shooting this home video
to be sent to his family...
when the blast occurred.
To update us now
on the situation in the Sinai...
we have on the phone
our reporter Nick Zarron.
Nick, what can you tell us?
I haven't seen carnage
like this since Beirut.
It's like
the ground is crying out.
There's so many trapped men.
As we can see, rescue efforts
are still frantically...
continuing throughout the night.
I want to donate a kidney.
That's enough of this.
Let's cash it in.
I can't believe last night
at this time nothing was wrong.
Merle, come on.
What is that animal
doing back in the house?
Mom, it's really cold out there.
She's been out all day long.
Have a heart.
She doesn't choose
to sleep with you.
It's only a cat, Mother.
With her whiskers and
bad breath in my face...
and her tail and butt
in your father's--
I mean, when he was
living in the house.
Well, at least
you get the good end.
If you think
it's such a great idea...
then why don't you
sleep with her?
-Fine. I will.
-Great.
Look, we're so tired,
we're sniping at each other.
Come on. Let's hit the sack.
Good night, sweetie.
Where are you planning
on sleeping tonight?
In my bed.
You know, back to back,
no touching.
I was hoping we could
have a conversation.
There's nothing to say.
This is sort of
the reason I left.
You left because
I told you to leave.
I left because I figured
if I was going to be alone...
I could do that by myself.
You left
because I told you to leave.
It was my decision.
Don't try to take that from me.
Your decision?
Yes. I told you to leave.
You have a really,
really bad memory.
I don't have a bad memory.
I have an excellent--
Anything that's important, I
remember perfectly.
What day did Alfred graduate...
from elementary school,
for instance?
Huh? June 27, 1982.
What does that have
to do with anything?
What day of the week
were we married?
What day of the week?
It was a Monday,
about 10:00 a.m...
Little Chapel of Bliss...
and the judge's name
was Wilfred--
It was
the Little Chapel of Harmony.
-Bliss!
-It was Harmony!
All right, I don't
remember who was there...
and what time it was...
and what day
of the week it was...
because all I saw
and all I cared about was you.
I was so madly in love
with you. I was so happy.
Well, what happened?
I mean...
What do you want, Mag?
I want a different life.
I never chose this one.
Well, who did?
Don't tell me it was me.
I didn't demand that we
have seven kids, you know.
I didn't say
you had to be cranky...
and angry and unhappy
all the time.
I'm going to take that
civil-service exam.
And if I pass it,
I'm going to take the job.
Well, good. Good.
That's good.
A lot of people have jobs.
A lot of unhappy people
have jobs.
Patrick, don't make fun of me.
I swear to God,
I'm going to take you...
right out of this bed
and kill you...
if you start making
a joke out of this.
Don't start that.
Come here.
It's not funny!
OK. I am cranky, and I'm--
I don't want to be cranky.
I don't like being cranky.
I used to be able to
laugh at your jokes.
I can't laugh at them anymore.
Because whenever I do...
I just feel like I'm
giving in to something.
I don't even know what it is.
That's pretty funny.
I'm sorry.
Patrick?
Oh, I thought it was...
See, they send
an officer to tell...
Gideon, it's you.
Oh, Gideon.
Oh, honey, welcome home.
That's the way it
was supposed to be.
Percival winning.
Hell, I only ran to be with him.
You know, train with him,
hang out with him.
Dad always said,
"If you're going to pass...
"you have to
blow around the guy...
"so he won't re-pass you.
"So you break his heart.
"He won't have the will
to catch up again.”
That day it sort of kicked in.
He hated me after that day.
Oh, sweetheart.
You can't blame
yourself for winning.
It was like I didn't even exist.
Look, you work harder
than Percival.
And you don't give up.
You should be proud of that.
You go on upstairs
and get some sleep, OK?
I'll make you some French toast
when you get up.
What's the matter
with your legs?
It's just...
it's a case of the flu.
Oh, Percival.
I hate you!
I'm not going to
tell you again!
Let go of him! He can't--
Stop it! You're killing him!
He can't breathe!
Percival, let go!
I'm going to stop this car!
Stop it! He can't--
All right, I'm going to--
Did you hear what I said?
Mommy, they're killing me!
All right,
I'm stopping this car!
Let go of him!
You're strangling--
He can't breathe!
I beat you!
Are you really leaving?
That's between
your father and I.
Oh, like it doesn't
affect the rest of us.
Are you still living
with that sweet little girl?
What's her name,
Cindy or Mindy...
or something like that?
Must be really
difficult for the girls.
I mean, you are so handsome.
And with this beard,
it makes you look so old.
Well, if you do find
a significant other...
please bring her home
so I can meet her.
Well, how can 1?
You won't be here.
Everybody's up early.
Oh, no. Not in this house.
Out you go. Come on.
Is this for me, Izzy?
It is now.
Thanks.
Go join your little cat friends.
Gideon came home last night.
He pulled out the old video
of his race with Percival.
He feels so guilty.
He's walking around
like he's a hundred.
He says it's the flu.
Oh, God damn.
Izzy, get the pills.
Why now?
Get the pills, Izzy.
I don't understand.
I was right here.
It doesn't make any sense.
I mean, he came down,
and he seemed fine.
He had some tea
and looked at the paper...
and then boom!
I can't figure it out.
I mean, this is a crisis, and
I can't do anything about it.
You can answer the door.
Go ahead. I've got
your father's pills.
All right, I'm coming.
I've got your pills.
I know this must seem like
a convenient way out...
but it just comes on me.
Wait.
Come on in, come on in.
We just had to tell you.
Tim just called me.
He's all right.
He was out on the perimeter
of the compound.
Well, do you know
where Percival was?
I mean, did he know?
The last time Tim saw
Percival was days ago.
Really, he hadn't
seen him all weekend.
Where was Percival then?
He was in the building.
The building that was bombed?
Yes, but he could have
been on leave or...
out in another perimeter.
It's so confusing
over there...
Tim couldn't get
any information.
Mom, it doesn't mean anything.
I'm going to get dressed...
and go take
my civil-service exam.
Mag?
Mom?
Yeah?
Look at those trophies.
Which ones did I win?
Which ones are Percival's?
Can't tell, can you?
You know why?
Because it doesn't matter.
Mine or Percival's,
it's all the same.
No. I had Percival...
then fourteen months later
I had you.
You're a separate person.
It's my fault if he's dead.
I beat him,
and he quit running...
and then he met Tim O'Neal,
and he joined the Marines...
and they sent him to Sinai.
Now he's probably dead
because of me!
I threw him
out of the car.
That's what
started him running.
Maybe it's my fault.
Well, maybe it is
your fault.
Or maybe it's
your father's fault.
If he hadn't been
so irresistible...
then we wouldn't
have had sex.
And if his sperm hadn't
been such great swimmers...
then maybe they wouldn't
have reached the egg...
Mom. Look, Mom,
I got the picture.
Finding somebody to blame
isn't going to make him safe.
This was a great race,
and it was yours.
Mrs. Singer!
One question, Mrs. Singer.
I know this is
a difficult time for you.
One question, Mrs. Singer.
Look at me! Look over here!
Look at me!
Mrs. Singer! Look at me!
Red Cross units are
being flown into the Sinai...
to give aid and comfort
to the growing number...
of wounded marines
injured in the...
Nice fire, Percival.
What are you using for kindling?
This is Newton's Second Law
of Thermodynamics.
That must burn pretty well.
Yeah. Funny how it
works out that way.
You know how I feel
about smoking dope.
You know, how can you
be so self-righteous...
about something you've
never even tried?
All right. Let me try it.
What?
Let me try it.
Clearly you're
not going to listen...
to a thing I have to say
unless I speak from experience.
So why don't you help me
gather some experience?
I think you've lost it.
Well, maybe, but let me...
Seriously?
Yeah.
Take a deep breath...
and then hold it
in your lungs...
till they feel like
they're going to burst.
Don't laugh. That's strong.
Just wait.
This is pretty cool, Mom.
This is pretty good.
Yeah?
So what classes are we cutting?
French...
English...and History.
What a coincidence!
All the classes you're flunking.
Yeah, so what?
Well, so you're not going
to graduate, that's what.
Doesn't matter.
I'm not going to college anyway.
Great. Just great.
You flunk a few classes,
so you quit school.
Your brother beats you
in one race.
You quit the team.
You can't play the guitar like
Jimmy Page in three lessons?
You quit.
Doesn't this seem to
be some kind of pattern?
You know, Percival...
the minute something
starts to get too hard...
or you can't do it immediately,
you just bail out.
You quit it, and you say...
"I'm out of the woods now."
But it's not true.
You're not out of the woods.
because...
the woods are all around you.
I mean, I'm in the woods,
you're in the woods.
There's always
something difficult...
that's going to
present itself.
Like some big tree,
some redwood.
Some majestic,
some mystical redwood...
pops up or some kind
of little fir tree.
You turn around, and there's
some little fir tree...
sitting there,
or some dogwood is...
you know,
somewhere else.
And you're just,
because you're--
I mean--
Life is the woods,
is what I'm trying to say.
Yeah, that's--
that's very deep, Mom.
You're very deep
when you're stoned.
I guess that's a little...
It was a little heavy.
Majestic tree.
You're totally out of it.
Percy, you're absent
from your own life.
It's breaking my heart.
You know, not once...
Not one time in
my whole rotten life...
have I gotten
one thing that I want.
What? What is it?
I want to live in a family
where I'm not compared.
Alfred is the oldest.
Izzy is the brain.
The twins are the twins.
And now Gideon is the runner.
Percival? Yeah.
Percival's the difficult one.
How do you think
that makes me feel?
I'm sorry.
I'm doing the best I can.
Yeah, well, what does
that say about you, Mom?
I'm joining the Marines,
me and Tim.
I'm old enough.
You can't stop me.
Margaret Singer.
Dad?
Are you all right?
Do you want me to come in?
Yeah.
Can you see?
It's starting to come back.
The shower.
Maybe it did some good.
It's never happened
two days in a row before.
It's getting worse.
What do you think,
it's an omen?!
Do you think God
is interested...
whether or not you pass
your civil-service test?
I should be dead, and I'm not.
It's a sign.
Yeah, but a sign of what?
That I shouldn't take the job.
Well, how do you know it
isn't a sign that you should?
No. God wanted me to stop.
I didn't stop.
He wants me to stay
at home for the boys.
Maggie,
let me tell you something.
You're a fruitcake,
you know that?
Life is capricious,
and you have to be vigilant...
and watch the signs.
Yeah, but things happen
to you anyway, Maggie...
no matter how much you worry.
I'm not going to
talk about Percival...
and if I pass the test,
I'm still not taking the job.
Oh, well, well, well.
Now we see.
You're nothing but hot air.
Let me tell you a secret.
God likes a go-getter.
I think I passed the test.
I mean, everybody there
was really young...
and just out of college...
but I had life experience
and common sense.
I know I passed it.
There is speculation
the explosion was caused...
by a highly combustible
plastic explosive.
Traces of ammonium nitrate
at the site...
led investigators to believe
that Semtex...
or C4 as it's called,
was the cause of the blast.
As of now, no known group...
Hey, Gideon?
Why don't you come on in here
and play a round?
What's the matter with you?
It's just the flu, you know.
You got a fever or what?
No, I don't think so.
Stomach?
I don't know what it is.
Come on, let's get out
of here. Get some air.
Dad, I can't. I'm sick.
I need you to drive
me somewhere.
I better drive you, Dad.
No. I want Gideon to drive.
Dad, where are you going?
Out.
From you?
Just a couple of words?
Nobody's been in contact?
They haven't called you?
Have they called you?
Has anyone--
Shit.
Vultures.
Mrs. Singer?
Mrs. Singer!
Can we talk to you just--
Do you have any information
about your son?
Do you think he's
still alive, Mrs. Singer?
What do you think
Percival's chances are?
Tim O'Neal says he saw
him in the building...
before it was bombed.
Have you heard
that the Marines...
are only recovering
dead bodies now?
Do you have any hope
that he might be alive?
Have they contacted you,
Mrs. Singer?
Fuck off.
Mom!
That's something
they can't say on TV.
Can't do this.
Cannot do this.
Mother! Mom!
Mom, you turned off my alarm!
Why? Why didn't you
wake me up?
I couldn't sleep,
so I was up anyway.
Well, what about my route?
How did you even know
which houses to do?
It was fine.
Look, I needed something
to do, that's all.
Well, so did I!
Did you ever think of that?
No! You are
the most selfish person.
Then clean the garage.
That's something to do.
I don't want to do that!
Ah, that's not
the right something.
I see we're testing
"Mefistofele”...
for its ability to deaden
the auditory nerves.
Tim O'Neal called his mother.
The last time he saw Percival...
Percival was in
the headquarters building.
Well, we can't draw
conclusions from that.
He was in the building
that was bombed.
Not necessarily
at that moment.
Oh, Alfred, if you're going
to keep splitting hairs...
please, you're just...
Yes. Assume the absolute worst.
It's really best for everyone.
It really helps.
So glad I came home!
I'd feel the same way you do.
I'd feel like, "Oh, my God.
He was in that building.”
Did you see the pictures
of the building--
what's left of it?
Yes, on the news.
Percival was always
my most difficult child.
I never seemed to be able
to make him happy.
But then, this past summer
when he came home on leave...
he seemed to have found
some kind of inner peace.
He needed to be away,
do you understand?
So let him not be absent.
Let him be present
at the bombing.
Let him survive it.
And let him get
the strength from that...
to be present
in the rest of his life.
I'm asking too much,
aren't I?
That's what every good
mother would want.
You got to keep
your head down.
Keep low, OK?
Keep a fluid line.
You're crazy, man.
I'm out of here.
What are you
going to do, quit?
No. Never, never
in my entire life...
have I ever quit anything.
Percival is the quitter.
You're mixing up your sons.
I know which son
I got right in front of me.
Yeah, the one you always
screamed and yelled at.
Why me, Dad, huh?
Why was it always me that you
screamed and yelled at...
more than anyone else?
‘Cause it worked.
It made you a winner.
No, you're wrong.
I made myself a winner.
So stop yelling at me.
Mom?
Oh, shoot.
That one could
be better. Sorry.
You're just in time.
Here, you want something?
Try it. It's fun!
You're supposed to send these
to Aunt Charlotte.
She's dead. Just toss it.
That's it.
Not bad.
Score for the Singers!
And he's off!
Ah, ready! On your mark!
Get set!
Go!
The flying Singers!
Let's have it, boys! Yes!
Here's one from Granny Singer!
I hated that!
Good-bye, golf.
Who played golf?
4.0 difficulty...
Hang time was good,
but you failed.
That was a hell of a throw.
And it's up, and it's good!
Mother?
Just a minute, honey.
Mother, I think you should
come inside now.
Just come inside. I think--
We'll clean this up
in the morning.
Izzy, come on.
Just come inside.
We're not going
to clean it up, Alfred!
It took me all day
to get it like this!
There's really a lot to--
Guys, come on!
There's a lot to do inside.
Mother, just--
Try this, Alfred.
I don't want
to throw anything.
to throw anything. Please.
No! It will
make you feel great.
Hey, I feel fine.
I feel fine.
How could you
possibly feel fine?
Obviously I'm the only
one feeling fine here.
Mother, please,
just put it down...
and come inside,
all right?
Please.
OK, Alfred. It's all right.
You go back inside.
We'll take care of this.
Come on, guys!
You know,
I hate when you do that!
I hate when you
assume that you--
What do you think?
That I'm utterly incapable--
Hey, come on!
You know, I--look, I could--
You know, I--
Whoo! Good one!
Hey! Everybody out!
Everybody out of the garage!
Move it! Move it!
Put it down!
Hey, you want to see
something wild?
You started a fire.
Alfred, that's so wonderful.
Sweetheart.
You make me crazy!
But you're going to
have some passion...
in your life after all.
Let's hear it for Alfred!
Oh, it's a beautiful fire.
Identifying the dead
is a tedious process.
So far we've accounted
for 147 dead.
But many of the men weren't
wearing their dog tags.
147.
Is there any hope at all...
that some of the men
are still alive...
beneath all that rubble?
We're operating
under that assumption.
We reached
some warm bodies today...
but the men weren't alive.
Simon, can you turn that off?
Marine spokesman reporting from
the site of the bomb blast...
where hope is fading now
that any more survivors...
Mag, if it's
all right with you...
I'm going to put him upstairs
in Alfred's old room.
Do you want to go upstairs?
Simon, can you give me a hand?
You're going to go
up to Alfred's room.
There you go.
Come here.
Thanks.
Yeah.
I don't know about you guys,
but I could use a drink.
Patrick, can I
get you something?
Mmm...no, thanks.
I'm allergic.
All liquor, Dad?
Yeah, just about.
I'll stick to tea.
I'm just trying to figure out
what it is about you...
that Alfred loves so much.
Maybe he sees you in me
or me in you.
I don't know. Who knows?
Yeah, who knows?
I mean, Patrick's been after
me for twenty-five years...
and I still don't know why.
Twenty-five years. Lucky you.
Lucky me.
And after all these years,
all he has to do...
is put his hand
on my lower back...
touch my neck, and I'm gone.
But gone to a better place.
One might even say,
“transported.”
Is that why
you're with Alfred?
That's one reason.
Let it suffice to say...
he has his father
in him somewhere.
That's really embarrassing.
Let's talk
about something else.
He's very good with my sons.
Another man's sons.
It's too much
responsibility, too soon.
Oh, I think he's having fun
in his Alfred kind of way.
He's rising to the challenge
like you did.
Are you kidding?
I was a lousy mother.
I always forgot
their permission slips.
Their milk money.
Their socks didn't match.
I've yet to have a complete
conversation with any of them.
Well, then who raised
those seven wonderful guys?
I mean, look at them,
every one of them.
They're every one
of them decent, honest.
They all love each other.
And they love you.
That's obvious.
I would be thrilled...
if my boys turned out
like yours.
Somebody did something right.
Who was that?
Patrick played with them a lot.
Well, that's good.
1 did all the boring
maintenance stuff.
I'll bet you did.
You know, today, when I took
my civil-service exam...
I had to describe myself
in fifty words or less.
So I started out.
I wrote down...
“I'm the mother of seven boys."
Yeah, right.
And then I just sat there.
I couldn't think
of anything to say...
for forty-five minutes.
I was sitting there.
And I couldn't--
I'm the mother of seven sons.
That's it. Oh, God!
And that wasn't enough?
Oh, well, I don't--
I always thought...
there'd be something more.
You know, one minute,
I'm hot for Patrick.
And then the next minute,
I'm the mother of seven sons.
What was that something
more that you wanted?
Oh, I don't know.
I mean, I was thirty-five
before I had a dinner...
where I wasn't cutting
somebody else's meat.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe you shouldn't have
had all those kids.
Oh, I can't imagine my life
without any one of my guys.
Honey, it's late.
Mom.
Look.
It was like my feet
didn't even touch the ground.
I didn't even have to try.
I just ran.
For the pure joy of it.
You were doing
what you were meant to do.
I was happy that day.
You were so happy that day.
I remember.
And you were loud.
I was loud.
Yeah.
Turn that damn thing off, Simon.
Hey, we're going to be late.
Come on.
This is the day
we're going to find out.
I'll wait for you downstairs.
See ya.
All right. Come on.
What do you want?
You want to get me?
Simon, run!
Mom!
Go!
Mom! Stop! Get up!
Go! Go!
Mom, stop it!
Mom, stop it. Get up.
Get up, please.
You're going to kill him.
Oh, my God.
This is the third day
in a row, Dad.
I have a theory.
I mean, I think
I've figured it out.
It wouldn't hurt you
to listen, Dad.
I don't want you
to tell anybody...
at home about this.
We'll tell them you fell...
We'll tell them you tripped
on the Swansons' lawn.
All right. You know
where that big rock is?
That's why you're so dirty...
because the lawn
was really muddy.
Maybe we could even say that
they left the hose running.
They'll believe us.
Sure.
People forget things
like that all the time.
I could have killed that dog.
Mom...
you saved my life.
Maybe.
No, you...
You did.
You're great, Mom.
Sit down, Dad. Here.
I can see that you're not
too fired up about my theory...
but you're going
to hear it anyway.
I've had it
with the theories.
Will you just hear me
out on this, please?
I think the blindness...
is an allergic reaction
to the cat...
and all the tea
you've been drinking.
Could I have my tea, please?
Izzy, try again.
Dad, go with me on this, OK?
The first day I got here,
you were blind.
Did you drink any
tea that morning?
I don't know.
What is this?
Give me my tea! Jesus!
I saw Mom throw Lucy out...
and then, minutes later,
after you talked to Gideon...
your sight started
coming back, remember?
And yesterday,
the cat was around.
And at first,
you were all right.
But then you drank tea
and looked at the paper...
And you went blind.
Later, you went upstairs
to take a shower...
which probably washed
some of the dander off...
and you could see again.
I was right there.
Dad, think about it.
What's the first thing
you do in the morning?
You drink tea!
And you drank a cup
of tea last night...
right before
you went to bed.
Do you remember?
You said,
“I'm allergic to liquor...
"and I should probably
stick to tea.”
Then you spent
the night with the cat.
And here you are.
Have you lost your mind? Huh?
Did you even have one
allergic blind attack...
when you were sleeping
at your office--
your office
without the cat? Huh?
I don't know.
I don't know. Maybe not.
Wow.
But if it's so simple...
how come the doctors
missed it?
They missed it because
it takes both components...
to trigger the reaction.
Look, I must have read
seven thousand articles...
about allergies
this past year, all right?
I probably know more
about allergies...
than anyone else
in the country.
Allergy expert.
I mean,
it can be totally bizarre.
There was a case of a guy...
who broke out in hives
if he was around dogs...
but only if he ate
tuna fish first.
Aha! Tuna fish.
Tuna fish.
Dad, people can be
allergic to each other.
That's for sure.
Have you tried
cutting out tea?
Dad, what have
you got to lose?
Just go shower
the cat fur off.
Dad, we have solved it.
Well...
I guess I'm not getting
any tea, right?
All right.
I'll try your shower.
Whatever's right.
You know,
Percival's not dead.
I know he's not.
All right.
I'll take the cat.
You two vacuum
everything off...
and let's see
what happens.
It looks like
it's supposed to.
Oh, I tripped on, um...
the Swansons' lawn.
They left
their hose running...
and on a rock...
and then
a great big rock, and...
I tripped.
Jesus, Izzy.
Izzy's an amazing kid,
you know?
I think he might have just
figured this whole thing out...
with my eyes.
He kept watching me,
making notes...
following me around.
I thought he was going
to drive me crazy.
He loves you.
He was determined.
Wouldn't give it up.
Singers never give up.
Well, that's not such
a bad thing, is it?
What happened to you?
Patrick.
What happened?
Is...is that why
we're still together?
After all these years and
all the fighting, is that...
because we can't give up?
I just...
I just don't think
I can live without you.
Patrick, I...
I won't be able
to stand it if he's dead.
What is all this stuff?
This stuff.
I like you when
you're naked, you know.
Why?
Do you know that?
Because you look more naked
than other women somehow.
You know?
Hey, all you Singers back home.
This is me and my buddies...
bringing you greetings
from the Sinai.
This is Kevin
from Rocky River, Ohio.
And this is Tommy
from Folsom, California.
You know, where the prison is.
Don't worry, guys.
He's never been in it
or anything...
but he's given me this t-shirt.
It says "Folsom Prison"
right across the front...
with a number on it.
Cool, huh, Simon?
I'm saving it for you, dude.
We'd like to give you
a panorama view...
of my home away from home...
the lovely countryside
in this resort community.
Yes, that's right, folks.
Sand, sand, and more sand
as far as the eye can see.
We even have palm trees
in the desert, right?
No. Just sand and heat.
And it gets over a hundred
practically every day.
Actually,
it's pretty boring here.
Hi, Mom. I miss you.
Hey, Dad.
Hi, Beth.
Any word yet?
No. We'll let you know.
Don't worry. They're
treating me pretty well here.
There's not a whole lot to do.
So it's given me
some time to think.
Sort some of the things out
about my life and stuff.
Mom, Dad, the phone!
Hurry up!
Yes, this is she.
Percival?
Percy!
Is he all right?
Mom, is he all right?
Oh, Percy!
Percival! It's Percy!
Where was he?
Trapped in that building?
...Sylvester Stallones
and "Lethal Weapons."
I think they're trying
to tell us something--
trying to make us
into heroes or something.
Hey, Mom, what they don't know
is I'm already a hero.
I grew up in the Singer family
and lived to tell about it.
If you want to be brave
Reach for the top of the sky
And the farthest point
On the horizon
Do you know
who you'll meet there?
Great soldiers and seafarers,
artists and dreamers
Who need to be close
Close to the light
They need to be
In danger of burning by fire
And I
I want to get there
I want to be one
One who is touched by the sun
Often I want to walk
The safe side of the street
And lull myself to sleep
End all my pain
Oh
Deep down inside I know
I've got to
Learn from the greats
Earn my right to be living
Let my wings of desire
Soar over the night
I need to let them say
She must have been mad
And I
I want to get there
I want to be one
One who is touched by the sun