LOOK AT ALL THIS STUFF.
THIS PLACE IS THE BOMB.
THE BOMB?
YEAH, THE BOMB.
REMINDIN' ME OF THE '60s.
YEAH, I KNOW,
WHEN YOU WERE A FLOWER CHILD--
HIPPIE, FREE LOVE.
WHO TOLD YOU ABOUT THAT?
COME ON, DAD,
I HEAR YOU AND MOM
TALK ABOUT THE GOOD OLD DAYS
ALL THE TIME--
ALL THAT CRAZY STUFF
YOU GUYS DID IN SCHOOL.
THANK YOU.
AND YOU THINK WE'RE STRANGE.
[laughs]
THANK YOU.
HEY, YOU THINK YOUR MOM
WOULD LIKE THAT?
DEFINITELY.
IT'S VERY COOL.
YEAH, I AGREE.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON
DOWN THERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
[music playing]
LET'S GO SEE.
HEY, DAD,
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
WELL, NOW THAT ALL DEPENDS.
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE
ABOUT WOMEN AND FREE LOVE?
I AIN'T GOING FOR IT,
YOU KNOW.
NO, NOT ABOUT THAT.
WHAT?
IT'S ABOUT GRANDPA.
HOW COME YOU WOULDN'T
TAKE HIS CALL THE OTHER DAY?
WELL, I TELL YOU,
ME AND MY FATHER,
YOU KNOW, WE WERE NEVER
REALLY THAT CLOSE.
WE NEVER DID TALK
THAT MUCH.
BUT--
THAT'S THE WAY IT IS.
THAT'S THE WAY
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN.
BUT HE'S YOUR DAD.
CAN'T YOU JUST, YOU KNOW,
KISS AND MAKE UP?
I DON'T THINK SO.
YOU KNOW, IT'S HARD
TO EXPLAIN.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE
YOU'VE GOT TO WALK
IN ANOTHER MAN'S SHOES
IN ORDER TO UNDERSTAND
HOW HE FEELS.
[laughing]
[chittering]
THERE'S A QUARTER.
GIVE IT TO THE MONKEY.
[Woman]
AW, THAT'S SO SWEET.
AW!
AW, JUST WAIT A MINUTE.
JUST WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT A MINUTE HERE.
HEY!
NO, WAIT A MINUTE. WAIT.
HEY, GET BACK HERE!
NO NO, FORGET IT.
NO WAY!
THAT'S A LOT OF MONEY.
HEY!
CLAY!
[coughing]
THIS IS TIGHT.
IT LOOKS LIKE SOME KIND
OF WEIRD MUSEUM.
HEY. HEY HEY.
YOU LIKE THESE?
THESE OLD POSTCARDS--
YOU KNOW THEY CARRY DREAMS.
[Woman]
WHO LET YOU IN?
CAN I HELP YOU?
WELL, UH...
UH, WE WERE JUST WONDERING
IF THESE POSTCARDS
WERE FOR SALE.
NO, NOTHING'S FOR SALE.
RIGHT.
THIS IS
MY PRIVATE COLLECTION,
GIFTS I RECEIVED IN MY TRAVELS
TO FAR-OFF PLACES.
AND NO, I DON'T DO FORTUNES.
THIS IS WHACK.
YEAH, WE IN THE WRONG PLACE.
COME ON.
OH, NO.
YOU'RE IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
FOLLOW ME, OVER HERE.
I HAVE THE EXACT THING
FOR YOU.
TRY THESE ON FOR SIZE.
THEY'LL MAKE YOU FEEL
LIKE A NEW MAN.
NO, THANK YOU.
I DON'T REALLY NEED
ANOTHER PAIR OF SHOES.
THESE AREN'T JUST
TAKE THEM.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
CONSIDER THEM A GIFT
IN EXCHANGE FOR THE KINDNESS
YOU SHOWED LAZLO.
WHO'S LAZLO?
[chittering]
YOU KNOW THESE PEOPLE,
DON'T YOU?
[coughing]
ARE YOU GOING TO WEAR
THOSE SHOES TO WORK TOMORROW?
I DON'T THINK I'LL BE GOING
TO WORK TOMORROW.
I'LL STAY HOME WITH YOU.
NO, YOU'VE ALREADY
MISSED ENOUGH SCHOOL
TAKING CARE OF ME.
THEN WHAT'S ANOTHER DAY?
WE'LL SEE.
[breathing heavily]
[classical music playing]
[music stops]
MMM.
[Girl] HI, DADDY.
HEY.
LOOK WHAT WE'RE DOING.
OOH, THAT SURE SMELLS GOOD.
MM-HMM.
DON'T TOUCH THEM.
THEY'RE FOR MY BAKE SALE.
MMM.
THANKS FOR THE COOKIES.
SLOW DOWN, SLOW DOWN, KIDS.
SLOW DOWN, GUYS.
SLOW DOWN.
[Girl]
GET BACK HERE!
IF WE COULD JUST HARNESS
THAT ENERGY,
WE'D PUT THE POWER COMPANY
OUT OF BUSINESS, HUH?
MWAH.
YOU LOOK TIRED.
EH.
WORE YOURSELF OUT,
DIDN'T YOU?
NOTHING THAT A FEW VITAMINS
AND AN HERBAL DRINK
WOULDN'T FIX.
PLUS A FEW OF THESE.
UH-NUH.
BAKE SALE.
WELL.
WHAT'S THIS?
NEW SHOES?
ME AND YOUR SON,
YOU KNOW, WE WENT
TREASURE HUNTING
AND GOT SOMETHING
VERY SPECIAL
FOR A VERY SPECIAL PERSON.
OH, FRANK,
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
FOR A VERY BEAUTIFUL LADY.
HEY, DAD,
I'M OFF TO PETER'S HOUSE.
HE'S GONNA HELP ME
WITH ME MATH.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
PETER GOT A 65 ON HIS LAST
MATH TEST.
HE DID.
AND I GOT A 44. SEE YA.
GOT IT.
OFF TO ANOTHER MEETING
OF THE MATHEMATICALLY
CHALLENGED.
HE WANTS TO STAY HOME
WITH YOU TOMORROW.
I KNOW.
HONEY, I'M A LITTLE WORRIED
ABOUT CLAY.
HE'S REALLY TAKING THIS HARD.
HE SHOULD BE OUT
MAKING NEW FRIENDS,
PLAYING BALL,
GETTING INTO TROUBLE,
THE WAY YOU USED TO
AT HIS AGE.
OH, MAYBE NOT THAT MUCH,
BUT SOME.
I'LL TALK TO HIM.
WAIT WAIT WAIT.
WHEN DID I
GET INTO TROUBLE?
HMM? HUH?
[laughs]
WHILE WE'RE ON THE SUBJECT
OF TALKING,
WHAT ABOUT YOUR PARENTS?
ARE YOU EVER GONNA MAKE PEACE
WITH THEM?
TIME FOR BED.
[makes creaking
sound]
[laughs]
THERE YOU GO.
DADDY?
YEAH?
CAN YOU SING ME
MY SPECIAL LULLABY?
OKAY.
♪ GOOD NIGHT,
CLOSE YOUR EYES ♪
♪ AND DREAM AWAY ♪
♪ TOMORROW
IS A BRAND-NEW WORLD ♪
♪ IT IS A BRAND-NEW DAY ♪
♪ AND SOMEWHERE
DOWN THE ROAD ♪
♪ SOMEDAY YOU MAY RECALL ♪
♪ THIS LULLABY I SING TO YOU ♪
♪ TONIGHT ♪
♪ AND I'LL BE WITH YOU ♪
♪ EVERY TIME YOU DO ♪
♪ GOOD NIGHT ♪
♪ HOPE YOUR DREAMS
WILL ALL COME TRUE ♪
♪ SO MANY YEARS AHEAD ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOOK FORWARD TO ♪
♪ AND SOMEWHERE DOWN THE ROAD ♪
♪ SOME QUIET PLACE
AND TIME ♪
♪ THIS LITTLE LULLABY ♪
♪ MAY CROSS YOUR MIND ♪
♪ AND I'LL BE WITH YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I AM TONIGHT ♪
♪ GOOD NIGHT. ♪
GOOD NIGHT, BABY.
GOOD NIGHT, DADDY.
I LOVE YOU, DADDY.
I LOVE YOU TOO, BABY.
[jazz playing]
[Clay's voice]
IT'S ABOUT GRANDPA.
HOW COME YOU WOULDN'T
TAKE HIS CALL THE OTHER DAY?
[dialing]
[hangs up]
[chattering]
[Clay]
IF MY DAD FINDS OUT,
HE'S PROBABLY GOING TO KILL ME.
[Peter]
YOU GUYS WANT TO GO
TO THE BUTTHOLE SURFERS CONCERT?
YOU NUTS, MAN?
THEY'RE THE FINEST GIRLS
IN SCHOOL.
BESIDES, THEY'RE SO STUCK UP,
THEY'RE NOSE BLEEDS BECAUSE
OF THE ALTITUDE.
JUST FORGET IT.
I GOTTA TELL YOU, MAN,
WHEN IT COMES TO BABES,
YOU ARE TOO LAME.
YEAH YEAH, WHATEVER.
LET'S GO TO THE MALL.
I BETTER NOT.
MY DAD STAYED HOME
FROM WORK TODAY.
IS HE OKAY?
OH, SURE, HE'S GREAT.
IT'S JUST THAT, YOU KNOW,
HE NEEDS A LITTLE EXTRA REST.
COOL.
WELL, CALL YOU TOMORROW, MAN.
PEACE OUT, MAN.
YEAH.
HEY, DAD, I'M HOME.
DAD?
[snoring]
[woman speaking over P.A.,
indistinct]
CLAY, HONEY?
I'M GONNA GET US
SOME DINNER, ALL RIGHT?
CLAY?
HI.
MOM WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
MAGGIE AND AUNT CELESTE
WILL BE HERE SOON.
HOW YOU FEELIN'?
KINDA LIKE I'M--
I'M KNOCKING ON HEAVEN'S DOOR.
SEE, A JOKE.
YOU'RE GETTING BETTER ALREADY.
YOU'RE GONNA
LICK THIS THING, DAD.
I JUST KNOW IT.
HEY, MOSES,
THERE'S SOMETHING I--
SOMETHING I GOTTA TELL YOU
THAT I NEVER TOLD ANYBODY
BEFORE.
IT'S OKAY.
SAVE YOUR STRENGTH.
WHEN I WAS A LITTLE BOY,
MY MOTHER USED TO...
HAVE THIS POSTCARD COLLECTION.
MY FAVORITE
WAS THIS PAINTING
OF THIS GOLF COURSE.
THIS WAS THIS--
THIS HUGE COUNTRY CLUB.
IT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
I WANTED TO GO THERE.
DAD-- DAD, YOU SHOULD REST.
MOM WILL BE BACK
ANY MINUTE.
AND I WAS DREAMING
THAT THAT GOLF COURSE
WAS HEAVEN.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
THEY WOULDN'T LET ME IN.
[laughs, coughs]
DAD, DON'T.
CLAY?
YOU GOTTA PROMISE ME
SOMETHING.
SURE, ANYTHING.
ME AND MY FATHER,
WE WEREN'T VERY CLOSE.
YOU GOTTA TELL
YOUR GRANDMAMA
AND-- AND YOUR GRANDPAPA
I ALWAYS LOVED THEM.
FIND THAT POSTCARD FOR ME.
IT'LL HELP YOU UNDERSTAND
OUR FAMILY.
PROMISE.
HMM?
I PROMISE.
[exhales]
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
[classical music playing]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH DAD'S STUFF?
JUST FOLDING,
GETTING THINGS ORGANIZED.
YOU'RE GIVING IT AWAY,
AREN'T YOU?
NO NO, HONEY.
THESE ARE ALL GOING RIGHT BACK
WHERE THEY BELONG.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO MISSES HIM.
THEN WHY ARE YOU PLAYING
THIS MUSIC HE HATED?
YOU THINK JUST BECAUSE
HE'S GONE, YOU CAN DO
ANYTHING YOU LIKE.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY
YOU DIDN'T FIGHT HARD ENOUGH
TO GET HIM OFF
THOSE STUPID HERBS AND VITAMINS
INSTEAD OF TAKING REAL MEDICINE
AND DOING THE JOB--
FOR YOUR INFORMATION,
IN MANY COUNTRIES
THAT STUPID STUFF
IS REAL MEDICINE.
DON'T FORGET
THAT KEPT HIM ALIVE
FOR MORE THAN SIX YEARS.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
CHEMO WOULDN'T HAVE WORKED
AND KEPT HIM ALIVE FOREVER?
I DON'T.
THAT'S A GREAT ANSWER.
I'LL HANDLE THESE SHIRTS!
I HATE THIS!
CLAY.
[door slams]
HERE YOU GO.
MOM, I NEED ONE MORE.
MAGGIE, THERE ARE
ONLY THREE OF US.
WHAT IF DADDY'S SPIRIT
IS HUNGRY AND COMES BACK?
GOOD THINKING.
[sobbing]
[Clay sobbing]
[knocking]
CLAY, HONEY?
DINNER'S READY.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
EAT SOMETHING.
I'M NOT HUNGRY.
I KNOW YOU'RE ANGRY
THAT YOUR DAD LEFT YOU.
WHILE YOU'RE IN THERE,
JUST TAKE SOME TIME
TO THINK ABOUT
WHAT HE LEFT YOU.
IT'LL MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
[Frank's voice]
CLAY, SOMETIMES
YOU HAVE TO WALK
IN ANOTHER MAN'S SHOES
TO UNDERSTAND HIM.
[gasps]
MAN, WHAT'S GOING ON?
[wind howling]
OH!
[children laughing]
THERE YOU GO, SON.
WHO'S NEXT?
COME ON.
[sound distorted]
[laughter continues]
[cash register dings]
35¢.
[woman laughing]
[music playing]
[roller coaster sounds]
[all laughing]
[Boy] WAY TO GO, FRANK.
WHERE AM I?
WHY ARE YOU JUST STANDING THERE
LIKE A JERK?
CLEAN IT UP, FRANK.
HURRY UP AND CLEAN THIS MESS
BEFORE WE GET A DETENTION.
FRANK?
MY NAME'S CLAY.
FRANK IS MY FATHER.
SORRY, I THOUGHT
YOUR OLD MAN'S NAME WAS RICHARD?
WHO ARE YOU?
HELLO, WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS,
TELEGRAM AND BRUCE.
DID YOU GET BEANED
BY THE TETHER BALL
OR SOMETHING?
OOH!
LET'S GO, MAN.
COME ON.
OH!
HOME FOR MY ROVER.
[Telegram]
SO I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DROPPED YOUR TRAY
IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE CAFETERIA.
I KNOW.
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN
SO EMBARRASSING.
THEN THE CAFETERIA LADY
GOT ALL MAD AT YOU.
LET'S SPLIT.
IT'S SORT OF GETTING
KIND OF DARK IN HERE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
YEAH, MAYBE THE OREO TRIPLETS
WANT TO BE LEFT ALONE.
MOVE IT, BOZOS.
UGH!
WHAT A BUNCH OF PECKERWOODS.
WHAT'S THEIR PROBLEM?
US, MAN.
YOU KNOW THAT.
SO, BRUCE, GOT A DATE
FOR THE DANCE YET?
NO, I THINK I'LL GO ALONE.
YOU KNOW, PLAY THE FIELD,
CHECK OUT THE ACTION
WHEN I GET THERE. YOU?
NO, NOT YET.
GOT ANY IDEAS?
HOW ABOUT LISA CALMENARI?
HUH?
[Bruce]
HEY, FRANK, HOW ABOUT YOU?
ARE YOU TAKING
MARY LOU?
FRANK?
DAD.
[vomits]
ARE YOU OKAY, FRANK?
WHAT'S GOT INTO HIM?
[bell ringing]
HEY, FRANK.
HEY, DID YOU HEAR
THAT AT A PARTY LAST WEEK,
FRANK ASKED SOME GIRL OUT
AND SHE SLAPPED HIM IN THE FACE?
YOU'RE IN MY SEAT, DORK.
OH, SORRY.
CLASS.
CLASS, SETTLE DOWN, PLEASE.
SETTLE DOWN, CLASS.
THANK YOU.
TODAY IS CURRENT EVENTS DAY.
I HOPE YOU'VE ALL
BEEN READING YOUR NEWSPAPERS.
[all groaning]
I CANNOT UNDERSTAND
THIS LACK OF INTEREST
IN CURRENT AFFAIRS.
YOU THINK IF IT'S HAPPENING
TODAY, IT'S NOT HISTORY?
FRANK, WHY DON'T YOU BEGIN?
PSST, THAT'S YOU, MAN.
GET UP THERE.
COME ALONG, FRANK.
GO ON.
ANNOUNCE YOUR TOPIC,
FRANK.
PRESIDENT KENNEDY
AND CUBA.
AH. GO ON.
I GUESS IT ALL STARTED
WITH THE BAY-OF-PIGS INVASION
WHEN THE C.I.A.
TRIED TO KILL CASTRO.
CASTRO THREATENED
TO GET EVEN.
LEE HARVEY OSWALD
WAS A CASTRO SUPPORTER.
HE VISITED THE CUBAN EMBASSY
IN MEXICO CITY
TWO MONTHS BEFORE
HE STARTED WORKING
AT THE TEXAS SCHOOL
BOOK DEPOSITORY IN DALLAS.
FROM A WINDOW THERE,
HE SHOT KENNEDY.
[All]
WHAT? WHAT?
FRANK CROSBY,
I HAVE SPOKEN TO YOU BEFORE
ABOUT YOUR BEHAVIOR IN CLASS,
BUT THIS TIME YOU HAVE GONE
ENTIRELY TOO FAR.
PRESIDENT KENNEDY IS CARRYING
A VERY BIG LOAD
FOR SUCH A YOUNG MAN.
HE IS TRYING TO DO MORE
THAN ANY PRESIDENT
HAS EVER DONE.
NOW...
I EXPECT
A FIVE-MINUTE ORAL REPORT
FROM YOU TOMORROW...
[all laughing]
...ON HIS PROGRAMS
AND POLICIES.
BUSTED.
♪ Ba ba ba
ba Barbara Ann ♪
♪ Barbara Ann ♪
- ♪ Take my hand ♪
- ♪ Ba ba ba, ba Barbara Ann ♪
♪ Barbara Ann ♪
♪ You got me rockin'
and a'rollin' ♪
♪ ROCKIN' AND A'REELIN',
BARBARA ANN ♪
♪ Barbara Ann ♪
♪ I WENT TO A DANCE ♪
♪ LOOKIN' FOR ROMANCE ♪
♪ SAW BARBARA ANN
SO I... ♪
♪ THOUGHT I'D TAKE A CHANCE! ♪
YEAH!
♪ Take my hand, oh,
Barbara Ann, Barbara Ann ♪
♪ TAKE MY HAND,
YOU GOT ME ROCKIN'
AND A ROLLIN' ♪
♪ ROCKIN' AND A'REELIN',
BARBARA ANN ♪
♪ BA BA BA
[Both]
BA BARBARA ANN ♪
♪ BA BA BA
♪ Barbara Ann... ♪
THAT WAY?
YEAH.
♪ BARBARA ANN ♪
♪ YOU GOT ME ROCKIN'
AND A'ROLLIN' ♪
♪ ROCKIN' AND A'REELIN',
BARBARA ANN... ♪
[song continues]
[Telegram]
LATER, FRANK.
YEAH,
THANKS FOR THE RIDE.
HEY, DON'T THANK ME.
THANK MY BROTHER
AND HIS BEAUTIFUL CAR!
[D.J.]
Yeah!
[Telegram]
LET'S HIT THE HIGHWAY!
[music fades]
[Woman]
FRANK CROSBY,
YOU GET IN HERE!
[horn honking]
FRANK!
IT'S OPEN
FOR GOODNESS SAKE.
GO CHANGE
INTO YOUR PLAY CLOTHES
AND COME HELP ME
MOVE THESE BASKETS
BY THE FRONT DOOR
SO THE LADIES
CAN PICK UP THEIR IRONING.
HELLO, GRANDMA.
GRANDMA?
MOM-- I MEANT MOM.
IT'S TRUE, THOUGH.
THE OLDER I GET,
THE MORE I LOOK LIKE MY MOTHER,
DON'T I, FRANK, HUH?
FRANK, YOU'RE AWFULLY QUIET.
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TODAY?
UH, NOTHING SPECIAL.
JUST THE USUAL STUFF.
IT'S JUST--
HEY, GRANDMA?
MOM-- IS THAT
A NEW POSTCARD?
IT SURE IS.
IT'S FROM--
CAN I SEE IT?
NOW SINCE WHEN HAVE YOU
BEEN SO INTERESTED
IN MY POSTCARDS?
[Richard]
IS THAT BOY BACK
FROM SCHOOL YET?
UH, UPSTAIRS
AND CHANGE YOUR CLOTHES
BEFORE YOU HELP YOUR FATHER.
MEANWHILE I'LL MAKE YOU
A MALTED WITH AN EGG IN IT.
GO ON NOW.
SCOOT.
[Clay thinking]
WOW.
COOL.
DAD, YOUR ROOM
IS SO UNREAL.
DAD, YOU GOT
A LOT OF STUFF.
YOU COLLECTED
A LOT OF JUNK.
LOOK AT THIS OLD THING.
BASEBALL CARDS?
MICKEY MANTLE? WOW.
[Richard]
FRANK, GET DOWN HERE NOW.
[panting]
WHOA!
MAN, I MUST BE DREAMING.
THAT CAN'T BE REAL.
I KNOW IT WASN'T REAL.
I'M DREAMING.
WELL, THAT WAS QUICK.
WHAT WAS QUICK?
YOU CHANGING YOUR MIND.
ONLY A MINUTE AGO YOU SAID
YOU WEREN'T HUNGRY.
[Maggie]
MOM, I'M OUT OF THE SHOWER!
IN A SECOND.
CAN YOU DO THIS?
IS SOMEONE COMING
FOR DINNER?
OH, MAGGIE SET IT
FOR DADDY.
[Maggie]
I NEED A TOWEL!
HERE I COME!
[Maggie]
I'LL PLAY WITH YOU TOMORROW,
I PROMISE.
BUT NOW IT'S TIME
TO GO TO BED.
YOU ALL IN?
HERE.
RIGHT.
IF YOU COULD BE ANY ANIMAL,
WHAT WOULD YOU BE?
UH, I DON'T KNOW.
I ASKED YOU FIRST.
OKAY.
I WOULD BE A LION,
QUEEN OF THE JUNGLE.
THAT WAY
NOTHING COULD HURT ME.
I'D BE A BIRD
SO I COULD FLY TO HEAVEN
AND VISIT DADDY.
GO TO SLEEP.
YOU'VE GOT SCHOOL
IN THE MORNING.
[Frank's voice]
♪ This lullaby I sing to you ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ And I'll be with you ♪
♪ Every time you do ♪
♪ Good night ♪
♪ Hope your dreams
will all come true ♪
♪ So many years ahead ♪
♪ You can look forward to ♪
♪ And somewhere
down the road ♪
♪ Some quiet place
and time ♪
♪ This little lullaby ♪
♪ May cross your mind ♪
♪ And I'll be with you ♪
♪ Like I am tonight ♪
[singing along]
♪ GOOD NIGHT. ♪
[door closes]
CLAY, ARE YOU STILL UP?
[knock on door]
GOOD NIGHT, HONEY.
I'M NOT LETTING YOU GUYS
OUT OF MY SIGHT.
HEY.
WHAT'S JAMMED IN YOUR BAG?
IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S GONNA EXPLODE.
STUFF.
WHAT KIND OF STUFF?
JUST STUFF.
LIKE WHAT?
SHOES.
SHOES?
YEAH, MY FATHER'S SHOES.
NEXT YOU'LL BE TELLING ME
YOUR FATHER'S ASHES
ARE IN THERE.
WHY WOULD I CARRY
MY FATHER'S ASHES AROUND?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHY WOULD YOU CARRY
YOUR FATHER'S SHOES AROUND?
BECAUSE I WANT TO, OKAY?
LIKE WHEN MY GRANDFATHER DIED,
MY GRANDMOTHER CARRIED
HIS FALSE TEETH AROUND
TILL SHE KICKED
THE BUCKET TOO.
HELLO?
JAN!
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
GREAT TO SEE YOU.
HOW YOU DOING?
OKAY, I GUESS.
WELL, COME AND SIT DOWN.
I WAS JUST GOING OVER
THE GUEST LIST FOR
TOMORROW'S SHOW.
DID YOU REDECORATE AGAIN?
YES, I DID.
[laughs]
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, IT'S GREAT,
IT'S JUST THAT ISN'T THIS
THE THIRD TIME THIS YEAR?
WELL, YOU KNOW I HAVE TROUBLE
MAKING UP MY MIND.
WHY DO YOU THINK I'VE
BEEN MARRIED SO MANY TIMES?
NOW TELL ME ABOUT
MY NIECE AND NEPHEW.
HOW ARE THEY DOING?
CLAY IS ALL CONFUSED
AND ANGRY
WITH NO WAY TO LET GO
OF WHAT HE'S FEELING.
AND MAGGIE--
OH, CELESTE,
HOW AM I GOING
TO GET THOSE KIDS THROUGH
THE REST OF THEIR LIVES?
HOW AM I GOING
TO GET MYSELF THROUGH?
JAN, MAYBE YOU SHOULD TALK
TO A THERAPIST.
IT HELPS.
TAKE IT FROM ME.
I BET I'VE SEEN
MORE COUCHES IN MY LIFE
THAN A FURNITURE SALESMAN.
[sighs]
I'M TOO TIRED FOR THAT.
I'M TIRED OF BEING BRAVE
AND I'M TIRED
OF BEING RESPONSIBLE.
I JUST FEEL SO ALL ALONE.
IT'S LIKE THE INSIDES
HAVE BEEN SUCKED OUT OF ME.
I KNOW.
I KNOW FRANK
WAS THE MOST...
SPECIAL PERSON
IN MY LIFE TOO.
WELL, YOU KNOW
THAT IF YOU NEED ANYTHING--
YOU OR THE KIDS--
HERE.
AND WE'RE OKAY,
HONESTLY.
I JUST GOT SOMETHING
IN MY EYE.
YEAH, TEARS.
[both laughing]
COME ON, DAD,
WHERE'S THAT POSTCARD?
OKAY, SHOES,
HERE WE GO.
HEY, DAD,
REMEMBER WHEN YOU HELPED ME
WITH MY PASSING GAME?
"CLAY CROSBY
THREW 264 YARDS
AND FOUR TOUCHDOWNS
AS CAROLLA HIGH
WENT ON TO WIN
THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP!"
[hissing]
"TOUCHDOWN!"
OH, YEAH,
THE LACES.
MMM!
[whistle blowing]
HERE GOES.
ONE STEAM BOAT!
THROW IT, FRANK.
TWO STEAMBOATS!
THROW IT.
MURDER HIM!
[all cheering]
FRANK, OVER HERE!
[Telegram]
LOOK OUT, HERE THEY COME!
THROW IT!
AHH!
OOH!
TIGHT.
I CAN CONTROL THEM.
POSTCARD, HERE WE COME.
[knock on door]
LIGHTS OUT, CLAY.
IT'S GETTING LATE.
I JUST HAVE TO FINISH
MY MYTHOLOGY HOMEWORK.
MMM!
[Clay's voice]
OKAY, POSTCARD.
LOOK FOR IT.
MAN.
ALL RIGHT, CONCENTRATE.
WHERE COULD IT BE?
UH-OH, BUSTED.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
DOWN THERE?
I'VE GOT SUCH A SPAZ
FOR A LITTLE BROTHER,
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
IT'S TIME FOR YOUR DANCE LESSON
SO YOU WON'T BE TOTALLY PATHETIC
AT THE STARLIGHT BALL TONIGHT.
I-- I CAN DANCE.
SEE?
BREAK IT DOWN!
BREAK IT DOWN, BREAK IT DOWN.
VERY POPULAR.
WITH WHO, RETARDS?
OKAY, NOW...
STAND WITH YOUR FEET
A LITTLE APART
AND BEND YOUR KNEES
AND PUT YOUR WEIGHT
ON YOUR RIGHT FOOT.
♪ Come on, baby... ♪
AND TWIST YOUR LEFT FOOT
LIKE YOU'RE GRINDING OUT
A CIGARETTE.
♪ Let's do the Twist... ♪
I'LL TAKE THAT.
NO!
NO! FRANK.
NOT MY CIGARETTE.
YOU'LL THANK ME IN LIFE LATER.
THOSE THINGS CAN KILL YOU.
WHAT'S KILLING ME
IS GOING TO JUNIOR COLLEGE
AND HAVING TO LIVE
IN THIS HOUSE.
WHAT'S KILLING ME
ARE THOSE MALTEDS AFTER SCHOOL
AND LOOKING AT GRANDMA'S POST--
MOM'S POSTCARDS.
ISN'T IT CRAZY THE WAY
SHE KEEPS THEM IN THE--
FRANK, JUST SHUT UP
AND TWIST YOUR PITIFUL
LITTLE BODY.
GOOD.
NOW SWITCH FEET.
[record scratches]
[gasps]
SORRY.
IF YOU SCRATCHED THE RECORD,
YOU'RE GONNA BUY ME A NEW ONE.
[sighs]
OKAY.
I'M GONNA START AGAIN,
AND THIS TIME
STAY OVER THERE...
[laughs]
AND JUST MOVE
TO THE MUSIC.
JUST PRETEND YOU'RE
IN THE PEPPERMINT LOUNGE.
OKAY.
[record starts]
YEAH.
[laughs]
[both singing]
♪ COME ON, BABY ♪
♪ LET'S DO THE TWIST ♪
♪ YEAH, COME ON, BABY ♪
♪ LET'S DO THE TWIST... ♪
HOO HOO.
♪ TAKE ME BY MY LITTLE HAND ♪
♪ MY LITTLE HAND ♪
♪ AND GO LIKE THIS ♪
♪ YEAH, TWIST... ♪
NOW KEEP 'EM TOGETHER.
♪ TWIST ♪
♪ OOH HOO YEAH... ♪
OH!
[Richard]
HEY, YOU KIDS!
TURN THAT LOUSY MUSIC OFF
AND DO YOUR HOMEWORK.
SHH!
♪ GO LIKE THIS ♪
♪ AND DO THE TWIST ♪
♪ OH YEAH, AND TWIST ♪
♪ OOH,
YOU SHOULD SEE MY ♪
♪ MY BIG SIS ♪
♪ SHE REALLY KNOWS
HOW TO ROCK ♪
♪ AND KNOWS HOW TO TWIST ♪
♪ And do the Twist... ♪
[Celeste]
FRANK, WHAT'S HER NAME?
NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
WHAT'S HER NAME?
IS SHE IN YOUR CLASS?
MAYBE.
MAYBE?
IS SHE PRETTY?
STOP ASKING ME
SO MANY QUESTIONS.
PASS THIS TO YOUR FATHER.
JUST ONCE I'D KIND OF
LIKE TO HAVE MEAT ON FRIDAY
INSTEAD OF CASSEROLE.
I MADE APPLE BROWN BETTY
FOR DESSERT--
DINAH SHORE'S RECIPE.
I FOUND IT
IN THAT LIFE MAGAZINE,
THE ONE WITH THE PICTURE
OF THE TROOPS AT THE UNIVERSITY
OF MISSISSIPPI.
THAT JAMES MEREDITH
SURE OPENED A CAN OF WORMS.
JAMES MEREDITH?
YEAH,
THAT'S THAT COLORED BOY
LIKES TO HANG OUT
WITH WHITE FOLKS, LIKE YOU.
COLORED BOY?
THERE AN ECHO IN HERE?
YEAH, WELL, ALL THIS TALK
ABOUT INTEGRATION--
YOUNG FOLKS ARE RUNNING AROUND
SPLITTING THE WORLD WIDE OPEN.
PEOPLE ARE CHANGING.
NEGROES ARE CITIZENS
AND JUST WANT THE SAME FREEDOM
AND EQUALITY AS WHITES.
NEGROES?
ZIP IT, THE BOTH OF YOU.
DADDY, CAN I BORROW
THE CAR?
I HAVE TO GET FRANK
TO THE DANCE AND THEN
I HAVE PLAY REHEARSAL.
[sighs]
ALL RIGHT.
THE TANK IS EMPTY,
SO YOU AND YOUR BROTHER
IS GONNA HAVE TO PAY FOR IT.
ALL RIGHT.
DON'T YOU CHANGE
THAT RADIO STATION.
I WON'T.
LET'S GO.
YEAH.
NOW YOU'RE SURELY NOT GOING
IN THEM DIRTY OLD SNEAKERS.
TAKE THEM OFF AND GO
PUT ON YOUR JARMANS.
AW, MA, THERE'S NO TIME.
WE'RE ALREADY LATE.
GO. GO.
WE'LL SEE YA.
IS THAT HER?
NO!
NO.
SHOW ME.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
HEY, FRANK, YOUR TIE.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
HAVE FUN.
[rock music playing]
FRANK, DO YOU WANT TO DANCE?
[coughs]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHOA!
OKAY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[grunts]
IS SOMEONE PLAYING WITH ME?
THIS IS VERY EMBARRASSING.
UH...
PARDON ME. EXCUSE ME.
HEY, WATCH IT.
COMING THROUGH.
EXCUSE ME!
WHAT A DOOFUS.
DAD, STOP PLAYING WITH ME.
YOU THINK THIS IS FUNNY,
DON'T YOU?
WATCH IT, FRANK.
RED LIGHT, RED LIGHT.
STOP! STOP! NO.
DON'T MIND ME.
IT'S JUST MY NEW DANCE.
OW!
[all laughing]
FRANK!
WHAT IS HE DOING?
[sighs]
DAD?
OH MY GOSH, IT IS YOU.
CUTE.
HEY, WHERE YOU BEEN, MAN?
UH, DANCING
WITH MARY LOU HISCOX.
YEAH, RIGHT.
AND I'VE BEEN KISSING
LISA CALMENARI.
YOU AND MARY LOU?
NO WAY.
YEAH, SINCE WHEN
DO YOU KNOW HOW TO DANCE?
UH, I'VE BEEN GETTING LESSONS
FROM CELESTE.
YEAH?
OH, LOOK.
♪ Maybe ♪
♪ If I pray
every night ♪
♪ You'll come back to me ♪
♪ And maybe ♪
♪ If I cry every day ♪
♪ You'll come back
to stay ♪
♪ Oh, maybe... ♪
WHOA.
I NEED A COLD DRINK.
I NEED A COLD SHOWER.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
♪ Maybe ♪
♪ If I hold your hand ♪
♪ You will understand ♪
♪ And maybe ♪
♪ If I kiss your lips ♪
♪ I'll be at your command ♪
♪ Oh, maybe... ♪
THERE YOU GO.
THANKS.
WELL, IF IT ISN'T
THE THREE STOOGES.
UH-OH, NO.
OH NO, DAD.
NOT NOW,
YOU'RE GONNA GET ME KILLED.
ARE YOU TALKING TO ME?
UH, I LIKE
THE THREE STOOGES.
YOU LIKE THE THREE STOOGES?
THIS IS WHAT I LIKE.
[laughs]
NO, DAD. OH!
[imitating Curly]
OH! NYUK NYUK NYUK!
NYUK NYUK!
HEY!
[growls]
OH!
♪ Ah ah ah ah... ♪
COME ON.
[rock song continues]
ARE YOU GUYS OKAY?
RUN FOR YOUR LIFE!
[Telegram]
"NYUK NYUK NYUK!"
THEY'RE DEAD NOW.
DENNIS!
♪ Come on, boys, let's... ♪
OH MY GOD,
HE'S GONNA KILL US!
WAIT UP, GUYS!
♪ Come on, boys, let's ♪
♪ Tear it up ♪
♪ Tear it up... ♪
[Lisa]
DENNIS!
[grunts]
BOZO!
OH!
DENNIS!
♪ Tear it up... ♪
UH...
♪ We'll be keeping score,
let's go... ♪
OH, GOD.
CAN-- CAN YOU SEE THEM?
NO, BUT I HEAR THEM.
KEEP RUNNING!
♪ Come on, boys, let's ♪
♪ Tear it up ♪
♪ Tear it up... ♪
[all panting]
OH, GOD.
YOU THINK WE SHOULD GO IN
AND PRAY THAT DENNIS BECK
DOESN'T MURDER US?
HE'S GOT TO CATCH US FIRST.
WE'D BE SAFER LIVING
IN ALABAMA.
THANKS FOR SAVING MY BUTT.
HEY, THANKS
FOR STICKING UP FOR US.
THAT TOOK GUTS, MAN.
IT DID, DIDN'T IT?
THE THREE OF US--
WE'RE GOING TO BE FRIENDS
FOREVER, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, TILL THEY FEED US
TO THE WORMS?
HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
BLOOD BROTHERS.
WHOA,
BLOOD ISN'T COOL, MAN.
WELL, MAYBE IT'S JUST MY BLOOD
THAT ISN'T COOL?
HEY, MAN,
HOW COULD YOU SAY THAT?
IT'S JUST THAT
BLOOD SCARES ME.
OH.
THE SIGHT OF IT
MAKES ME WANT TO RALPH.
RALPH?
I NEVER HEARD
THAT ONE BEFORE.
YEAH, RALPH.
YOU KNOW, LIKE BLOW CHUNKS?
HURL?
HEAVE? SPEW?
PUKE.
[Both] OH.
WELL, THEN YOU'RE GOING
TO RALPH YOUR HEAD OFF
WHEN DENNIS BECK
GETS A HOLD OF US.
THERE'S GOING
TO BE BLOOD EVERYWHERE.
BE SURE WHEN YOU RALPH,
YOU DON'T JUST RALPH
ON THE GROUND;
RALPH ON BECK.
HE ALREADY LOOKS
LIKE HE'S BEEN RALPHED ON.
[all laugh]
[Officer]
DON'T YOU BOYS KNOW IT'S LATE?
BETTER GET ON HOME
BEFORE I DRAG YOU DOWN
TO THE STATION.
UH, YEAH.
YES SIR, OFFICER.
YEAH, RIGHT-- RIGHT AWAY.
UH, LATER, MAN.
SEE YOU, FRANK.
YOU TOO.
I THOUGHT WE WERE BUSTED
FOR SURE.
BETTER A COP THAN BECK.
YEAH.
MMM!
DARN.
I'LL FIND IT, DAD.
I PROMISE.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP THIS
A SACRED SECRET.
YOU CAN'T TELL A SOUL.
PROMISE?
OKAY, I PROMISE.
YOU'RE GONNA THINK I'M NUTS.
YOU ARE NUTS.
OKAY. DO YOU THINK
TIME TRAVEL IS POSSIBLE?
LIKE IN THAT BOOK
BY H.G. WELLS?
YEAH, KIND OF.
OKAY, HERE IT GOES
BUT IF YOU LAUGH,
I'M GONNA
KICK YOUR BUTT, OKAY?
OKAY, LOOK--
BEFORE MY FATHER DIED,
A GYPSY LADY WHO RAN
THIS TOTALLY WEIRD SHOP
GAVE HIM A PAIR
OF WINGTIP SHOES.
AND WHEN I PUT THEM ON,
I GO BACK IN TIME.
BUT I BECOME MY FATHER.
I MEAN, I LOOK LIKE ME;
I SOUND LIKE ME;
I KNOW STUFF FROM NOW,
LIKE CIGARETTES ARE
NO GOOD FOR YOU;
BUT EVERYONE SEES HIM.
I DO THINGS
I WOULDN'T DO--
THINGS THAT MY FATHER
MUST HAVE DONE.
SOMETIMES HE TAKES OVER MY BODY
AND I HAVE NO CONTROL.
[sighs]
NEXT THING YOU'LL TELL ME
YOU AND MEG HAVE E.T. HIDDEN
IN YOUR CLOSET.
MAN, I KNEW
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE ME.
NO, IT'S JUST WEIRD,
THAT'S ALL.
MAYBE IF YOU COULD
BRING BACK SOMETHING COOL
TO PROVE--
I TRIED BUT IT DIDN'T WORK.
I STUCK THIS MINT
1962 ROGER MARIS CARD
IN MY MOUTH, AND--
IN YOUR MOUTH?
YOU WOULD HAVE GOT SPIT
ALL OVER IT, DUDE.
OKAY, HERE'S WHAT
YOU DO NEXT TIME--
YOU LOOK FOR
A MICKEY MANTLE CARD.
IT'S WORTH SO MUCH MORE.
YOU PUT IT IN AN ENVELOPE
AND YOU SCOTCH TAPE IT
TO YOUR BODY, OKAY?
THIS WAY IT BECOMES
A PART OF YOU.
THAT COULD WORK.
IF YOU DO THAT,
I'LL BELIEVE YOU.
[bell rings]
OKAY, WE'D BETTER GET BACK.
YOU GO AHEAD.
I JUST NEED A MINUTE.
DON'T BE LATE, MAN.
YOU'LL GET SO BUSTED.
OKAY, GUYS, A QUICK
LITTLE VISIT WITH GRANDMA
TO FIND THE POSTCARD
AND THE MICK,
THEN BACK TO SCHOOL.
LET'S DO IT!
MMM!
NOW OFF TO SCHOOL YOU GO
WITH A NICE HOT BREAKFAST--
BLUEBERRY.
IT'S YOUR FAVORITE.
DO YOU EVER THINK
ABOUT THE FUTURE, MOM?
LIKE ROCKETS
AND A MAN ON THE MOON?
I MEAN THIS FAMILY.
WHAT'S GOING TO BECOME
OF EVERYBODY?
THAT'S A PRETTY
BIG QUESTION, HONEY.
SOMETIMES I ASK MYSELF
THE SAME THING.
I WORRY ABOUT CELESTE.
I KNOW SHE WANTS MORE
OUT OF LIFE THAN I HAVE,
BUT LIKE ALL THIS TALK
ABOUT BECOMING AN ACTRESS
IS JUST PLAIN SILLY.
DO YOU EVER WORRY ABOUT ME?
OH, I WISH YOU WEREN'T
SUCH A CUT-UP IN CLASS.
OTHERWISE I THINK
YOU'LL TURN OUT JUST FINE.
I THINK I'M GONNA END UP
SELLING REAL ESTATE,
HAVING A BIG HOUSE
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
NOW FRANK, DON'T EVER
LET A JOB OR MONEY
BE THE MEASURE
OF YOUR SUCCESS.
THERE'S SO MUCH MORE
TO LIFE.
THEN HOW WILL I KNOW
IF I'M DOING WELL?
OH, HONEY,
I PROMISE,
WHEN YOU'RE DOING WELL,
YOU'LL KNOW IT.
YOU'LL SEE IT
IN YOUR FAMILY'S EYES.
TWO STRAWBERRY-JAM
SANDWICHES.
AND OFF TO SCHOOL YOU GO.
GO ON, SCOOT.
I GOT A MESSAGE
FROM DENNIS.
HE SAYS TO TELL YOU
HE'S GONNA HURT YOU
REAL BAD.
[all reacting]
YOU MAY EVEN DIE.
ALL RIGHT, CLASS.
LET'S BEGIN.
YESTERDAY
WE BEGAN TALKING
ABOUT APHRODITE.
WHAT DID WE SAY
WAS HER PARTICULAR FUNCTION--
[Clay thinking]
NO, DAD, STOP.
NO.
NO NO.
FRANK?
APHRODITE
WAS GODDESS OF WHAT?
SEX.
[all laughing]
LOVE. APHRODITE
WAS THE GODDESS OF LOVE,
MR. CROSBY.
NO, DAD, STOP IT.
STOP STOP.
SEX AND LOVE ARE NOT
NECESSARILY THE SAME THING.
YEAH, LIKE YOU'D KNOW.
[All]
OOH!
WE ALSO SAID
THAT IT WAS RATHER IRONIC
THAT APHRODITE,
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL OF GODDESSES,
MARRIED HEPHAESTUS.
WHY IS THAT, MISS CALMENARI?
SHE HAD TO!
MR. CROSBY,
IS YOUR NAME MISS CALMENARI?
[all laughing]
UH-NUH.
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
TO CONTINUE,
ZEUS THREW HEPHAESTUS
OUT OF HEAVEN
AND THE FALL RESULTED
IN A PERMANENT LIMP.
YOU'D LIMP TOO, MR. DORFMAN,
IF YOU WERE MARRIED TO
THE GODDESS OF SEX.
[all laugh]
[Bruce]
THAT WAS SO FUNNY, MAN.
YOU WERE A GAS IN ENGLISH
WITH THAT APHRODITE STUFF.
JUST LIKE YOUR OLD SELF,
MAN.
YOU UTTER ONE WORD
AND YOU'RE DEAD.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
YOU'RE GONNA
WALK DOWN THE HALLWAY
AS IF NOTHING'S WRONG
AND WE'RE GOING TO WALK
OUT OF THE SCHOOL
AND THEN
I'M GONNA KILL YOU.
OH!
[boys chattering]
NO, NOT ANOTHER DETENTION.
MY OLD MAN'S GONNA KILL ME.
[Richard]
DAMN GENERATOR.
ALWAYS SQUEALING.
[grunts]
HEY, BOY.
HEY, DAD, HOW WAS WORK?
[grunts]
THE ELECTRICAL BUSINESS
DON'T PICK UP,
I'M GONNA HAVE TO GO BACK
TO THAT FACTORY AND OPERATE
THAT DAMN DRILL PRESS.
[grunts]
HOW COME
YOU'RE NOT IN SCHOOL?
'CAUSE IT'S 4:00.
4:00?
YEAH.
A MAN SHOULD STILL BE WORKING
AT 4:00.
I GUESS.
WHAT?
YOU GUESS?
WHAT YOU KNOW
ABOUT WORKING? HUH?
I PUT HOT FOOD ON THE TABLE
FOR BOTH YOU AND YOUR SISTER.
WHO THE HELL
YOU THINK PAYS FOR THAT?
HAND ME THAT WRENCH
OUT THAT TOOLBOX.
[wrench clanging]
WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH YOU BOY?
CAN'T YOU HOLD ON
TO ANYTHING? HUH?
YOU SISTER SAYS SHE WANT
A BRAND-NEW CAR.
WHO DOES SHE THINK I AM,
ROCKEFELLER OR SOMEBODY?
AH, THIS WRENCH
IS TOO BIG.
GO IN THE GARAGE
AND GET ME A SMALLER ONE.
AND MAKE IT QUICK, BOY.
POSTCARD, YOU'VE GOT
TO BE HERE.
LET'S SEE.
GRANDMA.
WHERE'S THAT WRENCH, BOY?
JACKPOT! I GOT 'EM.
IF YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD
FOR YOU, BOY, YOU'LL HURRY UP.
UH-OH.
WHERE ARE YOU, POSTCARD?
MAKE IT QUICK, BOY!
IF YOU WANT THING DONE
AROUND HERE, YOU'VE GOT
TO DO IT YOURSELF.
COME ON, GET IN THERE.
WHAT IS TAKING YOU
SO LONG, BOY?
MMM!
YOUR GRANDMOTHER
CALLED TODAY.
SHE MISSES YOU.
SAYS SHE FORGETS
WHAT THE TWO OF YOU LOOK LIKE.
ANYWAY, SHE'S INVITED US
UP FOR THE WEEKEND.
THERE'S A WINTER CARNIVAL
WITH GAMES AND ANIMALS.
WANNA GO?
I WANT TO GO.
[knock on door]
COME IN.
MIND IF I PUT
THIS STUFF AWAY?
SURE, MOM.
IF SOMETHING WERE BOTHERING YOU,
YOU'D TELL ME, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
SO YOU SURE
YOU'RE OKAY?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST THAT...
I CAN'T CONCENTRATE
ON ANYTHING.
ALL I THINK ABOUT
IS DAD.
YEAH, I KNOW.
ME TOO.
REALLY?
YOU KNOW, WE GET IMPATIENT
WITH MAGGIE
BECAUSE SHE PRETENDS
DADDY'S AT THE TABLE
OR SINGING HER TO SLEEP.
BUT IN OUR OWN WAY,
WE DO THE SAME THING--
PRETEND, PLAY GAMES.
WE JUST
DON'T TALK ABOUT IT.
I THINK WE SHOULD.
I GUESS.
MOM, WHY WAS GRANDPA SO MEAN
TO DAD AND AUNT CELESTE
WHEN THEY WERE KIDS?
WELL, I DON'T THINK
HE INTENDED TO BE MEAN.
I THINK HE WAS
JUST DISAPPOINTED.
IN WHAT?
HIMSELF,
THE LIMITED OPPORTUNITIES
FOR AFRICAN AMERICANS.
SEE, HE'D DONE ALL THESE
HEROIC THINGS IN THE WAR
AND KEPT DEMOCRACY ALIVE.
AND THEN HE GOT BACK HOME
AND NOBODY CARED.
SO HE MARRIED YOUNG,
HAD A FAMILY
AND JUST SETTLED.
AS YOUR DAD
AND AUNT CELESTE GREW OLDER,
HE SEEMED TO BE RESENTFUL,
ALMOST JEALOUS OF THEM.
WHY?
THEY WERE YOUNG;
THEY HAD THEIR LIVES
AHEAD OF THEM.
HE'D GIVEN UP HIS DREAM
OF BECOMING A DOCTOR
IN ORDER TO SUPPORT THEM.
DID DAD GIVE UP
HIS DREAM FOR US?
OH.
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
YOU AND MAGGIE
WERE HIS DREAM.
YOU KNOW, SOME MEN
WERE BORN TO BE FATHERS.
YOUR DAD WAS ONE OF THEM.
SLEEP WELL.
GOOD NIGHT, MOM.
GOOD NIGHT, HONEY.
I WAS BEGINNING TO THINK
YOU HAD FORGOTTEN THE WAY.
WE STOPPED
FOR BREAKFAST.
HI, GRANDMA.
MY SWEETNESS.
LET'S SEE YOU.
DON'T STAND THERE WITH
YOUR TEETH IN YOUR MOUTH
LIKE THAT.
COME A LITTLE CLOSER SO I CAN
GET A BETTER LOOK AT YOU.
SOMETIME TODAY, BOY.
HI, GRANDPA.
COME ON, HELP ME
WITH THESE BAGS, BOY.
[Clay thinking]
SAME OLD JUNK.
SOME THINGS JUST NEVER CHANGE.
OKAY, GUYS,
LET'S GET IT RIGHT.
THE POSTCARD'S IN THE GARAGE
NEXT TO THE ROLLER SKATES.
MMM!
[D.J.]
Here's a little tune
you can groove to.
[bebop playing]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have seen some
sizzling skaters
so far here this evening
at Scooter's Rollerway.
You can leave your cares behind
and let your dreams come true.
Now I know the judges
had a hard time making up
their minds,
but they have done it.
In a couple of minutes,
we'll have the performances
of our two finalists.
In the meantime,
here's one more tune
you can bop to.
I SAID THE GARAGE.
WAY TO GO, MAN.
YOU MADE IT TO THE FINALS.
THESE SHOES
HAVE A MIND OF THEIR OWN.
WHAT'D YOU SAY, FRANK?
I MEAN THESE SKATES
HAVE A MIND OF THEIR OWN.
IF THEY'RE NOT LACED TIGHT,
I COULD TWIST MY ANKLE.
I THINK YOU LACED THEM
A LITTLE TOO TIGHT.
THEY CUT OFF CIRCULATION
TO YOUR BRAIN.
HURRY UP.
WE ONLY HAVE A FEW
MORE MINUTES TO WARM UP.
THESE SKATES
ARE PRETTY CRAPPY.
NOW BLADES--
THAT'S THE WAY TO GO.
YOU GUYS
SHOULD INVEST IN THEM.
BETTER YET, INVENT THEM.
YOU'RE ACTING LIKE
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN
ON SKATES BEFORE.
HOW YOU GONNA
WIN THE COMPETITION
WITH DORKY STEPS LIKE THAT?
WHAT COMPETITION?
DUH, THE COMPETITION
THAT YOU AND YOUR SISTER
MIGHT BE ABLE TO WIN
IF YOU STOP ACTING
LIKE SUCH A SPAZ.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
COME ON!
THESE THINGS
ARE DANGEROUS.
I NEED A REST.
HEY, DORK!
AH!
I'M GONNA WHIP YOUR BUTT
OUT THERE, CROSBY--
YOU AND
YOUR STUCK-UP SISTER.
LET ME GO!
[laughs]
AH!
[both scream]
[laughing]
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
DAD, YOU GOT TO HELP ME.
MMM!
HO HO!
BITE ME, BECK.
[laughing]
SEE YOU, DORK.
"BITE ME"?
WHAT ARE YOU, A MANIAC?
COME ON.
WE'D BETTER TAKE A REST
BEFORE THE FINALS BEGIN.
WHAT FINALS?
FRANK!
ALL RIGHT, ALL YOU COOL CATS
AND KITTENS OUT THERE,
I'M GONNA ASK YOU
TO STEP BACK INTO THE SHADOWS.
CLEAR THE FLOOR.
IT IS THE TIME WE HAVE ALL
BEEN WAITING FOR--
THE CHAMPIONSHIP ROUND.
NOW OUR FIRST CONTESTANTS
ARE LAST YEAR'S CHAMPS,
LISA CALMENARI
AND DENNIS BECK.
[jazz song playing]
♪ Give your heart to me ♪
♪ Kiss me softly ♪
♪ And love me always ♪
♪ Faithful I will be ♪
♪ Leave you never ♪
♪ I'm yours forever ♪
♪ Till the end
of time... ♪
LOOK AT THAT.
♪ Just tell me ♪
♪ You're mine ♪
♪ Won't you tell me
you're mine? ♪
♪ Mine ♪
♪ Wha ooh ♪
♪ Won't you tell me ♪
♪ You're mine? ♪
[D.J.]
INCREDIBLE PERFORMANCE,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
LET'S HEAR IT
FOR LISA AND DENNIS.
BEAT THAT, BUTTFACE.
[All]
OOH!
ALL RIGHT,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
IT IS TIME FOR
OUR FINAL CONTESTANTS.
AND I MUST SAY,
THEY HAVE THEIR WORK
CUT OUT FOR THEM.
LET'S GIVE A BIG
MOONLIGHT WELCOME TO...
CELESTE AND FRANK CROSBY!
♪ Where the California girls
are really the most ♪
♪ Where they walk ♪
♪ That walk ♪
♪ Where they talk
that talk ♪
♪ They twist
like this ♪
♪ They shimmy,
don't you hear me? ♪
♪ Yes, they're out there
having fun ♪
♪ In the warm California sun ♪
♪ The girls are frisky
in old Frisco ♪
♪ A pretty little missy
wherever you go ♪
♪ They walk... ♪
[Both]
♪ THEY TALK ♪
♪ THEY TALK THAT TALK ♪
♪ They twist like this ♪
♪ They shimmy,
don't you hear me? ♪
♪ Yes, they're out there
having fun ♪
♪ In the warm
California sun... ♪
[crowd cheering]
[D.J.]
WHAT A FABULOUS PERFORMANCE!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
LET'S HEAR YOUR APPRECIATION
FOR CELESTE AND FRANK.
YOU GOT IT
IN THE POCKET.
WRAPPED AND ZAPPED.
THAT WAS FUN.
ALL RIGHT, ALL YOU COOL CATS
AND KITTENS OUT THERE,
LET'S SEE WHO
YOUR FAVORITES ARE.
FIRST LET'S HEAR IT
FOR LISA AND DENNIS.
[all applauding]
ALL RIGHT.
NOW LET'S HEAR IT
FOR CELESTE AND FRANK CROSBY.
[louder applauding]
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
THE MOMENT WE'VE ALL
BEEN WAITING FOR.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE JUDGES
HAVE MADE THEIR DECISION.
NO PROBLEM.
I MUST SAY I AGREE WITH YOU.
THIS CONTEST WAS NO CONTEST.
THE $100 PRIZE
GOES TO...
CELESTE AND FRANK CROSBY!
[Girl] YOU GUYS WERE GREAT.
OH, THANKS.
SEE?
YOU EVER HAVE THE FEELING
YOU REALLY DON'T BELONG HERE?
OH WELL, YEAH.
RECENTLY I STARTED
FEELING THAT WAY A LOT.
ME TOO. THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO ABOUT IT.
DAD IS DEAD SET
AGAINST MY ACTING CAREER.
HE WON'T EVEN LET MOM
COME TO MY SCHOOL PLAY.
MAYBE HE'S RIGHT.
NO WAY.
YOU'RE GONNA BE
A GREAT ACTRESS SOMEDAY.
RICH TOO.
[laughs]
NOT IF I DON'T
FOLLOW MY DREAM.
HEY, CELESTE?
THEN FOLLOW IT.
HERE, TAKE MY HALF.
AND WHEN YOU'RE SUPER FAMOUS
WITH TONS OF MONEY,
DON'T FORGET
YOUR LITTLE BROTHER
AND HIS KIDS.
I SHOULD GO CHANGE.
MMM!
OH, MAN,
THESE ARE SO COOL.
[engine starts]
HE'S OUT.
POSTCARD, HERE I COME.
CLAY,
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
OH HI, GRANDMA.
WH-- WHERE DID GRANDPA GO?
GRANDPA WENT
TO FILL UP THE CAR.
HE'LL BE BACK SOON.
COME HERE.
COME LET ME MAKE YOU
A CUP OF HOT COCOA.
IT'S INSTANT
LIKE EVERYTHING ELSE
THESE DAYS.
GRANDMA, CAN YOU
MAKE ME A MALTED...
[laughs]
WITH AN EGG IN IT?
OH MY GOODNESS,
I PUT THAT OLD MACHINE AWAY
YEARS AGO.
YOU KNOW, YOUR FATHER
LOVED MALTEDS TOO.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I KIND OF LEARNED A LOT
ABOUT HIS CHILDHOOD.
GRANDMA, WHY WAS GRANDPA
SO STRICT WITH DAD
AND AUNT CELESTE?
HE THOUGHT HE WAS
DOING THE RIGHT THING,
YOU KNOW, BY NOT
SHOWING TOO MUCH EMOTION--
PREPARING HIS CHILDREN
FOR A LIFE OF LIMITED HOPES
AND OPPORTUNITIES.
BUT YOUR FATHER
AND AUNT CELESTE--
THEY HAD HOPE.
DID YOU HAVE HOPE,
GRANDMA?
AT FIRST
WE BOTH DID.
IN TRUTH,
WE NEVER LIVED THE LIFE
YOUR GRANDFATHER DREAMED OF.
BUT HE ALWAYS TRIED
TO PROVIDE THE THINGS
WE NEEDED.
I MEAN, EVEN IF
WE DIDN'T ALWAYS HAVE SOME
OF THE THINGS WE WANTED,
WE WERE NEVER POOR.
WE WERE NEVER RICH,
BUT WE WERE NEVER POOR.
AND I ALWAYS LOVED--
GOODNESS.
I HOPE MY TONGUE
HASN'T WORN OUT ITS WELCOME
WITH ALL THIS WAGGING.
THIS IS SO NICE,
JUST LIKE WHEN YOUR FATHER
USED TO SIT RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE.
WE'D HAVE LONG TALKS.
ABOUT WHAT?
[laughs]
I REMEMBER ONCE
HE WAS ABOUT YOUR AGE
AND HE-- OH, YEAH,
THAT WAS JUST BEFORE
CELESTE RAN OFF.
HE ASKED ME HOW HE'D KNOW
HE WAS DOING WELL
AS A GROWN-UP.
AND I TOLD HIM HE COULD TELL
BY THE LOOK IN HIS FAMILY'S EYE.
AND WHEN I LOOK
INTO YOUR EYES,
I CAN TELL
HE DID VERY WELL INDEED.
HE DID--
MOST EXCELLENT.
[laughing]
[Barker]
THREE FOR $1!
[Virginia]
HEY, THIS LOOKS GREAT.
[Clay]
THIS IS GONNA BE GREAT.
LOOK AT THAT CLOWN.
LOOK AT HIS HAIR.
WOULD YOU WALK IN
LIKE THAT-- THAT RED HAIR?
NO.
[Richard]
OH, WATCH WHERE YOU'RE GOING,
BOY. WALK STRAIGHT.
WE'RE SORRY.
HEY, MAGGIE, WAIT FOR--
MAGGIE?
MOM! MOM!
I WANT TO PLAY THE GAMES.
OH, MY, YOU AS FRISKY
AS A LITTER PUP.
HERE YOU GO, MY DEAR.
HERE YOU GO.
THERE YOU GO.
WHY DON'T YOU
GO WITH HER?
AND STAY TOGETHER!
HEY, MAGGIE, WAIT FOR ME.
HEY, LITTLE GIRL,
WOULD YOU LIKE A BALLOON?
FAT CAT BALL TOSS!
ONLY A TICKET.
FAT CAT BALL TOSS.
HERE'S MY TICKET.
HELLO, LITTLE LADY.
HERE YOU GO.
LET'S SEE YOUR STUFF.
GOT HIM!
WELL DONE.
YOU'VE DONE THIS BEFORE, EH?
THERE YOU GO.
YEAH!
GREAT SHOT, MAGGIE!
HERE, YOU GOT
YOUR LAST ONE.
YES!
OH, YEAH, RIGHT!
YEAH!
HERE, MY DEAR.
OH, MY GOSH,
A FISH.
YOUR VERY OWN GOLDFISH.
THERE YOU GO, SWEETHEART.
HEY, MAGGIE,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HEY, MAGGIE, WAIT UP.
I THINK YOU FORGOT SOMEONE.
I DON'T WANT HIM.
YOU SURE?
HE NEARLY JUMPED
OUT OF THE BAG AFTER YOU.
I THINK HE LIKES YOU.
HE'S GONNA DIE
JUST LIKE DADDY.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
COME ON.
LOOK,
BEFORE YOU WERE BORN,
MOMMY'S PARENTS DIED.
I CRIED A LOT.
THEY WERE NICE.
ANYWAY, DADDY TOLD ME
NOT TO BE SAD,
THAT I WAS MADE
OF A PIECE OF THEM
AND THAT THEY'D ALWAYS
BE PART OF ME.
AS LONG AS I LIVED,
THEY LIVED.
IT'S LIKE THIS LITTLE GUY.
HE'S MADE UP
OF A WHOLE CHAIN OF FISH
JUST LIKE ME AND YOU
ARE MADE UP OF A WHOLE CHAIN
OF FAMILY
WHERE EVERYONE LIVES FOREVER
IN EACH OTHER.
SO HERE, TAKE HIM.
TAKE HIM.
COME ON, TAKE HIM.
TAKE HIM!
GO SHOW MOM.
MOM! MOM!
LOOK WHAT I GOT.
[Woman]
CLASS!
CLASS, SETTLE DOWN, PLEASE.
[Telegram]
I HATE THOSE STUPID
PECKERWOODS.
[Bruce]
BE SURE WHEN YOU RALPH,
YOU DON'T JUST RALPH
ON THE GROUND;
RALPH ON BECK.
[Mary Lou]
WHAT A DOOFUS.
[Man]
OKAY, WHO'S GOING TO BE
THE LUCKY PANCAKE PERSON?
YEAH, I JUST NEED
ONE MORE PERSON.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE,
THERE'S A HUNGRY-LOOKING BOY
JUST RIGHT FOR THE POWER
PANCAKE-EATING CONTEST.
THE WHAT?
THE FIRST PERSON
WHO FINISHES ALL THE PANCAKES
WINS $100.
I DON'T THINK SO.
OH, COME ON, COME ON.
GIVE IT A TRY. YOU CAN DO IT.
NO ONE'S EVER BEAT
OUR CHAMPION DENNIS BECK.
HEY, GIVE HIM
A LITTLE ENCOURAGEMENT
THERE MAYBE, HUH?
HA HA HA!
HEY, THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
COME ON UP HERE.
WAY TO GO, WAY TO GO.
SIT RIGHT DOWN THERE
AND PUT THAT #8 CONTESTANT
BIB RIGHT ON HIM.
OKAY, WELL, LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE READY TO ROLL.
OH, MY GOD, IT'S CLAY.
ALL THE CONTESTANTS HAVE TO--
LET'S SEE
WHAT THE BOY IS MADE OF.
GET ALL THOSE FIXINGS
FIXED UP THERE ON
THOSE PANCAKES.
GET ALL YOUR STUFF
ALL SLURPED UP THERE.
GET YOURSELVES SET.
AND GO!
HA HA HA!
IT'S UNDERWAY, EVERYBODY.
COME ON, CHEER THEM ON.
PICK YOUR FAVORITE
PANCAKE PERSON AND GIVE THEM
ENCOURAGEMENT.
OH, IT'S LOOKING GOOD.
THE COMPETITION IS LOOKING
GOOD ALREADY.
KEEP EATING, EVERYBODY.
GET THROUGH THOSE STACKS.
OH, LOOK AT OUR CHAMPION GO.
LOOK AT HIM GO AT IT.
KEEP ENCOURAGING THEM,
EVERYBODY.
LET'S HEAR IT.
GO, CLAY, GO!
[All]
EAT EAT EAT!
GO GO GO!
OH, GOOD LORD,
HE'S GOING TO PASS OUT.
IT'S NOT LIKE HIM TO DO THIS.
IT REALLY ISN'T.
COMPETITION
BUILDS CHARACTER.
EAT, BOY! EAT.
[all cheering]
[Barker]
YOU'RE SLOWING DOWN, CHAMP.
YOU'RE SLOWING DOWN.
GO ON, BOY.
SHOW ME WHAT
MY SON IS MADE OF.
EAT!
WE HAVE A WINNER!
LET'S HEAR IT FOR HIM,
EVERYBODY!
NYUK NYUK NYUK!
[Female barker]
GUESS YOUR WEIGHT!
COME ON OVER HERE
AND GUESS YOUR WEIGHT.
COME ON NOW,
GIVE IT A TRY.
THERE YOU GO, BOY.
THANKS.
MM-HMM.
YOU CALLED ME YOUR SON.
YEAH, WELL,
I'M REAL PROUD OF YOU, BOY.
YOU BEAT THAT BLOWHARD BECK.
[laughs]
YOUR FATHER-- HE NEVER DID
LIKE THAT-- THAT S.O.B.
DID YOU EVER TELL MY DAD
THAT YOU WERE PROUD OF HIM?
HUH?
OH, NO NO NO,
DIDN'T HAVE TO.
HE ALWAYS KNEW.
HOW?
WAS HE SUPPOSED TO GUESS?
WHAT IS THIS,
THE SPANISH INQUISITION
OR SOMETHING?
YOU SHOULD HAVE
TOLD HIM, GRANDPA.
WHAT?
LOOK, BOY,
I WORKED HARD
TO TAKE CARE OF MY FAMILY.
YOUR FATHER AND THAT--
THAT AUNT CELESTE--
ALL THEY WANTED TO DO
WAS HAVE FUN, YOU KNOW?
LIVE OUT THEIR DREAMS.
WHAT'S SO BAD ABOUT THAT?
I WANTED TO
MAKE SURE HE TOOK CARE
OF HIS RESPONSIBILITIES.
I WAS SCARED HE WOULDN'T
BE PREPARED FOR THIS WORLD,
A WORLD THAT DIDN'T WANT HIM;
A WORLD THAT DIDN'T WANT ME.
I MUST ADMIT, THOUGH,
HE DID GET SOME GOOD GRADES.
HE KEPT MOUTHING OFF
IN CLASS.
HE HAD THEM MISFIT FRIENDS.
HE COULDN'T DO NOTHING
WITH HIS HANDS.
HE'D TRY MY PATIENCE SOMETIMES,
ESPECIALLY WHEN I'D GET HOME,
YOU KNOW?
I WAS TIRED FROM WORK.
AND THEN I'D--
HIT HIM?
NO NO NO NO NO,
I NEVER LAID A HAND ON HIM--
NEVER.
I WILL TELL YOU ONE THING,
THOUGH.
HE WASN'T SCARED.
HE NEVER WOULD BACK DOWN.
ONE DAY HE WALKED PAST
MY RAISED HAND
INTO ADULTHOOD...
NOW HE'S GONE FOREVER.
I GUESS I--
I GUESS I WASN'T MUCH
OF A SUCCESSFUL FATHER.
WELL, MAYBE YOU WERE
AFTER ALL, GRANDPA.
BECAUSE WHEN DAD GOT SICK,
HE REFUSED TO BE SCARED.
HE DIDN'T BACK DOWN.
AH, HE WAS JUST
TOO YOUNG TO DIE.
YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN PROUD
OF HIM, GRANDPA-- VERY PROUD.
THIS WAS A PICTURE OF HIM
AT HIS GRADUATION.
HE GRADUATED WITH HONORS.
I WAS SO PROUD OF HIM
I COULD BURST.
HERE.
YOU TAKE IT.
BUT YOU NEVER TOLD HIM.
NO.
I'M TELLING YOU.
I LOVED THAT BOY SO MUCH.
DAD GAVE ME A MESSAGE
FOR YOU, GRANDPA.
HE MADE ME PROMISE
TO TELL YOU--
TO TELL YOU
THAT HE LOVED YOU.
LISTEN UP, GUYS,
WE'RE REAL CLOSE.
POSTCARD'S IN THE GARAGE.
TAKE ME
TO THE POSTCARD.
MMM.
WHAT THE--
I GUESS WE'RE BACK.
DAD, I FOUND IT!
YES!
[Richard's voice]
25th OCTOBER, 1944.
LATE-DAY GOLF.
DEAREST GINNY,
AFTER THE WAR, MARRY ME.
OUR LIFE WILL BE MADE
IN HEAVEN.
LOVE, RICHIE.
YES.
COME ON, MICK,
LET'S GO HOME.
MMM!
DAD, I JUST CAN'T FIND IT--
YES!
[knock on door]
YEAH?
HI, HONEY.
CAN I COME IN?
SURE.
BOY, DAD LEFT A LOT
OF MEMORIES IN THIS ROOM.
[laughs]
HE WON THIS
ON OUR FIRST DATE.
HOW DID YOU AND DAD MEET?
OH, MY, I HAVEN'T TOLD
THAT STORY IN A LONG TIME.
UM, WE WERE IN
THE SAME PSYCHOLOGY CLASS.
AND I WOULD SAY
FOR THAT WHOLE FIRST SEMESTER,
I NEVER EVEN NOTICED HIM.
THEN ONE DAY,
ABOUT A WEEK BEFORE OUR FINAL,
I GOT THIS POSTCARD
IN THE MAIL.
YOUR FATHER
HAD A THING FOR POSTCARDS.
AND IT SAID,
"I'D LIKE TO GO OUT WITH YOU."
AND IT WAS SIGNED,
"ROW 4, SEAT 17."
SO THE NEXT DAY,
I TOOK SPECIAL NOTICE
OF WHAT WAS SITTING THERE.
AND AT THE END OF CLASS,
I GAVE HIM A PIECE OF PAPER
WITH MY PHONE NUMBER ON IT.
YOU KNOW AT THAT MOMENT,
MY LIFE CHANGED FOREVER.
MY LIFE CHANGED AGAIN
THE DAY THE DOCTOR
TOLD US HE WAS SICK.
DECEMBER THE 20th,
THAT WAS THE DATE.
AND EVERYBODY WAS FEELING
GOOD ABOUT CHRISTMAS
AND ABOUT THEIR LIVES.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL.
NO, I DO.
I DO.
YOUR FATHER
FOUGHT THE CANCER THE WAY
HE FOUGHT EVERYTHING,
LIKE HE COULDN'T THINK
OF NOT WINNING.
BUT THE RADIATION
WASN'T WORKING
AND THE CHEMO JUST TURNED
HIS BODY INTO A BATTLEFIELD.
THE PAIN WAS ALWAYS THERE.
SO WE FOUND A DOCTOR
WHO PUT HIM ON A SPECIAL PROGRAM
OF VITAMINS, HERBS,
ACUPUNCTURE,
VISUALIZATION.
AND IT WORKED FOR HIM...
FOR US.
SO CLAY,
PLEASE DON'T BLAME ME.
I DON'T.
TWO DAYS BEFORE HE DIED,
I GOT ANOTHER POSTCARD
IN THE MAIL.
IT SAID,
"I'LL WAIT FOR YOU.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
TAKE A LIFETIME."
AND IT WAS SIGNED,
"ETERNALLY,
ROW 4, SEAT 17."
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY--
I HAVE NO REGRETS
WHATSOEVER,
EXCEPT FOR ONE--
I REALLY WISH
YOU'D HAD MORE TIME WITH HIM.
I HAD FUN
AT THE CARNIVAL.
YOU DID?
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
LIKED PANCAKES SO MUCH.
HA! YEAH.
YOU THE CHAMP.
YOU KNEW THAT, HUH?
YEAH.
HERE WE GO.
WHAT A GREAT
GOING-AWAY PRESENT.
NAH, THAT'S A COMING-HOME
PRESENT, BOY.
YOUR FATHER
AND YOUR AUNT CELESTE,
THEY NEVER CAME BACK.
DON'T YOU BE A STRANGER
TOO, BOY.
ALL RIGHT.
I HAVE A PRESENT
FOR YOU TOO.
OH, YEAH?
[screen door opens]
[Virginia]
I NEED YOU TO EAT
YOUR ASPARAGUS, OKAY?
NOT JUST THE TIPS.
AND YOUR COLLARD GREENS.
YOUR MAMA EVER MAKE
COLLARD GREENS FOR YOU BEFORE?
NEVER?
WELL, LISTEN, YOU BE
GOOD CHILDREN AND DON'T GIVE
YOUR MOTHER ANY TROUBLE, OKAY?
OKAY?
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH, GRANDMA.
OH, SWEETIE.
I LOVE YOU BOTH.
YOU ARE THE DEAREST THINGS
IN THE WORLD TO ME.
OH!
ALL RIGHT.
BETTER GET MOVING NOW,
Y'ALL.
OKAY? OKAY.
BYE, SWEETIE.
BYE.
GO ON.
HERE YOU GO, BABY. HERE.
I FEEL LIKE
WE'RE ALL STARTING OVER.
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE FINE
FROM NOW ON. YOU'LL SEE.
YEAH. YEAH.
BYE.
GOODBYE.
HEY, BOY, DON'T YOU FORGET
THAT PROMISE NOW, HUH?
YOU TAKE CARE DRIVING NOW,
HEAR?
[horn toots]
[ringing]
HELLO, CELESTE?
Daddy?
YEAH.
[laughing]
♪ Well, I will
stand beside you ♪
♪ Hold you up... ♪
[Janice]
OOH, NOW THAT'S ROCK 'N' ROLL,
NOT THAT
STONE TEMPLE, SNAPPIN' DUMMIES,
CRASHING PUMPKINS STUFF
YOU LISTEN TO.
I'LL MAKE YOU A DEAL.
YOU CAN LISTEN
TO ANYTHING YOU WANT.
ANYTHING?
YEAH, ANYTHING...
IF WE CAN MAKE A STOP
ON THE WAY HOME,
NO QUESTIONS ASKED.
HEY, YOU GOT A DEAL.
HELLO?
ANYONE HOME?
I'M CLOSED.
I GUESS YOU DON'T
REMEMBER ME.
OF COURSE I DO.
YOU'RE THE BOY
WITH THE FATHER.
NOW GO AWAY
AND CLOSE THE BEADS BEHIND YOU.
I CAME TO RETURN
THE SHOES THAT YOU GAVE HIM.
DID YOUR FATHER WEAR THEM?
NO, I WORE THEM.
SO YOU JUST SLIPPED
INTO ANOTHER MAN'S SHOES?
DID THEY FIT?
YEAH, THEY FIT REAL WELL.
BUT I DON'T NEED THEM
ANYMORE.
I THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU COULD GIVE THEM
TO SOME OTHER KID--
LOOK WHAT CAME IN YESTERDAY.
[Clay]
I LOVE YOU, DAD.
[man vocalizing]
♪ OH ♪
♪ TONIGHT ♪
♪ JUST CLOSE YOUR EYES
AND DREAM AWAY ♪
♪ TOMORROW
IS A BRAND-NEW WORLD ♪
♪ A BRAND-NEW DAY ♪
♪ AND SOMEWHERE
DOWN THE ROAD ♪
♪ SOMEDAY YOU MAY RECALL ♪
♪ THIS LULLABY
I SING TONIGHT ♪
♪ TO YOU ♪
♪ I'LL BE WITH YOU
EVERY TIME YOU DO ♪
♪ MMM MMM ♪
♪ GOOD NIGHT ♪
♪ I HOPE YOUR EVERY DREAM
COMES TRUE ♪
♪ SO MANY YEARS AHEAD ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOOK FORWARD TO ♪
♪ BUT SOMEWHERE
DOWN THE ROAD ♪
♪ SOME QUIET PLACE IN TIME ♪
♪ THIS LITTLE LULLABY ♪
♪ MAY CROSS YOUR MIND ♪
♪ AND I'LL BE WITH YOU
LIKE I AM TONIGHT ♪
♪ SO WHEN YOU
CLOSE YOUR EYES ♪
♪ JUST DREAM
ABOUT TOMORROW ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ JUST LIKE
I AM TONIGHT ♪
♪ WHENEVER YOU HEAR
THIS LULLABY ♪
♪ SWEET DREAMS ♪
♪ CLOSE YOUR EYES ♪
♪ GOOD NIGHT ♪
♪ OOH OOOH ♪
♪ GOOD NIGHT. ♪