[dramatic music]
[gentle instrumental music]
[jazzy music]
- What do you want?
- [Lefty] I just, I
wanna talk to you, Becky.
- I told you I didn't
wanna see you anymore.
- Come on, babe, you
didn't mean that.
We're in love.
- I gotta go, my parents
are expecting me for dinner.
[door slams shut]
- I'll come with you.
- No.
How many times do we have
to go through this, Lefty?
And things just didn't
work out between us,
and now it's over.
I thought you understood.
- Yes, I understand, you
think you're better than me.
You always did.
- That's not true.
I just don't love you.
Why can't you accept
that and leave me alone?
- Not till I'm ready.
[Becky gasps]
[dramatic music]
- Don't you ever
come here again!
If you do, I'm gonna
call the police!
- Becky, come back.
I'm sorry.
[crickets chirping]
[laughing]
- Oh, Becky.
- A toast to our
wonderful daughter
who's not only had her first
novel fast-track published
to great critical acclaim.
- Thank you, thank you.
- But has sold said novel
as a five-hour miniseries, hear,
hear.
- Television, oh, well.
- Whoever said there's no
business like show business
wasn't kidding, you're gonna
learn that, sweetheart.
- I already know, Dad.
I had to listen to
your war stories
about how the studios abuse
us writers all my life.
- Most of which he made up,
Becky.
- I know that too, Mom.
- All right, all right.
Enough about my trials
and tribulations.
- I'd like to make a toast.
To my mom for giving me life,
courage, and the strength
to survive any situation.
And to my dad for his support,
belief, and inspiration.
I love you both very much.
[glasses clinking]
- Well, I always seem to be
the one to call it an evening,
but I really am rather tired.
- [Dad] I'll get your chair.
- You're gonna ask Dad
to tuck you in tonight?
- Oh, those days are over,
my sweet.
And even when we were married,
I always preferred
sleeping alone.
- Liar.
[Mom chuckles]
- What about you, honey?
You're not still seeing
that guitarist, are you?
- No, Mom, I told you.
I broke up with him.
- Oh.
- Well, I'm glad to hear
it, you deserve better.
- You've said that about
every guy I've ever dated.
- And all of us know
I'm never wrong.
- Oh, yes, Gus, and that's
certainly true.
- Need some help?
[Becky chuckling]
- Immaculata will
take care of me.
Now call me soon, both of you.
Goodnight.
- Goodnight, Peach.
- Goodnight, Mom.
- Wanna walk your old
man to his car?
- Only if you'll do
the same for me.
[gentle instrumental music]
- [Gus] You all right
about this breakup?
- [Becky] I'm fine, Dad.
It took me a while
but I found out
I really didn't love
him after all.
- Well, I'm proud of you, Becky.
You've turned into a wonderful
woman and a terrific writer.
- [Becky] It was easy.
I'm my father's
daughter after all.
- Ah, thank you.
Drive carefully, huh?
- I will.
- Goodnight, darling.
- Goodnight, Dad.
[suspenseful music]
[doorbell ringing]
- [Gus] Who is it?
- [Detective Jackson] Mr.
Augustus Bailey?
- [Gus] Yes.
- [Detective Jackson]
Detective Jackson, LAPD.
I'd like to talk to you, sir.
- What's the problem?
- [Detective Jackson] I'm sorry
to have disturbed you, sir,
but I'm afraid I have
some bad news.
You have a daughter,
Rebecca Lee Bailey,
living at 235 West Hayden
Avenue in West Los Angeles?
- Yes.
Dear God, she hasn't been
in a car crash, has she?
- No, sir.
I'm sorry to have to
tell you this,
but your daughter is dead.
It appears she was murdered.
- That can't be.
I was with her two hours ago.
Has to be a mistake.
- A neighbor reported
hearing screams
coming from inside your
daughter's apartment.
Our officers investigated
and found the body.
- No.
[dramatic music]
No.
Not Becky.
No, please.
- I'll need you to make an
identification, Mr. Bailey.
- Yes.
But I hope to God you're wrong.
You have to be wrong.
- We have a suspect in custody,
sir.
- Who?
- [Detective Jackson] Francis
Flint, also known as Lefty.
- I don't believe you.
- The police took me to see her.
- How did it happen?
- They are not sure.
- How did she die, Gus?
- She was murdered.
Strangled
by Lefty Flint.
- Oh, God.
Dear God.
Not my child.
Not my baby.
What do we do, Gus?
What do we do now?
- We make sure Flint goes away
for the rest of his damned life.
- A formal arrest has been made
in connection with last
night's brutal slaying
of Becky Bailey,
successful novelist
and daughter of writer Augustus
Bailey and his ex-wife,
socialite Peach
Prindible Bailey.
Francis Lefty Flint
has been charged with
murder in the first degree.
Flint, entertainer at a
Malibu restaurant
and estranged boyfriend
of the victim,
has admitted to committing
the violent crime,
and his trial is expected
to begin shortly.
[dramatic news music]
Until tomorrow, this is
Bernard Slatkin for Focus
on special assignment.
- Honey, we gotta go.
The van to the
airport's waiting.
- [Anchorman] Thank you,
Bernard.
- I'm sorry, I was
watching something on TV.
- [Friend] Ruby, are
you all right?
You look like you've
just seen a ghost.
- I have.
[solemn music]
- The night Peach gave
birth to Becky,
I remember thinking for
the first time
about my own mortality.
Suddenly my life became
more precious
because of that beautiful child.
I had to live long enough
to ensure her happiness.
I wanted to catch her
when she tried to take
her first steps.
I wanted to teach her how
to ride a bike,
dribble a basketball.
I wanted to introduce
her to the power of words
and watch her discover
the magic of love.
I wanted to walk her down the
aisle into a loving marriage.
And I wanted to hold her
first child and feel renewed.
Most of all,
I wanted to protect Becky
from any kind of harm.
Goodbye, my darling daughter.
- Peach.
I'm so sorry.
Gus.
- Thanks for coming, Faye.
- She's the daughter
I never had.
When Becky was seven,
eight years old,
you brought her to the
set of Memphis Belle,
do you remember that?
- Hmm.
- She told me that I should
read her father's lines
exactly as they were written.
And if I did, she promised me
that she would someday
write a movie for me.
You know, because of
that promise,
I never changed a
word you wrote.
[suspenseful music]
[reporters clamoring]
- Winding up what has been
a lengthy and heated trial,
Francis Lefty Flint, admitted
killer of Becky Bailey,
has just arrived at the
Santa Monica courthouse.
Flint's attorney has announced
that his client will take
the stand today
and testify on his own behalf.
And now I see Becky's
parents have arrived.
Peach Prindible Bailey herself
the victim of our cruel fate,
paralyzed after being thrown
from a horse five years ago.
And Augustus Bailey,
the noted Hollywood
screenwriter and journalist.
- Becky told me that her
parents didn't approve of me,
so I thought I'd make
it easy on her
and I told her that
maybe it would be better
if we didn't see one
another for a while.
- Are you saying that
you're the one
who ended this relationship?
- Yes, sir.
Not because I didn't love Becky,
I did.
Because I knew it would
be better for her
with me out of her life.
- And why were you at Becky
Bailey's apartment that night?
- Becky called me.
She said she missed me,
that she wanted to see me,
and that she didn't care what
her parents thought anymore.
- [Prosecutor] So you
went to Becky's apartment
at her request?
- Yes.
When I arrived, she asked
me to spend the night,
but I told her I didn't
think it would be right.
Without her parents blessing,
it would make the love we felt
for each other dirty, unholy.
So I started to leave,
and Becky got hysterical.
She started screaming
saying that if I left,
she'd do something crazy,
maybe even kill herself.
I tried to calm her down,
but she just kept hitting me,
you know,
just over and over again.
I just wanted her to stop.
I loved Becky.
I never meant to hurt her.
- But you did hurt
Becky Bailey, Mr. Flint.
You silenced her screams forever
and you used your hands
as your weapon.
[spectators murmuring]
[dramatic music]
- It is the judgment
of this court
that the defendant
Francis Flint,
having been found guilty of
the crime of manslaughter
by the jury of this court
for the City of Santa Monica,
California,
be imprisoned for a period
of three years.
[spectators gasping]
However, it is also the
court's judgment
that since the defendant
has no previous convictions,
he be allowed a parole hearing
after serving 1 1/2 years
of his sentence.
[spectators protesting]
The defendant will herewith
be remanded to the custody.
[hammer banging]
[reporters clamoring]
- You think you got a
fair sentence?
- God's on your side.
- [Woman] God will punish you!
- Mr. Flint, Mr. Flint.
Is there anything
you'd like to say
to Becky's parents, Mr. Flint?
- I just hope they
can forgive me.
God has.
- [Woman] God will
never forgive you!
- [Man] God loves you!
- [Man] You'll burn in hell!
[solemn music]
- Something else I can
do for you Mr. Renthal?
- Yes, you could sit down
and talk to me.
I can't ever seem to fall asleep
on these damn red-eye flights.
- Well, maybe for just a minute.
I thought people like you
never flew commercial,
Mr. Renthal, private
jets and all.
- It's Elias, and you
shouldn't believe
everything you read
in newspapers.
I'm just an average
guy from Chicago
who's made a little money.
- Oh, I guess that's why
you're on the cover of Wall
Street Magazine this week.
- Where are you from?
- Someplace I just fly over now.
- Married?
- Never.
- I used to be.
My ex-wife said she didn't
want to stay with a guy
who had no class.
But, hell, you could buy that.
You got enough money, you
can buy anything you want.
- Yeah, you can even
erase the past,
become somebody important,
you know, admired.
Forget all the bad things
that ever happened to you.
- [Elias] Did those happen?
- Not to people like me.
- I can make it happen for you.
- Oh, I'm sorry, Elias, Mr.
Renthal,
but I gotta get back to work.
I'll see you later.
- [Woman] There you go.
- [Gus] Hi.
- [Peach] Hi.
- My plane leaves in a
couple of hours.
Just came over to say goodbye.
- You sure you want to
move to New York?
I remember a time
when you couldn't wait
to get to Hollywood.
- Well, it's not popular
to write movies about
people anymore.
Only a lot of chases,
special effects,
and I have to make a living.
- What are you gonna
do in New York?
- I have a few appointments
with a couple of magazines.
Besides, there's no reason to
hang around here any longer.
- Oh.
[gentle instrumental music]
- I'm proud of you,
the way you've gotten
through all this.
- I'm proud of you too.
You'll miss your plane.
- Yeah.
It's not over yet, Becky.
I promise you.
It's not over.
[gentle instrumental music]
Good evening, Charlie.
- Good evening, Mr. Bailey.
[guests chattering]
[laughing]
- What I simply cannot
stand is to be bored.
And there's never
anything boring
with the doers of the world.
- [Man] That's just
what I was going to say.
- Thank you.
- Hello, Gus.
[laughing]
Aren't you glad you're
away from California?
Such a synchronicity of
theme at dinner, the movies.
The people are so superficial
and such frauds. [chuckling]
- Well, we couldn't accuse
anyone who comes to your parties
of being like that, could we,
Maisie?
- Well, my parties
aren't about people, Gus.
My parties are about
conversation.
After coming here for a year,
you should understand that.
Oh, excuse me, I see,
Senator Marx.
- Hello, Gus.
- Hello, Justine.
You look beautiful.
How's Lil?
- Oh, well, Mother is
Mother, always the same.
Tell me, Gus, do you
know that man over there?
Talking to Violet Bastito?
- That's Bernie Slatkin,
anchorman for Focus.
- That's where I've seen him.
Do you know him?
- We've met.
- You're sitting under the
Renoir next to Senator Marx.
Ezzie, I'm sitting you
next to Mrs. Renthal.
- Mrs. Renthal, the wife
of the hamburger king
who's in all the newspapers?
How dare you waste me
next to her.
- Oh, Ezzie, try to be nice.
This is the Renthals first
New York party,
and I want them to feel at home.
- Well, I'm sure they will,
as long as they keep
buying your paintings.
[Maisie scoffs]
- Now, Ezzie, you know
perfectly well
that Maisie Verdurin has
a genius for seating.
She absolutely agonizes
over her placement.
Besides which, had you
bothered to read my column
yesterday morning, you would
know that Elias Renthal
is the man to watch.
He made all those millions
in the past eight years
from hamburger franchises
to company takeovers, dear.
- Still say the only
respectable way to make money
is to inherit it.
And you can put that in
your column, sweetie.
- We're all wrong for
this crowd, Elias.
- Don't kid yourself, baby.
Once these people get
to know us--
- They'll ask us to leave.
- Oh.
I'd just about given you two up.
- I'm sorry we're so late.
I don't think you've
met my wife Ruby.
- Oh, I'm so pleased
to meet you.
- Thank you for inviting us.
- Hey.
- Oh, is that the painting
you wanted me to see, Elias?
- Yes, Monet's Water Lilies.
- Well, that is the
color pink I like.
- Maisie, I think you got
yourself a sale.
Go ahead, baby, take
a closer look.
- Oh, no, uh,
I want you to see the picture,
but the waiters are just
about to serve.
- You got the right idea,
Maisie, honey.
[Maisie giggling]
Never do business on an empty
stomach, huh? [laughing]
- Elias, I have you
sitting next to me,
and you are sitting with
Ezzie Fenwick,
who's the best friend of
all the ladies in New York.
- Great.
- It's been a long time, Mr.
Bailey.
Bernie Slatkin.
- Gus.
I always wanted to thank you,
the way you handled your news
coverage about my daughter.
You're the only reporter
who didn't exploit our loss.
- I just tried to put
myself in your shoes.
That made it hard to
be objective.
- [Gus] Well, we appreciated
your sensitivity.
- Gus, be a dear, give
us some advice.
I've decided to take
up reading as a hobby.
Could you recommend
something with short chapters
about rich people?
- What about Trollope?
- Excuse me?
- I think he means the
author, Anthony Trollope.
- Can I take him home?
Or will he keep me up all night?
- I hate to read in bed.
- So do I.
[laughing]
- Just look at that
Renthal woman.
She absolutely won't do.
Dress like she's going
to the opening of the
opera in Istanbul.
As you must be having
a field day.
- Where did you get that dress?
- [Ruby] Chicago.
- [Ezzie] I thought so.
Why on earth did you ever leave?
- Well, Elias's
business is here now.
- Your husband's not
quite as imposing
as I thought he'd be, Mrs.
Renthal.
- Well, my husband can
be very imposing
when he opens his wallet, Mr.
Fenwick.
- Goodnight, Bernie.
- Goodnight, Gus.
- Mr. Bailey?
- My friends call me Gus.
- My name is Ruby Nolte Renthal.
I want to talk to you
privately for a moment.
- [Gus] What about?
- I just wanted to tell
you how sorry I am
about what happened to
your daughter.
- Thank you.
- I wish I could have
done something for her.
- You sound like you knew Becky.
- No, no, I didn't.
You don't always have to
know a person to feel sorry.
- [Elias] No, thanks, I'm
sure I'll find her, thanks.
- Maybe you and I could
have lunch together sometime
and just talk.
- [Gus] I'd like that.
- So would I, very much.
- What the hell is
going on in here?
- Just getting my coat, Elias.
- Maisie wants us to look at
that picture again up close.
- Elias, this is
Augustus Bailey.
He wrote that article
you like so much
on Laurance Van Degan
in the Knickerbocker.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Same.
And nice meeting you, Mrs.
Renthal.
- [Ruby] My friends
call me Ruby.
- Guy's old enough to
be your father.
- You're old enough to
be my father.
- What the hell is this?
We go to our first
New York party
and I find you in the
bedroom with--
- The coats.
Calm down, Mr. Bailey
writes about rich people.
- Like us?
- Us, I love that word.
- Well, we made it through
the first party
without anyone asking
us to leave.
- Oh, we haven't made it
to the door yet.
Will we ever fit in
with this crowd, Elias?
- No problem.
We're important people now,
a team,
and don't you ever forget that.
- I love you, Elias.
- Same here.
Now, let's go look at
that $6 million Monet
and make sure it's the
right color pink.
[coins rattling]
- They shouldn't allow this.
- You give him anything?
- It's hard to pretend
you have no money
when you're climbing
into a limousine.
- Oh, let's go to The
Carlyle hear Bobby Short.
- Would you like a ride
home, Miss Altemus?
- No, thank you, I have
a driver and a car.
Actually, it's my mother's car.
- Well, maybe you'd like
to give me a ride home.
- Well, my driver doubles
as my bodyguard.
- Only my thoughts
will be impure.
[Justine chuckles]
Do you like it?
My place, I mean.
- Actually, no.
I know that I look crestfallen.
I've been brought up
on Empire sofas
and the neoclassic look as
dictated by Cora Mandell.
- [Bernie] Who's Cora Mandell?
- Well, the doyenne
of decorators.
- Is that what you do
for a living, decorating?
Or don't you work?
- I'm very involved
with several charities.
And one day a week, I work at
a hospital as a nurse's aide.
- Sounds strenuous.
When do you find time to relax?
- I'm here now, aren't I?
In that cab, that is what
you offered me.
[gentle instrumental music]
It's not what I was expecting.
- Are you sure?
- [Woman] They must be
here already.
- [Man] Mm-hmm.
[speaks faintly]
- [Woman] Nevel is so much
cleverer than Claude Montana.
- I don't wanna miss a minute.
- Oh, neither do I.
[exciting pop music]
[audience applauding]
- Thanks for meeting me, Ezzie.
I've never been to a
show like this before.
I'm used to buying off the rack.
- Never, not even in
an emergency.
It's better to stay home
than to be seen in rags.
- Oh, and I thought they
called it the rag business.
- It's how much you pay for the
rag that makes a difference.
The Nevel is very expensive.
- Isn't that Lil Altemus?
- Yes, she's matriarch of
all those gurus.
- Oh, I always read about
her in the society columns.
She has such style.
[camera shutter clicking]
- Which one do you like?
- I'm not sure.
[camera shutter clicking]
[audience applauding]
Oh, I think I like this one.
Yes, may I borrow your
pen for a moment?
- I know everyone's secrets,
Ruby.
- I bet you do.
- I'll tell you some of Lil's.
Her husband, Hubert,
left her for a much, much
younger woman.
You know, age before beauty.
- [Ruby] Oh, you're terrible.
- Oh, you love it.
- [Gus] You look great, Ruby.
- Very Lil Altemus,
don't you think?
- Very, if that's what you want.
- Well, it's important
for me to fit in here.
It's different for you, Gus.
You come from money,
you're used to it.
- Are you kidding?
Peach had all the credentials.
I'm strictly middle-class.
- Well, I'm not even that.
I grew up on a ranch in Montana.
Well, not really a ranch,
was more like a shack with
a few chickens.
And a mother who didn't give
a damn about fashion or me.
But you seem so comfortable
around those people, Gus.
I'm sure in the hell not.
- Well, maybe it's
because I don't care
what they think about me,
and you do.
- Well, if you don't care,
then why do you bother?
- It's a distraction.
Keeps my mind off worse things.
Now look, Ruby, I work
for a magazine
that caters to those people.
They invite me because I
write articles about them.
The rich love to read
about themselves.
Otherwise, I
wouldn't be invited.
- Well, there's no
harm in mingling.
- Just as long as you
don't join the club.
Believe me, all they care about
is the money you donate
to their charities,
not at all in who you are.
I don't want you to get hurt.
- Well, thanks for the warning.
[sighing]
Artichokes, they're so ugly.
I guess the only thing you
can do with them is eat them.
- Hmm.
One year, my daughter made a
Christmas wreath out of them.
Didn't look bad.
And after about a week,
started to smell.
But Becky was so proud of it,
we kept it up until Easter.
- You must miss her terribly.
I'm sorry, Gus, maybe you
don't wanna talk about this.
- There was a time that
that's all I talked about.
[sad music]
I mean, all I can do
what my anger
was to scream at everyone
about anything.
Then I stopped talking about it.
I felt no one cared.
As far as everyone else
was concerned,
justice had been done.
The subject was closed.
- But your anger
hasn't gone away.
- No, it hasn't.
I don't think it ever will.
- You take all your dates
to such fancy places?
- [Bernie] You're the first.
Mikey.
- I haven't seen you for
a while, Bernie.
Seems like you've been
spending your time uptown.
- Mike, I'd like you to
meet Justine Altemus.
Justine, this is Mike O'Rourke.
He owns this dump.
- Hello, Mike.
- Glad to meet ya.
But tell me, what's a
nice girl like you
doing with a bum like this?
- Obviously trying to
change my image.
- Well, grab any table.
No reservations necessary.
- Thank you.
What do you think?
- I like Mike, but I
have to save my review
until after we eat the food
because it's not quite what
I'm used to. [laughing]
- I bet you Clarence's is
more to your taste, huh?
I ate there once, hated it.
- Was it the place or
the people you disliked?
- [Bernie] The food.
- Ah.
[chuckling]
Well, that makes sense.
No one goes there to eat anyway.
Everyone who goes
there to be seen
and to look at each other.
- You're not like that, are you,
Justine?
- I'm trying hard not to be.
Why else would I be with you?
- You mean you're just slumming?
- Oh, I can accuse you
of doing the same thing.
Wanting to know how the
other half lives.
- No, I just wanna know
how the other half feels.
[slow saxophone music]
- [Juanito] This can't be true,
Hubie.
This cannot be true!
- Juanito, please.
- Where are you going?
- Justine.
- I just had picked a bad
time to drop by, Hubie.
- Oh, no, no, it's okay.
Juanito just got some
bad news about a friend.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- So, what brings you down here?
You wanna buy a piece of art?
- No, I just wanted some
advice from my big brother,
that's all.
- Mother would never approve.
[laughing]
- That's true.
Um, I think I'm getting
serious about someone
for the first time in my life.
- Congratulations.
Is his name Bernard Slatkin?
- I'm afraid so.
- And you're worried
about what she'll say?
- I'm afraid so.
- Don't be.
We can't live our lives
according to Mother's rules.
Or else we won't have any.
And God knows life is
short enough as it is.
- Okay, thanks, thanks.
And tell Juanito I hope
his friend is okay, okay?
[slow saxophone music]
[gentle piano music]
- It is well meant when
friends say to us,
"I know how you feel."
But they can't really
know how we feel.
Only someone who has experienced
the tragedy that we have
have experienced can know.
Someone like the total stranger
sitting next to you now.
That person can understand
our feelings of anger or rage.
But feelings, no matter
what they are,
they're only feelings,
aren't they?
They're not right or wrong,
and even the most negative
fantasies are not wrong to feel.
It would only be wrong if we
translated them into action.
- What about justice?
My daughter is dead,
but the man who murdered
her is still alive,
and the only
punishment he received
is to serve three years in jail.
Three years compared to
my child's entire life.
Now somehow, the rights of
the victim do not equate
with the rights of the criminal.
- That's true, and I think that
that's something we should
all work very hard to change.
- We have to change it.
We owe it to the
people we loved.
This is the last business
of their lives.
- My son,
he was beaten to death
in a racial encounter,
and I, I don't know how
to reconcile my feelings
towards the men who did it.
Mister,
what would you do
if you ever saw the man
who killed your child?
[dramatic music]
- What I wanna do is kill him.
And it scares the hell out me.
But that's what I feel.
I wanna kill him.
[gentle instrumental music]
- [Bernie] You really are
different from all the others.
- Others?
- Women I've known.
- Oh, I see.
- They all,
they all worked, and
they worked at working.
- And you don't consider
what I do a career?
- Sure it is, but you're
not driven by it.
You're just there for
me, there just for me,
and not always thinking about
the next power breakfast.
I've never known anyone
like you before.
You know, I told my aunt
Hester and uncle Sol about you.
I said that you were
almost as tall as me
and that you were fine looking.
- Oh, is that all?
- No, I also told them
that I was gonna marry you.
- Without asking me first?
- That's exactly what my
aunt Hester said.
- Yes.
The answer is yes.
- I wonder what it's like
having sex without a condom.
- Another intellectual
conversation.
The way you get around, Bernie,
it's that or nothing.
- I don't get around anymore.
I'm reformed.
- Since when, three minutes ago?
- Brenda.
- Mm?
- There's something I
have to tell you.
I'm engaged to be married.
Her name is Justine Altemus.
- You bastard, Bernie.
- Hey, that hurt.
- That was the point.
I know you may think of me
as the office convenience,
but we conveniences
have feelings too.
- You're not a convenience.
You're the best damn researcher
I've ever worked with.
Then, you're a good friend.
- Not quite the word I
was expecting you to use.
Well, you can tell
Justine Altemus
that I feel sorry for her.
All that money and she winds
up with a guy like you.
I hope she doesn't mind
sharing her husband
with every woman over the
age of consent.
- I'm gonna change.
- Sure you are.
What makes you think that
just by marrying someone
you're gonna change?
You'll still be the same
old horny bastard
you always were, Bernie.
[gentle instrumental music]
[door slams shut]
- I know you did.
- No.
- [Violet] You sat there
and you watched Lil
pick out that white suit
and you told Ruby Renthal
to buy exactly the same one.
I know you did.
- I did not.
- You can't like to me, Ezzie.
- [Violet] Someone's got
to tell her what to wear,
for God's sakes. [laughing]
- Lord Biedermeier, what
makes you think
that the average Joe will
pay good money
to read a book about me?
I wouldn't.
- [Lord Biedermeier]
That's just it, Elias.
You're not the average
Joe, not any longer.
And please call me Lucien.
You've made the American
dream a reality,
and the public wants
to know how.
- A book, huh?
I'll have to think about that.
I'm going to London on business.
You could reach me at
the Claridge's Hotel.
- Simply Claridge's, Elias.
Not The Claridge's, nor The
Claridge's Hotel, either.
[patrons chattering]
- Hello, Justine.
Haven't seen you for
quite a while.
How've you been?
- I've been in love, Chick.
- [Chick] That's wonderful.
Excuse me.
- [Elias] People Like Us,
I like that.
So will Ruby.
- [Lucien] By the way,
who's your tailor?
I could recommend mine
if you don't have one.
- Who is that
horribly dressed man
lunching with Lord Biedermeier?
- It's Elias Renthal,
the financier.
- Oh, oh, I read about him in
his wife in Dolly's column.
The new people. [chuckling]
Well, I'll have whatever
Justine's drinking, Chick.
I suppose you invited your
mother to lunch
to discuss Mr. Bernard Slatkin.
- Who have you been talking to,
Mother?
- Well, Joe doesn't tell tales,
but you have been keeping
him and the car out
frightfully late.
- I'd like to show you the ring
that Bernie has given me, look.
- Well, that's a garnet,
for God's sake.
With a lot of pokey
little diamonds around it.
An announcer who earns as
much as he's reputed to
certainly can do
better than that.
- But he's an anchorman,
not an announcer.
And the ring belonged
to his aunt.
- Yes, I'm sure it did.
Well, just turn it back around,
so when we leave and say
hello to Violet and Ezzie,
they won't notice.
- I found someone I love,
Mother,
and I'm going to marry him.
I hoped that you'd be
happy for me.
- You know I've always
wanted you to marry, Justine.
I would simply prefer my
son-in-law to be one of us.
I'm sure his family
feels the same.
- Bernie's parents are dead.
He was raised by his
aunt and uncle.
- How unfortunate for everyone.
Well, since that piece of
jewelry appears to mean
what I think it does,
we should discuss plans
for the wedding.
- Oh, Bernie and I want to
invite family and a few friends.
We'd like to keep the
occasion intimate and small.
- Your ring is small enough.
You are my only daughter,
Justine.
And I insist on giving
you a proper wedding.
You know, I wanna do
this for you.
Now please, don't be difficult.
- If you won't be when
Daddy gives me away.
- I haven't cared about
anything your father has done
in the last 10 years.
Now, when am I going to
meet your Mr. Slatkin?
- As soon as you say, Mother.
- Cocktails and hors d'oeuvres
with the entire family,
of course.
Although I don't know how
my dear brother
is going to react to this news.
- Well, he'll just have
to keep a stiff upper lip.
It shouldn't be too difficult
for uncle Laurance,
shouldn't it?
- I really liked your
father and your stepmother.
But you never told me why
your parents got divorced.
- Hmm, I think you'll understand
once you've met my mother.
She can be dreadful.
Polite and charming
[chuckling] but dreadful.
- I know all about
people like your mother.
I'm in show business, remember?
- So, why the party, Mother?
I thought you didn't
approve of Bernie.
- I can't ignore the situation,
so it's best just to
put on an approving face
and keep one's private
thoughts to oneself.
I think you'll find a
tie in your old room.
- I'm not staying.
- What?
[laughing]
- No, I can't stand the thought
of being in the same room
with uncle Laurance
and aunt Janet,
or my cousin and his
dreary wife.
- I won't hear a word
against my dear brother.
- Your dear brother
can't stand me, either.
He fired me.
Didn't approve of my
lifestyle, wasn't that it?
- You don't work at
the bank anymore
and all those pressures
are behind you.
- I love Justine and I would
do absolutely anything for her,
but I am still going, Mother.
- And one of these days
you'll find the right girl
and make your old
mother really happy.
My dear Hubie, you look tired.
- Wish Justine luck for me.
[gentle instrumental music]
[all chattering]
- [Justine] Mother,
this is Bernard Slatkin.
- Hello, how are you?
- Pleasure to meet you, ma'am.
- Mr. Slatkin, may I present
my brother, Laurance Van Degan.
- Mr. Slatkin.
- [Lil] And his wife, Janet.
- Hello, how are you?
- [Lil] And my father,
Ormonde Van Degan.
Father, this is
Justine's fiance.
- [Bernie] Nice to meet you,
sir.
- [Lil] Oh, and yes, our
cousin, Dodo Fitz Alyn,
my father's loyal companion.
- So happy to meet you.
- [Lil] My nephew,
Young Laurance.
- Mr. Slatkin.
- [Lil] And his wife, Laura.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you both.
- Oh.
Oh, Parker, tell Gertie
the canapes look yummy.
- Thank you, Parker.
- Some smoked salmon, Mr.
Slatkin?
- [Elias] Max, just because
you're my head trader
and we go back a long time
doesn't mean that you can talk
to me any way you want to.
- [Max] And why not?
I'm the guy who sold the
hamburgers you used to make
while you dreamed about owning
your own franchise someday.
- [Elias] So?
- I also remember you
used to think
the world would be your
oyster if you had a million.
Then I remember you set
10 million as your goal,
then 50, then 100.
- What's your point?
- The point is, you've got
$3 billion now.
When are you gonna stop?
- I can't stop, Max, it's
too damn easy.
You know what it's like?
It's like putting a hunk of
red meat in front of a lion.
Besides, how else am I gonna pay
for that new office building?
- I certainly wouldn't
presume to tell you
what to write, Gus.
But the family would prefer
that you focus the article
more on Justine's background
rather than on Bernie's.
Jewish.
- Bernie's heritage doesn't
seem to matter to Justine, Lil.
- Well, it should matter, Gus.
Marrying an outsider
can do nothing
but create problems
for everyone.
Oh, there's Ezzie and Violet.
There's that cheap man
one's always hearing about.
What is his name?
- [Gus] Elias Renthal.
- Laurance actually wants me
to invite him and his wife
to Justine's wedding.
I mean, he says that's
important to us.
The world has gone mad.
- Mr. Bailey.
- Call me Gus.
- I want you to meet Max Luby,
an old friend and
associate of mine.
- How do you do?
I don't believe you've
met Lil Altemus.
- Hello, how are you?
- Fine, thanks.
I know your brother.
We're in a couple of
business deals together.
- Really?
- Well, I guess
we'll go sit down
before they give our seats away.
Well, it was nice meeting you,
Lil.
See you, Gus.
- I simply can't imagine
Laurance doing business
with that man.
I mean, it's ridiculous,
it's absolutely ridiculous.
[phone ringing]
- Hello.
- Damn it, Gus, I've
tried calling you all day
but you're never in.
I have some information for you.
- Peach, what's going on?
- I had a call from
Lieutenant Jackson.
He wanted me to be the
one to tell you.
The date for Flint's parole
hearing has been moved up
due to good behavior.
- I see.
Okay, bye.
[gentle instrumental music]
- Now, what exactly do
you have in mind?
I mean, in regards to this Mr.
Flint.
- [Gus] I want you to
keep track of him
if he gets out next month.
Where he lives and what
he does with his time.
- Is that all?
- For now, yes.
- So, you want this guy
thrown out a window?
- No, I don't want
anything like that.
- It could look like
an accident.
You wouldn't meet the
person who'd do it
and he'd never know your name.
Easy, not cheap, but safe.
- No, Mr. Feliciano.
I have something else in mind.
Hi, Peach.
How are you feeling?
- Old, if you want to know,
and I hate it.
- I wanted you to know I hired
a detective to watch Flint.
If he's released after
that hearing.
- He can't be let out.
Dear God, has everyone
forgotten what he did?
I want to go to that
parole hearing, Gus.
I have to tell them again
what he did to a
beautiful daughter.
I have to make them remember.
I want them to remember.
- They won't forget Becky,
Peach.
I won't let them forget.
- I wish you could go to
the wedding too, Juanito.
- Maybe if I dressed up
as a loaf of white bread.
- No, it wouldn't work.
You would forget to cut
off the crusts,
and then uncle Laurance
would see right through
your disguise.
- Your sister said she liked me.
- She does and if it were
up to Justine,
she would have invited you,
but she's walking on
eggshells as it is
with this TV announcer.
- Isn't that what's called
marrying beneath you?
You know, you two are
a lot alike.
- Stop that, will you, please?
I hate it when you're that way.
- Honest?
- Bitchy.
You're like my mother.
[laughing]
- That's a low blow.
- How does this look?
- Look up here. [mumbles]
Thanks.
[Hubie groaning]
You could never tell.
Hubie, give it a little
more of an angle.
- You do it.
- Perfect.
Now let's go.
I gotta get back to the gallery.
One of us has to work
for a living.
[church bell tolling]
- Couldn't they have
gotten married
someplace a little
closer than Long Island?
- Bernie told us all of
Justine's people
get baptized, married,
and buried in this church.
It's their family tradition.
- [Sol] I still think my nephew
should be married in
a synagogue.
- And I say be glad that
Bernie's getting married.
[gentle organ music]
Where do you suppose
the girl is?
- Aren't brides always late?
- I wasn't.
[Sol chuckles]
- [Photographer] Mrs. Altemus,
would you look this way, please.
Thank you.
[camera shutter clicking]
- [Girl] Come on, there she is,
hurry.
[girls giggling and gasping]
- Hello, Lil.
- Hubert.
- Hello, Father.
- Hello, Hubie.
- Oh, it's a lovely bouquet,
Justine.
No one like Lorenza for flowers.
- Do I look all right, Mother?
- You look perfect.
Nevel at his best.
- Well, I meant me.
- You look beautiful, Justine.
- Hubie, it's time for
you to take me in.
- Good luck, Justine.
I really want you to be happy.
- Hubie, what's that?
- It's nothing, it's just an
irritation from my aftershave.
["Bridal Chorus"]
[jazzy music]
[girls giggling]
- You're gaining a lot of space
in the columns lately, I see.
- Oh, can you believe this?
You'd think I was
somebody important.
- You are.
- I'm with firm of Weldon
and Stinchfield, Mr. Renthal.
- They handle a lot
of takeovers.
- We do our share.
- Let's talk later.
I'm really interested
in takeovers.
- If I ever strike it rich,
my wife and I
would like to build a home
in Fairfield, in Darien.
But it's hard with kids.
We have two little girls.
- I'm sure in time that
could be arranged, Byron.
For the proposal I have in mind,
there would be nothing risky.
All you'd have to do is
identify certain companies
that retain Weldon and
Stinchfield in an advisory capacity.
You know, before takeovers
and mergers happen.
- This is beautiful.
- It belonged to Edward VII.
It's the original felt.
- Holy smoke.
- I'd be willing to pay
5% on any profit I make
with your help, paid in cash,
say,
on 80,000 shares of West
Virginian Natural Gas.
It would be a very
handsome amount.
- Holy smoke.
- Shall we go now and have
another brandy?
- Okay, Gus, I want you
to be honest with me.
What do you think?
- Well, I seem to be at a
loss for words.
I don't know how I'm gonna begin
to describe all this
in my article.
- Well, do me a favor, try
to write about our apartment
and not about us.
Elias thinks my picture's
been in the paper
too much already.
- It is.
And we gotta be careful.
There are a lot of crazy
people out there
who like to read about
people like us.
- Elias wants me to carry a gun.
- It's for your own protection.
- Look at this little
pearl-handled number he gave me
as a stocking present.
It used to belong to
Queen Marie of Romania.
Oh, don't be afraid, I
never keep it loaded.
It's just for show,
you might say.
- That's not why I bought
you the damn thing, Ruby.
- [Housekeeper] Excuse me,
Mr. Van Degan is on the
telephone, Mr. Renthal.
- All right, tell him I'll
be right there.
Ruby, why don't you
take Gus on a tour, huh?
Don't forget to show
him the fumary.
- You know, in California,
the first thing they do
after they give you a drink,
they show you their closets.
[Ruby chuckles]
- [Ruby] Will you
stay for dinner?
- I can't, I'm leaving
for the coast tonight.
Lefty Flint, the man who
murdered my daughter,
his parole hearing is
tomorrow afternoon.
- But he's only been in
prison for a year.
- Yeah, and Becky would
have been 24 this fall.
- Is your wife going with you?
- No, I talked her out of it.
She's not well enough.
And besides, there's no
point in her going through
what we went through in
court all over again.
- Well, there's a chance his
parole will be denied, right?
- Slim one.
He's been a model prisoner.
So, as far as the judicial
system is concerned,
he will have paid his
debt to society.
- Well, this isn't justice.
- [Gus] No, it isn't.
- Look, Gus, why don't
we take the grand tour
when you get back?
- And missing the fumary?
No way.
[gentle instrumental music]
- Macumber, why are you
calling me here?
I told you never to do that.
- I apologize, Mr. Renthal,
but I'm not in my office
and this was the only
number I could remember.
I thought this was urgent.
- All right, so
where's the fire?
- Omaha Fuel has hired Weldon
and Stinchfield as an advisor
on a proposal by Tri World
Incorporated to acquire them.
I thought you'd want to
know as soon as possible.
- All right, but from
now on you're Mr. Brown
and don't ever call
me here again.
- Yes, sir, I understand.
Goodnight.
[phone line humming]
[keypad beeping]
[phone line ringing]
- [Receptionist] Credit
Suisse of Nassau.
- Yeah, this is Mr. Rod
Nolte, get me Mr. Gerhard.
- [Gerhard] Yes, Mr.
Nolte, this is Gerhard.
- Buy 180,000 shares of
Omaha Natural Gas
the instant the market opens.
- [Gerhard] Anything else?
- [Elias] No, that's all.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
- The smoke.
- [Elias] That's why
you got me this fumary
so I wouldn't cloud up
your fancy-schmancy rooms.
- Don't say fancy-schmancy.
- Why not?
- Because it's tacky,
we're past that.
Listen, honey, I forgot.
I'll need the plane real
early tomorrow.
There's an auction at the
California ranch
and there's a couple
of Remingtons.
- Couple of who?
- [Ruby] Horse sculptures.
I thought they might be
nice for the country house.
- Okay, have your secretary
set it up with the pilot.
- Thank you, sweetheart.
I love you, Elias.
[gentle instrumental music]
[dramatic music]
- [Officer] Let's go,
single file.
- [Inmate] Yep.
- [Officer] I saw that one,
Peter.
- And I can't believe
that 15 months
constitutes enough time
to rehabilitate the man
who murdered my daughter.
I only pray you agree with me.
- [Warden] We will consider
your remarks Mr. Bailey.
Thank you.
I now call Mrs. Elias
Renthal to speak.
[door clacking]
Mrs. Renthal, please.
- My name is Ruby Nolte Renthal,
and I've come here today
to plead with you
not to grant Francis
Flint an early release
from his prison sentence.
- Warden, I object.
- This is a hearing,
not a trial, Mr. Pink.
Objections are not recognized.
Go on, Mrs. Renthal.
- I had a two-year
relationship with Francis Flint
that ended before the
murder of Becky Bailey.
On four separate occasions,
Mr. Flint beat me.
On two separate occasions, I
was hospitalized as a result.
Once after he threw me
down a stairway
when I tried to escape from him.
Another after he broke my
nose and teeth,
blackened my eyes, and
fractured my jaw.
- [Warden] Didn't you
press charges at the time?
- No.
- I ask why.
- I was warned not to.
- By whom?
- That doesn't matter now.
All that matters is that
the jury at his trial
was allowed to think that
Becky Bailey strangulation
was one single isolated
incident, an accident.
That's not true.
Mr. Flint is a classic
abuser of women.
His weapon is his hands.
[chair squeaks]
- Sit down.
- Are you finished Mrs. Renthal?
- Yes.
Yes, am I excused?
- Certainly.
And thank you very much.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Because I felt so guilty.
Ever since I heard about
Becky's death,
I've lived every day
knowing if I had only
gone to the police.
If I'd only done something,
Becky might still be alive.
- [Gus] Why say anything now?
- Because of you.
- Dear God.
- I knew Lefty years ago.
Long before he met Becky.
I just moved to Dallas, I
got a job as a waitress.
He played guitar at the
same restaurant.
I know you might find
this hard to believe,
but he could be very charming,
very sweet.
We started spending a lot
of time together
and after a while he
moved in with me.
It wasn't long before
the beatings started.
Afterwards, he'd always cry,
tell me how sorry he was, how
he never meant to hurt me.
- Why didn't you ask for help?
- I was too afraid.
When I did try to break
it off and get away,
Lefty came after me.
Oh, Gus, I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
- I'm sorry, Ruby,
for both of us.
Does Elias know?
- No.
No, I never told him.
I've been so ashamed.
I felt dirty just being alive.
Even now I don't know if I
could tell him,
and he's the best thing
that ever happened to me.
Someday maybe.
Not now.
- Well, I'll call in
a few favors.
Keep your name out
of the papers.
- Oh.
- [Gus] Nobody will find
out about this, Ruby.
I promise you.
[gentle instrumental music]
- [Ruby] Tell Frida we'll
have lunch about one, I think.
I'll leave the menu to her.
- Very good, madam.
- [Ruby] You see, there is
some justice in this world.
- Hi, did I miss everything?
- [Ruby] Well, you're too
late for the Easter egg hunt.
- [Gus] This wouldn't have
happened without you, Ruby.
- You gave me the courage
to do it, Gus.
- [Gus] You remember
that other woman
who was at the hearing?
- [Ruby] Yes.
- [Gus] Yeah, well, I had a
detective do some checking,
and it seems like Lefty
has found his next victim.
- I was afraid of that.
- Thank you.
Her name is Marguerite Hanrahan.
She started writing to him
when he first went to prison.
And I guess she believed
he was born again
because now she's
gonna marry him.
- After everything she heard?
- Hard to believe, isn't it?
Somehow I've got to convince her
she's making a terrible mistake.
- You have to, Gus.
Somehow you have to.
- For her sake, I hope I can.
- Look at your anemones,
so beautiful.
Lorenza has been here, I see.
- Just.
Mrs. Renthal has been
monopolizing all of her time
with that damn ball.
Happy Easter, Janet.
Imagine, new people like that
giving that kind of party
and inviting all of us.
- [Janet] Laurance feels
we should play along.
- Why, may I ask.
- [Janet] Because they are
taking charge, darling.
People like us in the
social register
are practically extinct.
- Janet, my brother,
your husband,
is still very much in charge.
The Van Degan Bank, the
Van Degan Foundation,
the Van Degan Building,
they're all his.
We'll just see who's in charge.
I wouldn't dream of accepting
the Renthals invitation.
- We should talk about that,
Lil.
- Who is this coming to see me?
Who is it, who?
Yes, there she is.
- Baby Janet loves her
grandma, don't you, sweetheart?
Yes.
- And then Juanito
told me that--
- I didn't know you two
had gotten so close.
- I bought a
painting for Ormonde
at Hubie and Juanito's gallery.
- Nice picture, Hubie,
big colors.
- Thanks, Grandfather.
- Parker, you'll be sure
I want you to tell Gertie
how much we enjoyed the
crab tartlets.
- I absolutely agree
with Father.
Elias Renthal is the most
fascinating man
to come into the financial
community in years
and necessary to it.
- It's a surprise.
I didn't think you people
liked this type.
- Well, we have been
known to make exceptions
when they're forced upon us.
[glass clinking]
- To the newest member
of our family.
[thunder rumbling]
- Long way may it reign.
[Violet laughing]
[all chattering]
- Where's Juanito today?
- [Hubie] Oh, he's with
some friends.
- Hubie, when are you
gonna tell me?
- Well, I thought that
you'd already guessed
at your wedding.
- Well, what's gonna happen?
- What eventually
happens to all of us.
[Justine crying]
Justine, please don't,
please don't cry.
Justine, please, don't cry,
not with all this family here,
please.
- You are gonna tell Mother,
yes?
- As soon as everyone
leaves today.
- Do you want me to be with you?
- Do you realize that even
though I am your big brother,
you have always tried
to take care of me, hmm?
I think I can do this.
But thank you very much anyway.
[solemn music]
Please don't cry.
- Fun, wasn't it?
Now you know what I've had to
go through all these years.
- [Bernie] You didn't
pick your family.
- No, but you did.
Listen, it'll be different when
we have children, I promise.
They'll wanna come home
for the holidays.
- Justine, you know how I feel.
I don't even know if I
wanna have kids.
All that responsibility.
- You'll change your
mind, I know you will.
We won't let them even
meet my family. [chuckles]
- Wasn't this nice, Hubie?
Dinner on trays and just
the two of us by the fire.
- Yes, it's nice.
- Well, I bet you
couldn't imagine
your old mother could
rustle up such a good meal
with Gertie and Parker
out for the evening.
- [Hubie] Mother,
there's something
that I want to tell you.
- Hmm, would you like to
watch television or just talk?
- Just talk.
- Good.
Try some of Gertie's fig mousse.
I don't know how she does it,
something about egg whites.
- Mother, you can see
that I'm not well.
- I know they have to use
ripe figs and only white figs.
I know that's very important.
- I have AIDS, Mother.
- It's just that your
color is not good, Hubie.
You eat like a sparrow.
- I have lymphoma
and not much time.
- Hubie, I thought you and
I might take a little trip
to, say, St. Moritz
out of season.
It's just too beautiful for
words and it's so healthy.
- I might be dead by then.
- Oh, Hubie!
This talk is just so morbid.
I don't know how you can
do this to your family.
[laughing]
- Thank you for all your
support, Mother.
- Paris.
Paris, that's where we
should go, Hubie.
Wally Simpson left all her
money to the Pasteur Institute
and they do marvelous things.
- Don't you think that I
would have already gone there
to get help?
It's too late.
But that's not why you
suggested it, is it, Mother?
You just wanna hide me so
that your friends won't know
that your son is gay
and has AIDS.
- Hubie, please.
Nevel told me all about
that disease.
But I never thought people
like us got it.
[gasping]
[suspenseful music]
Order Malvern water,
Israeli melons.
Gertie, please forgive
the ghastly mess I made.
I tripped.
P.S. The fig mousse was yummy.
- [Woman] Yes, we're ready.
- [Marguerite] Uh, hi.
The Chardonnay by the
glasses are special today.
- [Woman] Uh-huh.
- [Gus] Hi, Marguerite.
I'm Gus Bailey.
- What do you want?
- [Woman] I like Chardonnay.
- Talk you out of
marrying Lefty Flint.
- That's none of your business.
- Flint is a murderer,
you know that.
He killed my daughter.
- He was drunk when he did that.
He doesn't drink anymore.
Now I think you'd better get
out of here and leave me alone.
- Look, here's my
telephone number.
If you're ever in any sort
of trouble, you call me.
[gentle instrumental music]
- [Peach] I'm over here!
- Hi.
- Oh, hi.
I bet that detective you
hired doesn't know about this.
It's from Flint.
When he does get out of prison,
he wants to come and see me.
Our daughter's killer
wants my forgiveness.
If I ever see that man
again, I'll kill him
with whatever
strength I have left.
- You were always stronger
than I was, Peach.
- So, you left.
- You asked for a divorce.
I made you unhappy.
- I'm not much for looking back.
Don't be too hard on yourself,
Gus.
You were a good father.
Wheel me back inside, will you,
I've got to get back to bed.
- If you don't mind, Peach,
I'd like to look for something
in the basement before I go.
- [Peach] What you want
to go in the basement for?
- [Gus] Some letters my
father sent me
when I was in the Army.
- We packed all your things
and sent them to your apartment
when we broke up.
- [Gus] Well, they must
have been left behind,
wound up down there.
[suspenseful music]
- Can I help you?
- Yeah, I have a little Russian
made weapon here from Korea.
- It's a beauty.
Is it for sale?
- No, I'd like to get
it into working order.
Can you do that?
- Sure, I'll need a deposit.
Your name?
- Mertens, Gene Mertens.
[gentle instrumental music]
[somber music]
[dramatic music]
[woman chuckling]
[clapping]
- Happy birthday, Peach.
Now let's see, how old
does this make you exactly?
- Still younger than you.
- Would you like me to
cut the cake now, seora?
- Yes, thank you, Maggie,
my dear.
We'll have some more
coffee as well.
That was very sweet of
you to remember, Gus.
You could've just sent a card.
- Well I didn't want
you to celebrate alone.
- You always were too
sentimental.
- That is probably true
but I'm glad there are
still a few occasions
left to celebrate.
- You make the best
of everything.
- Not everything.
Flint's lawyer got him
another parol hearing.
Should take place within
a couple of months.
- And he'll get out this time,
won't he?
- Yes and it will all be over
and justice will be satisfied.
- But that's not how we feel,
is it, Gus?
- Maybe we will, Peach.
Someday.
- [PA Announcer] Arriving
passenger Miles Miller,
please meet your party at
baggage carousel three.
- Is that you, Gus?
- Hello, Faye.
- Well leave it to you not
to make a big fuss over me.
- No, you look great.
- That's better.
But I'll just bet if I
hadn't spotted you,
you wouldn't have gotten
up to speak to me.
- Oh yes I would have.
I was waiting for the
usual hubbub to die down.
Headed for Europe or
New York like me?
- Big Apple, honey.
Gonna be shooting "Judas
Was A Redhead."
- Oh, that would make
a good movie.
- Gus, they don't make
movies of books anymore.
They make miniseries.
[chuckling]
Gus?
- Yeah.
- I was in Italy shooting
a picture during the trial.
You know I would've been there.
Gus, you've really kept
it in control.
I would've shot the
son of a bitch.
Gus?
You know the Elias Renthall's,
don't you?
- [Gus] Yes, I do.
- I know we're talking
big bucks here
but is he generous?
- I don't think he'd
finance a movie.
- Cathy, my best friend,
she's dying of the Big A.
Married a guy, had no idea
that he was into needles.
You know the story.
[sighing]
I'm trying to raise money
for the disease.
In fact, big bucks.
Think you could help me out?
- Faye, you're famous.
You don't need me to meet
Elias Renthall.
- He didn't return my
phone calls.
At least not after I told his
secretary what it was about.
I guess he's only into
the safe, social
advancement charities.
Look,
all I want is an introduction.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Terrific.
We get to New York, I'll
take you to lunch
or we'll do lunch.
- How about we both
just eat lunch?
[laughing]
It's for an important cause,
Elias.
Maybe not to some members
of the social set,
but for thousands of
people afflicted with AIDS.
- Okay, I'll send the
lady a check.
- Good.
- Better yet, I'll invite
her to the ball,
I'll give it to her there.
Ruby will love meeting
Faye Converse.
- Yeah and you'll enjoy
the good public relations.
- It's for a worthy cause,
right?
- Right.
- Ruby hates these things.
She ever tell you how we met?
- No.
- It was on an airplane.
Must've been the altitude
that got her to marry me.
- I doubt that.
- She likes you, Gus.
- Well, Ruby's a terrific girl.
You're a lucky man.
- Well that's what
people say about me
but I've had my
share of trouble.
So have you, I've heard.
I love my wife, Gus,
and I won't let anybody
hurt her ever again.
- I understand.
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Hi.
It's me.
What're you doing?
- [Young Woman]
Clipping coupons.
- Just like my Aunt Hester.
- So when are you coming home?
- Oh, I don't think I can
get out of here
at least until two or three.
- Not again, sweetheart, that's
the third time this week.
- It can't be helped.
Don't wait up for me.
- Okay.
I love you.
- Same here.
[somber music]
- Feeling guilty?
- [Man] Shut up.
- I liked you better when
you were single.
At least then you didn't
pretend to care
about anybody but yourself.
- I care about Justine.
- Sure you do.
That's why you're here.
- And that's why I'm leaving.
[somber music]
- It's amazing.
Everyone we've
invited is coming,
including your mother.
[Justine laughing]
- Well I knew she'd
accept eventually.
Mother just wouldn't be content
having to hear about your
ball of anointed clearances.
[laughing]
- I'll let you in on a
little secret.
First Lady is coming.
- The First Lady?
How wonderful.
How on Earth, Ruby?
- Elias has been friends
with the President for years.
They used to do business
together when he was governor.
To be perfectly honest,
I'm happier about you
and Bernie being there.
I'm gonna need the
moral support.
[chuckling]
- I just hope Bernie
doesn't have to work
late again that night.
He's been doing a lot of
that these days.
- Oh, so is Elias.
But he says, "Somebody
has to earn the rent."
- Oh, I suppose.
It's just,
well, I just can't help feeling
that Bernie's keeping
something from me.
That there's some deep dark
secret he's afraid to tell me.
I always thought when you
married someone
there wouldn't be a need for
secrets between the two of you,
no matter what you'd done,
it wouldn't make any difference
to the person who loved you.
I just wished Bernie loved
me enough to trust me.
- Well he does love you,
that's what's important.
Right?
[pleasant music]
- [Worker] Watch behind you!
Oh, that's good.
- Be careful.
If you break any of those
I'll have you all
dipped in cement.
Mrs. Renthall,
isn't it just fabulous
what I have done?
Your ball will be magnificent.
Simply magical.
- Yes, I know, you've done
a wonderful job, Lorenza.
Would you excuse me?
- [Elias] Sounds like World
War III going on down there.
- But Lorenza's
winning the battle.
Elias, there's something
I wanna tell you about.
- Something you lied
to me about.
Like about how much this
is really costing me.
[chuckling]
- I've never lied to you
about anything, ever.
- I know that.
- Sometimes I haven't told
you everything.
But I've never lied to you.
I just don't think there should
be any secrets between us.
I wanna tell you about
someone I used to know.
- If that someone is
Lefty Flint,
I know all about him
and it doesn't matter.
- How do you know?
- Well when you took so
long in deciding
whether you wanted to
marry me or not,
I figured there must
be another guy,
so I checked out my competition.
- You didn't have any.
- What did I know?
I just couldn't understand how
an incredible woman like you
was still unattached and
even remotely interested
in a guy like me.
- Oh, more than remotely.
You are the kindest,
most gentle loving man
I have ever known.
- You mean you didn't
marry me for my money?
- Money?
You didn't tell me
you had money.
[laughing]
- I'm afraid I can't get to
your file at the moment, Gus.
But I'll make the necessary
adjustment in your will,
eliminating the bequest
to your daughter
and leaving everything
to your ex-wife.
[ominous music]
- Bea, who is that man?
- Listen, Gus, you can come
back when I've prepared it
and we'll have it witnessed.
- What is going on here?
Are those the police?
- Federal ones.
And that man is one of our
junior lawyers, Byron Macumber.
- Oh?
What's he done?
- Something about an account
in a Swiss bank in the Bahamas.
Look for a very big
head to roll.
- [Gus] At Weldon and
Stanchfield?
- Oh goodness, no, not here.
Elias Renthall, inside trading.
- This is Gus Bailey,
is Mrs. Renthall there?
No.
When would she be back?
No, no, no, no message.
Thank you.
- Hello?
- Hi, it's me.
I know this might upset you
but is it too late to
cancel the Renthall's party?
- You have to work late
again tonight?
- [Bernie] No, I just don't
feel like going to a party.
- Well, why don't we just
go to the Renthall dinner
and leave before the
ball starts?
- I really don't want to,
Justine.
I thought maybe we could go
out, get something to eat.
Spend some time
together talking,
just you and me.
- I promised Ruby but
I'll call and explain.
Where do you wanna go,
O'Rourke's?
- That's too noisy.
- Well,
how about Clarence's?
I know you hate the place
but it'll be empty tonight.
Everybody that goes there
will be at the Renthall's.
- That's fine.
I'll meet you in an hour.
- Okay.
I love you.
- See you in a little while.
Bye.
[phone buzzing]
[crowd commotion]
[cameras snapping]
- Dinner for 30 and
everything matches.
And monogram.
- R is for Renthall, right?
Wrong, R is for Rothschild.
They bought it at the
estate sale.
[people chattering]
- Oh, Lil, I thought you
were gonna turn this down.
- Oh, I just came to see
the furniture.
Cora told me she bought
certain pieces
from a palace in Yugoslavia.
- Hello, Gus.
Mrs. Altemus, I'm so
happy that you came.
What a disappointment
that Justine
had to cancel at the
last minute.
- Cancel?
She had an appointment Dodo.
Well, I'm certain she
had her reasons.
- Do you have a minute?
We have to talk.
- Yes, of course.
Excuse us.
- [Woman] Hello, Faye!
- Oh, here's Faye Converse.
Would you excuse me?
Excuse me.
- Sorry I'm late
and thanks again for
doing this tonight.
- Oh, no thanks necessary.
It's a thrill to meet you
and an honor to contribute
to such a worthwhile cause.
Come, I'll show you
to your seat.
You'll be sitting next to Gus.
- Oh, I love Gus.
He's the reason I'm
here tonight.
- Well I have missed you.
What's wrong?
Tell me.
- I guess there's never
an easy way to say this.
- What is it, your work?
You're being transferred
to LA, aren't you?
- No.
I almost wish I was.
That might make this easier.
I...
I want a divorce.
- Why?
- Because you expect me
to be a faithful husband
and I'm not.
I never will be.
- Is there another woman?
- There will always be
another woman.
And that's the problem.
It's the way I've always been.
- Well is it me?
Have I done something wrong?
- No, no, you haven't done
anything wrong,
except maybe marry me.
I'm sorry if I hurt you.
I never meant to do that.
- And I never thought you would.
[dramatic music]
[sobbing]
[eerie music]
[crying]
[somber music]
[fire crackling]
- Are you sure you're up
to making dinner?
- I have to do things.
- You know, I've always
hated these chairs.
- Well then you can sell
them after I'm gone.
Drive mother insane.
Would you like a drink?
- I'd like some wine.
- Ugh.
I can do it, I have
to do things!
- I know.
But let me.
You see to the food,
I'll be bartender.
[ominous music]
- Juanito!
- Hubey.
- I think you better
get me to the hospital.
- Should we call your
mother or Justine?
- No, they're both at the
Renthall ball.
You wouldn't be able to
reach either of them.
- Who needs them anyway?
I'll take care of you.
Just like always.
Just like always,
I'll take care of you.
[people chattering]
[glass shattering]
- So sorry, darling.
- Oh, don't give it
another thought, no.
Only give me an excuse
to change into
another one of your
marvelous creations.
Excuse me.
- Splendid woman.
The Duchess couldn't
have handled that better.
- Gus, who the hell are
these people?
- Well, seated next to
you is Lord Biedermeyer,
the publisher.
- Oh, Lucerne, darling.
How are you?
- Faye.
- I didn't see you.
Probably thinks I'm blind drunk.
- And to his left is Mrs.
Laura Van Degan.
To her left is the
Earl of Castoria.
- Oh my God, he looks
like my third husband.
After the wake.
[laughing]
- And need I say any more
about this great star's career
and the 40 pictures
that she's made?
- 60, darling, not 40.
[laughing]
- Well, whatever, anyway.
Faye,
here's the check
towards the cure
for the pestilence
that is dwindling the ranks
of the artistic community.
- Thank you.
[applauding]
Oh my God.
Two million dollars.
Oh, Elias!
Thank you!
[applauding]
Thank you.
Whoa.
Friends,
we are an army
fighting an enemy that
has no allies.
However,
every army must enlist support,
financial and otherwise.
The Renthall's generosity
will aid in the struggle
in which we must all bear arms.
Therefore I shall dedicate the
rest of my life to this cause
and I shall forever
be indebted to his
charitable gentlemen,
this extraordinary humanitarian.
Oh, ladies and gentlemen,
Elias Renthall.
[applauding]
[ominous music]
- [Hubert] I can walk in.
Let me walk in.
- [Juanito] Don't worry, Hubey.
I'm with you.
Everything's gonna be fine.
[pleasant instrumental music]
- There can't be a tulip
left in all of Holland.
- These new people spend
more on flowers
than we used to
inherit in my day.
And all they want in return
is to be accepted by us.
- That'll never happen.
- Oh, it will.
Times change.
- Why don't we retire
upstairs for a cigar?
There's an elevator we can use.
- It will never happen.
- Look around, Lily, it
has happened.
[pleasant instrumental music]
[applauding]
- Isn't it magnificent?
Of course, they could have
never done it without me.
- You mean, without me, darling.
- I'd like nothing better
than to publish a biography
of the Van Degan family.
- Damn good cigar.
- After all, Ormonde,
your roots in this city
and this nation
can not be matched by
any other family.
- Good cigar.
- You're looking
particularly well these days.
- Nothing like a good cigar.
[coughing]
- Your father was governor,
you uncle, ambassador to France.
I think it's time for
important work.
Yes, yes indeed.
[coughing]
[applauding]
- Ruby?
Ruby, I have to talk to you.
- Yes, I know but can it wait,
Gus.
I gotta go change for
the First Lady.
- I didn't know she was coming.
- Yes, any minute.
We'll talk later, I promise.
[ominous music]
- I'll pick up the rest of
my stuff later in the week.
I'll call first.
I'm sorry, Justine.
- Stop staying you're sorry.
[menacing music]
Stop saying you're sorry!
Stop saying!
- I still want you.
[ominous music]
[upbeat instrumental music]
- Well, Lil, how about a dance?
- How kind, Mr. Renthall.
- I must have a word with you,
Elias.
- Not until I've convinced
Lil to drop the formalities.
[upbeat instrumental music]
- Bye, Justine.
- Goodbye.
[upbeat instrumental music]
- Elias, it's been so gay.
- I don't think that's quite
the right word anymore.
- No, it's a marvelous word
and I simply refuse
to give it up.
My friends all know that I
mean it in the old fashion way.
[laughing]
[applauding]
- He's dead.
- Oh, this is gonna
ruin Ruby's party.
- It'll certainly put a
damper on it.
- Did you tell anyone?
- Heavens no.
- All right, how about we
don't say a word
until after the first
lady leaves,
then we call an ambulance,
get him back down on the
freight elevator.
He was an old man, it's not
like it's a big tragedy.
- All right.
[triumphant music]
[applauding]
- [Woman] Just imagine the
First Lady at the Renthall's.
So lovely.
- [Man] Just wait,
there's more to come.
- I'll let you in on a
little secret.
I told Ruby to allow 45
minutes for waltzing.
- I've got a better one.
I heard that she was warn
not to come here tonight.
Apparently Elias is under
investigation by the SCC
for insider trading.
- Nonsense.
- Exactly what I said.
Even I wouldn't
print that rumor.
[pleasant instrumental music]
- Laurance!
Laurance, we're
looking for father.
He came up here over
an hour ago.
Now what's in that room?
- Edward the
Seventh's pool table.
It's off limits.
Elias doesn't want the
old felt stained.
- It's locked but maybe
he's in there.
Old felt wouldn't mean
a thing to him.
- Look through the key hole,
Dodo.
- Oh yes, he's asleep.
Right on the pool table.
It's too sweet.
- Well, I better get
back downstairs.
Janet will be
wondering where I am.
- What about father?
- Let him sleep.
- Well, Dodo, push the door!
Or get one of the
servants to open it.
Maybe there's something wrong.
[knocking]
[dramatic instrumental music]
[gasping]
[applauding]
- It's the most beautiful
thing I've ever seen.
[applauding]
[dramatic music]
- Divine.
[applauding]
[upbeat dance music]
[electrical fizzling]
[laughing]
- Oh.
Oh.
[electrical fizzling]
[whimpering]
- The lights.
The lights.
The lights!
Turn out the lights!
[electrical fizzling]
- Let me out of here.
[crowd commotion]
- I was talking about
the chandeliers, damn it!
Turn the lights back on!
- I can't find the switch.
- How could you have
let this happen?
- You're the one that
wanted all this!
[crowd commotion]
- Turn on the lights now!
[women whimpering]
- Don't worry, Faye,
I'll get you out of here.
- Thank God.
[crowd commotion]
- Father's dead.
Upstairs on the pool table.
- What?
[crowd commotion]
- The elevator's not working.
- Who are these
Renthall's anyway?
- Well he's going to be
arrested for inside trading.
Just read my column tomorrow.
- Are those sirens I hear?
- Is it a fire?
- [Woman] Fire?!
- Fire?
- [Man] Fire?
- Break the glass!
[crowd yelling]
Oh my God, we're trapped!
[somber music]
- But my clothes, Elias,
my trunks.
I could never get ready to
leave for Europe in three hours.
- So have your maids pack
them and ship them to you.
Europe is nothing but a
big store anyway.
- Is something bad gonna happen,
Elias?
- Why'd you ask that for?
- Don't play games with me!
You told me we were a team,
remember?
A team in good times
and in bad times.
Do we need money?
- No.
- I have all that
jewelry, we could sell it.
There's the money you
signed over to me.
You can have it back,
it's yours.
- I'm all right in the
money department
but thank you, Ruby, I'll
never forget that you offered!
- You're in some kind
of trouble, aren't you?
- Maybe.
- What did you do?
- What people have
done before me
and people will do
after I'm gone.
- Elias, tell me
what's going on!
- Mr. Augustus Bailey is here,
ma'am.
- Oh, Gus, I'm so glad
you're all right.
- I came to see if you were.
- Oh yeah, I'm terrific.
The ball was a disaster,
some of my guests are
in the hospital,
dead butterflies everywhere
and Elias is in some
kind of trouble.
- I wanted to tell you
about Elias last night.
- What?
- Have you ever heard of
someone named Byron Macumber?
- No, why?
- Well he was arrested
for leaking inside information.
It's in all the morning papers.
Elias was mentioned.
Not accused but the
implication is unmistakable.
- Well that's illegal.
- It would be pretty bad.
- I just wish he'd been
honest with me.
There weren't supposed to be
any more secrets between us.
We're leaving for Europe today.
Look, Gus, if you need me,
if anything comes up
about Lefty,
you just call Max Luby,
he'll know how to reach us.
- I don't want you to worry,
especially about Lefty.
You just take care of yourself.
- You're a good friend, Gus.
The only one I have.
I'll miss you.
- I'll miss you too.
[somber music]
- This is Mr. Renthall,
put me through.
Larry.
I just wanted you to know
that I'm leaving the
country for awhile.
In case you're sweating,
I never squeal on a friend.
- That's very gentlemanly
of you, Elias.
- Well that's what
people like us are.
Gents, right?
[pleasant music]
- Mrs. Renthall?
Would you care for
something to drink?
Coffee, tea.
- Oh no.
I've had enough bad
coffee and weak tea
at 30 thousand feet to
last me a lifetime.
Thanks anyway.
[somber music]
[dial tone buzzing]
[sighing]
- Well there's no answer
at the loft or the gallery
and the machine's not on.
- You look terrible.
Do you know that?
Simply terrible.
- Wow, I must be such a
disappointment to you, Mother.
How embarrassing to
have a daughter
who is so emotionally unstable.
- Justine, you don't have to
over dramatize the situation.
- Bernie's left me and it hurts!
Weren't you hurt when
father left you
or wasn't that proper behavior?
- Of course it hurt.
But in our family, personal
misfortunes are not fodder
for public consumption.
I dealt with it silently
and I kept my dignity.
- How are you gonna keep
your precious dignity
when Hubey dies?
Your son's personal
misfortune is AIDS.
Not a wounded ego.
- He does not have that disease,
Justine,
and I don't want you
saying that to anyone.
It's just not true!
Now you go and you pull
yourself together
and you meet me at Campbell's
to go over some arrangements
for your grandfather.
Whatever we do, it should
be extremely private.
- What else?
- Yes, Jane?
- A Mr. Juanito Perez
is on the phone.
- Who?
- Hubey's lover, Mother.
- You know how I loath
that kind of talk, Justine.
You answer it.
- Hello, Juanito, it's
Justine, what is it?
[ominous music]
- It was good of you, Gus,
to come by
and take me out for a
breath of air.
- It's nothing, Lil.
- Well the doctor prescribed
something for my nerves
but I honestly don't know
what's to become of me.
Father dying and now
Hubey's ill.
Cancer.
I don't know how I can
live without my son, Gus.
I mean, know one knows
really what we had.
I adored him.
I absolutely adored him.
Then no one knows more about
that kind of thing than you do.
- Give Hubey my best.
Tell him I'll come see
him tomorrow.
- Well, at least your
grandfather died
with a smile on his face.
- He always said that a good
cigar was better than sex.
[laughing]
- He was feebleminded,
wasn't he?
- Juanito, before my
mother arrives.
- Don't ask me to leave.
- No, never.
Would you take out your earring?
- But you gave it to me.
- I know
but the diamond is from my
mother's engagement ring.
She gave it to me
when she thought
I was going to marry
Violet Bastito.
[chuckling]
- Well she would never
recognize it now.
But if it makes you happy.
[groaning]
- Juanito,
this is my mother.
Mother,
this is Juanito Perez.
- Hello, how are you?
- Mrs. Altemus.
- My word.
The World Trade Center
just out the window.
Prettier angle from here than
from Uncle Laurance's boat.
- Yes, much.
By the way, we're going to
scatter your grandfather's ashes
from his boat on the north side.
He had his happiest days
there as a child.
- How is Dodo taking it?
- She's coping.
We're all coping.
- I'm gonna split.
I'll come back later.
Goodbye, Mrs. Altemus.
[door closing]
- I brought you some magazines
and I thought you'd
like that new book
on the Princesses of Monaco.
- Thank you.
- Well,
I'm going to let you sleep now.
[ominous music]
[pills clinking]
[dramatic music]
[groaning]
[ominous music]
[water sloshing]
- Maybe you oughta call Gus.
Ask him to do another
article about us.
Talk about our charity work.
Now might be a good time.
- Don't think Gus is
the kind of guy
who will do a puff piece
on us this moment in time.
- Why not?
You're friends, aren't you?
I called Max this morning.
I told him to sell the plane.
No sense on holding on to
anything that they can seize.
Rent is my new policy,
whether it's sails,
sores or screws.
- How do I fit into
that new policy?
Am I rented?
- I meant the plane.
I meant this boat.
I didn't mean you.
- Well I guess it's
better to rent something
than to steal it.
- What the hell does that mean?
- You're the brains around here,
why don't you figure it out?
Don't.
I promised myself if a
man ever laid
a hand on me again ever,
I'd kill him.
For your information, Gus
explained things to me.
Something you never
bothered to do.
- Explained what?
- About how you were
paying off Byron Macumber.
- He doesn't know about that.
Nobody knows about that.
- I spoke to Gus yesterday.
He told me Macumber was
just the well known tip
of the the well known iceberg.
Elias,
the SCC has enough
information to press charges.
- I'm gonna need you to help me,
Ruby.
We're a team, remember?
- What do you want me to do,
Elias?
- Swear to my lies, if it
comes to that.
- No.
No, Elias, not that.
No.
- Mother sends her love.
She'd come by but she just
can't cope after her last visit.
- It doesn't matter.
- Of course it matters, Hubey.
- Justine?
About my inheritance,
you don't need money and
certainly Mother doesn't.
So I'm leaving it
all to Juanito.
- You can't, Hubey.
- I never thought I'd hear
you say that, Justine.
- Leave him 500 thousand,
even a million,
but not the whole thing, Hubey?
Uncle Laurance will just
take it to court
and call it undo
influence by Juanito.
He'll use everything he
can to discredit him.
- I love Juanito
and that's what I'm going to do.
Besides, I hired my
own attorney.
One of our kind.
It won't be so easy for Uncle
Laurance to win this one.
- But all of your money, Hubey.
You could leave some to
medical research.
- I know but
there's just
something inside of me
that wants to get even
with Uncle Laurance.
All my life he made me
feel like I was worthless.
Juanito never made me
feel that way.
So what's with your
TV announcer?
Has mother insist
upon calling him?
- Well he's up some
tropical isle.
Wherever it is your go to get
a quickie divorce these days.
- Are you taking it okay?
- Well,
I loved him
and someday I hope I
can forget him.
[chuckling]
Yeah, won't be easy.
I'm pregnant.
- Does Bernie know?
- No and Mother doesn't either.
- Are you going to
have the baby?
- Oh yes
and I'm going to be a
wonderful mother.
[laughing]
And you know what I'm going to
name the baby if it's a boy?
Hubert Altemus Slatkin.
[somber music]
- It has a certain
insouciant charm.
[dramatic music]
- I love being your sister,
Hubey.
And I am so proud of you.
[dramatic music]
[pleasant organ music]
- [Lil] Wouldn't you
think they could afford
some heat in this church?
- [Justine] Yes, Mother.
- [Lil] The lilacs are lovely.
- [Justine] Yes, Mother,
thank you.
[speaking foreign language]
- Amen.
- What is that man doing here?
Who asked him?
- You don't have to be
invited to a funeral, Mother.
The church is a public place.
He has much right to be
here as we have.
- Juanito.
- That's the lover.
- Did you notice the
whole family ignored him?
- Well everyone knows
he died from.
- Even though the obit
in the times said cancer.
- I do not want that man
at my house afterward.
Thank God we'll never have
to hear from him again.
- Well that's what you think,
Mother.
Hubey left
everything to Juanito.
- What?!
- Will you please rise?
The Lord is my Shepard I
shall not want.
He maketh me to lie
down in green.
- Oh, there's Gus.
Make sure you ask him to
come by, Justine.
- Yes, Mother.
- No one, else.
I repeat, no one.
- Juanito.
- I know how hard this
must be for you.
It is for me too.
We both lost someone we love.
- Thank you for saying that,
Justine.
- How could you even
speak to that man?
- He was my brother's
friend and heir.
- Oh, it's ridiculous.
My dear son would never have
done anything like that.
It's not only the money but
those Charles the Tenths chairs
are from the Altemus
side of the family
via Aunt Willaby.
Well, Uncle Laurance will just
contest the will, that's all.
- It's what Hubey wanted,
Mother.
Can't you at least
respect his last wishes?
- And have that man think
he is one of us?
Never.
- Well Hubey was one of us.
- Yes, he was.
[dramatic music]
[somber music]
- I wanna go back to New York,
Elias.
I can't stand hiding like
this any longer.
I wanna go back and face the
music, noisy as it may be.
- You know what that means.
Not only did I got to jail
but I'd have to give back
everything I made and more.
Where does that leave you?
- I've been poor most of
my life, Elias.
I can take care of myself.
- I wanted to take care of you,
Ruby.
[somber music]
- You have to walk home
from parties, Gus?
Don't you have a limo or
a private station wagon?
- I don't even have a bicycle,
Bernie.
Sorry to hear about
your and Justine.
- I'm sorry too.
I'll miss Justine but she
deserved better.
- Are you going away?
- No, Justine's put the
apartment up for sale
and she wanted me to get
the rest of my junk out.
Network sent a car for me.
Hop in, I'll give you
a ride home.
- Thanks.
According to Dodo, Lil
wanted to sue Juanito.
Laurance thought it would be
bad publicity for the family,
so Lil dropped it.
- The Van Degans are
a tough act.
- They're all tough,
those people.
- Tell me about it.
Ormonde Van Degan dies
and they stash his body
so as to not spoil the
First Lady's entrance.
- Yeah, well, there's
a strong indifference
to death everywhere, Bernie.
- I know, Gus.
It's about time for Lefty Flint
to be getting out of jail,
isn't it?
- So I heard.
- How're you gonna handle that?
- I'm gonna kill him.
But first I'm gonna
call out his name
because I want him looking at me
and know who it was.
- You're not really gonna
kill him, Gus, are you?
- Of course I am.
- I must tell you, Gus,
I've heard that you've
started declining invitations.
To Maisie's and Violet's.
You don't return calls.
You don't write thank you notes.
I say this as a friend, Gus.
No one will invite you anymore.
- I don't care.
- You don't care?
- I've seen enough.
- Well is it because of
what's happened
to your friends, the Renthalls?
I know you were especially
fond of what's her name, Ruby.
- No, it's not that, Lil.
- They never would have
fit in, you know, Gus.
Money can not equate
with breading.
- Well that may be my problem,
Lil,
I've never cared enough
about either.
- You must come to the country.
Come to Violet's with
me this weekend.
- I'm sorry, I can't, I'm busy.
[people chattering]
- Poor Lil, she's had so
much tragedy in her life.
Make the most wonderful book.
- I suppose Gus will
write it someday.
Carefully changing all of our
names to protect the guilty.
How disappointing.
[somber music]
- This was Hubey's jacket.
- I always liked it.
It's smart.
- Why are you here,
Miss Altemus?
- You really shouldn't
smoke, it's bad for you.
- What do you want?
- I'll pay you, whatever
you ask, for these.
- They're not for sale,
they're my possessions.
- It's really quite
charming here.
But it's so cold.
What do you think you're doing?
Those are priceless chairs!
Stop that!
For God sake.
What?
Stop it.
Stop that! Stop that!
You just stop that!
They're priceless!
Stop that!
- Now I can tell you,
had you bothered to
speak civilly to me
or offered me a seat at
Hubey's funeral
or invited me back to your
home afterwards
or if your lawyers hadn't
returned my letters unopened
in which I offered to return
the family heirlooms
I inherited,
I would've give you
those chairs.
But now there's no way.
- Whatever did my
son see in you?
- Love, Mrs. Altemus.
Please leave, now.
[dramatic music]
[somber music]
- Senora,
it's getting cold, I
brought you this.
- Oh, Candalaria, thank you.
That's so sweet of you.
Sit here.
- Oh no, no, no, gracias,
senora, no.
- There's a woman over there.
She sleeps here every night.
I see her from my
bedroom window.
Later, when it gets dark,
I want her to give you this.
- Oh, no, no, no, that's
too much, senora.
- No, no it's not.
Imagine what she must
think every night,
looking up to where we live.
- Ruby?
Hello.
- Justine.
Oh, Justine, it is so
good to see you again.
- You too.
Well do you mind if I join you?
- I'd love it.
I just had an urge to sit here
and look up at my own house.
Too big, I've decided.
I was so sorry to hear
about your brother.
- Yeah, well, thank you
for the lovely flowers.
That was very thoughtful.
- Somehow flowers
never seem enough.
How is your mother handling it?
- Well, she'll recover,
she always does.
Just takes some of us a
little longer, that's all.
- Well at least you have
Bernie to help you through it.
- Well, Ruby,
he finally told me his
deep dark secret.
He wanted a divorce.
- Oh, Justine.
- But
one wonderful thing did
happen while we were together.
I'm gonna have a child.
- Oh, how wonderful.
- Thank you.
- Oh, I've always
wanted children.
A whole house full.
- Me too.
But I think one's just
fine for now.
[laughing]
Ruby,
I want you to know how
much I admire you.
No matter how hard Mother
and the rest of the old guard
try to keep you out,
you always fought back
and never let them win.
All my life I wanted to
stand up to them
and make them accept me
for who I was
but I just never
found the courage.
- You're wrong about me,
Justine.
Oh, I wanted them to like me
but for who I'd become,
not for who I really was.
But it's over.
Now I can go back to
being myself
whether they like it or not.
- Well you make it
sound so easy.
- No.
It isn't easy at all.
- Well, I guess I
better be going.
It was really very good
to see you again, Ruby.
- Oh, good luck, Justine.
- Thank you.
- With everything.
You stay in touch.
- You too.
- How very sweet, Gus.
- They're from my terrace.
- I'll go put them in water.
Can I get you
something to drink?
Ice tea?
- No thanks, I can't stay long.
I just came by to wish you luck
when Elias' trial starts.
If you need anything, I'll
be in the courtroom everyday.
- You're a good friend, Gus.
- So are you.
- [Ruby] Anything new with
Lefty or his girlfriend?
- No, nothing new.
Still behind bars.
Take care.
[crowd commotion]
- I've realized I've committed
a very serious crime.
- Don't say too much.
- I can only hope that by
accepting responsibility
for what I've done,
I can easy the anguish that
I have cause my friends,
my colleagues and most of all,
my wife.
- How much are you worth
at present, Mr. Renthall?
- [Male Reporter] Any
comment from Mrs. Renthall?
- [Lawyer] No comment!
- It's impossible for any
observer not to notice
the courage of Mrs. Renthall.
She is a model of rectitude
at her husband's side
every time he's
appeared in court.
Silent, supportive, her eyes
hidden behind dark glasses.
Betraying little emotion
but admirable strength,
Ruby Renthall must be anxiously
awaiting the court's ruling
as the case against her
husband, Elias Renthall,
draws to its final conclusion.
That wraps up this
evening's edition of Focus.
I'm Bernard Slatkin.
Goodnight.
[knocking]
- [Ruby] Come in.
- I just wanted to say
goodnight and thanks.
Whatever happens tomorrow,
happens.
- Why don't you stay in
here tonight?
- Really?
- Really.
[dramatic music]
- [Woman] Step back, please,
excuse me.
[crowd commotion]
- Your crime, Mr. Renthall,
is too serious
to forgive and forget.
It would be a terrible
precedent for this court
to allow you to go unpunished.
Breaking the law is
breaking the law.
I have taken into consideration
the work you have done
for the homeless
for the last few months.
Never the less, I feel it
is my duty to sentence you
to five years in
Allenwood Prison.
[crowd commotion]
- I'm not gonna keep the
apartment, Elias.
- Why don't you move back out
to Rhinelander for awhile?
- Well I was thinking of moving
out to the country house.
- You'll miss your friends
stuck way out there.
- Gus is the only friend I have.
I will miss him.
Maybe he'll come out for
a weekend now and then.
- Maybe you'll come and see
me for a weekend now and then.
- You know I will.
[crowd commotion]
- [Reporter] Right now!
Right now!
[crowd commotion]
- I'm not gonna get out.
- No, of course not.
I can't find the words to
tell you how sorry I am
that I put you through all this.
- I know you are.
- And you know that I love you,
don't you?
- I know that too.
[report smooching]
Elias,
you've been great to me,
I will never forget that.
- [Female Reporter]
Here he comes.
[crowd commotion]
[dramatic music]
[somber music]
- [PA Announcer] Dr.
Barron to radiology.
Dr. Barron to radiology.
- [Man] Hi, Justine.
- Hi, Billy.
Would anyone like me
to write them a letter
or call someone?
- Justine?
Justine?
Don't you recognize me?
Do I look that bad?
- Oh, Juanito.
I didn't know.
- How're you doing, Justine?
- Well, I'm counting the
days till my baby arrives
and I'm inviting you to
the christening right now.
[chuckling]
- You know those Charles
the Tenth chairs
your mother wanted back?
Well I left them out on
the sidewalk one at a time
for people who take junk
to furnish their places.
[laughing]
Eleven poor people have
some priceless chairs
if they only knew of it.
- Well Hubey would like that.
- Justine, about the
money he left me.
- Juanito, I don't
care about that.
That was Hubey's money and
he wanted you to have it.
- I had Hubey's lawyer
come down to the loft
before I got so sick.
Hubey's money is going
to a hospice.
Some place for people who have
nobody to take care of them.
- Juanito.
- Your brother was the only one
who ever loved me in
my whole life.
- Don't you have any family
that you want me to get
in touch with?
- There's only my aunt
but she doesn't want to
hear from me.
- I'm so sorry, Juanito.
- I'm afraid to die, Justine.
Hubey wasn't.
- That's because he had you.
And now you have me.
[dramatic music]
- I want you to have this.
Your father gave it
to your mother
and Hubey gave it to me.
I want you to give it
to your child
so he can give it to
someone who he loves.
- Thank you for loving
my brother, Juanito.
[dramatic music]
[ominous music]
[prisoner commotion]
[somber music]
[ominous music]
- I can't bear that he's out.
I can't bear that he
should be happy.
- Sometimes I wonder why
they ever searched us
when we entered that courtroom.
Would've been so easy.
- What would've been so easy?
- Pow.
- I'm gonna call
Detective Jackson.
Ever since that letter, I know
that bastard's coming here.
I want a guard put
on this house.
- I don't want you to worry,
Peach.
He'll never come here.
I'm gonna take care
of everything.
- The geraniums are dying.
You can hardly kill a geranium.
Not enough tender loving care,
I suppose.
Not enough TLC.
- So long.
- You sound like you're
going on a trip.
- No.
- Gus,
are you all right?
- Goodbye, Peach.
[ominous music]
[knocking]
- [Marguerite] Who is it?
- Gus Bailey.
- Just go away, Mr. Bailey.
- Not until I see Lefty.
[ominous music]
- I should've listened to you,
Mr. Bailey.
You were just trying to help me.
But I didn't want to hear.
- Oh my God.
I've gotta get you to an
emergency room.
- I'll be okay.
He used me, you know,
just to have a place to
crash for awhile
when he got out of prison.
I guess I got off easy.
- Where is he?
- He left about half
an hour ago.
- You don't know where he went?
- Wherever Ruby Renthall is,
I guess.
Ever since she
testified against him,
she's all he ever talks about.
- I've gotta use your phone.
- Sure.
- Hello?
- Hello, Candalaria, this
is Gus Bailey.
- Mrs. Renthall is not at home.
She went to the city
and I don't think she'll
be back tonight.
- Is she at the Rhinelander?
- I don't know, Mr. Bailey.
- Well if you talk to her,
tell her Mr. Flint has left town
and may be coming to see her.
Tell her to be careful.
Very careful!
- [Candalaria] Yes, sir.
I'll tell her.
Goodbye.
[crowd commotion]
- The fabulous paintings
the Renthall's collected
in record time
are now being disposed
of in even less time
inside the prestigious Charles
and Charles Auction House.
And the vast Renthall
apartment has been bought by
an anonymous speculator
who plans to divide it
into three smaller dwellings.
[dramatic music]
[ominous music]
- Taxi!
[thudding]
[eerie music]
[people chattering]
[ominous music]
- Nice to see you again, Mrs.
Renthall.
- It's nice to see you
again too, Mike.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Think maybe I could take one
last look at our old apartment?
I know it's late and it's
probably not allowed but
do you think, maybe?
- Well, I'm not supposed
to but sure, why not?
The electricity's still on
and you can take a good
long look around the place.
Though you may not
recognize it much anymore.
- [Ruby] Thank you, Mike.
- Now come with me.
I'll have to let you
in upstairs.
[ominous music]
- Here , let me give you a
hand with that.
Looks like you could use a hand.
- Oh, thank you very much.
[keys jingling]
Thank you again, young man.
- I'd be happy to carry them
to the elevator for you,
if you want.
- Oh, no, there's no need.
- Whatever you say.
- Oh.
Well, if you wouldn't
mind, just to the elevator.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
[ominous music]
[somber music]
[thudding]
- Mike?
[eerie music]
[pleasant instrumental music]
[ominous music]
- Imagine having your
own ballroom.
You did good, Ruby,
for a stewardess.
- Lefty.
What do you want?
- Your forgiveness, of course.
I forgave you for testifying
at my parol hearing
and now it's your
turn to forgive.
[ominous music]
I want to hear you say it, Ruby.
And if you don't,
I'll make you scream it!
[ominous music]
- I laughed at my husband
when he gave me this.
He said to me over
and over again,
"There are crazy
people in the world
"who are out to get
people like us."
A smart man, my husband.
[chuckling]
- Not so smart, he went and
wound up in jail just like me.
- There's one big difference.
He can pay back the money.
You can never give back
the life you took.
Don't you come another step
near me, you son of a bitch.
- Hold it, Lefty.
You can't imagine how
long I've waited for this.
- I paid my dept, Bailey.
- You haven't begun to pay.
An eye for an eye.
Isn't that what the Bible says?
- It also preaches forgiveness.
- I never got to that part.
- Killing me will not
bring Becky back.
- I never thought it would.
[ominous music]
[gun clicking]
- Gus!
[booming]
[dramatic music]
- You're right.
You bastard.
Killing you would never
bring her back.
- [Gus Voiceover] Dear Peach.
It's rather ironic I should
be sent to Vacaville Prison
where Lefty Flint, I am
pleased to say,
is remembered without affection.
For the first time in
years I feel calm.
Lefty is no longer in
my thoughts.
All those nights in New York
when I was talking
about one thing
and thinking another.
How strange life is.
The way I planned it, I'd
probably be here 20 years
for murdering Lefty Flint.
Instead, I'm here for
wanting to kill him.
"Intent to kill,"
they called it.
But you know something, Peach,
at the very end, when
he came at me,
even then I knew I
couldn't kill him.
Life never is the way
you imagined it to be.
The good and the bad.
You know what I think?
I think it's possible to
be happy again.
Even here.
With love, Gus.
- I told you, you don't need
to keep coming back here, Ruby.
- You're always telling
me that and I come anyway.
Do you need anything?
- No.
This place isn't the
Rhinelander but I'm okay.
Now how about you?
I told Max to look out for you.
If you need anything,
anything at all.
- I'm fine, Elias.
I told you, I can take
care of myself.
- You always could, Ruby.
Well,
I gotta go back inside.
I love you, Ruby.
- I love you too.
- [Max] How's he doing?
- [Ruby] He seems fine.
- [Max] Elias wants you to
be happy, Ruby.
It's all he's ever wanted.
- I know, Max.
I want that for him too.
I just don't need
the same things
Elias needs to be happy anymore.
But I won't get a divorce.
Not until he's released.
He's been too good to me.
I owe him at least that.
- I understand.
- Paris is over, my dear.
Hundreds and hundreds of
dollars for one room at the Ritz
and not even suite.
And those ghastly common women
with those horrid little dogs
having lunch at the Rally Plaza.
And Arabs everywhere.
And the clothes are a disaster.
Skirts up to here.
It's just ridiculous.
- Well I have some news for you,
mother.
- Getting married again?
If you want to make your
mother really happy,
that's what she wants to hear.
- No, I'm not.
I've been asked to be the
executive head
at the Hubert Altemus
Junior Hospice.
- Well I believe that money
should've been given
anonymously,
without anyone's name
being exploited.
Is that your news?
- Yes it is.
- Well how long will
this Florence Nightingale
performance of yours go on?
- As long as I'm needed.
- Well what about your baby?
Your child?
- My child has a name, Mother.
He's six month old and
you've never called him
anything but "your child,"
never Hubey.
- That's not a very attractive
tone of voice, Justine!
Parker, I think we'll just
have coffee in the living room
and tell Gertie the
eggplant souffle was yummy.
- Mother, I just wish you
would try to understand.
All my life I've been identified
as Laurance Van Degan's niece
or Mrs. Van Degan Altemus'
daughter.
Oh, or even worse, the
Van Degan heiress,
as Dolly always refers
to me in her column.
- And now you're just
Justine Slatkin.
- Yes, Mother, yes.
Without even that terrible word
"socialite" in front of it.
- Why can't they call it
the "Juanito whatever
his name was Hospice?"
- Goodbye, Mother.
- You're not staying for coffee?
- No, I'm not
staying for coffee.
I'm going home to my son.
To Hubey.
[somber music]
- You love me, don't you?
You love me.
[somber music]
[crying]
[knocking]
- Come on in, it's open.
- Why didn't you tell
me you were out?
I had to read about your release
in Dolly Dulongpre's column,
thanks a lot.
- Good to see you again, Ruby.
- Same here.
What's all this?
- I'm selling the
apartment, I'm moving on.
- Where are you going?
- Oh, I don't know.
A block or two away.
Maybe.
Maybe out of New York.
I haven't decided.
Why don't you and I
talk outside?
I can't tell you how good it
feels to be alive and free.
I was lucky to get out
in nine months.
Good behavior.
How is Elias doing?
- As well as can be expected.
Why didn't you answer any
of my letters?
- Well, you had enough
on your mind.
Didn't want you to
worry about me.
- You saved my life, Gus.
- Yeah and my own too, I guess.
- That's what Becky
would have wanted.
- I know.
I'm glad it's over.
- So am I.
Have you seen or heard
from any of the old crowd?
[chuckling]
- Hardly.
What about you?
- Oh heavens, no.
- I tell you what,
why don't we go over
to Clarence's
and see what happens?
[laughing]
- But I thought Elias as
bared from trading for life.
- That's not to say
he can't get somebody
else to trade for him.
Max Luby, for instance,
with Elias calling the shots.
- I understand.
- But let's talk about you.
I hear you been keeping diaries.
You know, the public loves to
read about people like you.
- Ever since the dreadful
Stock Market crash,
no one is buying odd.
Which, of course, my dears,
everyone knows is the
most sensible investment.
- I heard Laurance Van
Degan knew the Stock Market
was going to crash
because Elias Renthall
called him from
prison and told him
to get out of the
market a week ago.
- Wish he called me.
- Oh my dear word.
Can you believe who just
walked into this restaurant?
[people chattering]
- Oh, I love all this drama.
So much better than television.
- [Ruby] So tell me, Gus,
did you make any new
friends in jail?
Elias has.
- No friends but I wrote a book.
- [Ruby] I always
said you would.
- Oh, Maisie.
- Gus Bailey.
- You know Ruby.
- Hello, how are you?
- How are you?
Oh, it's been ages.
- Nine months, two days,
14 hours and 10 seconds.
Prison life teaches you
to keep track of time.
[laughing]
- Gus,
I'm having a small
dinner party on Thursday.
I'd love you to come.
- I can't on Thursday.
- Well then come to the
country for the weekend.
- I can't this weekend.
- I suppose it must be difficult
to meld back into society
after being in,
after being away.
See you.
- You did that well.
- I thought a lot
about these people
and I realized all the
money in the world
can't protect anyone from
tragedy and heartbreak.
And yet, you look at them,
you think they didn't
have a care.
They cover their
feelings so well.
But I can't hide in their
world anymore.
I have to start living
my life again.
- Me too.
- Welcome back, Gus.
- Hello, Jake.
- It's wonderful to see you,
Ruby.
- Thanks, Jake.
Listen, Jake, we're not staying.
- That's just what I
was gonna say.
[pleasant music]
- [Woman] Of all the nerve.
Who do they think they are?
[dramatic music]
- Taxi!
Can I drop you somewhere?
So long, Ruby.
- Goodbye, Gus.
- You gonna be okay?
- Sure.
And you?
- You know what they say
about people like us?
- [Gus] What?
- That we're survivors.
- Luck.
- Same.
[dramatic music]
[pleasant music]
[somber music]