STEEL HEART
Thanks.
- You'll like my friends. - Nice car.
- Where are we going? - To the marina.
Cut it out.
Sindi!
Forget her, Steve. Let's go back inside.
- What is going on? - We'll meet a friend of mine.
Who is this? Let me! Richard ...
What is this?
Martial arts are an ideology to develop human potential.
Respect truth and justice
Respect the rights of the individual
And develop self-confidence in body and soul.
Martial arts codes:
1: Be loyal to your country. 2: Listen to your parents.
3: Defend honor and justice. 4: Respect friendship.
5: Courage. He never withdraws from the fight.
Thank you gentlemen.
You can relax, people. Today is a special day.
Sergeant Kim is a five-year veteran of this department
He served honorably and deserves the respect of his colleagues.
His loyalty, courage and sense of responsibility are well known.
He developed a training program to fight
To better prepare our officers.
His dedication earned him respect in the Los Angeles department.
Sergeant Kim, you are valuable equipment to this department
and it is my pleasure to promote you to lieutenant. Congratulations.
Come here, John!
I was born and raised in Korea,
But my heart belongs to this great country. Thank you.
John, come to my office. I have something to tell you.
Your old partner is dead, John.
Good news! I got the job. I start on Sunday.
- Seriously? - Yes. I'm moving to Portland.
Portland police found him with broken arms and bullets.
He must have made one hell of a resistance.
His last task was to find missing persons, most of them young girls.
Gather as much information as you can.
If you find out what happened to the missing, you'll find out who killed Douglas.
I'm sorry about this, John. I know you were best friends.
I'll call the Portland Police Captain and tell him you're coming.
- What can I get you? - Sandwich and a glass of ice water.
A gift with your next shipment. I will not disappoint you.
You will be pleasantly surprised. She is beautiful.
She's blonde.
I appreciate your work.
I like it when things go like clockwork.
I hate chaos.
She was lying down.
She screamed as I strangled her.
She lay down and threw her Friday.
She was lying there on her back and I was pushing her Friday.
I looked down and said, "Do you have a name, darling?"
See ...
What do you think?
Let me go!
Let's have fun baby.
You know you want it.
Do you want to work on me?
It will be great.
Come on, baby.
Let me go!
Aren't you nice?
Get lost, man.
- Or get in line! - Are you talking to me?
I'll take your sports car and drive to Acapulco.
Go and get him, Spike.
I'll blow you away, you son of a bitch!
- John Kim ... - Murder of Sergeant Douglas.
I'll take over the Coplands. Captain Kronos.
All of us are currently looking for the killer of a police officer.
And the missing persons? Is there anything new about it?
That. Cindy Kane.
- The same day Douglas was killed. - Yes. Her boyfriend reported her missing.
Thank you, Captain.
- You're from LA, Hollywood? - I'm trying to find Cindy Kane.
- What do you know about her? - She was my girlfriend.
But she got mad at me and left with some rich jerk.
- Can you describe him? - I don't remember that much that night.
I was too drunk. I remember he had a nice car.
- Where was the last time you saw them? - Nightclub. Girls go out there.
Why is an LA cop interested in all this?
- Can you show me that club? - Of course.
Here, right.
She looked at me as if I didn't exist. Then she jumped into the Mercedes.
Hej, Darene, Felix.
Did you see that jerk who took Cindy away?
- What are you doing? Stop it! - Let's go.
Who is he?
Get out of here.
You have a call, Mr.
John Kim from LA is here, investigating Douglas' murder.
I understand. Thanks.
John Kim?
Let's check out this John Kim.
- What's your name? - Stephen.
- Not you. You're Cindy's boyfriend. - John Kim.
I could have taken care of that myself, John Kim.
- How does she know Cindy Kane? - She's Cindy's dance instructor.
Her studio is located at 4 and Alder.
That's great. Great.
Feet back.
Good. Use your hips.
Great, Tina.
Smile, girls. Energy!
Irena, take over.
All right, keep up, girls. Smile!
- How can I help you? - I'm looking for Cindy Kane.
- Why? - She is missing.
Now that I think about it, I haven't seen her in a long time. She hasn't been here in a long time.
- When was the last time you saw her? - A few weeks ago.
Can you tell me something about her?
A typical tragic dance story.
She was very talented.
Then she got lazy, started playing in a nightclub and was looking for a rich man.
I know, some people don't have self-esteem.
I play because I like it. I don't know why anyone would work for another reason?
But again, I'm not Cindy Kane. I like to play.
That is almost the most important thing in my life.
What is the most important thing in your life?
Mommy!
- This is the most important thing, me and Erika. - Hi, how are you?
You were great last night, John. Do you dance?
Not in public.
I'll ask the other girls if they know anything about Cindy.
You lost him? I should tell Bolo to cut off your neck.
I'll give you another chance. Kill him.
Good news! I got the job. I'll start in a week.
I don't want to leave LA, but Portland is better for raising a family.
I'll see you. Come visit us. We can go fishing. What do you say?
Douglas and I always drank tequila. He was a good man.
- We got drunk here on several occasions. - He never got drunk in LA.
- Take care. - Okay.
- Let's go now. - Quinn, let me handle him.
I heard it got nasty there.
- Are you OK? - Yes I am.
- How about lunch tomorrow? My treat.
- No, I have to do something. - In Big Buster, you'll be there.
No, I won't.
Do you have a wife?
Very subtle.
- Your coffee. - Thanks, Jamie.
- I just went to your hotel. - Sit down, Steve.
I got this today from Cindy. Break up with me.
- Through a letter? - Close.
Is this Cindy's handwriting?
- I don't know, I didn't see it written. - Steve, you? - I haven't seen her either.
"I'll be back, but for now I want to get away from everyone."
Strange.
How far is Saint Peters?
- It's in the southeast? - Yes, about 15 km from here.
I have to go.
- Thanks for joining us. - Do you have children? - Erika.
- Christy. - Yes. - Looks like I'm free again.
Chip, can you take Erica to the studio, please?
My name is Stephen!
Shit!
Go, go!
Go faster!
Come on!
Come on! Shit!
We lose them.
Follow him!
Find him.
Blake, you go that way. Hollis, you check there.
Be careful.
- What are you doing here? - I came to warn you.
You're late. Are you OK?
- I am angry. - Me too. Because of you!
- So arrest me! - Get out of here. - I'm in this too. I'm going with you.
- No way! - I need you. I know this terrain.
- Follow me then. - I can't, the car won't start.
- Hell with the car, it'll track you down. - Then think of something.
That's great.
Now you owe me a car!
Did you hear me?
- John, you're hurt. - Nothing serious. It's just blood.
I drive.
Shit!
I have you now.
Did you call in his room?
А оnda "A".
Vidiš, "Еrikа". To je savršeno.
No, I didn't see her. Try Christie's house.
How's it going?
Someone obviously doesn't want you to find Cindy Kane.
- There's more to it than that. - Really? What?
What? Come on, tell me.
I had a partner ...
Forget it.
I will.
Well, I'm your partner now.
You have to tell me everything.
A friend of mine died while working on a missing persons case.
Cindy Kane disappeared the same day Douglas was killed.
- Coincidence? - I'll know when I find her.
- Simon Martine. - Sir?
- Are you happy with your job here? - Yes sir.
So you admit that every mistake here is a consequence of your mistakes? - Sir?
- Where are Blake and Hollis? - They're dead, sir.
- You saw when they died. - Yes sir.
- And your target? - I hit him, sir.
So the target is terminated? And?
- I'm sure I hit him. - Is John Kim dead or not?
I'm not sure.
You left the scene without checking to see if he was dead.
Blake and Hollis were loyal employees.
Their blood screams for revenge.
Hit it, Bolo.
Back!
My career is pretty great.
I danced in New York.
In Chicago.
I got pregnant with Eric and put everything on hold.
I wanted to come back after a year, but ...
Her father is gone.
He got the lead role in the dance troupe.
So I started to surrender.
It's nice to see how these girls are getting better.
But sometimes I find it hard to work on a book
So I go to nightclubs and just relax.
There is nothing wrong with that.
It is sad that her father never saw her.
It is a pity.
Yes, I think so too.
Speaking of Erika ... I have to go.
Erika, let's go home. I know you're tired.
- Good night, ladies. - Good night.
Hey, tell John Kim I found the man who took Cindy away. - Cindy Kane?
I would have beaten him, but he was among friends. Enough of them.
- And the rich man was there. - Milversted? - Yes.
I'll give him a message if he shows up.
Tell him I work at Hot Flash Pizza House tonight.
It's time for a hot meal.
Yes, I understand.
Bolo, would you like to exercise a little?
- Hey, John! Steve was looking for you. - What did he want?
I do not know. It sounded important.
He said look for him at the Hot Flash Pizza Company.
Wait.
John?
I'm glad to see you too.
Did you find out what Steve wanted?
He was killed.
But why would anyone want to kill Steve?
You have to take Erica and hide for a few days.
- Where are you going? - It's time to fight back.
- Then I'll go with you. - This is not your job. Stay away from this.
I know where you're going. And this applies to me as well.
I want a beer! Open up!
- Open the door, give me a beer! - Get out of here!
Mr. Kim ...
What the hell are you doing here?
You bastard!
Thank you, buddy.
He is a valuable opponent.
I will make a donation to your charity. In your name, of course.
Usual contribution?
It is always a pleasure to do business with you.
- Take care of Eric. - Why? What are you going to do?
Christie? What are you doing here?
I have a situation here.
I think Milversted will start now.
Call when you find out where he took the girl.
Be ready to help me.
I'll be in the car. The switchboard will connect you with 3-21.
This is 6743.
Give me Milversted.
He broke you. He has a girlfriend at the club who is looking for Richard.
Yes, I know, they're here.
He wants to play. Don't worry, they're not going anywhere.
Take care of him.
Are you up for a dance?
I think you'll like my place.
Yes, me too. Let's get.
- Hey. - We haven't seen each other in a long time.
Too bad you've come a long way in this game. We'll take good care of your girlfriend.
Bonus to whoever kills him.
Goodbye, Mr. Kim.
Your queen's turn, take care of him.
Good evening, Christy.
There are people who know where I am!
Mr. Kim? He will not join you.
Don't bet on that, you son of a bitch!
Let's say he's terribly busy.
Take them away.
Central calls 3-21.
- Wait for the call. - I am waiting.
- Captain? - John?
- I found the man who kidnapped Cindy. - Where?
Throw the gun out the window.
Get out!
Jesus, John ...
Did he pay you or does Milversted give you a commission from selling girls?
What the hell are you talking about?
Every time I went after him, his men showed up to stop me.
They knew when I was looking and where I was going.
I never suspected one of ours until tonight.
I never killed - Keep going! I just informed them. Bolo killed them.
Did he kill Douglas too?
Douglas was a good cop, but he didn't want to hear my warnings.
- And Stephen? - You got him involved!
How many girls did Milversted send over?
- How much? - Four!
I should break your spine. Where did they take the girls?
They took them out of the country. In Asia. In the Middle East.
As a gift. Use your imagination!
- What do you get? Money? - He could have killed me if he wanted to.
Your time is running out, Captain. I'll ask you one more time.
Where did they take Christie?
- Pierre 6! - You have a coward's heart.
I'll be back for you.
- Say hello to the instructor. - Christy?
- What did you do to her? - Nothing. Heroin took care of her appearance.
Why are you so upset?
Thousands of them in this city would sell their mothers for good heroin.
It's very expensive, but Cindy knows I'm generous.
He does beautiful things for her.
Come on, Christy first.
Check it out.
You're out of luck today!
Showtime!
John ...
Sindi!
Wait here. I'll be right back.
The next day, John returned to Los Angeles.
His partner is dead, as is poor Steve.
But again, there was reason to celebrate.
Cindy is free, and Milverstad's dirty organization is destroyed.
This adventure brought us very close.
And John suggests that dance school in LA is not such a bad idea.
He himself taught her a few dance steps and joined my school. translation by ear: ranko janković