[upbeat piano music]
♪ Build me a house ♪
♪ Where I can live in,
build me a house ♪
♪ Where I can stay ♪
♪
♪ I want to see the water ♪
♪ See the water fall,
I long to see the water ♪
♪ See the water fall ♪
♪ Build me a house ♪
♪ Where I can live in ♪
♪ Where I can stay ♪
♪
♪ Stone, bricks and walls ♪
♪ A room with a view ♪
♪
♪ Build me a house ♪
♪ Where I can live in ♪
♪ Where I can stay ♪
♪ In a new town ♪
♪ A place of my own ♪
♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ Stone, bricks and walls ♪
♪ A room with a view ♪
♪ See the waterfall ♪
[city din]
[motor rumbling]
[doorbell ringing]
- What?
- Nothing.
You said you weren't
going to drink tonight anyways.
- We can go get something else.
- We already rang the doorbell.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
[door opening]
- Hey!
- Hi!
Welcome.
[soft piano music]
[door closing]
[male guest]
Thanks for having us.
[homeowner] Of course.
Oh, your place is amazing,
Where did you get
all this art?
- We just got back from India.
- Really?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
The rest is
from Africa, Bali.
- Some pieces from China.
- Mark, look at this stuff.
I'm gonna dropped
this off in the kitchen.
Hi!
Oh, hugs are okay!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I didn't know.
[birds tweeting]
♪
- What are you drinking?
- We have wine, whiskey.
I'll have whiskey.
Um... I'll... I'm going to
hold off for now.
Come on.
Have a drink.
I have this scotch.
We just got back from Scotland.
Small batch. Only a couple
of hundred bottles.
I don't even want to tell you
how much we paid for it.
- How much?
- $100 a bottle.
[laughing]
I'll just have some
wine if that's okay.
Okay, coming right up.
Hmm.
♪
[female guest]
We got you something else.
You didn't have to!
Oh!
It's very nice.
Thank you.
Here we go.
Look at what
Beth and Mark brought us.
Oh.
Very cool.
Thank you.
We should put it up.
Yeah, let's find a spot.
How are the drinks?
The whiskey's good.
Peaty.
Very peaty.
That is a
Chateau Pontet-Canet.
- I hope you like Bordeaux.
- [Mark] Yeah, I love it.
- You do?
- Yeah, the city and the wine.
Have you been?
[Mark] Yeah, actually, when
I was studying in college...
- I've got a new job.
- Oh, you left the store.
- Her boss was a creep.
- It's complicated.
[Mark] Should you...
[Beth] Mark thinks
I drink too much.
What the hell?
I just got a new job.
[Mark] What the hell?
[Beth] This is the one
this is the one from China.
[Mark] Yeah, look at the
little gold flecks underneath.
Is there something?
It looks like
- there's something in there.
- There's like a hinge here.
- I should like... Careful.
- I don't want to break it.
- Oh, it's a...
- It's a TV. Of course.
Jesus, they have
cable and Apple TV.
[Mark] How do they watch it.
None of the furniture faces...
What do you think?
- How's dinner coming?
- [Beth] What is for dinner?
I thought you'd never ask.
Should I tell them?
I have prepared an exquisite
meal for you this evening?
Organic pork tenderloin with
chartreuse, compressed peaches,
dry melted leeks, chanterelle
mushrooms with golden fig
and seared foie gras with
lavender pork reduction
of the chef's own divining.
Wow.
Dave knows a lot
about food now.
- He's an excellent cook.
- Chef.
Excellent chef.
You should see his knives.
You know, I really should have
told you beforehand,
but I'm not eating gluten now.
- You're not?
- I hope that's okay.
When did you stop
eating gluten?
This morning.
You had a pastry
for breakfast.
I know after that
I did not feel well.
I can put the
bread on the side.
[doorbell ringing]
- Oh, that must be Charlie.
- I'll get it.
Hi, can I help you?
Yeah,
I'm here for the party.
Yeah... You must be one
of Annie's friends.
Yeah. Annie,
I am a friend of Annie.
[Dave] Yeah, of course.
Come in. Sorry about that.
I'll be fine,
one cheat day won't kill me.
It's your first day.
Annie's on her way,
right babe?
Oh yeah, yeah.
Are you a friend?
- I'm a friend of Annie's.
- Irene.
- [stranger] Paul.
- Mark.
- Paul.
- [Beth] Beth.
Paul.
- Oh, and I'm Dave.
- I'm Paul.
- I'm a friend of Annie's.
- Great.
She's running behind.
She'll be here soon.
Paul, can I get you a drink?
I might have a
beer in the fridge?
- Well, how about some wine?
- Yeah. Wine, sure.
- I have red wine.
- Just red?
Oh, we have some white too.
Oh, I meant cabernet, merlot?
Sorry.
Actually, it's a Bordeaux.
It's very tasty.
- Well, I'll try some of that.
- Great. Anybody else?
I'll give you a hand.
Please.
So, Paul,
what is it that you do?
I'm an electrician.
[Beth] Oh, what's that like?
I like it, all right.
It's actually very
trendy right now.
I'm writing a piece about
how people are returning
to more hands on work.
How did you get into that?
So glad we found another couple
who do this kind of thing with.
You know, it's hard to
find the right kind of people.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Hey, I hope Beth
can eat everything.
Oh, don't worry about that.
She'll have a new diet
by the time we're done in here.
- How are you guys, by the way?
- You know, we are...
We're a lot better lately.
- [Dave] Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
We started couples counseling.
Well, you seem a lot happier.
[Mark]
How's your work going?
Let me show you my knives.
Uh... yeah.
- Oh yeah.
- Got a full set.
Paring, peeling,
cheese, bread,
fillet, carving, cleaver.
[laughing]
- Cuts right through the bone.
- [Mark] Yeah, wow.
Yeah, cool stuff.
I'm upgrading, though.
We know this place on Randolph,
where all the shots in
Chicago get their knives.
Go ahead, take it up.
Feel the blade.
Go ahead.
- Just side to side sharp, huh?
- [Mark] Yeah, very sharp.
It's the same brand
Grant Achatz uses, Global.
- Oh, wow, the guy from...
- Alinea, Next.
Yeah, he's a fucking legend.
Told you it's sharp.
Were you always passionate
about electricity?
I never thought
about it that way.
Do you own your own
business or...?
Yeah, I have a small company.
I have a few guys who work
for me. My son helps out.
Okay,
so you're an entrepreneur.
Paul, here you go.
That is a Chateau
Pontet-Canet.
Hmm. It's good.
- It is, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Mark, Paul's an electrician.
Oh, well, yeah.
I'm... half Hispanic, so.
Oh, nice.
We can all use another drink.
Hmm.
[Mark] I have this new app
that makes for organizing
calls so much easier.
Oh, Dave is
addicted to podcasts.
I do spend a lot of time
in the kitchen.
What's the one
we had on in the car?
- Serial?
- No.
Oh, Serial is
fucking amazing, though.
How have you guys
not heard of that?
- It's almost as good as TV.
- Wow.
I just started listening to
this new one. It is so funny.
- Which one?
- It's these two guys,
and they do this social
experiment where they
- stop masturbating for a year.
- Mark!
What about you, Paul?
Do you listen to a podcast?
Yeah, no, I like to
listen to podcasts.
Hmm. Like what?
History mostly.
I like Hardcore History.
Oh, I've heard that was good.
And politics, I like to
listen to political podcasts.
- Oh, are you like...
- Oh, I almost forgot.
Paul, I hope you're hungry
because I have prepared
an exquisite meal for, well,
for everyone this evening.
Organic pork tenderloin
locally sourced
and responsibly raised,
of course, chartreuse
compressed peaches,
dry melted leeks,
chanterelle
mushrooms resting on
an ethereal bed of golden figs,
seared foie gras
and a lavender pork reduction
of the chef's own divining.
It's a meal that moves
the earth when you eat it.
To paraphrase Hemingway
in For Whom the Bell Tolls.
- Robert and Maria.
- Yes! He gets it!
You get it.
Yeah, they made love
and the earth moved.
Oh, did you,
did you read that in college?
No, just for myself.
Have you read
anything good lately?
Yeah, I just finished
The Brothers Karamazov.
I love the Brothers Karamazov.
Russian stuff depresses me.
Wasn't there a
show based on that?
I don't think so.
No, it's a novel by Dostoevsky.
What am I thinking of? The
Russian show you were watching?
The Americans?
Oh my God.
The finale.
I'm sorry.
I don't like
reading subtitles.
[Dave]
She jumps ahead of me.
- He travels for work.
- You're in logistics, right?
That's not who I am.
Oh, what about, have you guys
seen the show Master of None.
- [Mark] That's the one with...
- Aziz Ansari.
- [Dave] He's great.
- God, have you seen it?
[Beth] I've heard that
it was great. But then
Aziz became problematic.
So true. I mean,
there's so many good shows
on TV these days.
- I know!
- It's like... It's...
[enchanting music]
[laughing]
[doorbell ringing]
Excuse me.
- [Dave] Hey, stranger.
- Hi!
- [Dave] How are you?
- Good, good.
- You look great.
- Oh yeah, you too.
I'm actually working
on a piece about
non-traditional
roles in child rearing.
Oh, you mean like a homosexual?
- Mark!
- What? No, I didn't...
That's... You know
what I meant. Right?
Well, more couples are deciding
to have kids
without getting married.
And there's an interesting
shift in gender roles as well.
Mark and I were just
talking about this for us.
Are you and Dave
planning on having kids?
No,
we don't want to have kids.
- Oh, why not?
- It's not -
It's not that
I don't like kids.
It's just to not have
all the time, you know?
To visit when you
guys have kids,
- I'll babysit.
- Dave doesn't want them either?
No, he doesn't, actually, we...
I don't know.
It's complicated.
Well, Mark and I
are going to have a baby.
Oh, are you?
That's wonderful.
- Congratulations.
- Yeah, we're going with a
sort of
non-traditional approach.
- Okay.
- Are you adopting?
Um... artificial
insemination, actually.
Oh, are you...?
Am I what?
- [Irene] Like...
- Barren?
No. Oh my God, no,
everything's working fine.
We just don't
want to want to, um...
To conceive in violence.
Yeah, we want our
baby to be conceived
under peaceful conditions.
To avoid the
connotation of rape.
- Well, it doesn't have to be...
- Even the slightest overtone.
It just, it creates a safer
gestation environment
for the child.
As long as it's consensual...
It's the same as you wouldn't
want to grow up in a war zone.
Well, we don't want our
baby to be formed in
a traumatized womb.
Can't you just be gentle?
- Well, there's...
- Always the...
- The connotation.
- Exactly, the connotation.
Have you read
about this somewhere?
- I haven't read about.
- It's new.
So, is it going to
be your sperm?
[Irene] Well,
I would assume it is. It is.
- Yeah.
- We're discussing it.
Well, it should be.
Maybe your article
can help us decide.
Anyway, the bottom line...
We're having it done by
a really wonderful doctor.
- He's Chinese.
- Mark!
Cecily recommended her.
Is that
how Cecily had her baby?
No, this is new.
Well, that's wonderful,
really wonderful.
- Dave?
- You have guests.
Yeah.
Yeah,
Hi, everyone.
Hey, everyone,
this is our friend, Annie.
Sorry, I'm late.
[Mark] Nice to... Okay.
Oh, and of course you
already know Paul.
- Oh, hi.
- I'm a friend of Annie's.
Oh, hi.
You haven't eaten already,
have you?
Oh, no, no, no.
You haven't missed anything
except some
rousing conversation.
Beth and Mark are
going to have a baby, Dave.
Whoa. Wow!
That's fantastic.
Really happy for you guys.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
- So are you...
- No, not yet.
We're still exploring
our insemination options.
Oh, of course, yeah, I mean,
there are so many
options these days.
It might not be his sperm.
Oh, I see.
- How's dinner coming, babe?
- I'll check.
[whistling]
[cork popping]
That's me in Gaza.
That's the wall
at the West Bank.
- Wow.
- Hmm. Interesting.
Yeah, we had a great
group that day.
So you travel
around doing yoga?
It's for my non-profit
Yogis Without Borders.
Wow.
We do yoga in places that
have been ravaged by war.
There's the border wall.
[Mark] Seems dangerous.
[Annie] Everyone was
really nice to us.
Gaza heavy stuff.
I'm going to Iraq in the fall.
Oh, really for the,
um... is that still going on?
- I think so.
- Where's that?
- Oh, that's my flat in Paris.
- Oh, Paris.
Dave and I were just talking
about taking a trip there.
We have an office there.
Is that your
Instagram account?
22,000 followers.
[Annie]
You can stay at my flat.
I have always wanted to
take cooking classes there.
[Beth] I wish we traveled more.
- Why don't you come with us?
- We're saving for a house.
Paris would be so romantic.
- Well, think about it.
- How is the food coming, Dave?
Yeah, is dinner almost ready?
- Yeah, you should check on it.
- I'd like to propose a toast
to a wonderful
evening with friends,
to an exquisite meal
and to Beth's new job.
And to Irene's big cover story.
- [Annie] What's the cover story?
- Oh, it's nothing.
Her latest article is being
featured on the cover of
- The Atlantic.
- That's amazing.
- Wow. The Atlantic.
- Yes, The Atlantic.
Isn't she perfect?
She's a real writer now.
Thank you. It's my first
really big piece.
- What a great magazine.
- Yeah, I know, it's crazy.
She wrote a piece about
how women in their 30s realize
their prospects and settle.
Is it based on
personal experience?
No, not at all.
I'm one of the lucky ones.
We're not one of those couples.
I'm... I am a writer.
So, I mean, I'm writing
about the society that I see.
And I mean, I've certainly
drawn observations and...
but it's not about us.
- Yeah. If anything, Irene...
- [doorbell ringing]
That must be, Charlie.
[Mark] Finally, we can eat!
[Dave] I'll get it.
Hi, yes. I'd like...
I'm sorry, could you
hold on for one second?
- Hey.
- Everything okay?
Yeah. Why?
There's a
Frenchman at the door.
- A Frenchman?
- [Dave] Yeah, a Frenchman.
- [Irene] So...
- Do you know him?
I don't think so.
Well, he says
he's here for the party,
but I didn't invite him.
Well, is he the
sort of person
we'd like to have
at our party?
Well, he looks like a
professor and he's French,
so I guess he's some
kind of intellectual.
So let him in.
What are you doing in here?
My sister's on the phone.
Hi.
I discussed it with my wife,
and you are
just the kind of person
we'd like at our party.
Perfect.
You won't be disappointed.
[tense music]
♪
- [Mark] Hello?
- Hello.
- I am Edouard.
- Mark. Nice to meet you.
The pleasure was mine.
I don't know where everyone
went. They've scattered.
Have you two met already?
This is Mark and I am a
French professor of philosophy.
[tense music]
♪
[Edouard] It gives you
something to define
yourself against, you see?
- Yeah, I'm with you.
- What's he talking about?
You say you hate it?
Yes, CNN, Fox News.
- Doesn't matter.
- It matters.
- Yeah, I think it matters.
- No, this is what I'm saying.
The difference is a
media construction.
You go one way, you go the
other. It does not matter.
As long as the
emotion is there,
it gives you something
to define yourself against.
- You see?
- But I'm right to be angry.
- We should all be angry.
- Yes, of course.
But what does it do for you?
You're doing nothing.
- I'm... I'm...
- It gives you an identity.
it allows it to exist
against something without...
- Without what?
- Yeah, without what?
It allows you to self-identify.
Is the absence of anything
substantial in you.
That's... He's basically
defending Fox News.
No! I think it's
deeper than that.
- You're not serious.
- Yeah, I see people
- fall into this all the time.
- Perhaps you too, huh?
- No, I know who I am.
- Perhaps.
I fucking know.
[intense music]
Sorry.
[clearing throat]
Hi, I'm calling about...
Yes, Irene.
Oh, soon.
Okay.
- Hey, sorry about that.
- Everything okay?
Yeah, yeah.
- My editor called and...
- So great about the Atlantic.
Oh, thank you.
It's been a long road. Whoo!
- Yeah.
- [Irene] I'm very lucky.
I really need to
figure out what I'm doing.
It takes time.
You don't still smoke
by any chance, do you?
Um, I think I have some
upstairs if you want.
- Don't tell Mark, though.
- [Irene] Of course not.
Okay, this movie Transformers,
have you seen this?
- And you?
- The first one.
Okay, this film,
I teach it to my class.
It is a great meta
commentary on American culture.
You see this film,
or you don't.
It doesn't matter.
You hate it either way.
You hate Michael Bay and you
feel better about yourself.
But I haven't even
seen the movie.
- [Edouard] And?
- I hate it.
- Yes, of course.
- It's just a crass money grab
peddling to the
lowest common denominator.
It is just to make money,
that is one level.
Just noise and explosions.
And there are good movies
that people should be seeing.
Yes, of course.
But my question is,
why do you care so much?
This thing,
it is not beautiful.
It is not art. But....
It's popular.
So people hate it.
It serves this purpose of
giving you something to hate.
You don't even have to do
the work of being something.
The movie does it for you.
You don't even
have to watch it.
[epic music]
That's bullshit.
The same ways
you watch the news.
♪
- Hi.
- Oh. Hi.
I didn't hear you come in.
So do you have any
new trips planned?
Just the trip to
Iraq in October.
- To do yoga.
- Yeah.
Well, I'm going to
go see where everyone is.
Nice meeting you.
That French guy is incredible.
He's got these ideas.
I don't know. He's got this
outside perspective.
It's like he gets the culture.
Like how we consume media and...
What?
Do you know what's up
with the other guy?
Annie's friend?
Is he Annie's friend?
- [Dave] Yeah. Why?
- I don't know.
He just makes me uncomfortable.
Did he say something to you?
No, no, no.
I don't know, it's just
something off about him.
Yeah.
I feel horrible saying this,
but he just...
he looks like a loser.
Should I get rid of him?
[laughing]
Serve him for dinner?
No, I shouldn't have said that.
I don't know
what's wrong with me.
You're hungry.
Dinner will be ready soon.
[ethereal music]
Perhaps we should go
around the table
and get to know
each other better.
A lot of people,
they just think of me
as Dave from logistics.
I daydream about
disappearing to a new city
and starting over.
I wanted to be a novelist.
But I've let go of
all those things.
If only I had something
to give myself away to.
I worked so hard
and still feel so empty.
Maybe I could open up
a little shop.
I'm a chef.
I'm constantly thinking
of ways to improve myself.
A man of influence and taste.
The goal of the ego
is to not change.
Irene, could we have
some more wine?
The therapy, the drinking.
Speak to me in French.
You've got it
completely backwards.
- Irene?
- All the sacrifice.
Someday I'll show you
all how great I am.
Irene.
[Annie] I think
I'd like some more wine.
Irene, wine.
Oh my god, I forgot.
Sorry.
This is not who I am.
- This is not who I am.
But time moves on
indifferently.
[tires screeching]
[vehicle crashing]
What happened?
[Beth] He's dead.
- Can I help you?
- I was just...
I was just checking on dinner.
[Dave] What do you know
about being a chef?
- What?
- What do you...
know about food?
I was just...
I was just getting hungry.
Hmm...
Go ahead.
Open it up.
Have a look.
I don't want to.
Go ahead.
[tense music]
Looks good.
♪
[somber music]
Should we do something?
Maybe we should
call the police.
- Did you see that?
- Yeah. What happened?
There was a guy just
lying in the street.
- I think it was a hit and run.
- Probably a drunk driver.
Do you know what to do, Dave?
It's not clear to me.
All right. I don't want
to be that guy, but...
I'm famished.
You know,
maybe we should eat first.
He's right,
things might sort
themselves out once we eat.
Yeah, yeah.
Where's Irene?
Irene.
Dinner's almost ready.
Somebody else
must have heard it.
Someone better equipped
to deal with emergencies, huh?
Everything, okay?
Dave, we're all so hungry.
I'd be happy to lead
us all in some yoga.
It's all very curious,
is it not?
That we are all so
incapable of action?
These things tend to
work themselves out.
Only through a
dispassionate analysis.
If we can nibble on
something, even bread.
About dinner,
I wanted to say something.
Thank you, Irene.
What Irene
is about to say is,
and I'll be honest with you,
there has been a small
problem in the kitchen.
But everything's
under control.
- [Beth] What happened?
- [Annie] Is something wrong?
Just a slight
malfunction with the oven.
Unfortunately,
that does mean dinner will be
slightly delayed
from being ready.
How much longer?
- Only a few hours.
- A few hours?
Yes. But...
Could we order something
small in the meantime?
Some cheese maybe.
No. We're all adults here,
aren't we?
We are, aren't we?
[Mark] We're all so excited
about this amazing meal.
- But we're starving.
- Hey!
Now, I have made an
amazing meal for you tonight.
I am an excellent chef.
You don't go off to
some fancy restaurant
and order in, do you?
No! I don't think so.
We've all been
through a lot tonight.
I'm sorry.
Now.
We're going to have a lovely
meal that I prepared.
I'm doing this for you, okay?
Have some faith in me.
He's right. We should
have some faith in him.
We know there is
a meal on the way.
There's nothing to do,
but wait, and when it comes.
Enjoy it. It will be
worth the suffering, huh?
- Thank you, um...
- [Edouard] Edouard.
Edouard.
Thank you, Edouard.
Let's just have some more
wine and live in the moment.
Dave, why don't you
remind us what's for dinner
so that we can more
easily bear our hunger?
Excellent idea.
Thank you, Annie.
[orchestral music]
Let me remind you all
that I have prepared
an exquisite meal
for you this evening.
Organic pork tenderloin
so succulent you will cry.
Locally harvested.
Honestly, these pigs
look better than you or I.
Organic free range
non-GMO from pen to table
with the most
sublime chartreuse,
compressed peaches
that melt in your mouth.
Dry, melted leeks from
an Amish family farm.
Chanterelle mushrooms
snuggling on an
ethereal bed
of golden figs.
Foie gras seared to perfection
and a lavender pork reduction
so perfect you'd swear that
God himself had driven my hand.
Excuse me.
[eerie music]
[sighing]
[water running]
♪
Irene?
Someone should call police,
oui.
But not before we work on
the philosophical
implications of the situation.
[throat clearing]
- Beth, let's go.
- Excuse me, Mark, right?
- Yeah, what?
- Have you seen, uh,
What's his name?
The worker.
- Paul?
- Yes, that's it. Paul.
I want to discuss with
him the struggle of
the proletariat in America.
No, I haven't seen him.
- Beth.
- He makes me uncomfortable.
- Beth! What?
- We're just talking.
I don't know what to do.
You know, she just...
I don't know,
it's like she's disgusted
the way she looks at me.
Those are really bad for you,
you know?
You know,
I try to be nice,
try to give her what she wants,
but...
You should leave.
What?
What do you mean?
You should leave.
[somber music]
[knives scraping]
♪
There are two questions,
primarily.
It's a question of
what has happened,
a journalistic question
outside my formal
area of training.
But, the more interesting
question for me is...
was it a random act,
an accident?
Or was it intentional?
A murder has a logic to it,
but an accident,
it's meaningless.
[knives scraping]
♪
Once more into the bridges.
What are you doing?
♪
[orchestral music]
- Where have you been?
- Have you seen Irene?
what's going on?
Did I do something?
No, I just wanted a cigarette.
- You don't smoke.
- I just wanted one.
- Beth!
- What are you doing?
If I did something,
I'm sorry.
- Can we talk about it?
- No, you didn't do anything.
I just want a cigarette.
All right, we'll talk later.
What are you so happy about?
I have had a small adventure,
my friend.
What does that mean?
My appetite,
it consumes me,
to eat so much
and then to be empty.
It's a paradox.
What are you talking about?
Sex without love,
you understand?
- I hate you.
- I am nothing.
I am just a Frenchman
in the kitchen.
- I don't really matter.
- Fuck you.
You crazy
fucking people.
Fuck you,
crazy fucking people.
Good luck.
[knives scraping]
What's going on?
I don't know, I'm not...
I'm not really feeling well.
I'm starving and I thought...
You thought what?
I don't know.
Maybe I'd get a
quick bite to eat
and see if that
makes me feel better.
- I was going to come back.
- I get it.
I'm hungry too,
but dinner's almost ready.
Be a shame to
spoil your appetite.
Yeah.
I can remind you
what's cooking again.
No, no, I got it.
Great.
You'll stay then.
And I'm not a bad person,
I just did a bad thing.
You don't think
I'm a bad person, do you?
- No, no.
- Thanks.
I wish I had found
someone like Dave.
You guys are so
perfect together.
Yeah.
What is it?
- I don't know.
- You okay?
Where are you going?
Dave.
I want to help you.
Let me help you.
I love you.
No, you don't.
How could you?
You don't even see
the real me.
[tense music]
Oh, my God.
Where'd you find this?
- Shh.
- What?
If Dave found out,
he'd kill me.
Okay.
[jazzy brass music]
♪
Oh, my God.
That is so good.
♪
You Americans are so
sensitive about sexuality.
[speaks in French]
It is very refreshing...
To meet a real French person here.
The people here...
...they're so boring.
Aren't they?
You do speak French, don't you?
You know,
It's not polite
in mixed company...
You are a dirty coward, yes?
Oui.
You don't speak French, do you?
You are very funny.
You know this?
You aren't French, are you?
I'm just the kind of person
people like at their parties.
Stop it.
Stop talking that way.
Are you so different from me?
You're a very sad person.
You think you're
making a difference?
Do you think that the poor,
the war-ravaged,
that they need yoga?
[Annie] I can't believe
I slept with you.
The problems of war can be
solved with a good stretch.
That's the stupidest fucking
thing I've ever heard.
My work is important.
They sound so convincing,
don't they?
When they tell you
how impressed they are
with your work,
your difference making.
You want to believe
them so badly
so that your life
can hang on to that
- little thread of meaning.
- Fuck you.
At least I did the research.
I read the books.
I'm a good forgery.
You're a factory made trinket.
What do you think it says
about you that you valued
my words more
when I had an accent?
It's to have the courage
to be in on the joke.
You're a monster.
Beth!
- Beth.
- What?
Don't you think
we should talk about this?
No, I don't.
Not right now.
- [Beth] After dinner, okay?
- There's no dinner.
What?
- You...
- I thought you were...
- You're not French?
- [Edouard] No.
- Oh my God.
All that bullshit
about Transformers.
I believed you because I
thought you were French.
- I let you fuck me.
- You what?
Shut up, Mark! I'm so
not in the mood right now!
Who the fuck are you?
I did you a favor.
[dramatic music]
♪
[knocking]
[Irene]
Annie, are you okay?
Annie.
[sobbing and sniffling]
[knocking]
Annie?
♪
[Annie screaming]
Fuck!
Dave, I know everything.
Everything there
was to ever know. Okay?
Oh God.
Oh my God.
Dave, you're my husband.
You're a logistics man.
David, please.
It's not too late.
He was just lying there.
What the hell is going on?
Dinner's almost ready.
What did you do?
The man in the bath...
I thought he was your friend.
No.
What the hell is going on?
We want our food!
- I can explain.
- You promised us dinner.
Where the hell is the food?
- You brought us here.
- We want our fucking food.
Everyone calm the fuck down!
I can explain everything.
You just go back out to the
living room. I can explain.
[doorbell ringing]
- Who's that?
- [Mark] Must be Charlie.
- [Irene] It's not Charlie.
- Then who is it?
Who is it?
I ordered takeout.
[Mark] Why?
Then what's in the oven?
Yeah, what the fuck
is in the oven?
[Mark] Open the fucking oven!
[tense music]
Oh, my God.
[gunshots]
["Love and Kindness"
by The Indelicates]
♪ Father,
when you kissed us ♪
♪ We were cold
and listless ♪
♪ At kitchen
tables listening ♪
♪ To the tales of war ♪
♪ Daughter,
we were reading ♪
♪ All your special pleading ♪
♪ When the silence fell now,
we shall learn no more ♪
♪ Wise, rejecting reasons,
sated by the seasons ♪
♪ Watching all we're eating
as the night draws close ♪
♪ In deafness
and in blindness ♪
♪ Safe in love and kindness ♪
♪ Confident that we've
learned all we care to know ♪
♪ No one represents us,
governed by consensus ♪
♪ Guided by the spirit,
now we all agree ♪
♪ Don't listen to the others,
they are not your brothers ♪
♪ Rather love and
cherishing each family ♪
["No King" by The Outcalls]
♪ But once beloved ♪
♪ By the king ♪
♪ My king ♪
♪ Fingers crossed
until they bleed ♪
♪ Still hoping you'll
change your mind about me ♪
♪ Oh you try, then you fall
to the back of the line ♪
♪ And you take my
hand at the same time ♪
♪ Oh you try, then you fall,
now you lose ♪
♪ You lose it all ♪
♪ Oh you try, then you fall,
now you're losing it all ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ Oh you try, then you fall,
now you're losing it all ♪
♪ Give it to me the same way
that you give to the guys ♪
♪ All I wanted was a chance to
see the fear in your eyes ♪
♪ Give it to me the same way
that you give to the guys ♪
♪ Oh, I want it all
I see the fear in your eyes ♪
♪ Give it to me,
give me the crown ♪
♪ I spent everything I have
and after all that I did ♪
♪ I won't see it go down ♪
♪ I spent everything I have
and after all that I did ♪
♪ I won't see it
go down like this ♪
♪ Like this, like this ♪
♪ Oh you try, then you fall,
now you're losing it all ♪
♪ Give it to me the same way
that you give to the guys ♪
♪ All I wanted was a chance to
see the fear in your eyes ♪