[Vertical Entertainment
theme music]
[CMG theme music]
[MMF theme music]
[Mooncusser Filmworks
theme music]
[water pouring]
[dog barking in distance]
[DJ on radio] Hey,
I got a message
for all you parents
out there. Parents!
I have the solution
for the two and half
months of insanity.
Send them to camp! Yes.
Get rid of those snotty-nosed,
screaming children of yours.
-[blows raspberry]
Play a song already.
[DJ on radio] I
do it every year.
Overnight camp is
a godsend, baby!
[radio turning off]
[Pat] Kate! Cheryl's here!
-All right, Ma. I'm comin'!
-Next year at this
time, we'll be shoutin'
you and Kate's
names at graduation.
-[chuckles] I know.
Can you believe it?
[footsteps approaching]
-Believe what?
-That we're
graduating next year.
-Mm. It feels like yesterday
I was breastfeedin' you.
-Mom, come on. Come on.
Don't put that in Cheryl's mind.
Why would you say that?
-Yeah, too late. [chuckles]
-I feel like a high
school's been like waiting
in this very long line
for a roller coaster,
and only now are we
getting on the ride.
And the next year is
gonna be the first drop.
-Yeah. And we'll be laughing
and screaming the
whole way down.
[Cheryl chuckles]
- Dude.
- I bet you girls are.
- I know.
-I remember my senior year.
Bill and I had our first kiss.
-Okay. Thank you.
Nobody wants to hear about
you and Dad's love life.
Thank you. Thank you.
-I wanted to gag myself,
picturing you suckin'
on your Mom's tits.
-Fucking tell me about it.
Hey, good morning,
Mister Mclaughlin.
-Good mornin' Katie.
So are you excited about
your last day of school?
-Yeah.
-How about you, Cheryl?
-Yeah, no, I am.
I just, you know, I really
need a job this summer, so.
-Oh, well. Let's see what
we can do about that.
Now you just come
down to the office
and I'm sure we
can find something
for a really ambitious little
lady from the neighborhood.
-Really? Thank you so much.
That'd be great.
I'll be there.
-Good. That's good.
Now, listen now.
The best thing about
my daily routine
is watching you two
girls go to school.
-Oh.
-No, we love our walk
to school, really.
-Yeah.
-You know, we get to see
all of our neighbors.
-Well, you're great girls.
-Your money or your life.
-Marty, you dope!
-Marty, don't sneak up
on the girls like that.
-Yes, sir, Mister McLaughlin.
-Now, where are your
manners, really?
-I-I wasn't
thinking. I'm sorry.
-I may have to talk to your dad.
-Yes, sir.
-Oh, that's okay?
-Uh, I'm... I'm
sorry. [chuckles]
-All right.
-You have a good one, all right?
-You too. I'll... we'll
see you at the office, huh?
-Thank you so much.
See you at the office.
Yeah, thank you.
- All right.
[chuckles]
-Kate, you couldn't wait for me?
-Man, it was gettin'
late. We had to leave.
-Marty, take that puppy
dog look off your face.
You caught up to us.
-[giggles] You want
my father to kill you?
-I'm just holding your
hand. What's the big deal?
-Oh God, Marty,
don't be a prick.
Everybody knows Mister Coughlin
is overprotective of Kate.
Did you ask her to
go out with you yet?
-No.
-Why? Because you are
scared to death of him.
- I am not.
- Yes, you are.
- No, I'm not.
-No, I'm not.
[dog barking in distance]
-Hi. Good morning,
Missis Bunkley.
-Good morning, Kate. How's
your father and your mom?
-Oh, they're fine.
They're fine.
-Missis Bunkley,
you still need me
to sweep the steps after school?
-Yeah. If I wait on John,
it'll never get done.
If his father wasn't in prison,
maybe he wouldn't be so bad.
You kids. go on. Enjoy the day.
-[chuckles] All right.
Hey, you get some
rest, all right?
-Yeah.
-Good.
-Geez, why's she
so hard on John?
-Really? Man, I
think he's an asshole
for treating his
grandma the way he does.
-John's dad is locked
up for murder, ain't he?
-Yeah. He whacked a dude
for Mister McLaughlin.
Beat him to death with
his bare hands, I heard.
-Eww, Marty. Subject
change, please. God.
-You know this is the last time
you're walking to
school as a junior.
Next time you'll be a senior.
-[Wendy chuckles]
-Time flies. I'll
see you tonight.
-Uh, no. This afternoon. I'll
be home right after school.
We said we were
gonna go visit Mom.
-Right.
-Thank you.
[♪♪♪]
[birds chirping]
[lively chattering]
[door closes]
[birds chirping]
[siren wailing]
[lively chattering]
Hi.
- Yeah, you got something?
- I have nothing.
-Hey, hey, Wendy.
Last day of school.
Listen, offer still stands.
I can use someone smart like
you to help run the business.
You know, do the bookkeeping.
Help keep the whores in line.
-I'll pass, Bobby.
-You sure? It's a lot
of money for a kid.
All cash. What's the problem?
-It's this thing called ethics.
-[scoffs] Leave
that girl alone.
-Terrance!
-Smart-ass kid like
her smart-ass father.
-Terrance, come outside!
-Bye, Ma.
[door opens]
- Hey.
- [door closes]
-What's the rush?
-I'm excited. It's our
last day of school.
After today, we're
going to be seniors.
-How did I forget that?
-Because you forget everything.
-No, I don't.
-Yes, you do.
-Terrance, you
forget my birthday.
- Mm.
- To pick your sister up,
your homework.
- Osh.
-Should I keep going?
-No. You proved your point.
-Stop. Here.
[Terrance exhales]
[tense music]
[car engine revving]
-It's huge.
-I don't get it.
What's wrong with these people?
-Who?
-Them.
They sell drugs.
They flaunt their
cars and their whores.
Look at that guy.
That asshole looks like
he's about to fall over.
High as a kite.
And they call us pigs
when we lock them up.
[chattering over radio comms]
- [door chime rings]
- Thief! Thief!
-Stop the car. Stop the car!
-Thief!
Goddammit.
Come back here.
Get him, police!
'Bout time y'all showed
up in the neighborhood.
[car tires screech]
- [siren wailing]
- [thief crashes]
- [grunts]
- Slow down now, buddy.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- That's teamwork, baby.
-I'm sorry.
- Yo, yo.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey. [indistinct].
-Everybody, everything's
under control.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Ahh!
[grunts]
-Just tryin' to do our job.
Hey, hey.
Yeah.
Come on, guys.
[zipper unzips]
-We watching you.
We watching you.
-What the hell is this?
-I never steal, I swear.
Our baby ain't got
nothin' to eat.
My wife and I don't
know what to do.
We ain't got no money.
- Go easy. Go easy.
- Yo.
-Go easy.
-Let him go!
-You know him?
-Yeah, I've seen him around.
-How much does he owe
you for the baby formula?
[zipper unzips]
-Eight-fifty.
-Keep the change.
-Damn. I guess there are
some good white pigs left.
-I should arrest your
Black ass for that comment.
-Yo!
-Get the fuck... get the fuck...
Get the fuck out of here
before I change my mind.
Go feed your baby, and
don't say a goddamn word!
'Cause I don't want
people thinking
I'm a goddamn charity, okay?
Get the fuck out of here.
[baton smashing]
-I'da locked that nigga up.
-Tell me about it.
-Dad!
-[indistinct] cartoons, right?
-Uh-huh.
-But it's different
because it...
It's just a group of kids
and they solve mysteries
and there's monsters but...
- Hey, hey.
-Marty, you're talking
about Scooby-Doo?
- Hey.
- Well, I.
[school bell ringing]
- My little cousin watches that.
- Hey, [indistinct],
you still owe me a quarter.
- I'll catch you after class.
- Hey.
- You have a good summer then.
-Kate, you wanna take
that math class with me?
-Now, let's go with betting.
No games with me today.
- Yeah. I'm not sure I'll stay.
- I'm not tryin' to do nothin'.
-What's up, [indistinct]?
Wendy?
- Yeah.
- You ready?
-Yeah. [squeals]
-Come on. I'll
take your books?
-Okay, yeah, yeah.
[♪♪♪]
[reporter on TV]
.racial dominance.
Hardly anyone seems neutral
about [continues indistinctly]
-This is
un-fucking-unbelievable.
Pat! Patty! Come here!
Bastards are going
through with it!
-What?
-They're gonna bus
Kate around the city.
-Stop your nonsense.
-Uh, yeah.
These politicians are nothing
but fucking hypocrites.
They passed the bill to
bus the kids in Boston.
Not in the suburbs where
the rich people live.
Just Boston.
- Shhhhh.
Let me hear what they're saying.
And calm down.
We knew it was coming.
[muted chatter on TV]
Mother of God.
They couldn't wait
until she graduated?
-It's her fucking senior
year, for Christ's sake!
And my little girl will
have to go to school
in all this madness.
It's gonna be chaos!
It's not fucking
right, I tell you.
-At least, we have a couple
of weeks to prepare her.
-Prepare her? Think
about it, Patty.
It's gonna be hell!
Protests. Riots.
They fucked us!
-Will you stop cursing!
Oh, sweet mother of God,
they could send her to Roxbury!
-Don't say that!
Don't you say that.
It's too dangerous.
They better not send
my pumpkin there.
I won't let her go. They.
Look, I get it.
We gotta integrate, but
this ain't the way to do it.
-We are not taking
her out of school.
-Hey, we could get the
hell out of Boston.
-Really, love? And go where?
To the suburbs, with
all the rich snobs?
-I don't know.
[kisses]
[reporter on TV] The other
kids we're talking about
are largely the Black
kids who live in Roxbury.
[birds squawking]
-Oh, my god. Hey. Did
Marty ask you yet?
-[sighs] No.
- No?
- Not yet, but he's been like
hinting around about it.
- Yeah.
-Pretty much asking me
like what color prom dress
I'm gonna wear.
-God, he's such a
pussy. Just ask it.
-Hey.
-What?
-[whispering] Guess who's
been flirting with me?
-Who?
-[whispers] John Bunkley.
-Oh, my god.
Holy shit.
Wait, that's why you've
been coming by the office.
You don't want to see me.
You wanna bump into John.
-Stop!
-Literally.
- You're nasty.
- I know.
-You're disgusting.
You're perverted.
-You love it.
- I kinda do.
- [Cheryl chuckles]
I thought you didn't like him.
-No. I like him. No.
It's, like, John's had
a hard life, you know?
His father locked up,
mother off somewhere,
high on drugs somewhere.
-God, that sucks.
-He's got no choice
but to be a badass.
-Hm.
-Did Michael ask
you to prom yet?
-Yeah. He plans
on getting a limo.
-[chuckles] Are you kidding?
-No, I'm serious.
- That's so fancy.
- I'm like dead serious.
I know. Me in a limo? Oh, no.
- You know what?
My dad's gonna want to patrol
us around in his patrol car.
Like with the sirens blaring.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Lights on.
- Oh, that's good.
- Prom night.
- Really?
-You and me.
-[giggling]
[muted chattering]
-All right, quiet.
All eyes over here.
In a couple of weeks, the
new school year begins.
And as we all know, this
year isn't gonna be anything
like past years.
The courts have ordered
cross-district busing
in the poorest white
and Black neighborhoods.
-Jesus Christ. Blacks?
-You know what?
Let's keep our
feelings out of this.
Remember the oath
that we all took.
This entire city is angry.
So we are on high alert
until school opens.
Now I need to talk
to Officers Coughlin,
Riley, Jefferson.
The rest of youse, be careful.
And remember, be sure
to make it home to.?
-Our families.
-Your families. Let's go.
[overlapping chattering]
[telephone ringing in distance]
-Everything okay, Cap?
-Yeah.
You might wanna wipe
that smirk off your face.
-What the fuck?
-You and Riley won't
be working together.
-Come on. Why, Cap?
-Because you, Officer Coughlin,
and you, Officer Jefferson,
will be reassigned to Southie.
Jefferson, you will be
on the bus with the kids.
Coughlin, you will escort
those kids into Southie High.
-What? Cap, why?
I like it here.
-Because higher-ups
told me to pick two men
that I thought could
relate to the poor people
that are affected by
this whole fiasco.
-Why don't they
leave good alone?
-No offense, Jefferson,
but mixing the
Black and white kids
from the poorest neighborhoods
is not a good idea.
-No, I get it.
All I'm saying is it's going
to be tough for everybody.
-Cap, my neighbors
will turn against me.
-Hm.
Remember five minutes ago
when I said let's keep
our feelings out of this?
Let's keep our
feelings out this.
And your new partner
Jefferson is right. Huh?
This isn't going to be
easy. We all know that.
But I picked the two of you
because, well, Jefferson,
you're Black.
-He's Black?
-Yeah, he's Black.
And these kids need somebody
that they can identify with.
-Mm-hm.
-And I picked you, Coughlin,
because you're from
the neighborhood.
And I'm hoping that maybe
you can talk some sense
into your neighbors off hours.
Besides, all these kids,
the kids on the bus,
they know you from Roxbury.
Huh?
You got a good rep.
-Are you fucking
kidding me? I'm fucked.
I might as well paint my face
black walking with those kids.
No offense, Jefferson.
-No. None taken.
-You come back after your shift
and I'll paint your
face black for you.
Otherwise, you
fucking figure it out,
because your name's in it.
-This busing is gonna
rip this city apart.
-Hey. Listen, man.
We need to integrate, okay?
Don't be racist.
-Racist!
You think I am?
-No. Just a regular
old Bobby Kennedy.
-Racist.
[door lock beeping]
[gate opening]
[gate closing]
[dramatic music]
[soft rock music]
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
-Welcome home.
-[laugh]
-Feels good to be
out of that rathole.
Twelve years wasted 'cause of
that piece of shit Coughlin.
Yeah. What's the verdict on him?
- Hm?
- What's the verdict on him?
-The same.
-Are you fucking kidding me?
What is it with you and him?
-Are you questioning me?
-No. Of course not.
-Hm.
- [Lamont hums]
- [paper ripping]
-Dad?
-Yeah.
-Is that the letter?
Sit down, babe.
-What's wrong?
Roxbury High, right?
[car passes by in distance]
-Southie.
-What am... What
am I going to do?
They hate us.
-Hey, you're right.
They're gonna call you
every name possible.
And liberal Massachusetts
ain't no better
than confederate Alabama.
But there is nothing
that you can't handle.
And what have we
learned about hate?
-That it's like
an addictive drug,
because people who hate
have low self-esteem,
and putting others down
makes them feel better
about themselves.
-And what does
the Bible teach us
about how to deal with
those that hate us?
-We should pray for them.
-Good.
And how do we overcome hate?
-With love.
Dad, I'm scared.
-I know.
But we're gonna try
and be brave, right?
[knock on door]
-I have the letter.
You're going to Southie.
-Oh, yes!
Oh, my god. Yes.
[chuckles] I'm so happy.
I can stay.
-Kate.
It's going to be different
with Black kids there.
-Mm.
Why do niggas have to go
to our school anyways?
-Kate. Don't use that
language in this house.
You know better.
-Or what?
What? Like we're
not from Southie
where the word isn't thrown
around like confetti anyways.
-Change that tone.
And don't tell me what people
are saying in the streets.
I worry about my own home.
-I know. It's just...
it's not fair, you know?
The Blacks coming to our
school, causing problems.
It's just gonna ruin
our senior year.
-I understand.
It's okay to be angry.
But don't take it out on others.
Calling people
names or acting out
will make the
situation worse. Hm?
We have to be good Catholics
and love our neighbors
as we love ourselves.
-Yeah, but they're
not our neighbors.
That's the problem.
I'm gonna call Cheryl.
[giggling]
- [baby crying in distance]
- [dog barking in distance]
-I don't fucking believe this.
Cheryl! Will you get down here?
[footsteps]
[paper rustles]
-Dad, what is this?
This isn't fair. I'm not
going to Roxbury High.
I'll be the only
white kid in there.
-What you want me to do?
-I don't know, call somebody.
You know people.
-If any of those coons
put a hand on you
so help me God, I'll kill 'em.
I'll kill 'em all.
-I thought we could
pick her school.
It's her senior year.
-I don't know and I
don't give a shit.
They keep changing
the rules as they go.
[phone ringing]
-[into phone] Hello?
-[into phone] Hi.
Is Cheryl there?
-[into phone] Kate.
Yes, she's here.
-[into phone] Hello?
-[into phone] I'm
going to Southie!
-[Pat chuckles]
-[into phone] Cheryl,
are you there?
Cheryl, you there?
-[into phone] Yeah. They're
sending me to Roxbury.
-[into phone] What? Why?
What? No, no, no, no.
Why?
-[into phone] I don't know.
-[into phone] I know why.
Those spearchuckers
are ruinin' everything.
Oh, we gotta do
something. We have to.
Okay, I'll call you
back then, I guess.
-[into phone] All right. Bye.
[phone thuds]
-♪ I'm happy for
to see ye home, ♪
♪ Hurroo hurroo ♪
♪ I'm happy for to see
ye home Hurroo hurroo ♪
♪ I'm happy for to see ye home
I'm happy for to see ye home ♪
[continue indistinctly]
- Got your back.
- Hey.
Let me buy you a drink.
You're gonna need it.
-How you figure?
-Oh, you got a surprise coming.
-♪ Oh darling dear,
ye look so queer ♪
♪ Johnny I hardly knew ye ♪
♪ I'm happy for to see
ye home, hurroo, hurroo ♪
-Hey, how you
doing? How are you?
Hey, I got something
for you over here.
I think you're gonna love it.
-♪ Guns and guns
and guns and guns, ♪
♪ Hurroo, hurroo ♪
-♪ Guns and guns and guns ♪
All right
-All right. My
two favorite boys.
-Johnny's back.
-They let you out.
-Yep.
Just in time for the fireworks.
-[McLaughlin laughs]
-Fireworks?
-Yeah.
You know, I hold no grudge
against you for putting me away.
I get it, you know. Come on.
-[both laugh]
-You were just doing your job.
-Yeah, but she's still missing.
-Yeah.
Whores go missing every day.
-All righty, let's have a toast.
Hm?
- [cork pops]
A toast.
[wine pouring]
To Billy and Johnny.
As you all know,
Johnny's a free man.
He was doing 12 years upstate,
and he never said one word.
That's the Southie way.
Slainte!
- Slainte.
-Hm.
And now Billy.
Billy helped the authorities
to arrest Johnny.
-[men chattering]
-That's all right,
that's all right.
He's family.
And families forgive.
May the devil cut the
toes off of our foes,
for that way we will know them
by their limping.
-I'll fucking drink to that.
-Here. Here. Here.
-[whispers] Let's go outside.
[siren blaring in distance]
You don't see the
night sky in prison.
You know what you do
see? Of course you don't.
Lookin' through the cell window,
you see a striped picture
frame of the night sky.
[car honking]
-Nobody gives a fuck about
the time you spent in prison.
They should've buried
the fucking keys.
-What happened to
us, Billy? Huh?
We used to run wild through
the streets of Southie.
Nothing came between us.
-You remember Mister Kelley?
Well, I knew then that
we were nothing alike.
-Are you... are you
fucking kidding me?
All these years and
that busted your balls?
He owed me 20 bucks.
[laughs] That was a
lot of money back then.
Come on. Even McLaughlin
said I did the right thing.
-Fine.
-I tell you what, I forgive
you for rattin' me out.
You forget about Kelly and
we can be buddies again.
Come on.
- Fuck you. Never.
-No wonder you became a cop.
You couldn't stomach
the violence.
Yeah, but you know in
Southie, we make our own laws.
And we protect our own.
-Yeah.
I guess that rule never
applied to little Johnny's mom.
[siren blaring in distance]
-How's Pat? She
still a delight
to the Irishman's eyes?
- Oh, yeah.
Keep my wife's name out
of your fucking mouth.
-Yeah, you always
did protect her.
Well, I... I bet that
she didn't tell you.
I was there first.
She probably didn't
tell you that, huh?
- Fuck you.
I don't want Pat.
She's yours now. But
I have to tell you,
my son has a thing for
your teenage daughter.
And you know how
teenage boys can be.
-If you or your lowlife son
go anywhere near my daughter,
I'll fucking kill both of you.
You hear me?
- [laughs] Billy Boy.
Ah, two bodies.
- You hear me?
- Yeah.
Then you'll see the
striped night sky for sure.
I don't think you'll
fucking like it.
-Ah, there you are.
You two boys catching up?
-Like Cain and Abel.
-[laughs] Good, good. Yeah.
I'll come to the point.
This bussing is no good
for the neighborhood.
Now you being a man of the
law, we thought, you know,
maybe, maybe you could
use your influence.
-Keep me the fuck
out of here, phony.
I give a fuck about the
neighborhood bullshit.
-You know what,
that gun and badge
don't make you better than us?
You were born and raised here.
Don't you forget it!
-All right, let's...
Let's keep this
nice and civil, shall we?
Now, Bill,
I was told that you were
soft on spades in Roxbury.
Now, I didn't believe it.
I refuse to believe that
you forgot who you are.
-I know who I am.
And I ain't your errand
boy like the old days.
-Okay.
-And I sure as hell
don't want any part
of your tribal,
murderous bullshit.
-You're limpin', Billy.
[car door opens then closes]
[car engine starts]
[car engine revving]
You hear how he talks to you?
That arrogant motherfucker!
You have to let
me make it right.
Please let me make it right.
- All right.
- All right?
That cocksucker ratted
me the fuck out!!
-Calm down.
-Let me make it right!
You know, your problem
is you're too emotional.
That's what got
you sent away. Ah?
There's a time and a
place for everything.
And right now, it's
time to celebrate.
Come on, hey?
You just got out.
Come on!
[door slams]
[heavy footsteps]
-What's the matter?
-Johnny Bunkley
is out of prison.
[clears throat]
- And?
That's why you don't
want to kiss me?
Stop looking at me like that.
-Did you go steady
with him before me?
-Yeah.
[clanks]
-Did you?
-We had a real committed
relationship in junior high
when he held my hand.
What's gotten into you?
You gotta understand.
My parents came
into this country
and threw me into school
where I had no friends
and spoke maybe ten
words of English.
I got bullied because
I had a funny accent.
Johnny was the first
kid who was nice to me.
But as soon as I found out
how bad he was, I ran away.
I never mentioned it
'cause it was nothing.
Hm? I love you.
[engine roaring in distance]
-Where's Kate?
-In her room.
I don't like how you're acting.
-What's the name of
that kid who likes Kate?
-Marty?
You-Ah, just give me a minute.
Kate!
- Yeah?
-Get down here, now!
-Bill, are you gonna
keep me in the dark
or let me know what
the hell is going on?
[footsteps approaching]
-Yeah?
-Ah, John Bunkley, are you
and him in any kind of,
you know?
-[scoffs] What... what
are you talking about?
- Answer the question.
- No!
- Don't play stupid.
-Stay away from him.
You hear me? I mean it.
-Okay. Mom, what's going on?
-I don't know.
Your dad came home
acting strange.
-Go to your room. Let
me talk to your mother.
-Dad, you okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine. Are you?
Go!
[footsteps receding]
[approaching footsteps]
[Bill sighs]
Your mom told me the
good and bad news.
It's tough not
having your partner.
I had the same issue today.
-Really, what happened?
-They moved me to Southie.
I'll be escorting the
Black kids into the school.
-Oh my god, it keeps
getting worse and worse.
You're gonna be with.
You're gonna be with me on
my senior year at Southie?
-Come on. Is it that bad?
-Yeah! Yeah, it is!
Everything is going wrong.
-Look, kid, they forced
this bussing thing
down our throats.
It's not fair, I know.
- Yeah, I know.
I told Mom that and she
got all bent out of shape.
-Well, you said a
little more than that.
-I'm just saying what
everybody else has been saying.
If I call them Black or nigger,
it's not... it's not me.
-Hey, hey, hey,
hey. Stop, okay?
Your mother doesn't allow
that language in this house.
-Okay, I'm sorry,
Dad. But I'm...
-No buts, okay?
Don't say that word.
Where'd you learn to
say things like that?
-Um.
You and your friends?
And practically everybody
in the neighborhood.
-[inhales deeply]
Listen, if I tolerated
that word, it was wrong.
Okay, I understand
you're disappointed
but that doesn't give
you or me the right
to call Black people
names, or anyone.
-Hm.
-Okay?
Look at me.
[chuckles] Okay?
-All I want is a
normal senior year.
What is wrong with that?
-Nothing. If I could do
something about it, I would.
-Yeah, but we can't.
The only thing we can do is keep
them from coming to my school.
-Don't get sucked up into all
the neighborhood nonsense.
It's poison.
You hear me?
I mean it.
-Mm.
-And why is Johnny talking
about you and his son?
-That's not what you think.
-Huh.
What do I think?
Huh? You know my thoughts now?
You gonna tell me what I think?
- Don't get mad.
-Do I look mad?
I'm perfectly calm.
- Yeah, okay.
Do you know that, uh,
job that Cheryl's got
at McLaughlin's
office right now?
Sometimes I just. I just
go there to hang out.
-What? You shittin' me, right?
Fuck!
- Bill, stop cursing.
-Pat! Patty, get up here now.
How many times have I
told you not to hang out
with those people?
You see them, you
say hi and bye.
That's it.
-What's the matter?
-Tell your mother.
-What is it, Kate?
-She's been hanging
around McLaughlin's place.
-That explains why she's
using that kind of language.
-You know what? Both
of you are hypocrites.
What? You think you're
better than them?
You're not.
I've heard all the stories
about you growing up, Dad.
So don't tell me
about those people.
Don't tell me about those people
because you are those people!
You are!
-Watch how you talk
to your father.
-I have to take a walk,
or I'm gonna say
somethin' I regret.
-I think we all need a moment.
[receding footsteps]
You need to think about
the company you keep.
-[Kate groans]
[whispers] I hate them.
[dog barking in distance]
[birds chirping]
-Cannot believe they are
shipping me to Southie.
If any of those crackers mess
with me, I'm missing them up.
-Well, you can't go in there
with that kind of attitude.
-To hell with that.
I don't wanna go to
their damn school.
I don't.
[dog barking in distance]
I'm perfect right here.
But no, they want a bunch
of kids who hate each other
to walk hand in hand
and sing Kumbaya.
Politicians are dumb.
-I don't want to go
either, my dad's making me.
But I'm not gonna go
with the attitude of
a Black Panther or Malcolm X,
but a little Martin Luther King.
-Psh. Shut up.
And where's King?
Dead.
Murdered by a cracker.
-Don't tell me to shut up!
And Malcolm was
murdered by a Black man.
Now is one murder less
serious than the other
because of the color of
the person who did it?
-You're always tryin'
to find the good
in something bad.
But ain't no good in this.
I'm messing me up a white
boy if they screw with me!
That's all.
-If you go into that
school looking for trouble,
you're gonna find it.
-It found me.
I'm just getting
ready for a war.
[birds chirping]
[birds squawking]
[boat blaring]
-So.
You and Marty.
-Me and Marty.
-You got nothin', right?
I mean, he didn't ask you
to go steady or anything?
-No. He's too scared.
-Oh, okay.
Well, from this point on,
you're John Bunkley's girl.
I'll make sure and
tell Marty that.
-I'll tell him but I
didn't say yes to you yet.
Did you think about that?
-What, I couldn't hear you.
Say it a little louder.
-I didn't say yes to you.
-Well.
[boat blaring]
[birds squawking]
-My father's gonna kill
us when he finds out.
-Hey, don't worry
about your father.
Okay?
He and my old man,
they go way back.
They'll figure it out.
If not, we'll run away
and, uh, we'll be the
new Bonnie and Clyde.
-Bonnie and Clyde. Robbing
banks and armored cars.
-Can I tell you something?
-Tell me something.
[boat blaring]
-You want to know why my
old man went to prison?
Everybody thinks it's
because he killed that coon
for Mister McLaughlin,
which I guess that is kind of
true, but what nobody knows
is that the coon my
old man killed, he...
-You don't have to
tell me this, John.
I, um... it's all right.
-Just listen to me.
I'm gonna tell you.
Um, the coon my old man killed,
he ran away with my mom.
Yeah, the spade used to sell
dope for Mister McLaughlin.
My old man would
collect money from him
and my mom would just
go with him sometimes.
One day, my old
man went to collect
and the coon and my mom were
stoned out of their minds
and half naked,
just laying there.
So my old man lost it and
beat that coon to death.
And my ma ran away.
I'm sorry.
I brought you something.
I brought, uh.
This picture.
[chuckles] so you
can meet my mom.
How I remember her, at least.
[♪♪♪]
When my old man told
me what happened,
he made me promise
not to tell anyone.
So you're the only one
that knows the whole story.
-I'm not gonna tell
anyone the whole story.
-I want you to keep
that picture, too.
-John, you sure?
-Mm-hm.
You'll always have
my family with you.
[birds squawking]
-Okay.
-Hey.
-Hi, Marty. What's up?
-What's up?
Where's Kate?
-Ah, she took a walk.
-Without you?
-Yeah, she'll be right back.
Marty, let's talk.
Hey.
-You know something, don't you?
-Why didn't you ask
Kate to go out with you?
-Why do you think I
got this sweat box on?
That was my plan today. I
was gonna give her my jacket.
[scoffs] What's the matter?
-Marty, she's going
out with John now.
-Is she with him now?
-Yeah.
-They know?
-Them? Yeah.
[birds chirping]
[Marty exhales]
-Marty, come on.
Where you going?
-Going for a walk.
[approaching footsteps]
-Hey, um, you know what?
Just let me talk to him.
I don't want to cause
any problems or anything.
-All right, go ahead.
But if he talks any shit, I'm
gonna punch him in the face.
-[Kate shushes]
Hey.
-That's all you can say?
-No. I could...
I could say more.
I just.
I don't know what to say.
-Well, how about, all
the rumors are lies
and I want to be with you.
[birds chirping]
-Um.
Well, I'm sorry, Marty.
I can't say that.
-Fuck, Kate! What's
gotten into you?
-Hey, Marty, you better
watch ya fucking mouth!
-John, stop it! I think
you should leave, Marty.
-W-why? Because of him?
I don't have to go nowhere.
I'm not afraid of him.
-Shut the fuck up, Marty!
- [punch thrown]
- [Marty grunts]
- John! John!
- John! Stop!
[punches thrown]
-Marty! Marty!
That's enough!
-Get off me! Ah!
- Get off him, John!
- John!
-John!
-Are you okay? Are you okay?
Did I hurt you? Are you okay?
Are you okay?
- [Kate trembling]
-It's fine, Marty.
Are you okay?
It's okay. So breathe.
It's okay.
Kate, are you all right?
-Are you okay? Did I hurt you?
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to hurt you.
[panting]
[Marty spits blood]
-John, you can't
push her like that.
What the hell's wrong with you?
- [door opens]
- [door chime rings]
-Hey, Coughlin. Usual?
-Yeah.
-And you, Riley?
-Pastrami.
When you retiring, Spanelli?
-[chuckles] No time soon.
Still a lot of life
in this ticker.
-My momma said if a
cracker calls me a name,
punch him in the face.
-I said don't say that.
The police will be
there to protect you.
-Do you hear her?
You can't force people
to like each other.
You got to gradually
move 'em along.
-Too bad you ain't mayor.
-Yeah. That's what I say.
-My momma said don't
trust the pigs.
-I, uh, just want to let
you know that we're...
We're gonna do
everything in our power
to make sure that you
get a safe education.
-Can I ask you a question?
-Go ahead.
Why do white people
hate us so much?
-No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't... I don't hate you.
And I know a lot of white
people who are like me.
I mean, look at Mr. Spanelli.
He's nice, right?
[birds chirping]
[beer can thunks]
-Hey, old man.
-Old? Watch your mouth, kid.
Where you been?
[chair slides]
-Went to the park.
-Oh yeah?
-Yeah. I had to beat
this motherfucker's ass.
-You better have beaten his ass.
-I did just like you taught me.
-There you go.
[cigarette sizzles]
[birds chirping]
-Can I ask you something?
-Is it about that Coughlin girl?
You need some tips?
-It's about Ma.
-What're you
bringing her up for?
What, your grandma and me,
we didn't do enough for you?
-Yeah, but...
-But... fuck the buts
you ungrateful little prick!
I know what the fuck it is.
The Coughlin girl's
making you weak.
Let me give you some...
Hey, let me give you some
fucking advice about women.
They ain't to be trusted.
They're all whores.
And your mother, who
you're so concerned about,
left you for a fucking nigga.
Let that sink in.
-[sighs deeply] I didn't
mean it like that.
-Yeah, how'd you mean it?
-I was just wondering.
You know, I mean, you think
she might be dead or something?
-Oh, fuck that whore.
What you looking at
me like that for?
What, you think I killed her?
-Did you?
-Well, if I did, she got
what was coming to her.
Get the fuck out of my face.
Get the fuck out of here!
Go back to your
whore girlfriend.
-Fuck you!
-She's just like all the rest.
-Fucking piece of shit!
-Good luck, you piece of shit.
[beer can clanking]
-He's just like you.
You gonna clean up
this yard or what?
-Always with the yard, Ma.
When your old man was beating
my brains in, where was you?
In the yard with them
stupid fucking roses.
-I couldn't fight your father,
so I prayed.
[cigarette sizzling]
-[blows] Well, God
don't give a shit
about your prayers, Ma.
Yeah. That much we know.
-That's not true.
I prayed you got out
of the joint early.
Well, here you are.
I pray for you every
day, 'cause you're
an evil man.
[soft music]
[cigarette sizzling]
-You're home early.
-Yeah.
After the other night, I'm
giving Mully's a break.
Where's Kate?
-In her room.
-What's her mood?
-She came home from the park
smiling from ear to ear.
-Yeah. You sure she
was at the park?
-We have to trust her.
-Not after the other night.
She has to earn that.
[groans]
Thanks.
You said she was
smiling. About?
-I think Marty asked her to
the prom and to go steady.
She was in a special place.
-Did she tell you that?
-No. But a mother can tell.
-Well, I guess he's better
than the Bunkley kid.
Yeah.
[sighs] Well, I'm...
I'm gonna talk with her.
I'm gonna give her
my approval. Okay?
-All right.
[kisses]
What's that for?
-For being a great
mother and a great wife.
Without you, well, I don't
know. I'd be a different man.
Someone we wouldn't like.
[footsteps]
Kate?
Katie-Kate.
Oh, fuck.
Pat! Kate's not here!
-What do you mean?
She went upstairs.
-She better not be
where I think she is.
You call Cheryl's house.
I'll check the park,
but so help me God if she's
at McLaughlin's place.
[footsteps receding]
-[Pat sighs]
- [door slams]
- Kate.
-Hey.
-What's the matter?
-It's just family problems.
Don't worry about it.
[car engine revving]
-[Lamont chuckles]
-Hey.
Hey, look who thinks they
can drive through Southie.
Hey, hey, come here.
Come here.
Let's throw these fucking rocks.
- Me?
- Yeah. Yeah.
[car engine revving]
-Don't look at them.
-[whispers] Throw it.
- [window smashes]
- Ah! Go, go!
Daddy, drive! Drive!
[car tires screech]
[indistinct shouting]
-Okay, motherfucker. Fuck you!
Hey, hey. What a throw!
[laughter]
That's my fuckin'
girl. Fuck you, bitch!
-Are you okay?
I'm sorry, babe.
[car tires screech]
-Dad, no. What are you doing?
Where are you going?
No, no, no, no. No, no, no.
Dad, I wanna go back home.
- [car tires screech]
- Please. Please, Dad.
Don't! No, no, no.
I wanna go home.
Dad, please stop.
No, no, no. No, Dad.
I wanna go home.
Please.
Dad, I wanna go home.
[car engine stops]
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
-[Wendy breathing heavily]
I wanna go home.
[car engine revving]
-Hey.
You okay?
Your window. What
happened to your window?
-Look, we don't want
no more trouble.
-No, I'm... I'm a cop.
You need help?
You okay?
-We're good.
-All right, then.
Just get that window fixed.
[car engine revs]
-Why didn't you tell
him what happened?
-You don't know who to trust.
Did you see a badge?
[heavy exhale] Times like this,
I wish your mama
was still around.
She had nerves of steel.
I don't even know how
she did it, you know.
Even when she was
facing the cancer,
she never, never cried once.
You know, I cried all the time.
[sighs]
And if she saw some
injustice, she just,
she'd jump right into action,
regardless of the danger.
I called her on it once or twice
and she'd just throw
her famous Gandhi quote.
She said, "You got to
do the right thing.
You never know what's
gonna be the results.
But if you do nothing,
there will be no results."
-Gandhi never had to
drive through Southie.
-I've made a decision.
Your mama wouldn't
approve of it,
but I'm not gonna make
you go to that school.
It's. it's too dangerous.
[sliding door rattles]
-What the fuck?
[chuckles]
I thought you left.
Go rent a room.
Come on. Look what we got here.
-Hey, John, come on.
You don't bring
young ladies up here.
Especially not Kate,
do you hear me?
- Yes, sir.
- All right.
Good work, kids.
-He's certainly your son.
-Yeah, he is.
Likes a little
after school work.
- [door slides]
- That's what I'm sayin'.
I don't know what you...
Is... is he qualified?
- Yeah.
- To fucking do it?
-Yeah. Yeah. [laughs]
[knocking on window]
-Who's... who's this?
[banging on window]
-McLaughlin, I know
you're in there.
-All right, man.
- You see what I'm talking about?
- Kate!
-Hold on. I'm fucking coming.
-Huh? Kate! Kate!
Where is she?
Where's my daughter?
- She ain't here.
- Calm down, Billy.
-Ya fuckin' prick.
-Calm down.
-What do you think we are?
A bunch of fucking tree
jumpers? Look around!
Is this a place
for a teenage girl?
-Okay, you're
right. I apologize.
-Yeah, you damn right I'm right.
We got a bunch of
morals and codes
that we don't fucking break.
Don't disrespect
us like that again.
One more time, and
like that fucking ball
-Ooh.
-I just swung at,
you won't fucking exist.
-Hey, hold on. Hold on.
If Kate's missing,
maybe we can help.
-I don't need your kind of help.
-Oh, be nice, Billy.
- Yeah.
- [phone ringing]
-[into phone] Yeah? Yeah, sure.
Billy, you got a call.
-Here we go.
-We work for you now apparently.
-There you go.
-[into phone] Hello. Yeah.
Okay.
[phone thuds]
Kate's home.
-Uh, Billy, then.
-Billy, don't you ever come
in here like that again.
-[laughs] Nice job.
[door opens then closes]
-When did you start
sneaking out of the house?
-Mom, I just wanted
to go and hang out...
-Marty? He asked to
go steady, didn't he?
-Yeah.
-[Pat chuckles]
-Marty.
I just. I didn't know how
you guys were gonna react.
-Yes, I knew it.
You know how relieved
your Dad is gonna be
when he finds out
-[Kate chuckles]
that you're dating Marty?
When you came in
the house earlier,
I knew something special
happened in your life.
-Really? How?
-Your smile, and a
mother's intuition.
We just know these things.
-Yeah.
-I told your dad.
-Oh. What did he say?
-Marty is a good kid.
-Kate, you better
have an explanation!
-Calm down.
-Why is everyone telling me
to calm down all the time?
I'm calm. Where was she?
Huh?
-She sneaked out to go
hang out with Marty.
-Is that true?
-Yeah.
-You weren't with
the Bunkley kid?
- No!!
- You better not be lying!
-I'm not... I'm
not lying to you!
-Okay.
But I don't like the idea of
not knowing where you're at.
So next time, I don't give
a damn who you're with,
just let us know.
- All right.
- Am I clear?
-Yeah. Not a problem.
Can I go to my room now?
-Go ahead.
[footsteps receding]
[door slams]
-That girl is gonna drive
me to an early grave.
-I used to sneak out of
the house to meet you.
[soft music]
[birds chirping]
[fridge door closes]
So, what's on the agenda?
-Play catch.
And have the birds and
the bees talk with Dad.
-I'll let your mom tell
you all about the birds.
I'm gonna teach you about
the bees. They sting.
Get your glove.
Nice.
Oh, kid. Come on.
-Relax.
-Tell me about Marty.
-What do you mean,
tell me about Marty?
-Oops, strong arm.
Why you like him?
[birds chirping]
Hey.
Ball.
You gonna answer me?
-He reminds me of you.
-How you figure?
That kid is nothing like me.
I think he's a little soft.
You know, I'm not... I
was never a soft guy.
Which is why I like him for you.
You know, guys like that
don't have the sting
but they still get the honey.
You get my drift?
What's with that look?
-No, you're right.
Marty ain't nothing like you.
[locker door closes]
-How was it, workin' the jungle?
Hey, new guy. Talkin' to you.
-The name is Officer Coughlin.
-Okay, Officer Coughlin.
Don't bite my head off.
We're on the same team here.
I was askin', how was
workin' in the jungle?
-What are you talking about?
-Roxbury.
You know, land of the.
[clicking tongue] Negroes.
[locker closes]
[Bill sighs]
-It's like anywhere.
It has its ups and downs.
-Anyway, we decided
not to come in to work
on the first day of school.
-What about the kids?
-What, the spades? Fuck 'em!
-That's fucked up.
We swore an oath to
serve and protect,
and you cocksuckers
want to back out
now that the goin' gets tough?
-Hey, you don't fuckin'
talk to me like that!
You don't know me and I don't
think you wanna find out.
-Listen to me carefully.
My little girl is
going to school
and I'll be there to
protect her or anyone else
who needs my assistance,
so if you assholes
wanna keep your
asshole kids at home,
that's your choice.
[train honking]
[car honking]
[car door opens]
[gun cocks]
I'm a Boston police officer!
[car door closes]
Don't take another step.
-Billy, it's me.
Put the gun down.
-McLaughlin! What
the fuck, man?
Why you following me? I
coulda blown your brains out.
-[chuckles] Look, I knew
you wouldn't kill me.
I mean, you haven't
got it in you.
-I came pretty close.
What do you want?
-Uh, I hear you're
not cooperating.
It's this busing thing
that's driving me crazy.
I-I-I can't sleep. I
don't know how you can.
-Easy. I just close my eyes.
-[McLaughlin sighs]
Look, you and me,
we go way back.
I remember you like this.
Snot pouring out of your nose,
running around in your diapers.
We're family.
I protect my family
no matter what,
and I expect you to do the same.
Now your fellow officers have
asked you to band with them,
to protest this injustice,
this... this attack
on our neighborhood
and our way of life.
By these people that...
they're not like us.
They're just not like us.
You know, these
animals, they're...
They wanna destroy
our neighborhood.
Don't you get it?
Our neighborhood that
took generations to build,
that's what I'm talking about.
It means something.
Don't you fucking understand?
And what do you say?
All you say is what?
"Fuck you."
I mean, I'm beginning
to take it personally.
-Take it how you want.
-[McLaughlin sighs]
You know, there's
an old Irish saying:
"It's often that a man's
mouth breaks his nose."
-Is that a threat?
-Look, Billy boy.
What? You got that all wrong.
Threat?
[chuckles] No, no, no.
No, this is Southie.
This is my neighborhood.
[rumble of traffic]
Don't you make me
fucking do this.
Please.
All right?
You and Kate?
Stay home.
I mean it. Stay home.
[car door opens then closes]
- What's he talkin' about?
- I don't know.
[car door closes]
-I don't know why you
waste your time with him.
-He's a fucking rat.
You know, I could do it.
-Do what?
-Take care of business.
-Psh. You do what?
Just... you can
drive. That's it.
-Watch it.
-Maybe it's time for
some of your justice.
Make him into the saint
that he thinks he is.
[birds chirping]
-[Wendy sighs]
Ma was real pretty.
How come you never brought
another woman home?
-Why are you, all of sudden,
so interested in my
personal love life?
-[Wendy chuckles]
'Cause I know you sacrificed
your social life for me.
But, come on. I'm
about to go to college.
I think it's time for
you to find someone.
-Do you really?
-Yes. Yes. [chuckles]
-Don't worry about me
while you off in college.
Trust me, I will be fine.
I'm gonna grow me a afro,
I'm gonna go on Soul Train,
and I'm gonna get me a bad girl.
[laughter]
-Oh.
-Can you imagine if your
mama saw me in that?
-[Wendy laughing]
Well, um, I'll come
home every week
to check on you.
-[Lamont chuckles]
That would be
really, really nice.
-I'll knock first.
-Now, that would be wise.
[chuckles]
[overlapping protests on TV]
-[man on TV] Niggas suck!
-Those people hate us.
-Yes, they do.
That's why I'm glad you ain't
going to school tomorrow.
I mean, people teaching
their kids to hate.
Like. like them kids that...
that attacked us the other day.
I've never been so angry
and felt so powerless
to protect you...
-But you did protect
me. I'm still here.
-No, no, no, no,
because my first impulse
was to go and attack those
kids and make them regret
they'd ever picked up
a rock in their life.
And I almost put you in danger.
God knows if you
hadn't been there...
-God did know.
That's why I was there.
I've been thinking.
Because those kids attacked us,
I think that's why I
need to go to school.
-Not possible.
I-I-I would be so
worried about you, girl.
-Look, I need to go.
-Look.
-You're always
the one telling me
never let anyone make you
compromise your principles.
If kids like me don't
go, those white kids,
they'll... they'll
never get to know us.
There'll be no change,
and I need the teachers
and my classmates
to respect me for me
and not for who their
parents tell them I am.
I have to be brave.
Didn't you say that recently?
Didn't you want me
to go to school?
-That was before.
Black people have to.
Be ready to make one
choice in America,
and that's the choice
whether to stay in control
when white people
are out of control.
[people protesting on TV]
They're protestors.
But if you did
what they're doing
you would be called a criminal.
And you know how they treat
Black criminals in this country?
I don't want to put
you in a situation
where you got to make
that kind of choice.
-But if you believe
something is right,
you should do it.
-Them kids, they rattled me.
-Me too.
But we can't let them win.
[soft tense music]
-Patty Engel.
Patty Coughlin now, sorry.
How long's it been?
-Not long enough.
-Don't be like that.
Come on. You were my girl once.
Pat.
Listen.
I protected you
when all the other
kids made fun of you
because you was different.
Because you talked funny.
[car hood slams]
-That was a long time ago.
-I know.
I still feel a spark.
[keys jingle]
-Don't touch me.
-The way your husband is
acting, you never know.
You might be a widow someday.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-I'm just saying that
he's playing with fire.
All right? Making a
lot of people angry.
You never know
what could happen.
-You're sick. Get help.
-Well, listen.
[car door slams shut]
If anything happens,
I'll always be here
for you, all right?
Just like before.
You can count on me, all right?
- [Pat breathes deeply]
- [crickets chirping]
-[Bill sighs]
-McLaughlin insists you and
Kate stay home tomorrow.
It might be not a bad idea.
-I can't, Pat. I got
a responsibility.
-Just think about it.
-I have.
I've thought about it a lot.
You know, the other day
a Black child asked me,
"Why do white people hate us?"
-And you said?
-I said that I didn't hate her.
And there are more
people like me.
Besides that, I mean, I
didn't know what to say.
-What is it?
-Am I a racist?
-Of course not! What
makes you even think that?
-Nah. Jefferson said as much.
It made me think, that's all.
-You're the sweetest, most
honorable man I've ever met.
You're a good Catholic.
You love people, no matter
the color of their skin.
-I hope that's true. I hope.
I hope that's true.
But I think I know
what Jefferson meant.
You know, I deal with
racist people all the time
and, you know, I
don't say anything.
I don't call them on it.
So what does that make me? Huh?
-Stop.
Stop being so
critical of yourself.
It's not easy.
You know, we live on this
planet with all kinds of people,
some good and some bad.
You can't fix them all.
All you can do is make sure
our daughter turns out like us
and not them.
-Yeah. Okay.
Where you going?
-I almost forgot.
[dresser door opens then closes]
We have a problem.
-What?
Where'd you find this?
-In Kate's room.
-What the fuck?
Where'd she get this?
-Stop cursing! I don't know.
-[yells] Kate!
Come here, you.
[door opens]
Kate? Huh?
Where'd you get this?
Huh?
Answer me.
-You know. You know already.
-We don't know, so tell us.
Now!
-John gave it to me.
-Why'd I tell you to
stay away from that kid?
You think I said that
to be an asshole?
Look at it.
-[cries] No.
-Look at it.
Look at it.
Look at it very carefully.
-Mm-hm.
-Look at John's mother's face.
What do you see?
-She looks.
Scared.
-Yeah, she looks scared.
I took that picture.
Johnny beat the hell out
of Brenda the day before.
-[Kate sniffles]
-You wanna know why?
Because she took too
long talking to the guy
at the grocery store.
I had to drag him off of her.
[scoffs]
-So John is who
you're really dating?
-For Christ's sake,
you've been lying to us.
Why? Huh? Why you lying to us?
-What's gotten into you?
-He's not like his father,
and I knew you would
never approve of him.
I knew you would
-Let me tell you something.
Let me tell you something
about Johnny Bunkley,
okay? He's vicious.
I believe he killed
John's mother.
-You never told me that.
-Because I had no proof, okay?
And some things are not
meant to be talked about
till crap like this comes
up and secrets come out.
-Okay, did you
ever think of this?
Did you ever think that
maybe she deserved it
for sleeping with a coon?
[slap thrown]
-Don't use that
language in my house!
And how dare you say anyone
deserves to be killed?
What have you turned into?
-Okay, this has
gotten out of hand.
She's not going
to school tomorrow
till I talk to that
kid. You hear me?
Stay here. Don't you
leave this house.
-[Kate chuckles]
-And don't you ever
use that word again.
-Thank you. Thank
you, Mom and Dad,
for the best senior year ever.
Thank you! [chuckles]
-Clean up this mess.
-[Kate cries]
[dramatic music]
-I'm sorry I hit you.
But I'm disappointed
in your behavior.
I love you and I know
you're better than this.
-[Kate sniffles]
[birds chirping]
[clanking]
[newspaper rustles]
-[Bill sighs]
-Your pin.
-Not today.
I don't want the kids thinking
I'm not on their side.
Remember, that one.
She's not going to school.
-I know.
-Hey, I mean it.
-Okay.
[door opens then closes]
[door opens]
-[man on TV] [indistinct]
deserted his heritage.
It is his brother,
the late president,
[indistinct].
- [door closes]
-You scared?
Me too.
I got your back though.
Can I tell you something?
-Sure.
-Look, if I die today.
-Stop. You're not gonna die.
-Anything is possible
with these crackers.
I just, you need
to know how I feel.
-About what?
-About you.
Wendy, I. I like you.
More than a friend.
-We talked about this.
That can't happen.
-Why? We're always together.
-Yeah, we're...
We're best friends.
Best friends don't
think like that.
I can't believe you're
bringing this up right now.
-I-I don't want to die without
telling you how I feel.
-Stop. [chuckles]
[school bus door opens]
You ready?
[♪♪♪]
[people chattering]
-Fucking cops. [indistinct].
What the fuck is going on here?
What the fuck are you doing?
Why don't you go back
to fucking Roxbury
where you fucking belong?
Don't fucking touch me!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Do it. Do it, motherfucker.
You go back to where
you fucking came from.
Hey, let's get a chant going.
Hey, here we go,
Southie. Here we go.
[crowd] [chanting] Here we
go, Southie. Here we go!
[water running]
-You haven't touched your food.
-It's not right,
not letting me go.
-How could we trust you?
Everything you've told
us has been a lie.
-I know. I'm
really sorry, Mom.
But you and Dad would have
never approved of John.
-Could you blame him?
-Can't judge people
based on their parents.
You can't.
-Okay.
But to say someone
deserves to die,
that scares the hell out of me.
And to think my child
could utter those words.
-No, I know.
It was a heartless thing to
say and I'm really sorry.
But, Mom, Daddy isn't even sure.
Daddy's not sure that
Johnny killed his wife.
We don't know.
-Kate, are you listening
to what you're saying?
The fact that we're even
discussing this is scary.
Shame on you for hanging
around people like that.
-I know it was wrong
to lie to you guys.
I know that,
and I'm really sorry.
But how is keeping me
home gonna fix anything?
We're just gonna look
like the other families,
keeping their kids home
because the Black kids
are gonna be there.
It's wrong.
Mom,
you and Daddy are gonna look
like racists when you're not.
And Daddy was just really mad
and you didn't think of that.
-Are you trying to con me?
-No, it's the truth.
You know it is.
[sniffles] Plus,
I'm better off.
Dad's gonna be there and
he's gonna protect me
if anything happens.
Please, Mom. It's
my senior year.
So, can I go?
Thank you.
-Your father is going
to be very mad at me.
-[Kate sniffles]
-Love thy neighbor.
It sounds simple,
but it's the hardest
commandment to live by.
-I know.
[footsteps receding]
[door opens then closes]
Hey, good morning,
Mrs. Bunkley.
[siren wailing]
[protesters rioting]
Marty! Marty!
-Let me guess. John
thinks you should protest.
I never thought you
would have given up
the start of your senior
year to be out here.
-No, no, no.
There's not gonna be
a senior year, Marty, okay?
The Blacks took that from us.
-Kate, you got it wrong. We
took that from ourselves.
Look around you.
You know, you're a
different person now.
John can have you.
-Marty!
[horn blaring]
[man] It's the bus.
Hey, hey. Get out of here.
Get out of here!
- [protesters rioting]
- [intense music]
-Let me off this bus.
[protesters rioting]
I'll fuck those peasants up!
I'm not scared of these fuckers!
[protesters rioting]
Fuck this, man!
Fuck you! Fuck all y'all!
Fuck you!
-Fuck you!
[glass shatters]
[protestors shouting]
[car door closes]
-Go home!
This is not the
way to handle this!
Disperse in the name
of the Commonwealth
or you'll be arrested.
-Just tip it over.
[bus rattling]
[protesters rioting]
Help me push it over!
Let's go! Let's do it!
-Stay in here.
Stay in... don't!
Do not go there.
Lamont! Lamont!
Lamont, what the
hell are you doing?
You can't go in that crowd!
- I told you,
my daughter is on the bus.
-Listen, let the police
do what they're gonna do.
They see a Black man and
it will make matters worse.
[protesters rioting]
-Hey, what the fuck!
[thudding]
[bus door opens]
[bus driver] Oh, thank God.
We... we've got a
troublemaker back there.
-Listen, no one is
starting trouble, okay?
These kids are scared to death.
-No, no. That... that little kid
standing there with
the... With the afro.
He's been agitating all
those people outside.
- Screw you.
- Fuck your mother.
-Hey, sit down.
[protesters rioting]
-Clear the way for the students.
If you stand in the way,
you will be arrested.
All right, everybody, listen up.
I know you're scared, okay,
but we're here to protect you.
I want everyone to stay as close
to me and Officer Jefferson
when you get off the bus, okay?
Single file. Am I clear?
All right, let's go to school.
-I wanna go home.
-This is shit, man.
[indistinct] Huh?
Wendy? Wendy!
-Hey! Oh.
-Wendy! Wendy!
-Wait, wait, wait.
Stay behind me.
Stay behind.
[protesters rioting]
-Wendy!
Get the hell off!
[protesters rioting]
-[crying] They're
not listening to you.
-'Cause they're fuckin' idiots.
-Excuse me. Excuse me!
[rapid gunfire]
[protesters screaming]
-Wendy!
-[Kate screaming]
Ah! No! No, no!
No, that's my dad!
[car engine revving]
-Oh, my god. Baby, you okay?
Hey, get somebody over here.
-Daddy! Daddy! Daddy!
-All right, give me this.
Pressure's really, really
low. Keep the pressure on.
Get him.
I need you to look
after my little girl.
I need you to take care of her.
Honey, honey, deep breaths.
- More pressure. More pressure.
-Deep breaths!
-That's my dad! That's my dad!
Daddy!
[woman] [on intercom]
Dr. Gale, please call the ER.
-How is he? How's my husband?
-In the operating room. Okay?
All right, he's a
fighter. All right?
And next time you talk
to him, you tell him
I'm sorry that I ever
doubted him. Okay?
Bobby Kennedy can't
even walk in his shadow.
He'll understand what I mean.
It's because of him
Bill made it this far.
-Is that my husband's blood?
-Your husband stepped
in front of a bullet
meant for my little girl.
If he hadn't been
there. [cries]
[sniffles]
-Thank you for being there.
-[Lamont sniffles]
-[Mayor White speaking on TV]
-You mean school
really wasn't that bad?
-No. Ma, it was fine.
-I don't get it.
They wasn't nasty?
And then they didn't
call you names?
-No. They're
actually really cool.
I sat with a bunch
of girls at lunch.
We're friends now.
-Hm. Will wonders never cease.
-I do. Turn up the volume.
I want to hear what
this asshole has to say.
-. to act responsibly and
hold the community together.
[chattering on radio comms]
[dog barking in distance]
-Hey, what's going on?
What are you doing?
I. what's going on?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Stand the fuck down.
Stand the fuck.
What'd you do?
What'd you do, man?
[footsteps]
-Are you okay?
I want you to meet the
wife of the officer.
This is Missis Coughlin.
This is my daughter, Wendy.
-Hey, nice to meet you.
-Thank God you're not hurt.
How are you feeling, dear?
-Okay, I guess.
-And this is their
daughter, Kate.
Will you look after
her for a second?
I want to go and talk to the
doctor just to ask a question.
I'll be right back.
-I'm sorry for what
happened to your dad.
-[Kate sniffles]
I hope he doesn't
die because of you.
Don't look at me like that.
Am I supposed to be happy
if my dad dies a hero?
Why did you have
to come to Southie?
Why couldn't you
just stay in Roxbury?
-I've seen you before.
-What?
No, I don't think so.
-Yeah, I have.
You were throwing
rocks at our car.
You tried to kill us.
You know, if your dad dies,
it's not because a
Black man shot him.
It's because people like
you who pulled the trigger.
Racist, hateful people...
-[Kate sobs]
I'm sorry. I'm
sorry. I'm sorry.
Mom, I should've
listened to you.
I'm sorry.
[cries]
I should have listened to you.
-It's gonna be okay.
-Oh, Dad. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[sobbing]
-How is he?
-Uh, he's stable.
-Can we see him?
-Uh, yes, for a few minutes.
-Come on. Let's go see him.
[footsteps]
-Dad, she was one of the kids
who was throwing
rocks at our car.
-I did not see that coming.
I mean, with parents like that.
I don't even know how to feel.
-I'm angry.
Like you said, I don't
understand... her parents. I...
-You know, your
mother used to talk
to the neighborhood hoodlums.
And I'd always ask her,
"Why do you waste your
time talking to them?"
And she'd say that a bad act
doesn't make a bad person.
-Ma was special.
-Yeah, she was.
And she would be so very,
very proud of you today.
You put yourself in danger.
And I don't ever want
you to do that again.
But, my god, you reminded
me of her so much.
[sniffles] You're so brave
and I'm very proud of you.
-Thanks, Dad.
[cries]
[heart monitor beeping]
-[whispering] Bill.
If you can hear me,
you need to know.
You're a good man.
You're a very good man.
[heart monitor beeping]
-[Kate cries silently]
[beeping echoes]