(energetic hip hop music)
♪ Oh get it baby ♪
♪ Everybody get butt ♪
♪ Naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ Everybody get butt ♪
♪ Naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ Let me get right to the point ♪
♪ You sure now put me on ♪
♪ You say you like the way I hang ♪
♪ And I like your body form ♪
♪ Do what we ♪
♪ Get out of here ♪
♪ My place is out the door ♪
♪ Just as soon as we get there ♪
♪ We gonna spread out on the floor ♪
♪ Everybody get butt ♪
♪ Uh huh yeah ♪
♪ Naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ Don't ya don't ya ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ Don't you like it baby ♪
♪ Everybody get butt ♪
♪ Naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ Just as soon as we get through ♪
♪ I'm gonna pick up the telephone ♪
♪ Got to call some party people ♪
♪ Got to get them here to my home ♪
♪ And I know they'll be on the way ♪
♪ And soon be at the door ♪
♪ But they don't want to exchange them things ♪
♪ They just want to get in yours ♪
♪ Everybody get butt ♪
♪ Uh huh yeah ♪
♪ Naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ Don't ya don't ya ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ Now don't you like it baby ♪
♪ Everybody get butt ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
♪ Naked ♪
♪ We gonna get butt naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ Freaking freaking ♪
♪ Like it ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Somebody say ♪
♪ Call them Mona Lisa ♪
♪ Anything your ass can try ♪
♪ Girl like to party ♪
♪ You know she just like through down ♪
♪ Call them Mona Lisa ♪
♪ Anything your ass can try ♪
♪ You do what you want ♪
♪ She likes to get her freak on ♪
♪ Shook 'em up, freak 'em up on the left ♪
♪ Shook 'em up, freak 'em up on the right ♪
♪ Shook 'em up, freak 'em up, freak 'em up ♪
♪ Shook 'em up, freak 'em up, shook 'em up front ♪
♪ Shook 'em up, freak 'em up in the back ♪
♪ Shook 'em up, freak 'em up in the rear ♪
♪ Butt naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
(bell ringing)
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey.
- How y'all doing?
- Hey, hey.
- Can I help you? - What's up, what's up?
Yeah my name Dayrun Southboy.
- Uh huh.
- This my main man, Kenny Flyy.
- Kenny Flyy.
- And, Fly you got reservations, right?
- Yeah.
- All right but hold on, let me type you on that.
See what we got here.
Brothers I don't see a Kenny Flyy in the computer.
- I thought you made reservations, man.
No, it wouldn't be under my name.
- I called man,
check under two Y.
F L Y Y.
- I thought you made reservations, dog.
- Man I called up in here, man.
- Damn.
- I'm sorry fellas, I don't have anything
under Kenny Flyy with two Y's.
- Check this out, all right.
You got rooms right?
- Yeah, we have rooms.
- OK, Flyy got his credit cards.
- Oh y'all straight.
Y'all in there.
Let me see what you got.
Oh.
We don't accept this card.
- Don't accept it?
- No we can't take this, baby.
I don't know what to tell you.
I mean there's a couple of other hotels down the road
if you want to try them.
I mean, they accept this but we can't take it.
I'm sorry.
- No, no.
Flyy done bought everything with that card.
CDs, food, gas.
Even rented a car.
We got a car to get down here.
- Yeah I understand all that,
but we can't take that card.
You can't get no hotel room with that card.
Car, CD, like you know whatever.
Can't get no hotel room with it.
I'm sorry, baby.
- Look, look, look, we drove all the way down from Watts
at Howell University.
- Uh huh.
- We're very tired and I mean
all the hotels are crowded.
You know its black spring break.
- Yeah you right, so I'm saying,
you're from Howell University, fine.
Why is taking you so long to understand
that we don't accept that card?
- Baby, baby.
- Yes, what?
- How about we do dinner tonight?
Me and you?
- Me and you?
- Me and you.
- Dinner?
- Dinner.
- What time?
- You make the time.
- Let me see if I can run this thing.
Oh, what do you know?
It went through.
- What do you know?
- OK, hold on.
Let me, do some last minute things here.
Hey, you're all set, fellas
and here go your keys.
So while you fellas have a great black spring break.
♪ We freak 'em high ♪
♪ We freak 'em low ♪
♪ We freak them girls ♪
♪ Straight to the floor ♪
♪ Do this ♪
♪ Get 'em up ♪
♪ Pump that. ♪
- Daytona!
- Its about time.
(mumbling)
- You don't know about this beach, boy.
(chattering)
- What's up with ya, man?
- Something to it.
- Been ready for this day, man.
Get ready for this day.
- Oh girl, I can't believe we here.
- Girl we about to have some fun.
This my third time here and I always have fun
but see this will be the most fun of all.
- Why's that?
- There's no man in my life
and I don't have to feel guilty
if I meet someone I like.
Since Southboy and I broke up,
I've been yearning to get here.
- Damn dog, you know what I don't understand
about this shit, man?
- What's up?
- We got 24 hours, dog.
All other colleges have two whole months, dog.
We got one day, my nigga.
- Hey damn, Flyy.
I just put in one year rap.
All right, man.
All I know is that we in Daytona Beach
and it's time to get loose.
- I feel you on that, though, baby.
I feel you on that.
You know what I'm saying?
- You out here to get your freak on?
- See, I'm free now.
I free, so you never know.
- Girl you is crazy.
- You know its time to what.
- [Both] P A R T Y.
- And you know DJ Spankx is here.
- Oh DJ Spinx.
I just love me some DJ Spankx girl.
- The girl in the lobby said that he's having his record
release party tonight and you know see all
the football players and actors are here, too.
- Girl, we could party later.
First thing first, I need to go see my man.
- See your man?
Look, look.
You my baby cousin, I love you right
but you need to wake up.
Michael ain't called you in what, two months
and he wouldn't even tell you which hotel
he was staying at.
- He probably didn't know yet, Raynesha.
- Excuses excuses, girl.
- For your information, I called his mother
and she told where he was staying at.
- OK, miss freshman, OK.
- Man you know in about a couple hours, man,
the beach gonna be full of honeys.
Just lovely honeys.
- Yeah you right about that, my nigga.
Bitches gonna be everywhere, you know what I'm saying,
black bitches, red bitches, brown bitches,
know what I'm saying?
The beach gonna be packed with bitches.
- Just make sure you knock first
'cause he may be in there knocking boots
like H-Town if you know what I'm saying.
- Flyy, why they got to be bitches, man?
I mean why can't they be honeys and ladies
and something like that?
Why they got to be bitches?
- Hold up, Southboy, what kind of nigga is you, man?
You about to go to the NFL, dog.
Know what I'm saying?
Make that little $2,000,000 a year.
Get commercials, man, do shoe contracts,
the whole nine dog, you know what I'm saying?
Let me tell you what Flyy think.
I think any lady you meet right now
ain't gonna be no honey or no lady.
You know what I'm saying?
Just a straight up bitch.
Nigga, that's right.
Bitch, gold digging, foot dragging, bitch.
Know what I'm saying, dog?
- So what happened between you and Southboy?
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Why not, Ray?
I thought y'all was about to get married
and all that.
I remember everything was Southboy this, Southboy that.
Y'all was together since your freshman year
and now it's towards it the end of your junior year
and it's over just like that?
- Just like that.
I don't want to talk about it.
OK?
- All right.
- Look, I will tell you this.
You need to be careful with Michael
'cause ain't nothing out here in Daytona
but some booty shaking freaky girls this weekend.
- Ray, Michael loves me and nothing's gonna change that.
- Look look you my cousin, I love you,
but you're a freshman, you're just in puppy love.
- Ray, that's killer, all right,
me and Michael are cool.
- OK, see see, I'm through with it.
But let's go get our grub on but do me a favor.
Please let them pay for it,
do you hear me?
- Why you telling me this?
- 'Cause you pay for everything on the way down here.
Gas, food, all of that.
- Well Kenny charged the rental car on his credit card
so I thought we could at least pay for a few things.
- See, all I'm saying is this.
Let Southboy kick out a little bit.
If he decides to leave school and go pro
he'll be making a bank load of money
in a couple of months.
Make 'em pay, that's all I'm saying.
- Make 'em pay, then.
- And Flyy, you tripping man.
And you using Ebonics while you doing it, dog.
- Feel me, dog?
Do you feel me?
- Hey man, all I know, all right,
is that we in Daytona Beach, all right,
no reporters, no sports agents, no coaches.
Just fun and sun.
(bell dinging)
- Hello?
- What you want?
- I want a room.
- Can't you see that this is black spring break?
- Well yeah, I know that.
- And your ass still want a room?
- Well yeah.
- Well, all right.
I don't want to see your little white ass
jumping out the elevator screaming,
oh my God, I was attacked.
It was awful.
Five niggas jumped on me.
They took my bag, they beat me down,
they called me names, oh God.
Somebody call the police.
It was horrible.
I think one of them was Tupac.
I think one of them was Big Poppa.
Oh God damn, why did I come to black spring break?
Why, why?
Why?
- Look here, boy, you in a whole heap of shit.
It's black spring break and it's a bunch
of niggas running up an down this beach here.
Let me show you what I mean.
See that there?
You gonna need it.
911.
Quick.
Watch it's all in the wrist.
Not all.
911, get his ass up out of here.
Let's go.
Make it quick, make a move.
Get the hell on.
Let's go.
Act like he ain't want to get up out of here.
- Excuse me, is there like, I mean like a problem here?
- Oh no, I'm just letting you know what the deal is, sir.
Now do you have a credit card?
- Well, yeah.
- Well, are you going to use the damn credit card?
- Well, first I need some information.
- Look, $85 for a single room,
$100 for a double room
and I need a $200 deposit.
- No, no.
I mean, I need to find out if there's somebody staying
here in the hotel.
- Well, what are you, some kind of cop or something?
Huh?
Haven't you all arrested enough niggas this year?
Now you got to come down to Daytona Beach
and arrest somebody and mess up
they little spring break, huh?
- No, OK.
No, you got it all wrong.
See, my name is Vinnie, OK, I'm a sports agent.
Here's my card.
I'm looking for a all American by name of Dayrun Southboy.
He's from Watson Howell University.
- Is he going to the NFL?
- You're damn right he's going to the NFL.
He's like the best of the hands on a tight end
since Kellen Winslow.
- Kellen who?
- It doesn't matter.
Just let me know, is he staying here in the hotel?
- What's in it for me?
Oh, shit.
This ain't no money.
Uh uh, you can't get no room number with this.
No, no.
Don't you know?
I got two kids at home and they daddy
won't do shit for them?
They probably crying right now at my mama's house
saying all kinds of crazy shit like,
why my mama got to be my daddy?
I want my daddy.
I don't want to be a bastard.
I want my mama to make good money on her job.
Why white people don't tip her good?
$20 ain't shit.
Can't you hear my children screaming?
- Yeah, I can hear 'em screaming, all right?
Well here, here's 100 bucks.
Just tell me what the damn room number is.
- OK well, he's in room 415 and he checked in
about an hour ago with one cute guy and two hoochies.
- Wait a minute.
I thought this hotel didn't take pets.
What's he doing with hoochies?
- You are dumber than you look.
A hoochie is a girl, got it.
Where you from anyway?
- New York.
- Yeah, you look like you from New York.
What you here.
You one of them mobsters kind of people, huh?
Yeah your last name ends in O, don't it?
- What difference does it make?
- Nah because it do.
Now what is it, huh?
Bet it's some crazy shit like Gambino
or Deniro or Pacino or Del Greco
or Spaghetti-o or Romeo or Oreo.
- What are you kidding me?
- Peso or Amico or Stereo or Texaco.
- Look, its DelVechhio, OK.
DelVecchio.
D E L V E C C H I O, OK?
And if it will make you happy
it's Vincenzo DelVecchio.
- Well, wait a minute now.
See 'cause you ain't got to try to shine on me
'cause I can act like a nigga when I gots to.
OK?
Now.
Did I hear some money coming from your way?
- Jesus, what is everyone here on the take?
- Oh, I don't know about everybody else.
See 'cause I'm just concerned
with Daquala Sayonra Guladalajara Mascara Cleoptra Smith.
- DeShawn, I told you that was Dayrun Southboy
that checked in this morning.
That agent looking for him girl, he going pro.
- Oh how you know so much about him?
- Girl you know I get all the sports magazines
in the mail.
He on the cover of College Football World this month.
He got to Watson Howell.
Remember when they came to beat us?
- Girl, everybody came and beat our team.
- Don't they they but you know what?
I'm gonna get Dayrun Southboy.
- You seen him walking in
with them two girls, didn't ya?
- Oh, it don't matter 'cause once I put it on his ass,
he'll be wilt.
- And how you figure?
- 'Cause girl, my shit is so tight.
I'm talking about making him scream and holler, OK.
And sleep like a baby.
- Nigga, I think I heard you talking that same shit
the last time you was after a football player
and what happened to him, OK.
Uh huh.
- Shit, the problem was he was looking
for the same thing I was looking for.
- Which was?
- Dick.
- You ain't telling me nothing about that, girl.
- Girl.
He wasn't nothing but a peanut butter
pack of dookie lover, or whatever you want
to call it.
All I could do for him was show him another man.
- Enough about him.
Anyway, Neeka, how you gonna rope off Southboy?
Enough about him, OK.
- Lashawn, shit is different, OK.
And I got that hair back on right now.
And it's so crucial.
- How crucial?
- So crucial, straight up crucial real like that girl.
- You ain't got no cocks.
You ain't got no go sister.
- Yeah, yeah.
Hey yeah, it's me.
Uh huh, oh yeah, yeah.
Yeah Southboy's already here.
Already the center of attention.
(laughing)
Hoes and agents all over the place you see?
Yeah, look, look, look.
I think I'm gonna need you to
fly Sherry down here, you know
open up his nose a little bit, you know?
Yeah, oh yeah you right.
Nobody can resist that man. (laughing)
Yeah but look, look you just get her down here.
Now whatever it takes.
OK?
Whatever it takes.
(laughing)
- So what's up big dog?
Who you want to play for, know what I'm saying,
the Dolphins, the Bears, the Steelers.
Who?
- Hey Flyy.
Know why I wear this, man?
- No, I don't.
I've been wondering.
- So I don't forget where I come from, man.
See what I'm saying?
I ain't never had shit, man.
So it don't really matter to me who I play for,
you know what I'm saying?
It ain't even about the money, dog.
As long as I get a chance
to start at tight end.
You know what I'm saying?
- I feel you dog, I feel you.
But I'm saying that when you get to be
that big football player and all that shit, dog,
I got one thing I want you to do for me, dog.
- What's that man?
- Man I want you to start a record company, dog.
I got some bombing ass shit, know what I'm saying,
but don't none of these motherfuckers
want to put me on, dog.
- Cool, you got my word on it.
You got it. - True dat, true dat.
- Hey what happened to that demo record
you sent up there to Pacific Records in California, man?
- Man like I'm saying, man.
These record companies are flawed, dog.
Man, I sent 'em some shit, dog,
the motherfuckers, you know what I'm saying,
don't do, you know what I'm saying.
They say I sound too different, dog.
I tried accommodating them, man.
They said I sound like some other niggas,
you know what I'm saying?
I'm in a no win situation, dog.
- Fuck you doing, Flyy?
- Exercising, dog, exercising.
- Man how in the fuck is that exercising, man?
- You see how I curl it up, dog, back and forth?
- Flyy, I'm in training, man,
you know I can't be around this shit, man.
- Man, just repeat what I'm telling you
about the exercise, dog.
I curl it up.
Puff.
And a puff, know what I'm saying?
Then if I, another nigga was here,
I'd hand it to him, you know what I'm saying?
That's exercise, too.
Know what I'm saying?
- Hey man, you tripping man.
Get your ass ready to go, man.
We got breakfast with Ray and Cindy, man.
Get ready to go man, put some clothes on.
- All right, dog.
After I finish exercising, all right?
- See, now that's a tattoo.
That is a tattoo.
- That ain't no damn tattoo.
My boy Flyy got tattoos.
These niggas bullshitting.
Flyy, come on, dog.
Show your tattoos.
- See no real motherfucking.
- Show your tattoos, dog.
- Hold my shit.
- Let's see what Flyy got.
- Come on, Flyy, what's up?
Yeah.
- Let's see.
Flyy ain't got no tattoos.
- Damn all that bullshit.
My dog does, my dog got tattoos, you know what I'm saying?
Damn.
- Stop. - They aight.
- Hey C, you like that?
- It's fine.
- She like them pretty motherfuckers.
She like them untampered with motherfuckers.
- You know you like them ripples.
- Like Michael.
- Hey where Michael at?
- Why y'all tripping?
- Flyy here.
Damn Michael.
- Michael!
- Mike!
- Where Michael at?
- Y'all is bugging.
- Flyy here.
- Mikey, I like him.
- Y'all bugging.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Check this out, check this out.
I got some money.
You ain't see Mike this weekend.
That's what I'm saying.
- Anyway, anyway.
- [Southboy] Mike don't give a damn about you girl.
- Ain't see you in two months.
- He ain't come by the hotel.
He ain't come by the hotel.
He ain't answer your call.
What's up?
- His mama had to tell you where he was at.
- I tell you with Flyy.
Know what I'm saying?
I say you with Flyy.
- That's cute, that's cute.
♪ Everybody all around ♪
♪ Is jamming on their chain ♪
♪ Yeah yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
♪ Everybody all around ♪
♪ Is jamming on their chain ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
♪ Everybody all around ♪
♪ Is jamming on their chain ♪
♪ Yeah yeah ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
♪ Everybody all around ♪
♪ Is jamming on their chain ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh baby ♪
(funky electric music)
(man grunting)
- Damn that shit what y'all talking about.
Know what I'm saying?
Told his ass to be ready at 4:00 a.m.
He wasn't man, he missed the boat, man.
Fuck him.
- Man, Greg will be mad he ain't got a ride to Daytona.
- Hey hey, I don't see how he was
gonna fit in the car anyway.
- Know what I'm saying?
- He would have fit.
We probably should of waited for him a little longer.
- Look, we were ready.
He wasn't, fuck him.
- Man, I don't care what none of y'all say.
I still think that was Greg standing on the highway
trying to hitch a ride.
- Ray, that don't make any sense, all right.
We left the boy at school.
How we gonna see him on the highway?
- To me it looked like Greg there, I still wasn't sure.
- I'm telling you that was Greg.
That was him.
- I didn't see no Greg on the highway.
- Man shit.
Niggas ain't shit, niggas ain't shit.
Can't believe they me got into this.
It's hot as hell out here.
Niggas left me, man.
That's fucked up.
Man you.
I knew I should have took my ass to Harvard
or Yale or somewhere the hell away from this.
Man you wait, you wait.
I see Kenny Flyy, I'm-a fuck his ass up.
Southboy, Raynesha, Charity, all of them.
Fuck 'em!
Hey give a nigga a ride.
Hey!
Hey.
Come on give a nigga a ride.
I ain't OJ, I ain't gonna cut your ass.
Damn, man, damn!
- Oh man, that was good, that was good.
- [Flyy] Got me tight though.
- It was straight.
- Southboy? - Yeah, yeah?
- Look at them girls over there pointing at you.
- [Southboy] Who's that?
- You like my boy?
- Girl, he think all the girls are looking at him.
He's the football all American.
Day Southboy, Day Day.
(fake moaning)
- I know it hurt, Ray, but it's all good.
- It's all right.
- It's all good.
- Waitress. - Yes?
- Can I please get the check?
- Sure.
- Oh shit.
What y'all niggas paying for something?
Take a picture of this.
- Ray, I don't know why you tripping, all right.
Me and Flyy rented the car to get down here.
- Oh hold up.
Well Charity and myself fed y'all niggas
the whole way down here.
Gash up that little card.
And bought us taste at the truck stop.
Thank you.
- Well Ray, you wanted the new music.
I was perfectly fine listening to Flyy's demo tape.
- Weak.
- You liked it?
- Yeah.
I think you're good
but I got one suggestion for you.
- What's up baby?
- You need a fat track with a girl singing on it
while you rap back at that slamming.
- You know any young ladies that can sing?
- Charity can sing, she is the bomb.
- Chill, Ray.
- Girl you rode your skills, let it be known.
- Why you holding back, baby?
Flaunt your skills.
- Cash or credit card?
- That will be credit.
- Damn, Flyy.
How much money you got on that credit card.
- Enough to feed y'all greedy motherfuckers.
That's for sure.
- God damn, every time I turn around
you whipping that card out your ass
to buy something with.
- And there they go again.
Sweating Flyy about his god damn credit card.
Look, the crackers gave it to me.
I'ma use it, dog.
- Hey damn that man, you done bought everything
with this card, all right.
Everything from the CDs, the hotel rooms to reefer.
(laughing)
- Tell me something, Flyy.
How much interest do you put on your credit card?
- Bitches, look, I don't know about that.
- Well, can you tell me how long your grace period is?
- I don't deal in all that shit, know what I'm saying?
- Look, look.
It figures.
Just another nigga that get a credit card
in the mail and out to run it up
as high as he can.
- Hey man, why you people sweating me, dog.
- She's sweating you, man.
- Hold up, I ain't sweating you.
Who gonna be sweating you are the credit card people.
It's time for you to pay that bill.
- Fuck them.
- Yo look man, you got to understand Ray, all right.
- Understand Ray.
- Look, Ray is an accounting major.
OK?
So she's on this niggas can't handle credit cards kick.
- Look, look.
All I'm saying is that if he keep using the card
the way he is, he's gonna pull it out one day,
little credit card bus gonna say declined.
Then what, Flyy?
- It look like my card working fine right now.
- Hey, ain't no need to get upset, man.
Yo, yo, Ray.
You are tripping.
- Hold up, hold up, hold up.
What you talking bout, Southboy, huh?
What you gonna do with your millions?
What you gonna run out and buy what,
10 Benz and five Hummers like the rusty sore ass niggas
that go pro?
Or are you gonna be a man about yours
and invest it.
- Ray, Ray.
We in Daytona Beach and you're talking about investments.
What's up?
- No chill, chill.
Chill, see it's cool, it's cool.
For your information, Ray.
I plan on doing a lot of investing.
- Oh a lot of investing.
- Yeah.
There's one key.
I'm gonna have an accountant I can trust.
(laughing)
- Oh shit.
- Somebody I can really really trust.
- Hey let's jam, big dog.
Let's get the fuck up out of here, man.
- I'm out.
- OK.
Protect yourself, Southboy.
Don't want you to get caught tripping
before the draft, you know what I'm saying?
- You don't have to worry about it.
- What he mean he need somebody he can trust?
- Man girl, bump him, OK.
I'm out.
With his sidekick Robin.
I'm about to go find me a real nigga.
I'll see you later.
- I'm going to see Michael.
I'll catch you later.
- [Receptionist] Next.
- Hello. - Hi.
- I would like to know if there's
a Michael Williams staying here.
- Yes ma'am, he sure is.
- Can I have his room number?
- Well, it says here he requested his room number
be blocked from anyone who calls or walks in.
- Well, there must be some kind of mistake.
He knew I was gonna be down here.
Can you call him downstairs for me?
- Yes, please let me try.
Yes, Michael Williams, please.
Front desk, hi.
I have a young lady requesting your room number.
Your name please?
- I'm his girlfriend Charity Hawkings.
- Charity Hawkings.
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
That's not nice.
I understand.
Thank you.
Enjoy your stay, sir.
He says please leave your hotel name
and your room number and he'll call you later.
- You're kidding right?
- I'm sorry.
Would you like to leave the information?
- No, I do not want to leave no information.
If he's upstairs, why he can't come downstairs
and talk to me?
- I'm sorry, Charity, that's all I can do.
- I can't believe this shit!
- Yeah, hi honey, it's me.
Yeah, yeah he's here.
What?
Oh the weather.
What are you kidding me?
Its beautiful here.
No, no honey, I haven't seen him yet.
No, but I got a room right down the hall from him.
Yeah honey, I know.
Yeah honey, I understand.
Honey, I said I know.
OK, if I don't sign this guy
I gotta go back to selling used cars.
Honey, I know the kids are hungry.
Yeah, I know the mortgage is due.
OK honey, look.
What?
Some guy came and repossessed the car?
What you didn't offer to blow him or nothing?
No honey, honey, no I'm just kidding, honey.
No, I don't want you blowing strange men.
- See Shaw, it say right here, girl.
- What it say, girl?
- It says Dayrun Southboy decided the NFL draft
he'll be a top five pick in the first round.
His services will demand at least 2,000,000 a year
and probably signing bonus
in the neighborhood of $3,000,000.
- So what you gonna do, girl?
- Oh my god, girl.
I'ma set his ass up, girl.
I'll lay it right now, girl.
Oh I can feel it.
If he bust a good one in me right now,
you know I gots to get paid up for 18 years.
And you know what?
Might get a little sign up bonus myself, girl.
- Neeka, you is ruthless.
But that's what I love 'bout you.
You know what you want.
- You damn straight and I want Southboy, Shawn.
I'm gonna get his ass.
- Well, you ain't gonna get him looking like that.
So you best to go up to the room and get hooked up.
- Let's do our thing, girl.
- OK girl.
- Hey damn, she fine, man.
See that?
- That's real dope, boy.
God.
Black spring break.
Like box of chocolates.
Never know what type of bitch you gonna get.
(laughing)
Know what I'm saying?
- Hey, hey you can crack jokes all you want, man,
that was messed up you left Greg on the highway.
- Like Forrest Gump say, shit happens.
(laughing)
♪ Friends the word we use everyday ♪
♪ Most the time we use it in the wrong way ♪
♪ Now you can look the word up ♪
♪ Again and again ♪
♪ But the dictionary doesn't know ♪
♪ The meaning of friend ♪
- Yo, buddy, I'm trying to get to black party spring break
in Daytona, you headed that way?
- Yeah man.
- Can I get a ride, man?
- $50, man.
Take it or leave it.
- $50?
Man this is ain't no grand.
What you got a bathroom here or something?
You showing a movie right?
- Show me the money, man.
- Show me the mon, ain't this a bitch.
Show me the money.
Niggas ain't play.
I tell ya, y'all shady.
Y'all motherfucker's shady.
Here, $50 right here, man.
Just let me get my bags aight.
- Go get your bags, man.
- Hey!
Oh hell no.
Damn, shit!
I know this ain't happening to me.
- Hey boardwalk is thick dog.
Damn you got the camera?
- No dog, it's up in the room.
I'm feeling go up there anyway, dog.
That shit from this morning, man,
fucking with my stomach, dog.
I got to go take a shit.
(laughing)
- Nigga got the runs.
Hey chili side,
I'm go and take a walk down on the beach, man.
I'll be on this end.
- All right, man.
- All right.
How's the prettiest girl on the beach?
(mumbling)
Chill, chill, Ray, it's just me.
- Hey Dayrun.
- Dayrun?
What's this Dayrun shit?
You ain't called me that since god knows when.
- Well everybody else calls you Southboy.
- You weren't everybody else though, right?
You're my girl.
- Oh your girl?
When I started getting treated like everybody else
I started acting like everybody else.
- Come on chill, Ray, all right.
Damn.
What's up girl?
You looked stressed out.
You want me to run you down today?
(laughing)
- I can handle it, OK.
You know I love attention.
Something I couldn't get from you?
- Ray don't even go there, all right.
- You know its true, Dayrun.
- True? - True.
- What we talking about true and trust, all that shit?
- Yes. - That's why you
go out there and fucked Terry Miller, huh?
You violated our trust, Ray.
- Don't tell me about trust, OK?
When every ho on campus has your telephone number.
You just got what, over 50 set of roses
and over 200 damn Valentine Day cards.
Besides, I told you it was something that just happened,
anyways, so leave it at that.
- Happened? - Happened.
- Happened?
Give me a fucking break, all right?
Hurricanes happen, car accidents happen.
You giving Terry Miller some pussy
ain't no shit that just happen.
(clapping)
- Are you hurt, Southboy, huh?
When every freak on campus is running behind you
day and night, Southboy, Southboy, Southboy.
- Ray, damn those other girls, OK?
All I wanted was you.
- Then why in the heck were you screwing them hos
if I'm the only one you wanted?
- Ray, I wasn't fucking nobody, all right?
Damn what they was telling you.
I wasn't fucking nobody.
I wasn't cheating on you.
- Don't worry about it, it's all right, OK?
Look, you'll be a multimillionaire in a few months,
you can have all the cars, and all the girls you want.
- Damn all that shit, Ray.
Damn that material shit, all right?
Fuck the cars, hos, fame.
It ain't about that, OK?
Me and you been together since our freshman year.
You should know me better than that by now.
- Better than that, better.
From the moment I met you,
I didn't lay my eyes on anyone else, OK?
I changed my life around for you.
Until-- - Until you
fucked Terry Miller.
- I told you it was an accident.
- Accident? - Accident.
- Back on this accident shit.
Tell you what, Miss Accident,
why don't you answer this question for me?
Was the dick good?
No, no, I got a better question.
Did you suck his dick?
- How could you say something like that to me?
- Fuck that, Ray, don't turn this shit around on me.
You the one that fucked him. - Go to hell.
- You the one that fucked him.
- Damn, big dog, what's up, man?
You got your people fire hot with you, man.
- Ex-people, man, ex-lady, all that.
- Whatever, dog, whatever.
What's up?
- Hey, camera ready?
- Camera ready, dog.
- Let's go look at some real hos, man.
Damn this shit.
- God.
How could I be so stupid?
Ray was right, he ain't about shit.
I can't tell Ray, she'll never let me live it down.
Oh my God.
- Say, what you doing here?
- I'm waiting on Michael.
He's saying he might be running a little late.
- You saw Michael?
- Yep, I went over to his hotel room and I saw my baby.
- I mean, was he glad to see you?
Did he run up, pick you up, kiss you all over
and tell you how much he missed you?
- Act like you know, girl, he was going crazy.
I told you, Ray.
- I guess I was wrong about him.
I thought he get around all these hoochie mamas
acting like he don't know you or something.
I guess you lucked out, baby cous.
Now I wish Southboy had a little Michael in him.
- Where is Southboy and Flyy?
- Where do you think?
Out there videotaping booty on the boardwalk.
- Southboy got you acting crazy.
- Oh, hold up.
Since you found your man, you think you can give
your big cousin advice, right.
- Just an observation, just an observation, girl.
- Since you trying to observe something,
the beach is getting packed.
Get your stuff.
You can get Michael some coochie later.
Come on.
(upbeat music)
♪ Ooh, brand new boots I bought ya ♪
♪ Fine, fine, blew your mind ♪
♪ Finally thought I caught ya ♪
♪ And your love was mine all mine ♪
♪ I see you walk by with other guys ♪
♪ Step, step, steppin' on my toes ♪
♪ The whole world's talkin' 'bout ♪
♪ How I'm your standby Santa Claus ♪
♪ But ooh, your kisses thrill me ♪
♪ Sure love your angel eyes ♪
♪ The devil in you kills me ♪
♪ But I made up my mind ♪
♪ I'm gonna be your Sugar Daddy ♪
♪ Give you honey all my money ♪
♪ Well, LA to Cincinatti ♪
- Excuse me, ladies.
I couldn't help but to hear that you all are from
Watson Howell University.
- Yes, we are.
- Well, look, let me cut to the chase.
My name is William Crooklin.
President of Crooklin Sports and Entertainment Agency.
I'm looking for--
- You don't have to say it, we already know.
The football all American Dayrun Southboy, right?
- Yeah, right.
Miss? - Raynesha Hawkins.
- Raynesha.
- And this is my cousin, Charity Hawkins.
- Charity, hello Charity.
That is a beautiful name.
- Thank you.
Thank you, but can I ask you who do you already represent?
- Oh, well, I represent over 50 NFL, NBA players.
And I got a roster of musical groups,
they already signed to the agency.
- Like who?
- Oh, well, just hottest DJ in the country.
Goes by the name of DJ Spankx.
- DJ Spankx?
Love me some DJ Spankx. - Oh, I love DJ Spankx.
He be jamming.
He be having the whole crowd jamming, girl.
He be monkey thumping.
(laughing)
What?
- Yeah, well, look here, ladies.
DJ Spankx is gonna have a big party tonight
for the release of his new album.
I'm gonna put y'all on the VIP list.
- What?
Thank you, Mr. Crooklin, that is the best thing
to happen to us all day.
- You're so sweet, Mr. Crooklin.
- Oh, cool, cool, cool.
Well, look.
I need you all to do me a little favor.
Now, I need you to get Southboy up to my room
no later than five o'clock.
Now, I'm not gonna ask him to sign anything, you see.
I just want to, you know, talk to him about
the advantages of letting us represent him,
if he decides to go pro, you know?
Look, look, my room is 122.
- All right, all right, we can do that.
But right now, he out videotaping booty
with his homeboy Flyy.
(laughing)
I'll make sure he get up there.
- All right, all right, well, thank you ladies.
And I will see you tonight at the party.
- All right.
It's on.
(laughing)
(hip hop music)
- Girl, I told you Southboy was gonna be
at that party, we got to be there.
- You ain't hear, girl.
That man gonna put them on the VIP list.
We got to be in the VIP, OK?
- You know what, don't even worry about it.
Let's just get our ass down to the boardwalk
and catch up with Mr. Southboy.
- Jesus Christ, Billy the Crook.
I got to get into that party.
(foreign language singing)
(chattering)
Hey, man, what kind of camera you got there?
- A camera, man.
- I mean, how does it work?
I mean, does it feel good in your hand?
- Hey, man, what's up, cameras turn you on or something?
- No, man, it's nothing, I'm just curious.
- Nosy is more like it.
- Nosy, I like that, pretty funny.
- We came down here to roam weekend,
I thought it was supposed to be black spring break.
- You know what, I think it is black spring break,
you know what I'm saying?
- Yeah, you know it is black spring break,
because I heard it on the radio, man.
It was like hey, Daytona Beach,
are you ready for the true jam, you know?
It was like hey, black spring break.
Bass mixed music all around, it was the hottest groups
in hip hop, there's gonna be red bows, black bows.
There's gonna be, oh, man.
Music gonna be provided by rap productions
and face bottom DJ's.
OK.
You know what, ladies, if you want to make some money,
you got to take it all off, yeah, woo.
- This cracker done bumped his motherfucking head, Southboy.
- What the fuck is your problem?
- Whoa, man.
Let me be straight with you.
You're a big fella, right?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Look, look.
We ain't into that dookie love shit,
you know what I'm saying?
We're pussy lovers over here.
- It ain't like that man, man, you got it all wrong, OK?
It's nothing like that, all right?
He's just a big boy.
He must be playing like football some place.
(sniffing)
- I smell an agent.
- No, man, I ain't no agent,
I mean, I'm just like hanging out on the beach.
- Let's jet, big dog.
That little red seat right over there, man.
- Yeah, I'm with you, man.
- Know what I'm saying?
- No, OK, OK, all right?
I recognize you.
You're Dayrun Southboy from Watson Howell University, man.
Fuck, man, you're great, man.
- Hey, look, I haven't made my decision yet, OK?
But when I do, I think I want an agent
that's at least six feet tall.
- No, that's funny, man, I like that, I like you.
Hey, let me start again, OK?
My name is Vinnie DelVecchio.
I'm with DelVecchio Sports Management.
- So you do know who I am?
- What, are you kidding me?
Everybody knows who you are.
You were the talk of the pro camp, man.
All the scouts were going nuts for you.
If you sign right now, man.
You could make a fortune.
- Yeah, my agent will make a fortune, too.
Catch you later.
- Hey, it was nice meeting you.
We'll have lunch, OK?
Check you later.
- Hey, that cracker's a trip, man.
- Who was that anyway, big dog?
- He was an agent, man, just like you said,
you know what I'm saying?
God damn, man.
Probably all over the place.
- Probably.
- Probably followed us down here.
- Speaking of agents.
- Charity. - We might as well tell him.
- Tell me what? - Tell him, Ray.
It's all right.
- Tell me what, Ray?
- We bumped into William Crooklin.
- Crooklin?
Damn, from Crooklin Sports and Enter, oh, man.
Hey, what'd he say, what'd he say?
- He wanted to meet you at five o'clock at his hotel.
- Damn, man.
- I heard about this cat, man.
He got long, dog.
- Hey, check this out.
If I say our recruitment, right,
I probably could play for whoever I want,
you know what I'm saying?
He's about to get me.
- Hold up, hold up.
I thought you didn't care what team you played for.
- Hey, that was 'til you said William Crooklin.
Tell her about Crooklin, man.
- Crooklin, big time shit, he be on CNN
and shit like that, you know what I'm saying?
- Hey, check it out, right?
If I sign with him tonight, you know what I'm saying?
I probably could hold out at training camp.
I probably get more money, too.
- Wait a minute.
I thought you said you never hold out
at training camp, that you always want to
negotiate honestly and quickly
and playing the game was first and foremost, Southboy.
- Hey, Ray, I love the game of football, all right?
But damn, my agent just sat there and told me
I could make $5,000,000 a year.
- This doesn't sound like you. - Damn, what room he in?
- I think he said 122.
- 122.
122.
It's a trip, man.
- Damn.
- [Ray] I'm really confused.
- What you confused about, Ray?
- You said you always wanted a small agent
to represent you so you get more attention
and be a priority, instead of just another client, Southboy.
- Hey, we're talking about William Crooklin, all right?
All rules change for him.
She don't understand.
All rules change.
- I hope this guy doesn't sweep you off your feet
like you're some damn Prince Charming
because it's business, Southboy, business.
- Ray, Ray, Ray, chill.
You just want to talk to this nigga, right?
- Yeah, you ain't gonna sign nothing, right, Southboy?
You know my dad's an attorney,
so you're not supposed to sign no agent contract
without no lawyer representing you, right?
- Hey damn all that, all right?
Y'all want to go get something to eat
before I go see Crooklin?
- Yeah, whatever. - Chicken shack down the road.
- Look.
We about to go to our room, get our purses.
- Hey, we ain't got time for that shit, Ray.
We ain't got time for that.
- Look, look, look, ladies, ladies.
I got my credit card, you know what I'm saying?
Lunch on me.
Y'all take care, all right?
- Oh, thanks Mr. Credit Card Man.
- Thank you, Flyy.
- Mr. Credit Card Motherfucker now, huh?
- Hey, hey, hey, damn all that.
Let's just go, man, let's go.
- Lashawn.
Come in, Lashawn.
Hoochie mama, hoochie.
- Neeka.
What's Southboy doing?
- I just seen him, girl.
He with that little cute nigga and them hockey hos.
They going up to the little chicken shack.
- Oh, I know where that's at.
I'm coming up there, girl.
I'm coming up there.
♪ Reminisce, reminisce ♪
♪ So way back when there used to be so young ♪
♪ And innocent then ♪
♪ Had dreams about making it big ♪
♪ I don't know what the fuck must have flipped your wig ♪
♪ I peep your flopsing through the set ♪
♪ Like all eyes on you ♪
♪ Used to be about some things ♪
♪ Now you look all through ♪
♪ Damn, boo ♪
♪ What the fuck happened to you ♪
♪ Today he sagging, foot dragging ♪
- What's the deal?
Who is he?
You know I aim to please you.
- I know that, Sherry, oh, I know that.
(laughing)
But what about you and I?
We just go on up to the room.
Get a few drinks.
And you know, I ain't expecting anybody until five o'clock.
And that'll give us plenty of time to go over the details.
(laughing)
Oh, damn.
Oh, baby, you hot.
(laughing)
- Damn it, I can't believe he brought that bimbo in
to seduce Southboy.
Think, Benny, think.
Honey, I'm just doing this to get into the meeting
with the other agent and the player.
Honey, your husband is not a tooty fruity.
Do not tell me daughters that I'm a tooty fruity.
Yes, honey, I make them wear condoms.
What am I saying?
I don't sleep with men.
No, I don't sleep with little boys either.
You are making me crazy.
Honey, your husband is not tossing salads.
No, I don't swallow, either.
You make me nuts, look.
I love you, kiss the girls for me, OK?
Goodbye, I got to go.
Vinnie, sometimes you got to do what you got to do.
Go get 'em, go get 'em.
Go get 'em.
(chattering)
♪ Be the realist ♪
- Hey.
- What's up, baby, what's up?
(chattering)
- He was about the sorriest motherfucker I ever had.
That nigga was five seconds from being retired.
- Willy.
- The nigga sounded like a runaway slave.
- Look, Willy, you don't need to talk about that boy
because you know what, he was the only one
that lasted longer than two days.
- Now, who asked you to open your trap?
I need to go upside your damn head.
- Tell you something.
You go upside my head, you gonna be exchanging stories
about hot grits with Al Green.
- See, that's why I told him all that.
Get out of here.
Leave my apron, leave my shit.
The chicken shack was here before you,
and it'll be here after you're gone.
- Boy, you about the craziest nigga I know.
Oh, here comes your friend.
(laughing)
Fred the security guard.
- What's up, Fred?
- Hey there, boy.
What's going on, what's all this?
- What the hell do you want?
- I come in here to get one of them good ass donuts.
All right with that?
- You looking kind of thin there.
- Boy, this ain't nothing but love.
Ain't no lie.
- What you want, man?
(chattering)
- Get some coffee right there.
- And you better pay me.
Last time you skipped your ass out of here without paying.
You better pay me this time.
- Who the hell do you think watches
this stinking motherfucker?
- There, you bouncer.
Don't pay me, I'm gonna run you down and kick you.
(chattering)
What the hell do you want?
- Welcome to the Chicken Shack.
Can I take your order?
- Yes, I would like four chicken combos.
Four Cokes.
And give me all the sugars, OK?
- No problem.
(chattering)
- That's gonna be about $40, boy.
You got that kind of funds on your person?
- Y'all do take credit cards, don't you?
- Hell no.
- Yes we do.
Don't mind him, baby, OK?
Here are your drinks.
You're welcome.
(low hip hop music)
(chattering)
- Damn, man, I can't believe that fucker
would even try me like that, man.
- You know how niggas is, man.
Absolute disrespect, dog.
- Look, come on.
Let's just leave it at the beach.
Let's have some fun.
We're about to eat, OK?
No.
- Oh, hell no.
He just put a french fry in that bitch mouth.
Boy, I'm gonna go ahead and turn the Chicken Shack up.
Oh, Lord, I'm gonna be all right, I'm gonna be all right.
You wait.
- Excuse me, excuse me.
Let's put it, let me put it down.
Girl, you on here, get your ass on there, let's go.
- You ain't nothing but a security guard.
- I see you out there on the beach.
- You ain't seen this cat since Christmas.
Y'all here in the same town.
(chattering)
- Yo, man, let's just eat, all right?
I got to go see Crooklin.
- So how was the food?
- It was up, everything was lovely.
Everything was lovely.
- Good, good, well, that'll be 38.59.
- Here you go.
- Oh, you're gonna use your credit card.
OK, well, let me just swipe it right here, OK?
- I ain't never know a nigga to have a credit card
that worked unless he was driving one of them
Lecoosis, BWM's, or Mercecedes or something.
(beeping)
Oh shit.
That ain't sound too good.
- The thing say this card is declined.
This transaction could be fraud.
Please confiscate the card and call the police.
- There got to be some kind of mistake.
- Well, look, baby.
That's what the machine say.
So, we ain't gonna call the police,
but you gonna have to pay for this food
one way or another.
- Well, if you ask me, I think we just hired
four new dish washers.
- Uh uh, I ain't washing no dishes.
Raynesha Hawkins ain't washing nobody's dishes.
I don't believe this.
I do not believe this.
- Yeah, Flyy.
Why didn't you call the credit card people
and see if there's been a mistake or something?
- A mistake, this ain't no mistake.
Flyy done used that since he got it.
- Hey, fuck it, all right.
Just wash and dry, wash and dry.
- Y'all motherfuckers didn't have to
play while I was eating.
- Yeah, tell me about it, Flyy.
- Goodness.
I can't believe we have to wash all these dishes.
- Well, believe it.
Because you gonna wash all of them.
- Chill out, Mr. Willow, we doing our thing.
- I know you from somewhere, boy.
I done seen you in a magazine or on TV
or something like that.
- Probably saw me playing football.
- Yeah.
That's right.
You might be going pro, boy.
You're that tight end from Watson Howell.
What's your name?
South something.
- Southboy. - Yeah, that's it.
Southboy.
Shit boy, come on over here.
You gonna be a pro one day,
you ain't need to be washing no dishes.
- So you gonna let us go?
- Sho 'nuff, sho 'nuff.
I just need you to sign a few napkins for me,
and then I'll let y'all go.
Just sign a few napkins for me.
- Oh, damn.
- Yeah, yeah, now make one out to Ricky Phillips.
Because that motherfucker don't never believe
I got a star up in this here restaurant.
(chattering)
Yeah, now I need another one made up to Ellen Green,
up there at the free wheel, love all that shrimp,
up there on Cannon Street.
She likes football, too.
Yeah, Ellen Green.
That's right.
Yeah.
Yeah, now make this one out--
- Nah, nah, nah, nah, uh uh, uh uh.
- Hey, man.
- What's happening, man?
Where my God damn money at, man?
For the donut and coffee this morning, motherfucker?
Yeah, you give me my damn money.
I was gonna visit your bad leg ass.
- Let me tell y'all black ass,
a visit ain't a visit until your black ass sleep.
Get your ass on up out of here.
Wait, motherfucker talking about a stank ass motherfucker.
(chattering)
Look here, head man, what's up?
- Look here, Santa Claus' black skinned cousin,
I'm trying to get in my room, man.
I walked all the way here.
I'm tired.
(chattering)
Give me my damn key.
- Ah, that shit.
Get your stank ass on up out of here with this
non working shit.
- What you mean I got to leave, man?
I just paid money to get in.
I tell you what, I'm gonna my uncle.
(chattering)
- Girl, look, Neeko, Neeko, Neeko.
- Oh, excuse me.
- What's happening, baby?
- Ain't you that all American football player
from Watson Howell?
Your name is down south something.
- Southboy, Dayrun Southboy.
- All right.
- This is my main man, Kenny Flyy.
- How you doing?
- Nice to meet you.
My name Neeka, and her name Lashawn.
I ain't never met no all American before.
And I damn sure don't know nothing about no football, girl.
(laughing)
- Damn, that's good because every girl I meet
know about football.
- I know I ain't one of them damn girls.
- So, what are the haps tonight, young ladies?
- Well, you know we going to that DJ Spankx party.
Everybody who is somebody is gonna be there.
How about y'all?
- Yeah, yeah, me and my man gonna be there, yeah.
Maybe all four of us can get together
and make things happen, you know what I mean?
- For real.
- Sounds like a plan to me.
- Hey, well, check it.
Me and my man got a meeting upstairs.
Business meeting upstairs, you know what I'm saying?
So check y'all tonight at the party.
- Before you go, let me give you some sugar
for your meeting for good luck.
Mm.
- All right, break your finger down there.
- We gonna see about that now, won't we?
- Oh, we can.
- I want to put it right here first.
But you better not break my teeth.
- Just keep them out the way while you're
handling your business and everything, be cool.
- Oh, baby, you won't even know they there.
It's crucial like that.
- Hey, let's do it.
- Hey, we'll see about that, Neeka.
- No, I'm gonna see about it.
You gonna feel me.
- Oh, shake it shake it now.
- Anyway.
I do now how to ride the pony without falling off.
- Damn.
- Neeka, you is so crazy girl.
- Girl, you ain't seen his dick rising up in them shorts?
But you know what, he gonna have to work for his.
- Girl, we best to get some rest before this party.
- OK, 'cause Southboy is backed up
and ready to be cooked, girl.
- Neeka, you got his ass open.
He was slobbering all over you, girl.
- OK.
(laughing)
- Michael.
- What's up, Charity, what's up?
- How you doing, how are you?
- I'm all right, you know, busy and all that.
- I dropped by the hotel and the lady said you was busy
or something like that, what's going on?
- That's your problem, Charity, you don't just
drop by the hotel.
You know, call first.
Show a nigga some respect.
- Respect, Michael, what are you talking about,
I'm your high school sweetheart, you're my boyfriend.
- Charity, it's a new day, all right?
You're at your school doing your thing,
and I'm at my school doing my thing.
So you know we both got a thing going on.
So I don't know why you tripping.
- But I'm not seeing anyone else but you, Michael.
I'm not talking to any guys at school, baby.
I'm all yours.
- I don't know that, Charity.
I don't know what you're doing at your school.
Look at you.
I bet you get all kind of niggas hanging on you.
Man, go and fuck Charity somewhere else.
- Michael, this doesn't even sound like you.
What's wrong with you?
- Hey, Charity, I want something new and improved
right now, all right?
- New and improved?
- Yeah, meet Sue.
We met at school.
This is the girl of my dreams.
This is all the woman I ever want.
- Michael, how could you do this to me?
- Charity, I ain't returning your phone calls,
I ain't answering your letters,
I thought you'd get the picture by now, bitch.
- You can ask Raynesha, I haven't been cheating on you
or nothing like that and you're gonna come to Daytona
with this bitch?
- Bitch, hold up with that-- - Hold up.
- You ain't shit, Michael, you ain't shit.
I don't need you no more.
I wasted all my time with you, motherfucker.
You owe me, you owe me. - It's all right.
It's all right.
Charity.
Why did you lie to me about going to see Michael?
- Because I didn't want to hear you say I told you so.
- You my cousin, so what if I ride you a little bit?
That's my job.
You didn't have to lie to me about
going to see a punk like that.
- You're 100% right, Ray, I'm sorry.
I know we're much closer than that.
- Yeah, Charity, much closer than that.
Look.
It's been a long day, OK?
Let's forget about it, OK?
- OK.
I'm sorry, I love you, girl.
- I love you, too.
- Well, that's the story of
Crooklin Sports and Entertainment.
You see, I can get you into film, commercials,
all of that.
Just as soon as you sign with me,
and I hope that's gonna be tonight.
- I got some good shit.
Bitch, I don't know if I can smoke all this shit,
but I'm gonna damn sure try.
- Well, I'm really impressed with your agency, Mr. Crooklin.
I think you guys could do wonders for my career.
- Well, good, good, good, I'm glad to hear that.
Hey, that's wonderful.
(laughing)
- That's cool, that's cool.
- Yeah, yeah.
- But could you just shoot straight with me
for a minute, Mr. Crooklin?
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What, what, what?
- I mean, how high do you really think I can go
in the NFL draft?
- Oh, well, Southboy, they've already told me
no less than third. - Damn.
- Yeah, no matter what.
Man, the way you put up them numbers this season
and the way you performed last week at that camp,
man, you already in the driver's seat.
(laughing)
- That's good to know, that's good to know.
God.
- Hey, look, tell me, tell me Southboy.
You engaged?
Got a girlfriend, you know?
Anything of that nature?
- Remember that girl you met today, Raynesha?
- What's the real deal, you're still not
telling me nothing.
- Look, see, I don't know, I don't know.
Look.
I guess I started to feel ignored.
It seemed like every girl on campus
knew where my man was but me.
I was starting to get pissed off.
I thought I was the laughing stock of the campus.
So I tried to get Southboy's attention.
I did what you did today.
- What was that?
- I lied.
I told Southboy I had sex with Terry Miller.
- Raynesha. - Look.
I was lonely, I tried to get his attention.
- Like that?
- Look, I gave him this excuse about it being an accident,
but he didn't buy it.
Now he thinks I'm some slut or something.
But nothing happened between me and Terry, nothing.
- You sure you ain't sleep with Terry Miller, girl?
- Look, hold up, Raynesha Hawkins may talk a lot of mess,
but that's one thing I would never do to my baby
is cheat on him.
Because I love him too much.
- She cheated on me with the star basketball player.
(laughing)
We just friends now.
- Yeah, well, Southboy, look.
I think I got a little something something
that's gonna take your mind off of all of that.
- Yeah?
- Mm hmm.
Oh, Sherry.
(hip hop music)
- [Flyy] Oh, motherfucker.
♪ I can see clearly now that my high is off ♪
♪ I can allude all obstacles in my way ♪
- [Crooklin] Yeah, that Sherry is something else, huh, huh?
- [Southboy] Hey, she all that, man, she all that.
(laughing)
- Yeah, well, you ain't seen nothing yet.
(knocking)
Sherry, look, man, don't hurt him now.
Now he's still got to play some football, huh?
Y'all have some fun and I'm gonna go and get this door.
- Hey, I'm here just to dust for ya.
Hopefully I'm not interrupting.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Nobody asked you to come in and dust, come on.
- Oh my God.
There's a fire, there's a fire.
(chattering)
Don't worry about me, let me save you.
I'll save you all.
(chattering)
Hey, don't worry about a thing because I saved us all.
(laughing)
- Hey, hey, hey, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Now you ain't no damn maid.
You a man, now who the hell are you?
(coughing)
- This some of the best shit I ever smoked.
- Damn, hey, that's that damn agent
from the boardwalk today.
- Damn sure is.
- Oh, no, see, you gonna have to get the fuck out
with your stank white ass, come on.
(laughing)
- Hey, Southboy, popped his motherfucking head.
- Hey, hey, hey, I can't believe he was dressed
like a maid, dog.
(mumbling)
- I'm sorry you had to see that.
You see.
Hey, hey, hey, tell me something.
You boys done rode through town since y'all been here?
- No. - Oh, well, look, look,
DJ Spankx is down in Heaven's Park throwing a DJ party.
Now this is gonna be, he ain't riding blue,
because this is gonna be live.
- Man, nigga, let's ride.
- Yeah.
You know I'm game, dog, you know I'm game.
- Well, look, y'all have fun.
I'm gonna go back home and change for the party, you see.
So look, I'm gonna put you on the VIP list, huh?
So we can talk about that later.
And you know what?
I forgot, I almost forgot.
The limo is gonna be here at nine o'clock
to pick y'all up.
- Limo?
Like in limousine?
- Oh, yes, indeedy.
- Oh, man.
Thank you, Mr. Crooklin.
- All right, that's all right, that's all right.
- God damn.
Man, I want to thank you, too, Mr. Crooklin, man.
This hit though.
I needed this shit here bad.
I needed this.
- Any time, brothers, any time.
Look here, I will see you tonight at the party, huh?
Take care.
(chattering)
All right.
This is gonna be easier than I thought, mm hmm.
You know that Southboy kid?
He's pretty stupid.
Yeah, I thought he was gonna be a tough guy
and everything but he just like the rest of 'em.
Thinks with his dick.
(laughing)
Yeah, well, look, send him a limo
for Spankx' party tonight, uh huh.
Hey, hey, hey, look, look.
I tell you what.
I need you to go ahead and set up a press conference
tomorrow around noon, OK?
And make sure that all the press is there at the hotel.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, he's gonna sign, he's gonna sign.
I guarantee it.
- Yes, I'm OK.
No, my room was not on fire, I said I put a fire out
in my hotel.
No, I'm not a fireman now.
No, God damn it, no, I am a sports agent,
I am not a fireman.
Yes, I know I got to go to school for that.
What are you, nuts?
No I did not race in there to save my boyfriend.
Honey, I don't have a boyfriend, Jesus Christ.
All right, Billy the Crook, no more Mr. Nice Guy.
To the party I go.
(hip hop music)
♪ Baby ♪
♪ It's just an everyday thing ♪
♪ The way those players swing ♪
- [Spankx] So how long you been rapping, dog?
- Dog, I've been doing this shit for years.
You know what I'm saying?
My nigga, right now, I'm just--
- What's up, man?
- You know what I'm saying?
Trying to get a record deal.
And blow the hell up like you, nigga.
- Yeah, right, right.
Boy around?
- Parked around the corner.
He about to go pro and shit, you know what I'm saying?
- That's straight, man, that's straight.
- What's up with your record business, nigga?
- That's a hard ass business to break into,
you know what I'm saying?
Saying sometimes your own record label
don't give a fuck about you. - Say what?
- Man, let me tell you something, man.
I'm having management problems.
Loads of tech problems.
All types of other bullshit, you know what I'm saying?
- Damn, how about Crooklin?
- Crooklin, nigga, what?
- Nigga told me Crooklin's supposed to be
one of the best.
- Shit, let me tell you something, man.
That cat flawed, dog.
He owe me 100 grand, dog.
100 grand, that's only from last year.
- Real, nigga?
- Man, everybody that's involved with this motherfucker
man got a lawsuit against him, right?
And I'm suing his ass next week.
You know what I'm saying, man,
this cat owes me a lot of cheddar, dog.
- That's fucked up, y'all.
My boy's thinking about signing with this nigga.
- Yo, man, tell him, don't do it, man.
Fucking up his career, man.
- Damn, man, I got to go holla at my boy, right?
- Yo, man, check it, dog, check it.
- We gonna go to the hotel, man,
you know, put on some chill, you know what I'm saying?
I'm gonna holla at you tonight.
- True, man, I got the take right here, man,
I'm gonna direct dial, you know what I'm saying?
Hey, yo, yo, man, check it out, man.
You want to rock the spot tonight, man?
- Hell yeah, nigga, all these bitches, you know,
nigga, blow that bitch up.
- Cool, it's on, baby, true.
- Man, what you talking about, though?
What you got, what you got talking to me about?
- Man, look, Spankx say the man was a crook.
- How you feeling, man?
- Spankx say he owe all these people hella money, dog,
and he'll fuck you if he can.
- Man, Spankx don't know what he talking about, man.
- I feel the brother, you know what I'm saying?
All I'm saying is you need to get him checked out first.
- Hey, Crooklin is straight, Flyy.
Damn, nigga, you said it yourself.
- Like I said, that's before I got
the 411 on that nigga ass.
Spankx say he is a crook, dog.
- Man, fuck you and Spankx, man.
Crooklin's straight, dog.
Damn, man, shit.
I think you jealous of me, nigga.
- Jealous?
What is this jealous shit?
This is me, dog.
Why are you talking to me like that?
- Man, why are you trying to put
fucked up shit in my head, man?
Crooklin's straight, Flyy.
And I'm gonna sign with him tonight,
if you like it or not.
- Just like Ray say, man.
You lost your mind, dog.
- Ray, man, fuck Ray, man.
Fuck that bitch.
I don't fuck with her no more.
- You tripping, dog.
You tripping big time.
- Damn, man, shit.
I think you jealous of me, dog.
- Jealous, nigga, man, look here.
You done bump your motherfucking head Southboy.
I'm gonna tell you something else, too, dog.
I get to the motherfucking club.
Fuck y'all limo, man.
- Damn right, shit about me, Flyy.
You just tagging along on my shit.
The limo's for me, dog.
That shit fucking with your head.
I the one did this shit, Flyy.
I the one worked out and lift weights
and weigh in in the morning and shit
while your ass was sleeping, smoking weed.
I'm the one doing this shit.
Me, dog.
- Man, you think I don't know that shit?
I'm gonna tell you something.
This shit is all good that you did it,
you know what I'm saying, but it ain't shit
if you ain't got nobody to share it with
and another thing, and none of them fucking niggas
is gonna be there for you, God damn it,
when you're down, and you can believe that shit, nigga.
This shit here is real.
- Man, fuck you.
I'm the one doing this shit, Flyy.
Me, me.
- Nigga, Lord help you, nigga.
- I'm the one did this shit, Flyy.
Fuck you, man.
Fuck Ray, all y'all.
I did this shit, me.
(hip hop music)
♪ Flopping we're closing ♪
♪ No Z's and that funk ♪
♪ I break that trunk ♪
♪ Giving 'em what they want ♪
♪ Whenever that G type of mind state ♪
♪ You know that thug shit that fucks with your break ♪
♪ Yeah in that FLA all day ♪
♪ We lay low, burning on nothing but the best ♪
♪ Of that NO ♪
♪ Keeping us mac mo ready to unload ♪
♪ Gang to a foot dragging down ain't no shame ♪
- Southboy, why you ain't hollering for your boy?
- Yeah, I thought Flyy was your dog.
- Man, I catch y'all later.
Much later.
- What's up with him?
- I don't know.
♪ Gots to keep them fat and jingling ♪
♪ Just like this dingaling ♪
- Southboy acting kind of strange, Ray.
You seen the jewelry he had on?
He never wears jewelry.
Where'd he get that from?
- I don't know.
I guess he got it from that agent.
I think he rode here by limo.
- Limo?
He brought a limo, and none of us ride with him?
- Look, just forget him, OK,
niggas and money don't mix.
Forget him, let's go get our dance and party on.
We out.
♪ Pimping ain't easy ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ Sure ain't easy ♪
- Girls, Spankx' party is so big tonight.
- OK, sure you right.
I looking so good, you know it's on now, girl.
- Girls pumps.
Nigga, please.
- Man, where the hell Kenny Flyy at?
Hey, what's up, baby, God damn.
- See, this real my uncle never told me girl.
- Your Aunt Quinnella?
- Yeah, you know my brother Zero.
Man, him ain't got the same thing.
- They supposed to be my dogs, they left me.
Motherfucker, what you looking at?
Big pretty boy ass.
Bald headed motherfucker.
- She didn't know which one she was pregnant from.
And they both claim her.
Anyway, I don't even know how that shit work that girl.
- Girl, how old is holding onto your Aunt Quinella?
- Oh, hell no, it Raynesha and Charity right there.
Stanking hos.
- That pussy ain't the same, and it damn sure ain't free.
You figure all that out, you be fucking me.
- You is so crazy.
I got to remember that, girl.
- OK, it be working for her because they be
right up trying to figure it out.
- OK.
♪ Everybody, let's keep jamming ♪
♪ Yeah they keep on monkey popping ♪
♪ Everybody in the house keep jamming ♪
♪ Just pump it, pump it ♪
♪ Just pump it, pump it, pump it ♪
♪ Just sling it, just sling it ♪
♪ Just sling it, sling it, sling it ♪
♪ Just pump it, just pump it ♪
♪ Just pump it, pump it, pump it ♪
♪ Just sling it, just sling it ♪
♪ Just sling it, sling it, sling it ♪
♪ Just, just funky ♪
♪ That monkey pot ♪
♪ The monkey butt ♪
♪ That monkey butt ♪
♪ Come on, just monkey butt ♪
♪ Ooh, baby baby ♪
♪ Just ride, ride, ride, ride, ride ♪
♪ Running ♪
- Yeah, you see this party is rocking, huh, huh?
- Yeah, yeah.
- You like it, you like it?
- Everything's cool, everything's cool.
- Good, good, good, good, good.
Hey.
Where your little homeboy at?
- I don't know, man.
Probably running around here
sniffing up DJ Spankx' ass, you know?
He tried to get one of them record contracts.
- So nigga, you listen to the tape?
- Yeah, I'm gonna tell you straight, dog,
I'm gonna tell you straight.
Go back up the way, give it to my boy
and see if they can't get you this record deal,
you know what I mean?
- Yo, hook that shit up, nigga.
Hook that shit up.
- Hey, man. - Hey, man.
I want to introduce you to this homeboy here.
Daniel Zirelli, from LA, man.
That's my man does all my videos and all, right?
- Hey, man, I heard your tape, it's pretty tight.
- Yeah, you vibing up that shit?
- Yeah, I am, man.
Next time I'm in town, maybe I'll do your video.
- Damn. - Boy, I tell you, man.
- I heard Southboy's fucking with Crooklin.
That shit's a mistake.
- Look at this, Southboy.
Now, I know Flyy.
Flyy is your main man.
I know that.
But once you become part of the Crooklin family,
you see, well, then you're gonna have to get you
some new main men.
You know what I mean?
- You mean like get some new friends?
- Mm, mm, no, no, no.
(laughing)
No, absolutely not.
See, no, you know, see, you gonna be a pro ball player, see?
With lots of resources.
So you need to hang around folks who are just like yourself.
- I can't believe that guy gave Southboy
all that jewelry.
- I can't believe he's actually taking a drink.
- As long as I've known him,
I've never known him to take a drink,
smoke a joint, or anything like that.
Southboy is tripping.
- Look, look, look, Raynesha and Charity there.
No, no, no, they can't compare to Sherry.
Sherry.
Sherry is the type of woman that you need on your arm.
Not them two tramps you drove down here with.
You see what I'm saying?
- Yeah, I see what you're saying.
To be honest with you, Mr. Crooklin,
I'm tired of all of 'em.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, well, see, that's only natural, Southboy.
You see, money, money hangs with money, you see?
(laughing)
Yeah, you see.
You never heard of no pro ball player driving
they Benz in the hood talking about
picking up an old school buddy, you see?
No, you see that.
That just don't happen.
- I see where you're coming from.
- Yeah.
- You know what?
I think that Crooklin guy's a bad influence on Southboy.
- For an ex-girlfriend, you sure sound concerned.
- See.
I do miss him a lot, OK?
This has been part of my life.
- So what you gonna do about it?
- Do about it?
I'm gonna get my man back tonight.
Come on.
- If you ask me, I think you need to
dump that whole crew I seen you with this morning,
you see, including that Kenny Flyy.
- Word to your mother, man, tell him we'll do it, man,
if your friend make him understand you, man.
Crooklin gonna rob his ass, dog.
- Yeah, if you see that fucker Crooklin,
tell him he better give me my money,
or else he's gonna be waking up with a horse head
in his bed, I'm serious.
- Hey, man, I don't know, Crooklin got this nigga
nose wide ass, you know what I'm saying?
- Telling you, man, got to make him understand.
It's important, dog.
- Nigga hard headed, dog, you know what I'm saying?
- Hey, man, hard head make a soft ass, man.
Can't tell you, you know what I'm saying?
Can't stress it.
- Gonna go solo, man, I'm gonna go hard at him,
you know what I'm saying?
- Do what you got to do, boy.
- Southboy.
You more than that, hmm?
You about to be a pro ball player.
(laughing)
- I feel ya, I feel ya. - Yeah, yeah.
- I said a night club.
No, I'm not dancing for money, honey.
I'm looking for Southboy.
What are you nuts?
No, I didn't say little boys, I said Southboy,
that's the player's name.
(hip hop music)
- Oh, shit, there goes Southboy right there.
Oh, yeah, it's on, it's on.
- Girl, Southboy standing over there all by himself.
It's time to go make your move, OK?
- I know that.
Damn agent going over there talking to him.
- Girl, every bitch in this place want that boy.
If you don't go over there now,
you'll never be able to have Mr. Southboy.
- You know what, I'm gonna get his ass high, look.
- Nigga, you gonna get his ass,
and take him to the room,
and fuck the shit out of his ass,
for you and for me, OK?
- You know what?
I look damn good.
- Neeka, you go girl, and do your thing.
♪ And the house keep jamming ♪
♪ They keep on monkey popping ♪
♪ Everybody in the house keep jamming ♪
♪ Yeah they keep on monkey popping ♪
♪ Go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go ♪
♪ Go, get get, get get ♪
♪ Get get, get get, go ♪
♪ Put ♪ (gun shooting)
♪ At times it seems like I hold the weight of the world ♪
♪ On my shoulders ♪
- So who was that guy who shot Southboy?
- Who's the cat from the beach earlier today?
The police called him, I guess that's a good thing,
but all my boy thought about was playing football,
that was the most important thing in his life.
Now it may all be taken away.
Doc, Doc, how is Dayrun, Dayrun Southboy?
- Oh, oh, yeah.
They're just finishing up with him.
He'll be out any moment.
- See, he's gonna be OK.
- Yeah, we got to stop shooting each other over the BS.
That cat was just jealous of Dayrun.
Just jealous.
- And Raynesha was just about to go tell him
how much she loved him.
- Hey, here's your all American.
- Are you OK? - Yeah.
- How you feeling, playboy?
- Everything's cool.
- Yeah? - Everything's cool.
- He was lucky, the bullet passed clean through.
That's what we call a flesh wound.
I'm gonna keep him tonight,
but tomorrow I'll give him some crutches
and let him go.
- Thanks, Doc.
- Thank you, Doctor. - Good looking out, Doc.
- Doc, can I have a few minutes with my friends?
- Oh, sure.
We're gonna do some rounds.
I'll come back for you, OK?
- All right.
(chattering)
So where's Ray?
- She couldn't take it,
so she's at the hotel packing.
So I came instead.
- So where's Crooklin?
- Man, I hate to say I told you so, man,
but the cat was a crook.
- While you were passed out,
he came and took all the jewelry he gave you
and ran out the door with that damn tramp.
- Said something about you being a wounded horse,
wasn't no good to him no more, you know?
- Wait.
So how did I get to the hospital?
- Man, Vinnie brought you to the hospital.
And jumped on the guy with the gun
and held him down 'til security came.
- Damn. - Vinnie did all that for you
and that Crooklin didn't even come to the hospital
to see if you was dead or alive.
- Damn.
Wait a minute, so where's Vinnie?
- He's at the police station, man, filing a report.
So what you gonna do, man?
- Man, when I was in there talking to the doctor,
made my decision.
God gave me talent, I'm gonna use it.
- That's right.
- No more fucking around, I'm turning pro.
- That's good.
- How about this, big dog?
- I need that, man.
I need that.
Thanks, Flyy.
- Any time, big dog, any time.
So.
What's up with you and Michael?
- I ain't thinking about Michael no more, man.
I'm tired of running behind that boy.
- Good, 'cause you don't have to run no more anyway.
You got a new nigga.
- Why you looking at me like that?
- How about being Flyy lady?
- You gonna be OK?
- Oh, I'm gonna be straight.
Why don't y'all go and discuss details?
(hip hop music)
- Dayrun, are you all right?
- Yeah.
I'm cool, Ray, I'm cool.
Just a flesh wound.
Went right through me.
Nothing's wrong, I can play the football.
Got to say this, though.
- OK.
What happened to, where's Flyy and C?
- Got a little thing going on.
- What? - Yeah.
Look, look, Ray, forget about that.
I want to apologize to you.
- Dayrun.
Let me apologize to you, OK?
I haven't been very supportive, whatsoever.
I realize you have a lot of pressures on you
for being a football star.
I just thought you were looking for
some cheerleader or something so I started acting childish.
- Ray.
I don't know if I ever could forgive you
for having sex with Terry Miller.
I mean.
I can't not ever forget that.
- Honey, that's just it.
I never slept with Miller.
I haven't been with any other man
since you laid eyes on me our freshman year.
I lied to make you jealous.
And just think, I may have never had
had a chance to tell you.
Never. - Damn.
I mean.
You went to that extreme, I must have really been tripping.
- Oh, yes, so, Mr. Southboy,
your butt was definitely tripping.
- This shit has got me spinning, man.
Money.
Pro football.
It's scary.
- Yeah.
- You know, I was thinking.
I don't think I want a girl
that might just want me for my cash.
And of course I need an accountant.
So you know what I'm saying?
- So, what are you saying?
- I'm saying, how would you like to be my wife?
How does Raynesha Southboy sound?
- Yes, yes, Southboy.
- I love you.
No more lying to each other.
- No more lying to each other.
- I have you all here today to announce
that I'll be foregoing my final year of eligibility
at Watson Howell University to enter into the NFL draft.
I made this decision after a careful self analysis
of my skills and accomplishments,
and I feel that I can be an immediate impact
for any teen that would welcome me.
Last night, I also realized the true meaning
of friendship and trust.
Once again, Dayrun Southboy, from Watson Howell University,
will be turning pro.
If you have any questions,
you can speak with my agent,
Vinnie Carusso.
- My boyfriend did not shoot him, OK?
I'm not cheating on my boyfriend, all right?
Because I don't have a boyfriend.
But I did get the job, OK?
Not a blowjob, the job.
OK, yeah, Dayrun signed with me last night.
I'm a real fucking sports agent.
No more fucking used cars, OK?
- Come here.
See, you about to get on my last nerve
with that damn bullhorn.
- What you mean?
- What I mean is you pissing me off.
Nipping around here like you the principal
of some rowdy behind high school or something.
- Yeah?
I'm just trying to--
- What you trying to do is make me act like a nigga
on this here job.
Just like I done on the one before this one
and the one before that one.
- Now, look here.
I don't tell you how to check folks in in here.
So don't you come tell me
how to keep 'em safe.
- Southboy, don't worry about a thing.
I'm gonna be the best damn agent you ever heard of.
- Hey, cool, Vinnie.
Hey, I appreciate that.
You know, don't forget to get to get Flyy
a recording contract, it's real important.
- I got that shit covered, man.
- All right, cool, cool.
Look, I'm gonna haul ass to school, all right?
As soon as I get there, I'll call ya,
we'll get ready for the draft.
- Rocking.
- Later, V.
- Later, D.
- Now, so far as I'm concerned, you little flashlight cop,
you ain't nothing but a certified 911 dialer.
- Security guard is very, very important.
- Important?
Y'all ain't even got no TV show.
Everybody got a TV show.
They got Cops.
They got FBI Stories.
Everybody got a TV show but I ain't never seen
no TV show about no security guard, huh?
I ain't never seen no camera crew following you around
asking you what it was like to be a security guard, huh?
Man, get up on out of my face before I about to tell you
about that tight ass suit they got you wearing.
Looking like a 1975 Greyhound bus driver.
- Sup, home boys?
(chattering)
Check this out, here, check this out.
Y'all see this?
See this?
(chattering)
Let's ride, baby, let's ride.
You know what I'm saying?
- Woo, this has been a hell of a weekend, huh?
- Got that right.
Got my heart broken and fell in love,
all in the same weekend.
- Damn right.
- Let's ride, dog, let's ride.
You know what I'm saying?
Ride, baby.
(hip hop music)
- Hey, you ain't leaving me here, no.
Hey, I'm gonna get you, Flyy.
Hey, man.
Man, Raynesha, hey, wait.
That's fucked up.
Hey, Flyy, hey Southboy.
Raynesha.
Hey.
(hip hop music)
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ Don't ya, don't ya ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ Don't you like it baby ♪
♪ Butt naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ Everybody get butt ♪
♪ Take it off ♪
♪ Naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ Come on up ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it, baby ♪
♪ Butt naked ♪
♪ We gonna get butt naked ♪
♪ You like it ♪
♪ Freaking, freaking ♪
♪ Come on, jump on it ♪
♪ Call the Mona Lisa ♪
♪ Anything, your ass is fine ♪
♪ Girl like to party ♪
♪ You know she do like to cruise ♪
♪ Call the Mona Lisa ♪
♪ Anything, your ass is fine ♪
♪ You do it for it ♪
♪ She likes to get her freak on ♪
♪ Take it off ♪
♪ Baby take it off ♪
♪ Money, naked, baby, shake it, baby, take it off ♪
♪ Money, make it, I'm not flaking, baby, take it off ♪
♪ Everybody get butt naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ Everybody get butt naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ Everybody get butt naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ Everybody get butt ♪
♪ Naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it, baby ♪
♪ Butt naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ Everybody get butt ♪
♪ Naked ♪
♪ Don't you like it ♪
♪ You know you like it ♪
♪ Hey, check this out, miss thing. ♪
♪ Or should I say bitch ♪
♪ You like to shake your ass in the club ♪
♪ You a motherfucker ♪
♪ Freak hos, freak hos ♪
♪ Let your motherfucking knees touch your elbows ♪
♪ Bust your ass and let your knees touch your elbows ♪
♪ Freak hos, freak hos ♪
♪ One time chase me ♪
♪ They couldn't take me ♪
♪ My baby mama, two kids couldn't break me ♪
♪ So I went to the club and met Nina ♪
♪ Have you seen her ♪
♪ She look like Leena ♪
♪ With the big butt, got it going on ♪
♪ But got more kids than Children of the Corn ♪
♪ That's why I couldn't fuck with her ♪
♪ Even though I know she was a gold digging bitch ♪
♪ Out the project ♪
♪ Living for the county check ♪
♪ But got the killer pussy ♪
♪ That's why niggas say ♪
♪ Why's that ho ♪
♪ Why's that bitch ♪
♪ Silly rabbit, the trick's on you, bitch ♪
♪ Because true niggas stay true to gizame ♪
♪ Get the coochie and don't know your nizame ♪
♪ And leave a bitch duck with dick on her breath ♪
♪ Dope in the hose and one way out ♪
♪ Freak hos, freak hos, freak hos ♪
♪ Bust your ass and let your knees touch your elbows ♪
♪ Freak hos, freak hos ♪
♪ Now once a trick, always a trick ♪
♪ They want to know why I talk like this ♪
♪ Supposed to be me and you ♪
♪ You fucked my whole crew ♪
♪ And that's why I call you a bitch ♪
♪ I shake these hos like vice ♪
♪ Keep them in the check like mice ♪
♪ I would not fuck turn on lights ♪
♪ When they go left, I go right ♪
♪ I can't deny, I treat them like women ♪
♪ But bitches like hos ♪
♪ Not kind of hos like crumbs ♪
♪ I ride them hos like brand new phones ♪
♪ I want the show at the show ♪
♪ Get 'em in and split 'em and quit 'em and duck 'em ♪
♪ Fuck 'em ♪
♪ I hear the back of my brand new cutlers ♪
♪ But it ain't no thang ♪
♪ Wipe the sheets off and I'm out this bitch ♪
♪ I told you no hos get out for free ♪
♪ So that I found my shit ♪
♪ Freak hos, freak hos ♪
♪ Bust your ass and let your knees touch your elbows ♪
♪ All you niggas talking about that ass ♪
♪ This ain't no free show ♪
♪ We want that motherfucking cash ♪
♪ Fuck you ♪
♪ We don't want no Drake ♪
♪ Don't even think that you can fuck me ♪
♪ You ain't got enough to even touch me ♪
♪ I seen you stunting in the band ♪
♪ But do them broads know it's for your ♪
♪ Motherfucking friend ♪
♪ Want to be baller ♪
♪ Nigga, you'se a ho ♪
♪ How you claiming player still ♪
♪ Getting fronted dough ♪
♪ Calling us freaks ♪
♪ But you the freaky one ♪
♪ Tongue licking on my pearl ♪
♪ Like a stick to a snare drum ♪
♪ Until I cum ♪
♪ All in your fucking face ♪
♪ Floss your teeth with my pussy hairs ♪
♪ And get 'em out of there ♪
♪ I care ♪
♪ So fuck about how you feel ♪
♪ But I will slip a mickey in your drink ♪
♪ Get you out your dough in your place ♪
♪ Leave you stank ♪
♪ 'Cause I ain't the ho ♪
♪ To shake my ass in the club for you Negros ♪
♪ I can't stand a motherfucker talking shit ♪
♪ When he knows he gets blown ♪
♪ Whilst the pussy lips drip ♪
♪ That little dick ♪
♪ Yeah you call me bitch ♪
♪ But I wonder why you still trying to sweat me ♪
♪ Trick impress me trick ♪
♪ Now ain't that a trip ♪
♪ You niggas try to flip the script ♪
♪ But still ain't saying shit ♪
♪ You niggas call yourselves pimps ♪
♪ And try to spit the game ♪
♪ But it's too lame for a true bitch ♪
♪ Freak hos, freak hos ♪
♪ Bust your ass and let your knees touch your elbows ♪
♪ Bust your ass and make your knees touch your elbows ♪