[♪♪♪]
Your attention, please...
Will all foot passengers
please make their way...
Do I know you?
Let me try
to jog your memory.
I like your idea
of a sightseeing tour.
I run this tour
four times a day.
Do you have any idea how
the judge will rule on this?
Come here.
[Breathing hard]
We can't do this here.
Yes, we can.
Yes, we can...
We can't, we can't.
We're just two tourists
enjoying the view.
Oh, god.
[Zippers fly]
[Gasping]
[Panting and sighing]
[♪♪♪]
[Sighs]
Good morning,
Dr. Nick.
Morning, Yolanda.
Okay...
Bye, sweetie.
You have a good day, okay?
You too, daddy.
Bye-bye, doctor.
Bye, guys.
[Front door opens and closes]
Oh, morning, missus.
Good morning, Yolanda.
Boy, I'm running late.
Where is...
Dr. Jarretts
already left for work.
Oh.
Daddy had an emergency
at the hospital.
You look awfully
pretty today.
No, I don't.
I hate
what I'm wearing.
Well, what's wrong with it?
I hate this skirt.
It's too big.
Well...
Come here, sweetie.
What do you think
about this?
It's really cool!
[Chuckling warmly]
Hey, you're
squishing me!
[Laughing]
I'm sorry.
Come on, Emily.
You're going to be late
if we don't leave right now.
[Emily]:
Okay, okay.
I decided.
I want to have a pinata
for my birthday party.
A zebra pinata.
Oh, zebra pinatas
are very rare.
Peter had one.
Well, if Peter had one,
then you should have one, too.
Have a nice day, honey.
You too.
Okay.
Come on.
[♪♪♪]
Tillie, it's been a week.
I was starting to worry.
Nah, I'm okay.
My gallbladder
was giving me trouble.
Oh...
How'd the little one
like the locket?
Oh, I'm saving it
for her birthday.
She would love that.
How much?
Um...
Five bucks.
Ah...
[Shutter clicking]
You take care, you hear.
Wait a minute,
your change.
For you.
Aw...
[Kisses bill]
[Elevator dings]
Morning, Cathy.
Suzanne
wants to see you.
Thank you.
Hey, Suzanne.
You wanted to see me?
Hi, uh, any news
on the magnolia
ranch house?
I'm showing it again at 3:00.
Ah, great.
I am under all kinds of pressure
to get that place sold.
I've had that listing
for nearly three months.
Well, I'm working on it.
I've got a good feeling
about this client.
I think it's right up her alley.
You're a lifesaver.
A pleasure.
[Beeping speed-dial]
[Clears throat anxiously]
It's me.
You were amazing
last night.
Sam, please...
You can't stay away from me.
And you know why?
You want to know why?
Because we're fabulous
together.
I've got a little
surprise for you
this afternoon.
Not today.
I can't get away today.
Sure you can.
No, Sam.
Things are not good at home
and this makes it
more complicated.
Well, it didn't
feel complicated last night.
It's never complicated
when we're together.
I can't think straight
It's after I leave you
that it gets difficult.
I don't like myself right now.
I don't like
what I'm doing to Nick.
I'm no threat to your husband
or your family.
I've been completely
up front on that.
You're the one that's
making it a problem.
Because it is a problem,
for me.
Okay, I don't mean
to make light of it.
I know it bothers you,
but you know,
this thing with us,
I mean, this will burn out
soon enough,
so what do you say we just...
Enjoy it
while it lasts.
You sure know how to
sweep a girl off her feet.
I... gotta go.
[Birds twittering]
[Sighing with satisfaction]
Look at this place.
It's pretty great,
isn't it?
The minute
I walked in here,
I felt like I was home.
I think I'm in
some real trouble here.
I still haven't told Harry
that I want to move.
Oh.
Don't worry,
I can be very persuasive
when I want something.
Good.
I love the wood floors.
Great bathroom.
I love it.
Mm-hmm.
That bathtub
is fabulous.
Yeah.
Let me show you
the closet.
Okay.
And feel free
to just wander around.
Stainless
kitchen...
Love it.
[♪♪♪]
I've seen enough.
So, what
do you say, Nina?
I think Harry's in
for a good time.
Good news
for Harry.
[Laughing]
[Panting and moaning]
[Gasping]
[♪♪♪]
♪ Lately my baby come and go
♪ and he never around
♪ lately I...
♪ Been thinking about
the days... ♪
You know what
your problem is?
I didn't know
I had a problem.
[Chuckles]
You have too much time
on your hands.
Well, I don't see that
as a problem.
In fact, you know
I've arranged my life
to have afternoons
just like this.
Aren't you glad
you passed on lunch?
Mm, well, I don't know,
I'm starved.
Hell, you have a great ass.
[Giggles]
Speaking of which,
I sent you
a little present.
If it's not
pastrami on rye,
I'm not interested.
[♪♪♪]
♪ Lately I've been thinking
back to that and this ♪
♪ and our first kiss
♪ lately I've been thinking
what's gone wrong ♪
♪ with our love song...
♪ I can see you
right before me ♪
♪ but it feels like
you're miles away ♪
♪ I can touch
your body, baby ♪
♪ but you don't have
a word to say... ♪
[Chuckles]
Boy,
I pick three losers
in a row,
and you get flowers
and sexy underwear
from a guy
in the same day?
Look, maybe I’m
way off-base here...
And feel free to stop me
if this isn't my business.
I know what can happen
when these things
get out of control.
I've been there,
and it didn't end well.
What happened?
Jim was a...
A master seducer,
and I was vulnerable.
Yeah.
It's a deadly combination.
How did you end it?
Ella Browning.
Shrink extraordinaire.
Well, you seem
to have survived.
Only after I lost everything.
[Laughing]
Come on, I thought
you said you were good.
Come on...
[Shutter clicks]
[Shutter clicking]
Now what are you
gonna do, huh?
Emily...
Emily,
where'd you go?
Mommy, mommy, save me!
[Laughing]
Oh, there's
no helping you now...
[Shutter clicking]
[Squealing playfully]
Thanks for seeing me
on such short notice.
Well, any friend
of Suzanne's...
What can I do
to help you?
Um, well,
I'm married,
I have a young daughter.
My husband, Nick, is
everything I could ever dream,
yet I can't stay away
from this guy, Sam.
I don't know
what's wrong with me.
I-I don't understand
why I'm doing any of this.
All right.
Let's start with
what this guy,
Sam,
has to offer
that you're not getting at home.
Oh, well, I don't know
how to describe it.
Everything about Sam is intense,
passionate,
from someplace almost primal.
He makes me feel alive.
Is this affair only about sex?
Don't...underestimate that.
Sex can be
a very powerful draw.
Well, if it was
just about sex,
this would be easy.
Maybe...
You're afraid you're
going to have to choose
between Sam and Nick?
No,
no, Sam's not
the marrying kind.
I mean, he loves me.
I know he loves me,
but, uh, Sam is never with
just one woman for long.
That's pretty definite.
Well, he says he's never seen
a good marriage,
including his parents.
He doesn't think it works.
That kind of challenge can be
a real allure for a woman.
Are you sure you're not
harboring the fantasy
that you can change all that?
No.
Absolutely not.
Are you sure
about that?
I'm positive.
I love my family.
I love my husband.
They mean everything to me.
Yet you risk losing them.
Yeah, that's what terrifies me.
That's why I'm here.
Suzanne said
that you helped her
and I know
I need help.
I know this is crazy,
but I can't stop what I'm doing.
[Playing a blistering
jazz solo]
[♪♪♪]
[Applause and cheers]
[Starts a slow
and sultry number]
[♪♪♪]
I didn't expect
to see you tonight.
How did you get away?
Does it matter?
Take me home.
[♪♪♪]
I want to
show you something.
Anyone I know?
Well, you're not here
so I have to work
from memory.
Well, I'm here now.
How am I ever going to
walk away from this?
Why would you want to?
It can only end badly.
Oh, I don't know, baby,
I'll bet we have
a spectacular end.
That is exactly
what we're looking for.
I want my wife
to see it.
Anytime.
Okay, well,
I'll get her schedule
and call you later?
All right,
thanks.
Laura, I don't mean
to alarm you,
but some guy
has been calling here
asking questions
about you.
What kind of questions?
Just, whether
I knew you,
if you work here...
Um, of course,
he wouldn't leave me his name.
What did you tell him?
Nothing.
I wouldn't discuss you
with a stranger.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thanks.
[♪♪♪]
[Phone speed-dialing]
I found her, Charlie.
It's her, I'm sure of it.
Stay on her.
What's wrong?
What's happened?
[Crying]
It's Nick.
He's having an affair.
I saw him with her.
They were kissing in the street.
It wasn't a friendly kiss.
So it's okay for you
but not for him?
I know what Sam's about,
but this thing with Nick...
Oh, my god, what if
he's in love with her?
What if he leaves me?
What's wrong with me?
You want to save your marriage,
don't you, Laura?
Yes.
But if you do...
You're going to have to be
completely honest with yourself.
[Sniffles and sighs]
Did you perhaps sense Nick
pulling away from you?
Is that what drove you
to get involved with Sam?
No.
Nick wasn't pulling away.
He was loving.
He's been...Perfect.
Things are as good
as they've ever been.
Do you think that
Nick knows about Sam?
I know I've had
the feeling lately
that I'm being followed...
And Suzanne said
that someone's been
asking questions about me.
What did you
do about it?
Well, what do you suggest I do?
Call the police,
and tell them what?
"I'm having an affair
and my husband's
having me followed?"
Laura...
What did you think
was going to happen
when you started this?
No, let me...
What did you want to happen?
Not this.
You can justify this
any way you like, Laura,
but the fact is,
you've been
having an affair,
and things in your life are
going to start to unravel
unless you deal with
that messy reality,
and the why of it.
[Phone dialing]
Hey, babe...
Are you free?
Certainly not,
but I can be had
for the right price.
Meet me at le bistro,
half an hour.
I'll wear my usual disguise.
"Woman with yellow hair."
Picasso's muse.
He loved her.
Among many.
You're the only one right now.
Listen, Sam, um...
I can't do this anymore.
My life is falling apart.
And you think not seeing me
is going to make that easier?
If it's not
too late already.
Is that why
you wanted to meet me here,
where I couldn't make a scene?
You know,
you still turn me on.
It's not going to be easy
letting go of this.
For me either.
You know, I may not be
the best guy in the world,
but...
I wouldn't have gone about
blowing somebody off like this.
Sam, please understand...
I do understand.
I just don't like the way
you went about doing it.
Take care of yourself.
[Shutter clicking]
Hey!
Hey, stop!
Excuse me, ma'am,
can I help you
with something?
Excuse me, I've got to...
Wait!
She's working as
a real estate agent.
She has a boyfriend,
although I think
she blew him off
the other day.
That doesn't sound like her.
What do you think, Willacker?
I got the wrong girl?
No.
No, that's her, all right.
It's none of my business,
but, um...
Who is she to you?
She ruined my life.
♪ We will sing for joy
♪ we'll sing to the lord
with songs of grace ♪
♪ sing for joy
♪ we'll sing to the lord
the king ♪
♪ the earth, the sea
♪ the sun, the moon
♪ all show his might
♪ to the lord we will sing
for joy ♪
♪ hallelujah
♪ sing hallelujah
♪ let all who serve
the lord rejoice ♪
♪ rejoice and sing, be glad
♪ that we belong to him
♪ let all who serve the lord
♪ exult his name
♪ he is the lord
♪ the god of all
♪ all nations bow
before their lord ♪
♪ and sing for joy
[applause and cheering]
That was great.
As the chair of the PTA,
I'd just like to
quickly remind all of you
that the school
art fair and auction
is in two weeks.
The planning meeting
will be here tomorrow
in the auditorium
at 3:00 P.M.
We could really
use the help.
Thanks for coming.
[Applause]
She's a parent
at the school.
I saw the way
she looked at Nick.
Is it possible
that you're imagining all this?
[Scoffs]
No, it's not possible.
I know what I saw.
Are you going to
confront him?
I can't.
What if he...
What if he says he loves her?
What if he says he's leaving me?
Okay, no, let's
go with this.
Ask all those questions
you're afraid of.
Come on, Laura.
"How often have you
seen her, Nick?"
"Is she everything I'm not?"
"Are you bored
with me?"
What is the point of this?
Come on...
I don't want to do this.
Say the words,
let's get to the root of it.
Tell him.
Why is he doing this to me?
No, no, not me.
Ask him.
No!
I don't want to hear
the answers.
He's-he's treating me
like I mean nothing to him,
like I’m...
Worthless.
That must feel terrible.
I'm used to it.
Why?
Who else has treated you
this way, Laura?
Who else, other men?
Come on, Laura, look at me.
Who has treated you
this way?
Let's get to the root of it,
come on.
My father.
Okay?
You know, we lived
in the same building,
and we're biologically
connected, but that's...
That's about all
he ever was to me.
Tell me about him.
He was a bum,
always broke.
Always another
get-rich-quick scheme.
The only thing
he ever bought me
was a letter opener
from Atlantic city,
with a little
diving horse on top.
A letter opener
for my 10th birthday?
[Sighs in disgust]
Probably had it
lying around in his car.
You must have felt
so very empty.
I don't...
I didn't need him.
I took care of myself.
How did you do that?
I did what I had to do,
whatever I had to do.
Meaning?
Meaning
exactly that.
I-I needed things,
I got them.
Clothes, I got them.
I wore this-
this fabulous dress
to my prom.
Red satin.
[Chuckles]
I bought it myself.
Where did you get the money?
You don't want to talk about
where the money came from?
No.
[Children's laughter,
parents gush]
Was it fun?
Did you like it?
Jess, we've
got to go, honey.
Laura, I thought that was you.
Laura, hi!
How fortuitous.
I've been
wanting to call.
Julia Lancaster.
You showed
my husband and I a house
on Mercer island
a few weeks ago.
Oh, yes, right.
I'm sorry, I'm running late.
Quick question, is it still
available, by any chance?
Let me check
and call me tomorrow, okay?
[Cell phone rings]
What is it, Cathy?
I can't come now.
We'll have plenty of time
to make the counter-offer
before the deadline.
Charlie who?
Well, if he calls again,
tell him you don't know
here I am.
[Sobbing]
[♪♪♪]
[Nick]:
Let's go, em!
You can do it!
[Kids cheering]
[Laughing]
[Whack]
[Kids cheering]
Good job, kiddo.
Gimme a big birthday kiss.
Happy birthday, sweetie.
Laura said she had
several appointments today.
She might not be able to
make it in at all.
I'll wait.
Maybe you'd like to
leave your name and number?
I said I'll wait.
[Crowd applauding]
All right, ladies
and gentlemen,
so far, we have a bid of $10
for this priceless piece
by Peter
from Mrs. Kreger's
fourth grade class.
So...
Do I hear 11?
11!
We have 11.
Do I hear 12?
$12, ladies
and gentlemen.
No?
Oh, this is
a tough crowd tonight.
Going once...
Going twice...
Sold for $11
to the woman in
the purple blouse!
[Applause]
All right.
For our next item,
we have this beautiful vase
from an up-coming artist
in the second grade,
and I'll tell you,
I should know this
because it's my daughter, Emily.
Now, I'll
tell you what,
for this item only,
I am going to start
the bidding myself,
at $5.00.
So...
Do I hear six?
$6.00.
Do I hear seven?
Seven?
I'll bid seven.
Seven, thank you!
Seven.
Do I hear eight?
$8.00?
Eight.
$8.00!
We have a bidding war,
ladies and gentlemen.
Can you believe it?
$8.00. Do I hear nine?
$50.
[Crowd gasps, chairs turn]
I know a brilliant artist
when I see one.
[Chuckling from crowd]
And I love a woman
with great taste.
Sold!
For $50.
[Applause]
All of them.
They're ganging up on me.
That woman was with us
in the park that day,
and now at the art fair.
They're choosing her over me.
You think your daughter
is choosing her?
She doesn't even know her,
does she?
Laura,
I can only imagine
how you felt as a child,
when your parents weren't
looking after you.
That was the least of it.
I was paying for their rent.
I was 13 years old
and I was buying the food
that they ate.
How?
I had an arrangement
with my best friend's father.
[Sniffles]
And your parents knew?
They were taken care of.
They didn't ask
any questions.
They had to know where
the money was coming from.
They did nothing to stop me.
That's hard to believe, Laura.
Believe it.
Does Nick
know about this?
No.
No, he would never
have married me.
That kind of past
wouldn't play for Nick.
But I think that's why
Sam appeals to me.
I'm meant to be
with men like Sam,
men who only want sex.
But you told me that...
That Sam loves you,
right?
Ow, Laura,
do you honestly believe
he loves you?
I do,
but I'm not sure
if Nick still loves me.
I won't let this
ruin my life again.
You don't think
it's too late, do you?
No, Laura,
it's not too late.
Inhale...
And exhale.
Cycle through again.
Don't forget
to keep your head,
your spine,
your ankles
all aligned
in one straight plane.
Great.
Now we're going to into
Trikonasana,
the triangle pose.
I want you to pivot
your left foot in 60 degrees,
your right foot out 90,
make sure you keep
your hips forward,
and reach...
And down.
Remember to
drop your shoulders,
keep your head turned
up to your left hand.
And relax,
and breathe...
Great.
And come back up...
And exhale...
As you go
through your day,
remember the energy
you've created here
and use it to make it
a productive one.
Namaste.
[Applause]
A reminder,
the studio's
being painted tomorrow,
so take everything
from your locker.
Thanks, guys.
Do I know you?
We haven't been introduced.
I saw you at the school.
Probably.
Too many yoga straps.
Darn it...
What grade is your child in?
Third.
Mine too!
I don't know how
I got roped into this.
Let's just call it
a fashion statement.
It's a long way to come
for a yoga class.
I came looking for you.
Me?
Yeah.
Why?
To tell you
to stay away from my husband.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Don't play games with me.
I don't know you
or your husband...
I am not stupid!
No, but you're crazy.
[Clasp locks]
I saw you with him.
[Rope strains]
[Gasping and choking]
[Choking]
[♪♪♪]
You seem
very chipper today.
Things are
getting better.
All that worrying
for nothing.
Well, what about
the other woman?
Gone.
It's over.
Are you sure?
Positive.
You must be very relieved.
I'm grateful,
very, very grateful.
And Sam?
Done.
I don't need him anymore.
My life with Nick is-
is working now.
That easy, huh?
That easy.
What if he calls you again?
Tries to
get you back?
He already has called.
[Chuckles]
He told me how much
he misses me.
Oh, so romantic.
Wanted to take me
back to the club,
like the night we met.
When he brought me
up to the stage and sang to me.
I don't remember you
telling me that.
No, you told me
you met him at the bar,
after his set.
You sent him a drink.
Uh, no, well, we had drinks,
of course we did,
but that was later,
that was after
he sang to me.
Sounds lovely.
Mm...
I doubt that is something
I would forget.
That first night,
from the first instant,
we were like a shooting star,
but now it's time
to get back to real life.
It's good you see things
so clearly.
I always know
when it's time to walk away.
How do you know that?
Well, um...
Guys have always had
this thing for me.
It's been like that
all my life,
then they get, um,
they get a little too crazy.
They become obsessive...
And when I can't make them
understand
the reality
of what we really are,
I have to go.
That must be very difficult.
It is. It's...
It's so frightening
I have to disappear
so they can't find me.
It's happened
more than once,
but that's not
what's happening now.
Now my life is perfect.
Listen, um,
I appreciate
everything you've done,
but I won't be coming back.
No, now that my life
is straightening out,
I don't see the point.
Laura, it's...
It's never this simple.
I'm sorry, uh,
in my case, it is.
No, no,
I-I don't think so.
There are things
that you've told me
that have me
very concerned.
The way you deal with
your relationships.
Your recollections differ
from one session to the next.
No...
No, I maybe carried on.
I-I exaggerate a little,
but I'm fine.
I'm really fine.
Laura, i-I'm not
comfortable with...
It's okay.
I am.
Well, at least
keep in touch
so I'll know how you're doing.
That won't be necessary.
[Sniffling]
Here.
Hey.
Hey, what do you
think, Lou?
I want to do
something special
for the holiday.
You know,
it's been a rough year,
for everybody.
How can you beat Turkey?
Well, Turkey's
pretty ordinary.
I was thinking more like duck.
What do you think about duck?
For 16?
For 12.
Well, you're going to
want to get 'em small,
they're more tender that way,
and figure on
half a pound a person,
so... two three-pounders
oughta do it.
That sounds good,
and they'll look fabulous
on my table.
And don't even bother about
makin' sauce.
We've got orange, sour cherry,
they're all homemade.
Outta this world.
It's going to be perfect.
A perfect family dinner.
Laura...
There's a gentleman
here to see you.
Thank you.
Hi, detective Mcauliffe.
Seattle pd.
Do you know this woman?
I think I took
a yoga class with her.
When was that?
A few days ago.
Um, Wednesday, I think.
She died
on Wednesday.
She died?
We found her
at the yoga studio,
in the elevator.
She was, uh, she was hanged.
Oh, my god...
We're just
talking to everyone
who signed in for
that last class.
Well, I don't know
what I can tell you.
Um, it was a regular class,
nothing out of the ordinary.
Well, could you tell me
who was at the studio
when you left?
I-I didn't really
pay attention.
I-I changed my clothes
and I left.
A Giselle sandler said
that someone who fits
your description
was one of
the last people there.
It's possible, I guess.
Well, do you, uh,
do you remember
if the victim was still there?
I...
You know, I saw her
packing up.
Was she alone?
I don't know.
Look, I...
I had a lot on my mind
and, um, I’m...
I'm actually embarrassed
to tell you
what I was really thinking
when you're asking me
about something so horrific.
Well, please, indulge me.
Well, the truth is,
the holidays
are coming up,
and, um, I was thinking about
how many people
were coming to dinner,
what I would be cooking.
I...
You know, I just didn't
pay any attention
to who was still in the gym.
You can be reached
at this number?
Anytime.
All right, well,
thank you for your time.
Thank you.
[♪♪♪]
What do you think?
This is perfect.
How short an escrow
will they take?
I start a new job
on the 15th,
and I want to get in,
get settled
by the first
of next month.
Well, that's pretty fast,
but I'll see what I can do.
Do it,
and you've got a sale.
You have my numbers.
Get back to me by tomorrow,
or I'll move on
to my second option.
I'm sure I can make it work.
Smart lady.
[Dialing phone]
Suzanne,
I'm at the beach house.
Will the sellers take
a 15-day escrow?
The loan's not a problem.
It's an all-cash sale.
Terrific.
I'll make it happen.
We're going to
end this year strong,
you'll see.
Bye.
All right,
so I pulled together
a couple of the flyers
like you've asked.
Just take a look,
see what's good.
I want it to be
a complete surprise.
I want to whisk him away
for the weekend,
something completely indulgent.
Okay, so we've got
a couple packages to Paris,
maybe Venice?
Paris, I like that idea.
Croissants on the left bank
in the morning.
Ice cream on ile St. Louis.
Emily would like that.
Maybe I should bring Emily.
No, no, no, no, no.
We need to be alone for this.
Okay, can you
put together
a package for Paris?
A romantic week for two.
This is just what we need
right now.
Absolutely.
I will have a couple options
drawn up for you tomorrow.
Thank you, Linda.
I am going to sweep Nick
off his feet.
Patient presented
as an ordinary uptown woman
with a boring marriage
and an exciting affair...
But, lately, her behavior
is becoming more and more
inappropriate.
While she does not present
as a traditional depressive,
more often than not,
her affect is flat
and dispassionate,
yet her descriptions of Sam,
subject of affair,
are embellished and idealized.
Her descriptions
of their first meeting
change with each telling.
I'm becoming very concerned
that this whole relationship
exists only in her mind.
Laura...
Charlie Willacker.
We're going to talk.
No, I've got to
get to a meeting.
No.
No, now.
No more ducking me.
My life has been a train wreck
since you passed through it.
Oh.
I thought you'd been doing well.
I-I see you're doing stories
on the network news now.
See?
I still follow your career,
even though we stopped
seeing each other.
We didn't
see each other, Laura!
Well, let's not get into
that argument again...
My wife believed that crap
about us having an affair.
Maybe because it was true.
We didn't, Laura!
It was all
in that head of yours!
There might have been
two people in your fantasy,
but there was only
one of us involved
here on planet earth.
I don't know why you feel
you need to deny what we had.
You are going to fix
what you destroyed.
You're going to convince Alix
that there was nothing
between us.
You are hurting me.
I have nothing more to lose.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were so hurt.
Come with me to see her
to tell her the truth.
Yeah, I will...
You know what,
I just have to get
to a meeting,
and I can't be late.
I'll wait.
No, it'll be hours.
I'll meet you there.
I don't trust you.
Well, you're going
to have to
if you want me
to go along with this.
All right, I'll meet you
back here at 5:00.
Don't mess with me, Laura!
I know where
to find you now!
[Cell phone ringing]
Hello?
You wouldn't have gotten
that taxi anyway.
The lady with
the plaid pants
would have wrestled you
to the ground for it.
Sam?
Where are you?
I don't have to
be there
to know where you are,
what you do.
[Chuckles] Okay...
Now you're scaring me.
You know you can't
keep secrets from me.
What is it you think you know?
I know you miss me.
[Chuckles]
Wrong.
I know you miss
what we had.
Wrong again.
And you've got
the best legs in town.
I'm digging
the trench.
Okay, where are you?
Right here.
Right in front
of you,
right where I always am.
What do you think you're doing?
Kidnapping you.
I don't have time
to be kidnapped.
One hour.
I want to take you somewhere.
I want to show you
that I wasn't
a complete bastard.
One hour.
Where to?
Pioneer square.
King street.
For once, you're
speechless?
She's beautiful.
I don't know
what to say.
I really miss you.
Come on.
Ah...
Oh, oh...My gosh.
[Chuckles]
Mm.
[Groaning in delight]
Oh, this is completely
out of bounds.
Well, you're irresistible.
I'm glad one of us has
a little self-control.
[Chuckles]
So, how are things at home?
Just all right.
That sounds promising.
Tell me you miss me a little.
I miss you,
a little.
[Giggles]
[Chatting]
Oh, my god,
there's Nick.
Get me out of here.
Okay, we'll get two of these.
[Cell phone rings]
This is Laura.
Laura, hello,
it's Ella Browning.
I know you said
you were done with this,
but I honestly don't think
that you should just walk away.
I think you need to
come back and see me.
I'm fine.
I have an opening
today at 4:00.
Thanks, but I don't need it.
- You can't just barge in here!
- Laura!
You can't just
barge in here!
Laura, where are you?
I'm through playing games!
Where is she?
Laura, Laura, I won't
fill the appointment.
Please do try to come.
I gotta go.
Laura!
Are-are you looking
for me, Charlie?
No, I want to buy a condo.
Thanks, Cathy.
Let's not do this here...
We do this here,
or we do it in front of Alix,
but we do it now.
I'm not letting you
out of my sight again.
You were
supposed to meet me
two days ago.
You didn't show up.
You obviously didn't
come to work yesterday
because I was here.
I waited all day,
so I am through taking you
at your so-called word.
Let's go.
[Knocks]
I expect you
to tell her the truth.
I'll tell her what
you want me to tell her.
I want you
to tell her the truth.
[Sighs in disgust]
No, no, no,
please, please,
five minutes.
That's all I want.
What is she doing here?
Please, just listen
to what she has to say.
I don't want to hear
anything that she has to say!
St-start talking.
It's not what you think
about Charley and me.
Um, we met at work,
and we had lunch
a few times.
You had lunch?
I thought you said
she was a total stranger.
No, we didn't
have lunch.
We met in the coffee
shop downstairs,
at the counter.
Making small talk
at a lunch counter
doesn't qualify
as "having lunch."
You can't even get
your stories straight.
No, I swear to you
that is all that happened.
We chatted
a couple of times,
the next thing I know,
she's blowing
our lives apart.
Tell her the truth,
dammit.
Charlie and I didn't
have an affair.
I wanted to,
but he wouldn't.
What about
all the phone calls?
The letters?
The...flowers
that kept
showing up?
She did it all,
unprovoked.
This whole thing
is in her head.
Is that true?
Yes.
You didn't
know him?
No.
So you made the whole thing up?
You blew
our lives apart
because of some crazy fantasy?
What kind of sick twist
are you?
I cared about Charlie.
I am here now because
I cared about Charlie,
which is more
than I can say for you.
You didn't care
enough to fight.
You just ran out,
first chance you got!
I did it.
I said what
you wanted me to say,
and, frankly, I don't think
she's worth it.
Now leave me alone.
Yoga, right?
That's where I know you from.
I manage the yoga studio.
You were in that class,
when the teacher was killed?
Oh, god, right.
Um, yeah, what a freak accident.
I'm not sure
the police think so.
They've been
all over my studio,
checking for prints,
other clues.
They're suspicious
of something.
Hey, um,
weren't you the woman
I saw there when I left?
I don't think so.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I-I thought it was you.
Did you see anyone else there?
Like I told
the police,
I-I really didn't notice.
Look, I'm sorry
to rush off like this,
but i-I'm really late.
I'm glad you decided
to come after all, Laura.
Well, I'm not sure
why I'm here,
but, lately, I've been
feeling bombarded by things,
um...
I thought maybe
talking with you...
Well, I'm very glad
you could make it.
I think it's important
that we talk some more.
What do you want to talk about?
About your
relationships,
especially
the one with Sam.
I'm...concerned
that your life isn't
on a strong enough footing
to keep you from...
Drifting back to him.
Well, the truth is,
I-I have seen him.
He, uh,
he brought me to see
a sculpture he made
of me,
of my body.
It was in a gallery
near the art museum.
[Quietly]: I see.
Sometimes,
our view of relationships
is not completely realistic.
W-We become
so emotionally needy,
we create fantasies,
connections,
and we believe
they're real.
What's not real?
You think I'm not real?
Y-You think Sam's not real?
Well, I-I know
that you're real,
and I believe Sam is real,
but I...
I wonder if your love affair
with him is real.
That's crazy.
You think I'm imagining
my relationship with Sam,
is that what you're saying?
That's what I'm asking.
Often, when things
aren't going well
in our primary
relationships,
we create an escape,
a-a connection
that gives us what we need.
For instance,
you want to go to Rome,
but you can't get there,
so you paint a picture of it
on your wall,
a mural, a scene.
Trompe l'oeil.
What?
Trompe l'oeil,
that's what it's called.
It's a "trick...Of the eye."
Well, you understand that,
don't you.
You did it
when you were young.
I did not imagine that man
when I was young.
Believe me, he was very real.
Yes, yes,
I know, I know,
but...
What you were doing
was antithetical to your soul,
so you created fantasies
around it
to make it more palatable.
It's not unusual
to recreate fantasies
throughout your life
because of it.
Like Sam...
Let me help you
get through this.
understand this,
let go of it.
What you have with Nick,
that's real...
And good,
and worth fighting for.
I don't need help.
I'm fine.
Laura, please.
You don't need to be concerned.
I have everything under control.
I don't believe that, Laura...
Please don't walk out that...
Believe what you want.
I'm going.
[Jazz band plays]
[Scat-singing]
[Saxophone starts soloing]
[Singer and saxophone duet]
[Song ends]
Valerie Robinson,
ladies and gentlemen!
[Cheering and applause]
I'm not
sleeping with her!
I didn't say you were.
Not in so many words.
I asked who she was.
That's a perfectly
reasonable question.
It was how you asked.
You know, you showed me
the sculpture,
and I thought I meant
something special to you,
but I’m
out of the picture
for a few weeks,
and, true to form,
you've moved on
to someone else.
Look, this is not
what you think it is.
Our singer dropped out.
I called Valerie to fill in
because I knew how good she is.
Mm, I can only imagine.
I didn't come for this.
You go home to your husband.
Wait, don't
walk away from me!
Hey, hey!
Don't walk
away from me...
Take it easy. Stop!
What's wrong with you?
You're driving me crazy!
Take it easy!
Hey...
[♪♪♪]
What are we doing?
This.
[♪♪♪]
Nina Panker just called.
She wants you to meet her
at the magnolia
ranch house right away.
She says she's got her husband
right where she wants him.
Let's hope so.
I like this place,
a lot.
I just don't like
being played.
Come on, Harry,
whenever I push you
into anything,
you always end up
thanking me.
Like I said, I don't
like being played.
[Nina chuckles]
You've been saying
that you're tired
of apartment living
and you work so hard,
and this place
is perfect to come home to.
How'd it go?
Nina's still
working on him.
I think she'll get
what she wants.
Hey...
So your client
went back
to the magnolia
ranch house today.
Not only that,
but I think your guy
is going to make an offer
on the Mercer island house.
We're on a roll.
You're amazing.
Get them both in escrow,
and we've got some big-time
celebrating to do.
I am all over it.
Hi, Sam.
Are you still the hottest
property in the office?
You say that
to all the brokers.
Only the ones
I have to cancel on.
I'm sorry, babe,
I can't do it tonight.
That's okay.
I...
If you hadn't canceled,
I-I would have canceled myself.
Um...
I really want to
make my marriage work, Sam.
Well, if that's what you want,
then that's what I want for you.
Thanks.
I know you mean that.
Gotta go.
[Speed-dial beeping]
[Ringing]
[Woman's voice]:
Hello?
Hello, um...
I must have dialed
the wrong number.
Sorry.
[Ringing]
[Same woman]:
Hello?
Hello.
Um...
Are you looking for Sam?
Yes.
Who's this?
Valerie.
A friend.
Where's Sam?
Um...
He's in the shower.
Can I give him
a mess...
[Beeps phone off]
[Banging insistently]
[Banging on door]
[Pounding]
Ah.
I wanted to see you
one last time,
so I could keep
this image in my mind
in case I ever weaken.
What are you talking about?
It should never surprise me
to catch you in a lie,
but somehow it always does.
Where is she?
Where's who?
Valerie.
I called you back.
I didn't want
to be cruel.
I wanted you to know
how difficult it was for me
to let you go.
I opened my heart to you!
You did it again!
[Sighs]
Strawberries
and chocolate?
What's that about?
You're a liar!
I trusted you!
Hey, hey!
Listen, listen!
Valerie means nothing to me.
She's crashing here.
Okay?
I swear to you.
Just relax, sit down.
I'll get you a glass of wine.
I was saving this
for when I fixed you
dinner next,
but, clearly,
now's a better time.
Where you going?
Go to hell.
Hey!
Taxi!
[Car honking]
[Brakes squealing]
Are you insane?
Are you out of
your mind?
Do you have any idea
what that horn costs?
Forget that it meant
something to me!
And just for
the record,
not that it's any
of your business,
I'm not sleeping with Valerie.
Oh, stop it already.
I'm not a fool.
And neither am I!
She's got a boyfriend back home
that weighs in at about 280!
She's staying with me
until her place is ready.
W-What is this place?
Who lives here?
This is you?
Get the hell out.
This is your place.
Get out of here!
Hey!
You live here alone?
There's no husband, is there?
No child either.
You're out of your mind,
aren't you, Laura?
Get out of my life.
Believe me, I'm going.
Who's this doctor?
Is he real,
does he exist?
Of course he's real.
Somebody better warn
the poor bastard.
Wait, Sam!
You can't do this!
Let me explain!
I know everything
I need to know.
You're insane!
No, please don't,
don't wreck my family...
Get help, Laura!
You need
professional help.
[Crying] No, don't...
Let me get you to a doctor.
Please.
No, please, I know you want to
destroy my family.
Please don't.
This is out of hand!
You need help!
You're going to hurt somebody!
I don't want to hurt anybody!
[Knife stabs]
[He gasps in pain]
[Sobs]
I just don't want you
to upset Nick.
[Gasps]
[Crying]
[Groans weakly]
[Sobbing, gasping for breath]
My piano will look
amazing in this corner.
Oh, it's the perfect
place for it.
Harry just loves
this room, you know.
Oh, well,
I'm glad to see
you got him
to come around.
I always do,
once I convince him
it's his idea.
I am going to
cook up a storm
in this kitchen.
Oh, this is
a wonderful place
for family dinners.
You're right.
It will be perfect.
Why are they selling?
They're no longer together.
You're kidding?
Everything seems so perfect.
I'm sure it was at one time.
Some things aren't meant
to last forever.
Well...
We want to buy it.
I did it.
I got an offer on
the magnolia ranch house.
A good one?
Close to asking.
Oh, my gosh, you are amazing.
Well, your clients want me to
present the offer tonight.
Tonight?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, that won't work.
I need to leave for
bainbridge island in an hour.
Oh, hell,
you made it happen.
You can handle it alone.
Why don't you
make the offer,
and I'll discuss it
with him after,
and we'll fax the counters
in the morning.
Sounds great.
He usually gets home
around 6:00
to have dinner
with his kid.
Well done.
Thank you.
[Cell phone rings]
Hello.
Laura,
it's Ella Browning.
Hello.
I'm glad
I finally reached you.
You haven't been
returning my calls.
I've been busy.
Laura...
I read about Sam in the paper.
That was your Sam,
wasn't it?
It said
he was a musician.
He worked at the jazz club
on 65th.
Sad, isn't it?
They say he was mugged
in the street.
You must be devastated.
[Casually]: I am.
Laura...
Have you...
Talked to the police?
Why would I?
I thought you might have
something to tell them.
What could I tell them?
I wasn't there.
Does it not bother you, Laura,
that the man you say
you were involved with
was murdered in the street?
I don't say
anything.
That's your fantasy.
Sam was very real,
and, frankly,
I'm starting to feel harassed.
I'm just concerned
about you, Laura, that's all.
That's why I'm calling.
No, it's not.
You want to involve me
in Sam's death somehow.
Well, I'm not
going there.
It was a random
street crime.
That's what
the papers say,
and I believe them.
Well, I don't.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means I think
you need help, Laura.
It means I don't believe
any of this happened
the way you say it did.
I think you need
to come and see me.
You know, I think I do, too.
[Laughter echoing]
Emily!
Emily,
where'd you go?
Mommy! Mommy!
Save me!
[Family laughing]
[Emily squeals and giggles]
[Kids singing]
Good job, em!
[Ferry horn blares]
[Gasps in fright]
[Splash]
Well, hello, missus.
Please come in.
Hello, Yolanda.
Dr. Jarretts?
Laura Phillips.
Oh, hi.
We haven't formally met,
but I've seen you
showing the house, of course.
Hello, Emily.
It's good
to see you again.
Um, listen,
I brought
something for you.
You like charm bracelets,
don't you?
Oh, you bet.
We collect them.
Well, I like
this little bear the best.
Me too.
Put your hand out.
There you go.
[Chuckles warmly]
Wow, huh?
Now, let me show you
what I've brought for you.
You'll need to discuss
this offer with Suzanne
and then respond
by 7:00 tomorrow night.
[Sighs heavily]
It's a good price.
Yeah, I'm sure
we can make this work.
My clients will be
very pleased.
[Sighs ruefully]
My wife and I, we were...
We were happy here.
I heard about what happened.
You have my deepest condolences.
Thank you.
We had, um,
planned on
moving downtown
to shorten my commute
so I could spend more time
with the family.
Well, I guess that's
more important now
than ever, isn't it?
Look!
So pretty, huh?
That was really
kind of you.
It was nothing...
[♪♪♪]