[ bleep ]
deep water is where
the alligators like to lurk.
♪
We're here and one's
down by our camp.
We're here and
one's up this creek.
One's over here, which
we've never heard before.
This could be deadly.
There's a gator right there.
It's about an
eight-foot alligator.
Oh, [bleep].
♪
Whoo!
All right.
Narrator: Over 10 seasons,
the "naked and afraid" challenge
has proven to be the ultimate
test of endurance and skill...
Holy [bleep]. It's working.
Narrator: ...Where
extreme necessity...
No sleep, no
food. It's miserable.
Narrator: ...Demands
innovative solutions...
What if we had an a-frame
coming out this way?
I hope this works.
Narrator: ...And ingenuity...
Seems to be a taj mahal by
the end of a couple days here.
Narrator: ...Is
often the difference
between success...
Fire!
- I made a door.
- Nice work.
Narrator: ...And failure.
Holy [bleep].
Narrator: From
customized tools...
Anything that you need,
you're gonna have to make it.
Got us a bow.
Narrator: ...To
complex structures...
Just decide it's time now
we go black macgyver on this.
Narrator: Survivalists
break down the process...
If we don't keep experimenting,
you're never gonna find out
what that magical solution is.
Narrator: ...Of
what went right...
Yes!
Narrator: ...And wrong...
Ay!
Narrator: ...When they tried
to outsmart mother nature.
Woman: Oh, my god, we have fire!
Narrator: ...For 21 days.
Whoo!
- Oh, my god.
- High-five, good job.
[ speaks indistinctly ]
- holy [bleep].
- Right!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Yeah!
-- Captions by vitac
--  www.Vitac.Com
captions paid for by
discovery communications
the bugs are terrible.
We need a fire.
One of the most
essential problems
the survivalists
must solve is fire...
I'm failing miserably.
Narrator: But in
difficult conditions,
traditional methods
must often be reimagined.
We have to have fire
because we're really cold.
It's difficult enough
to start a fire
in a primitive environment.
Man: Everything's wet here.
Sarah: It's about the kind
of tinder that you're using,
the kind of wood
you have available,
the conditions that
you're starting the fire in.
Damnit!
Bone makes a great top piece
because it's not gonna burn.
- You ready?
- I'm mad.
Come on, ej.
[ groaning ]
narrator: In the yucatán,
where fire to boil
water was essential...
Luke: Oh, god. Looks like urine.
Narrator: ...One
survivalist exemplified
the spirit of ingenuity
more than most.
[ squeaking ]
I'm just gonna go slow with it.
Trying to start
fire in the yucatán
was quite the challenge.
The water was stagnant.
So you need to be able
to boil that to purify it.
And the bugs were
constantly there
and they were constantly on you
and they were
constantly annoying you.
- You're doing awesome.
- Oh, that little [bleep]
is biting the back
of my leg right now.
The only way that you're
gonna keep them away is fire
and the smoke from the fire.
So we absolutely
had to have a fire.
Oh, my hands are
getting all slippery.
God, it smells hot.
When it comes to making
fire, you've got tons of options.
The most basic
is the hand drill.
You need a simple
little board with a notch,
a long, skinny stick,
and you rub them as
fast together as you can.
It creates enough
friction to create an ember
that you drop into
a tinder bundle
and give it some oxygen
and bursts into flames.
It's just sitting there
cooking the wood.
My hands are starting
to get rubbed raw,
my muscles are getting
tired, and it got to a point
where I realized really
quick that we're gonna need
to figure out something
a little more efficient.
Okay, I think I'm gonna
start cranking it, ready?
All right, go.
Luke: The great
thing about a bow drill
is it allows you to turn
the spindle about 10 times
faster than you can
with the hand drill
with a third of the energy.
While you can be
more efficient with it,
it's a lot more difficult
to keep under control.
It pops out of the board a lot.
The cord can make it
fly in different directions.
♪
- [ groans ]
- ugh.
It was time for
technique number three.
I decided I was gonna make
my version of a pump drill.
Just a different idea.
I've split a stick
down the middle here
so that I could get
this little wedge in here.
It works the same
way as the bow drill,
but you need to
figure out some way
to put weight on
each side of it.
I'm gonna fill each
of these with rocks.
I'm gonna put
one on either side.
Like that, so these
will spin with the stick.
It might actually work.
And then you hang
a piece of wood
with a piece of cordage
going up over it and twist it up.
When you pull the
two handles down,
it untwists it and
the centrifugal force
brings it back up and twists
it back up around the spindle.
♪
Energy-wise, it's an
extremely efficient method.
♪
The centrifugal
force of the rocks
is doing most of the work.
All you're doing is pumping
it every few seconds.
Oh, it's bending in the middle.
This is done, shot.
In hindsight, it's
something that looks
really good on paper,
but is not that easy
to pull off in nature.
To make it work,
I would've needed
a perfectly straight stick
that was twice as strong.
And that's not that easy
to find in the yucatán.
Woman: At this point,
no idea is a bad idea.
This cord is stronger
than any other one.
Strongest cord yet, huh?
But you know, if you
don't keep experimenting,
you're never gonna find out
what that magical solution is.
♪
- Okay. I know, okay.
- It's coal. It's totally coal.
That's gonna be it right there.
Come on, baby.
There you go.
- There we go.
- Oh!
- Oh, my god, we have fire!
- There we go!
- All right, partner.
- Awesome!
Luke: Every failure we had
was a learning experience.
And it's because of those
failures that we figured out
what was gonna work.
And that's why
we finally got it.
This is... Christmas.
♪
Narrator: In the exumas,
sarah proved that
sometimes the solution
is right in front
of your face...
So I gather you've
done this before.
Yeah, we'll have fire today.
Narrator: ...If you have
the creativity to see it.
Without fire, we
couldn't cook anything
and we didn't want to be eating
raw sea snails the entire time.
[ coughs ]
♪
These bifocal
lenses and this mask
have magnification properties
that are indicative of
the ability to make a fire.
I had equip my dive
mask with bifocal lenses
so that I would be better able
to see things up close
while I was scuba diving.
They're not a very
strong prescription.
They're basically
like reading glasses.
But I did have an idea
that I'd be able to
start a fire with them,
although it was not
something I had done before.
It's not an exact science.
It's more of a trial and
error kind of a thing.
First, I tried using a single
lens that wasn't working.
Then I tried using a double
lens that was almost working.
Yeah, I thought there
was smoking, for sure.
What if we rub one of
those pieces of tinder
in the charcoal?
We were able to grind up
charcoal in with the tinder
to lower the ignition
point of the tinder bundle
so that the magnification lenses
would be able
to ignite the fire,
so put that inside and
it'll get hotter faster.
♪
- It's happening.
- Yeah.
♪
There is nothing more
satisfying than starting a fire
when you desperately need it.
It feels amazing.
Ooh, hoo, hoo!
[ giggles ] I did it.
[ laughs ]
fire!
That was probably the first
and by far the most
satisfying fire I have ever built.
Let me flap my feathers.
[ laughs ]
♪
- Ah.
- We have to find water.
We've got water right there.
We've got to find
a way to process it.
Narrator: With fire
comes the ability
to boil and purify water.
Ah.
Narrator: But when fire fails,
the survivalist must
devise new methods
to capture every
fresh drop they can.
Man: Oh, shoot.
I can't believe how
much it's raining right now.
This is insane.
You just put one of
these at the bottom.
Narrator: ...From
rainfall traps...
- Drink, drink!
- Oh, my god.
Narrator: ...And seep wells...
It's a very small trickle.
Narrator: ...To natural
filtration systems.
Charcoal pulls
all the impurities
out of water and
filters it and cleans it
and makes it drinkable.
It's great.
I remember that the
moss round here has iodine
which use iodine
for purification water.
As far as filter and water
there are several ways that
you can sit here and filter.
Our problem was we
couldn't find any damn water.
It wasn't there.
♪
Don't it suck there is so much
water out there in front of us
and we cannot drink it?
This location in
the philippines,
there wasn't a fresh
water to be found.
No creeks, no ponds, no
streams, no lakes, nothing.
♪
Woman: So hot.
Out here, if you want
something, you go get it.
We need a long-term
source of water.
- We got to find that water.
- Yep.
I figure somewhere
on this island,
we got a water table.
You got the wet
season in the philippines
where it's getting just
drenched with rain.
It's gonna seep down
through the ground
and it's gonna hold down
there around the sand.
So we have to get out there
and we had to dig a well.
I definitely can tell that
I'm getting dehydrated.
Oh, absolutely.
I was looking for a low area at
possibly held water at one time
and I was looking
for green plants
that are just thriving off of
water source somewhere.
Being out here,
it's hot, it's humid.
It really pulls all the
moisture out of you.
I remember when we
started digging this thing,
I knew I wasn't gonna
hit in a couple feet.
You know, I was thinking
maybe, you know, five, six feet.
Let's see it.
It's getting moist.
Let me jump in now, yeah?
And as it turns out,
it was at least eight feet
before I hit a water table...
Whoo!
Jeremy: ...Which I
think has to be a record
on "naked and afraid."
I don't think anybody's
dug a well that deep.
I got to throw that in there.
We finally get the
water pot collected,
me and cassidy
finally got that fire going
and that was a huge
morale boost right there.
This is just such a huge moment.
I figured, long as we
got that water well,
long as this working, we
was gonna make our 21 days.
I'm sorry?
As thirsty as I was
drinking my own pee
really never crossed my mind.
Too damn hot.
Narrator: In guyana,
extreme heat led
fans survivalist shane
to a hydration method
few ever considered.
I don't think I've
ever been this thirsty.
- In the lid?
- Yeah.
- Why?
- 'cause I'm thirsty.
I'll eat rat, I'll eat anything.
I will never drink my
own urine for survival.
Woman: He is gonna
drink from the lid.
There's definitely a reason
why your body dismisses urine
because it is not
fit for drinking.
No pee for me.
I have to be pretty close
to death's door to try that.
Just now looking
back, I'd have done it.
[ laughs ]
[ vomits ]
are you okay?
[ vomits, coughs ]
narrator: Coming up...
What kind of shelter
are you thinking?
Something simple.
Oh, damn.
This is so not fun.
We had to consider
bugs, floods, wind.
It was an intense environment.
Build the shelter.
Now that's a fireplace.
- It's pretty solid.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Oh!
What kind of shelter
are you thinking?
Something simple.
What if we had an a-frame
coming out this way?
We're just running out of time
and it's, like, freaking me
out a little bit to be honest.
I'm with you.
This is probably
the worst shelter
that anyone has
ever constructed.
A lot of survival
it comes down to
engineering and physics.
Shelter's a priority just to
get away from all the critters.
To do something right
to where it'll work for you
and it won't fail is
an essential skill.
Man: Oh, this is is nice.
Darrin: You can't afford
to waste your energy.
- Oh.
- Ow!
Oh!
Whoa, [bleep].
Ow.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I've had about
enough of this [bleep]!
Narrator: In the hill
country of northern india
where cold air crashes down
from the himalayan mountains
two survivalists had to take
their shelter building skills
to a whole new level.
It's cold out here.
Oh, damn, it's cold.
In our location in india,
we're about 6,400
feet elevation.
I might have to go a
little bit slower up this hill
because I'm feeling...
Okay.
During the daytime, it
normally didn't get over
about 60 degrees.
At night, we're looking
at, like, 30 degrees.
- How you feeling?
- Really cold.
I wanna get this started.
Our first shelter
that we built was
an a-frame debris shelter
and the debris helped us
trapped in our body heat.
It worked as an
insulating layer,
but the shelter had
to be small enough.
♪
These nights have
been challenging.
It's been unseasonably cold.
I'm really worried that
I won't be able to stay
warm enough tonight.
Oh, damn.
Hakim: As far as
debris shelters go,
I mean, it was a great shelter,
but my partner phaedra
had less body mass than me.
She was really freezing.
I don't know if you
understand how cold I get.
Every single night is,
like, a disaster for me.
Hakim: And we knew
that we were gonna have
to build something better.
We were both going to
make it through this challenge.
What do you think about
bringing a little fire inside?
Like a fireplace? Okay.
So you want your
fire pit like that.
Phaedra thought that
fire was really important
and I thought the shelter
was really important.
So we tried to combine the two.
I just decided, hey,
you know what?
It's time now we go black
macgyver on this, you know,
so we wanted to pretty
much make a log cabin.
We took a lot of pine saplings
and that created our front wall
and our sidewall.
The gaps in between the logs,
we filled those
with moss and mud.
We need double this amount
if we want to be waterproof.
Okay.
And that allowed us
to keep a lot of the heat
enclosed in there,
but also to keep the
elements from outside
from flowing
through really easily.
The roof was made
of a few saplings
and then on top of that,
we took bark off of trees
and we used that as shingles
to help shed the water.
The fireplace had to
be completely enclosed
and we did that using
mud, moss, and rocks.
Now that's a fireplace.
Hopefully, we'll
see what happens.
So at the end, we had a shelter
that was totally enclosed
with a chimney system
that had the smoke
going up and out.
There was a lot that
went into the design.
♪
So we're about to cook up
some crabs that we found today.
Cooking them on a hot stone.
The shelter worked.
It was a great success because
it represented compromise
between what she
needed and what I needed.
- Okay, this is effing good.
- Good night.
Narrator: Perhaps the ultimate
test of a shelter's strength
came in the storm
ravaged marsh land
of the wekiva river basin.
It's very dense in here.
Our location in
florida was no joke.
We were in a swamp.
Wow, yeah, this is...
Looks a little
different, doesn't it?
Mm-hmm.
We had to consider
bugs, floods, rain, wind,
it was an intense environment
to try to build the shelter.
One shelter that I know about,
it's a double lean to
or like an a-frame --
Mm-hmm.
But it actually it tapers down.
- Yeah.
- Are you down with that?
We knew we needed a shelter
that's gonna withstand
crazy rain, crazy winds.
That was our main goal.
So the design that we came up
with was sort of a
modified lean-to situation
where we were stacking
sticks onto an existing tree.
So we had an anchored
point to help with a secure build
and something that we
knew we could rely on.
After we had that really
strong anchor point,
we built these beams coming
from the top of the anchor point
against the tree
down to the ground.
- We got --
- We could put lats.
Yeah, we can put
here and then...
- Lats across the way, yeah.
- Yeah.
- The palms in there.
- Mm-hmm.
What that was gonna do was
gonna give us a support network
for our lattice to hold all
of our palm fronds shingles.
And our palm frond shingles
didn't just stop at the ground,
they actually extended
outward several feet.
And that created no
possible way for that wind
or that rain to get
blown in sideways
and mess with us
inside our shelter.
We'll be all right. Hope so.
Those first few
days with our shelter
were really like a test run.
- Man, it's coming down.
- Yeah.
♪
Well, it's a good
time to fix leaks.
We got hit with
some rain and wind.
So we're out there,
we're constantly tweaking
with our shelter
and fixing the roof
and it just keeps
raining and raining
and then raining some more.
[ thunder crashes ]
it's pouring down
outside, like, pouring down.
I'm kind of nervous that
the lake that we're by
will rise up and
come into our shelter.
What we didn't realize
is that we were seeing
the early notes of
what was gonna be
one of the strongest
hurricanes ever recorded.
♪
I mean, it was knocking
trees over all around us.
It became pretty clear
pretty quickly that we were
in a dangerous scenario.
- Amal and duke?
- Yeah?
We have a safety issue.
We need to take you out.
- Okay.
We need to go now.
The producers
came in and took us
to an offsite location until
it was safe to go back in.
And honestly, I didn't expect
to ever see that shelter again.
♪
- Oh, my god.
- It's crazy.
Duke: We're finally cleared
to go back to our location
and we're walking in,
it literally looks
like a battlefield.
Amal: Nothing
even looks the same.
We come around the corner,
we see that despite
the craziness,
our shelter withstood
a [bleep] hurricane.
It looks usable as
long as it's not...
Whoo! Yes!
- ...Flooded.
All of the shingles
are still on it,
like, our shelter's still there.
We are ecstatic.
Our tinder that we put
up here still very dry.
Oh, dude.
It's just a little bit
of wetness in there
and just some
holes here and there.
But the hurricane
did not win. [ laughs ]
narrator: Coming up.
There are all types of
dangers in every direction,
snakes, and there were
alligators everywhere.
So it'll be a noose at one end
and I'm gonna pull
it from the other end
once we get it around
the gator's neck.
Whoo!
Let's try to steer
clear of this spot.
Narrator: When competing
for food with the world's
most evolved predators...
[ roars ]
[ growling ]
narrator: ...The
survivalists have to create
any advantage they can.
Oh, [bleep].
Hey... [ speaks indistinctly ]
[ screams ]
I found a hollowed
log on the bank.
Let me get it to where
these crayfish swim in here.
I just had to try
everything, you know?
I had try all the skills I got.
Hmm. Perfect fit there.
Green ants in there for bait.
Improvising on
different skill sets,
you know, as far as,
like, what kind of trap?
Aah! [bleep].
Holly: Get it, get it, get it!
Dan: You got to be persistent
and you've got to know that
if you're doing the
right steps, it will pay off.
I've added a barb
to the spear point.
Holy [bleep].
- All right!
- Oh, my god.
And know that your 1 out of 10
is gonna turn up
eventually, you know?
♪ Got myself a prawny prawn ♪
♪
Narrator: In south africa,
an experienced hunter
had to adapt his backwoods
skills to a strange land.
I decided early on in a
challenge to go ahead
and make a hunting implement.
I've been making bows
since I was like 4 years old.
I'm no stranger to
that hunting weapon,
but I don't know the
materials out there in africa.
So I have to trust my skills
and work with what I have
and then hope
for the best on it.
You want pretty dense
timber to start with.
That may work. It
very well may work.
My normal rule of thumb
with making a long bow
is I make the bow as
tall as the shooter is,
because if we have a little
short bow with the limbs
you've got to bend
back so much further
it's more likely to bust.
As far as bow wood, you
want a hard, dense wood
because if you have
something that's real sluggish
and weak, well, it's either
gonna break or when you pull it,
it's gonna be bent.
What are you
using for the arrow?
That square stuff I
do for a hand drill.
It works great. I'm
gonna see what happens.
The biggest thing is
having a good arrow
because if you don't, if
you don't take your time
and flesh it right,
you'll have a strand.
And a strand and six
inches don't seem like much
until you -- until you're
shooting at a rabbit,
you know?
You need it
straight, very straight,
and there's not a lot of
straight sticks in nature.
So you improvise,
use fire, heat it up,
bend it into place
where you need it
and straighten it.
I heat it up right here,
I hold it place once it's hot,
and once I let go, it'll
stay. It's pretty neat.
One trick to measure an arrow,
you take the end of the
arrow, put it on your throat,
my middle fingers where
they end right there,
that's how long
your arrow should be.
There it is.
This arrow right here is
tipped with a piece of bone.
You know, the
penetration's not very deep.
With the arrowhead,
you can sharpen
the end of the stick
and it would work,
but I want a bigger
cutting blade.
So what I do is I take a
piece of bone, I sharpen it up,
tie it up with some
cordage, works great.
What the feathers do,
they guide the arrow
in a straight path
as they do a bird.
Baobab, tree of life.
For the cordage, I go
back to the baobab tree.
It made really good cordage
because the
elephants would strip it,
then they would chew on it.
So it was pliable.
Twist clockwise,
wrap counterclockwise.
It's simple, but it's what
holds the whole thing together
and it works great.
And the moment of truth.
We got us a bow.
Oh, yeah.
It wasn't the prettiest
bow I've ever made.
It's what you call
a survival bow.
I don't need it to be
pretty. I need it to work.
This is awesome.
You're really impressive.
Thank you.
[ bleep ]
now I got some shots off,
but the animals out
there are elusive.
[bleep], yeah.
But the bow, it
felt great, actually.
I would've loved to
have been able to just
bring it home with me.
I would've been able to
take it out here in arkansas
and so some small
game hunting with it.
Look at all the animal
dung around here.
Oh, [bleep].
[bleep] happens, man.
♪
Narrator: In the
florida everglades,
a different ryan
needed the right tool
for a very deadly task,
ryan: Surviving
in the everglades
was a huge challenge
for me right off the bat.
There are all types of
dangers in every direction.
Florida panthers,
venomous snakes,
and there were
alligators everywhere.
We're here and one's
down by the camp,
we're here and
one's up this creek.
One's over here, wish we
never knew that they were there.
There's a gator
nest right in here.
They like to make their
nests in the middle of these.
- All right, I'll go over there.
- I'm not.
- Why don't you wanna go?
- I'm not stupid.
I don't, like, not
think things through.
Earlier on in the challenge,
my partner amber gave
me quite the hard time
about not wanting
to go after gators.
We're gonna gator hunt.
You have to go
to places like that
to catch a gator.
There is no exceptions.
- There is an exception.
It's called thinking.
It's called you being a [bleep].
Up to this point,
I feel like I had
been very successful
with my hunting capabilities
and my intake on
protein from a fish.
Ha ha! Whoo!
My partner amber
had just tapped out.
Amber: My body aches so bad.
And I knew I needed
to find some source,
a bigger protein, to
help me get to extraction.
The only thing that seems to
be left around here is alligators.
It was time to take
it to that next level.
Last night I woke
from a dream that I had.
And it was someone
that was using giant
boomsticks with a noose on it.
I laid awake for an hour or
more last night just thinking about
how I can create one of
those with natural materials.
The boomstick noose
is a pretty basic concept,
if you've ever seen a
dog catcher using one.
So here I've got my 12-foot
boomstick that I found.
The next piece of
material I needed
was a durable vine.
And that's gonna be the noose.
So it'll be a noose at one end
and I'm gonna pull
it from the other end
once we get it around
the gator's neck.
And in order to
fasten that noose,
I had to find smaller vines to
make a bunch of fixed circles.
At the very end of
my broomstick noose,
I had six to eight of them.
That's where the most
durability had to be.
fight was gonna come from.
And by fixing these circles,
I had made to
the top of the pole,
I was able to run the vine
through all the fixed circles.
So once you pull it through,
that noose on the end
starts to get smaller and
cinches tighter together.
In my mind, it was gonna be
strong enough and durable enough
to go after an eight
to 10-foot alligator.
[ water splashes ]
I just heard this intense
splashing around over there.
Morning of day 18,
this huge splash happens
off to my right hand side.
Right then, I knew I
had something big.
I knew that this was the
moment I'd been waiting for.
Stay there.
Whoo!
He ain't going anywhere
with this thing on him.
The alligator broomstick
noose worked flawlessly.
We're gonna go and
take care of this one now.
But I spent a
little too much time
getting up on the alligator
and finishing the job.
The noose actually broke off
the alligator's neck and
he started to barrel roll.
♪
All right.
It wasn't very clean,
but it was quick.
Having crafted something
out of natural materials
after everything I've
learned throughout my life
and in implementing
it in a real time
survival situation,
it was probably one of
the greatest moments,
honestly, of my life.
Remember when
amber called me a [bleep]
said I was scared of alligators?
Ha!
♪
Narrator: In another
florida swamp location,
the spark of inspiration came
in a very unexpected moment.
- Wow.
- Oh, see some water.
- Ah, yes.
- Yep.
Amal: Where we were at was
obviously very swampy and wet.
So a couple times I would
go into the creek to pee.
And each time I peed, I noticed
that the fish would get closer.
♪
Mm. They are first.
Human urine and a
lot of other bodily fluids
actually have a lot of proteins
that attracts certain animals.
And so, I put two and
two together and I was like,
"oh, I can actually attract
them to you this way."
wow.
The next time around I
went out there and I was like,
okay, I'm gonna catch
some fish with my pee.
And I didn't tell nobody that
'cause they don't want
to be embarrassed.
I'm gonna do a
little bit fishing.
There's a bunch of
baby ones over there.
Sweet, okay. Good luck.
I was like, let me make
sure I can catch these fish
before I go out there
and promise something
that's not gonna happen.
♪
We didn't have a fishing net,
we didn't have fishing line,
hooks or anything like that.
But I had to pee
and I had a bag.
♪
I did it just one time.
I had the bag and then
I peed really close to it.
The fish swam up and
basically went right into the bag.
Got some.
Hey, duke, grab
the pot, if you can.
I just caught some fish
and I don't wanna put it
back in the water 'cause
I don't wanna lose them.
Awesome. What's your technique?
It's kind of gross, to
be honest with you.
When you pee in
the water, they smell it
and then they kind
of get attracted to it
and they just kind
of linger right here.
That's what they're
doing right now.
Oh, that's hilarious.
I was kind of like,
did you plan that?
Was that accidental?
We'll put them in here for now,
but we can come up
with a better container.
Yeah.
It's not how I
usually catch fish,
but if it's gonna
get us some protein,
I love you, girl. Get it.
Drink some water. Do it again.
This is so awesome.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Well, this is really exciting.
You take every win you can get.
You appreciate every
little scrumptious bite,
no matter how you got it.
Oh, my gosh. Here we go.
But the fish maybe did
taste interesting with kind of,
I don't know, like a
tangy after note, perhaps.
You know, they're tiny,
that's definitely
good protein for us.
I'm so thankful.
Thank you for your
amazing technique.
No problem.
Oh, I feel really good
about that. I am so happy.
[ laughs ]
narrator: Coming up...
The sun is killing me.
This place is brutal on my skin.
[ buzzing ]
oh, what are those
horse flies after? My life?
- It's for your sunburn.
- Oh.
Making a little
warthog fat lotion.
And it feels so good.
Only problem with this is
that it turns your skin purple.
♪
Narrator: From the moment
the challenge begins,
a skilled survivalist
wastes no time identifying
the innovative possibilities
of their surroundings.
Oh, man.
We can use it later
for some good cheese.
Oh, wow.
Charcoal makes
a good toothpaste.
Once you step foot out there,
your wheels are turning,
your mind's going.
You're looking for things
that's gonna be able
to help you later on.
I see a shoulder bone.
I don't see it just
as a shoulder bone.
I see it as a shovel.
I don't see just an antler, I
see spear points or an all,
which is a hole punch
because there's no store around.
Amazon's not
gonna send it to you.
Looks like a leg bone.
That may come in use, thank you.
You might not need
them right then and there,
but I can promise
you later you will.
Let's do this.
- [ laughs ]
♪
There's a thorn in there.
Aah!
Narrator: From
thorn-covered jungles...
Ow. [bleep].
Narrator: ...To sun
scorched deserts...
The survivalists' need
to protect their feet
has inspired a
variety of solutions.
That is a partner, using
her hair for my feet.
How's that?
Oh, yeah. That's so much better.
Angela, you gotta
size them to your feet.
And I had this rope,
so I pulled apart
those inner strands to
bind the sandals together.
You tie a little string
onto that and then little
loop behind your heel
and you go over the top of
your foot and tie it together,
and it's super
simple, but it's secure.
They lasted the entire
challenge and have been
on several backpacking
trips with me in the utah desert
and they're still going strong.
Angela: I wouldn't
be able to walk
this far without these shoes.
Narrator: In south africa, a
chance discovery gave ryan
just the raw material
his feet needed.
Ryan: I see a animal hide.
Around day five, I stumbled
across this hide I found.
It was big, it was
in great shape.
Oh, yeah.
I knew right then and
there that that's a jackpot.
It may look bad,
probably smells a little
bad, but that's a resource
I ain't gonna pass up.
The hide, luckily, has
already been picked clean,
so I don't have to
do any scraping.
All I had to do is
just soak in the water
and then it was very
pliable, much easier to use,
and I could shape it to
the contour of my foot.
Let's hope it works.
It's a lot of
effort if it don't.
I cut two really big pieces.
Then all I had to do
is just make the laces,
which I made them
out of baobab cordage.
That's a shoestring.
Now what I need
is a leather punch.
So let me run to
the store real fast.
There it is.
That's when the bone
come in handy that I found.
All I did was sharpen it up,
punched a hole to
sew up the leather.
Boom, piece of cake, baby.
That's nice. Now we'll
go fire to harden these.
I would harden
the bottom of them
by stepping on hot coals.
Once you put the
leather on the heat,
what it does is
constrict and it hardens
and it makes for a really,
really good pair of shoes.
What this is doing is just
taking the moisture out
and it fit my feet.
I could feel them right
now just shrinking up,
just fitting my
feet like a glove.
Oh, yeah. Bring
it [bleep] thorns.
It opened up a whole
new set of doors
as far as being able to travel
out there, trek through thorns,
and briars with no problems.
So much easier traveling
with good shoes. So nice.
♪
Nike can kiss my ass.
Narrator: The risk of exposure
extends well beyond
the survivalists' feet...
The sun is killing me.
Narrator: ...As
extreme sunburn...
Woman: I've never
had a sunburn this bad.
Narrator: ...And ravenous bugs
wreak havoc on the naked body.
Woman: What are those
horse flies after? My life?
Narrator: Making
natural remedies
and creative
concoctions a necessity.
The noni leaves are working.
My swelling in my foot's going
down. It's pretty awesome.
There is a tree. It's
the gumbo limbo tree.
It's for your sunburn.
It might hurt a little bit.
Oh.
Right now,
making a little
warthog fat lotion.
You just take some
fat and you can heat it
on a stick with that
elephant dung --
Yeah.
...And you can make some
good lotion for yourself.
I have been so
dry since day one,
and this is just amazing.
It just -- my skin
is just sucking it up
and it feels so good.
Right now, I'm
looking for a specific
root that helps with
skin inflammation
and acts as an antiseptic.
God, my legs were on fire.
Only problem with this is
that it turns your skin purple,
so we're gonna look
like smurfs tomorrow.
♪
Narrator: In panama,
desperation and ingenuity
combined to create
a very memorable,
primitive bug repellent.
I'm getting eaten alive by bugs.
They're, like, worse than
they have ever been, I swear.
One of my biggest
challenges being out there
were the chitras.
Ugh, these chitras are
driving me nuts today.
A little, you know, sand bugs.
They are very painful,
they're relentless.
Ugh, stop.
Oh, man, nature is a bitch.
I would put a lot of mud on
me. I would put ash in water.
That would help with keeping
the bugs away from me.
But there was one night I
didn't have time to go down
to the water to get
ready for the bugs.
I went ahead and did something
a little out of the ordinary.
I'm standing there
and I'm catching my pee
and I'm putting it on me.
And then I grab ash and I
use ash to keep it on my body.
Narrator: In addition to
serving as a liquid binding agent,
urine also contains
high levels of sodium,
which helps repel bugs.
I peed on myself
and I used the liquid
with the soot of the fire
and rubbed it all over me.
I have pee on my face.
[ sighs ]
narrator: Coming up...
It'll definitely work.
Time to go.
Hakim: We use this ingenuity
to adapt and overcome.
This is sailing.
We're sailing for real.
It was this great
sense of pride,
this great sense
of accomplishment.
There's a freaking reef
shark over here on my left.
- Holy [bleep].
- Oh.
♪
In survival, they say
the number one thing
is to build your shelter.
Well, clothing is your
number one shelter.
Yes.
And you know, I'm not a nudist.
I present to you, myself.
♪
Feel like a man now.
Check me out.
Whoo-hoo!
I cut a piece of
the bug net off.
I'm trying to keep the
bugs out of my goods.
[ bell dings ]
if I could not see darrin naked
for the remainder
of the challenge,
that would be great.
[ music slows ]
what you think about
bra straps right here?
Oh, yeah. That's even
cleavage enhancing.
I had a really
bitching devo-style hat
that was actually a fish trap.
♪
We could save the skin,
make you a penis cover with it.
We could.
I don't know if that'll fit.
Oh, ah, no judging here, okay?
[ laughs ]
oh, my god. It's kind of far.
Yeah.
Looks like we have to dodge
some tons of crocodiles right there.
Narrator: As the challenge
comes to an end...
I think that's our next
push is building that raft.
Narrator: ...Oftentimes the
biggest creations are needed
to make it to the finish line.
Man: Now we've got the
flooring starting to go in.
Put some chairs on there.
That's some good
primitive work right here.
Tide's gonna be coming in.
So I'm gonna be battling
tide the whole time.
Woman: We can't
just go kicking our way
into shark infested waters.
- Donesky.
- Nice.
My extraction almost failed
if I hadn't thought ahead
to make a flotation device
to get me off the island.
It'll definitely work.
Time to go.
There we go.
I'll suck it up and go for it.
[bleep] [ speaks indistinctly ]
there is a freaking reef
shark over here on my left.
He got behind us.
Narrator: And when
you arrive by sea,
the only way to leave is by sea.
Look, the beach, there.
♪
- I'm exhausted.
- Yeah.
Let's just get it to the
closest piece of sand.
After we used the raft
to paddle to the island,
I thought perhaps we
would be able to use it
to leave on extraction day.
We're getting
extracted from that point.
It's about seven miles, I think.
But by the end of the challenge,
the life raft was nothing
more than a pile of junk.
That's a big tear.
And extraction was not
something I was ready
to do just by swimming.
It was a multi-leg journey
between two islands
with stingrays and
sharks in the water,
as well as the current
and the exposure.
Swimming was not an option.
There was no
way that the life raft
was gonna be useful
in any way as a boat.
However, it had a
lot of really good parts
I could use to make
something different.
I mean, surely
it'll leak a little bit.
But it might hold long
enough. Worth a try.
Sarah: There were bladders,
both of which had been
popped and needed to be tied.
There was some paracord,
there were some straps.
Every element of the life raft
was useful in its construction.
I based the design on the
hawaiian outrigger canoe.
It's basically a long
canoe that has an arm on it
that helps to aid in flotation
and keep it from capsizing.
[ blowing air ]
I use the inner
tubes for flotation,
wood from the beach
for infrastructure,
strapping from the raft
in order to tie it together,
and there was also
the bottom lining.
I figured could be
used to make a sail.
And I had crafted a mast out
of a branch that I had found.
We can lower it like this
and catch the wind this way.
We're gonna wind surf
out of this thing, huh?
Yeah.
Ben did not believe that
a sail was going to work.
And I just wanted
to prove him wrong.
Well...
There, what do you think?
- It's [bleep] tight.
- So I'm gonna be sitting here.
- Yep.
And I'll be sitting
right back there.
♪
Are you ready
to grab onto the...
Yeah.
This is sailing.
We're sailing for real.
Good work. Nailed it.
I was so proud to
have pulled it together
and made something that
actually worked out there.
Do you want to go in
between the islands?
Yeah.
Sarah: We were cruising
out of there like champions.
Ha ha.
And I don't think that
I could have done it
without my ingenuity.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
We did it. We did it.
Adios, exuma!
Every stroke burns.
Dig in deep, ej, I
know you're on empty.
It was this great
sense of pride,
this great sense
of accomplishment.
- There is a boil.
- [ exhales ]
that we use this ingenuity
to adapt and overcome,
to really win out at the end.
Every environment's different.
You never know what
you're gonna run into.
Cordage is breaking.
So creativity is essential.
That's it. We're able
to start hunting now.
In a survival situation,
I've always felt that
brains versus brawn
will win nine out of 10 times.
We did it. I'm so proud of you.
Improvise, adapt, and overcome.
- Ah! Yeah!
- Whoo!
We [bleep] did it!
That's survival.
- Yeah!
Bye, amazon, thank you!