[Music]
- Good morning and welcome to the new school year,
Bueller high school students.
Whoa, Bueller reds!
This is going to be the best school year yet.
[Music]
Today's quote of the day comes from
sophomore Scott Pruitt.
"The difference between a stumbling block
and a stepping stone
is how high you raise your foot."
Thank you, Scott.
And because we've used your quote,
you will receive a voucher for one free lunch
to be used in our school cafeteria.
All incoming freshmen will be happy to know
that the year-long hazing tradition
has been shortened
due to the dramatic number of students
who transferred last year.
Cheerleading tryouts will be
after school at five
and this year are co-ed
become a cheerleader.
Our football team also needs your support.
Speaking of support,
today's special person of the day
is our star quarterback Connor Tucker.
As you know, Connor led our football team
to victory many times last year,
but unfortunately he broke his leg
in our state championship game win over Rydel High.
On doctor's orders,
Connor will be sidelined
for the whole season this year
and as a result he'll be spending
his senior year
just like the rest of us,
watching from the sidelines.
it's going to be a tough year for
Buehler High School's favorite.
Connor, we want you to know
that we stand behind you.
[Music]
- Mr. Sansberry,
you are partnerless no longer.
- Hi, Berty
- Hi.
- What's up?
- Today...
When baking a cake,
your most important tool is...
- The temperature of the oven?
- Wrong
The whisk
- What are you doing here?
- I want to learn how to cook
Yeah!
- Right.
The school'star quarterback suddenly
has a burning desire to
be the next Gordon Ramsay.
This class is for girls.
Are you sure this isn't just
some screwed up way
to pick up girls?
- Hey, come on.
Do I look like I need help
picking up girls?
Besides, if this class is just for girls, then
why are you here?
- I...
I want to be a chef
- Well chef,
I think you should reconsider
some of those sexist attitudes you have
towards who should be in the kitchen then.
Here, help me out, will you?
- Okay, once.
Just this once.
- Yeah, sure.
No any time now, really.
- There.
- How do I look?
- Okay class,
today we're also going to learn
how to bake chocolate chip cookies.
- How you feel?
- Okay.
- So, why are you really taking cooking?
- Hmmm....
You see, I broke my leg...
- Yeah.
- So, now I can't play football
It's pretty easy A.
- It's not going to be an easy A.
If you wanted an easy A,
you should have gone off for choir.
- Oh yeah. I...
I had a really good reason for
not doing that
- And what was that?
- Can't sing.
- Okay
- Hey, Jayden!
- Hey Samantha, come here.
- Trinity, her name is...
Hi Trinity
- Hi Connor
- Okay
- You know...
it's rude not to know people's names.
- Noted.
- There she is... My baby.
- Yeah... Yeah I know that car.
Everyone knows that car.
Prime parking spot too.
- Yeah.
And it's noticeable.
Bueller red
- Go bears!
- Oh yeah
- Hey, you lost that game.
- Yeah, I broke my leg.
- You still lost.
- Don't be a dick.
- So, how many girls have carried these bucks?
- Hundreds.
- Wow!
- Yeah.
- So, you need a ride?
- Yeah. you're gonna drive me with
a busted leg and
this thing?
- This thing? Yeah.
You know this baby has four...
- Yeah,  411 hp,
6.2 liter v8...
uh... hill descent control system,
automatic locking rear differentials and
an upgraded three-link suspension
with bottle shocks.
Did I miss anything?
I mean... uh besides it being
bad for the environment.
- Yeah, smart ass!
It also has an integrated rear view camera system
- Ah....
- Got me
- So you know about cars,
where does that come from?
- Brothers,
five of them.
- So you need a ride or...?
- No thanks. I got choir practice.
- Cool. See you tomorrow.
Yeah
- Not if I see you first.
- Shit!
♫ Aaahhh aaahhhh ♫
- Hi, Connor.
- Hey, Kara.
- Can we help you, Mr. Tucker?
- Not really.
Mr. Sansbury over there can.
Are you sure you know what you're doing?
- Okay. Try it again.
- Hey, thanks man.
- You're welcome, man.
- So, what's your deal?
- My deal?
- Yeah, I mean like are...
are you gay?
- Why? Because I'm in the choir?
- Nah man, I'm just asking
- Is that what people around school are saying?
- I've heard it.
So... are you?
- Very much.
Does that bother you?
No, no!
Hmm... I mean
Live and let live, I say. Right?
- You know, you're the first person to ask me.
- Really?
Do you have a boyfriend?
- Nope.
Not yet.
- So, how do you know you're gay?
- You just do.
Do you need a girlfriend to know you're straight?
Bingo!
- Fair enough.
So do you need a ride?
- Are you sure that's what you want to ask me?
- Yeah, man.
- Okay, dude.
- Do you want to watch a movie tomorrow night?
- I'm moving
On a saturday night?
- Yeah.
- It looks like a date... Ah, ah
- No. It's two guys going to watch a movie.
I'm asking you to hang out with me
and watch a movie tomorrow night.
- Hmm, hmmm...
You're asking me on a date
on saturday... night.
- Dude, I'm asking you to a movie.
Do you want to go or not?
- Do i want to see a movie with you?
I...
On a saturday night...
oohhh... let me think about it
- Okay, you don't have to if you don't want to.
- Uh, give me a minute.
I'm thinking about it
Oh...ah
aahhh... ohhh...
I'm thinking, uh okay...
I guess...
Sure, why not?
- You sure?
- Yes
- Okay
Cool. So i'll pick you up around eight.
- Seven.
- Eight
If you pick me up at eight
the movies will have started.
Most movies start around seven
- Who told you that?
- No one had to tell me,
that's just the way it is.
- Geez, you're worse than a girl
Just give me your address
- Give me your arm
- What?
- Give me your arm.
[Music]
- So, you won't lose it.
- It's not a date
- Yes, it is.
- No, it's not.
[Music]
- Yeah, okay. I'll see you at seven.
- Eight.
- Seven.
[Music]
- You are paying again?
- You have money?
- Hi
- Can i help you?
- Yeah. Hmm... Cameron?
- Oh, yeah, it's Cameron
- Okay, uh well...
Can we get two tickets to "Anderson's cross" please?
- Oh man ,that movie started a half hour ago.
- Of course it did.
- The next showing's at 9.20.
- Hm... do you want to watch anything else?
- "The perfect night"
- "The perfect night"?
- Already started...
- "Hostage diner" ?
- "Hostage diner" started at 7.45.
I'm sorry. For future reference most movies
start around seven.
Also for future reference, all our movie times are posted
on the internet.
- Good day.
- I'm sorry?
- I said good day.
- Thank you.
- Hassles!
- Are you cold?
- A little
- There we go
- Thank you
So what are you gonna do if you can't play football?
- Hmmm...
Probably do what I voice
I was gonna do.
Go study and become a lawyer.
- Really?
- No, I'm just messing with you.
No, I don't know what I'm going to do
but football is all I've ever known.
It's kind of cliche, heh?
- Yeah... but...
you're selling yourself short.
I think you could be a lot of things
- Hmm...
all right, okay.
All right mr. I know it all
what, what could I be?
- A real estate agent
- Come on... boring.
- Fine
Hmm... a politician?
- Oh... I...
I have these uh tapes
that I took a couple months ago... cheerleading...
- Can I see it?
- Let's say you have to talk to the  cheerleading squad.
- Say no more.
- Yeah, exactly.
Well, could I become a chef?
- I don't think so
Yeah I know, I saw that cake you baked
in miss Hannigan's class.
- Yeah okay.
- I think you can say easy goodbye
- What could I... Can I be a teacher?
- Maybe.
- A science teacher?
- No. I was thinking more gym.
- Yeah.
A gym...
Well, I mean... can I be a police officer...
- No... too skinny.
- Can I be your friend?
- I have to think about that one
- Could I, hmm...
be your boyfriend?
- What are you doing?
- I...
I'm... kissing you
That was my first guy kiss
- Mine too.
- How... how was it?
- I think... we should...
I think we should practice a lot more
- Yeah.
[Music]
- You can spy the book
- What? What book?
- Romeo and Juliet. It's a quote.
- Oh!
[Music]
- What?
- I... I'm thinking
all the people's reactions when they see us
at prom together.
[Music]
- So, this isn't
a one-time thing?
You know like the straight guys try it out?
Just...
It means nothing
- It's that what you want?
[Music]
- No
- Me neither
[music]
- So, what do you want?
[Music]
- I want you
- Hey
- I want you too
♫ Everyone has something to say ♫
♫ but all that noise can get in the way ♫
♫ the world will tell you what you need to be ♫
♫ but your eyes will show you what they kept might see ♫
♫ and if we were the only ones left in the all world ♫
♫ I would want forever be with you ♫
♫ but you already knew ♫
♫ If we were the only ones left
in the whole wide world ♫
♫ I would want forever be with you ♫
♫ My only ♫
♫ Falling in love is such a time ♫
♫ take me away I'll do the time ♫
♫ Though I'm not yet the man I wish to be ♫
♫ I know that you can see the best in me ♫
♫ If we were the only ones left
in the whole wide world ♫
♫ I would want forever to be with you ♫
♫ but you already knew ♫
♫ If we were the only ones left
in the whole wide world ♫
♫ would you want forever to be with me ♫
♫ My only ♫
♫ I've been thinking,
I'm losing my mind ♫
♫ when you told me that your heart
was feeling grey ♫
♫ I just couldn't stand to see you walk away ♫
- So, this break is a break up.
[Music]
♫ If we were the only ones left
in the whole wide world ♫
♫ I would want forever to be with you ♫
♫ but you already knew ♫
♫ If we were the only ones left
in the whole wide world ♫
♫ would you want forever to be with me ♫
♫ My only ♫
♫ If we were the only ones left
in the whole wide world ♫
♫ would you want forever to be with me ♫
♫ My only ♫
- Hello handsome
- Stop
- That's it.
Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Shall we?
- Play it again, boys
- First prom starts at seven
Dude, did she actually say she was coming?
Did she give you a definitive yes?
- I don't know, I don't remember.
- Maybe she's lost
Maybe she lost your phone
- Maybe she wasn't coming in the first place?
[Music]
- So, okay.
- I listen
- Tell the story. Okay. So, so...
So I walk in the class and I'm like cool
There's another guy in class
- Hmm, hmm...
- Uhm... I was like
Oh my god!
He's so hot,yeah.
- Yeah
And then, then we baked a cake
and then he carried my books
and then he fixed my car
- And then...
he asked me out on a date.
- Oh... to a movie
- On a saturday night
- To a movie.
- On a saturday night.
- Then we missed the movie.
- Mh, mhh
We missed three movies because
you didn't listen to me
- And I, and I'll listen to you again.
Okay, now I know that they start at seven
I... yes that start at seven
- At seven
- Right...
And then...
then we kissed... and...
we kissed again and again
and then
he asked me out to prom,
eight months earlier.
- What can I say?
And in the meantime
we fell in love
-We fell in love.
[Music till the end]