- Get in here
captain coke dealer,
you're gonna give us both up.
- Sorry, man.
Just wanted to make sure
you weren't some kind
of cop or something.
- Do I look like a cop?
- It's all good,
what you need man?
- I need the hardest
stuff you got.
- You do, huh?
Let me see some money.
- I just saw you sling a
whole bag to that crackhead.
Now show me what you got.
- How much you want?
- All of it.
- That's all I got man,
better have the money.
- So concerned with the
money, I got your money.
So here's the deal.
We can do this the easy
way or the hard way,
you can either go down
for possession and intent,
or you could write down the name
of your supplier right here
and I'm gonna go after the
bigger fish, your choice.
You got three
seconds, three, two.
Have a nice jog loser.
I'm gonna ask you one more time.
What did you do with it Shannon?
- Didn't do nothing.
- You're lying to me,
you are lying to me.
I had four bags of that stuff.
What did the drug fairy fly
in here and take off with it.
- You probably used
it all yourself.
- Your pupils are
as big as quarters.
How much did you use?
How much, I was gonna sell
that to pay bills Shannon.
You have no idea what
I had to go through
to get that, I could
have been shot.
You want me dead Shannon?
You want me dead,
you want me dead?
You call the cops,
I'm gonna kill you.
- Don't you take my car.
- What happened
to your neck, bro?
- What do you think
happened to my neck?
Shannon stole my stuff again.
- What?
- Yeah.
- That's just wrong.
- Yep.
- Did you call the cops?
- No.
- And so what's the description
of that stolen vehicle again?
- I think she did though.
Yep.
Hold on.
- They bow him out with two.
- Clear.
- Come on, man, get up.
- On your knees now.
Now, get down.
Get down onto your knees,
hands on your head.
- Sorry man.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Excuse me, ma'am,
do you mind if I use your
phone just for a minute?
Oh no, it's okay.
I just wreck my car, I just.
- I don't think so.
- Dude, I need you
to come pick me up
at your grandma's
house right now.
- What,
what are you doing
at my grandma's house?
Is she home?
- No, she's not home.
Look, I had a ditch Shannon's
car, Harley got arrested.
The cops are everywhere.
I need you to come
pick me up right now.
Thanks for getting me, man.
- Yeah, man, no worries.
Are you you sure it's safe
to come back here so soon?
- Oh yeah, the lights are out.
So she's either in
bed or she's split.
Actually, I hope she's gone.
She uses too much
of my stash anyway.
- Yeah, you don't want that.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- All right man.
- Later, stay safe.
- Yep.
- Morning sunshine.
- You see what you
get for hitting me.
You see what you get.
You stole my car and got it
impounded, big man now, huh?
- Get him in the car.
- He's got weed
in the house too.
- Mr. Highberger,
you're back again.
- He's racking up the
frequent flyer miles.
- Put him in D2.
- You do know the rules, right?
You resist to hand
you a whooping.
- I know my rule, never
go without a fight.
I gave as good as I got.
- Yeah, maybe,
but I don't see them
sitting on this bench
with a fancy bracelet on,
but I will give
you credit though.
It took about four of them
to drag you up in here.
- It's not even my
best number, man, six.
- Six, impressive.
- I was younger.
- Yeah, weren't we
all the first time in.
- I was 16 I think.
- That looks like our boy.
- Battery to a police officer,
resisting arrest, disorderly
conduct, minor in possession.
Possession of a
controlled substance.
Possession of drug
paraphernalia.
- Oh, why can't kids
go to the bowling alley
to actually bowl?
- It looks like
the owner was cited
for serving alcohol to a minor.
- Good, any other churches
for our esteemed client?
- That's not enough
for you counselor.
I've got his entire
criminal history right here
if you have a few hours, first
brush with the law was at 12,
stole his mom's car and burnt
up the engine and a pursuit.
- Be a public defender they
said, it'll be fun they said.
- That's the same thing
they said to social workers.
So his risk assessment
is way above 12.
So he'll be staying in the
padded cell until his hearing.
They say he is an
irrefutable danger
to himself and to others.
- Don't suppose it
will do any good
to request the judge
remand him to mom
and dad in the interim?
- Don't want him,
mom and stepdad say
he's too much to handle.
And he says he doesn't wanna
be bothered with them either.
So that's why I'm here.
- What about bio dad.
- Florida, not much contact.
- Okay, let's have
them bring him in.
- I ain't got nothing to say.
- Relax kid, we're on your side.
- You my lawyer?
- Kyle Devidy, court
appointed counsel,
looks like you've
had a busy night,
drinking, drugging, fighting.
You're off to a
flying start kid.
- We're here to help you Scott.
- Nobody can help me.
- Well, we can
try if you let us.
- I think the judge
will reduce the felony
to a misdemeanor if we.
- Just plead guilty
and send me to jail.
- You want to go to jail?
- Beats going home.
From that day on,
I never backed down from a fight
and I never pled not guilty.
I was always like to the police
and the courts and
just whoever, bring it.
You're not gonna break me.
- Winning, right?
- I guess so.
- And like I said before,
yet you are the one
sitting on this bench
with a fancy bracelet.
And those guys you just showed
are heading home to a good meal
and night sleep
in their own bed.
Well, I'm just making a pit
stop on my way to the pen
and by the looks of things,
you're not too far behind,
I'll save you a bunk kid.
- You want to
plead guilty Scott?
- Might as well, if I get out,
they're just gonna
find another reason
to stick me back in here.
- Pleading guilty can have
very serious ramifications,
with your criminal
history, the judge will.
- Just plead guilty and let
me worry about the rest.
It's my life, okay.
Nobody runs it but me.
- All right, I'll
enter a guilty plea.
I hope you know
what you're in for.
- I've known my whole
life what I'm in for.
- We had a special
request for you.
- Will be at eight yourselves.
- D block
visitation will be between one.
- You also brought me
out of a horrible ditch,
out of the clay
and set my feet upon a rock
and establish my steps.
Psalm 40, verse two.
- Amen.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Where you get stuck
in some quick sand,
guy's gonna pull you out?
- That's exactly what
it means to my brother.
See, every one of us
are behind these bars
because we fell into
some kind of quick sand.
- Yeah.
- Maybe not the real kind,
but the spiritual kind.
And the really sad thing
is, most of the time,
this quick sand
we made ourselves,
you like using your fist to lie.
- Why, you wanna go?
- I used to be a fighter
too, just mad at the world,
blaming it for all my problems.
It turned out the person I was
really fighting was myself.
Took me a long time to
go from this, to this.
- But once I did, it
made all the difference.
Why don't you come
with us tonight?
I mean, what have
you got to lose?
I should asked what have
you got left to lose?
- Glad to see
everybody here tonight.
Jones, good to see you,
glad that everybody's here.
Steve, I'm glad you're
able to make it out.
And it's great to see
everybody here tonight.
Looking forward to a
great time, Bible study.
It's always a blessing
to see everybody.
And I hope that you've
got your Bibles with you.
Take just a moment.
- Hello Scott.
- Oh, hey warden.
- Glad to see you finally
here, have a seat.
Yeah, come on.
- Something a
little differently.
Does everybody
know what this is?
Yeah, sure, we all do.
It's a yo-yo, its sole
purpose is to go up
and down and back and forth.
Unfortunately it's
like many of us,
we've been in and out
of jail, back and forth
so many times that
just makes you sick.
Just get so tired of it.
But yet we find ourselves
doing the same thing
over and over, my friends, it
doesn't have to be that way.
We don't have to stay
in this orange jumpsuit.
God has given us his grace,
he's given us his love.
He's given us his son
and through his son,
we can transcend these bars,
we can overcome the chains.
We can be free
through Jesus Christ.
The Bible says he that
hath the son hath life
and he that hath not
the son, hath not life.
The Bible says that
the thief cometh,
but for to still and
to kill and to destroy.
But Jesus said, I am come
that you might have life
and have it more abundantly.
Romans 8:2 says that for the
law of the spirit of life
is found in Jesus Christ.
And it overcomes the law of sin.
My brothers with Jesus,
you can break these bars.
You can transcend these chains.
Are you sick and tired
of being like a yo-yo,
being pulled back and forth?
You can overcome, you
can cut this string.
If you want freedom,
true freedom that these
bars cannot contain,
then I invite you tonight
to come to know the one
who can set you free.
Jesus said that I am the
way, the truth in the life.
And no man comes to the
father but through me,
every one of us is guilty
of sin and we deserve to pay
the price for sin.
But Jesus has paid the price.
All you have to do is believe.
All you have to do is
accept it, stop fighting,
stop resisting in
just surrender.
- And the Lord is my
light and my salvation,
whom shall I fear?
The Lord is the
stronghold of my life,
of whom shall I be afraid?
When evil do me, uttering
slanders against me.
My adversaries and, they
shall stumble and fall.
- Our father who art in
heaven, hallowed be thy name,
thy kingdom come, thy will be
down on earth as is in heaven.
Give us each day our daily bread
and forgive us our trespasses.
We figured those
trespass against us,
lead us is not in a temptation
but deliver us from for thy.
- What, you got a problem, what?
- Grace and power,
give you all the pain,
all the fear, all the
anxiety paralyzing me,
please free my mind and my body.
I'm gonna be what
I was meant to be.
Amen.
- Well done.
- Hello Scott, how you doing?
- Doing good, Mr. Pazera
- Have a seat please.
Well, your street
clothes still fit.
- Little snug, but
anything's better
than prison orange, sir.
- Yeah, I bet.
So you ready for the real world?
- Ready as I'll
ever be, I guess.
- You know, we want
you to understand
that we consider you one
of our success stories.
I mean you've
cleaned up real well.
Even earned your
associate's degree.
- Yes sir, business.
I'm gonna go to college
and get my bachelor's
and maybe run my own
company one day, who knows?
- No reason in the world why
you can't, really proud of you.
You understand that don't you?
- Thank you, Mr Pazera, that
really means a lot.
- Well, I would say don't
be as stranger, but.
- I hope I never
see you again, sir.
And I mean that in a good way.
- Yeah.
Look, you take care,
but don't forget, in all
your ways acknowledge him
and he'll make
your path straight.
Proverbs.
- Three, six, yes sir.
- Thank you for everything, sir.
- You're welcome.
Now get outta here.
- Yes, sir.
♪ Every page before
was a man defeated ♪
♪ Every page before was
a life off the tracks ♪
a record of failure ♪
♪ I was on my knees
and you heard my plea ♪
- Scott, this is looking
pretty good, man.
Welcome aboard.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Thank you very much.
- Happy to have you here.
- I'm gonna go get this out.
- Look, look, I know the
numbers are a little down.
They're gonna come back up,
there's no reason to panic.
No, no you don't tell me to
listen, I tell you to listen.
Everything is fine, just
stop worrying Dwight.
- I am worrying Scott,
you're late every day.
Your numbers are down.
You look horrible.
I mean, dare I ask you
to take a drug test?
- Me?
Why don't you ask everybody
down on the third floor, Dwight.
There's more snowfall around
down there than in Colorado.
- Look, Scott.
- Don't look me Dwight.
I have made you a ton
of money and all I ask
is that you just back off.
- Not everything's about money.
It's about professionalism.
So far, I haven't seen any.
- How's that for
professionalism, Dwight.
- Hey man, I got a
surprise for you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah man.
- Check the glove box.
- You got something for me?
- Yeah, got a little
something, something.
- Nice, thanks man.
- Of course, man.
So what happened to the BMW?
- Company car.
- Oh, is it getting fixed?
- Not exactly.
You can't drive a company car
if you no longer
work for the company.
- What, you quit?
- Terminated.
- Dude, what happened?
- Poor work habits,
poor attitude Scott.
Plus I didn't fill
up the lemonade cup.
- Lemonade?
Oh, well yeah, gotcha.
- You got a dollar bill?
- Dude, it is a
sad day my friend,
when I have more money than you.
- Tell me about it.
- So does Tracy
know you got canned?
- No, not yet.
She's not gonna be too
happy about it either.
Man, let's just go get wasted.
I wanna forget about all
this stuff right now.
- Yeah, dude, dude,
done, say no more.
If a party is what you need,
then a party you shall receive.
- Yo man.
We are all out of booze, are
you sober enough to make a run?
- I don't know, where's Sam?
- Passed out in the bathtub.
You buy, I'll fly.
- Should do it.
Thanks.
- 307 Dispatch.
I've got Scott Highberger
passed out at Larry's Liquors.
Let me a few more units please.
- 104307, do
they need to bump it up?
- He's passed out right now,
but if I know Highberger,
it'll end up in a fight.
Scott, Highberger
again, let's go fellas.
Rise and shine sleeping beauty.
Come on Scott, let|s go.
- I'm good.
Listen to me, you
guys, listen to me.
You guys do do me
every single time.
You ain't got
nothing on me, man.
You ain't got nothing
on me, all right?
You ain't got nothing on me man.
You ain't get nothing.
Ain't get nothing on me.
Leave me alone,
man, come on man.
- Get him in the car.
- What's up punk?
- Excuse me, fellas.
- Highberger, visitor.
- Hey mom.
- Hey honey.
You've cleaned up,
gained a few pounds.
- Three square meals a day
and all the time in
the world exercise.
- Well you look good.
- Thanks.
- Come on mom, spill it.
- Spill what?
- You came here alone,
what's going on?
- There's no easy
way to say this,
I went to the doctor last week.
They ran some tests.
One came back positive,
I have cancer.
- Cancer?
- The doctors believe
they can treat it.
So I don't want you
to worry about it.
I just came here in
person to tell you myself
so you wouldn't have to
hear it from anybody else.
- You're gonna be
okay though, right?
- I don't want you to
have to worry about this.
The important thing is you.
I want you to get clean,
I want you to be somebody.
- I will mom.
- Promise me, Scott, promise
me you're gonna stay clean.
- I promise.
- I love you.
- I love you mom.
♪ For another chance ♪
♪ Just one more chance ♪
♪ Don't give up on me ♪
♪ I promise I'll try ♪
Accept any judgment,
limitations deposed by me
or anyone else, I no
longer alow myself.
Give the strength
to love myself.
♪ Don't give up on me ♪
- Scott, come on
in, take a seat.
So I got a new one for you.
16 year old kid looks
at his dad says, dad,
can I borrow the car?
Dad looks at his
son, says, no son,
not until you cut your hair.
Son looks at his dad says, dad,
you realize that
Jesus had long hair.
The dad looks at his son
and says, you're right son.
And he also walked
everywhere he went.
- That's a good one, sir.
- Yeah right.
You know, you're the only
one that laughs at my jokes.
But thank you.
- What's this?
- Open it up.
- What happened
to that kid Scott?
He was doing so well.
- I don't know, I guess
he just lost his mind.
- When he had to go back to
prison to find it again, really?
You get outta here real soon.
What's gonna change after you
leave these bars behind you?
You just gonna throw away
everything you've
accomplished here,
just leave it at the front gate.
- No sir.
I'm gonna do better.
- Yeah, that's what
you said last time.
- But I mean it this
time, I mean it this time.
- Yeah, well I hope that's true.
I really do, speaking
as your warden,
I really hope you stick to
the straight and narrow.
Is it okay if I talk to
you as a brother in Christ?
- Of course.
- You know when you left here,
you turned your
back on the only one
who would never turn
his back on you,
created this void in your life.
Tried to fill it with drugs,
alcohol, Lord knows what else,
I've seen you working out
around the gym, right?
And what happens when
you exercise a muscle?
- Get stronger.
- Exactly, don't you
ever forget that?
So you exercise your
faith, guess what?
It gets stronger, but say
you choose to exercise sin,
it gets bigger and bigger
until it consumes you.
- A man cannot serve two masters
for you either love
one and hate the other.
- Yeah, Matthew 6:24.
Yeah, you can say that
all you want up here,
but you gotta get it here son.
Can I pray with you?
Heavenly father, I
pray over this man.
Your son, your servant,
Scott Highberger.
- Hello, Hello, dude,
you're supposed to pick
him up, did you forget?
I'm gonna be late for work.
- Hi buddy.
- I'm working
really late tonight.
I'll be back very
early tomorrow morning.
All of his stuff
is in here, okay?
- Okay.
- Can you clean up around here?
It's disgusting.
- We're just gonna be
chilling, it's fine.
- I love you baby, okay.
Be good for your daddy.
Come on man, like, bye.
- No man, he's
still not back yet.
I don't know.
He was supposed to just go
pick up a little something,
should have been back
like two hours ago.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, yeah, I can do that.
All right.
All right, I'll be right there.
Right, bye.
I forgot about you little man.
Yeah.
Hey, hey man, come here buddy.
Wanna go get a little
food or something.
Gonna go for a little ride.
Oh buddy, buddy, buddy, buddy.
- Where have you been?
What are you talking about?
He needed.
- I don't wanna here it, okay.
- He needed food, you
know I needed food.
- Oh my God.
You two are the most
worthless men I have ever met.
- Come on, would you do this
if you had your own
kids, seriously?
- I don't have kids.
- Hello.
- Scott, what's the matter?
- I'm a terrible person, mom.
- No, you're not,
what's wrong honey?
- I took a little kid
on a drug run with me.
- A kid, what kid, what
are you talking about?
- I'm gonna make the
world a better place Mom.
It's gonna be better
without me and it mom.
- Scott.
- Just wanna apologize.
All the stuff I've done
to you, love you, man.
- Scott, where are you?
Talk to me.
- Open the door Scott, your
mother called every hotel.
We know you're in
there, open up.
Oh man, step back.
Dispatch, give me a
squad at this location.
Scott.
He's still alive.
Have that squad step it up.
Relax, relax, I'm
here to help you.
- Please help me God,
I can't do this alone.
- Hieberger, let's go.
- Which cell block are we going
- Nope, you're outta here.
- What, they cut you
loose, just like that?
- Yeah, just like that.
No criminal charges, even
paid for my stitches.
- Got love the criminal
justice system, man.
They give you three hots
in a cot, free education
and free healthcare.
So you break the law
and reap the rewards.
- Yeah, I gotta try
to stay free and clear
this time though, man,
I really dodged the
bullet with this one.
- I don't know, sounds like
it's a reason to celebrate.
Let's go party.
- No, I just wanna get home.
- Dude, you ain't got no home.
- I guess we're
going to Harley's.
- Let's go to Harley's.
- Look who we got here, my man.
- Glad to see you're
doing okay man.
- What's up man?
- Yeah, I'm doing okay, man.
Had some tough times,
things are turning around.
- Well I'm sure we got something
here to lift your spirits.
- I'm sure you do man.
- It seems like you're
pretty taken care of.
I think I'm gonna get myself
a little something,
something too, yeah.
- Okay, see you a few.
I'll catch you.
- Yeah, all right.
How's Sam been doing?
- He's been doing right I
guess, just hitting it hard.
- Hello Scott, long time no see.
- How you doing Layla?
- Lonely.
- Okay.
- Take it easy girl, my
man just got outta prison.
Give us a few minutes, yeah.
- I'll catch you later.
- Sure you will Layla.
- Anyways, I wanna pick that
business degree brain of yours.
- All right, what
you got in mind?
- Wait seriously,
you could do that?
- Absolutely man.
All we gotta do is sit
you with an LLC, right?
It'll look like a totally
legitimate company.
And then you could funnel
whatever money through it
that you want to.
- Alright then, sounds
perfect, let's do it.
- All right, done.
Look at Jr, over there,
he bit it hard, hasn't he?
Hey Sam, you doing all right?
Sam, Sam, Sam.
- Hello.
- Dad?
- How are you son?
- Not good.
- No?
- No, I was wondering,
I think I could come
down and see you dad?
- Are you clean?
- Just gotta get outta
here for a while Dad.
This place is killing me.
I didn't have
anyone else to call.
- Okay, come down.
But no drinking
and no drugs Scott.
Breakfast is ready.
You okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
Just my stomach's
bothering me a little bit.
- You'll be better after you
get a little food in you,
you wanna butter some bread?
- Sure.
- Three eggs, right?
- Yeah.
- Used to drive
your mother crazy
you and I wanting an odd
number of eggs every morning.
Orange juice?
- No thanks Dad.
- Come on, it's Florida,
you gotta have some OJ.
You sure you're okay?
- Yeah.
I think it's the time change.
- Nice try, Indiana
and this part of Florida's
on the same time zone.
- Oh, I just need to
catch up on my sleep then.
- You've been sleeping
for two days kid.
Anyway, I got some
errands to run today.
I'll pick up a
newspaper and tomorrow
you start looking for a job.
You can stay here until
you get enough money
for an apartment, is that fair?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Thanks dad.
- Yes, what is it?
- I need to cash
that check please.
- Sure, may I see
your ID please?
Indiana?
- Yeah, I'm visiting my dad.
That's his check, he banks here.
You can see we have the
same last name though.
Hey pop.
Get your errands done already.
- You stole from me.
- What, what are
you talking about?
I would never do that.
- You stole from me.
I opened my home to you
and you stole from me.
- Dad, what are
you talking about?
I would never steal from you.
- The bank called,
the manager was suspicious
about a check they cashed.
- I just needed a loan, I
thought you'd be okay with it.
- There's puke all
over the bathroom.
You've been drinking
my mouthwash.
- No, I was just freshening up.
- Just get out.
You haven't changed one bit.
- But dad.
- No buts, just go.
Or I call the cops and you
go to jail for forgery.
- Check this guy out.
- How you doing
over here, you okay?
- Yeah, I'm good, thanks.
- Yo, who are you?
No one.
- Why are you tossing pennies?
- They don't make
anything smaller.
- Are you crazy or something?
- Bullseye.
- Looks like we gotta teach
him a little lesson in respect.
- Wanna teach me about respect?
All right, how about you and me?
One on one.
- You got it.
- Hey man, that's my car.
- What is this?
Ah, you gotta be kidding me.
- Good afternoon, sir.
The reason I stopped you
is you were going 57
and a 30 back there.
Can I see your license please?
- Yeah.
- Does
somebody break and start.
- Indiana,
this your car?
- No, a buddy loaned it to me.
- Okay,
you been drinking?
- I had a beer earlier.
- Alright, sit tight.
- Thank you.
Do a report and
the disturbances.
- Sir, I need you to
step outta the car.
- What for?
- Sir, just step outta the car.
Step around the front please.
- What for?
- You got a suspended license.
- Oh, can you just write
me a ticket or something?
- What happened at
that bar back there?
- Oh, that was just
a misunderstanding.
- County county, do you
wanna be in a foot pursuit?
I'd like to make a collect
call please, Indiana.
Scotty, is that you?
- Yeah man, it's me.
- How you doing?
- Thanks for picking me up, man.
- No problem.
- Hey man, me casa, su casa.
- Thanks bro.
- You need a cold one?
Look like you could
really use it.
- No, I'm okay, thanks.
- Oh, I got it, I got
what you need in the back.
You want some of that, or?
Scott, Scott,
dude, where are you going?
Scotty, where are you going?
Call me when you get
picked back up again.
Dude finally lost his mind.
♪ Every page before
was a man defeated ♪
♪ Every page before was
a life off the tracks ♪
a record of failure ♪
- Beautiful morning, ain't it?
- It's cold.
- Ah, it might be cold on the
outside, but the word of God
keep us warm on the inside,
you know what I'm saying?
- Sure.
Could still use a coat though.
- I got something that'll warm
me up like a warm blanket.
- Nah, I'm good man, thanks.
- Come on man, you
won't regret it.
- I don't really wanna listen
to any music right now.
- Ah, man, this ain't music.
This is the word.
This is the bread of
life that feel you up.
Check this cat out, his
preaching is something else.
Sermon's about Joseph.
You know about Joseph, right?
- Yeah, he had a coat.
- But the
Lord was with Joseph
and showed him mercy
and gave him favor
in the sight of the
keeper of the prison.
Remember, God loves you
and God forgives you.
♪ Every page before
was a man defeated ♪
♪ Every page before was
a life off the tracks ♪
a record of failure ♪
♪ I was on my knees
and you heard my plea ♪
♪ And now I'm pardoned ♪
♪ My slate is wiped clean ♪
♪ Pardoned, the
old me is history ♪
♪ I'm pardoned ♪
♪ Pardoned by grace ♪
- Morning, welcome home.
- Hey man, welcome to over life.
I'm CJ.
- I'm Scott.
Nice to meet you Scott.
Right through the door, sir.
- Thank very much.
- Proverbs 10:5 says, he
who gathers during summer
and takes advantage
of his opportunities
is a son who acts wisely,
but he who sleeps during
harvest and ignores the moment
of opportunity is a son
who acts shamefully.
Jesus is communicating
to his disciples,
the harvest, it's too
big for any of us.
And we need to pray for God
to send more workers
into the field.
The word worker here
in the Greek is,
and it's used 15 times
in the New Testament.
It elevates action
over business.
A worker is a disciple
who is actively
involved in the process
of evangelizing the lost
or establishing the saved.
Let me clarify that a
worker is not someone
on full-time staff at a church.
Once you become a
Christ follower,
you become a
co-labor with Christ.
If a paycheck is what motivates
you to minister to people,
you're doing it for
the wrong reason.
Look at Paul in Acts
28 versus 30 and 31.
It says Paul lived
there for two full years
at his own expense, in
his own rented lodging
and welcomed all
who came to him,
preaching and proclaiming
the kingdom of God
and teaching about
the Lord Jesus Christ
with all openness and boldness,
unhindered and unrestrained.
Amen.
- We work on the ones
that you have to have
committed to your memory,
that's how works.
Anyway, okay.
Hey, very nice to meet you.
Thank you, thank you so much.
Thank you.
Hey, what's up?
I'm Dave.
- Oh, hey, I saw you
preaching up there.
My name is Scott.
- Hi Scott, nice to meet
you, first time here?
- First time, yeah.
Hope it didn't put you to sleep.
Sermon a little long, but.
- No, no it was great.
- Good.
- Great, yeah, well thank you.
All right I'm gonna get going.
- Come back anytime.
- Okay.
- All right.
Hey Scott, crazy question.
Are you looking for work?
- What are you thinking?
- Well we're kind of in
desperate need around here.
Just for clean up,
stacking chairs,
actually mopping floors
believe it or not.
- You know, I actually have a lo
of experience mopping.
- No way, Seriously
- I do.
- um...
Sure, I'll take it, you have
time, can I show you around?
You have time?
Can I show you
around?
Yeah, now?
- Yeah, like five, 10 minutes
just to show you
around the place.
- All right, okay.
- Scott, you already
stacking chairs?
- Of course pastor.
- Church's only been
over 20 minutes.
You are a godsend,
do you know that?
Did I say something wrong?
- I just been needing to
talk to you about something.
- Sounds serious, what's up?
Step into my office.
So what you got?
- Well, haven't always
been, I used to be.
- A troublemaker,
addict, alcoholic, felon.
I know, so what?
- You're not worried?
- About, what?
That you're gonna drink
all the communion wine
here at the church.
We use great juice Scott,
let me ask a question.
An important one.
Do you believe Christ died
on the cross for your sins?
- Of course.
- And do you believe
the blood of Christ
is sufficient to
wash your sins away?
- I'm just worried about
what other people think.
- It doesn't matter
what other people think,
what matters is what God thinks.
He says you're redeemed,
you're redeemed.
- But I've done so much.
- It doesn't matter, period.
Let me ask you something,
when you were in lockup,
did you meet other prisoners
who had come to know Christ?
- Yeah.
We called them
the crucifix crew.
- And I guessing there
were a bunch of choir boys
who were only in there for a
few parking tickets, right?
- When you're inside,
you don't really talk about
what you're locked up for.
But judging by their sentences,
they did some pretty bad things.
A few of them were lifers.
- Yeah.
- Worse the crime, harder
the punishment, right?
- Something like that.
- So can you imagine
any harder punishment
than being nailed to
a cross until you die?
- No.
- Exactly, what sin could
not be covered by that?
Clean up.
- I'll tell you, I sure wish
some more guys in the joint
could understand what Jesus did
so that they too could be saved.
- Wait a minute, like
a prison ministry?
- Yeah.
- Hey pastor Vanessa.
- Hey you, what
brings you in here?
- Pastor Dave says he
needed my help down here
at the church
thrift store today.
- He did did he?
- Yeah.
- Well, what I actually asked
was for him to come help me,
but that's okay.
It looks like my husband
did the old switcheroo,
Danielle and I
could use some help.
And it's good to see
you just the same.
- Danielle.
- Yeah, the one you've
been too afraid to talk
to the past couple of months.
- I haven't been afraid, I just
didn't have anything to say.
- Well, that's good
because these somehow
got in the wrong section
and you can bring them
to her for revamping.
- Want me to bring them?
- I do.
- Okay.
- Right over there.
- She's over there?
- All right.
- You can do it.
- Hey, pastor Vanessa wanted
me to hand these to you.
- Okay, did you say
what to do with them?
- Just label them or
unlabel them or something.
- Okay, you can put
them right there.
- Put them over here.
Yeah, okay.
I cannot believe
I just did that.
I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- Hold on a minute.
- I got it, I got
it, don't, it's fine.
- You sure?
I'm such an idiot, I'm sorry.
- You're fine.
- Oh man, I'm sorry.
- Yeah, it's fine.
- Okay, all right, okay.
- I'm Scott, by the way.
- I know.
- That's awesome.
Pastor Dave, which light
did you say needed?
- Yes, sir, come here.
Yes, sir.
Yeah, that's great.
All right.
All right, thank you so much.
All right, we'll see you then.
That was the prison Scott.
No, nothing bad.
They approved our request.
- What request?
- I kind of made a
request for you and I
to go minister to the inmates.
- We minister to the prisoners?
- I sure hope so.
- What about me?
I mean, are they gonna let
a convicted felon in there?
I asked them about that
and they just want you to
fill out an application.
God's got a plan Scott,
no rule of man can
deny that purpose.
He's still calls the shots.
Remember, I'm optimistic
enough for both of us.
They're gonna email
us the applications.
- That's great.
- Yeah.
- Had a
great time today.
It was fun hanging with you
and thanks for the help.
Sweet dreams, Danielle.
- I had a really
good time with you to.
If you ever need someone
to fold your clothes,
I am your man.
There's something you probably
need to know about me.
- Surprise.
- What are we doing here?
- Well, the good news is,
they've approved the first part
of your application process.
Today, they just wanna talk,
it's okay, we're early.
Just take a deep
breath, it's all good.
Hey, by the way,
how'd the date go?
- What date?
- What date he says, come on.
- You know about the date?
- You know, the best way to
spread gossip in a church.
Telephone telegram, tele
deacon, the small church, Scott.
Everybody knows.
- She's amazing isn't she?
She's amazing.
- I know, she's funny,
smart, pretty, godly.
I'm gonna marry her.
- Should I be worried Scott?
- No, God told me to do it.
- Not hearing voices are you?
- No, no, actually, before
Bible study last night
I asked God, I said,
please just give me a sign
that she's the woman for me.
Let her show up with a red
bow in her hair or something.
- That's pretty specific.
- It is, but you
wanna know something?
- What?
- She showed up last night
with a red bow in her hair?
- No way.
- Yes she did.
- You gotta be kidding.
- Yeah, I told you.
- That's amazing.
- I'm gonna marry her.
- That's awesome.
Hey question.
Does she know about?
- Yeah, I told her everything.
- And?
- She said, if God says
you're clean, you're clean.
That's good enough for me.
- Now that's the response
of a godly woman.
- Proverbs 31, good woman
is worth more than rubies.
- Amen to that.
- it's time.
No handcuffs today my brother,
they just wanna interview you.
Okay.
They just wanna talk, ready?
Morning, everyone.
- Morning.
- How's everybody doing?
- Good.
- Thank you all for
being here this morning.
I brought my lovely wife,
pastor Vanessa up here with me
because we have a special
announcement today.
Matthew 19:26 tells
us that with God,
all things are possible.
Things like turning our
lives completely around,
going from hopelessness
to giving hope to others
who are in the exact
spot we once were.
- We serve almighty
God, don't we?
- Yes.
- We do.
Well yesterday I received
a certified letter
from the correctional facility.
Danielle, would
you do the honors?
- Dear pastor Gargano,
we are pleased to inform
you that your congregant,
Scott Hieberger
has been approved
for the prison ministry program
with Road to Life Church.
We look forward to receiving
him into our facility.
- Thank you, are you
kidding me, what?
Thank you so much,
this is such an honor.
This is literally the
greatest day of my whole life.
Amen, right?
Amen, wow.
Hey morning.
- Get your turn around.
- Thank you.
- And he said it to Moses,
I, my father-in-law,
am come unto thee,
And my wife and her two
sons, thy kingdom come,
thy will be done will
be done on earth.
- On earth
as it is in heaven.
- Give us each day
our daily bread.
Wanna walk with him, okay?
You wanna walk with him?
Step by step, walk with him.
Don't ever turn
away, all things.
Okay, and when he's your
physician, you go to him,
you have a problem,
you go to him.
Some times are thinking, why?
Why, but that's not the
question that we need to ask.
We need to actually say
thank you, I understand.
I understand.
- Okay, got one for you.
Who was the greatest
financier on the Bible?
- I have no idea.
- Noah, he was
floating his stock
while everyone else
was in liquidation.
- All, right, all right,
now that is a good one.
- So that kind of
reminds me of you though.
- Why is that?
- Well, Noah listened to God
and fulfilled his purpose.
It's exactly what
you've done Scott.
I'm really proud of you.
- It's not me, God's
doing all the work here.
- Yeah, well what a
work he's doing, man,
how many today?
- 438 in attendance, sir.
Three walked the aisle.
- That is amazing.
Hey, keep going, keep
up the good work.
- I plan on it, as a matter
of fact, we're reaching out,
seeing if we can get into the
juvenile detention center.
- Wow.
- Because maybe if we
can get them young,
they won't never end up here.
- Look, if there's anything
that I can do for you,
any way I can help,
you gotta let me know, okay.
- I already put in
the application.
We're just waiting to hear back.
- Of course, great.
- All right, thank you.
- Hey.
I'm sorry, we have a problem.
- Everything okay?
- Your pass has been revoked.
- But you know me, I
preach here every week.
- I'm sorry to inform you
that it's been revoked
and you no longer have
access to this facility.
- Why?
- You have a warrant
for your arrest.
- It's outta Florida.
Some old trouble I
had from years ago.
- And it just now popped up.
- Yes, when I applied for access
at the juvenile detention.
- I don't understand if you
had a warrant for your arrest,
then why didn't they arrest you?
- Florida won't
extradite this far.
- Okay, so if they
won't arrest you,
then why won't they let
you back in the prison?
- As long as I have
a felony warrant,
I'm disqualified for entering
any correctional
facility in the state.
Isn't that ironic?
I spent my whole life
fighting to stay outta prison
and now they won't
let me back in.
- You go knock over
a liquor store.
I'm kidding.
- This is serious.
If Scott isn't
allowed back inside,
then everything he's
worked for is gone.
- So what are our options?
- I can either quit the
prison ministry altogether,
or I can go to Florida,
turn myself in and take
care of the warrant.
- Turn yourself in,
what happens then?
- It's up to the judge.
- Worst case scenario?
- With what I've done.
Looking at the
possibility of 20 years.
- Okay.
It's a little overwhelming,
but we can't forget
we serve a big God
and we don't stop
at overwhelming, period.
So what we do, we pray.
Oh gracious heavenly Father.
We ask you father for your
guidance in this dark hour.
- All right guys.
So Scott recorded a
video message for us.
You guys ready to see it?
- Yeah.
- Hey, what's up guys.
As you no doubt
have already heard,
the reason why I'm
not there in person
and I'm sending you this video
is because I'm on
my way to prison.
Something foolish
I did years ago
has finally caught up with me
and rather than run from it
like I've done my whole life,
I've decided that this time,
I wanna put it in God's hands.
I'll see you soon.
I might be spending the next
20 years behind the wire.
But if that's what God
has in store for me,
I'm willing to accept it.
Don't be upset.
Hey, the apostle Paul
did some amazing things
while he was incarcerated
and we can too.
Okay, come on.
- We're gonna all be
down for the trial.
And pastor Dave wanted me
to tell you that the church
is gonna keep paying
you all you're away.
So you don't have
to worry about bills
piling up and all that.
I love you.
- I love you too.
- I don't know
what's gonna happen.
All I know is God has a
plan and it's perfect.
I spent too many years
trying to do things my way.
Now it's time to
do things his way.
You guys pray for me and I'll
be praying for all of you.
God bless.
Thanks again for
picking me up, dad.
- Ah, no worries.
Still can't believe
that's all you brought.
- Where I'm going, I'm
not gonna need much.
- I guess you got that right,
are you a little hungry?
- Yeah.
- Well, let's go get
something to eat.
- Okay.
- You know, I almost
didn't answer the phone
when you called.
- I wouldn't have blamed
you if you hadn't.
I did some terrible things
to you and mom and everybody.
I'm sorry, dad.
- When you called and
asked for a ride to prison,
I thought sure you
were drunk again.
- I could see why.
- You sure you wanna do
this, turn yourself in?
- I am.
I'm submitting myself to
God's will now, not my own.
- Proud of you son.
- Thanks dad.
- Let me buy you a real meal.
- Sounds good.
- Fill that out and
turn it back in.
Hi.
- I'm here to turn
myself in for a warrant.
- Spelling on the last name.
- HIGHBERGER.
Highberger, Scott.
- Get some back up
here to the front desk.
Sir, stay right
there, don't move.
- Sir, turn around,
hands behind your back.
- Mr. Highberger, I'm
Levi Watts, your attorney.
- Pleasure.
- This is a first, I've
never been hired by a church
on a criminal proceeding before.
- They're a great
group of people.
- Okay, let's get to it.
I think our best defense
is to plead not guilty.
Then ask for a reduced bond
until you're trial, while
we're waiting I can.
- I'm gonna plead guilty.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm guilty.
I did all the things that
they're accusing me of.
So I'm guilty.
- Scott, with your record,
pleading guilty would ensure.
I know, I know,
I've done a lot of
terrible things in my life
and now it's time to pay for it.
- Well, I don't think the church
is going to paying
me just to help
put you back by it's bars.
It|s okay.
- We're gonna put it
in God's hands now.
- Well, that's good because
if you plead guilty,
it's certainly out of mine.
- I know.
- All right, we'll offer them
a year and see if they bite,
but don't hold your breath.
- It's okay.
Highberger, you're up.
- Good luck, preacher boy.
- All rise, court
is now in session.
The honorable judge,
William Palmer presiding.
- Please be seated
in the case of the state of
Florida versus Scott Highberger,
counselor, am I to understand
your client has made it known
he wishes to enter
a plea of guilty?
- He does your honor.
- Is he aware of
the ramifications
venting such a plea?
- He is your honor.
- How refreshing, someone
who's actually willing
to save the taxpayer's little
time and money, very well.
What is the state's
recommendation?
Your honor, considering the
extensive criminal history
of the defendant,
which includes numerous
and violent felonies,
the state recommends the maximum
of 20 years on each count
to run consecutively.
- What does he mean by
that, to run consecutively?
You means one after another.
- Your honor.
- He'll be in jail for
the rest of his life.
Yes counsel.
- I know.
- Before judgment is entered,
the defense would request
that his honor be made aware
of several letters and
statements that have been made
on behalf of the accused.
They address the changed nature
of my client, that we pray
the court would take
into consideration.
- Very well.
As long as we don't turn
this into an all day affair.
- Thank you, your honor.
- Anytime we were dispatched
to a call involving
Scott Highberger,
we knew we were in for a fight,
but now I can honestly
say he's a changed man.
Now we love seeing him walk
into the Sheriff's department.
- Scott is one of the few
Christians I identified
as being serious concerning
his walk with God.
My interactions and
communications with him
showed me his love
of the Lord was real.
And I believe him, I believe
him to be a changed man.
- Scott has become so
instrumental to our church.
I don't know how we ever
get along without him
or how we will get
along without him.
- Scott is absolutely wonderful,
been a real role
model for my children.
I don't know what
we do without him.
- Judge, I gotta tell you
that Scott growing up,
he wasn't a good kid and
he got progressively worse
as the years went by,
caused me a lot of grief
and a loss of sleep.
There was even a
time, God forgive me,
but I prayed that the next
cruiser to pull in the drive
was there to tell me,
Scott's never coming home.
But now, now I'm proud
to call him my son.
I love you, Scott.
- Scott has reached
thousands of inmates
with his prison ministry,
it's just simply astounding.
And your honor,
I have hundreds of letters
here on Scott's behalf.
If it's okay, I would
love to just read a few.
Thanks to Scott and
the prison ministry,
I finally see the
opportunity to forgive myself
and feel the light and
love of Jesus Christ.
Scott has been a real
inspiration to me.
I admire that he
had the strength
to walk away from his old life.
He has the kindness to
welcome his old friends
into his new life, but the
courage to stay away from them
if they want to drag him
down to his old place.
Here's another one, your honor.
I've been down 13 years
when I was 11 years old,
I was in a graveyard
and read these words
on a stone, where you are,
I once was, where I
am, you'll soon be.
I've never forgotten
those words.
I want what Scott has.
If it had not been for Scott,
I would still be on the
streets, getting into trouble.
Scott showed me a brand
new way to live life.
No more drugs, no more crime.
I'm alive today because of him.
I am what Scott was and
he is what I want to be.
And that's just a few again,
from the hundreds of
letters that we received,
nothing further, your honor.
- Would you please bring me
the defendant's
criminal history?
- Thank you.
- Quite the checkered past.
I have one question for you son.
Since you've been
spending all this time
preaching behind bars,
telling people to
accept responsibility
for their actions,
why have you not taken
care of this warrant?
- Just be honest.
- I was scared your honor.
- I guess I was just hoping
that it would go away
so that I wouldn't
be held accountable.
- This court will
take a short recess
while I weigh my
decision on sentencing.
Mr Highberger,
earlier I asked you
why you had not taken care
of this outstanding warrant
here in the state of Florida.
Your answer plain and simple
was that you were afraid.
You do realize that
Jonah felt the same, yes?
He didn't want to go to Ninivah,
So God sent a giant whale
to swallow him up
and drag him there.
I sir am your giant whale.
I hold in my hand a plea
agreement you have signed,
offering to do 14
months in prison.
The state wants you to
do considerably more.
I cannot in good conscience
accept your terms,
Mr. Highberger.
This court has the
authority to either accept
or reject any negotiated pleas.
And I have elected to
not accept this one.
So if you mean to move
forward with your plea,
I want you to know I am not
going to have my hands tied.
Gonna ask you one more time.
Do you still wish to
enter a guilty plea?
- Your honor, may I
confer with my client?
- Of course.
- What's going on?
- He's rejected
our plea agreement.
You need to know, know
that if you plead guilty,
you're basically
signing a blank check.
- Mr. Highberger.
♪ Every page before was
a record was a failure ♪
♪ I was on my knee and you ♪
- I am guilty, your honor.
♪ My plea ♪
- Very well, the court
accepts your plea of guilty.
Saul was a pretty
dreadful human being
until he finally saw the light.
Then he did some mighty fine
work while he was behind bars.
I think you have too, and
can continue to do so.
I've been on the bench
now for a number of years
and mostly it's
business as usual.
Your case though is unique.
You have made some bad
decisions in your life
which have led you here.
In your case however, I
don't think incarceration
is the right answer.
If you're behind bars, you
may reach a few people,
but not nearly as many as
you would as a free man.
God has plans for you son.
So go make them happen,
this case is dismissed.
Would one of you come up
and give this boy a hug?
♪ I'm pardoned, you
have released me ♪
♪ I'm pardoned ♪
♪ The old me is history ♪
♪ I'm pardoned,
pardoned by grace ♪
♪ For the rest of my days ♪
♪ I sing a hallelujah ♪
♪ 'Cause you left me out of
this life that I knew before ♪
♪ Before ♪
♪ Thank God I'm pardoned ♪
♪ My slate is washed clean ♪
♪ I'm pardoned the
old me is history ♪
♪ I'm pardoned,
pardoned by grace ♪
♪ I'm pardoned, you
have released me ♪
♪ I'm pardoned, the
old me is history ♪
♪ I'm pardoned,
pardoned by grace ♪