[MUSIC]
&gt;&gt; COME ON, PUNCH HIM.
HIT THE GUY IN THE...
COME ON, FIGHT, MAN.
KICK HIM IN THE NECK.
GIVE HIM...
WHAT?
&gt;&gt; REMEMBER THE TIME
ON THE iCARLY WEB SHOW
WHEN YOU PLAYED THE COWBOY
WHO TALKED
TO THE IDIOT FARM GIRL?
&gt;&gt; YEAH.
DID THAT ONE A FEW TIMES.
&gt;&gt; REMEMBER GIBBY?
&gt;&gt; NO, I DON'T REMEMBER GIBBY.
EVEN THOUGH I DID
THE iCARLY WEB SHOW WITH GIBBY
FOR FOUR YEARS,
I HAVE NO MEMORY OF THAT.
WHO'S GIBBY?
&gt;&gt; GIBBY WAS THE KID WHO ALWAYS
TOOK HIS SHIRT OFF.
AND SOMETIMES HE'D GO,
"UH, GIBBEHHHHHH."
REMEMBER?
&gt;&gt; HEY, SAM,
REMEMBER THE TIME...
&gt;&gt; HEY, BOBBY?
&gt;&gt; YEAH?
&gt;&gt; REMEMBER THAT TIME
YOU ASKED ME
WAY TOO MANY QUESTIONS
SO I TOOK YOUR PANTS
AND I SLAPPED YOU
ACROSS YOUR OWN FACE
WITH YOUR PANTS?
&gt;&gt; SAM, THAT'S NOT NICE.
&gt;&gt; WELL...
&gt;&gt; BOBBY LOVED WATCHING YOU
ON THE iCARLY WEB SHOW,
SO YOU SHOULD
ANSWER HIS QUESTIONS.
&gt;&gt; HEY, CAT?
&gt;&gt; SHUT UP, I'M BUSY.
&gt;&gt; SO, WHAT WAS IT LIKE
MAKING THE iCARLY WEB SHOW?
&gt;&gt; AHH, IT WAS FUN.
WE DID A LOT OF WACKY STUFF,
I GOT TO GO TO JAPAN,
I MET THE FIRST LADY,
WE GOT KIDNAPPED
A COUPLE OF TIMES.
&gt;&gt; KIDNAPPED?
&gt;&gt; BY WHO?
&gt;&gt; SOME PSYCHO CHICK, NORA.
&gt;&gt; WHERE IS NORA NOW?
&gt;&gt; WELL, SHE'S LOCKED UP
IN PRISON
SOMEWHERE NEAR SEATTLE.
&gt;&gt; DERSHLIT, PLAYTIME'S OVER.
I'M TAKING YOU
BACK TO YOUR CAGE.
&gt;&gt; OKIE DOKIE.
YOU KNOW, I'M REALLY STARTING
TO ENJOY IT HERE IN PRISON.
&gt;&gt; I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU ENJOY.
JUST...
[SCRATCHING]
YOU HEAR THAT?
&gt;&gt; HEAR WHAT?
[SCRATCHING]
[CLUCKING]
&gt;&gt; CHICKEN?
WHO LET A CHICKEN IN THE PRISON?
&gt;&gt; SPLOOSH.
&gt;&gt; HEY, CAT?
I DON'T GET IT.
&gt;&gt; WELL, I LOVE CRANBERRY JUICE.
AND MY FAVORITE FRUIT IS APPLES.
SO, I FILLED THIS FISH TANK UP
WITH CRANBERRY JUICE,
AND I'M SOAKING
THE APPLES IN IT.
&gt;&gt; YOU GET IT?
&gt;&gt; NOPE.
&gt;&gt; I'M MAKING CRAPPLES.
&gt;&gt; CRAPPLES.
&gt;&gt; WANT TO TRY?
WHAT'S IT TASTE LIKE?
&gt;&gt; LIKE CRAPPLE.
&gt;&gt; RIGHT?
♪ I'M NEVER THAT FAR ♪
♪ NO MATTER WHERE YOU ARE ♪
♪ BELIEVE IT ♪
♪ WE CAN MAKE IT COME TRUE ♪
♪ AND I-I-I-I-I ♪
♪ I'LL NEVER SAY NEVER ♪
♪ AS LONG AS ♪
♪ WE KEEP IT TOGETHER ♪
♪ IT'S THE LIFE THAT WE CHOOSE ♪
♪ AND WE STILL BREAK THE RULES ♪
♪ BUT IT'S ALL GOING TO BE ♪
♪ JUST FINE ♪
♪ (JUST FINE) ♪
♪ YOU AND ME ♪
♪ WE'RE GOING TO BE JUST FINE ♪
♪ HMMM... ♪
&gt;&gt; NEAR SEATTLE, WASHINGTON,
A DANGEROUSLY PSYCHOTIC
YOUNG WOMAN IS STILL
ON THE LOOSE AFTER ESCAPING
FROM PRISON TWO DAYS AGO.
THE WOMAN, NORA DERSHLIT,
WAS SERVING A FIVE-YEAR SENTENCE
FOR A PRIOR KIDNAPPING.
[TIMER DINGS]
&gt;&gt; IT'S READY.
&gt;&gt; HO YO.
I'M HERE
AND I'M NOT LEAVING TILL MONDAY.
&gt;&gt; HEY.
DID YOUR MOM ALREADY LEAVE TOWN
FOR THE WEEKEND?
&gt;&gt; YEAH.
HER CAR BROKE DOWN,
SO THEY TOOK MY...
&gt;&gt; HEY, NO.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
HEY, DICE, I NEED YOU
TO GET ME A MEXICAN
DRIVER'S LICENSE.
&gt;&gt; EASY.
YOUR NAME OR A FAKE NAME?
&gt;&gt; FAKE.
MAKE MY NAME
SAMATIO PUCKATITO.
&gt;&gt; I GOT IT.
&gt;&gt; HEY.
WHO WANTS TO TRY
MY HOT CRAPPLE PIE?
&gt;&gt; LET'S ANSWER TOGETHER.
&gt;&gt; LET'S SING THE ANSWER.
♪ NOBODY ♪
&gt;&gt; HEY, YOU WANT TO SNUGGLE?
&gt;&gt; BABE, COME ON,
THERE'S PEOPLE HERE.
GET OFF.
&gt;&gt; HELLO, GIBBY.
&gt;&gt; WHOA. WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
NORA?
&gt;&gt; THAT'S ME.
&gt;&gt; WAIT, WAIT,
I THOUGHT YOU WERE IN PRISON
FOR A COUPLE MORE YEARS.
&gt;&gt; RIGHT, I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE,
BUT TWO DAYS AGO, I ESCAPED.
&gt;&gt; WOW. GOOD FOR YOU.
&gt;&gt; HOW'D YOU ESCAPE?
&gt;&gt; BABE? BABY.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
ANSWER THE TRIVIA QUESTIONS?
&gt;&gt; SO, GIBBY, I DON'T WANT
TO INJURE YOU...
&gt;&gt; COOL.
&gt;&gt; BUT I WOULD LIKE
TO LOCATE AND DESTROY CARLY,
THEN SAM, THEN FREDDIE.
&gt;&gt; AH, FUN.
&gt;&gt; SO, WHERE WOULD I FIND CARLY?
&gt;&gt; SORRY, DUDE, SHE'S IN ITALY.
&gt;&gt; AW. THAT'S TOO FAR.
WHAT ABOUT SAM?
SAM PUCKETT?
&gt;&gt; SAM'S NOT THAT FAR.
SHE'S JUST DOWN THE COAST
A WAYS IN LOS ANGELES.
&gt;&gt; LOS ANGELES.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, I CAN TEXT YOU
HER HOME ADDRESS IF YOU WANT.
&gt;&gt; YES.
I WOULD LIKE THAT VERY MUCH.
&gt;&gt; NO PROB.
&gt;&gt; LATER, GIBBY.
&gt;&gt; HEY, GOOD LUCK.
&gt;&gt; HOLA CHICAS.
SAM, YOUR DAY IS ABOUT
TO GET MAJORLY BUENO.
&gt;&gt; YEAH.
&gt;&gt; MIRA ESTO.
&gt;&gt; [GASPS]
YOU GOT ME
A MEXICAN DRIVER'S LICENSE.
&gt;&gt; SHH.
&gt;&gt; WHOA.
&gt;&gt; WOW.
CONGRATULATIONS,
"SAMATIO PUCKATITO."
&gt;&gt; MUY QUESO.
&gt;&gt; AH, MY LITTLE DICE MAN.
HOW MUCH DO I LOVE THIS KID,
HUH?
I TELL YOU, I'D BE LOST
WITHOUT THIS LITTLE
FUZZY-HEADED MOP FACE.
&gt;&gt; WELL, IT SEEMS
THAT SAM PUCKETT
IS QUITE FOND OF THE YOUNG BOY
WITH THE GLORIOUS HAIR.
[PHONE DINGS]
&gt;&gt; AH, JEEZ, I BETTER
GO TO GOOMER'S APARTMENT.
&gt;&gt; [GROWLS]
&gt;&gt; WHAT FOR?
&gt;&gt; HE SAYS,
"DICE, PLEASE COME OVER.
I THOUGHT I WAS IN THE BATHROOM,
BUT I WASN'T."
&gt;&gt; OH.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, LATER.
&gt;&gt; [GRUNTING]
SO LARGE.
NO ONE HELPING ME.
&gt;&gt; HEY, YOU NEED SOME HELP?
&gt;&gt; OH, HELLO, LITTLE BOY.
&gt;&gt; HI.
WHATCHA TRYING TO DO THERE?
&gt;&gt; OH, I'M HAVING TROUBLE
PUTTING THIS INFLATABLE KAYAK
INTO MY CAR.
&gt;&gt; WHY DON'T YOU JUST
LET THE AIR OUT OF IT?
&gt;&gt; OH, NO, NO, NO.
&gt;&gt; WELL, IT'S NOT GOING
TO FIT IN YOUR CAR.
&gt;&gt; MY CAR'S INTERIOR
IS A LOT ROOMIER THAN IT SEEMS.
CHECK FOR YOURSELF.
&gt;&gt; OKAY.
IT'S REALLY NOT THAT ROOMY
IN HERE.
HEY, LET ME OUT.
MY FRIEND GOOMER
WENT TO THE BATHROOM SOMEWHERE
THAT'S NOT A BATHROOM.
&gt;&gt; TOO BAD.
I'VE GOT AN APPOINTMENT...
WITH REVENGE.
&gt;&gt; BUT...
WHAT ABOUT YOUR KAYAK?
&gt;&gt; ANSWER, ANSWER, ANSWER.
&gt;&gt; DID YOU FIND DICE?
&gt;&gt; NO, HE WON'T
PICK UP HIS PHONE.
DID YOU LOOK FOR HIM?
&gt;&gt; YEAH.
I WENT TO INSIDE OUT BURGER,
AND TUBBA CHICKEN,
AND I WENT TO CHUB-WAY,
AND ROCKIN' RIBS.
[PHONE RINGING]
&gt;&gt; IS THAT DICE?
&gt;&gt; NO, DANG IT.
IT'S GIBBY.
WHAT, GIBBY?
&gt;&gt; HEY, SAM, GUESS WHAT?
&gt;&gt; I CAN'T TALK RIGHT NOW.
&gt;&gt; REMEMBER THAT GIRL,
NORA DERSHLIT?
&gt;&gt; YES, I REMEMBER NORA.
WHY?
&gt;&gt; SHE BUSTED OUT OF PRISON.
&gt;&gt; HOW DO YOU KNOW?
&gt;&gt; SHE CAME TO SEE ME
AT THE MOVIES.
&gt;&gt; SHE CAME TO SEE YOU?
FOR WHAT?
&gt;&gt; LET'S SEE,
SHE SAID SHE WANTED TO LOCATE
AND DESTROY CARLY, THEN YOU,
AND THEN FREDDIE.
&gt;&gt; AND WHAT DID YOU SAY?
&gt;&gt; DON'T WORRY.
I TOLD HER CARLY'S IN ITALY
AND NORA SAID
THAT WAS WAY TOO FAR.
&gt;&gt; GOOD.
&gt;&gt; AND THEN I TOLD HER
YOU WERE IN L.A.
AND I GAVE HER YOUR ADDRESS.
NO.
OKAY, THIS IS BAD.
&gt;&gt; WHO'S NORA?
&gt;&gt; SHE'S THAT INSANE CHICK
THAT KIDNAPPED ME,
NORA DERSHLIT.
&gt;&gt; BUT I THOUGHT
SHE WAS IN PRISON.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
&gt;&gt; WHO'S THAT?
&gt;&gt; AH!
WHAT'S IN THE ENVELOPE?
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW.
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S IT SAY?
&gt;&gt; "I HAVE YOUR FRIEND, DICE."
&gt;&gt; OH MY...
&gt;&gt; "AND IN CASE
"YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME,
HAIR'S A LITTLE PIECE OF HIM."
&gt;&gt; [GASPS]
&gt;&gt; SIGNED, "NORA."
[PHONE RINGING]
HELLO?
&gt;&gt; DID YOU MISS ME?
&gt;&gt; NORA?
&gt;&gt; SO, YOU REMEMBER MY VOICE.
&gt;&gt; WHERE'S DICE?
&gt;&gt; OH, SAM,
NO "HI NORA, I MISSED YOU?"
NO "HOW WAS PRISON?"
NO "SORRY FOR CAUSING
"THE SOCIAL WORKERS
"TO SEND MY CHICKEN
TO A FOSTER FARM?"
&gt;&gt; THEY TOOK YOUR CHICKEN AWAY
'CAUSE YOU'RE A LUNATIC.
&gt;&gt; YOU BETTER WATCH IT,
SAM PUCKETT.
I HAVE YOUR YOUNG FRIEND, DICE,
AND I HAVE PLANS FOR HIS HAIR.
&gt;&gt; HIS HAIR?
&gt;&gt; SHH.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN HIS HAIR?
&gt;&gt; BYE, SAM.
[DIAL TONE]
&gt;&gt; POOR DICE.
&gt;&gt; HE'S SO HOSED.
&gt;&gt; NO.
NO, WE JUST GOT TO FIND HIM.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, BUT SHE WON'T TELL US
WHERE HE IS.
&gt;&gt; I KNOW. SO...
SO WE JUST GOT TO TRY TO,
YOU KNOW, FIGURE OUT
WHAT NORA WOULD DO.
&gt;&gt; YES.
&gt;&gt; WE GOT TO THINK
HOW SHE THINKS.
&gt;&gt; YES!
&gt;&gt; AH!
&gt;&gt; YES?
&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW WHO COULD REALLY
HELP US THINK LIKE A DISEASED,
EVIL, CRIMINAL MASTERMIND?
&gt;&gt; WHO?
&gt;&gt; ANOTHER DISEASED, EVIL,
CRIMINAL MASTERMIND.
&gt;&gt; WHY DO YOU WANT
TO SEE MY PATIENT?
&gt;&gt; WE NEED TO ASK HIM
SOME QUESTIONS.
&gt;&gt; WHY IS HE HERE
IN THIS HOSPITAL?
&gt;&gt; HIS MOTHER BROUGHT HIM HERE
FROM SEATTLE.
HE HAS A VIRUS.
VERY CONTAGIOUS.
THAT'S WHY HE MUST BE
KEPT DOWN HERE, LOCKED AWAY
FROM THE GENERAL POPULATION.
&gt;&gt; WHAT KIND OF VIRUS?
&gt;&gt; IT'S CALLED PORCUPOX.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW HE GOT IT.
ALL WE KNOW IS THAT
IT CAME FROM A PORCUPINE.
&gt;&gt; WHATEVER.
JUST LET US TALK TO HIM.
&gt;&gt; IT'S THAT WAY.
THE LAST ONE.
GIRLS.
DON'T TOUCH THE GLASS.
&gt;&gt; WHY NOT?
&gt;&gt; I JUST CLEANED IT.
&gt;&gt; COCKADOODLE DOO,
THE COW SAYS MOO.
&gt;&gt; SAMANTHA PUCKETT.
&gt;&gt; 'SUP, NEVEL?
&gt;&gt; WHY ARE YOU HERE?
&gt;&gt; OKAY, SO, WE HAVE
THIS FRIEND, DICE.
&gt;&gt; YOU MEAN THE YOUNG BOY,
AGE 12, WHOSE FULL NAME
IS DICENIO J. CORLEONE,
SIXTH GRADE,
MAGNIFICENT HAIR?
&gt;&gt; HOW DO YOU KNOW SO MUCH
ABOUT DICE?
&gt;&gt; I KNOW A LOT OF THINGS
ABOUT A LOT OF THINGS.
&gt;&gt; WELL, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED TO DICE?
&gt;&gt; TELL ME.
&gt;&gt; SOME WEIRD GIRL TOOK HIM.
&gt;&gt; HER NAME IS NORA DERSHLIT.
HERE, TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
&gt;&gt; SAM!
SAM LISTEN TO ME,
GET ME OUT OF HERE.
SAM, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
&gt;&gt; PUT YOUR HANDS BACK.
&gt;&gt; WHAT IS THIS?
&gt;&gt; IT'S THE NOTE NORA GAVE US.
&gt;&gt; [CLEARS THROAT]
"I HAVE YOUR FRIEND, DICE.
"AND IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME,
HAIR'S A LITTLE PIECE OF HIM."
&gt;&gt; HERE'S THE PIECE OF HAIR
SHE PUT IN THERE.
&gt;&gt; THE BOY DOES HAVE
AMAZING HAIR.
&gt;&gt; WE KNOW.
&gt;&gt; WE JUST NEED TO FIND HIM.
&gt;&gt; THEN WE MUST
LOOK AT THE CLUES.
&gt;&gt; WE DON'T HAVE ANY CLUES.
&gt;&gt; WRONG, SIR.
SEE THIS?
NOTICE THIS STAIN?
&gt;&gt; IS IT KETCHUP?
&gt;&gt; NO.
THIS HAS MORE FLAVOR
AND THE TANG OF...
PINEAPPLE.
THIS STAIN WAS MADE
BY DONKEY SAUCE.
&gt;&gt; DONKEY SAUCE?
THE ONLY PLACE
THAT HAS DONKEY SAUCE IS...
ALOHA BURGER.
&gt;&gt; CORRECT.
&gt;&gt; SO, YOU'RE SAYING,
IF WE HAPPEN TO FIND A DONKEY
EATING A HAMBURGER,
THEN DICE IS SOMEWHERE
IN HA-WAI-AYE-AYE?
&gt;&gt; OKAY, THIS GIRL MAKES GIBBY
SEEM LIKE A GENIUS.
&gt;&gt; JUST TELL US WHERE DICE IS.
&gt;&gt; WE REALLY CAN'T KNOW
FOR SURE.
BUT...
THE PERFECT PLACE
TO HIDE A PERSON WOULD BE
IN AN ABANDONED HOUSE.
AND WITHIN ONE MILE
OF ALOHA BURGER,
THERE ARE
THREE ABANDONED HOUSES.
&gt;&gt; HOW DO YOU KNOW?
&gt;&gt; I'M STUDYING FOR
MY JUNIOR REAL ESTATE LICENSE.
&gt;&gt; ALL RIGHT.
&gt;&gt; THERE IS ONE ABANDONED HOUSE
ON CROSBY STREET,
ONE ON STILLS LANE,
AND ONE ON NASH AVENUE.
LOOK IN THOSE HOUSES THREE,
AND YOUR FRIEND DICE,
YOU SHALL SEE.
&gt;&gt; GREAT.
WE JUST NEED TO CHECK OUT
THOSE THREE VACANT HOUSES
ON CROSBY, STILLS, AND NASH.
&gt;&gt; LET'S HURRY.
&gt;&gt; SAM! SAM, WAIT!
GET ME OUT OF HERE!
&gt;&gt; HEY, GIRL.
I'M GETTING HUNGRY.
&gt;&gt; HELLO, DICE.
HOW'S THE HOLE?
&gt;&gt; CAN I GET
A SANDWICH OR SOMETHING?
&gt;&gt; ALL RIGHT.
&gt;&gt; WHATEVER SANDWICH YOU GOT.
TUNA SALAD, PEANUT BUTTER.
I JUST NEED FOOD.
&gt;&gt; LOOK IN THE BASKET.
&gt;&gt; HAIR CONDITIONER?
&gt;&gt; IT PUTS THE CONDITIONER
IN ITS HAIR
IF IT WANTS THE SANDWICH.
&gt;&gt; WHO'S "IT"?
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE "IT".
&gt;&gt; I'M NOT PUTTING
THIS CONDITIONER IN MY HAIR.
&gt;&gt; IT PUTS THE CONDITIONER
IN ITS HAIR OR ELSE
IT GETS THE HOSE AGAIN.
&gt;&gt; AW, MAN, AGAIN WITH THE HOSE?
&gt;&gt; THAT TEARS IT.
[GRUNTS]
&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW YOU'RE JUST
WASTING HOSES.
[DOORBELL]
&gt;&gt; OH, DEAR.
SOMEONE'S AT THE DOOR.
&gt;&gt; WAIT.
IT'S STILL HUNGRY.
&gt;&gt; HELLO, GIRL.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
&gt;&gt; HAVE YOU SEEN MY FRIEND DICE?
&gt;&gt; NO.
&gt;&gt; ARE YOU SURE?
&gt;&gt; OH, WAIT.
IS HE A LITTLE YOUNG PERSON
WITH GREAT BIG FAT HAIR?
&gt;&gt; YES, HE HAS BIG HAIR, MA'AM.
&gt;&gt; WELL, I KNOW NOTHING.
HEY, HEY, BEFORE YOU GO,
YOU WANT TO COME
CHECK OUT MY BASEMENT?
&gt;&gt; WELL, SURE.
OH!
&gt;&gt; CAT! WHOA, ARE YOU OKAY?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, I'M ALL RIGHT.
LUCKY I LANDED ON THESE HOSES.
&gt;&gt; WELL, WELL.
GET IT?
YOU GUYS ARE DOWN IN A WELL,
SO I SAID, "WELL, WELL."
&gt;&gt; THAT'S GREAT FUN, BUT...
I THINK YOU KNOCKED ME DOWN HERE
BY ACCIDENT, SO, COULD YOU
PLEASE GIVE ME A HAND?
&gt;&gt; CAT, IT WASN'T AN ACCIDENT.
&gt;&gt; HAIR BOY'S RIGHT.
YOU BOTH ARE MY PRISONERS.
&gt;&gt; WAIT. I THINK THAT'S NORA.
&gt;&gt; WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS TO US?
&gt;&gt; BECAUSE I HATE SAM PUCKETT
AND YOU TWO ARE HER FRIENDS.
SO, FIRST,
I'M GOING TO SHAVE DICE'S HAIR
AND MAKE IT INTO A WIG
FOR ME TO WEAR.
&gt;&gt; WHAT HAPPENED TO THE LIGHTS?
[CHICKEN CLUCKING]
&gt;&gt; MAURICE, WHERE ARE YOU?
&gt;&gt; WHO WANTS CHICKEN?
&gt;&gt; SAM PUCKETT.
DON'T YOU TOUCH MY CHICKEN.
&gt;&gt; OH, I'M ALREADY TOUCHING IT.
&gt;&gt; YOU LEAVE HIM ALONE.
&gt;&gt; LET'S MAKE A DEAL.
YOU THROW A ROPE DOWN
SO CAT AND DICE CAN CLIMB
OUT OF THAT PIT,
AND I WON'T PLUCK,
COOK, EAT, DIGEST,
AND POOP OUT THIS CHICKEN.
&gt;&gt; NO.
WHY DON'T YOU AND I FIGHT?
&gt;&gt; [GASPS]
&gt;&gt; AND IF YOU WIN,
YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS
MAY GO FREE.
&gt;&gt; COOL.
LET'S DANCE.
&gt;&gt; BUT IF I WIN,
DOWN THE PIT YOU GO.
&gt;&gt; SAM, DON'T DO IT.
&gt;&gt; THERE'S NO SANDWICHES
DOWN HERE.
&gt;&gt; JUST HOSES.
&gt;&gt; SO...
READY TO BATTLE?
&gt;&gt; YOU READY TO BLEED?
&gt;&gt; I DON'T THINK
I'LL BE INJURED.
YOU SEE, SAM,
I'VE BEEN IN PRISON
FOR TWO YEARS LIFTING WEIGHTS,
GETTING STRONGER AND ANGRIER.
AND WHAT HAS
SAM PUCKETT BEEN DOING?
OH, BABYSITTING.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S TRUE.
&gt;&gt; COME ON, COME ON, SAMMY.
COME GET A TASTE OF NORA.
YEAH.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
READY, SET...
[SCREAMS]
NO FAIR GRABBING MY FOOT.
&gt;&gt; OH, YEAH, SORRY.
&gt;&gt; YOU LET GO RIGHT NOW.
&gt;&gt; OKAY.
&gt;&gt; [SCREAMS]
&gt;&gt; ARE YOU GUYS OKAY?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, WE'RE FINE.
&gt;&gt; I'M NOT FINE.
[ALARM RINGING]
&gt;&gt; OH, MY G...
EMERGENCY.
EMERGENCY!
NEVEL PAPPERMAN HAS ESCAPED.
&gt;&gt; COCKADOODLE DOO,
THE COW SAYS...
&gt;&gt; WE KNOW WHAT THE COW SAYS.
&gt;&gt; SO, WHAT HAPPENS TO NORA NOW?
&gt;&gt; SHE GOES BACK TO PRISON
IN SEATTLE.
WE'RE GONNA PUT HER
IN MAXIMUM SECURITY.
SHE WON'T BOTHER YOU AGAIN.
&gt;&gt; OH, YES I WILL.
I WILL RETURN
AND I WILL BOTHER SAM AGAIN.
AND THAT GOES
FOR ALL THE FILTHY iCARLYS.
AND YOU DIRTY SAM AND CATS.
I'M A CHARACTER
THAT NEVER DIES.
&gt;&gt; OH, YEAH.
I REMEMBER YOU,
FROM THE iCARLY WEB SHOW.
&gt;&gt; THANKS.
&gt;&gt; HEY, REMEMBER THAT GUY
WHO ALWAYS USED TO GO "GIBBEHH"?
&gt;&gt; GET OUT OF HERE.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS,
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE HIT UP
SOME ALOHA BURGER?
&gt;&gt; DONKEY SAUCE.
&gt;&gt; YAY.
&gt;&gt; MISS PUCKETT.
PHONE FOR YOU.
&gt;&gt; ME?
PUCKETT.
&gt;&gt; SO, DID YOU FIND
YOUR BIG-HAIRED FRIEND...
DICE?
&gt;&gt; NEVEL.
&gt;&gt; HELLO, SAM.
&gt;&gt; WHERE ARE YOU?
&gt;&gt; OH, I CAN'T TELL YOU THAT.
YOU MIGHT SEND PEOPLE
TO LOOK FOR ME.
&gt;&gt; NEVEL, TELL ME WHERE YOU ARE.
&gt;&gt; OH, I'M AFRAID
I CAN'T DO THAT, SAM.
YOU SEE...
I'M HAVING AN OLD FRIEND
FOR DINNER.
&gt;&gt; NOT JUST ONE OLD FRIEND...
CHECK IT.
DOUBLE HEADER.
HA.
&gt;&gt; SAM, I GOT TO GO.
&gt;&gt; NEVEL.
[DIAL TONE]
&gt;&gt; I TOLD YOU
NOT TO BRING THAT THING.
&gt;&gt; COME ON,
LET'S GO GET SOME TAPENADE.
&gt;&gt; OOH, ALL RIGHT.
BUT WE'RE SPLITTING THE CHECK
THREE WAYS.
&gt;&gt; AW, DUDE.
&gt;&gt; WHOA.
INFLATABLE KAYAK?
I COULD USE THIS
AT MY BEACH HOUSE.
MY LIFE'S GOING GREAT.
[OVEN BELL]
&gt;&gt; MMM...