Come on! I'm not a 3-year-old!
No, I got it.
What do you think, Tate?
"Amityville Horror."
Okay. All right.
Look, I know it's an old shit
box,
but your mama really likes it,
and we're doing what makes
her happy right now. Okay?
- Where am I sleeping anyway?
- Upstairs.
Want to go check it out?
You get first pick.
You can choose any room you
want.
This pizza's so good.
You going to be okay back
there all by yourself?
Okay. I'm sorry.
I thought you just might be
a little scared
not being across the hall from
us anymore.
- I'm 10.
- I know.
Mom. Dad.
Yeah, buddy?
Can you tuck me
in just for tonight?
I got ya.
All right. Giddyap.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Any time.
Da-dump, da-dump, da-dump,
da-dump.
You're hitting yourself.
Why are you hitting yourself?
Why you hitting yourself?
Time to go to sleep. Handshake.
Aw...
- Come on.
- Okay.
You got a rocket ship.
- Yeah!
- There you go. Oh, you beat me.
All right. Love you, bud.
- Good night, Dad.
- Good night. Sleep tight.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
Oh, yes!
Oh! Come on. Come on. Come on.
I'm so close. Just get it.
I've been trying to finish
this game for 5 years.
Make yourself useful, Tate. Dump
by the back steps please.
Late night, huh?
Tate!
A government spokesman
has stated that there is not...
Isn't there some sort
of day camp or--
- No.
- YMCA?
We missed the sign- up
deadlines.
You have to take him with you.
Frannie, you're not
listening to me.
I cannot take him to work with
me, okay?
He has to go to work with you.
Why didn't you figure out this
before now?
Why didn't you?
Hey, I can just go to
Brandon's.
Oh. No, baby. They're on
vacation in the Ozarks.
Why can't he go to the office?
For Christ's sake, Frannie,
he'll be less
visible and intrusive
at your job than mine.
She just gave me a week off
for the move.
I can't just show up with him.
Hey, I'll just stay here by
myself.
- No!
I'm responsible.
Fine. Tate, you'll come
to Bliss with me.
Can't let your father
give the illusion at the office
he's a family man.
- Get your backpack.
- Okay.
- Perfect. Oh--
- Wait.
There's something missing.
Ohh!
Oh, my gosh. Look at that.
Oh, Mommy.
I'll give you ladies a minute.
Thank you so much, ladies,
and please let me know
if there's anything you need,
even up to the minute
you're walking down the aisle.
This is my home number.
- Oh, good.
- Aw, Frannie.
- This is great.
- I am simply elated.
- I can't thank you enough.
- We're just so happy.
Thank you so much. I just--
- I'm elated for you.
- Thanks.
- You're so welcome.
- "Elated, verb.
To elevate the spirits up,
excited, exhilarated, inspired.
Antonym, depressed."
Mom, can we go now?
You're not wearing your grubby
sneakers in there, are you?
No. Now, for the
hundredth time, can we go?
Oh, you little turd. You had
your shoes on in there again!
Oh! My socks are dirtier!
- All finished?
- Oh, yes, Phyllis.
It went very well.
- Sales?
Just over 2,800.
Oh, that's good.
They were happy then.
Oh, they were just elated.
Very satisfied.
So how's the new house?
It's depressing.
We love it.
And thank you again
for giving me last week off
so I could get us settled.
Well, see you in the morning,
Phyllis.
- Both of you?
- Don't worry.
He'll be with his dad tomorrow.
- Good.
- Good night.
Shit!
Why are people waving at us?
We live in a small town
now, Tater.
That's what people do
in small towns. They wave.
It's called hospitality. It
means--
Don't! I want to look it up.
Give it time, baby.
It's only been a week.
These small town kids are super
friendly.
You're going to be grateful
for that hospitality
when you start
your new school in the fall.
Yeah, it's right
above hospitalized.
♪ I step across the road to
where a little girl is crying ♪
- Hey, George.
- Hey.
- George, your hair looks great.
- Thanks, Jimbo.
George?
Stop. See?
- What a goddamn fruit.
- Hey, Dad.
Hey, buddy.
Frances, did you see this?
You get a load of that faggot on
a bike?
- All right. I'll see you later.
I mean, Jesus Christ.
Next door to a tranny.
Frances, did you know about
this?
The real estate agent
said the house was owned
by a retired English professor.
- Hey.
- Hey, girl.
- Tate, kitchen now, baby.
- But why?
- Watch TV.
- Oh.
That's wonderful, Frances.
You found us a house next
to another John Wayne Gacy.
Gacy was a clown,
not a tranny.
Well, I bet this one
has got little kids' bodies
buried in the crawlspace over
there!
You stop it!
You're going to scare Tate.
Well, Jesus, I'm scared.
Don't unpack anymore.
We're not living here.
Because of a neighbor?
We're not moving again.
Hey, we can move back
to the city.
That's always an option.
- No.
- Oh.
Look. You know, I packed up.
I left the city no questions
asked, for you, Fran.
Now, if we are going to
give this another shot,
then I cannot be worried
about Tate's safety
or what he's being exposed to.
Billy, I'm exhausted,
and I can't take off
any more time from work.
I know. You don't have to lift
a finger, okay?
No, no. No, no. I will rehire
the movers.
I will repack what has been
unpacked,
and I'll find us another house.
Okay?
I'm serious. A great house
with great neighbors.
- Out of the city?
- Yeah, out of the city.
And while I'm doing that,
all you have to do is
just keep Tate away
from that deviant across the
driveway.
All right?
Frances Jean.
♪ Getting it right
in your eye. ♪
Some of these are really
good, girl.
Hmm.
No, shorter.
Girl, any shorter and your whole
ass is going to be hanging out.
There's no fancy footwork.
Choreography is me
just standing up there, looking
pretty.
Oh, okay. Would you like me
to get you a jacket?
I did not pay $6,000
to hide these girls.
$6,000 of whose money?
Girl, I got to pin you,
so I need you to stand still.
All right?
I'm going to go see Carmen
on Sunday.
You should come.
No, um...maybe next time.
Is she awake yet?
She's in and out of
consciousness.
But she's never going to be
the same after what those guys
did to her.
It was more than one of them?
Cops said a witness
saw three or four guys jump her.
That's crazy, but you know
what?
It ain't like cops
are going to do shit about it
or her parents for that matter.
That is why we have to get out
of the heartland, Gossamer.
It's got no heart for us.
The heartland?
Girl, you are crazy.
That was very clever.
- Hello, Edward.
- Hi, Diana.
- Can I help you, Daddy?
- George, Aunt Rita called
and left another message
regarding your cousin Brenda's
prom dress.
- Okay, Daddy.
I'm working right now.
- It's her fourth call.
- I'll call her as soon
as I finish with this,
Daddy. Okay? Thank you.
But what time?
Really, Daddy?
Must you come and do this?
Come and interrupt me
and disrespect me
in front of one of my clients.
Look, when the beads are down,
I'm unavailable. You know this.
I might not be writing some
book or teaching some lecture,
but I'm working.
I'm aware of that.
Well, just have Aunt Riri
bring Brenda by tomorrow, okay?
- But what time?
- Two, Daddy. Okay? Two o'clock.
All right then.
Whew.
Intense.
- George.
- It's not funny.
You could be my leading man.
- It's really not funny.
- Come on, George. Let's dance.
- It's not funny. Move.
- I think it suits you.
Yeah? You can step out now.
"Tranquilize, tranquil,
tranquility."
- Hello there, young fellow.
- Hi.
- Is your mommy or daddy home?
- My mom's in there.
- Do you like tuna casserole?
- No, it's heinous.
All right then.
There's no one to play
with here.
I hate this place. It's so
boring.
You know what's boring?
Working all day for naggy
Phyllis and then listening to
you whine at me,
and now I have to let out all
the seams on this bridesmaid
dress
because she forgot to mention
two months ago that she's
pregnant.
Well, I'm starving.
Microwave some of that
lady's casserole.
I'd rather die of starvation.
Why did we move here? Ugh!
God. So ignorant.
Good afternoon.
Hey.
Hey. I said what's up, little
man?
Hey, that's mine!
Get off, lady! That's mine!
You're too big. You'll break it.
Relax, baby.
I'm just borrowing it.
That's theft, not borrowing!
Um, you weren't riding it.
I was about to, and besides,
it doesn't matter.
- It's my property.
- I'm sorry.
By all means, ride your little
stupid skateboard.
And I will.
What? I didn't bust it.
Go on. Hop on.
I'll ride it when I
feel like it!
And stop staring at me.
Ain't that the little teapot
calling the kettle black.
You've been staring at me
for the past few days like
I was something stuck
on the bottom of your shoe.
Ha! That's ludicrous.
Why would I stare at you?
- Because I'm divine.
- No, you're a deviant.
Oh, really?
And what's a deviant?
One that deviates from
accepted norm, noun.
- How old are you?
I'm 25 years old.
Now how old are you?
10.
Kind of puny for 10,
ain't you?
Well, you're enormous.
I'm tremendous.
What's your name?
- What's your name?
- Little boy, what's your name?
- Tate.
- Tate?
Like Darrin's boss on
"Bewitched"?
- What?
- Never mind.
- Now, what's your name?
- Gossamer.
You know what that means?
- Yeah.
- What's it mean?
- Hold on.
- Gossamer is the--
- Don't tell me!
- Why not?
You clearly don't know what it
means.
- I want to look it up.
- What?
In my dictionary. I don't like
people to tell me stuff
'cause I like to find out for
myself.
Ha. Okay.
"The heaven was spangled
with tremulous stars,
and at the horizon, the clouds
hung down in gossamer folds."
You know, I'm trying
to concentrate here.
Okay. What's it say?
G, G, G, Gossamer. Okay.
Gossamer, noun.
Hmm. I'm a noun.
"An extremely light variety of
gowz--"
Gauze.
"Gauze used especially for
veils,
any thin light fabric, something
extremely light or delicate."
- Hmm. Yeah. That's me.
- Hardly.
- Look up Tate.
- I've tried. There's no entry.
Then how do you know you
exist?
Tate! Come inside!
I'm avoiding you!
Now, please.
Your dad's on the phone.
- Your mama is real pretty.
- She's exasperating.
- So how long was he over there?
- I don't know.
However long we were
on the phone, maybe 10 minutes.
Jesus Christ.
Frannie, he cannot be over
there, period,
and unsupervised?
I mean, who knows
what could have happened.
He's 10. I can't watch him
every second.
He could have been taken
inside.
He could have been molested,
for God's sake.
Jesus, then be here.
You're already sneaking off
every chance you get.
Hey, buddy.
- Am I in trouble?
- No, baby. Not at all.
Why don't you like
the girl next door?
What girl?
- Billy.
- Her name is Gossamer.
- She lives there with her dad,
Edward.
- You know what?
We just don't want you talking
to people we don't know.
Just give your dad and I a
chance to meet them before you--
Do not go over there again.
Baby, it's going to be okay.
Here.
Come help me set the table. Come
on.
How come you got two of those?
Because I'm sending copies
of the best design
in my portfolio to the Pyramid
Club.
Pyramid drag shows are the gold
standard
of all the balls
and ballrooms in New York City.
I don't know why anyone
would ever want to live
in such a big city.
You'd never know your neighbors.
There's no trees to speak of,
and people are always getting
run over by them subways.
Name me one person you heard
of that's got run over by a
subway, Jimbo.
I'm with Jimbo.
It's safer here, George.
Dammit, Daddy! Ain't nothing
happening to queers in New York
that ain't happening
in Kansas City, so please.
You met them new neighbors yet?
Yeah.
Thought I'd have to chase them
down and tackle them
just to get them to say hello.
He's a feisty little shit. I
like that.
Your mother would have
appreciated his spunk.
Yeah. Mama always had
a soft spot for misfits.
Like me. I still have
that blazer she sewed me
for my daddy's funeral.
I wear it to church.
It might be time for me
to update your wardrobe, Jimbo.
I mean, seriously, wide lapels
went out with feathered bangs.
- Where's Mom?
- Oh, I don't know.
Crazy Phyllis has her running
all over the city today,
so today, it's just us men.
Just us men.
That's right, buddy.
All right.
You really need to get
a new car.
- Ha. Thanks.
Hey. Do you want
to practice pop-ups?
Yeah, we can.
I'll just go grab my glove.
Here's your glove.
Hey, you know, I got to make
a phone call real quick,
so I will be back in a second.
All right, buddy?
Wait. So then you'll throw
for me?
Yes, sir.
I'll just be 5 minutes,
so stay out here in the yard.
Tate, in our yard!
- Okay.
- Good man.
Hey! I hear the Royals
are looking for a new pitcher.
What was that?
You been recruited by the
Royals?
- No, the Cubs.
- Eh.
The Cubs suck this year.
You might have a shot.
- So...
- You need a haircut, boy.
My dad's going to give me
a summer cut.
What's that?
He buzzes it with the clippers
every summer.
His dad used to do it to him
when he was a kid.
- Mm. That's the Welfare Cut.
- What's that?
It's the cut all the kids
on welfare get.
Okay.
- What? You looking up welfare?
- Yep.
Mm-kay. So what's it say?
"Noun, well-being, happiness,
wealth and prosperity."
Nah, that's the wrong
definition, baby.
Okay.
"Financial support given by
a government to the unemployed,
- disadvantaged."
- Bingo.
- Poor people.
- Wait, so you're telling me
that poor people have summer
cuts?
Food stamps don't work
in salons, Tate.
Believe it or not,
I went to beauty school.
- I believe you.
- Yeah?
And I bet I could
finesse you the most chic
and stylish haircut
third grade has ever seen.
I'm actually going into
fourth.
Think David Bowie, baby. Mm!
Okay.
♪ Blue Jean ♪
♪ I just met a girl named Blue
Jean ♪
♪ Blue Jean ♪
♪ She got a camouflaged face and
no money ♪
♪ Remember they always let you
down ♪
♪ when you need them ♪
♪ Oh, Blue Jean ♪
♪ Is heaven any sweeter than
Blue Jean ♪
Tate. What are you doing?
Where's your dad?
- On the phone.
- Tate, this your mama?
Oh, hello.
I'm sorry for the bother.
Oh, not a bother.
I'm Gossamer, Gossamer Bryant.
- Hi, I'm Frannie, Tate's mom.
- Nice to meet you.
I love that skirt.
I'm a sucker for patch pockets.
- Thank you. I made it.
- Perfectly symmetrical.
I'm a seamstress myself.
You should come in
and see some of my stuff.
- Boring.
- We really have to go.
Hey, neighbor.
We meet at last.
Edward Bryant.
Pleasure to meet you, Mrs...
- Frannie. Frannie Milliken.
- Glad to have you next door.
I understand you've come to us
from the city.
Yes. We really have to go.
Oh. Would you care to take
some sweet corn?
We have plenty.
No, thank you.
Later, Tater.
Bye!
I think she was intimidated
by you, old man.
Don't worry. I've won
over tougher folks than them.
You and I need to have
a conversation.
Ain't got time now,
eavesdropper.
Hey, get your Goddamn hands off
of me!
I'm your father, boy.
You will start treating me
with a greater level of respect!
Mhm. I know.
You are in hot water,
young man, boiling, scalding!
Do you know where he was?
- What? Where?
- Next door on the porch.
Tate, go upstairs! Go!
When I came inside, that faggot
was nowhere in sight.
All right?
- Who were you talking to?
- Work.
We can't watch the kids every
second of the day, now, can we?
- And I can't trust you 24/7.
- Jesus Christ. You're paranoid.
And you're deceitful!
Are we going to keep exchanging
insults,
or are you actually going to
cut off contact with her
like you said you would?
I did cut contact! We can't
keep talking about this, okay?
- This is exactly why...
- Don't blame me!
Well, look who's back.
I was wondering if your offer
was still available.
- What offer was that?
- I'm hungry,
and I'd like to have
some of your corn, please.
Lucky for you,
I have half a dozen heads
already in a pot on the stove.
You could just continue
shucking these remaining ears.
- I don't know how to shuck.
- Well, sit down, and I'll show
you.
Grab it here at the top of
the ear.
And pull down on the husk.
There you go.
Yes. That's what shucking is.
You got it.
Yeah. Wring it a little bit at
the bottom.
You got it. Now put it right
there.
So good.
- What style?
- Salty style.
And then you do it over and
over again.
I'm getting full already.
- Are you?
- Yeah.
- This was so good.
- Oh, my God. It was the best.
It's a pleasure, a pleasure.
This is ridiculous!
Did your wife leave you?
No, Tate.
I'm a widower.
Do you know what that is?
How did she die?
Cancer, nearly 7 years ago.
- Everyone dies of cancer.
- Well, it seems that way
sometimes,
doesn't it?
He'll stay out of the way.
I had no other option.
Frannie, we have a full schedule
today!
We are booked solid until 6:00.
Okay, go this way. Shh.
He has everything he needs.
You won't even know he's here.
Please, Phyllis. This is the
last time.
Yes, it is. I do not want
to hear a peep out of him.
Take it!
- You need anything?
- A new mom.
- I know.
- A new dad.
- You need your summer cut.
- Why? Are we on welfare?
- What?
- Mom!
Hello. Oh, of course. The
Rivieras.
Absolutely. I am all set
for the appointment.
Do you ever wish
you had brothers or sisters?
Oh, I have siblings.
- You do?
- Mm-hmm. Brother and a sister.
I'm the baby. Can't you tell?
- No.
- They moved away,
have their own lives,
their own families, their own
opinions.
- Don't they come and visit you?
- Me? No.
They'll occasionally come to see
Daddy.
- Don't they like you?
- Mm.
Tater, some people...
I'm not for all palates.
I'm more of an acquired taste.
You get me?
Not really.
Do you miss your mom?
The love of a mother
is the veil of a softer light
between the heart and the
Heavenly Father.
My mother accepted and loved me
for who I was
before I even had the words to
ask her to.
Hey, Mom!
I caught 16 lightning bugs,
but I let them all go
because if they lose
their light, they die.
Good. I need you to go to
bed now.
Are we moving again?
I don't know what we're doing.
Please go to bed.
Where's Dad?
Mom, is he coming back?
Why do you constantly make me
repeat myself?
Just for once, do what I ask.
Go. Go!
- Afternoon, Mr. Edward.
- Afternoon, Mrs. Maybelle.
- Is Gossamer home?
- No, he isn't, Mrs. Maybelle.
George is over at Jimbo's
trailer.
Apparently,
he wrecked his bike last night,
and he's pretty banged up.
Oh, gracious.
He may be coming to stay
with us for a while.
Well, I hope Jimbo
will be all right.
- Mm-hmm.
- Gossamer has always been
such a caring young woman.
Anything else I can help you
with?
Would you mind giving this
elastic to Gossamer for me?
I want her to use it
on the seersucker skirt
she's working on.
Yeah. I'll put it on his
workstation with a note on it.
- All right, then. Goodbye.
- Mrs. Maybelle,
- I'll be glad to carry that bag
the rest of the way for you.
- No!
Thank you, Mr. Edward.
You don't seem to know a strong
woman when you see one.
"A bundle of sticks or twigs
or branches,
especially used for as fuel."
Sticks and twigs.
Morning.
Eggs and bacon for my boy.
Where's Dad?
He'll be back soon, Tate.
He's mad at me, not you. Okay?
Wait. Do I still have to go
to work with you?
- Tate!
- No! No!
I don't like that place. I
refuse, Mom.
That place is tortuous,
and Phyllis is evil.
I know. I know.
But I called Brandon's mother
and arranged for you
to spend all day tomorrow
with Brandon while I'm at work.
- What about today?
- I'm sorry, Tate.
I need you to do this today.
Oh, Mom!
Wish you'd get
fired.
Hello?
Oh, good morning, Phyllis.
We were just on our way out the
door.
No. Billy is actually not around
today after all.
No. I understand.
I'll figure something out,
and I'll see you at 9.
No, I promise. I won't be late.
My favorite neighbors.
Hi. Gossamer, right?
- That's right.
- Is Edward home?
Yeah. Yeah. Come in.
Mrs. Milliken, everything all
right?
Mr. Bryant, I know
you don't know us...me.
I haven't made the effort
to be as neighborly as I...
The thing is, I work in the
city,
and Tate's dad is unavailable,
and I know it's a great deal to
ask.
Excuse me. Miss Frannie,
how would Tate like to
hang out with us for the day?
We have no other plans
other than looking after Jimbo.
I'll be back by 6.
He's in capable hands.
I raised three children myself.
That's right, and we've all
become upstanding individuals,
particularly myself.
Tomorrow, you get to
go to Brandon's.
Come on, Tate.
Let's go make Jimbo breakfast.
Thank you, Edward.
And I'm so sorry.
I know I haven't--I mean we
haven't--
It's all right, Mrs. Milliken.
I understand.
Frannie. Thank you.
Here is my work number
in case there's a problem.
Oh, we'll be fine, and don't
worry.
I won't let them paint his
fingernails.
- I love it!
- Of course you do.
Welcome to my hideout.
Come in.
I don't want to ruin anything.
Son, I wouldn't be able to tell
if you ruined everything.
Come in.
Take a look around if you'd
like.
Whoa.
So what do you do in this place?
I'm writing a book of sorts.
Actually, I'm assembling a
compilation
of several of my short stories
for publication.
Hmm.
Is that Gossamer's mom?
The love of my
life,
and that's our wedding day.
- Is that Gossamer?
- No, son.
That's my daughter, Celia.
Then where's Gossamer?
- She looks like a boy.
- Well, I suppose you're right.
It's that welfare haircut,
Tate.
Did Daddy show you his
dictionary?
What?
It's a bit decrepit, I'm
afraid.
Tate, look up decrepit.
I already know what that
means.
Is this a first edition?
No. Publication 1864.
The first edition was published
in 1806.
This was actually its third
publication.
Dorks.
Mm-hmm.
And I suppose
she's going to have it.
Okay. And what are you going to
do?
I know that I know the answer,
but I want to hear you say it.
Stop being a Goddamn coward
and tell me that you're leaving!
There. Now find the guts to tell
your son.
Frannie, I need to talk to
you.
Listen, I've tried to be
really understanding
about your situation,
but today I found this.
It's actually the second one
that I've found
where you rang her up for
$149.63
instead of
$1,496.30.
Shit. I am sorry.
Take it out of my pay.
No! This shop is all I have.
It was my mother's dream,
and she handed it down to me.
I didn't lose it to my second
husband.
I'm certainly not going to lose
it to you.
I am asking you to get your
things,
and I will cut you your last
check.
So what did your little eyes
spy?
Hmm.
That's a French
lucky button.
- Is it really lucky?
- Has been for me.
Hmm.
You may have it if you like.
- It's okay.
- Look, I only have one,
so I'll never be able to use it
again.
It's my gift to you,
so you'll always remember me.
Hey, Georgie gives me stuff
all the time.
She's even making me this
jacket.
She's not going to
charge me nothing for it.
Hmm. Wait.
Who's Georgie?
It's just an old nickname I
have.
Here, take it. I'll even teach
you
how to sew it
on the garment of your choice.
Help me pick out something
for Jimbo's jacket.
Are you leaving?
♪ I'm going to Kansas City ♪
♪ Kansas City here I come ♪
You really should stay in
tonight.
Daddy, you know I got to work.
- You work at night?
- Yep.
I'm a costume designer
for the most prestigious
musical review show in Kansas
City, perhaps the entire
Midwest.
- What's it called?
- "Doppelganger."
- Well, that sounds dumb.
- Excuse me.
Do you know what a doppelganger
is?
- No.
- Yeah.
Well, you better consult
that dictionary, boy.
I could use your help with
Jimbo.
You don't need to go
gallivanting.
Jimbo is sleeping,
and I have a job, Daddy.
Can we please not?
For one night, can we not do
this?
Just let me go.
Let me go, and let me be me.
My mom's home.
I am trying.
It may not seem like it, but I
am trying.
Mom?
Mom? Mom!
What's wrong?
It's 8:30.
Oh, um...
I'm off today, baby.
Can you make yourself some
cereal?
But what about Brandon?
- I'm not going into the city
today.
- Mom!
It has to be another day.
Come on, Mom! You promised!
Fine! Dad will take me!
He can't, baby. He's not here.
He's never here.
Where is he, anyway? Where is
he?
I'm calling his work.
When are you coming home?
What? I don't want to be a big
brother!
Stop calling, you lying asshole!
Stop calling!
Yuuhh!
Hey, Tate. You okay?
Baby, why don't you
just come over here with us?
You know what? I bet he's got
another woman over there.
Now, that's exceedingly
speculative.
They've just moved out here.
Why would they rent a house out
here?
Because he's got someone in
the city
and Frannie's trying to keep
him away from her
geographically.
You've been watching too many
afternoon drama programs
on the television.
Okay, but mark my words,
Daddy.
He's been double dipping.
Maybe he has a drinking
problem.
Maybe that's your problem.
Hello?
Yeah. He's here, Junior.
It's your good son. He forgot to
ask,
so you can tell him my ass
is doing just fine.
George.
I wasn't aware of
your presence out here.
- What is this?
- This is compost.
- Huh?
- Look it up.
I don't have my dictionary
with me.
Giving up on academia?
No. It just doesn't tell me
what the word really means.
This compost is rotting
vegetation.
Like stinky old vegetables?
Primarily, but they act as
a nutrient for new vegetation.
- My dad is having another baby.
- What, your mom and dad?
No. My dad and some lady
that works at his office.
He's leaving me and my mom
to make a new family with her.
He's such a cliche.
Do you know what that means?
I do. Oh, Tate.
How do you stay in the lines
so good, Georgie?
Channeling Max Factor, baby.
What are you doing with that?
George.
Preparing to protect myself
if need be.
From who?
Is someone messing with you?
You don't have a clue.
None of y'all have any Goddamn
idea
what I gotta go through on a
daily basis
just to live my life, just to be
myself.
I swear, I can't wait
to get the fuck out of here.
- Georgie!
- Gossamer!
Gossamer. My name is Gossamer.
Dammit, Jimbo, for the past 7
years,
all I've asked you to do
is to call me by my name.
Why can't you remember that?
I'm sorry, Gossamer.
I promise I won't forget again.
I mean, why is it so
difficult?
Why is all of this so hard?
I'm living in a cage, Jimbo.
All I see is bars, closed doors,
and me being stuck here
for the rest of my life.
Hell, even if I save up enough
money, things may not even be
better in New York.
They may not be better nowhere,
so tell me that there's
something out there better
for me.
It is. I know it is.
It's going to be better.
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
It's time to get up.
Fedora.
Easy, a hat,
usually a felt hat, I think.
Fetlock.
Is that something to do with
a horse or part of a horse?
Wow, you're actually smart.
Faggot.
What's the word?
Faggot. F-A-G-G-O-T.
You found one I don't know.
What's the dictionary say?
Never mind. How about gambit?
- Tate.
- What is gambit?
Tate, it's okay to ask.
What does it mean?
A faggot is a cruel name
for a person who likes someone
who's the same sex they are,
like if a boy likes or loves
another boy
as more than just a friend.
Like if a boy wanted
to kiss another boy?
Yes.
Well, why isn't it in the
dictionary?
Bad words aren't in
the dictionary, and we should
never use it.
Any other questions?
Can we have Gossamer
and Edward over for dinner?
Yes, and Jimbo?
Yes, definitely Jimbo.
Well, that's going to be fun.
Gooseberry.
Gooseberry? It's a berry.
It's a little berry.
It's a poisonous berry.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Did she bring you her
tuna noodle casserole?
- What is in that?
- She won't tell.
It's her secret recipe.
Daddy thinks it's shoe polish.
I said it tastes like shoe
polish.
Well, either way, it was so
chewy we couldn't eat it,
and it clogged up the disposal.
Man, she's been bringing
those things to us for years
ever since Mama died.
And we don't have the heart
to ask her to stop,
though God knows we've hinted.
And hinted and hinted.
I like the tuna noodle
casserole.
- No!
- Ew.
- It cleans out my bowels.
- Shoe polish.
Oh, Tater, it's 10:30,
way past bedtime.
Oh, no.
School starts next week.
We've got to get you on
schedule.
But I'm not tired.
Well, this old man certainly
is. We should get going.
Say good night, go brush
your teeth, and I'll be
upstairs in a sec.
- Okay. Good night.
- Good night.
Wait, can Gossamer tuck me in?
If she wants to.
- Race you upstairs.
- Oh, you're on.
Bet I'll beat you!
Last one up is a rotten egg.
- I ain't no rotten egg.
- We needed this.
So did we. Thank you.
So did I.
Oh!
Whoo!
Fran, Tate, hello.
Tater?
Where's Tate?
- Get out.
- Where the hell is he?
How dare you break in here.
"Break in." My name is on the
lease, Frannie.
I've been calling here umpteen
times a day for weeks now.
Oh, yes, we have been
so impressed with your
dialing skills.
Your concern is so Goddamn
apparent.
- Yeah, well, I am concerned.
- Oh, bullshit. You left us.
We're splitting up, Frannie.
That's what happens.
Somebody leaves. Jesus, you
don't just stick around
treading in the waters of
misery.
Oh, well, that's so easy
for you to say.
You're already swimming
in another fucking pool.
Oh, you seem to forget,
Miss Holier Than Thou,
that I'm not the only bad guy
here, okay?
You cheated on me first, you,
Frances.
That was a long time ago
before Tate, and you know it.
It was just your misfortune
that he didn't love you back.
You asshole.
You'd be doing the exact
same thing that I'm doing.
If he had snapped his fingers,
you would have left me in a
second.
You would have been long gone,
and you know it.
Where's Tate, Frances?
He's fine.
He's at a new friend's house.
Now get out.
Slow down, Tate.
Got to watch yourself. Oh.
Hey, you got your bag?
Tate.
Hey, buddy.
What are you doing, Tate?
Are you listening to me?
Come here. Get over here.
Come on. I'll go with you.
Get over here.
Come over here.
God, Tate, don't act so happy to
see me.
I missed you, buddy.
What in the hell is that?
We haven't met, Mr. Milliken.
I'm Edward Bryant.
We haven't? I thought maybe
when we moved in--
No, we did not.
Well, now we have.
- Are you going to leave again?
- No. Hey.
Come here.
I came here to spend some time
with you.
Okay, buddy? Do you want
to go to the ballpark?
We can practice a few grounders.
We can get a couple
of root beer floats at A&amp;W.
How does that sound?
Come on, Tater.
I haven't seen you in weeks.
Let's just get out of here just
for a little bit, just us guys.
We should probably consult Mrs.
Milliken before you take
Tate anywhere.
- Mister, uh...
- Bryant.
Yeah, that's right, Mr.
Bryant.
Thank you for taking an interest
in my son.
These past few weeks
have found him in your care
for more than what is
acceptable.
I found it perfectly
acceptable
to assist Mrs. Milliken
in Tate's care, Mr. Milliken.
That's nice of you, but...
your help is no longer needed.
I'm back now,
so if you wouldn't mind
leaving me and my son alone.
Mr. Milliken, let me be clear.
I will not allow you to
remove Tate from the premises
until I hear directly from Mrs.
Milliken that you have her
permission.
Listen, neighbor,
contrary to what you've
probably heard about me,
I'm not a bad guy.
Frances, she isn't innocent in
all this.
I'm neither judge nor jury,
Mr. Milliken.
My sole concern is Tate's
wellbeing.
Red rover, red rover,
we thought we'd come over.
Well, perhaps if you had
that kind of concern
for your own son,
you wouldn't have this freak
on your hands.
- Sticks and stones, little man.
- I know what you are.
And I know what you are.
Faggot, don't think I won't lay
you out just 'cause you're
wearing a dress.
Yeah, well, this is my
ass-kicking dress.
Stop!
Just stop.
What's going on?
Billy?
Just trying to take my son
to the ballpark,
trying to give him
some father-and-son time.
- I don't want to go.
- Then you don't have to.
Go inside.
I suppose we should depart now.
Thank you, Edward.
- I apologize if we intruded.
- I don't.
You can't just keep him from me.
I won't. Let's just see how
interested
you are in Tate when your new
baby comes.
This is a nice family
you put together, Frances. Ha.
Court should be interesting.
Hey, babe. Oh, honey.
Aah!
What you fucking looking at,
Grandpa?
- Hey, Grandpa!
- Whoo hoo hoo!
Hello. I need to report
a missing person--
My son.
- Mom!
♪ Found your way
upstream ♪
- Your son.
- Yes, he's a transsexual,
a cross-dresser, if you will,
but he's still a male
anatomically.
- History of mental illness?
- No.
- Drug use?
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
- Why are the police here?
- Tate. I'm sorry, Edward.
Where's Gossamer?
I don't know, Tate, missing.
That's why the police are here.
Well, did you look?
We can all go help look for her.
I must get back to the
officers now.
Of course.
Mom, we just have to look
in all of her favorite places.
Tate, police will find her.
We just have to wait.
They'll find her, baby. Come on.
Come on.
Thank you.
How are you doing?
Coping, I suppose.
How's Tate?
Confused, heartbroken.
Well, we both are.
Edward, can I do anything?
Is there anything that we can do
to--
No, no, but I thank you for
wanting to.
First couple of days, I hoped
he'd run off to New York City.
George has dreamed of working
there
since he was 10 years old.
But to just, you know...
jump up and go and not say
goodbye--
he wouldn't do that.
He wouldn't just leave me.
He'd say something.
George always had something to
say.
- Her real name is George.
- Yes.
George.
He's my child.
I haven't always accepted him.
I was always too hard on him,
too hard,
and now he's gone.
She is gone.
Gossamer is gone.
Oh, Gossamer, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Eight.
Well done.
Go on, get out of here.
Can you help me?
Thanks, Mom.
- Mm-hmm.
- Bye.
Bye, baby.
I miss her.
I miss her too, more than
I have words to tell you.
Edward...
Can I ask you something?
Gossamer was born a boy, wasn't
she?
Yes, Tate, she was.
How come she wanted to be a
girl?
I think she thought she made a
better girl than she did a boy.
It was more natural for her.
Oh. Well, that's okay.
Yeah, that's okay.
Do you think Gossamer
will ever come back?
I'm not sure, Tate.
But this came in the mail for
you today.