You got
a hitch in your giddy-up.
And that can feel never-ending.
But when that overwhelming
urge to self-medicate hits you,
that is exactly
when you need to
lean on someone for help.
It's the only way forward.
You need someone
to help pull you back
on the healthier path.
And that someone
can be a family member,
a neighbor, an old friend...
a new friend.
You know, maybe someone
in this very group.
So, we have all been there.
We are all still there.
And we are all facing
the same four tasks.
One, to accept
the reality of the loss.
Anyone want to continue
with the next one?
To experience the pain of grief.
And the third?
Ronnie?
Adjust to an environment
where the deceased is missing.
And the fourth.
To emotionally relocate
the deceased and move on.
Right.
We all share these tasks.
And we all understand
at least an element
of what you are going through.
This is what binds us together.
All right, that's about all
the time we have for tonight.
Um, does anyone wanna
add anything before we go?
Will?
How about you?
You've been quiet.
You wanna share something?
Uh.
No.
I don't have anything
at the moment.
Of course. In your own time.
All right, well, that does it.
Oh, uh, and just a reminder
for those of you
with court orders,
see me afterwards
and I will get them
signed for you.
See you tomorrow.
- Ronnie. Always a pleasure.
- Thanks.
Take care.
Lydia,
I think that you can work
a little harder to participate
I am doing
the best I can, child.
You have more,
you have great things to share.
All right, that's fine.
You signed it? Thank you.
Yeah, I just wish--
You know, I like to keep
groups like this small.
More intimate.
I find it makes
people feel more comfortable
expressing themselves.
Speaking their truth.
Do you like small groups, Will?
Yeah. Works for me, I guess.
I certainly hope so.
Hey, Will, hold up.
Need a ride someplace?
-No, I'm good.
-I'm Bryan, by the way.
Yeah, I remember.
From the meeting.
-I'm gonna head out.
-It's a group.
We're a group. It's a group.
-Yeah, okay.
-Well, you called it a meeting.
And a meeting could be
different factions coming
together for a brief period,
but a group
functions as a whole.
We help each other.
We're a group.
Right.
So, Bella wants us
to call it a group
and that's what you're saying?
See you next time. In group.
♪ You can find it anywhere ♪
♪ Sniff,
and honey ♪
♪ None of these compare ♪
Bon appétit.
♪ Together,
how I find my own way down ♪
♪ I know the day I choose
will be a good day soon ♪
You need to wake up, brother.
Living one day at a time.
Give you a ride?
Enjoying one moment at a time.
Living one day at a time.
Accepting hardship
as a pathway to peace.
Taking this world as it is.
Not as I would have it.
I gotta keep asking.
Trusting that you
will make all things right.
So that I may be
reasonably happy in this life.
-In this life.
-Bon appétit.
In this life.
And supremely happy forever.
Forever. Forever. Forever.
Forever. Forever,
forever, forever.
Forever.
And that's...
Denial. Anger.
Bargaining. Depression.
Acceptance.
As difficult as it may seem,
it is important
to remind ourselves
that these five
stages of grief--
Bargaining.
That's the one that keeps
sending me down the rabbit hole.
It's like every second
of every waking hour,
it's just...
-I just keep going through the--
-The what-ifs.
Yeah, right,
the fucking what-ifs.
Like, what if--
what if we had left
five minutes later
instead of always insisting that
we leave five minutes early?
Should be a sixth stage.
A sixth stage to grief?
Reversal.
I-- I'm not sure
we understand, Lydia.
What if you could reverse it?
Okay, so, this
is what bargaining is about.
You're bartering with yourself
in your own head
in an attempt
to change something
that cannot be changed.
- But what if there was a way?
- Lydia.
There are those what-ifs again
and that is
a dangerous game to play.
Yeah.
Whatever you say.
Okay, that was a very--
Will.
Something on your mind?
It just seems to me that
if there's five stages
to this thing then...
I don't know, it just seems to--
to close our minds
to other options.
Other options?
Options, stages, levels,
I don't know, uh,
just seems to limit us.
Well, Will,
I appreciate the, uh,
many levels of your opinion,
I can assure you that
what Lydia is dealing with is--
Not talking about her.
Uh-oh.
-Unsatisfied customer?
-Oh, no. Not at all.
Uh, Will was just
expressing concern for Lydia.
- Oh.
Thank you, Will.
Take that all
into consideration.
Almost like they
don't want us to get better.
How about you?
-You feeling any better yet?
-Not really.
No, not at all.
You're not like the others.
I could tell.
So, why are you stuck here?
My heart got ripped open.
I was sad.
Then angry.
And sad again.
Then angry all the time.
Shit happened.
And they thought
I needed some group time
to get my head right.
- Is it working?
- No.
I'm horrible.
Constantly horrible.
But I'mma get better on my own.
I'mma feel better.
Real soon.
100%.
I'mma see my baby again.
Let me give you a ride.
Come on.
I could use the company.
No, I'm good.
Could use the exercise.
All right, well, suit yourself.
I can take a hint.
I'll see you in group.
There you go, you got it.
See you in group, friend.
♪ You can find it anywhere ♪
Bon appétit.
♪ Together,
how I find my own way down ♪
♪ I know the day I choose
will be a good day soon ♪
Ah!
You need to wake up, brother.
You see it.
All the time, every day.
After a while, death,
or the finality of it, you know.
Just doesn't quite
pack the punch it used to.
And that day
was like any other day.
I-- I had already seen misery.
Already seen death.
All in a day's work, right?
So, I'm on my way home
and I get one last call.
And three blocks
from the house...
it was a single car collision,
one person,
I was third on the scene.
I get there and I-- I--
I make my way
down the embankment.
It didn't look
that bad, you know?
Just upside down there and--
and the creek bed--
Dunbar Creek, uh, you know,
ankle deep, usually.
But shit, we had all
that rain the night before.
It was like
God turned on the faucet,
forgot to turn it off, you know?
She never had a chance.
She hit her head.
She's just hanging there
upside down and
her head in the water.
All that life ahead of her.
That was the one.
That was the one
that got stuck right here.
That was the one.
Thank you, Bryan.
That was very brave and
you are wonderful for sharing.
Insanity is doing
the same thing over and over
and expecting
a different result.
Now, that's often misattributed
to Mr. Albert Einstein,
but the point is clear.
I know that
dealing with
overwhelming grief day after day
can make you feel
like you are insane.
And we all know what
the result is going to be
when we express
our grief to each other.
A little bit of relief,
no matter how brief,
from the guilt,
anger, sadness,
whatever it is that
we are feeling inside.
Now, let me be clear.
There is nothing
wrong with temporary relief.
No matter what stage we are at.
But if you begin to
live life only for that relief,
for the next blackout
from reality,
you are not learning.
You're not growing.
You are not healing.
So, to make Einstein,
or whoever said
that quote happy,
We're going to do something
a little different.
Instead of expressing
our grief to each other,
we are going to
write a note or a letter
to our departed.
Something you
want to add, Lydia?
No. I'm all set.
Not interested in
breaking the cycle, Lydia?
I'm almost done
with my cycle forever.
Thanks.
What's that supposed to mean?
Sounds like lady problems to me.
Stupid motherfuckas.
-Good to see you.
-So you almost there?
-You feeling better?
-Damn right.
The shit ends tomorrow.
Take care, Sam.
- See you outside.
- Yeah.
Something I can
help you with, man?
Because if this is
about a ride, I'm good.
Brother, you're stuck
in a shit cycle right now,
going round and round and round,
and nowhere in that circle
is the starting point
to the healing process.
You don't know
anything about me.
I know what those
cough drops are for.
And that is not the answer.
That much I know.
Brother, waking life,
it can be tolerable.
Not perfect, but tolerable.
But it starts by getting
out of the circle of despair.
It sure sounds like
you had that memorized.
So, let me guess.
It's vodka on the way in
because it has
the weakest scent, right?
Then pop a few menthols
and you're on cruise control
through a whole new group.
Right?
And on the way home,
pick up a bottle
of your favorite stuff.
Just to get you
through the night.
Am I getting warmer?
I mean, I was just trying
to check off the boxes, okay?
Taking it one day at a time.
One day at a time.
That's the secret sauce.
Time.
It can be your best friend
or your worst enemy, Will.
You decide.
Yeah. Time could
be your best friend.
If you lay down
and let her fuck you.
But not me.
You wanna stop living in
their dream world of despair?
What do you mean? Like drugs?
I'm talking about
not living with the reality
they keep preaching to us.
You interested?
Yes.
There's this place
hidden away.
Follow these directions.
Go to that place.
Tell 'em I sent you.
Go to that place, Will.
Then, you'll see.
You'll open your eyes.
No more sadness.
Only joy.
Home, sweet home.
It's not much but...
they say home is
really in here and here, right?
Yeah.
Keeps demons away.
You're not a demon, are ya?
No, I can't say that I am.
That's good for your sake.
So, what are you--
Just living out here or--
or passing through?
I'm sorry, you're, um--
Von.
-My name's Von.
-I'm Will.
I'm here on
Tuesdays and Thursdays, Will.
Okay.
So, what brings you out
this way tonight?
Um, Lydia.
Lydia, she said
that I should come here.
That I should come see you.
Lydia.
But your path and her
path are very different.
I can tell.
Though no two paths
are ever the same.
What did Lydia tell ya?
Just that I should come see you
and there'll be no more sadness.
You experienced loss.
Take this.
Draw, sketch, paint.
Do whatever you want.
Put it on that canvas
and bring it back to me.
You want me
to just draw you a picture?
You can do whatever you want.
But whatever you do,
do it for you.
And then bring it back.
Bullshit.
Yeah.
Ah!
You need to wake up, brother.
"...but instead,
I'm here by myself.
And so, I begin another night
and tomorrow
will be another day.
Another day in my new reality.
I'll never stop hurting.
Never stop missing you.
But I promised to
see a way forward
until we've reunited."
Thank you, Ronnie.
Will, let's hear yours.
Um, no, I-- I'm not ready.
The exercise is
not meant to be perfect.
It's not even
meant to be finished.
The exercise, Will, is to share.
Come on, Will.
It's okay, give it a read.
"My...
sweet Shelly. I--
That's it.
It's all I have right now,
I'm just, um...
I can't find the words.
You said her name.
That's a brave step.
And Shelly is?
She's my daughter.
All right, well,
that's about it for tonight,
um, but before we go,
I do want to address something.
As you have probably noticed,
Lydia is not here tonight
and moving forward,
she will no longer
be a part of this group.
Now, of course,
we wish her the best
on her healing journey,
but I would like
to remind you all that
when one in the group
refuses to do the tasks,
it can damage the healing
of the whole group.
Sometimes permanently.
See you guys tomorrow. Oh.
Hey, Bryan.
Will. Good meeting tonight,
right?
Hey, I see you doing the work
and I am proud of you, brother.
-Okay.
-I knew I'd get through to you.
We're gonna have
your head thinking straight
before you know it.
So, I'm curious.
Why isn't Lydia coming back?
She claims she
doesn't need the group anymore.
So, just like that, she's cured.
She believes her daughter
has come back to her.
-Come back?
-Yeah.
Her departed has come back.
It's tragic, really.
I mean, you've heard
her babbling on, Will.
Obviously, it's impossible.
What are we talking about here?
Turning back time?
I mean, we--
we can only try to help,
-but sometimes we--
-Fail.
Did not fail.
She chose not to accept help.
Yeah. Sounds tragic.
-Will! What the fuck was that?
-Not tonight, Bryan.
Hey. I know this is about
checking a list for you, man,
but pulling shit like that
is only going to prolong this.
The more you resist
what is here to help you,
the longer it's going to
take for you to see the light.
Don't try and be
a cop with me, man.
How dare you say that to me?
I'm here to help you.
What's going on in there
is not helping anyone.
It's just rehashing
the same horrible shit
over and over again.
That's the cycle.
You need to wake up, brother.
I was wondering
if you were gonna
make your way up here tonight.
You know, it's funny,
everybody can
express themselves.
So, everyone is an artist.
What comes out of here...
it ends up there.
The artist's history.
A life lived.
Lessons learned.
Growth. Improvements.
Discovery of truth.
You know, Lydia is
making some pretty bold claims.
And people are making some
pretty bold claims about Lydia.
Lydia is on her own path,
and you are on yours, Will.
This your daughter in this?
It's okay if you don't know.
This kind of work,
it exists in two spaces.
A physical space
and a psychological space.
-You are truly a bright soul.
-Oh, I don't know about that.
I want you to look at
all those souls up there.
Look.
Did you know when a star dies,
it continues to shine
its light across the universe
for many millenniums to come?
You just got to be
looking for that light.
So, what are you willing to do?
-To do for what?
-You know for what, Will.
Lydia was willing
to approach her obstacle
with an open mind.
And with truly open eyes.
Now, all her sadness is gone.
There's nothing I wouldn't do.
-For your sadness to be gone.
-To end the cycle.
Me and my daughter. Shelly.
Oh, no, no. I-- I--
I couldn't take your vinyl.
These are meant
for someone who needs them.
And your path has
led you to need these.
I don't know.
What you got in there?
I got a little of this
and a little of that.
Listen to 'em.
See which one speaks to you.
All right. Okay. Yeah,
I could do that.
I-- I can do that.
But there are rules, Will.
You must listen
with a clear and open mind.
Free of outside influences.
Yeah, I got it.
Sometimes, what we think is lost
is not lost at all.
Just needs to be rediscovered.
A clear and open mind, Will.
That's your path forward.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
...to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them...
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Do you want to
play catch, Daddy Monster?
Yeah, I got one.
...your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
Your mind is--
Is that you, baby girl?
Do you want to
play catch, Daddy Monster?
Yeah, I got one.
Come on.
Von!
- Von!
- Hey, Will.
Where did you get
those records from?
-You played one of mine?
-Yes, I played yours.
With a clear mind?
That was your voice.
Are you doing this?
There's this--
there's this red ball
that my daughter
used to play with.
And-- and Von,
that ball came rolling
right up to me.
It was as if Shelly,
she just rolled it
to me herself.
And then
I played the record again,
-nothing happened.
-Yeah, that can happen.
That can happen--
Come on.
You gotta work with me, man.
You got-- you gotta
give me something here,
cause I need to know
that I'm not going crazy.
You're on the path now, Will.
You're on the path.
There was a time,
when I was experimenting
with recording.
At first,
it was just music, noise.
And then I started
to introduce the spoken word
and as time passed by...
strange things
started to happen.
The recordings actually...
started doing things.
Good things, Will, good things.
To people that had open minds.
But then you got to be
careful what you wish for.
Because...
well...
folks don't always like
what they discover
about themselves.
That's the next one, Will.
So, there are some after this?
That is the next one.
Von.
Von!
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
The burden you carry
is heavy and fierce.
Vanquish it now or your heart,
it will pierce.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
The burden you carry
is heavy and fierce.
Vanquish it now, or your heart,
it will pierce.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
The burden you carry
is heavy and fierce.
Vanquish it now or your heart,
it will pierce.
I'm right here, Goblin.
Daddy, look at
the wind chime I made.
You made that,
Goblin? It's beautiful.
Fuck.
Von!
Hey, Von. Hello.
You're on the path now, Will.
Lydia, where did you come from?
-Where's Von?
-Don't leave your path.
Keep your goal in sight
and don't let them stop you.
I did.
I'm so happy now.
Lydia, I'm so--
I'm so confused,
and I don't know
- what to do here, I--
- You know what to do.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
The burden you carry
is heavy and fierce.
Vanquish it now or your heart,
it will pierce.
Embrace the pain
that dwells within
for healing can start
once you let it in.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
The burden you carry
is heavy and fierce.
Vanquish it now or your heart,
it will pierce.
Embrace the pain
that dwells within
for healing can start
once you let it in.
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
The burden you carry
is heavy and fierce.
Vanquish it now or your heart,
it will--
There's one mystery solved.
You're alive.
You okay?
What's the matter, Will?
You look like
you've seen a goblin.
How'd you find me?
We know things.
Mind if I come in?
Nice place, Will.
This room could
use a little light.
But nice.
You mind telling me
what you're doing here?
I was on my way out the door,
headin' home.
Dispatch gets a call.
Welfare check.
Normally I'd say, "Fuck it.
I got pot roast
waiting for me at home."
In dispatch,
they get the address,
name of the owner.
You.
So, I say, "Fuck it.
That pot roast can wait."
Was it worth it, brother?
I haven't had a drink
since last night.
-I swear, on my daughter.
-Don't.
Do not.
Never swear on that.
All you had to do
was reach out to me, man.
I was ready, willing and able.
But then you had to have
yourself a three-day bender.
I told you I haven't
had a drink in 24 hours.
Oh, Will, just stop.
Stop it, okay?
Look, I get what
you're going through, man.
I get it.
But there's what
you're going through
and there's what
you're required to go through.
Bender? Three days?
What are you talking about?
Okay, okay.
You skip three nights of group,
refuse to answer your calls,
then you get
a welfare check called in.
You know how
this thing works, Will.
Too many strikes.
-Fuck you, man.
-Oh, fuck me?
-Yeah, fuck you.
-Okay.
You know I was there earlier.
You're just trying
to mess with me now,
like some kind
of healing strategy.
Oh, yeah,
I saw you three nights ago
and you were pretty charged up.
Man, I should have
come up here a long time ago.
You know, Bella's really
torn up about this.
Losing you from group
so soon after Lydia?
She's really beating herself up.
Yes, I know.
No, but he will soon.
We have to stay united
on this, okay?
It's the only way.
What do we always say?
"This too shall pass."
In the end,
I promise you, you will see,
this was the best for everyone,
the best for you, the best for--
Hey, listen, I gotta go, okay?
Yeah.
How you feeling?
What was that?
That was a work thing.
So...
to recap.
You left the meeting?
About an hour ago.
You say an hour,
I say three days.
You left the meeting.
Then you went to visit
this homeless man
who lives in the woods?
A man you've been...
visiting and speaking with.
So, this fellow, he...
He gives you records,
and these records, they--
-Only some of them.
-Some of these records...
have brought back...
...items that
were in photographs
with your little girl, right?
Okay.
Let me tell you what I see.
I see a man who has
refused help over and over.
I see a man who insists on
drinking himself into a coma
every single night,
refusing to face
his new reality.
You hit the sauce extra hard,
blackout, lose track of time,
start going through
your daughter's old stuff.
Start drinking again,
repeat the process and, brother,
Three days...
gone.
After we lost our Shelly...
her mother took all her stuff.
Including these.
So, it would be impossible
for me to pull out these things.
Look.
I'm not saying this is the case,
but is there any reason
your ex would be
maybe coming in here?
Poking around, moving things,
trying to...
bait you into some sort of a--
-Will?
-Yeah.
Is this you?
Me?
Will, I-- I don't-- I don't know
-what you're talking about.
-Who put you up to this?
- Me?
- Who put you up to this?
I can assure you I have no idea
who or what
you're talking about here.
How does she get to you?
-Are you fucking--
-Hey, hey, brother.
Let's take a breath here,
you and me, okay?
Take a seat
and let's count to ten, okay?
Tell me what
you're thinking here.
Will.
Will!
Shit.
Daddy Monster? Hi, Daddy.
Hi, Goblin.
Daddy Monster,
I've been practicing
holding my breath.
Can you get me the bubble
blower under the sink?
Sure.
Ah!
Easy, Will.
Is that thing loaded?
She--
-she was here.
-Who was, Will?
Shelly.
She was here.
She was getting ready
for her bath.
These are her things. It worked.
How about you and I take a walk.
Von!
Uh, wait.
Who's-- Lydia.
Okay.
All right.
Lydia was right here.
She told me that
I needed to stay on my path,
and that--
that she was happy now.
Well, that's impossible.
What is?
Will, Lydia is dead.
She killed herself
two nights ago.
No. No.
Where is he?
I know he's here somewhere.
Von is here. He's here.
Oh, God.
"The victim,
Shelly Foster, age nine,
was taken from the home
to Hope Memorial Hospital,
where she was
later pronounced dead.
-Cause of death was ruled..."
-Accidental drowning.
-Where did you get that?
-Inside, in a box.
"The distraught mother
claims that she had arrived
at the house with
her friend to discuss
custody issues
with her estranged husband,
Will Foster."
Who is this man, Will?
And why would he have
these clippings about you?
About your daughter.
It's-- it's Lydia.
Lydia, she gave a map.
"Your mind is open...
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear."
And that's what he'd say
on the records?
Yeah.
And then after a while,
he would say to...
"Embrace the pain
that dwells within.
The healing starts
once you let it in."
And there was another two.
Those were different.
"The burden that you carry,
it's heavy and fierce.
Vanquish it now
or your heart, it will pierce."
And then this last one, "The
ending must occur to begin anew,
but only in the pure
can this be true."
And you memorized that?
All the repetition.
And now there's nothing on here?
When you play it
back again, nothing.
Bible verses.
-What?
-These are Bible verses.
Not written in
the correct catalog format,
but they're-- they're scripture.
-Which one was first?
-Matthew.
Matthew 7:7.
"Ask, and it shall
be given unto you.
Seek and you shall find."
John 9:25 next, right?
"Whereas once I was blind,
now I can see."
And the latest one?
It's a...
It's a story about Lazarus.
A man who was
raised from the dead.
And you memorized all this, huh?
Repetition.
Sunday school.
Lots of it.
So, it works.
It works, it's working.
Shelly....
she's not gone.
She's just stuck.
She's gonna come back,
'cause I'm gonna bring her back.
It's just like Lydia said--
Will, L-- Lydia let
her grief consume her.
Okay? She went chasing a ghost
and it took her life, too.
She was getting better.
Happier.
No, delusion could
seem like that, Will.
And what we're
talking about here it-- it...
It's supposed to be impossible.
Yeah, but I saw her.
And I know you saw it.
You saw that it works.
I can see what's
going on here, okay?
And I can help you.
I will help you.
But, Will...
you cannot let
this take over you,
like it took over Lydia.
You have to be strong, Will.
I have to get my girl back.
I have to get the next one.
That could be the one
that brings her back.
Okay, here's what I'm gonna do.
You're gonna go back
to group tomorrow night.
Listen, we're gonna talk
to Bella.
We are going
to do everything we can
to help you
with the judge, okay?
Okay?
- But--
- No, hey, hey!
You're gonna do this for me.
But more importantly,
for yourself.
And no more booze, okay?
Get yourself to group
tomorrow night.
And then we will go from there
to fix all of this.
And I'll find
this man for you. Von.
How?
How-- how you can find him?
I got resources.
We'll get this resolved.
I promise.
Thank you.
So, tomorrow.
-No alcohol
-And?
I'll be there.
I'll be at the meeting.
Okay.
Huh.
You know, I think
I left my cell phone in there.
I'll grab it, I'll grab it.
All right.
See you tomorrow.
-Which one of you did it?
-Bryan, he has a gun!
Hm? Which one of you?
Which one of you called in
the bullshit welfare check?
Hm?
Which one of you is watching me?
You, motherfucker? You, Stan?
Okay, Will, listen to me.
You and I just need to talk.
What have you been up to?
Hm?
You little fucking snake.
What have you been up to?
-Where is he?
-Will, let's just calm down.
I'm sure we could
work something out--
No, you shut the fuck up!
You shut the fuck up,
'cause for all I know,
you killed Lydia.
You want to keep her quiet.
You don't want
to hear the truth.
Okay, everybody, relax.
I know Will,
and Will is
a very reasonable man.
Bryan, you don't know shit.
And I've had about enough
of that fucking,
"I'm here
to help you," bullshit!
Von is in custody.
Okay? I had to do it, Will.
I had to call it in.
It's my job.
A man was squatting
on public property.
I see you're trying
to keep Shelly away from me.
She's not gone, Bryan.
She's stuck.
She's stuck,
and Von is the only one
that can bring her home.
But you don't want me to
get my Shelly back, do you?
Hm? It's been you.
It's been fucking you
all along, Bryan!
I can get what you want.
I was there when
they brought him in, okay?
They brought in
all his possessions.
I processed it.
Guess what?
There's another record.
It's the one you want.
- You're lying.
- Mm-mmm.
It's the last record.
It might be the one to do it.
To bring your daughter back.
Shelly.
-Where is it?
-It's at the station.
So, let's you and I,
we'll go get it.
Leave everyone else out of this.
What do you say?
I say yeah.
- Okay.
- Let's go to the station.
But you're bringing
this fucking bitch too.
Okay. No, Bryan, it's okay.
-It's okay.
-Let's go.
It's okay. It's okay.
Oh, Jesus.
He's usually talking by now.
-Man, if we just--
-No, shut up!
Come on.
Shelly.
You need to wake up, brother.
Will, where's Shelly?
What did you say?
Now, Bryan!
Your mind is open,
your heart is clear.
Now, open them both
to what is dear.
This your daughter in this?
- Jesus!
- Hey!
You're not going to
be needing that, Will.
-Oh, this?
-Easy, brother.
Will, just give me Shelly
and we'll be out of here.
I think
she's staying with me tonight.
You know that's
not the arrangement.
The arrangement?
The arrangement,
like the one we had,
not to fuck other people?
Like that one
you're talking about?
Hey, come on, come on,
this is not you, man.
You don't know me, man.
You don't know
any fucking thing about me.
Will, this is insane.
You're pointing
a gun at me, at Bella.
What would Shelly think
if she saw what
you're doing right now?
Don't. Don't you say her name.
Whatever you think
about Bella and I,
this is not how
you want this to go down.
Will, where is Shelly?
Shelly, no.
Ah!
The burden you carry
is heavy and fierce.
Vanquish it now or your heart,
it will pierce.
Will.
Brother, you're stuck
in a shit cycle right now,
going round and round and round.
You need someone
to help pull you back
on the healthier path.
And that someone
can be a new friend.
Yeah, maybe someone
in this very group.
Embrace the pain
that dwells within,
for healing can start
once you let it in.
John 15-13.
"Greater love
has no man than this,
to lay down one's life
for one's friends."
Bible verses.
These are Bible verses.
John 15-12.
"My commitment..."
Can I have a cigarette?
Lydia, no,
you can't have a cigarette.
Can I have a cigarette?
No.
Please, can I talk to Dr. Von?
Can I talk to Dr. Von?
- Please.
- Not now.
Dr. Von helps us feel better.
They don't want us
to get better.
Almost like they
don't want us to get better.
-Come on.
-One day at a time.
That's right, my dear.
That's right. Come on.
One day at a time.
Lydia's on her own path,
and you are on yours, Will.
That's it.
Bon appétit.
This kind of work,
it exists in two spaces.
The physical space
and the psychological space.
Beautiful, Will.
That's beautiful.
You know what I see?
I see a dad leading
his daughter by the hand.
Embrace the pain
that dwells within,
for healing can start
once you let it in.
It's a beautiful night,
huh, Will?
You know,
when a star dies,
it continues to shine its light
across the universe
for many millenniums to come.
You just gotta be
looking for that light.
You're on the path now, Will.
Well done.
An open mind and a clear heart
is a wonderful path for you.
You're a bright soul.
See you later, Will.
Looking good, kid.
Stay on that path.
The ending must occur
to begin anew.
But only in the pure
can this be true.
doctor] He's still not
coherent enough, Mrs. Foster.
The new neurosonic treatment
with Dr. Von
seems to be working.
His last MRI shows
much higher brain activity.
We-- we just need
to keep being patient.
- I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
I'm going to keep coming back.
And I'm going
to keep bringing this.
And one day
you're gonna feel better.
Better enough to sign this.
And then I will be free.
And you will, too.
The ending must occur
to begin anew.
But only in the pure
can this be true.
You need to wake up, Will.
The ending must occur
to begin anew.
But only in the pure
can this be true.
The ending must occur
to begin anew.
But only in the pure
can this be true.
The ending must occur
to begin anew.
- Will!
- But only in the pure
can this be true.
The ending must occur
to begin anew.
But only in the pure
can this be true.
- The ending must occur
- Daddy.
to begin anew.
But only in the pure
can this be true.
Daddy!
The ending must occur
to begin anew.
But only in the pure
can this be true.
Bye, Will.