All the names of these /
The four quite oddly
Sorry, bravery And pride
I feel didnt 30 minutes
[music playing]
I swear to God, if you
pick up one more ball,
any ball, for as long as you
live, you're a dead boy walking.
[groaning]
[moaning]
- Oh, my God. - Honey, are you OK?
- What happened? - What happened to Adam?
I was smacked into the baseball at me,
through a window, through the glass.
That's a lie, you little weasel.
Sam, that nose ring wouldn't really
fly up military school, do you think?
Mom, Adam's smirking.
Look at him.
Hey, get up.
Who taught you that girls were stupid?
Huh? I know it wasn't me.
So let me give you a
word of warning, pal.
You can only push us
so far before we snap.
You know, the hormone thing?
So you get up, you get that ball,
and you bring it to me right now.
[clicking]
Save the drama. We're all on to you.
Thank you.
And you're paying for the window.
But I--
[sighing]
[clicking]
Thanks for waiting.
He didn't call. We were hungry.
I figured you'd be really late, as usual.
Mm-hmm.
He did miss all the excitement, though.
Adam broke another window.
What does that make this year, honey, 10?
It's a good thing your dad worked so hard
to pay for all that.
You said I had to pay for it.
May I?
Mm-hmm.
Since you're only 12 and
you don't really have a job,
your money isn't really yours at all.
Yes, it is. It's my allowance.
Where do you think that money comes from?
Dad, you idiot.
All right, everybody, calm down, please.
Excitement's over.
May I?
[sighing]
Jessica.
Jack, we need to talk.
About what?
About this relationship.
Oh, God.
Please, just not again.
All we do is fight.
I don't want to live that way anymore.
Everybody fights.
Some people say they're married their
whole lives with a lot
less love than we have.
I don't want to be one of those people.
I don't want to spend the rest of my life
regretting that we all had a chance to be
happy and didn't take it.
We're not good together anymore.
Come on, Katie.
We can try one more time.
Don't we have other
kids at least that much?
We can go see that therapist guy.
We tried that. It hasn't worked.
Don't you remember when
we were first married?
And you thought I was
funny and sexy and attractive?
You don't even laugh at my jokes anymore.
You haven't wanted to touch me in ages.
And in the past few
years, nothing I do is right.
I think it's destroying all of us.
I don't understand how this happened.
[sighs]
Okay, okay. I'll go find a place.
You stay here with the kids.
Kids need their moms a lot
more than they need their dads.
Well, that's not true.
Well, maybe it is and maybe it isn't.
You guys should stay here.
I don't think we
should tell them right away.
At least not until you find a place.
Right.
It wasn't all bad, was it?
No, Jack, it wasn't.
We have two great kids, don't we?
Yeah, we do.
[sighs]
What am I gonna do?
♪ Living alone ♪
♪ I think about the friends I love ♪
♪ But when I die, how
do you tell a phone ♪
♪ Nobody's home ♪
♪ All by myself ♪
♪ Don't wanna be all by myself ♪
♪ Even though it's hard to be sure ♪
♪ Sometimes I feel so insecure ♪
Funny, I'm whole.
♪ And I love so distant and obscure ♪
♪ Living alone ♪
I get it. I get it.
[gunshot]
Take the nose ring out, dear.
We don't do that sort of thing here.
♪ You're there ♪
Thanks for dressing.
You want a little sherry, dear?
Yes, please.
I don't believe I was speaking to you.
Nothing for me, thanks, Mother.
Mary?
- Hi, guys. - Hi, Mary.
- Hi, Mary. - Mary, can
I have a small sherry?
Yes, you can, if you get it yourself.
And I can't cook your whole damn dinner
and serve cocktails, too.
Nor should you, Mary. I'll do it.
Dorothy, what can I get for you?
What I've had every
single night of my life
for the last 50 years, Jack?
- Sherry. - Right.
Kate.
- Kids? - Coke.
It'll rot your teeth.
What do you know?
Children, why don't
you go help your father?
Well, I suppose we can sit down.
Oh, can we?
Keep it up and I'll
leave everything to Mary.
So, what cause have
you taken up this week?
And do bleeding-heart
liberals ever bleed to death?
Could we please not do this, Mother?
Fine. I'll change the subject.
Did you and Jack have
another fight today?
No, we're not fighting anymore, Mother.
We're separating.
So you've had no experience in sales?
No, sure I have.
I sell things to my family all the time.
Like eating
vegetables, doing their homework,
you know, things they don't want to do.
That's the ultimate hard sell.
Well, that's not exactly
what we're selling here.
What I really need is someone with sales
and fashion
experience, and you're not it.
I wouldn't exactly call
what you sell here fashion.
I don't know.
I don't know what I would do with you.
Nice drapes, Martha.
You look fabulous.
You won't be single for long, honey.
No, what, you're not hair stylish,
you're not a manicurist, right?
You're nothing to--
What are you?
Guess I'm someone who knew that streaks
are pretty much finished in the '90s.
Thank you.
Oh, hey, streaks are not--
[phone ringing]
I think we should show
it the week of the 10th,
and let's book the inspection.
When can we get, what, the 15th?
Yes, I'd like to have all that done.
OK.
Terrific.
Thanks.
Can I help you?
Or do you just want
to stand there all day?
I was thinking about
standing here all day.
Sit yourself.
Want to know why?
Sure.
Not the hell.
It's a little slow.
I got time.
Because if you're a
woman rapidly approaching 40,
and you've made the
unbelievably stupid mistake
of thinking that trying to
raise a family was a good thing,
all you ever wanted to do
was be a wife and a mother,
and your children grow up, and they can't
wait to get away from you, and your
marriage is falling apart,
so you try to start over
with no skills whatsoever.
And all you hear is that
damn song all by myself,
then you would just stand here, too.
You're right.
That song's irritating.
You want to come in for a cup of coffee?
OK.
Brad, Mack, this is--
what's your name?
I'm Kate, Kate Mayer.
Hey, Kate, I'm Maggie.
Hi, Maggie.
Which one's Brad and which one's Mack?
Hi, I'm Brad.
I'm just kidding.
I'm McNally, Mack for short.
And this is Brad, just Brad.
Kate's having a really bad day.
She doesn't know
whether to go left or right,
so I invited her in for a cup of Choke.
Great.
Let me get that.
Cream, sugar, black, please.
OK.
Hey, why don't you come take a load off?
Brad?
She won't buy.
Take a break.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about all this.
I was just having a moment out there,
and Maggie here took pity on me.
No, it's fine, really.
No explanation needed.
Look at who I have working for me.
If I didn't hate you
already, I'd take offense to that.
See what I mean?
You don't really need a receptionist.
You're not just offering me this job
because you feel sorry for me.
Assume to be separated, mother of two.
No, I really need a receptionist.
Maggie and I are out all the time,
and Brad doesn't like
to answer the phone, so--
Does he ever talk?
You know, it's not
really a people person.
He's brilliant, just not a people person.
Kind of a bad job for him
to happen, don't you think?
Yeah, he's working on it.
OK, so when do you want me to start?
Well, when's good for you?
How's tomorrow? - Great.
OK.
That's terrific.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah, terrific.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
So you hired him?
Yeah.
She's cute.
Oh, shut up.
Hi.
How was your day?
Good.
I got a job.
Repeat back to me what I just said.
You-- you said you had a
good day and you did the usual.
You don't do that in court, do you?
Do what?
Makeup stuff.
No, I don't make up stuff.
I just said I got a job.
How you got the usual out of that?
I'm not sure.
Wait a second.
You got a job?
What kind of job?
I'm going to be a
receptionist at a real estate office.
A receptionist?
That'll barely cover sitter costs.
What is the point of that?
I mean, come on, Kate.
Isn't that kind of
silly and counterproductive?
Maybe it is, but you got
to start somewhere, Jack.
Bye.
Good morning.
Va-Va-Voom.
Keep your hands off of her, Mac.
I'm gay.
Maggie thinks it's
hysterically funny to make
little homophobic jokes about it.
You're gay?
Yeah, but don't
worry, it's not contagious.
I bet she's never met a gay person
ever less than personal.
How is that possible in 2002?
No, no, no.
I've met a few.
It's just they don't
usually look like you, do they?
I've got a plaid shirt I could slip into.
I tried it once.
Wasn't my cup of tea.
I don't know who really asked you.
I'm sorry.
But if this bothers you--
No, no.
Actually, I think it
probably makes you more interesting
than I thought you were.
Really?
I didn't mean that.
What I meant to say was, I think people
should be able to be whoever they are.
This is your desk.
We set it up for you.
So there you go.
Thank you.
You just answer the phones, haze realty,
you know, transfer calls, take messages.
That's it?
And that's it.
It's kind of like
stealing money, isn't it?
It is kind of.
You know, I think the point to this job
is to have some fun.
Because most of us here haven't had much.
We are the walking wounded.
I am not the walking wounded.
Yes, you are.
No, I'm not.
I don't know why I
put up with this abuse.
How'd you love us?
No, I don't.
Yes, you did.
See, it's not really like stealing money.
Thanks, you guys.
You're making my reentry painless.
Our pleasure.
If you want to see your
kids, then we'll lock up.
OK.
Good night.
Night.
Have a good one.
You too.
You like her.
I can tell.
Will you stop trying to set
me up with every woman that
walks through that damn door?
You know what?
You're an idiot.
Because you believe if a person is gay,
that they like all
people of the same sex.
That we are
indiscriminate, shark-like creatures who
never sleep or are just
looking for our next victim.
Well, guess what?
Some of us actually do discriminate
and don't want to sleep with
every woman who ever lived.
Which, by the way, if that were true,
would include our mothers.
And yes, I like her.
News flash, I like you too.
Doesn't mean I want to
sleep with you either.
Got it?
Got it.
Good.
Let's go, guys.
Should I forward calls to yourself?
No, you won't be able to.
Are you going to be out of rage?
No, you will be.
You're going to put us on the caravan.
It's a caravan.
Jeez, have you read any
magazines, a book, anything?
A caravan's where all the
brokers go on to see all the new
houses that are on the market.
Hey, isn't Brad coming?
You know, he doesn't like the caravans.
Well, why does he come on you?
For sure.
Ready?
I know it's one of my
business, but it seems like Brad's
not very good at his job.
That is correct.
Why does it Mac fire him?
You didn't hear this from me, but Brad
used to be a computer
geek at a dot com.
It went under, and Mac brought him here.
Besides, Mac could never fire anyone.
It's loyalty to the
point of absurdity, isn't it?
Yeah.
This is the part you
really didn't hear from me.
He's her ex-lover's brother.
Well, why doesn't she help him?
That'd be hard.
She's dead.
Yuck.
Maggie.
Sorry.
I think it has potential.
You think everything has potential.
Sorry, she scraped off those crud.
She's too.
She got the new light.
She should get the premade ready to hang
cabinets, get a whole
new line of the cheap
old steel appliances.
He did white white, and
it's a gay man's dream.
What?
Am I right?
[phone ringing]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. [phone ringing]
Hey, it's realty.
May I ask who's calling, please?
Just one moment.
It's a Mr. Brubaker.
Hello, Mr. Brubaker.
Mm-hmm.
Great.
When can I bring over the paperwork?
Uh-huh.
No, tomorrow morning's fine.
OK.
Bye-bye.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You have a tradition here.
Any time a house is sold, we
go out and celebrate my treat.
Girl, I'll be light and drunk.
OK.
You want to come?
Sure.
I'll ask Jack to stay with the kids.
You know, I have a suggestion.
Let's just tell him you
have a business meeting.
I think about the
drinking and drunk part.
OK.
Call him from the car.
Come on.
OK.
[music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hey, JJ.
Hey, hey, guys.
How you doing?
All right.
Now, was he a purchase
price, a selling price?
You bet.
All right.
My round.
OK.
[laughter]
And so this guy says, does the carpet
come with the house?
And I say, it's wall to wall.
What do you think?
And then he says, I don't know.
And then I said, you're
going to make this more on it
than I've ever met.
And then I said--
It's like a damn
miniseries with no end to it.
Not unlike South Pacific, nice scenery,
no real point to it.
What?
Now you speak.
By the way, it wasn't a miniseries.
It was a play, then a movie,
then a badly miscast TV movie.
By the way, I hate you.
[laughter]
I think it's time for another round.
Yeah, Brad, you're buying.
What?
Mac always pays.
Yeah, well, her money is your money.
So what difference does it make?
Hey, what's it like being gay?
Well, you don't beat
around the bush, do you?
No.
I don't know.
What's it like having blue eyes?
You know, I think I
must be a little bit drunk,
because maybe that was an
incredibly stupid question
to ask you.
Oh, that's OK.
I think gay is kind of like
being part of a freak show.
You know, people like to
stop by the cage and stare.
I think what I meant
was, when did you first
know that you were attracted to women?
Like, when did you
decide, that's it, I'm gay?
It's not really a decision.
And I think I've always known.
Must be hard.
Is it hard?
Well, you get to
disappoint a lot of people,
starting with your parents.
Oh my god, my mother, who
is the most judgmental person
alive, would have a field day with that.
Mom, not only have I disappointed you
as a daughter, a wife, a
mother, and a homemaker,
but I've decided to sleep with women.
I ought to say it just to piss her off.
Yeah, that'd probably do it.
Honey, I'm home.
Hey, Bob.
Hey, you've got a good one.
Come on.
Let's go. Come on.
Let's go.
So this is just to show you
what we deal with, you know?
But don't be daunted by this couple.
They've interviewed
every real little tale, OK?
Well, we haven't been happy
about what any of you people
have said in terms of your commissions.
We're too high.
It's as simple as that.
Well, the normal commission is 6%,
so what were the other agents asking for?
3%. Uh-huh. 3%.
Well, I'm new, but it seems
to me that at either of those
numbers, you're going to get an agent
who's not going to work
very hard at selling your house, and you
want to move to Florida
sooner rather than later, am I right?
Also, I noticed some
problems with your foundation,
not to mention the fact
that Mac here is the best agent
in town, which means you'll get a higher
price for your house,
making lower commission
a moot point, am I right?
[music playing]
Problems with your foundation.
Where'd you come up with that?
I'm Vila.
Oh, you are something.
What?
You'd make a great agent.
You should think about
getting your license.
What?
Your real estate license.
We don't help you.
So I don't know what to say.
Say yes.
I don't know.
All right.
Say you'll think about it.
OK.
Don't think about it.
Good.
This is good.
This is really good.
[inaudible]
It's interesting.
Did you hear the question?
I think you're right.
[inaudible]
OK.
A red light shows the couple
apartments only on the first
floor, so which of the following is true.
The rental agent is
protecting the other adults
from the disruption of the child's
running rate or her.
Now, when an inspection
goes wrong, what do you do?
Well, the contract all inspectors use
holds them harmless reliability.
Therefore, you don't have to do anything.
Excellent.
Yeah.
[cheering]
[laughing]
[inaudible]
You haven't been looking for a place to
move to at all, have you?
I've been too busy.
Jack, I'm going to get
some listings tomorrow.
If you can't go see them, I will.
Fine.
Come on.
We're late.
You know how Bernie and Sandy hate that.
Please.
You look fantastic.
Why?
What are you doing differently?
You had Botox or a peel?
No.
She's having an affair.
I'm not having an affair.
I'm having a life, plenty to ask.
That's not it.
There's something else going on.
What is it?
Jack and I are separating.
Oh my god.
You can't be serious.
We're not happy, and we
haven't been for a long time.
Well, nobody's happy.
What has that got to do with anything?
Kind of everything.
What about you and the cuttings?
There's hours away.
Guys, I got to tell you something.
Yeah?
Kate and I are splitting up.
You are the perfect couple.
Now looks are deceiving.
This is going to change our whole lives.
Sandy's not about you.
It's about us.
I love you guys.
I hope you don't take sides,
and we can all stay friends.
I don't get it.
What happened?
Just out of the blue of
the two, you just set it
at the same time to separate?
Poof.
I think Jack would
have been fine with things
staying the way they were.
I asked for the separation.
You OK?
Yeah, I'm fine.
If this one's not good, I'm
going to blow my own brains out.
Yeah, well, I'll put
my head next to yours,
make it two for one.
Are you sure you're the one that should
be finding Jack an apartment?
Well, if I don't, nobody will.
Kate?
What's wrong?
Are the kids all right?
They're fine.
Well, then what am I doing
home in the middle of the day?
So I can take you to
see your new apartment.
And then we're going to tell the kids.
[music playing]
Andrew!
Yo!
Turn it down.
Yo, it's off.
Speak.
Time is precious.
Sometimes you're smarter than you know.
Sam, we need to have a talk.
I know all about the
birdies and the bees.
Remember, we have this
talk each and every year.
Oh my god, you're exhausting.
I know that too.
Mom, Dad, what?
Well, this is going to be
hard, so just get us a name, OK?
One minute, OK?
You know that your dad and I both love
you very much, right?
Yeah.
And how in life sometimes things change.
Yeah?
Well, the problem is that we
don't love each other enough.
We're going to separate.
Did you hear what I just said?
Yeah.
I've known for a long
time that things were bad.
I was just hoping for a miracle.
I know, sweetie, we were too.
I don't want to upset
your life or Adam's.
You both mean the world to us.
This is the last thing we wanted to do.
All I know is I want my
parents to stay together forever,
just like every other kid.
But Adam and I are also tired of hearing
you guys fight all the time.
I don't understand.
Why did you start fighting?
What happened?
I don't know.
Why do people forget why they loved
each other in the first place?
Because even though we try to do the best
we can, we're human.
And sometimes we get stuck.
I just can't move.
I'm so sorry, sweetie.
Yeah?
Hey, sport.
Hey.
Listen, your mom and I have something
pretty important to
talk to you about, so...
Can you put the Game Boy down?
Thanks.
OK.
You have all my numbers
that you need me, right?
Yeah.
Come here.
Come here a little bit.
I want you to listen to me.
Everything's going to be all right, OK?
I'm only five blocks away.
I see you all the time.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Why are you all standing there?
Why are you staring at me?
I'm fired, aren't I?
Yeah.
I'm afraid I'm going to have
to fire you as our receptionist
because I'm hiring you
as a real estate agent.
You passed.
Maggie opened it.
I couldn't stand the system.
Oh, my god.
Well, congratulations, right?
That's just great.
Yes.
You.
Well, I'm a little excited
when I first opened the house.
Yeah, I don't get too excited.
I haven't seen it yet.
I'll find a pony in there somewhere.
I know you will.
Ta-da.
Oh, wow.
Nice, huh?
Yeah.
OK, let's sell this house.
- OK. - Got your specs?
Yeah.
Cate.
They looked fine when you did them last
time, five minutes ago.
I know.
It's ridiculous.
I feel like I'm 15 years
old waiting for my first date.
Well, you'll get over that
as soon as the 100th loopy
locks through that door.
Go ahead.
You got to answer it. - Right.
OK.
Of course.
Hello. - Hey.
Hi, Bethan.
Come on in.
Thanks.
Oh.
Oh, my.
This place hasn't been
touched in like 50 years.
That's right.
But I think that's a good thing.
No bad addition to contend with.
A clean pallet.
One owner.
Has anybody died here?
Well, yes.
But we all have to
die somewhere, don't we?
Thank you.
Yeah, thanks.
Thanks for coming.
OK.
Thank you.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Do we have to tell them the bad things
when we show a house?
Yes, Kate.
Remember?
Disclosure?
Yeah.
Unless we're doing something wrong.
Little advice?
You want to hook them into the potential
before you tell them that
it's only had one owner.
That way, they're
slightly invested in the house
before they find out someone died there.
Great.
Thanks.
Hang on.
Thank you.
Thanks.
There you go.
That's fine.
What was your girlfriend's name?
Lauren?
When did she die?
Five years ago, May 30th.
Or didn't Big Mouth
Maggie tell you that part?
I'm sorry.
It's none of my business.
No, it's OK.
But I'm sure it's still incredibly painful.
You know, you always think
that it will get less painful.
But the fact of the matter is it doesn't.
How long were you together?
Almost 10 years.
I mean, we'd known each other
for a long time before that.
But I wasn't ready to acknowledge it.
And she waited and waited.
I just wish she had been with me for a long time.
I just wish that I
hadn't wasted so much time
we didn't end up having.
But I think you were lucky to have the
time you did with her.
She was lucky to have it with you.
OK, shall we?
Yeah.
Hi, Sandy.
Rita.
How are you?
Fine.
Good.
How are you?
I'm OK.
This is McNally Hayes, Sandy, Rita.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
We're late.
Have a nice lunch.
Oh, hi.
I didn't know whether or
not I should use my key.
No, you can use the key.
Oh, OK.
So, got the TV all hooked
up, plenty of junk food.
It'll be just like home.
Hey, give me a kiss.
You too.
[kiss]
See ya.
[crying]
Kate, what are you doing here?
Well, I was alone in my
house for the first time
in my entire life.
I had no kids.
I had no husband.
I have no friends.
So I came here.
Come on in.
This is Bob.
Hi, Bob.
What's the matter with you, huh?
You ever seen anybody fall apart before?
Bob, what are the rules, huh? Bob, think you know 'em. [crying] My kids left to spend the
night with Jack for the first time.
And I just came undone.
I've never not been with my kids.
You know, it's funny.
I gave up on my kids.
I was like, what? I was like, what? I was like, what? I was like, what? I was like, what? I was like, what? I was like, what? I gave up on myself so
long ago to be Jack's wife,
or be Sam's mother, Adam's
mother, to be a homemaker.
I was like a stepford wife.
But I wanted this.
I wanted things to change.
And now, I don't know.
I don't know anything.
Do you want them back?
No.
I don't.
But this has torn my kids' lives apart.
And that's the hardest part of it.
It's overwhelming.
Yeah, of course it is.
I wanted more.
I wanted more from my life.
I wanted more from myself.
And I wanted more from Jack.
But she couldn't or
didn't want to give me.
Maybe he didn't know how to.
I think maybe it was me.
OK.
Something in me provoked him.
No.
I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore.
You know what?
This is not all your fault.
Really, it's not.
OK.
You made the right decision.
And you're going to be fine.
OK?
You're going to be fine.
OK, don't--
Why?
Because you don't know what you're doing.
You don't know what this means.
Yes, I do.
It's what I feel.
It's a little more complicated than that.
You're straight, and this is wrong.
And you're just
responding to a little kindness,
to a little attention.
That's all.
You just don't have a clue.
It's not what I'm responding to.
I'm not some stupid teenager man.
Kate, I'm gay, and I know what it means.
This is my life, not some
abstract thought or feeling.
It isn't a switch I
get to turn on and off,
and it's not to be taken lightly.
I don't take this lightly.
In most of my life, I lived a lie,
trying to be my mother's daughter,
not acknowledging the fact that I was gay
because I was so scared
of the hate and the shame
until I met Lauren.
And she taught me how not to be afraid.
But this, it scares the hell out of me.
And I don't want to be scared anymore.
And I'm not the one to take another
person on that journey
because the first trip almost killed me.
I didn't mean to put
you in that position.
OK.
It wasn't my intention.
I know.
I don't know what this means.
I've never done this before.
But you should know I was
not looking for a quick fix
to my problems or the
touch of another human being,
whoever it was.
Believe it or not,
everything changed for me
the minute I met you.
It scares the hell out of me, too.
I should leave. [phone ringing]
[phone ringing]
Hey, Israel T.
This is Mrs. Wilson.
Let me try herself.
The person you are trying
to reach is out of range.
I'm sorry she's out of range.
Can I take a message?
If you ever hear me call back.
I'll tell you a call of Mrs. Wilson.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Where is she?
She hasn't been in
the office in two days.
I'm going out for a smoke.
Brad, you think you could answer the
phones just this once?
I don't think so.
It gets really scary.
You let it go to voicemail.
[phone ringing]
Maggie, what's going on?
Where's Mac?
Honey, I've known Mac.
It seems longer than I've known myself.
And where she is is in the dumper.
Screwed.
What are you talking about?
I've only seen her
come unglued three times.
When she met Lauren,
when she lost Lauren,
and when she met you.
[knocking]
Are you avoiding me?
No.
We haven't been in
the office in two days.
I've been working.
I get that, except you
haven't not come into the office
ever before, if I'm not mistaken, which I'm not.
I don't think there's
a real sense, is it?
Who cares?
Aren't you going to ask me in?
OK.
Do you want to come in?
Well, if this is what it's like being
attracted to someone
of the same sex, it
doesn't feel too good.
You're right about that.
What are you talking about?
Being shunned?
You're shunning me.
No, I'm not.
And you know, this isn't just about you.
That's about me, too.
Well, the least you could do is be an
adult and speak to me.
I'm sick of more dialogue from a woman.
What happened the other night shouldn't
impact our friendship.
We can still be friends, can't we?
I don't know how to be
your friend now, after that.
Why?
Because I feel more for you
than a friend should feel.
So why don't we just
stop speaking to each other,
and I should quit working
for you and just disappear
because it's easier?
No.
I don't know.
Why is this so simple for me?
Why is this so simple for you?
It's not.
That's the part you're not getting.
Look, I have a big life
with lots of people in it,
and I was prepared to see what my
feelings were about,
knowing the risks involved,
not knowing if it was real.
I understand if you can't.
But I don't understand that you don't
want to talk to me or see me.
Don't you know that's all I want to do?
It's to see you, it's to talk to you.
Final translation
Never could I love like this before
'Cause it feels so much more
Than my heart ever knew
Never will I have to search again
For a shelter from the rain
You gave me a brand new start
And I found the missing part in you
Jack. Hi.
Come in. Kids aren't here, remember?
Yeah, I know. I want to
talk to you for a minute.
Sure. I'll have to leave
in a second, but come in.
Thanks.
You look very nice. Thank you.
Where are you going?
Dinner with Matt and some clients. What
do you want to talk about?
Well, I got the divorce papers.
I'm absolutely positive about this.
Yeah, I am. I'm sorry, Jack.
Hi. Hi.
Hey, Jack. How are you?
Nice to see you again.
Yes, nice to see you.
Well, I hope you have a
successful dinner with your clients.
Goodbye.
Thanks.
That's a great
outfit. Where'd you get it?
You know, I never thought I'd say that to
someone I was dating.
Dinner with clients, huh?
What was I going to say that
I was going to date with you?
You know by the look on his face at the
wheel, it's starting
to turn already, right?
So if he hasn't
figured it out, he will soon.
I'm going to tell him.
Just not now.
When?
When your shirt isn't just a face?
It's not fair.
Sure it is. I mean, I don't know. Maybe
you're just trying it out like a car.
That's insulting and ridiculous.
Okay, I've seen it
happen a million times before.
Really? A million?
Don't be stupid. You know what I meant.
Actually, I don't know what you mean
because, you know, I'm new to the secret
club of yours with your
secret little handshakes.
We have to stop this. We
have to be careful now.
Why?
Isn't that one of the
perks of being with a woman?
You talk and talk and talk about
everything until you go insane.
If you're trying to pick a fight with me
because you're scared about what's
happening, instead of just saying how
terrified you are,
consider yourself successful.
It's just everyone
expected coming from you.
Let's go out, Pat.
No.
Get up.
Okay, I'm out back. Now what?
You're in there moping around like a sad
sack. What did you think would happen?
You plunge into your first post-Lauren
relationship with a straight, confused
mother of two. You
should give her some time.
What I should have done was to have stuck
to my life plan, which was to never, ever
get involved with anyone again.
There's a problem with that.
I think I'm in love with her.
I just want to say, I'm sorry. I
pressured you and I just forgot for a
moment what you were going through
because it hasn't been so
long since I've been through it.
And I did it without kids, so if you
can't do this, I understand.
I just want you to know that no matter
what happens, you'll always have a job.
You'll always have me as a friend.
Hi, we didn't have to
ring our own doorbell.
See you on Saturday.
How's it going?
Not great. They hate my place. They'd
rather be in their own
rooms. I can't blame them.
Why don't I come over some time and try
and help you make it more of a home?
Sure.
Thanks.
Bye-bye. I have to tell you something.
Sure.
Go ahead, sweetie.
As grown up as I
pretend to be, I'm really not.
One minute I understand it, and then the
next minute I don't.
I'm really not okay that
we're not a family anymore.
But we are still a family. Fractured,
yes, but a family nonetheless.
It's not the same.
And the thing is, I guess I thought life
would always be the same.
Things would never change, which is
stupid, because everything changes.
But I never thought the first person to
move out of the house would be Dad.
Sandy, this is a surprise.
Can I come in so I don't have to stand on
here groveling in front of the neighbors?
Sure. Come on in.
I just came over to apologize.
I guess I didn't want you to shake things
up, because then that just means I'd have
to take a look at my life
and see how crappy it is.
I get it. But I'm
really glad you came over.
Me too.
Do you love your job?
I do.
Are you going to start dating again soon?
Oh, God, what a terrible fog.
Well, you know, it's
funny you should mention that.
I'm going to tell you something, because
even though you're a snob, I think you're
an open-minded snob.
And I think I am attracted to someone.
Who?
The woman I work for.
You're joking.
No.
I don't believe you.
Oh, why would you be so
shocked? Your sister's gay.
Because I don't approve of her lifestyle.
Since when did you become a bigot?
I'm not a bigot.
Must be tiring to sit in
judgment of everyone, Sandy.
Jack?
Dad?
Hey, hey, I'm in the kitchen.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
I'm impressed.
Yeah, I made enough if you want to stay.
Sure, sure. That'd be nice.
Great.
You know, Dad, if it isn't any good, we
could always hire a
cook or a maid who cooks.
Yes, I realize that, but I am trying to
spend more quality time with
my children, if you don't mind.
If you don't mind, it's just you think
poisoning your kids is the
best way to bond with them?
Same.
So?
Not bad.
Yeah?
I was very impressed, Jack.
Thank you.
Can I go over to Betsy's?
Yes. After you do the dishes.
That's okay, honey. I'll do them.
You see how shallow
their love for me really is?
Can I go to Peter's?
What is wrong with you guys?
You have your mother and father in the
same place, together
again, and you want to leave.
Yeah.
Go. Get out of here.
I, I, I, I, kiss, kiss.
My home. I'm good, Tom.
See ya.
See ya. Bye, Dad.
Bye-bye.
Well, it's good to know
something's never changed.
Yeah.
You know, I, I could do some stuff in the
living room, if you like,
to help make things better.
Yeah, that'd, uh, be great.
See ya. It looks a little better, huh?
Maybe, maybe there's some curtains, you
know, and, uh, little
black and white photos.
Stuff.
Yeah. Definitely looks better.
Jack, we need to talk.
Yeah. The rule is you can only say that
once in a lifetime to the same person.
That's it.
I need to tell you something so you don't
find out another way.
Uh, what are you talking about?
I'm attracted to
someone and I'm pursuing it.
Who is he?
It's not a he, it's Mac.
Mac? Who's...
Maybe Mac, your boss?
What, if Mac's a woman, what is...
You can't be attracted to a woman.
She's a person, Jack.
What are you talking
about? She's a woman.
I don't understand this.
What are you telling me here?
That our whole life
together was this big lie?
No, that's not true.
Well, then explain something to me. How
can you suddenly be attracted to a woman?
I don't know.
I wasn't even looking for any kind of
relationship and
certainly not one with a woman.
Wait a second, wait a second, wait a
second, wait a second.
Is this the problem? Is this the problem?
All along, deep down inside, you had
these feelings, you felt this way, and
that's why our marriage failed?
No, the failure of our
marriage is both our faults.
It's nothing to do with Mac or any other
woman. I've never had feelings for
another woman in my life,
Jack, and I met Mac after we split.
I can't believe this.
You don't have to. It's not about you.
No, really, really, it's
not about me. That's great.
Okay, let me put it another way.
It's my life and I can live it any way I
want. It doesn't concern you.
Okay. But it does concern my children,
and I will not have them around this.
What does that mean?
It means that you have put them through
enough, and you are not
going to do this to them too.
Monday morning, I am
filing papers for sole custody.
Hey, what's wrong?
I told Jack about us. Mainly because
Sammy came by to apologize, and like an
idiot, I thought I could share something
with my best friend who has a gay sister.
Instead, she's the moral
majority. I'm an idiot.
Yeah, bigotry is stunning, isn't it?
Afraid that's not the end of it. Jack
wants to take the kids away from me.
He's just scared. He
doesn't really mean it.
Tell that to the court he's
filing papers with Monday.
Oh, God. I don't know what to do. I don't
want to tell the kids. I feel like
they've been through enough already, but
I'm afraid if I don't, he will.
And I don't want him to
drag you into court either.
Don't worry about me.
I think I have to tell him
before he does. Are you sure?
I don't think I have a
choice. He's forced my hand.
Maybe you should wait.
Well, I have to tell Sam
at least before he does.
Listen, I'm sorry for the saying yes,
saying no, saying yes thing.
Please have faith in me.
I know I sound like a broken record, but
are you sure about this? About us?
I don't know if this is going to last
forever, but the night that we fought and
you left, it was as if
someone pulled my heart out.
And when you came back, you brought my
heart with you. So right
here, right now, yeah, I'm sure.
There are some real consequences, which
you've just encountered. Are
you prepared for more of that?
No. Kate, I don't want you to
lose your kids because of me.
I don't want to lose my kids either.
The truth is, maybe I'm not prepared for
any of this, but I made an adult
conscious choice to be with you. Not a
man, not a woman, but you.
I am prepared to stand by my
heart, which I've given to you.
As complex as it might
be. This much, I know.
Hey, Bob.
Hey, Joe.
Why'd you pull me out of a play date?
I was kidding. What's
happened? Is it Dad? Adam?
No, honey. Everyone's fine.
Then what?
I need to tell you something that's going
to be very difficult.
On a scale of one to ten, with ten being
a divorce, what would it be?
Two, Sam.
Six?
I don't know.
Okay, just tell me.
It's hard to put into words.
I'm not going to guess.
Well, you know how your teacher, Mr.
Jackson, lives with a man, and I've
always told you you could
love or be with anybody.
Yeah?
Well, you know Mac,
the woman I work with.
Yeah, she's a lesbian. So?
How did you know that?
I'm not dumb.
But how could you know? She
doesn't even look like one.
No, she doesn't look like one. Look, Mom,
could you please tell me why you dragged
me out of Betsy's house?
I... I really... I
don't know how to start.
Mom, just start somewhere.
Well, Mac and I have become very good
friends, as you know.
And I know this is going to sound
strange, but I'm attracted to her.
Okay. I don't
understand. What do you mean?
I'm attracted to Mac like I used to be
attracted to your father.
You mean in a sexual way?
Yeah.
That would make you
gay and you're not gay.
No, I'm not. I mean, I wasn't. But if I
want to be with Mac, I guess I am.
You've only known her for a few months. I
mean, I don't understand.
Did you like girls before?
No.
Well, you said people were born that way.
Well, I don't look at Mac as a woman. I
look at her as a person.
I... I don't understand. And you weren't
born gay. But now you are. And...
You're with a woman? I don't get it.
I know. I... I don't know what happened.
I don't know what it means. Does this
mean I'm gay forever now?
I... I don't know, Sam. I know this is a
shock to you. It's a
shock to me too, but...
I told your father and he's really upset.
Gee, I wonder why.
Don't let the nose ring and
the purple streak fool you.
I'm upset too.
Honey, I care immensely for Mac. And the
only reason I'm telling you all this is
because your father was
to take you away from me.
Now, maybe he's just angry. Maybe not.
But I'm telling you because I love you.
And I don't want to lose you.
You know what? I don't really want to
talk about it anymore.
I raised you to have an open mind.
Please, honey, can't
we just talk about this?
No. No. We're done talking.
I know that's a very good idea.
Jack is angry enough to try to get
everyone on his side to get custody,
including my dear old mother, who, by the
way, is rich enough to buy the court.
Even Bob doesn't think it's a good idea.
I'm just hoping that blood is thicker
than I've been lit to believe.
Don't count on it.
Hey, Katie. Is your mother expecting you?
No.
You know how she hates surprises.
Yeah, well, she's going to love tonight.
She's in the bath now, but
she'll be down soon. What is it?
I'm going to try this out on you first.
Ten seconds left. Brad,
sorry. I... Come on in.
No.
Okay. Stand there.
I just came by to tell you that I think
Lauren would've really liked Kate.
Okay, Katie, what's going on?
Well, I've met someone, romantically.
Well, if you're happy, I'm happy. You
know I'm not speaking for your mother.
But I don't know why you're
making such a big fuss over it.
Well, the thing is, the person that I met
and I'm involved with,
romantically, is a woman.
What? You don't have anything to say?
I'm thinking about it.
I haven't seen you this happy since you
got that swing out back when you were 12.
So it's okay with me.
May I make a suggestion?
Sure.
I'd get out of this house
before your mother comes down.
Who wouldn't take Walt Geddy's name when
you're talking to, Mary?
I know it's too late for your soap opera.
No, it's not.
Well, Bellwell, an unannounced visitor.
You know how I love that.
I know you do, Mother.
That's too much, Mary.
No. Trust me, it's not.
Well, what is it?
I hope you haven't come over here to ask
me to babysit for your children now that
you're a single mother with a job.
God, that was hard to say.
You know, Mother, I think they'd sooner
have their eyes gouged out.
You know what your problem
is, what it's always been?
No, but I'm sure you're going to tell me.
You're a smartass. Always have been.
I know.
What?
Just spit it out.
Well, I've met someone, and
I'm seeing them romantically.
Well, that was a little
fast, don't you think?
Yeah.
And it's a woman.
Mary, you don't need to hear this.
I won't have it.
Do you hear me?
It's really not up to you, Mother.
It's against God.
You'll burn in hell for it.
Well, then I'll burn in hell for it.
It's not natural,
don't you understand that?
To care about another human being who is
spectacular is natural.
I've finally come back to life.
Mother, I've waited years for someone
like Mack to come along.
What kind of a name is that for a woman?
Is that a lesbian nickname of some sort?
No, it's not.
I did not raise my
daughter to be a lesbian.
This is not about you.
I won't have it. You'll
stop seeing her right now.
I'm an adult now, much
to your astonishment.
You can't boss me around anymore.
But you can stop seeing
me, which I hope you won't.
Because in spite of all of
our problems, you're my mother.
And I love you.
And I'm your only child.
So I hope once the shock wears off,
you'll try to open your
mind to this and accept it.
There's one thing you can count on.
That day will never come.
What?
Sorry. It didn't go well
with your mother, did it?
No, it did not.
What happened?
She pretty much did the
biblical thing and disowned me.
I didn't have to give her time. My mother
did the same thing and
now we couldn't be closer.
First of all, your mother
and my mother are not the same.
We've never been close. And she doesn't need time because she's
going to feel this way forever.
So in addition to not having a mother, I
have a daughter who's processing it.
A son who doesn't know.
An ex-best friend who's all of a sudden
is related to Jerry Falwell.
Husband who wants to take my kids away.
So all in all, I'd say this coming out
thing's been a big hit.
I did try to warn you that
it could get really messy.
I did not get this messy if I did.
What?
You wouldn't have done it or you wouldn't
have had feelings for me?
Or you wouldn't have
gone through with it?
I don't know.
Then I should leave.
No, no, no.
Then what do you want me to do?
I don't know.
Because I can't sit here and let you lose
everything because of me.
One minute I think I can handle it and
the next I'm sure I can't.
Then I think of you and I know I'm
completely out of my mind.
[Music]
Jack.
Kate.
I'll go.
No, no, it's fine.
It concerns both of you.
Mary called me and she
told me how Dorothy reacted.
Which was pretty much how I reacted.
And I don't want to be like your mother.
You know, I don't want
to be small and petty.
But I do want to be small and petty, but
Sam says that's a really bad thing to be.
She's a kid and somehow, I
don't know how she knows that.
She also forced me to come down here,
which I really did not want to do.
My instinct was to hurt you.
The way you hurt me.
But see, I don't want to do that either.
I don't want to take
the kids away from you.
I don't understand what you're doing.
Maybe I never will.
Maybe I would have known how to compete
with another guy, but I have no idea how
to compete with a woman.
Very confused.
But what I loved about you when we met,
I still love about you.
I want you to be happy.
And I want to be happy too, so...
I'm going to try and do better.
That's all I wanted to say.
(Music)
Hey, beautiful.
Hi, Mary.
Would you consider us living together
someday in the faraway future?
Not the reaction I was hoping for.
Oh, you need to slow down.
I just jumped through some huge hoops.
I'm too tired right now to even think
about jumping through another one.
And as you're saying
goes, "Love me, love my dog."
Mine is, "Love me, love my two kids."
And they're not nearly
as well trained as Bob is.
Hey, are you prepared for that?
An instant family?
One of whom doesn't even know about us?
Yes.
Well, I'm going to have to catch my
breath. That's a big leap.
Okay.
Just a breath.
Since when do you care if
your grandma comes to anything?
I don't. I'm doing this for Mom.
Don't get up.
(Music)
If you've come here to lecture me, you
know where the door is.
We didn't come here to lecture you.
I came here to invite
you to my graduation.
Isn't that sweet?
And I'm sure your mother and
that woman will be there too.
I'm sorry, Samantha, but
I won't be where they are.
First of all, that woman
has a name. It's McNally.
And second of all, this
isn't about you. It's about me.
This is my graduation.
And if you don't come, you don't have a
daughter or a granddaughter.
It's so much easier, Dorothy, to remember
why you love someone
and to move past things,
even if you don't understand them.
You can just pretend to, like I'm doing.
Kate's a remarkable person.
She gave me that kid.
Even you have to admit.
That's some kid.
We present to you the
graduating class of 2002.
[Music]
I'm very proud of you, Sam, and I love
you very, very much.
Don't you dare make me cry. It took me
three hours to get my eyeliner on.
I'm really sorry it took
me so long to come around.
I know you didn't raise me that way.
Honey, what made you change your mind?
I realize that you're really happy now. I
mean, you haven't been for a long time.
That's it. Simple, huh?
You are a spectacular person.
You should stop pushing me. I'll get
there when I get there.
Yes, and we'll all be dead by then.
What do I call her? What do I call them?
They have names, Grandma. Start there.
See you about that. I'm glad you took
that thing out anyway.
You're a graduate. Why did you do this?
Isn't this a foreshadow?
-Is it? -No, it's permanent.
Now that the ceremony makes you a maid,
this is Mac. This is my mother Dorothy.
Hello, Dorothy. Nice to meet you.
-Hi. -Brad?
-How are you? -I'm good.
-First thing. -Yes.
-I'll work together. -Yes.