[silence]
[woman muffled scream]
[woman screaming]
[suspenseful music]
[woman sobbing]
[Mary Ann] Daddy!
Daddy!
Honey.
[Mary Ann] I heard a monster.
Uh-oh.
What did it, uh...
What did it sound like?
Was it like a bear?
[Mary Ann] No, it sounded
like a monster, a real one.
Oh, no.
Is Tilly scared?
[ominous music]
[Mary Ann] A little.
Well, what do we say?
One, two, three.
Nothing scares me.
Can you say it with me?
Okay.
[Father And Mary Ann] One,
two, three.
Nothing scares me.
Good.
You feel better?
[Mary Ann] Can you turn on the
light?
No, no, wait a minute.
I think, I know what's
really bothering you.
Mommy and I have been
fighting a lot lately.
And...
Daddy, I don't-
Let me finish, okay.
You just get so tired,
so frustrated when
things just don't
go the way you want them to.
You wanted a raise
not just a promotion.
You wanted Henry to be
healthy for good this time.
You wanna give mommy the
life that you promised her
when you got married,
one with vacations, huh,
dinners out,
and not just to Olive
Garden or Applebee's.
Wanna know a secret?
I hate Applebee's.
Yeah, and you know what?
So does Mommy.
[tense music]
[Mary Ann] Daddy.
But, she knows that
that's the best we can do,
and she's a good woman,
so she doesn't say
how unhappy she is.
But I can tell.
In the way she looks at me,
the sigh she lets
out every morning.
She loves you, she loves Henry
there's no doubt about that.
But, I know that she stopped
loving me a long time ago.
And, you know, the truth is that
moms and dads don't
have to love each other
to stay together.
And sometimes, I think...
Sometimes it's gotta be better
that way.
It's gotta hurt less, right?
I mean, it must. [chuckling]
[sighing heavily]
There's no such thing as
monsters, honey.
Life is scary enough
without them.
[Mary Ann] But they are real.
I heard one.
They're as real as Tilly.
[Mary Ann] He's real.
Now we've talked about that.
[Mary Ann] He's a real doll.
You said that mom made
him with her love.
You know, you're right.
[Mary Ann] Can we
please turn on the light?
No, there's no...
[suspenseful music]
See, there's nothing
to be afraid of.
Nothing at all.
[chair creaking softly]
Jesus!
[suspenseful music]
[breathing heavily]
[tense music]
[faucet water splashing]
One, two, three.
Nothing.
[shower water splashing]
[suspenseful music swelling]
You're a mess.
You wanna join me?
God, yes.
[gentle music]
I meant to pick up Henry's meds.
It's taken care of.
Do I need to pick up
Mary Ann at school?
No.
Not anymore.
Jess.
Don't.
There's this song
stuck in my head.
It's not really even a song.
[Father] I really screwed up.
God, what is it?
I'm so sorry.
[dad moaning softly]
That's it.
One, two, three.
My sweet pea went and
killed his whole family.
[ominous music]
We suffered, you know.
None of us went quickly,
not Henry,
not Mary Ann,
not even me.
You couldn't even do that right.
[Father] This isn't real.
No.
No, it's not.
[gentle music]
[dad sobbing softly]
[suspenseful music]
[Mary Ann] Daddy, you
don't have to be alone.
[Jess And Mary Ann] You
can be with all of us.
[Father] One,
two,
three.
I saw a monster,
and he was me.
[suspenseful music]
[woman screaming]
[woman sobbing]
[woman spitting softly]
[soft knocking on door]
Hello.
[loud banging on door]
Ugh, what the fuck!
[tense music]
[dramatic music]
[gentle dramatic music]
[creature growling lowly]
[ominous music]
[chuckling softly]
A stupid toy.
[suspenseful music]
[creature screeching loudly]
[soft knocking on door]
[ominous music]
[creature screeching lowly]
[monster screeching]
[gentle rattling]
[suspenseful music]
[woman screaming]
[woman gasping]
No, please!
Oh, my god!
[woman sobbing]
[creature screeching]
[breathing heavily]
No, no, no, no, no!
No!
[suspenseful music]
[breathing heavily]
Shit, shit, shit!
[footsteps approaching swiftly]
[ominous music]
[suspenseful music]
[gasping deeply]
You motherfucker!
Go to hell!
[woman screaming]
[creature growling]
Ah, stop!
No!
[woman screaming erratically]
[suspenseful music]
[woman screaming]
[bones crunching]
[dramatic music]
[Jordan] Mom.
[John] So, you sure
I never mentioned
my friend Dennis to you before?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Maybe you were too
young to remember, huh?
Last time he saw you,
you were just knee high.
[Paul] Maybe.
Yeah.
Dad, can I please
go to the washroom?
Just hang on let me stop.
[reporter speaking
faintly on radio]
[Reporter] But no further
information on numbers
to be released until
relatives have been informed.
Law enforcement officials
say the attacker
was a 46-year old man who had
ties to the Ontario school.
One went missing
yesterday night.
[lively rock music]
So, it's been quite a while.
How you been?
I've been good.
Just glad we finally
decided to get together.
I mean, we've been talking
about it so long, right?
So you're Paul.
Yeah.
Dad, told me all about you.
He's been telling
stories, sending pictures.
Ain't nothing like
the real thing.
Isn't that right, dad?
You guys should get
somethin' to eat.
The food's really good.
No, we're okay.
You're not hungry?
You're not in a hurry, are you?
Well, we ate already.
Had muffins, right.
So.
Muffins.
[chuckling softly]
That ain't much
for an appetite, Dad.
[Waitress] Another top up?
Check please.
♪ You got a heavenly face
♪ And a sinful tongue
[Paul] Oh, God,
it smells in here.
Don't say that, okay.
Just be cool.
You sure
you're not hungry, Dad.
No, I'm fine.
Thank you.
20 years.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, hmm-mm.
Been 20 years since your
dad and I were in college.
Damn, we shared a lot
of courses, didn't we?
Yeah, we had quite a few.
What were they again?
[flies buzzing]
Hey, Paul.
What should we do today?
Hmm, you got any ideas?
What do you think, Dad?
What about fishing?
Huh, what do you say, Paul?
Your dad ever take you?
[Paul] Uh-uh.
Really.
Well, now I don't know
about a father who never
taught his boy to bait
a hook or cast a line?
Something special about all
that time alone on the water.
Allows for a special kind
of bonding, you know?
We're more into sports.
Right, buddy?
[ominous music]
Paul.
Hey.
It's okay, Dad.
I guess, the ride up must
have tuckered him out.
Just let him nap.
Or would you prefer him awake?
See you hadn't thought
this through, have you?
Hmm?
Maybe this whole thing was
some kind of misunderstanding.
So what you gave him
is it gonna hurt him?
So he's just gonna sleep.
I thought we understood
one another.
Be back in an hour.
Or [sighing],
you can go home to your wife.
[ominous music]
[dramatic music]
[Paul gasping softly]
Hey, oh, son, that's okay.
That's okay.
Don't worry, don't worry.
Don't worry it's okay.
It's all right.
Son.
What the?
[suspenseful music]
[Paul gasping gently]
It's something, isn't it?
I had a feeling.
Wasn't sure, of course.
I knew my gut was
telling me something.
Then I had a look at Paul.
He was untouched.
Not a mark on him.
Then I thought that's odd.
Now it all makes sense,
doesn't it?
No.
No, none of that here.
Don't hide it.
It's really beautiful
once you get used to it,
once you start
to recognize yourself.
[Paul gasping softly]
[tense music]
I suppose it's a little
off pudding at first.
I can't remember.
[Paul sobbing gently]
[suspenseful music swelling]
[skin squishing loudly]
[Paul sobbing gently]
I don't know how
you hid it for so long.
Must have been hell.
[gasping gently]
Perhaps it was for the best.
No bad habits to break.
[gasping heavily]
[flying buzzing]
[dramatic music]
[door creaking]
Paul.
Paul, wake up.
Wake up.
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Paul.
Wake up.
Are you alright?
Are you okay?
What?
[breathing heavily]
It's all right.
It's okay.
[ominous music]
[creature growling]
Paul.
Let go of him.
No!
[creature screeching]
[grunting heavily]
[creature growling]
[suspenseful music]
[dramatic music]
It's okay, Paul.
It's okay now.
[children yelling faintly]
It's okay.
It's okay now.
[dramatic organ music]
[Priest] God loves you,
but God hates the sin in you.
God did not call you
to such perversions.
The perverted homosexual spirit
and the spirit of delusion
and confusion
it has deceived many
men and women.
Homosexual acts are an
embarrassment to the church.
You're an embarrassment
to yourself, your family.
But fear not God is a deliverer.
A reading from the gospel
according to Romans 1:26.
For this reason God gave them
up to dishonorable passions
where their woman
exchanged natural relations
for those that are
contrary to nature.
The word of the Lord.
[Group] Thanks be to God.
[dramatic music]
[Priest] Please join me
for the holy Eucharist.
Jesus himself,
his flesh and blood.
[gentle music]
I am not worthy to receive you.
But only say the word,
and I shall be healed.
Amen.
[dramatic choral music]
I am not worthy to receive you.
But only say the word,
and I shall be healed.
[dramatic music]
[Alien] Warden.
Chief Administrative
Official in a prison.
Hey, mom.
[Alien] Parasite:
Plant or animal that
lives in or on an organism
from which it derives
sustenance or protection
without benefiting the host
and usually doing harm.
In time, these jailers
will take everything,
rob you of every
wish, hope, and desire.
It's up to you to make a plan
to break free, to escape.
After all these years,
I have my opportunity.
Four more months
the kids off to college.
Pull out the
savings, buy a truck,
leave, never look back.
After 45 years of existence,
my life is about to begin.
[utensils clanking]
What's the matter, sweetheart,
had another bad day?
Now you're waiting for
me to ask you about it,
but I won't because you're
just gonna tell me anyway.
Here it comes.
Three, two, one.
They're expecting me to
go in on Saturday again.
Can you believe that?
Well, they don't appreciate you
or your contributions
in that branch.
They really don't.
[Alien] Your contributions?
What exactly should they appreciate,
your GED or your half
year of community college?
You're on time every day,
so are my bowel movements.
You're a knot on a bolt
on the ass-end of a useless cog.
They should've
fired you years ago.
[somber music]
Please don't touch me, you pig.
You okay?
Yeah.
Uh.
Well.
Well, what?
[Alien] We're having a
baby like it's nothing.
Like it won't ruin everything.
Anything but that.
You're dying.
You're leaving.
You're cheating.
Anything but that.
[humming softly]
Haven't you done enough,
taken everything.
You're enjoying this aren't you?
All a part of a plan, isn't it?
Checkmate.
She can lock the door,
and throw away the key now,
can't she?
It's over again.
But it can't be over.
We've waited too
long to just give up.
There's a solution,
always a solution.
We can beat her.
You're smarter than her.
Get us out of this, John.
[dramatic music]
[computer mouse clicking]
What are you doing?
Hmm?
Go on, go on, no peeking.
Go.
Okay.
[Alien] Don't stop.
Almost there.
[toilet flushing]
[somber music]
You okay?
[Charlotte] Yeah.
Fine.
Good.
[sobbing gently]
[somber music]
[Alien] Brought it on herself.
Don't forget that, John.
It's almost eight.
You getting up?
[somber music]
Hey.
[Charlotte] What?
What's wrong?
[Alien] Depression.
Oh, she's good.
Didn't see this
one coming, did we?
But we're on to her,
aren't we, John?
She can't act sick forever.
[Charlotte] Thanks.
[Alien] What an actress.
Think you've won, huh?
Fooled the kid, family,
the doctor, your boss.
But not me.
So,
I've been thinking.
[Alien] Is that
what you call it?
About how much this
whole thing's upset you.
Yeah, it's been tough.
But, sometimes things
there're just not meant to be.
I guess not.
But that doesn't mean we
can't try again, right?
[Alien] You see.
She'll never quit.
The depression thing was a ploy.
And now she's
going for the kill!!
You know that, don't you?
She'll never stop.
Until her last egg is dried
up, she'll keep trying.
After that,
she'll want to adopt.
It'll never end.
But there's still
a chance for freedom,
for everything
we've dreamt about.
Leave it to me, John.
Mom's been acting funny.
Keep an eye on her, okay?
I'm worried about her.
I want you to keep an eye on
Mom, okay?
Why?
[Alien] Well, dear, the
pills, the depression,
I'm just afraid she might
do something stupid.
She may hurt herself.
Go on.
I'm just not sure about
all those pills she's taking,
you know.
[Alien] Say it the
right way, idiot.
Say it.
I'm worried she
might hurt herself.
What are you doing?
Don't think, John, just follow.
It's what you're good at.
Wake up, honey.
Have some tea.
It'll make you feel better.
Wake up, honey,
and have some tea.
What are you doing?
Pour the tea.
John.
Don't do this.
Feed that bitch the tea.
[breathing heavily]
Get back in there.
Want another 20 years of hell?
You'll never have
this chance again!
We'll never get away from this
hell hole!
Do it!
Finish it!
Set us free!
Stop thinking it's not your
strong suit.
Let me take care
of this like always.
Don't start getting ideas now.
Just do what comes naturally.
Give me control now!
No.
[dramatic music]
[Alien] Stop it, don't touch me.
What are you doing?
Keep that thing away from me.
[suspenseful music]
[soft knocking on door]
[Charlotte] What are you doing
in there?
[Alien] Don't do it.
[Charlotte] Why aren't you at
work?
Be right out, honey.
[Charlotte] Get it away from me.
[Jordan] Dad, it's like 8:30.
Dad!
Yeah, you take the car, honey.
[Charlotte] Really?
Yeah, I'm gonna stay
at home this morning.
[Jordan] Alright, see you later.
[ominous music]
[Alien] Wait.
You're gonna kill us.
Stop, listen to me.
I've only ever wanted to make
you happy.
I'm not your enemy.
It's not my fault
they've disappointed you.
I wish they made us happy,
gave us everything you need.
But they don't, do they, John,
and they never will.
I'll never accept that.
[John gasping]
We can start over,
do things your way.
Listen to me, John.
Calm down.
I'd never hurt you.
I want the best for you, for us.
I understand you're scared,
but don't do this.
[gasping heavily]
You're not thinking it.
Stop and think.
Listen to me.
We can fix this, fix everything.
Stop it.
Get your hands off me!
[suspenseful music]
Listen to me, John.
Undo the belt.
Calm down, be reasonable.
We can talk this out.
You and I we've
always been together.
Let's not fight.
That's right, John, relax.
Think about it.
I'm your best friend.
I'm the one you know.
No one knows you better.
No, John.
Don't do this, John!
You'll bleed out.
You'll die.
Don't do this.
How will you explain this to
Jordan?
You can't do it.
You don't handle
pain well, John.
Do you know what
a razor feels like
being pulled across your flesh?
[gasping heavily]
Idiot, you think this is the answer.
Pull it out now.
Stop, look at the blood.
You're bleeding it's
not going to stop.
Listen to me you can
still turn things around.
We can sew you up.
It's not too late.
What are you doing?
You don't understand what you're
getting yourself into,
you idiot.
[gasping heavily]
It's not gonna work, John.
You're gonna die alone in
this dark, filthy basement
like a rat, like an insect.
You love me so much, don't you.
[John groaning heavily]
She's gonna remarry, get a
new daddy, bring another rat.
You bastard.
[gasping heavily]
No one is going to remember you
because you didn't matter.
Because at all things you failed
took the easy way out.
Traitor.
You can't get rid of me.
You're not going anywhere.
[Alien] I'm a piece of you.
Cutting me out
won't change that.
[John grunting heavily]
You wasted your life, John.
You didn't make a difference.
You failed your family,
failed in school,
failed in your career.
[grunting heavily]
You're bleeding to death.
You're going to die, John.
So are you.
[groaning heavily]
[Jordan] Dad, it's 8:30!
Dad!
[footsteps running downstairs]
[dramatic music]
[suspenseful music]
[woman screaming]
[woman sobbing]
Hon.
Don't use up
all the hot water, okay.
I need a shower too.
I skipped the shower at
the gym this morning.
James.
What are you doing?
He doesn't know anything.
You're just being
paranoid, relax.
So how was your weekend?
It was
amazing.
I worked out,
did some shopping,
had an extramarital
affair that's about it.
What about you?
You're disappointed in me.
I know it was wrong,
completely and utterly.
But, at the time it felt right.
I mean, the guy was cute.
I was horny, and FYI,
a vibrator most definitely
isn't a replacement
for human contact.
So it happened.
What are you doing here?
I sent a text.
I didn't get a text.
Are you certain?
'Cause I did hit send.
I'm very certain.
Well, anyway, I'm here now,
so why don't you
invite me inside?
No.
Does, uh...
Does he know about our
extracurricular activities.
[chuckling softly]
Extracurricular,
I like that word.
I literally like how it
feels rolling about my mouth.
Extracurricular.
Why don't you try it?
Look, I don't have
time for games.
So, if you don't mind,
please leave.
Wow.
Last week you
couldn't get enough,
and now you just
wanna see me go.
That's, uh...
That's a little rude,
don't you think?
Do you want money, is that it?
Oh, no, no, no.
Money does not
take the shame away.
Somethings, they just
stay with you forever.
Look, I was lonely
and things happened.
But I don't wanna
hurt my husband
over a little indiscretion,
so please.
Oh, but there is sin
in your indiscretion.
It molds to you
with great certainty.
Please, let go of the door.
Let go.
Fine.
I'll leave.
But you'll be seeing me again.
Not tomorrow.
Not next week,
but sooner than later.
Just leave!
Castigate.
[chuckling softly]
That's another one of my
favorite words.
To castigate it feels
oddly pleasing in my mouth
like a piece of watermelon
flavored hard candy
on a warm summer day.
[whistling gently]
Castigate this, asshole.
Motherfucker.
Fuck, fuck, fuck shit, shit!
Oh, my god!
James.
This guy has been following me.
It started at the gym,
and now he's followed me home.
He's delusional.
He thinks we've been together.
I'm so scared.
That'll work.
James, baby, I need
to speak to you.
It's really important.
[phone rings]
[man chuckling sinisterly]
Infidelity, I like it.
It just rolls off the
tongue, don't you think?
[woman screaming]
[man chuckling sinisterly]
Getting spun out isn't gonna
make him
call you any faster, you know.
Just like, kickback.
You're tripping.
I'm not stressing anyone.
If I were hypothetically
waiting for a call,
he would be blowing my phone.
Does your ass get
jealous of all the shit
that comes out of your mouth?
So rude.
Come on, let's do this.
I'm good.
I didn't ask if you were good.
So come on.
[Keisha] I don't see why I
have to go.
Alright, beat this car, come on.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
[Keisha] Damn, girl.
[dramatic music]
[locks disengaging]
Hello.
Yo.
This is so hood.
I love it.
Breaking and entry.
What do you know
about the hood, Keisha.
I will let you know
that my minority status
isn't diminished by my
style or education, okay.
I'm 100% Afro-centric
with a dash of Latino goodness,
boo, boo.
Don't you parents even realize
that they're living proof
that two wrongs
don't make a right?
Whatev'.
So, where is this girl?
'Cause I'm hungry and bored.
I don't know stop
riding my bumper, Keisha.
Maybe she's outside playing
Candy Crush.
Or maybe she's
busting out a grumpy.
A what?
A grumpy?
[grunting heavily]
You know [chuckling],
the kind that makes
you strain so much
that the veins in your
neck pop out.
[suspenseful music]
[woman screaming]
You asked.
I'm gonna go check the bedrooms.
Okay, you do that.
But, if you ask me,
I'd check the bathrooms first.
[ominous music]
I brought a friend.
[dramatic music]
What the fuck?
Sam.
[Sam] What?
[Keisha] Did you find her?
[Sam] Yeah.
Great, so we can get
the fuck out of here.
[Sam] Come over here
first then we can leave.
[suspenseful chord striking]
Don't stop.
She was in the bedroom all
this time.
[Keisha] So, she wasn't
taking a shit.
She wants to meet you.
[suspenseful music]
[Keisha screaming]
[dramatic music]
[creature growling]
It's what you wanted.
Now let her go.
Release my sister.
[gentle music]
Jessica.
[suspenseful music]
No.
Jessica, don't leave me.
Please stay.
No, goddammit you promised!
No!
[groaning heavily]
You promised!
Wait where are we going?
I thought we were
getting something to eat?
I have to pick up something
from a friend first.
You wanna come along?
I promised it'll be quick.
I guess, at least I can
put my lipstick on inside.
[thunder rumbling]
[woman screaming]
[suspenseful music]
[creature screeching loudly]
[dramatic music]
[gentle music]
[keyboard clicking]
[suspenseful music]
[Alien] The world is asleep,
dreaming peaceful, safe.
These are the hours I love
when all that I hate is
silent and unconscious.
[gentle music]
The world is different
when people are asleep, better.
I wish they would sleep forever.
But they always wake up
and ruin everything.
[knife pounding
on cutting board]
[gentle dramatic music]
[dramatic choral singing]
[suspenseful music]
[gentle music]