I know what you're gonna say.
Why'd you move the
satellite transponders?
Do I need to ask
the question again?
It's not that big a deal.
Are you joking?
Because even if you
are, it isn't funny.
What you did is a federal crime.
So gimme a little
help here, Bill.
Can you explain to me what
the hell you were doing?
Those antennas were pointed
in the wrong direction.
Okay, here's a month's
worth of research
on the Artemis Belt,
all right, look.
Now we know those meteors
are headed towards Earth,
but up until now, we've been
blindest to when and where.
All right, it's all
right here. Just look.
Shit, Bill, leaving everything
else aside, which we can't.
Are you outta your mind?
You know the US
government monitors
those goddamn satellites.
The NSSDs already called me
three times this morning.
They're sending
someone out right now,
and you want me to
come at them with,
"New Mexico is gonna be
destroyed by a meteor?"
That is the truth.
It's called an impact winter,
if you would just look!
Even if that's
true, don't you think
they would be first in line
to know about it, not you?
Not if they're looking
in the wrong direction.
Okay, I'm sorry. Look,
maybe this is a good thing.
Is that another joke?
Are you a standup comic now?
You suck at being funny.
It's an opportunity
at an audience, okay?
Someone at the national level
needs to listen to this.
We're talking drastic decreases
in global temperature,
mass extinctions upon countless
species, including ours.
He's here.
Shit, he's here.
I haven't had to wear a
fucking tie since 9/11.
Hey, I just need
five minutes, please?
That's not gonna happen.
You're gonna wait inside and
when our conversation ends,
you better hope you're not
taken outta here in handcuffs.
So?
Leave your badge with Brenda.
Take a long vacation.
I don't understand.
You don't understand?
I saved your from going to jail.
Think of this as early
retirement. Enjoy the mountains.
What about my research?
What about Artemis?
If we're faced with an impact-
- Lower your fucking voice.
Impact winter, we're
talking total global freeze.
The dust and the
debris from the impact
are gonna block out
the sun's radiation.
It's gonna make it impossible
heat up the atmosphere.
You're still here?
Listen, Bill, you ever
heard the expression,
"Quit while you're ahead?",
do me a favor and
just do what I ask.
Ungrateful prick.
God...
Has anyone seen Hailey?
Hailey, your niece?
I haven't seen her
since the bouquet toss.
I don't want her
to miss the finale.
I know where she is.
Last time I saw her,
she was in the bathroom
arguing with somebody
on her cell phone.
She said something
about a meteor.
A meteor?
- Yes.
- Seriously?
She said something
about a meteor.
Listen, do you not worry?
Today is your day. I
will go find Hailey.
Thank you.
God, that's weird, huh?
Geez.
Dad, you're
being a little bit paranoid.
What's that noise?
I told you I'm in Vegas,
at Nicole's wedding.
Vegas?
Hailey, listen to me.
In 15 hours a
meter is gonna hit,
and you're not safe in Nevada.
Dad, you know?
I don't have
time to argue with you.
I'm leaving the office.
Meet me at the cabin
as soon as you can.
Hailey?
Yeah, sure. All right.
I'll be there.
Hey.
What? What is it? What happened?
You forgot.
I didn't forget.
I just figured with work and
the images we have to analyze
that, you know, maybe
we could celebrate
the anniversary this weekend?
You know what, I'll
get changed right now.
Our anniversary is next month.
I know that.
Hailey, she didn't
get into Stanford.
Oh...
Stanford was a reach anyway, so-
- She really wanted this.
She wanted to go to the same
school you graduated from.
You know that.
God, you didn't even call to
ask if the letter came in.
I lost track of time.
UNLV, Seton Hall is
still a good choice.
Great backup.
Right...
Kel, this Artemis thing
could change my life.
Our lives.
If I'm right on this live
Ken's desk by the holidays.
Oh my God, she doesn't
care about Ken's desk, Bill.
And you know what? As a
matter of fact, neither do I.
God, you've been just-
You have spent half of
your daughter's senior year
just making empty promises
to the both of us.
How long do you expect us to
sit by and just accept it?
What are you saying?
You leaving me?
I-I don't know.
What I do know is that she'll
blame you for the split.
You know?
And then she'll
resent both of us
for whatever happens after that.
I'll make time for this.
We're not gonna get a divorce.
Here.
What's that?
Call your daughter.
Okay? She needs to know
you still give a shit.
- Dad?
- You're late.
Yeah, I called the
office to let you know
I was running late.
Ken Hollis said
your phone was off.
You called Ken?
Yeah, there's too
much shit going on
for your phone to be off.
Here's footage of
White Sands this morning,
which is part of
the Chihuahua Desert
and is mostly uninhabited.
You can see the catastrophic
devastation of a meteor hit.
Again, this is nothing
to be concerned about,
but authorities will
keep us informed
on if anything else
happens this morning.
Just incredible footage
of a meteor striking.
They've been playing it
over and over, all morning.
I didn't know who else to call.
Where was this?
An hour north of White Sands.
What's wrong?
White Sands?
Yeah, the Chihuahua
Desert, why?
It's exactly where I said
the first impact would hit.
Nothing's out there.
No one was injured.
Yeah, I know that, Hailey,
but this is just the beginning.
There're gonna be more
meteors and more impacts
and they're gonna be closer to
more densely populated areas.
Well, shouldn't you
get back to the office?
Maybe tell someone about this?
What did you do?
I got fired.
Fired?
I did my best to warn
everybody what was gonna happen,
but they let me go.
Three weeks before
tuition is due?
We got more pressing
issues at hand, Hailey.
Like what? Like me not going
to college next
semester, problems?
Like, no one going
to college ever.
Okay, well, what
are you gonna do?
I need to warn people.
A lot of people all at once.
That final wave hits the mountain
range, we're in deep shit.
You can't just put that
kind of thing up on YouTube
and expect millions of
people to take you seriously.
No, that's a good idea.
That's exactly what
we're gonna do.
What, dad, no.
It was an asteroid.
Meteor.
Okay, fine.
It was a small meteor
that landed in the middle
of an empty desert.
Don't you think you're making
a mountain out of a molehill?
You are not listening to me.
I need to tell people
to evacuate the city.
If I'm right,
Albuquerque is next,
followed by the mountains.
Okay, well do
what you need to do,
but you're gonna have to
find somewhere else to go
all ballistic
doomsday this weekend.
What, why? What's
wrong with here?
You don't remember?
Lucas came up here
with me this weekend
before he leaves for Aspen.
Lucas. You had to make a stop?
He's in the car.
And before you say I
never told you about this,
I can show you
the text messages.
But Lucas?
That's my name,
don't wear it out.
Lucas, what a
pleasant surprise.
Be nice.
Why don't you put the bags
in the guest room for us?
You got it, babe.
Oh, and Mr. Z, Hailey told
me all about your job.
Man, awesome. I would hate
to lose something like that.
Like I said, I can show
you the text messages.
All right.
I have to go, but I'll be back.
All right, do me a favor,
promise me you'll
stay put? Stay inside.
Lucas can go out if
he wants to though.
What, why him?
Because I think he's a loser
and I don't care
what happens to him.
I'll be back.
It doesn't
matter. You have to-
Then you gotta put it in order.
Hope it's not an important
phone call? Hang it up, Ken.
Hold on, just a second.
Mr. Zito, I told you
that you cannot be in here.
Now don't you believe me?
What do you think's
gonna happen next?
Do you want people to die, Ken?
I'll call-I'll call you back.
What the hell are
you doing here?
I'm gonna call the police.
Do you want me to call
the police?
No, thank you Brenda.
It'll be fine.
You know I can have
you thrown in jail
just for calling up here.
You have to leave like, now.
12 Hours from now, Ken.
Two more strikes,
one in Albuquerque,
the one after that
in the snow caps.
I don't need to tell
you what kind of damage
that's gonna do.
What do you want
me to do, Bill?
Evacuate the city.
Evacuate the
city? Are you nuts?
I don't have the
authority to do that.
You worked here for six years,
don't tell me you already
forgotten how we paid the rent.
Your name is gonna be
all over the headlines
as the guy who had
this information
and turned a blind eye to it.
Information? This shit
is far from confirmed.
My data is accurate.
Will you just listen to
what I'm telling you, Ken?
Your son, your son,
he's a sophomore
up in Carrington, right?
What's your point?
And be real fuckin'
careful what you say next.
Evacuate the city.
Ken, evacuate the city.
I'm wasting my fucking time.
Son of a bitch.
Good morning.
You didn't come
back last night.
I did.
It was late. Didn't
wanna wake you.
Well, did you get
anyone's attention?
Not really.
Well, maybe you're
wrong about this one.
Fingers crossed.
You're really worried
about this, aren't you?
I tracked Artemis
for six years.
Where's Lucas?
Oh, there it is.
Go.
Go!
What you're looking at
are the first
images coming into-
- Isn't that your building?
- In apparent meteor-
- Holy shit.
Sir.
You need to see this.
Early reports say authorities
are urging individuals
within a 90 mile radius
of the city of Albuquerque
to stay indoors and be
with their families.
Stay tuned for more
breaking news as it comes.
We'll be here detailing the
media attack on Albuquerque,
New Mexico.
Should I call someone?
Get me Zito.
Now.
The number
could be catastrophic.
Fuck.
Yeah, I'm watching
it right now.
Yeah, I can be there in
two hours. I'm on my way.
What's going on?
Lab has been destroyed.
Artemis is getting closer,
I gotta go into town.
Right now? It doesn't look
safe to head into the city.
I don't have time to argue
with you about this, okay?
The next round of impacts,
they're gonna be much worse.
Well, you can't just
leave me here alone.
Well, you have Lucas.
Goddamn it, Where'd
you say he was?
Lucas!
Shit.
What's wrong?
Phone isn't working.
Something's up.
Go back to the house, check
it out. See if he's there.
Lucas!
The hell are you dip shit?
Anything?
Found phone lines
are out at the house.
No sign of Lucas?
Nothing, dad. What
are we gonna do?
How important is
this kid to you?
Dad... I love him.
Let me get my rifle.
Ah.
Ah!
Fuck!
Shit!
Lucas!
He's only been
gone a couple hours.
He couldn't have
gotten too far on foot.
Especially if he has no
idea where he is going.
I'm thinking we're gonna
patrol here or here.
Either one's a hike, so
we need to get moving.
We're running outta time.
Running outta
time before what?
Artemis, more strikes.
Won't be safe out in the open.
And my predictions are correct,
the animals in this area
are gonna get very
confused and very angry.
So Lucas isn't safe either way.
I got about eight hours
till the real fun starts.
So we stick together
and find him
as quickly as possible, yes?
No wondering off.
All right, as time goes by,
we won't have any idea
what's happening out there.
So stay close, understood?
Say it loud so I
know you hear me.
Yes, I understand.
We stick together at all times.
All right, good.
All right, let's go.
Lucas!
Fuck!
Shit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Is it-Is it Lucas?
It's a wolf.
It's close by.
We need to find
your boy. Come on.
Come on.
Lucas!
What is it?
It's been an
hour since we left.
That sun's gonna go down soon.
So?
Well kiddo, I know you're
infatuated with this kid, but...
At some point-
- That's not happening.
It won't be safe for us
once that sun goes down,
do you understand
what I'm saying?
So what, We just
leave Lucas here to die
because you're too
chicken shit to be outside
when it gets dark?
That's not what I meant.
He could be lost.
He could be dead.
What do you see in
this kid, anyway?
He's kind to me.
All the doctor's
appointments, all the therapy,
and Lucas was a cure all
along, who would've thought?
Mom liked him.
She said he made her think of
you when you two first met.
He met your mother?
Thanksgiving, a
week before she left.
Really?
Help me!
Please!
No stopping.
Okay.
You're mad.
You always clam up when
you get mad. What is it?
We can't go on walking
in silence like this.
So whatever you
have to say, say it!
Go on.
You took him to
see your mother.
Here we go.
That's something you
do when you're engaged.
You're not engaged, are you?
No, but what if I was?
That isn't your decision.
And just so you know,
mom was fine with it.
She thought he was
a perfect gentleman.
Don't.
So, whatever problems
you have with Lucas,
get over it, Dad, it's my life.
I'm trying to save your life.
You couldn't save mom's life
and I don't need
you to save mine.
Is that what you
think happened?
I just let her go, that
I allowed that to happen.
Well, if you do, I feel
very sorry for you.
I wasn't there, so I couldn't
bring myself to see it.
Thought it'd be
less real Somehow.
We all know I was wrong.
And I'm sorry, kid.
Trust me, It's gonna haunt
me a lot longer than you.
Look-
- No, you look, I'm going back.
I know Lucas is
important to you,
but millions of people are
gonna die if I don't help them.
Now, I'm not expecting
you to understand that,
but I'm asking you to try.
Now enough, let's go.
Enough!
Lucas?
Lucas.
Lucas!
Is that you?
Hailey!
Lucas!
And he just looks at me
with that oily Russian smile.
Makes me wanna punch the wall.
Oh, and Ken, Ken is
absolutely useless.
You know, he might
as well come out
and say he's on his side.
The fact of the matter is
that research isn't his.
You can't own facts, you know?
You can't put a monopoly
on the solar system
and what's happening
inside of it.
Unbelievable.
Are you listening to me?
Hailey went to see
a movie with Lucas.
Okay?
Did you hear what I said about
this asshole in the office?
Unbelievable.
Yes, I, I heard you,
but you really need
to just stop talking
and listen to what
I have to say.
I asked Hailey to leave
for the night because...
The test came back in
from the doctor's office.
And well, I went down
there this afternoon.
I left you message, I guess
Brenda didn't tell you about it?
No, of course, Brenda didn't
tell me about it. What is it?
The tumor has metastasized.
Metastasized.
The cancer has spread to
another part of my body.
I know what it means,
babe. Which part?
My brain.
Can they operate?
No.
The hospital administrator
called an hour ago.
They can try to remove
the lump from my thyroid,
but it isn't covered by
our medical insurance.
No, that's a mistake.
We have major medical.
You're fully covered.
I called the
insurance company.
They don't consider
an elective procedure-
- This isn't a facelift
we're talking about.
All right, it's a county
hospital, they can't refuse care.
I don't wanna argue with you.
I'm just telling
you what they said.
If they won't cover the
bill, what options do we have?
Cash.
How much?
Kel, how much?
$300,000.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
You know the only
other option is we can-
We can just transfer
my files to regional.
No, absolutely not.
Your doctor's a top
oncologist in the state.
We're not gonna lose
him to save money.
Okay, then what do we do?
Okay, Hailey starts
school in six weeks.
She can go to
community college.
I can't ask her to do that.
Why not?
You know how many
teachers with degrees
are working at Walmart, by
choice, because it pays better?
She'll understand.
She won't understand.
Then she'll
fucking learn to try.
You know, there's one
other thing to consider,
that we do nothing.
You know, just make
me as comfortable
here at home as we can.
I think they called
it quality of life.
The doctor thinks
that since my brain
is considerably beyond the
point of corrective surgery,
that we should, we
should start thinking of-
We should start-Start thinking
of ways to say goodbye.
You know, maybe take a trip.
Make it a happy time.
You're not gonna
die, all right?
I'll fix this.
I don't want to say goodbye.
Okay?
I won't take no for an answer.
Hailey, wake up.
Hailey!
Dad?
What's going on?
Can you move your
arms, hands, anything?
I'm stuck.
If we can rock our
weight back and forth,
I think we can scoot over
that counter, can you see it?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm bleeding.
Me too.
Who did this?
I don't know.
Just do as I say, okay?
Okay, ready?
Just wanna rock on three.
One,
two...
Do you know why I am here?
Interesting research.
Just tell me what you want.
You know what I want?
You really don't remember
who I am, do you?
Liar.
Dad.
Quiet Hailey.
Huh.
Hailey.
You know I had a daughter once.
She was not much younger
than you when she was killed.
Did you know in my country
you would be considered
old enough to marry?
Tell me what you want!
Talk to me!
Artemis.
That's what it was, yes?
The news was showing the
initial onslaught, yes?
Yes. Artemis was-
- I know what Artemis is.
And not because I just read
six years of your research
while you were tied
to fucking a chair.
I know you.
I knew what Artemis
was even before you came
to work at the CSR.
Dad, what the hell
is he talking about?
Your father must be getting
older or have lost his memory
at such a young age.
You know this guy?
Do you want to tell the
girl or would you like me to?
Yeah, I know him.
He's just a former
disgruntled employee.
Yeah?
Yeah, you heard me.
Disgruntled!
You stole my life's
work, you ruined me.
Dad, what's going
on? You're scaring me.
Don't listen to him.
He's full of shit.
Always has been.
Your father. You
say thief and a liar.
He's stole my life's
research on Artemis
and pissed it off as his own.
He's lying!
Call me a fucking liar again
and I'll peel the
flesh from her face!
- All right!
- Dad!
All right!
Let her got, we talk! We talk!
Tell me what you want!
I want what you stole
from me, I want what's mine!
Jesus.
Jesus has nothing
to do with this.
Don't you think it's a
little late for all that? Huh?
Millions of people
are gonna die.
We are gonna die!
Then we will all
die knowing that I
am the man who discovered
Artemis, not you.
How?
There is a telecommunication
station two hours from here.
We make the call from there.
No power.
The station runs off
of gasoline generators.
We leave soon before
the sun goes down.
And you know this
how, you've been there?
You're lack of faith
in me is insulting.
And what if I refuse, huh?
What if I say fuck it,
we're all gonna die, anyway.
Why give you the satisfaction?
Because if you refuse...
I will kill Lucas.
No.
No!
Hey!
Keep fucking moving.
Go.
Is he even still alive?
That depends.
On what?
Don't waste your time.
The man's a psychopath,
look what he's done.
It depends on how often
you insist on stopping
to ask if he's still alive.
I have a right to know.
He's alive for now.
The more time we waste,
the less I can guarantee
you'll still find him that way.
Hailey, Hailey!
No stopping.
We need a break.
We need water.
Keep moving.
I said we need a break.
30 Minutes.
You heard her, half an hour.
He's your friend, what
you do with the time
he has left is up to you.
Does it hurt?
No, I'm alright.
Do you think he's
telling the truth?
You don't understand, kid.
I was trying to make
a name for myself
when your mother got ill.
We didn't have any money
for medical, hospital bills.
I was scared and I fucked up.
I just have to live with that.
And I have lived with it so
I could watch you grow up.
I always thought I could save-
- Dad, you were always
trying to save the world.
I always thought I could
try save your mother.
What about Lucas?
Oh, kid.
Pretty far out.
We don't find him soon,
it doesn't look good.
I understand why
you did what you did.
I love Lucas and if
there's any chance
that he's still alive
and breathing out here,
I'm gonna do whatever
it takes to save him.
All right.
Keep moving!
No more breaks, your
friend's life depends on it.
Go! Go!
No more fucking
breaks, keep moving.
Dad!
Oh.
Go!
Move, go!
Stop.
I need to take a leak.
Think we can get
that gun away from him?
Why would we do that?
I thought we were gonna
make the call first.
Yeah, what if
we make the call,
and he doesn't tell
us where he is?
There's two of us, one of him.
I don't know, if we try
and we don't get the gun
and he kills one of us,
then we don't get to Lucas,
and this was all for nothing.
Yeah, but the call
will be pointless
if there's no one on the
other end to answer it.
You understand?
Stop.
What is now?
I hear you whispering.
Planning something.
Is that a question?
Don't fucking fuck with me.
We were just
talking about Lucas.
What about him?
We need some
assurance he's alive.
We make the call, I
give you the coordinates.
How far away is he
from the com building?
No more questions, move!
No, bullshit.
I need you to be
straight with us here.
You want straight?
I only need you for this.
You wouldn't do that.
Won't I? Try me mother-
- Ah!
Get the gun!
Shoot him!
Get the fuck over there!
Get over there, move!
Lennox.
Please! Just tell
us where it is.
Tell is the coordinates,
just tell us the coordinates.
Tell me, where's the boy?
Please.
You win.
No, no, no.
Lennox!
Lennox.
I'm sorry.
We need to go.
Dad.
We need to keep going.
What's wrong?
Frank called.
Trust papers will be
here in the morning.
Like we discussed.
You'll need to sign.
You up to it?
Well, it still works.
There's a conference
in Santa Fe.
I told Ken to go on without me.
You should go.
I'll make it
through the weekend.
I know that, but
it's done, I'm staying.
No, you don't have to
be to okay with this.
I'll never be okay with this.
I know.
Hey, can I ask you a question?
This thing with the
Russian at work.
What about it?
You already know this,
but if your actions in
this life don't live up
to who you are, then you
really haven't done anything.
You know that thinking
you're doing the right thing
and actually doing it
are two different things?
You need rest.
You can't marry
again, you know?
I'll haunt your
dreams if you do.
I believe it.
You all right?
Did you mean what
you said back there?
You said that we
were all gonna die.
- Hailey.
- Don't do that.
Don't waltz around me
like I'm 10 years old.
Just answer the question.
No one survives impact winner.
No one.
Then what's the
point? Lucas is dead.
We don't know that.
Let's go to the con
building, radio out,
see if there's any
help out there.
Anybody can help
just look for him.
But what if it's
like you said,
what if no one's
there to answer?
I'm trying my best to stay
on top of the situation.
All right, we're almost there
sweetheart, let's keep moving.
I only blamed you
because I needed to believe
that someone killed her and
not some stupid disease.
It was wrong for me to hold
you responsible for that.
I'm so sorry.
I know you loved her
as much as I did.
Okay.
Let's keep moving, all right.
Hold on.
This is it, isn't it?
We need to run,
come on. Go, go, go!
What is this place?
It's an old weather center.
There's nothing here.
There's gotta be a radio.
Find something.
I found it.
Somebody please come in.
Is there anybody there?
Is there anybody
reading me, over?
You're right.
There's nothing here.
No, I don't understand.
I'm waiting.
I don't understand.
It's a goddamn
fallout shelter.
Why did he lead us here?
What's funny? Why
did he lead us here?
You win.
You win?
As he laid there dying,
he whispered, "You win."
"You win," what
does that even mean?
He knew this was the only
place you could survive
what's happening out there.
He was gonna ride
it out down here.
We beat him to it.
Stay right behind me.
Stay close.
What do you think's
going on out there?
God only knows.
Oh, Hey!
Oh!
No, no, no, it's me.
You're alive! Oh, my god,
I knew you were alive-
oh! Yeah, ah, yeah.
Oh my god, your leg.
What happened?
It's nothing.
I tripped, but the Russian
guy, he patched me up.
Hey, Mr. Z.
Bitching gun.
The Russian?
Croatian, Russian,
I don't know.
That part of the world
just bleeds together.
How'd you get in here?
Lennox brought me here.
After he patched me up, he
said he was going downhill
to look for you.
Strange guy, if you ask me.
Really cool accent though.
Any idea if we can
use any of this stuff?
I got only a little
bit of it working
off what little
battery power we have.
The radio is a little spotty,
but the PC can run morse
code if we need it to.
Morse code?
In DOS, yeah.
You know Morse code?
Yeah. Eagle Scouts.
Lucas, you're just
full of surprises.
My guess is no one
answered back, huh?
Nothing yet, but I found
a freezer full of food.
We can wait it out.
Food and water?
For at least six months,
yeah. There's three of us.
I'll tell you what, Lucas,
let's get something to eat first
and then we'll start
on these messages.
Wait, wait, wait.
To who?
Anybody who'll listen.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
How'd you end up logging
into the mainframe?
Oh, easy, I just
figured out the cipher.
Cipher, how?
Easy.
Okay.
A monoalphabetic sub-cipher maps
individual letters
to plain text, right?
So everything's on
a one to one basis.
As in, every instance
of plain text,
there's a matching
cipher letter for it.
Kid stuff.
Okay.
So see this plain
text here and here?
All I had to do to
encipher the firewall
was just to create a shift map.
Enter it as a password.
I'm in.
Jesus, Lucas, English.
Sorry. Okay.
I took every instance
of plain text,
matched it to a cipher letter
from a table I created.
Like I said, candy from a baby.
How'd you know how to do that?
Oh, the internet.
Oh, you read about
it on the internet?
Yeah, yeah. I mean,
it's really interesting.
Makes sense.
First cipher was for
what, Julius Caesar?
It was just simple
shift mapping,
but it was still
complex for its time.
Okay, so what's the password?
It's a weird one.
Zephyr.
Like the skateboard. We went
to the warp tour that one time.
Lucas, I may have seriously
underestimated you, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too, about the
whole end of the world thing...
And your job...
College.
But, none of that matters
now because, well...
Artemis sent
Earth into an impact winner
just as Lennox predicted.
And just seven hours after
the tops of the mountains
were struck, the surface
temperature fell 30 degrees,
never returning
above freezing again.
We were never supposed
to prevent Artemis
from destroying our planet.
We were only meant
to survive it.
Testing. Testing.
Okay.
News?
No. Small blips on the
radar, nothing to brag about.
Transmissions?
Same as yesterday.
You see anything out there?
I took about
halfway down the base
and sun's starting
to peek through.
A couple more weeks,
we could get lucky.
Food's running low.
There's enough for three.
Four.
Thought you were checking
the tower antennas.
I was, but Lucas
insisted he do it.
Really?
It's a lot of stress
climbing up that far.
Stress?
What the hell is going on?
Either one of you can answer me.
- I'm pregnant.
Sorry. No, she's
pregnant, not me.
I'm the one that did the
impregnating and fun-
- Oh, I got that.
- Sorry...
- Thanks Lucas.
Well, what do you think?
You're gonna be a grandpa?
I don't know why
that sounds so strange.
Man, we thought you'd be mad.
Put her there dad.
Too soon.
Yeah. Yeah. It's
too-My fault.
Lucas, please.
My only concern is
medical supplies.
What if you go into
labor? I am not trained.
Santa Fe Command, does anyone copy?
Santa Fe, coming in.