- There was a list, a long one.
All your names are on it.
♪ Gotta beat the circumstances ♪
♪ Try hard to get by ♪
♪ Trying to see a million
in cash 'fore I die ♪
♪ Gotta see a million in cash 'fore I ♪
♪ Circumstances ♪
♪ Gotta beat the circumstances ♪
♪ Try hard to get by ♪
♪ Trying to see a million
in cash 'fore I die ♪
♪ Gotta see a million in cash 'fore I ♪
♪ Circumstances ♪
♪ Same OG, same old me ♪
♪ Real nigga business
in the game, low-key ♪
♪ 99 problems, seen a
couple million dollars ♪
♪ I'ma still keep it pimpin'
'cause the game won't flee ♪
♪ Racks on deck, money on the couch ♪
♪ Down, bad bitch, got
a dozen in the house ♪
♪ See me getting money ♪
♪ Now these niggas acting funny ♪
♪ And these suckers got a warrant ♪
♪ Trying to run up in my house ♪
♪ Tell 'em, "Back up," ♪
♪ FBI wanna track us ♪
♪ 'Cause my ho's to the track up ♪
♪ All we know is rack up ♪
♪ Money get us with the side tuck ♪
♪ Doing numbers 'til we back up ♪
- I'm sorry, I can't do it.
- Your record is cleared.
No identity.
You don't exist.
- I was wondering when he was going to
try to cut all his loose ends.
And doing this, what do
you think that makes you?
It's just a vicious cycle.
And when do you think it all ends for him?
Does it hurt?
- When does it end?
- Well, the dead has arisen.
- Bone?
- We thought you checked out, boy.
- Oh, what's up?
- Yeah, don't worry about that.
We gonna take care of that
soon enough, all right?
Glad you're back, man.
- What?
What happened?
- So was there anything in particular
that you're interested in?
You need a two-door, four-door, SUV?
- Nah, I just need something low-key
so I can get back to Milwaukee.
- Is there a
price range you wanna be in?
- Don't matter the price.
- I got you, okay.
I might have a few things, though.
Let me grab some keys,
I think I got some cars.
- Cool.
- Be right back.
- T.A., T.A., T.A.
- Fuck.
- You know, you're a hard brother to find.
Not good to show your face.
- Figured I'd give myself
a moment to breathe.
- Stupid and not like you,
but apparently you've been doing
a lot of things out of character.
- Come on now, nigga.
That shit was faked, man.
You know I don't get down like that.
- Maybe, but that's not
a chance I could take.
Plus, I'll be doing a lot of
other acquaintances a favor.
- Now, you know you don't
gotta do this, right?
- I wouldn't do that if I was you.
Might as well give that to
me and come on for this ride.
Not completely stupid.
Good.
You seen which way he went?
Fuck.
- That motherfucker know we on his ass,
so you know he ain't gonna
get caught slipping twice.
- We make him come to us.
Heard he got a girl back at
his old stomping grounds.
- In motherfucking Milwaukee?
- Let's see if he misses her.
- You bet.
- Agent Bender, sir.
Bender, sir.
- What?
What is it?
- I followed up on a lead
that's relating potentially
to the Little Dawn case.
- Uh-huh.
- You see, we've stumbled
across something big.
Connections, networks,
and it puts all of us
right in the center.
- What do you need?
- I need a all-hands-on-deck approach.
- Miraflores, have you asked her for help?
- Sir, this is more than just one person.
- What's she working on?
- Stop!
Don't move.
- I'm sorry.
I know what I said,
but I have to finish this.
I have to go back.
- You hit hard with your strong ass.
- Oh, I can hit a whole lot harder.
Why'd you run?
- Someone starts chasing me with a gun,
I don't stick around.
- You heard me yelling, and
I know you saw my badge.
- I can get one of those
delivered to my house tomorrow.
- There's a killing spree
going on in this city, okay?
And the monster that did it
is staying at a warehouse you own.
- Look, two envelopes filled with cash
showed up in my PO box outta nowhere,
talking about renting out my warehouse,
pays for a given timeframe.
- And?
- And I accepted.
- Well, that seems unprofessional.
- I got paid.
That's all the professionalism I need.
- Yeah, that's right, 'cause you're a
all-about-the-money type, right?
- Thought you feds was
too busy getting killed
to worry about little old me.
- Good people died, you hear me?
He paid for a spot.
Tell me who he is.
Don't.
- Don't what?
- Don't try and talk me out of it.
- So you know it's a problem.
- The only problem is, is that
he's out there a free man.
I looked that monster in the
face and I didn't do anything.
- Well, good.
From everything you've told me,
that's not enough evidence
to bring in a random guy.
- That was his car in the parking lot.
It was him.
- Let's say you're right,
with everything we know about him,
and you try to take him alone,
do you really think you'd be
standing here with me today?
You've got to let this go.
- Man, you'd just think, with
a description of his face,
there has to be something in the database.
- And there wasn't.
- With a skillset like that?
There has to be a rap sheet or something.
- Some people fall through the cracks.
- Cracks?
No one should be allowed
to walk through a city,
flip it on its head, and
then just go about their day.
- Look, you need to channel
this energy into something constructive.
Gruber's got this prison thing,
scheme or something he told me about.
Why don't you go see if
you can help him with that?
- What about this Tyler?
Maybe I ought to go see what he knows.
- Tyler Franklin?
- Yeah.
- No, that's a no-go.
Apparently we didn't cross
our t's and dot our i's.
- He almost shot and killed an agent
in the middle of a shootout.
There's no double-checking needed.
You can't be serious.
- Goddamnit, I said no.
- Sir.
- The kid's a screw-up.
He's gonna screw up again.
- So we just give up.
- Do I need to remind you that we won?
- And I wonder at what cost.
- Who this?
- Dorian, it's me, nigga.
Look, I know you're in
Milwaukee right now,
and I know what the fuck
you're trying to do too.
- And what's that?
- Yeah, I overheard your
loud ass last time we met up.
- You're a sneaky little
hiding motherfucker, just like a snake.
- Nigga, listen carefully.
I'm gonna say this one time.
Don't do this shit.
- Aw, a snake who's in love.
Let me guess, you here too, huh?
I'll take that as a yes.
- Nigga, we go way back.
- You got two options.
- You ain't gotta do this shit.
- Two options.
You come with us and die like a man,
or she's gonna die like
the bitch that she is.
- So you wanna try to play me?
- Don't test my patience.
Call me when you're ready, bitch.
- Man, I'm about sick and
tired of all this walking.
- One more time around the block.
- I'm good.
- No, you're lucky.
- Bone, you didn't tell
me you was coming by.
- My man, I just wanted
to come check on you, Ty.
How you doing, man?
- Ripping, still moving.
- That's good, that's all that matters.
- I can't thank you enough.
- Man, listen, that's nothing.
That's what we do, you understand?
- Yeah.
But you know, I don't know how or what,
but I will repay you.
- Gratitude.
That's what it is, man.
That's the kind of energy
we need around us, baby.
Somebody else gotta take over
this shit now, you feel me?
- Take over?
- Nigga, you funny.
With T.A. and Key out the picture,
somebody gotta take the reigns.
Might as well be you.
- That's a lot of responsibility.
- And I'm glad you understand that.
So I'm gonna leave you two
lovebirds to it, all right?
Get yourself together, man.
We got a lot of work to do, baby.
- All right.
- Hey, Miss, you wanna take a stroll?
- That's sweet, but I'm not looking
for a relationship right now.
- Agent Miraflores,
I've been looking for you.
- And why is that?
- 'Cause I heard you're
looking for a killer,
and I thought I might be of service.
- Look, I don't have time for dead ends.
- Well, how about a family member of his?
You wanna take that stroll?
♪ Green, green, green ♪
♪ I can hear the money callin' my name ♪
♪ Green ♪
- Oh, it's boring.
You wanna play a game or something?
What's wrong with you?
- When he said, "Run things,"
do you think he meant everything?
- I don't know.
- Really, like, do you
know what this means?
- I know I don't have a good
feeling about this or him.
I was so excited to come
back home after graduation,
but I had to come back
home to you in a coma.
You know, at first, I
was supposed to be sad,
but I was more mad that you put yourself
in this type of situation.
Then I thought, "Maybe he
would wake up and realize
that you don't belong up
in this type of world."
And I'll be here to help
you walk right away from it.
And here you is, ready to go
right back into it.
- I can't just walk away.
- Yes, you can, Tyler.
This isn't your life.
- Look around.
I'm an orphan that came from the dirt.
No help, no assistance, no love.
How do you think I got here, honest work?
- Tyler, you do have someone.
- Angela...
- Tyler, my family is moving.
- And?
- And they want me to go with them.
- You a grown-ass woman.
You don't gotta go nowhere
you don't wanna go.
What about that nice job you got?
- The city's starting to
be too violent for them.
And I believe it's a little
too violent for me too.
- What about us?
What do you want?
- I want a reason to stay.
♪ Green, green, green ♪
♪ I can hear the money callin' my name ♪
- I heard about the bodies
piling up in Milwaukee,
and I only know one man that
can create that kind of ruckus.
- Okay, and who are you?
- Reginald Banks.
He is my nephew.
My niece, bless her sweet soul,
I finally got custody of
her when she was seven.
They were married when
they were in their 20s.
- Okay, listen, I can get a history lesson
some other time, okay?
I need the important stuff, like his name,
where he lays his head, stuff like that.
- But I think you need to know who he is
and understand why he is the way he is
if you wanna stop him.
You remember the Moncado sweep?
- Yeah, the disappearance
of the ACEs Organization.
It was a bloodbath,
but I thought it was some
government conspiracy
that wiped 'em out.
It had to be, for all of them
to end up dead like that.
- Nah, no group, no
secret government agents.
Just one man.
- Not possible.
- You would think.
But what they did unleashed
an evil in him that I see now
that he can't even turn off.
He's a different breed, Miraflores,
and I think you know that.
You know, he's not perfect.
No killing machine is.
And what they did to his daughter,
to my niece, was unimaginable.
And you ask yourself maybe
why I didn't try to
talk him out of it then.
I don't know, but I can't sit back now.
The death has to stop.
- And I couldn't agree with you more.
But until you give me a name,
there's nothing I can do.
- I can give you three.
- No, no.
Stay home.
Please don't go.
T.A.
♪ Yeah, I got cheese, but
I ain't gotta spin it ♪
♪ Pussy's free when I'm up in it ♪
♪ That's your girlfriend ♪
♪ I probably done hit it ♪
♪ My bad, dog, just gonna kill you ♪
♪ You want one in the mouth ♪
- Okay.
So I called this meeting today
to express my gratitude to all y'all
for holding shit down
through this rough time.
It's been a fucked-up six
months, but we made it.
Now, if we finna get
back to this real money,
it's time for us to appoint a new head,
and that's gonna be Ty.
♪ They always come back,
but I never keep 'em ♪
- My dog, really?
This little nigger?
- Yeah, this little nigger.
♪ I fuck too good, but
you can't leave me ♪
All right, back to business.
♪ I can't shoot that if it ain't human ♪
♪ I can't hit that if she ain't free ♪
♪ But I can't get back
if she gonna pay me ♪
♪ Just sit back, relax ♪
- Hey dog, you good?
- Are you sure about this?
- Listen, man, all you
gotta do is make sure
that when you tell a
motherfucker to do something,
you drop your hand firm,
and they gonna fall in line.
- You think?
- Absolutely.
Plus, T.A. would've wanted it, trust me.
You got this, man, all right?
- Ooh, boy, I see you.
Big dog on campus.
What's up, Bone?
- What's up, bruh?
I'm finna get up outta here, man.
Congratulations, all right?
♪ Real fly shit, I love
that for my posse ♪
- So you ready for this?
- I hope so.
- This shit real business.
It's that part where you can't pass up.
It's everything.
- You can never pass up a good donut, huh?
- Long time, no see.
- You didn't get my greeting cards?
- I didn't
know you were still here.
- Is that why you contacted Miraflores?
Been back for a little bit.
Just trying to get the lay
of the land before I execute.
- Do you hear yourself?
It's eating you alive, isn't it?
The death, the mayhem, the rage.
You have to let it go, please.
This is not about family anymore,
and this is not what they would want.
- There's a lot of things
they wouldn't have wanted.
You need to leave the city
before things pop off.
- Please.
- Leave, now.
- No.
- Come on, you haven't even
heard what I have to say yet.
- You still working that hitman case?
- Yes.
- Then no.
- I'm so close to having
something good on him.
- What do you charge a
man that can't be found?
- You're scared.
Why?
You used to work close with Bender,
that's the reason I came
to you in the first place.
- Too many people close to him
have ended up dead or missing,
and I want no part of it.
- This case or Bender?
- Both.
- You don't trust him.
- I don't trust anyone, especially you.
- You swore an oath.
I have something that can
make everything right.
- This is my private number.
Only call me if you
have something concrete.
- Yeah.
- US Attorney O'Malley,
we need to get eyes on him.
- How come I didn't
know about this place?
- It's above your pay grade.
- Why?
- You'll see.
- Another disloyal-ass nigga.
My, these niggas.
I swear, nigga, I thought you was
a better nigga than that.
You already had to kill his cousin.
Man, these motherfuckers,
man, I swear to God.
- Who the fuck is that?
- Some clown who thought
it was a good idea
to try to take advantage of us
when we thought we was at a weak spot.
So this nigger's name is The Messenger.
That's who that is.
- That ain't shit.
You seen this shit before.
You a body.
- He probably going to clean the shit
out his pants right now, man.
- Man, what happened to you, man?
Man up.
- You know you need somebody
that can handle this shit.
Ty, my guy, he can grow
into it in due time.
But do we got time?
Let's get this nigger up outta here, man.
- You should've left me alone.
- You should have done a
better job at disappearing.
- My files, are they gone?
- Did you think
I'd completely erase them?
Don't worry, they're not
in the system, but they're somewhere.
- Where?
- Why don't you ask him?
- No flashing your badges?
No reading me my rights?
- No, this one's off the books.
You were an idiot for coming here.
It's not like you.
It's almost like you wanna die.
Holy shit, you do wanna die.
Well, the good news is,
is that's gonna happen.
But it's up to you on how painful
the experience is gonna be.
Who did you tell?
- Tell who what?
- Who knows about me?
I need names.
- I got nothing for you.
- I'm gonna ask you one last time.
Who knows about me?
- You're paranoid, and this
isn't gonna end well for you.
You can't cover up everything.
- I don't have to.
I've got everything on
everyone, including you.
If I go down, this gets leaked.
You see, I will always win.
We will always win,
because we understand the
necessity of what we do.
What the fuck was that?
- A dislocated thumb.
- Fuck.
- Damn,
these motherfuckers, man,
I swear to God.
Bitch-ass nigger.
- Baby, I can barely keep
eye contact with anyone.
Can't eat, can't sleep,
can't even think straight.
I feel unstable.
But thanks for coming, though.
I needed this.
You know, when I'm around you,
I feel like I can breathe again.
- You need to go get help.
You need to go see somebody.
People aren't meant to experience
the things that you have.
- I can't.
- Don't say you can't afford it.
- I'm just too busy.
- What, too busy with Bone?
Don't seem like it help.
- It doesn't matter.
- But you do.
Don't forget that.
- Make sure
your motherfucking pipe
ain't on safety, too, nigga.
- Nigga, Glocks ain't got no safety.
- Fuck up.
I don't like that shirt, you know?
- I don't like your mustache.
- You thought you was
on a fucking X-Men movie
with that shirt on?
Dumb-ass shit.
- Man, that's how you gonna do it?
- Man, where the fuck is this bitch at?
- Man, I don't know,
but he need to hurry up.
Man, I don't know what's going on.
- Oh shit, here this nigger go again.
Fuck dude want, bro?
- Change?
Change?
- Man, I ain't got no fucking change, man.
- Change?
Now, where the fuck is Dorian at, nigger?
- 4919 North 19th, nigger.
- Ah, about damn time.
I wasn't gonna wait too
much motherfucking longer.
You ready to man up?
- You shouldn't have come here.
- I can go wherever the fuck I please.
You know, like that little restaurant
where that pretty little thing works at.
- You sure you wanna do this?
- 100%.
Hey, listen, leave me waiting any longer,
and that bitch dead tonight.
- Was a third option, motherfucker.
- T.A.?
- Nigger, I thought you was dead.
- Me too, but I'm still alive.
- And free.
- I know, crazy.
You know what they said about you?
I know you wouldn't.
- I know you know.
There's some other niggers
that I'm worried about.
- Bone's nephew.
But thanks to you, I got put on top.
- On top, huh?
Congratulations, li'l bro.
You're moving up in the world.
- You should come by,
check us out sometime.
You know I got your back.
- Nah, I'ma lay low for a little bit.
But I'ma beat through for sure.
- Whoa.
Bar fight?
- What?
Oh, long story.
Anyway, what do you need?
- What's going on?
- There were a string of homicides
last night that look targeted.
- Well, and the local PD can't handle it?
- Miraflores, it's his work.
Our favorite hitman, he's back.
- And I'm the last to know?
- Knowing you, I figured
you were already on it.
- Well, how am I supposed to know?
- You make any headway on his identity?
- No.
- You need to come to me
with any new info directly.
- What's up, man?
- I'm good.
- Just checking on you, man.
You gonna bring this place down.
- I'm just taking it all in.
- Good, 'cause it's all yours, homie.
- And you won't believe who's back.
- Don't tell me.
- T.A.
- Wow.
- Told him to come by, but you know,
he wanted to lay low for a minute.
- Man, I never even thought
he would've came back, that's all.
That's good, though.
He just gave another reason to celebrate.
Go grab us a waitress.
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ So I don't complain ♪
♪ Just part of the game ♪
♪ When you livin' down, you're low, yeah ♪
♪ They say you get one life ♪
♪ Say you get one life ♪
- Goodbye, guys.
- No!
Jesse?
Oh no!
No, no, baby, no, no.
No, no!
- It's been a while
since we met like this.
Must be big.
- There was an execution-style
shooting last night.
Suspect was wearing a black face mask.
- He really is back.
Well, why just bring me in?
We need everyone on this.
- In due time.
But first, I need you to tell me
everything you've gathered about him.
- It's not much, you know that.
- So who've you been talking to?
When are the lies gonna stop?
I know you know something.
- Yeah, and I can say
the same thing to you.
- I know you've been talking
to Attorney O'Malley.
I hate what has to happen next.
- When did you lose your soul?
The murders, are they really him?
- I don't know, I don't care.
We got more important
issues to worry about.
- Yes, you do.
I'm glad we're all here.
Did you tell her who hired me?
Like I believe you said,
"Cleanse the city."
- I did what I had to.
- And what was that?
- I took responsibility.
I took on the burden of everyone's sins.
- That job's already taken.
- You were just a tool for bloodshed.
- But yet you tried to get me killed?
- Some tools gotta be thrown
away after their first use.
- Stop.
Good people died.
And if you're the one to blame,
then maybe you won't
be leaving here alive.
- Bone.
Bone is the other side of the coin.
He understands.
- No, I did my research.
He's just T.A.'s cousin
with a few connections.
- Connections, indeed.
He understands balance and order,
which the two of you could be a part of.
- Two guns to your head, and
now you want us to team up?
I don't think so.
- No, stop.
Both of you are going in.
- He's not leaving alive.
- You're not making the shots, okay?
I am.
You're not calling 'em for me.
- He's not leaving alive.
- Are you just gonna give
him the easy way out?
He has to face the consequences.
- Cute, but my plan's more effective.
- And where has that gotten you?
- And so they took everything from me.
They didn't deserve what
those monsters did to them.
There's no purpose, no life.
Choices are made by the
ones with the biggest stick.
- Do you believe that?
- Does it matter?
- Dimitri, is
that what they believed?
- Don't.
- Allayah and Alana?
- Uncle already told you everything, huh?
- Enough.
We both just want this
senseless violence to stop.
- It's all senseless, isn't it?
- You're the one to talk.
- I'm the one to finish it.
- The mayhem, it
won't stop with you, will it?
What if we just finished it?
All of it.
This has to come to an end.
Everyone has to go down,
which in turn means you won't have to
keep looking over your shoulder.
I can't give you a way out like you want,
but how about a peaceful night of sleep?
- This could all be pinned on Bender.
- That's
just gonna bring him down.
He has to have some sort of paper trail.
- His hard drive, it's
how he protects himself.
It'll have all the evidence you'll need.
- Can you get it?
- You mean you need me to
do the illegal stuff, right?
- Look, if you get it to me,
I can get it to the right person.
- You must be hopeless.
- Call it angry.
You know, I made myself a
promise that when I found you,
I wouldn't let you get away again.
- Well, it looks like I'm
not going anywhere for now.
- And Bender?
- The idiot is paranoid.
We'll find him.
We just have to wait on him to slip up.
- We'll need to
figure out a way to get the-
- I'll take care of it.
Just give me time.
- How could
I possibly trust you?
- Trust my need for revenge.
- Where the fuck is this fat motherfucker?
It's about damn time.
- Are you serious?
FBI's all over my ass.
I can't take a piss without
looking over my shoulder,
and you're sitting here just
like it's a perfect day.
- That hard to leave?
- What do you think
I've been trying to do?
And it takes you two
weeks after I've been made
to answer my calls?
I need a way out.
- And you come to me for that?
- After all I've done,
it's the least you owe me.
- I don't owe you shit.
I just happen to be your only
option of a fast getaway.
They froze all your accounts,
got all kind of warrants on your ass,
and you can't get in touch
with your other connections.
Don't forget who you're
talking to, Bender.
- Oh, I know who I'm talking to,
but if I go down, you go down too.
- You like casinos?
I like a nice night at
Potawatomi every now and then.
- And your point?
- I'm a humble, simple, betting man.
And for a while, you
were actually a good bet.
The eyes on you now, not so good.
- Bone, don't do this.
- Make it look like a suicide.
He couldn't handle the
stress of what he did
to this great city of his.
- I know you know about the hard drive.
I got people who will release that info
if anything happens to me.
- You mean this hard drive?
Careful who you trust, Bender.
Some people actually like
money more than relationships.
- After all I've done for
you, this is how it ends?
- See you around.
- He knows about you.
He'll be coming.
- Good, I need the exercise.
- Just get off me, man.
Get off me, man.
♪ The worst came to me ♪
♪ But they ain't gonna stop saying ♪
- All right, yeah, gimme about 10 minutes.
I'm gonna take care of
something real quick, all right?
I'll call you.
♪ I'm ready for booty-shake ♪
- What's up, cuz?
♪ This shit ain't new to me ♪
- What's going on?
- You good?
- I'm good.
Are you good?
- Sure.
- All right, gimme a minute, I'll be out.
♪ I don't fuck white shit
'cause I'm true to me ♪
♪ That floor is my pain,
that floor is my hurt ♪
♪ I was raised under the
pavement, I rose from the dirt ♪
♪ Harsh excuses for my nigger ♪
- Look at this bitch ass.
- His punk ass probably shot you.
- Can't believe you, dog, man.
- Get this fucking rat outta here, man.
♪ Watch me go harder for my tribe ♪
♪ Send the shot, muffle my ears ♪
- Appreciate it, bruh.
♪ You see the hate up in my eye ♪
- These bitch-ass niggas, man.
- Man, fuck them niggers, man.
You know niggers gonna talk for a minute.
That shit ain't nothing.
It'll blow over.
- Yeah, you right.
Fuck 'em.
- Yeah.
Man, I heard about Autumn.
That's messed up.
- Yeah, man.
- Sorry about that, man.
Good to have you back, though.
- Appreciate it, cuz.
- Yeah.
I got something nice for you.
- Look, man, I appreciate y'all
keeping the streets clear for a nigger,
but I need to lay low for a-
- Nah, nah, you wanna see this.
- Who the fuck is that?
- That's the nigga in the mask.
♪ I don't fuck white shit
'cause I'm true to me ♪
♪ True to me ♪
♪ I anticipated the
fuckery, highly prepared ♪
♪ It's rushing on your face ♪
- That nigga is mine, bruh.
Don't nobody touch him but me.
- No doubt.
But you know he ain't easy to find.
But maybe-
- Man, listen, fuck all that.
He gonna show up at some point.
And when he do, point him to me,
and everybody get the fuck outta my way.
- Welcome back, dog.
♪ Caged, I don't wanna release the beast ♪
- Hey, cuz.
Appreciate you.
- Always.
♪ Look the devil eye to eye ♪
♪ The pain was my survival guide ♪
- Larry, Alan, Forregan,
Gruber, front and center.
Good.
You're fired.
Drop your guns and your badges.
You're done.
If you have a problem with this,
you can check out the big old file we got
about all your illegal
and problematic activities
that have been going on around here.
Oh, please test me.
Goodbye.
Hello.
My name is Jacobi Norman.
Don't worry about a
title for me right now.
Just understand I'm Mr.
Head Honcho in charge here
for the time being.
And as such, I'm here to let you know that
they found Bender dead
by suicide in his house.
Neighbor reported hearing a gunshot,
and police went in and found his body.
As shocked and as unprepared
as you are by this,
that puts a cold chill down my spine.
I need to know about every single case
you guys got going on.
So get your shit together,
because I want reports on my
desk by the end of the day.
We are gonna start...
What's this stuff still
doing on the ground?
Come on, people, we are not Congress.
We are gonna start working with efficiency
and common sense around here.
Can someone please get
this where it belongs?
And the rest of you start
working on those reports.
You, come with me.
- I'm sorry, sir.
You all right?
- Yeah.
- You should know we checked
every inch of Bender's place,
and he was long gone.
- Yeah, I know.
Looks like the guilt brought him back.
- That doesn't make any sense.
- Nothing does in this
corrupted-ass place, except for you.
Look, I don't believe
this was a suicide either.
And I am positive that the
autopsy's gonna confirm that.
- So what was it, a distraction?
- You know, when I read your reports,
I just knew I was gonna like you.
There's a lot you can tell
about an agent from their reports.
You know what I can tell about you?
- No, what?
- You're trustworthy.
And you confirmed that again
by figuring all this out about Bender.
- Well, thank you, but I
can't take all the credit.
He kind of revealed himself.
- Look, I assume that you know that
the hitman is back in the city.
- Allegedly.
- Right.
So do you happen to have any clue
where he allegedly might be?
- No, no.
I wish I did.
- As do I.
As do I.
- Looks like the VPs are
trying to test our patience.
They've been popping up in
seven of our territories.
- Why ain't we taking off?
- That was it, we already tried that.
In my opinion, we're
still in recovery mode.
I think it's better-
- You've gotta be fucking
kidding me, right?
"In my opinion, I think..."
This that bullshit.
This little nigga can't even come through
with his mind made up.
Bone, you should be the one-
- I'm just a man waiting
on orders like you.
- From a kid?
- You can talk to me, nigga.
- And what you gonna do with
that besides make me mad?
♪ I can't entertain you
niggers, I'll be too busy ♪
- Exactly.
Nothing, like I thought.
Now put that little shit down
and get back to barking
your weak-ass orders.
♪ I can't entertain you
niggas, I'll be too busy ♪
♪ Pick your punk ass up, it
ain't even wet over there ♪
♪ I drive soft, and that
part, it got so hard ♪
♪ Sludgehammer for the
dog, it was so hard ♪
- You good, boy?
♪ I get mad at them
testers for no charge ♪
♪ And when there's beef,
I'll be in the bushes ♪
- Next time you pull that
thing, be ready to use it.
No time for hesitation.
When there's a move to be made, move.
Come on, bruh.
♪ I'm like every group of
what you need, just one call ♪
♪ 24 hours, bitch, I'm like Adderall ♪
♪ Nigger trying to take ♪
- Babe, where you wanna eat at?
- Um...
- Man, come on, stop playing.
- What?
What do you mean?
- 'Cause I was gonna beg you
to make a choice like usual,
just so we can end up
eating at Sherman Phoenix.
- Because I like Sherman Phoenix.
- I do too, but maybe we
just switch it up a little.
- Okay.
Well, let's switch it up, then.
- We're going to Sherman Phoenix?
- Yes.
What happened to your hand?
- I got angry.
- And who was on the
other side of that anger?
- Someone that just kept
running their mouth.
I tried to keep it cool.
- But you didn't.
Tyler, if you keep on
going down this road,
it's gonna change you for the worst.
- What if I'm already changed?
When I got shot, I went down as one man.
But when I'm with you,
I feel myself again.
I feel good.
- So what happens when you're not with me?
You know, for the longest
time, I dreamt of the day
that you will wake up and see
the stupidity of all of this.
But then we thought
that you was gonna die.
You know, I just...
I felt like I failed you.
Then you made it through,
and I just felt like
I should have just told
you all my worries.
You know, I wish that you would see
the chance that God gave
you to leave this life.
- I can't just leave.
- Yes, you can, Tyler.
It's destroying you.
Don't you see that?
- Long work day?
- Was it you?
- Was what me?
- We had a plan.
All we had to do was wait
for the right moment.
Why?
- What are you talking about?
- Stop playing dumb, okay?
I put my career on the line for this plan.
If they find out...
Why'd you kill Bender?
It wasn't you.
Then who?
- Somebody powerful who probably still
has the hard drive right now,
if they didn't destroy it already.
- Who could it be?
- How far did you take Bender at his word?
- Now?
Not as far as I can throw him.
- We have no other leads.
- Bone.
- I'll look into it.
- Well, you better pray he has it.
Oh, and Dimitri, don't you
ever come into my home again.
Oh my God.
You want me to what?
- Just let it sink in, okay?
You don't have to make
any decisions right now.
- Well, what about you?
- Me?
No, my time here is not permanent.
I'm more of a stepping stone.
- Oh.
- An exampled standard of what
the new head honcho oughta be.
- And you want that to be me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Sir, there are other agents
that have been here longer than me,
and I'm not qualified.
- Oh, gimme a break.
Qualifications are just
words on a piece of paper.
You've seen more in the last
year than half these agents
are gonna do in their entire careers.
Now, you need to understand something.
You got the attention of all
the right guys at the top,
and they think you can do this.
And more importantly, they can trust you.
- Sir, how do I lead people
that don't respect me
and, to be honest, I don't trust?
- Yeah, that is an unfortunate
occupational hazard,
especially in your case.
Look, all I'm asking you
to do is think about it.
There's no rush, okay?
- I know we in recovery
mode and all that shit,
but we could be making bigger moves.
Tyler my dude, but we need to be loyal
to this shit here first.
That nigger ain't good for it neither.
Moving too scary, moving too slow.
- Why'd you say that?
- I'm saying that 'cause he
ain't built for this shit,
not for no shot-calling.
I don't know why Bone picked him,
but shit, we gonna handle
his understandable mistake
so we could get things back
to how they used to be.
♪ Gotta be there for my children ♪
♪ So they don't make the
same mistakes as me ♪
♪ Taught you how to get it ♪
♪ So you ain't never gotta wait on me ♪
- Tyler, my family is
moving in a couple of days.
We've been ignoring the inevitable.
- I don't see any packed boxes.
- Yeah, and I haven't put in
my two weeks at work either.
You wanna know why?
- Because you want me to change?
- No, because I love you.
You don't see that?
You don't see that I had chosen you?
Why can't you choose me?
- I have.
- As long as you've chosen
this world, Tyler, you haven't.
- Is this what this is?
The crew or you?
- No, I'm just...
Looks urgent.
- Man, I gotta go.
- You know what, you're right.
It's either them or it's me.
♪ He had to focus on survival ♪
- Don't do this.
I'll be back.
♪ No one was there to teach me ♪
♪ I cut off all the fake niggers ♪
♪ So no one's there to leach me ♪
- I can't believe, brother.
- Man, what are you doing?
- Well, unfortunately, your OG here
just happens to be a fucking snake.
We've been tracking his movements
and come to find out
he been sneaking behind our backs,
killing our fucking people.
- So now what?
You kill the killer?
- No, you will.
- Why?
- I can appreciate your hesitancy,
but this nigger's full of envy,
and there ain't no room
for no motherfucker like
that in this organization.
He got to go.
He been plotting on you this whole time,
and you fell for it.
Good thing word got
back to me when it did.
Ain't that right, Jay?
- Gimme a reason why I shouldn't
blow your brains all over this floor.
- Nigger, you weak.
You don't know shit.
I know it and they know it.
I wouldn't give a fuck if
you was my mama, nigger.
- Listen, I know that was hard to do,
but it was very necessary.
Now it's time to celebrate.
- Man, I think I need to go.
- You need to go?
Listen, I don't have the time for that.
You just killed one of your own,
and you did it for a valid reason.
You can't be showing no weakness,
I keep telling you that.
You keep doing that shit,
nobody's gonna listen to you, right?
Be able to grab the first one,
and you know, you take me over there,
I can handle that shit, nigga.
You know what I'm saying?
- Bone.
- Yeah.
- Why you had me do that, man?
This isn't the game.
This is death.
- This the part of the game
you need to understand, young dog.
You see, it ain't all about
fucking bitches and getting money.
You know that, right?
It's deeper than that.
All this shit we got?
Blood, sweat, and tears,
hustling on them corners,
well before you came along.
What you need to understand is
this shit requires you to
know how to move pawns.
And when you learn that,
then you can do this shit.
- A pawn?
That's all I am?
- Listen, no one lives
forever, not even me.
As much as I would like to think that,
it's just not realistic.
You know, when I think back
on when me and you first met,
I seen you breaking niggas,
the fearlessness you had in you,
that shit reminded me of myself.
Then, when you got shot, and
I seen you in the hospital,
it reminded me of every young
nigger that ever came along.
But one thing about
you that was different,
you was a fighter.
And that's when I knew you
had to carry this shit on.
- Carry what on?
- The balance.
You can't see it, but it's like gravity.
It's necessary.
You need to let me show you
what's behind these curtains,
man, 'cause I believe in you,
just like I told you in the beginning.
That's what's gonna move us
through this whole ordeal.
- I want peace.
- Nigga, fuck peace.
You think greatness is
attained in times of peace?
It's not.
The shit you did in that
basement was required.
Get that in your head.
That's what you gotta understand,
that ain't gonna be the first time.
But if you let me show
you, we gonna be all right.
- So now what?
- You locked in now.
Ain't no getting out,
this shit is forever.
Wanna drink?
- Your gun.
Where's the hard drive?
- Hard drive?
I don't own a hard drive.
Dimitri Foster, right?
- Drive, now.
- Let's go inside and talk about this.
- Drive.
- So this is where you kill me?
A raggedly-ass warehouse?
- Where is it?
- Where's what?
- Don't play stupid.
Bender been working for
you the entire time.
- Bender?
The FBI agent?
- Why so desperate to
hide behind the curtains?
- Why are we at a warehouse near the dump?
- I know you run this city.
- Man, I don't know where the fuck
you getting your information from.
I'm just a man picking up the pieces.
- Get out.
You can make this painless.
Just tell me where it is.
- You kill me, you'll never find it.
- I thought you had no clue.
- Look at you, a man full of threats.
I will admit, though,
your follow-through game is impeccable.
- Then you know not to make me ask again.
- Before we proceed with the dramatics,
I would like to ask you one question.
When will all this shit break you?
- I could ask you the same thing.
- Nah, bruh.
We different.
When I look at you, all
I see is desperation.
It's all in your eyes.
Pain,
death,
taking lives everywhere you go,
even the ones you love.
Yeah, Bender told me everything.
You were the perfect hire.
To me, I didn't give two fucks.
I'm gonna tell you just
like I tell everybody else.
Fall in line and get
the fuck outta my way.
- Not just picking up the pieces.
- Maybe yours.
- Hey, this is Angie.
I'm sorry I couldn't get to your call,
but if you leave your name and message,
I'll get back at you soon.
Thank you.
- Hey, baby.
About the other day, I'm sorry.
You know, there's a
lot going on right now,
a lot of responsibility,
and I hope you understand that.
But even if you don't, I do.
But I'm about to be on the
way over there to talk to you.
- You gonna make me ask?
- I was set up.
- Do you need more time off?
- No.
I'm pissed.
Bender was right.
It's Bone.
And he has the hard drive.
- How did you know?
Did he show you?
Did you see it?
- I know it.
- We cannot afford to go
off your guesses right now.
- I've been following his crew around.
I think I know where he's keeping it.
And if I'm right,
I think there's a way we can
kill two birds with one stone.
- Since when'd I tell you
to start sitting down?
- We got a new boss.
Asshole's cracking down on everybody.
- Man, that sounds like a you problem.
- It's kinda light.
They won't like that.
- Yeah, that hard drive from Bender,
I'll be keeping that,
which means I'm gonna be
giving you and your friends
what I wanna give you from now on.
Get the fuck outta my face.
- There was a list, a long one.
All your names are on it.
- Bone, cuz, may I ask you a question?
Who was in charge when
all of this shit happened?
- Dog, you forgot what we said
when we first started this whole thing?
I was gonna play the back,
you was gonna play the front.
- Right, right, right.
- What happened
with all of that?
- So where's the man of
the hour, huh?
- Man, listen, I get it, man.
You took your shots, you
missed, and you pissed.
But we gonna get another chance.
Next time this lang stick his head out,
we gonna tear that motherfucker off.
- Was I ever really
calling the shots, bro?
- Dog, that's this shit talking.
Now it's Ty's time to shine.
- Oh.
- And hopefully, with our help,
he won't make the same
mistakes that we did.
- Right.
Right, right, right.
So tell me, what's it?
Where's Egg?
Yeah, the hitman?
- Dimitri?
I don't know.
- What's he looking for, man?
- I don't know.
- Mm.
Are you sure?
- I'm positive.
Why would I call you in if I
had something to hide, man?
- Right.
- What's up with all
the 21 Questions, cuz?
- Hey, man.
♪ Girl, that nigga ain't shit ♪
♪ It ain't my kind ♪
- Dog, everything gonna be cool, man.
I just need T.A. to get back to T.A.
- How the fuck am I supposed
to get back to T.A., huh?
Knowing that this nigger
here is out here, huh?
- So you telling me you
worried about this clown?
Since when we worried about
motherfuckers like that, man?
Huh?
- Yeah, all right.
- Come on, baby.
Come on.
♪ You just another guy ♪
- All right.
- Baby.
Angela.
- Tyler, you in too deep,
and I won't be a part of it.
I'm gone.
And don't come looking for me.
Angela.
- Damn, I hope they left this key.
- Man, what are you doing?
- Ty, man, I was just-
- We made the streets safe for you again.
We brought you back into our home.
- Man, I ain't asked for shit.
- Nigga, you ain't have to.
Now you sneak around like a little bitch.
- Oh, you feeling yourself, huh?
Man, there's a lot of shit going on
that you don't know nothing about.
Bone been-
- Bone's not in charge, I am.
- Wow.
Well, let me tell you something, nigga,
you killed a whole fucking
federal agent, and not in jail.
How the fuck do you think that happened?
Bone been playing us, nigga.
Get your shit together.
- Couldn't wait a second to
make your move, could you?
- Nigga, fuck you.
- Oh shit.
- How the fuck do you
think you and Keyshawn
kept slipping through the feds' fingers?
Luck, nigga?
And how do you reward me?
By outsourcing guns and drugs.
- Nigga, we was trying to come up.
- No, you got cocky, nigga.
Think I wasn't gonna find out.
I gave you all the game you got,
and that's how you repay me, cuz?
It was me that killed the bitch.
You forgot the rules, nigga.
- Your own cousin?
- That's right.
You slipping, man.
- The hard drive.
- Don't you play dumb with me.
- I'm working on a case.
- A case I should have
been informed about.
- I have to keep this to myself.
- Really?
You know, you're not sitting
in this chair just yet,
and you are seriously risking
the opportunity to do so.
So you either bring me up
to speed on what's going on,
or you put your badge and your gun
on this desk and you leave.
You can't trust us,
we can't trust you.
- Man, what?
- What you mean, "What?"
What, you best friends with the feds now?
Look man, I'm having a real
hard time not killing your ass.
- I know.
This her.
- Man, I'm not working
with the fucking feds.
It's the lot that got me into
this mess in the first place.
- Well, good, 'cause I'm
not one anymore anyway.
- Fuck outta here.
- Wait, what?
- It doesn't matter.
What does, is this evidence.
We need to finish this.
- We?
- Yeah.
- But I just outed Bone.
I'm not going down with these-
- Stop.
He took everything from you.
Why not take everything from him?
- And then what?
Can we even take that shit to the feds?
- To be honest, I don't trust them either.
- Oh fuck, man.
- Maybe the guy that doesn't trust anyone
is the one we can trust.
- Man, y'all figure this shit out.
- Are you ready to do your job?
- I told you to only call me
if you had something concrete.
- Okay, look, I'm working
with the hitman, all right?
- Are you insane?
- He helped me get the evidence.
- Blinded by your own
ambition, just like Bender.
- No, I'm nothing like Bender.
Can I trust you?
- Can you trust me?
You're the one who called me.
- Look, if I get you the evidence,
will you just do what needs to be done?
- Even if it means bringing you in.
When?
- Tomorrow, I'll text you a time.
- Where?
- You choose.
- You sound just like
my wife on date night.
Listen, I don't got time for this.
I'll send you a location later, all right?
♪ Hey, Primo, you a fool for this ♪
♪ Okay, Nine ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm a product of the
trenches everywhere ♪
♪ Where you gotta be prepared ♪
♪ 'Cause we all know life ain't fair ♪
♪ I'd rather be a suspect ♪
♪ Ain't no victims over here ♪
♪ If you're pussy, they gonna try you ♪
♪ You can't live your life in fear ♪
♪ No, oh ♪
♪ Can't expect love from everybody, oh ♪
♪ Can't expect them to be real ♪
♪ Don't expect them to be solid ♪
♪ Gotta be bad about it ♪
♪ Can't leave the house without it ♪
♪ That's a survivor tactic, oh ♪
♪ Your enemies might be
disguised as your friends ♪
♪ Get the feeling that
your vibe getting wet ♪
♪ My pride killing me inside ♪
♪ It took some time to come
to life, but I realize ♪
♪ Feeling like I ain't getting
the same love in return ♪
♪ The anger ignite the fire ♪
♪ My heart's starting to burn ♪
♪ They ain't grow up on the same morals ♪
♪ You gotta learn, everybody
don't owe you no loyalty ♪
♪ You gotta learn ♪
♪ They ain't got your best interest ♪
♪ Gotta keep pimping ♪
♪ I ain't falling out over money ♪
♪ You're tripping about bitches ♪
♪ Feeling envy when they notice
they can't defeat y'all ♪
♪ Something going wrong with their motor ♪
♪ They need to recall ♪
♪ I been brought up by the trenches ♪
- Not a good spot.
- Well, it has to be a spot he chose.
Dimitri, I need you to know,
when this is over and we take them down,
you have to go down too, okay?
You just...
You've done too much-
- I hear you.
I hear you.
This him?
- Mm-hmm.
Are you okay?
- Sorry.
- What's going on?
What's wrong?
- They know where I live.
- Huh?
- My family's not safe.
Think I'm being followed.
- Who could be following you?
- Well, well, well.
I'll take that.
Party without me?
I have eyes everywhere.
- You're not leaving with that.
- Hell if I'm not.
You must be Agent Miraflores.
Look just the way they described
you, sexy and succulent.
How you doing, angry man?
Okay, let's get to business.
I'm here to extend an offer.
There's a lot of power and
determination at this table.
Why let it go to waste
when we can do such great
things for this city?
- Is that the same lie you told T.A.?
- You mean the traitor?
- Man, what the fuck
is wrong with you, Ty?
Yo, man, stop this shit.
I'm not fighting no more, dog.
- You a bitch-ass nigga.
Always been one.
- Listen, officially, I
can get up from this table,
walk away, and make all y'all disappear.
But I can't.
Why would I do that when we
have such a great thing going?
- If you even think
you're leaving this table,
I will happily shoot you.
- Guns, please.
I have eyes everywhere.
- Get on your knees.
- Look, man...
All right, I'm sorry, man.
Sorry I brought you into this shit, dog.
There ain't shit but pain
and misery with this shit.
- Truly the man in charge.
- That was Key and T.A.
I'm just cleaning up the mess y'all made.
- And now you about to make somebody else
the face of it all, right?
- You ain't gotta do this.
- Don't complicate things.
All you gotta do is tell
people what they wanna hear,
not what they need to hear.
- Hmm.
- Dimitri.
- He needs to die.
- And what about us?
- It's a sacrifice.
- It's not gonna make it better, okay?
No, look, it can't help anything,
'cause it's just gonna make it worse.
- You know what?
This whole room, everybody
in it, we need to die.
- Move in, move in, move in!
- Everybody, put your hands up!
- Put the gun down.
Put the gun down.
- I'm not going to jail.
- No!
- Everybody put your hands
up and drop your weapons.
Drop your weapon!
- What happened?
We could have worked together, hmm?
Pitiful.
- I still don't know how they
figured out where I live.
- Relax, as soon as we heard
about it, we sent people over.
Your family's safe.
- Thanks.
- Take his ass away.
He got a new home now.
I had a feeling Bone
would make a move on us,
just didn't know how or when.
You know, having evidence on him is great,
but catching him in the
act, oh, it's even greater.
- Yeah.
What I'm really trying to figure out is
how the fuck you get away
with that without a leak?
I guarantee you're gonna find
a couple of your homies on that drive.
- Yeah, you're probably right.
Well, we only told the ones
that we thought we could trust,
and that wasn't a lot, you know?
The ones that would do the right thing.
It wasn't easy, but it worked.
Everyone will catch wind of this soon.
The rest, we'll get to 'em.
Looks like the rumors are true.
You worked with the feds.
- Now what?
- Well, the way I see
it, you got two choices.
One, you could run.
There's a lot of distractions going on,
and maybe you'll get away.
Or two, word on the street
is I'm due for a promotion,
so I could see to it, with
the best of my ability,
to seek immunity for all your help.
- Even with all the shit that I've done?
- I mean, I didn't say
it was gonna be easy.
- Look, I'm tired of running.
- Hmm, what's so funny?
- You proud of yourself?
- Yeah, actually, I am.
- You have no idea what you've done.
- And what might that be?
- Baby girl, you didn't win.
I kept balance to this shit.
You just exposed Milwaukee
to the most horrifying situation.
And believe me, they coming.
- Well, we'll be waiting for 'em.
Enjoy your new home.
- Bye-bye.
♪ No man stands alone ♪
♪ Treat each man as your brother ♪
♪ And remember that ♪
♪ Each man's greed is alone ♪
♪ Two guns ♪
♪ Quick run ♪
♪ Make a quick run ♪
♪ Nappy head ♪
♪ Yeah, nappy head ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Just a nappy-headed
nigga from the mill ♪
♪ What the fuck is my deal, nigga ♪
♪ Hardly ever home, living on the go ♪
♪ Never sitting for a still picture ♪
♪ Hoes on the phone,
thinking that I'm on ♪
♪ Got no fucking time to deal with ya ♪
♪ Fuck his tissues ♪
♪ Nigga got real issues ♪
♪ Sleeping in the same old picture ♪
♪ Can't enable, able to see the light ♪
♪ Was riding by Mike's ♪
♪ Doing shit just outta spite ♪
♪ But fuck it, I'm living that life now ♪
♪ Don't even look at a price now ♪
♪ Motherfuckers should pipe down ♪
♪ Sike, what's up ♪
♪ Nigga been nice enough, said ♪
♪ All my life, wanted change ♪
♪ Fast cars, money, diamond rings ♪
♪ Just a young go-getter ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ You fucking with the wrong nigger ♪
♪ Two guns, I'm the shooter ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Got your girl, I recruit her ♪
♪ Just a nappy-headed nigger ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Two guns, I'm the shooter ♪
♪ Got your girl, I recruit her ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I'm just a nappy-headed nigger ♪
♪ All my life, wanted change ♪
♪ Fast cars, money, and diamond rings ♪
♪ Just a young go-getter ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ You fucking with the
wrong nigger, yeah ♪
♪ Just a nappy-headed
nigger from the mill ♪
♪ Where the fuck is my hood at ♪
♪ Middle fingers up ♪
♪ Boys fuck with us ♪
♪ Niggers got to know Steal Traps ♪
♪ Steal Trap in the band, dog ♪
♪ Rambo clip loaded ♪
♪ Die broke, live rich ♪
♪ Suicide, nigga, I voted that ♪
♪ Nigga like me never going back ♪
♪ Jail not intended for me ♪
♪ Land of the free, home of the brave ♪
♪ Unless you're meant to
be put on your knees ♪
♪ Nah, nah, nigger, not me ♪
♪ Box out like Rocky ♪
♪ Cocky-looking like,
"Who gonna stop me now?" ♪
♪ All my life, wanted change ♪
♪ Fast cars, money, and diamond rings ♪
♪ Just a young go-getter ♪
♪ You fucking with the wrong nigger ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Two guns, I'm the shooter ♪
♪ Got your girl, I recruit her ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Just a nappy-headed nigger ♪
♪ Two guns, I'm the shooter ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Got your girl, I recruit her ♪
♪ I'm just a nappy-headed nigger ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Baby ♪