* [INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
* Um...
* Uh...
* Bum, bum...
* Um...
* Uh... uh, uh... uh...
* Oh...
(DISTANT LAUGHING)
(BACKGROUND CHATTER)
* Uh...
* Uh, uh...
(SIGHS)
(SNIFFS)
* Oh... oh, oh...
* Oh...
(BACK GROUND CHATTER)
* Uh...
(WHISTLES)
* Chicka-chicka
Oh, hi. I'm, uh, I'm Jack.
I'm the so-called "Sexist Pig".
But, I don't think I
really am, ya know?
I'm... I'm just a guy.
Plain and simple.
Like any other guy you
might know, or go out with...
...or even love.
Now, some women say that
all men are sexist.
And I agree with them.
I believe there are fundamental
differences in how each thinks.
You see, I've...
I've given this whole male...
...female thing a lotta thought
over the past few years.
And I've come up with a
Few theories of my own.
Most of which, don't provide for
fairy tales about ever-lasting
love.
Oh boy.
I can tell I'm gonna piss
a lotta women off.
Eh... what the hell.
You know what?
I'm gonna tell you everything
that goes on inside a man's
head. Even what he would never
say out loud.
Let me warn you that, uh,
some of it is pretty wild.
And you're probably gonna
hate me for sayin' it.
But, uh, oh well.
Here goes.
Let me start right off with
a discussion about safe sex.
First of all,
I believe in it.
Absolutely. Positively.
Without a question.
But, you know, I don't
believe in abstinence, okay?
It's unnatural,
it's unnecessary.
It's downright
stupid, ya know?
Sex is too important a
part of the male
female relationship to be
left to a moment until
after you've already committed
yourself to someone for life.
Hello. Thank you
so much, Lucy.
- Good morning.
- Hi.
* Uh...
You look very, very,
very beautiful this morning.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
See, the first step in
being liberated,
is being honest
about who you are.
(HORN HONKS)
Do you have any idea
what a good looking
woman does to a man?
Huh?
No.
Of course you men do.
But, for you women's sake,
let me tell ya.
There's a really primitive
response that makes you
wanna grab her,
rip her clothes off,
and screw her,
right then and there.
Of course,
I'd never do that.
Nor would any normal guy.
But that's what we're thinkin'.
Believe me.
Hi.
It's New York, ya know?
I mean, you can't
win 'em all.
- (LAUGHS)
Excuse me. But aren't
you Dr. Grayson?
-Yes.
-It's wonderful to meet you.
My name is Barbara.
Barbara Michaels.
Oh, Barbara. It's a
great pleasure to meet you.
-I'm Jack.
-(LAUGHS)
My... my friends and I have
been talking about you for
for two years now.
-Really?
You're very popular in this
part of town.
Okay.
That's great.
Here, let me give
you my card.
I'll write my home
phone on the back.
Well. I, uh, I'll try to call
you later this week, maybe.
I hope so.
Bye, bye.
Bye.
INTERCOM: Dr. Westin. Please
come to the nurses' station.
Dr. Westin...
Is that Beth's chart?
-Yeah.
-(SIGHS)
Medication's not working.
Her white blood cell count's
over one-sixty.
I guess I'd better tell Richard,
right?
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
No, no, no, no, no.
You don't have to do that.
She's my patient.
Yes, but I've known them
both since high school.
(SIGHS)
It should be me who tells them.
Okay.
Thanks.
INTERCOM: Dr. Miller,
extension 112.
Dr. Miller, extension 112.
-(DOOR CLOSING)
-(SIREN WAILING IN THE DISTANCE)
(SIGHS)
(KNOCKING)
Dr. Grayson.
I need to talk to you.
Michelle, it's only natural
that a mother would
feel the stress of her son's
illness.
(SIGHS) Oh, no. It's...
It's not that. It's...
It's you. It's me. Uh...
(LAUGHS)
Haven't you noticed?
I'm in love with you.
Oh, you... you can't be.
For the past three months
you're all I can think about.
Michelle, you've... you've got
to understand that with...
with Martin's death
and Jason's illness,
you're under tremendous
strain.
Are you saying that
you don't love me?
I'm married to Jenny.
And as corny as it sounds,
I love my wife very much.
Oh God. I've made
such a fool of myself.
No, no, no you haven't.
You haven't even come in here.
(SIGHS)
Hey? This whole thing
never happened.
(SIGHS) Thank you.
(SIGHS)
Okay.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSING)
DIRECTOR: That's a take!
(HONKING EQUIPMENT SOUNDS)
That was great, Jack.
What do you say we break
for chow, huh?
-Sure.
-Good.
(SIGHS)
-(KISS SOUNDS)
Okay, everyone.
That's a wrap for lunch.
We'll see you back at 1:20.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES)
No thanks.
So I'm an actor.
But you probably figured that
out already, right?
I love acting. God, you know,
it's a wonderful profession.
You get to entertain people.
Make 'em feel good.
Excuse me.
You get paid for it, too.
I mean, I can't think of
anything else I'd rather do.
* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
Right now, I'm just a soap
opera actor. But, uh...
one day I'd really like to
do some serious work.
Couldn't you see me as Hamlet?
(SNIFFS) Yeah, me neither.
-* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
-Shh. We gotta go.
Michelle?
(DOOR CLOSING)
Michelle? It's me.
You in here?
Huh? Huh?
* (SEXY MUSIC PLAYS)
Oh. Dr. Grayson.
I'm so glad you came.
I'm so glad you called me.
You know, Dr. Grayson,
I just haven't been
feeling well lately.
-Oh, no, no, no.
(GIGGLES)
-Well, let me make you feel
better.
-Oh.
-Does this help?
-(GASPS) Mm... a little.
How about this?
(SNAPS BUTTON)
Oh, yes,
I'm starting to feel better.
-Maybe this, too?
-(SQUEALS) Yes. (GIGGLES)
(GASPS)
Oh, yes. Yes.
-Oh?
-(GIGGLES) Doctor!
* Um... uh...
Hey. Yeah, um, they're just
finishing cleaning up our
editing stuff.
-Ten minutes?
-Okay
Okay. Alright.
That's Tracy.
She's a good friend of mine.
* Ooo, ah...
We've developed our own
technique for getting into
character.
It sort of goes one step
beyond "The Method".
Not only effective, but
very fun, as well.
Let me clarify one thing,
alright? I'm not advocating
impersonal,
non-emotional,
one-night-stand sex.
No. Sex is meaningful.
And an expression of feeling
towards the other person.
It just doesn't have to be the
one and only person.
Besides, there's no such
thing as the one and only.
We are not, by nature,
a monogamous species.
We lust after
many different people.
That's...
that's how God made us.
Now, I understand the importance
of commitment, obviously, once
you have children. But until
that time, I intend to follow
my natural instincts.
(INDISTINCT BACKGROUND CHATTER)
-(CLEARS THROAT) Welcome.
-Hey.
Hey, Shelley.
(KISS SOUND)
-(SIGHS)
-Marty. Sorry, I'm late.
-Oh, hi. I'm, uh, I'm Jack.
-Anne
Were you rehearsing
With Tracy again, huh?
Well, we were going
over some lines.
You were banging her
weren't you?
No. No, not at all.
Damn you. I bet
she's hot isn't she?
Would you shut up? We
Have a guest at the table.
Sorry about this discussion.
Forget it, Jack. I already
warned her about you.
You gotta understand, we've
all worked together for like
three years. And, uh, well,
It can get pretty raunchy
sometimes.
(LAUGHS)
You sound like you're
almost proud of that.
Well, I guess we're not always
politically correct around here.
What's wrong with being
politically correct?
Well, sometimes people can go
A little overboard with that
kinda stuff, don't you think?
No. Not if it's offensive.
Yeah, but people think
offensive thoughts
and no amount of
political correctness is
ever gonna stop that.
How can you be sure?
Because it's human
nature, that's how.
I... I, for one, have been
imagining you naked
during this entire conversation.
And no matter what I talk about
I'm still gonna be
thinking about that.
You're disgusting.
Well, and so is just
about every other straight
guy you ever met.
Isn't that right, Marty?
Yeah. I mean...
I mean I'd love to see you in
your birthday suit.
(LAUGHS)
He's...
I'm sorry, Shelly.
I have to leave.
You know. I'd make a comment
about your "whatever" but
what's the point?
-(LAUGHS) Oh.
-(LAUGHS)
Jack, when are you going
to learn to shut your mouth?
Yeah, Jack. You really
pissed her off.
Oh, be quiet.
You were even worse.
Who was she, anyway?
Uh, well, she just signed
on as your new leading lady.
Well, I guess I ticked her
off pretty good, didn't I?
(CAR HORN HONKS)
It's just that I've decided
that being truthful is very
important
More important, in fact,
than being polite.
Because, unfortunately,
hypocrisy seems to
characterize most
male and female interactions.
Men say what women
want to hear.
Women say what
men want to hear.
No one knows what the
other one really wants.
-Dr. Grayson?
-Yeah?
Can I have your autograph?
Of course you can
have my autograph.
-What's your name?
-Julia.
Julia? That's a
very pretty name.
I think you're the hottest
guy on the whole show.
(LAUGHS)
So do I.
-Thanks.
-Bye bye.
I know what you're thinking.
The only reason I get all
these women is because I'm
on a television show.
You know what?
You're right.
Two years ago when I
was a bike messenger
nobody noticed me. Now I'm
beating 'em off with a stick.
But I'm not
complaining really.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
(PHONE RINGING)
(KNOCKING)
-Hey!
-Hey, Shelley.
-(LAUGHS)
-Uh, look, um...
I'm sorry about what
Happened at lunch.
Oh, please. Don't
worry about it.
It's mostly Marty's
fault anyway.
Yeah, well, I just, I don't
wanna screw anything up.
-Mm, you're not.
-(KISS SOUNDS)
(LAUGHS) Wow. Uh,
what was that for?
What do you think it was for?
Come on. Let's get off our
clothes.
Uh, Shelly, what are you...
what are you...
What are you doing?
(LAUGHS)
Jack, you have been
flirting with me for months.
And, today, you're gonna get
lucky.
(LAUGHS)
Uh, don't you think we
oughta talk about this,
actually?
What's there to say? Do you deny
that you were coming on to me?
Uh, no. I admit I'm, uh,
attracted to you.
But, uh,
what about Marty?
-What about him?
-Well, he's your husband.
Oh, you mean my
soon-to-be ex-huband.
We've been separated
for three months.
You know, he's... he's
still my friend.
And I am not your friend?
Jack, I know that he has
been sleeping with other people.
-Right?
-Uh, yeah, um...
-Mm-hmm.
-I couldn't say, really.
That's what I thought.
(LAUGHS)
Uh, you know,
I...I really can't do this.
I'm sorry.
You told me that you wanted
to do what comes natural.
Yeah, um, right.
I do, uh...
Doesn't that feel natural?
-Oh. Uh, if you insist.
-Uh-huh.
(KISS SOUNDS)
Alright. I'll admit it.
I love sex.
I think it's the most intense,
wonderful experience you can
have.
What's wrong with doing
It as much as possible?
Americans are way to uptight
and neurotic about sex.
If everyone weren't so
guilty about it,
we'd have a lot more
healthy and happy relationships.
Now isn't that something
worth fighting for?
(KNOCKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(SIGHS)
What do you want?
Look, I just wanna
apologize for before, okay?
I think I got a little carried
away with my argument.
And, uh, I probably never
should've made that comment.
I accept the apology.
Look, it's just, you know,
honesty's a big issue with me.
You know, I, I, uh,
I feel it's at the root of most
problems between people.
I already accepted the apology.
Yeah, but can I just
explain it to you?
(LAUGHS) You see, I think
if everyone told the truth...
...the, uh, the world would
be much better off.
Oh, and that's why you talk
about seeing me naked?
Actually, yes. I'll admit it
was, uh, inappropriate but,
uh, I mean it wasn't wrong.
Wow. The truth is
I don't wanna hear it.
-(DOOR SLAM)
-Oh, ow! (SIGHS)
-(HONKING EQUIPMENT SOUNDS)
-DIRECTOR: Action!
* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
(KNOCKING)
-Dr. Grayson?
-Yes.
I'm Molly Baldwin,
The new radiologist.
Oh, Molly, yes.
Come, come on in.
It's good to meet you.
I've heard a lot of
fine things about you.
Well, it truly is a great
honor to meet you.
A great honor, no less?
I feel like I should be bronzed.
(LAUGHS) Everyone in
County General says you
are the best
surgeon in the state.
That's pretty high praise
for someone who's only
been practicing
for two years.
Well, I believed it.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have
traveled 400 miles to be here.
I only hope I can live
up to your expectations.
Well, on one account, you've
already exceeded them.
Uh, no one told me
how handsome you were.
Well, no one said how
beautiful you are, either.
(SIGHS)
But if they had, I probably
wouldn't have hired you.
I don't understand.
I'm a very busy man,
Dr. Baldwin.
I don't know if could
handle such a distraction.
Dr. Grayson, I'm gonna
take that as a compliment.
I'm glad you are.
Oh, yes. Mmm.
(HONKING EQUIPMENT SOUND)
-That was great!
-Oh.
-(KISS SOUND)
-(LAUGHS)
I don't think we can
do better than that, huh?
-Okay.
-Yeah, that's a day.
Terrific. Just terrific,
Anne, give us a hug.
Oh, uh.
(LAUGHS)
I loved it.
I really loved it.
-(KISS SOUND)
-Thank you.
Jack, come on.
Let's talk.
(INDISTINCT BACKGROUND CHATTER)
So what'd ya think?
-About what?
-About her.
Think we oughta keep her?
Uh, you're asking me?
Of course. Why not?
Well, it's just you never
asked my opinion about
anything before.
Jack, you're my star.
Come on.
You got an eighty-six
"T.V.Q." I want you to be happy.
I mean I saw what
happened today at lunch.
And if, for any reason, you
don't
like her, she is off the show.
Well, as a matter of fact,
she is kinda uptight and touchy.
Well, that settles it, then.
She's gone.
Hey, oh, uh, wait, wait, Marty.
Marty, wait a second.
Uh, you know, she is
a pretty good actress.
And, uh, I guess
that's what counts, right?
(LAUGHS)
Whatever you say.
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT BACKGROUND CHATTER)
Hey, Anne. Look,
I just wanted to, uh,
congratulate you.
You know, I thought you
did a really good job before.
(LAUGHS) Good.
Come on, Jack.
-She was great.
-(LAUGHS)
What, you guys know each other?
Yeah, actually, I just
introduced myself a minute ago.
I was telling Anne here,
she's gonna be a big star.
Man, she was so good
in that scene, she even made
you look good.
(LAUGHS) Thanks, Troy.
(LAUGHS) I'm just kidding, man.
Come on, lighten up.
Seriously, though, I did,
uh, warn her about you.
That you've screwed every
leading lady you've ever had.
Which, of course,
shocked me.
Well, thanks again, Troy.
Thanks. What else did you say?
Oh, just that if she needed
any help rehearsing her scenes
that I would be happy
to go over them with her.
Uh, you know,
I really appreciated that.
Well, I, I, uh, I guess you've,
uh, covered all the bases.
I sure have.
Well, I guess I'll go get some
lunch.
Excuse me.
(INDISTINCT BACKGROUND CHATTER)
(LAUGHS) Sorry, Chief.
But all's fair in love and war.
You know that.
That's okay, man.
You did me a favor.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Because, man,
I think she was pretty cute.
I was gonna ask her out.
(LAUGHS)
You're not serious, are you?
Dude, did you see the butt on
her?
She's perfect for me, man.
Nice and tight.
(LAUGHS)
Look, Troy,
I spent some time with her,
alright?
And, believe me,
she's definitely not for you.
Oh, yeah, why? Because she
shot you down? No, no, no, no,
no.
No. Because she's in a
serious state of denial about
men.
Oh, she... you mean she's...
No, I'm not falling for
your tricks this time, Jack.
She likes me.
And I'm goin' for it.
Alright.
(SNIFFS)
I'll call you next week.
Okay? I miss you.
I love you, too, Mom.
Alright, bye.
(DOOR CLOSING)
(HEELS CLICKING)
Jack, I have to talk to you.
What's wrong?
(SIGHS) Jack.
I wanna get married.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I'm lonely and I want
somebody to wake up with.
And I want somebody to love.
Tracy, you know how I,
I, I care for you. But, um,
You know,
I never figured we'd
Sweetie,
I don't wanna marry you.
-You don't?
-No.
(LAUGHS) Oh.
I wanna marry
somebody more normal.
Oh. Well, who?
Hm. Troy.
(GIGGLES)
-Troy?
-Yeah. Troy.
Because he's sweet
and he's handsome.
And i just feel like we're
on the same, like, you know,
like thinking length... brain
wave.
-I could see that.
-Yeah. So will you help me?
-Help you what?
-Get him. (LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS)
What makes you think I could do
that?
Oh, because, Jack,
you have all those theories
about love and you know.
And I just, I know that you
could get him to like me.
Well, of course, I mean,
I probably could, but, uh,
I mean,
isn't that a little
manipulative?
Oh, Jack.
Please. Please.
I want it so bad.
Well, when you put it that way.
No, not that.
No, no.
I'm gonna be a married person
now.
You mean it?
Yeah. Just tell me.
Tell me what to do first.
Uh, I'm gonna have to
give that some thought.
Oh.
-I'll tell you what.
-What?
-I'll hatch a plan tonight.
-Okay. (LAUGHS)
And call you tomorrow.
-(SIGHS) Thanks, Jack.
-Sure.
(KISS SOUND)
(SIGHS)
-Hm.
-Let's go get you married.
(GIGGLES)
Okay.
Hey, big guy.
What's up?
Oh, hey.
What do you think? $15.99.
Pick that up for yourself?
No. It's for Anne.
We're going out to dinner
tonight.
And you're giving her that?
Yeah. I do it with all
my dates,man.
It works like a charm.
Troy, how would you
like to make $200?
(LAUGHS) Yeah, sure.
Wait. How?
Well, that's how much
money you're gonna save
by not wasting your time taking
Anne out to dinner tonight.
Jack, no, I already told you.
No way.
Just give me five minutes to
explain,
in detail,
why it would never work out
between you.
-No, Jack.
-Troy, it's for your own good.
Buddy. Three words.
Absolutely not.
-That's... that's two.
-Shut up.
That's two words, Troy.
* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
INTERCOM: Dr. Gordley to
Pediatrics.
Dr. Gordley to Pediatrics.
Well, what do you think?
Oh, no, no.
You're much more
experienced than I.
I don't want to make a fool out
of myself.
Well, in looking at this area
right here, it's obvious
we have an abnormality.
Yes, I guess you're right.
You don't seem sure.
No. No, no, no.
I'm sure of it.
Molly, you're not being
paid to agree with me.
Okay. It's just that the
location bothers me.
90% of tumors originate here,
near the bronchial passages.
This one is further up.
* (MUSIC STING)
That makes me think it
may be a residual infection...
from an undiagnosed
case of pneumonia.
* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
Okay, I'm sorry.
I knew I was wrong.
I'll just learn to
keep my mouth shut.
No, no. You're... you're right.
You're absolutely right.
I am?
Yes, it's a brilliant analysis.
Great. (LAUGHS)
This must be my lucky day.
Luck has nothing to do with it.
You are a very,
very smart doctor.
You'll never know what that
means to me,
coming from you.
Well, you'll never know
what it means to me...
to have you working here.
* (ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS)
(KISS SOUNDS)
I shouldn't have done that.
Well, I'm glad that you did.
* (MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
DIRECTOR: Alright, it's a take.
(HONKING EQUIPMENT SOUND)
(INDISTINCT BACKGROUND CHATTER)
Anne, wait a second.
What do you want?
You're not really interested in
Troy,
are ya?
(LAUGHS)
That is none of your business.
Yes, it is. Troy is my friend.
And I hate to see him hurt.
He is not your friend.
He told me so, himself.
Well, I consider him my friend,
regardless.
Anyway, I think you're
perceptive enough to realize...
that you and Troy will
be completely incompatible.
Which is a compliment to you,
by the way.
I mean, Troy's idea of heavy
reading is the back of a cereal
box.
Oh, and you, on the other hand,
have a P.H.D. in philosophy.
Well, at least I read
without moving my lips.
You're a Jackass.
Just trying to help.
No, you're not.
You're trying to play
some sort of game.
What it is,
I don't know.
But I'm certainly not
gonna be a part of it.
Why do you always
think the worst of me?
Just give me one reason not to.
(SLIPPERS SHUFFLING)
Hey. Troy, is going
out with Anne tonight. Huh.
I know.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Well,
I thought you said you could
stop that.
Don't worry about it.
After one date she'll
never go out with him again.
(EXHALES SMOKE)
How can you be so sure?
Because I know,
that's how.
Well, you just better be.
Because that is my future
husband you're talking about.
(SLIPPERS SHUFFLING)
(SIGHS)
-* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
-Now, I know some of you
are thinking...
where does true love
fit into all this
talk about sex?
Well, love is one of the
most important things in life.
Obviously.
But, it's also in direct
conflict with our sexual drive.
Because no matter how
much you love a woman,
after awhile,
the sexual impulse wanes.
Now, married men will deny
this until the day they die.
because their life
depends upon it.
But the truth is,
after about two years,
sex is almost always more
intense and exciting...
with someone new.
Why is that?
And shouldn't that be a
serious consideration before
anyone decides to get married?
I think so.
* (MUSIC STING)
(SIGHS) Oh.
(DOOR LATCHING)
TROY: Oh!
Hey.
-Hey, man.
What, uh,, what do you want?
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SNIFFS)
So, uh,
what happened last night?
(LAUGHS) I'm not
telling you, Jack.
What kinda guy do
you think I am?
(LAUGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
-She shot you down?
-Yeah, right.
She shot me down?
What are you kidding?
-She did, didn't she?
-(PHONE RINGING)
Troy? Come on.
Dude, there is something
seriously wrong with that chick.
I mean ,one minute,
she's telling me how sweet I am.
And then the next
the next minute,
she's calling me a "Pig".
Well, what'd you do?
Nothing, dude.
I swear to God!
I just... I tried to
give her some tongue
and she kicked me
in the balls.
Oh, shit.
(SIGHS)
It's not funny, Jack.
It's funny, Troy.
(LAUGHS)
-It's not funny.
-I tried to warn you, man.
Hey. Jack! Don't...
don't tell anybody, Jack.
Hey! Don't...
(DOOR LATCHING)
* (DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(DOOR OPENING)
* (MUSIC SWELLS)
(FILE HITTING FLOOR)
Okay. No, we mustn't.
-(HEELS CLICKING)
-(SIGHS)
DIRECTOR: That's a take!
(ELECTRIC EQUIPMENT SHUTTING
DOWN)
(HONKING EQUIPMENT SOUND)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(SIGHS)
So you knee'd Troy
in the balls, huh?
He told you?
Yeah, well, we're all
like a big family around here.
You know,
we don't really have any
secrets.
Well, as far as I'm concerned,
it's none of your business.
No, look.
Can we stop this?
Let bygones be bygones?
I mean we're supposed
to have some sort of
relationship on the show.
It's pretty hard to
pretend all the time.
That's called acting.
Yeah, well,
just stop for a second,
alright?
-(SIGHS)
-(SGHS)
Look, I know we,
uh, you know,
got off on the
wrong foot before.
And it was
probably all my fault.
But why don't we
just go to lunch,
you know,
talk a little?
I just,
I don't think it's a good idea.
(SIGHS)
Humor me, okay?
Where?
Ziggy's.
Twenty minutes?
Fine.
* (JAZZY MUSIC PLAYS)
(SIGHS)
MAN: No!
Well?
Well, what?
Say something. You're the
one that wanted us here.
I wanna be careful
about what I say.
-Why?
-So I don't provoke you.
You don't have much regard
for my intelligence, do you?
See?
I've already done it.
Okay, you're right.
Maybe we should just
forget about this whole thing.
Just, just wait a second,
alright? Just
sit down. Please?
Just
We can work this out.
I'm gonna try to be as
honest as I can.
Okay?
Is this where you talk about
me being naked again?
(LAUGHING IN BACKGROUND)
Look, I think, somehow,
you've gotten the idea
that I'm coming onto you.
Which, uh, just isn't so.
Let's face it.
You and I are incompatible.
That's an understatement.
I mean I do have to admit,
I do find you sexually
attractive.
What a surprise.
-But only on a physical level.
-Thank you.
It's just an involuntary
reaction,
you know?
It's like seeing a
piece of chocolate cake.
Wow.
I feel sorry for you.
Why?
Well, you think it's alright
being controlled by your loins?
All I'm saying is that,
when I see a beautiful woman,
I have an instinctual reaction.
Alright, come on.
Don't you ever react when
you see a handsome guy?
Once in awhile.
You see?
It's only natural.
Yeah, but, I control it.
I don't go sleep with a guy
just because he has a great ass.
Why not?
You're single, aren't you?
Look, how are you gonna
find anyone unless you
go out with people?
Physical attraction is just a
small component of a real
relationship.
Ah, but it's the first and
the most important one.
Yeah, for you, maybe.
But, but, friendship and
compatibility is much
more important to me.
And, and it takes
time to develop.
(LAUGHS) You are so
serious all the time.
I mean don't you ever just
do anything just for the hell of
it?
What do you mean?
Just be spontaneous without
calculating the long-term
affects.
See, that would
be irresponsible.
Yeah, exactly.
I bet you've never done
anything in your life on a whim.
-Of course I have.
-Like what?
That's what I thought.
(LAUGHS)
Don't move, okay?
(SIGHS)
Hi. (LAUGHS)
(KISSING SOUNDS)
(LAUGHS)
That's very funny.
(KISSING SOUNDS)
Alright. Yeah, that's enough.
I, uh, I get the point.
Hey, hey. Leave him alone.
Leave him alone.
No. Come on.
Come here. Look...
Hey,
I said "Bug off".
You know what? Just...
It's okay. It was a joke,
alright?
Look, you and me,
outside. Right now.
-This is none of your business.
-Right now. Right now.
You're all going outside.
Now.
Thanks for lunch.
* (JAZZ MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CHIMES JINGLING)
-* (INSTRUMENTAL)
-Mm.
Alright, I'll admit.
It was, uh, it was funny.
-* (INSTRUMENTAL)
-Mm
It's just,
you know what bothers me?
What kinda woman would
do something like that, ya know?
What... I just...
I've got a serious suspicion...
that she could have
some real problems.
-* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
-Uh...
Schizophrenia.
-* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
-Sha-sha-sha.
Yeah.
Jack, Jack,
Jack, Jack, Jack.
(HEELS CLICKING)
Jack, how am I
gonna get Troy?
I already told you.
Anne has dumped him.
So why don't you
just go ask him out?
(SIGHS)
I can't do that.
Why not?
Because then he would
know how I felt about him.
Well, that's the point,
isn't it?
No. The point is to get him
to feel that way about me first.
-Oh, so you wanna decide him?
-Yeah. (LAUGHS)
I'm sorry. I believe that
honesty is the best policy.
(DOOR OPENING)
(HEELS CLICKING)
Jack. (SIGHS)
If I wanted to be honest,
would I come to you?
(SIGHS)
Come on.
(SIGHS) I suppose
it is for a good cause.
Good.
(SIGHS)
So, what's the secret
to getting a man?
Oh, you use his
weaknesses against him.
Oh, that sounds good.
How do I do that? (LAUGHS)
What's a man's most vulnerable
point?
His woody.
(GIGGLES)
(LAUGHS) No.
Not exactly.
See, his penis is just an
extension of his real liability.
His ego.
Ooo, that's good.
How do I use that?
Well, first you build it up,
and then you tear it down.
Tear it down, why?
Mm, well, that's how
you get control.
Okay. I don't understand.
(LAUGHS)
Alright.
Stay with me, okay?
-You're creating an addiction.
-Oh.
So, first you give the
reward to the subject for free.
Until you've developed
a dependence upon it.
-Yeah?
-Alright?
Then you take it away.
So, without even knowing it,
your subject has come
under your power and...
will do whatever you want.
-So, Troy's gonna love me?
Mm-hmm.
With all his heart.
(SQUEALS) (GIGGLES)
Thanks. (KISS SOUND)
-Go get him.
-Okay. (SIGHS)
(HEELS CLICKING)
* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
(KNOCKING)
Yeah.
Come on in.
(DOOR CLICKING OPEN)
Hey, do you have a minute?
Yeah, sure.
What's up?
(DOOR CLOSING)
Um, I just, uh, wanted
to speak to you about something.
Look, Trace,
if this is about my breath,
I stopped eating garlic
for lunch, okay?
Oh, no, no, no.
It's not that. (SIGHS)
-(SIGHS)
-It's your acting.
Oh, ho, ho! (LAUGHS)
Really?
Well, you know what?
I've just started taking...
acting lessons and it's
gonna take a little time...
for the improvement to show.
No, no, no.
(GIGGLES) No.
-(GRUNTS)
-I like your acting.
Oh, yeah, right,
you do. (GRUNTS)
Hey, I, really, I do.
-Really?
-Mm-hm.
I mean, I think that you are
the best actor on the show.
(LAUGHS)
You do?
(WEIGHTS CLICKING)
(LAUGHS) Alright.
(LAUGHS)
(GIGGLES)
Wait a minute. Why are
you telling me all this?
Oh, um, well,
I was just kinda hoping...
that you would give
me some pointers.
Pointers?
(LAUGHS) Okay.
Yeah. Yeah?
Yeah, if you really
wanted me to, sure.
(SIGHS)
Just whenever.
I mean, whenever's good
for you, ya know?
Just, maybe we could,
um, go to lunch.
-Okay. I'd like that.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-You would?
-Anytime.
-(SIGHS)
* Someone's soul,
Where logic cannot reach...
Uh, what about,
uh, Jack?
I thought you two were,
you know? (LAUGHS)
(GASPS) God!
(LAUGHS)
Um, Jack's kind of an idiot.
Don't you think?
-Totally.
Really?
-(LAUGHS) Yes.
-Don't tell anybody.
No. Never.
(SIGHS) Okay.
Lunch then?
-Or, whatever.
-Or other stuff. Yeah.
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
You're losin' it.
Losing what?
(SIGHS)
Whatever you had.
You don't have it
anymore, Jack.
(URINATING SOUNDS)
What are you talking about?
Well, you'll find out soon
enough.
Would you speak English,
Troy?
I'm gonna laugh so hard
when you find out. (LAUGHS)
Not as much as me.
Oh, no, sorry, buddy.
This time the joke's on you,
Jack.
(SIGHS)
* (BASS BEAT PLAYS)
(ZIPPER ZIPPING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
* (REGGAE BEAT)
Okay, okay.
I'm still thinking about Anne.
You know what I think's
really goin' on here?
She likes me.
You know that old saying,
"She protests too much"?
Well, (LAUGHS)
that's Anne.
Yeah. How could she
get so pissed at me unless,
underneath,
she really liked me?
Yeah,
she's just fighting it.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
FROM APARTMENT)
(KNOCKING)
(DOOR OPENING)
I'm sorry. I just can't
get you outta my mind.
(SIGHS) How'd you
find where I live?
I checked the files at work.
(SIGHS)
Why are you here?
I think you know.
Look, this can't happen.
No, it already has.
For me, anyway.
I want you to go right now.
No. No, not until
you answer one question.
What?
Do you love me?
(SIGHS)
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I, I, I need to know.
(SIGHS)
(KISSING SOUNDS)
(MOANS)
DIRECTOR: Alright,
that's a take!
(KISSING SOUNDS)
(HONKING EQUPIMENT SOUND)
(DOOR SLAM)
(INDISTINCT BACKGROUND CHATTER)
* Om...
* (PLAYFUL MUSIC)
No, no, no.
These go to Anne Henning's
dressing room, alright?
t's the dressing room
right down there.
Third one on the left.
Oh, that's for you.
Thanks.
* (PLAYFUL MUSIC)
I know it's corny.
But, believe me, it works.
Because women love flowers.
No matter what a
woman tells ya,
she's always a
romantic at heart.
Yeah. It's an
innate response, really.
I mean,
they can't help themselves.
(HEELS CLICKING)
Hi. Could I talk
to you, please?
Sure.
(HEELS CLICKING)
(DOOR OPENING)
I just wanna know one thing.
Anything at all.
What gives you the right
to send me flowers?
Well, I didn't know I
had to ask permission.
Here's to fresh starts.
(LAUGHS)
Did you really think I
was gonna fall for that?
It seems harmless enough.
Eh, is this some sort of
scheme of yours to torture me?
Or are you really that
insensitive and callous?
Neither.
I like you.
(LAUGHS)
Look, I know things haven't
gone so well, thus far.
But, you know,
if you give it a chance,
I think you'd be
pleasantly surprised.
I can't believe
you're saying that.
I mean, what makes
you possibly think...
I would go out with you?
The way you kiss me.
Kiss you?
I've never kissed you.
When we're on the show.
See, that's just acting.
I don't think so.
See, I,
I just have this feeling.
Well, I don't.
Oh, just answer
one question, okay?
Is there anything that
you like about me?
(SIGHS) Why are you
asking me all this?
I mean,
what difference does it make?
Because I wanna know.
Come on.
I'll have to think about that.
There's gotta be on thing.
I mean, my eyes?
My smile. My laugh.
Disposition. I don't know,
my fingernails.
Well,
you are sorta cute.
I have to admit,
you're never boring.
That's two things.
Two things. You know,
I... if you think about it,
there could be even more.
(LAUGHS) Wow.
Don't press your luck.
So, you'll reconsider
going out with me?
Eh.
(DOOR OPENING)
* I'll be loopy,
I'll be tame.
Jack. Jack.
(GIGGLES)
It worked.
After this publicity
thing tonight,
(HEELS CLICKING)
Troy asked me out.
(GIGGLES)
On a date. (GIGGLES)
-That's great.
-(GIGGLES)
So, what do I do now?
(GIGGLES)
I don't know.
(GIGGLES) Come on,
Jack, you know.
I can't tell what
Troy's gonna do.
No one can.
Well, then make
something up, Jack.
You're the expert on men.
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS) Alright.
Let me think a moment.
Okay.
Ssh. Ssh.
Is he gonna want
to sleep with you?
(GASPS) I would think so.
(GIGGLES)
(LAUGHS) You wanna
sleep with him?
Yes! Yes!
(LAUGHS)
Alright, then do it.
But only once.
What?
-Only once.
-(LAUGHS)
* Never here all day.
Ever?
(LAUGHS)
Eh, once a month.
(SIGHS)
Jack, that's inhuman.
Exactly. We wanna bring
this boy to his knees.
Hm. (LAUGHS)
What do I tell him?
What do I say?
Tell him, uh,
tell him it's so overpowering,
emotionally,
for you to be with him,
that you can only
do it every so often.
Oh.
(GIGGLES)
(LAUGHS)
That doesn't make any sense.
Of course it doesn't.
But Troy doesn't know that.
You're a woman --
life's greatest mystery.
(SIGHS) Okay.
Guess it's worked so far, huh?
* ...when she gets...
(KNOCKING)
* (SOAP OPERA MUSIC)
Molly, we have a problem.
I know.
I think I should resign and
transfer to another hospital.
You can't.
It's the only solution
I can think of.
No. No.
You're needed here.
It's me who should leave.
I can just go back
to County General.
I won't let you do that.
I must.
It's the right thing to do.
I know it. And,
deep inside, you do, too.
Yes, of course.
* (SOAP OPERA MUSIC)
Then I'll send my
resignation in the morning.
Alright.
Goodbye,
Dr. Grayson.
Bye, Dr. Baldwin.
(SIREN IN THE DISTANCE)
-Molly, wait.
-I can't go.
(KISSING SOUNDS)
DIRECTOR: Take!
(HONKING EQUIPMENT SOUND)
(KISSING SOUND)
You can pick me
up at eight.
* (BASS BEAT)
Yeah. I just had an
intuition that she liked me.
Probably comes from
the extensive amount of
experience I've had with
women over the years.
Mm. Or my natural,
extra sensitivity.
(LAUGHS)
* (ROMANTIC PIANO MUSIC)
-(WINE POURING)
-(INDISTINCT BACKGROUND CHATTER)
(INDISTINCT BACKGROUND
CHATTER CONTINUES)
Well, here we are.
Yes, we are.
Well, I, I, uh,
I hope you like the food.
Oh, I'm sure I will.
Uh, I'm really glad,
actually, that you, uh,
decided to come.
Look, uh,
before we go any further,
I think we should go
over some ground rules.
Ground rules?
Yes, I wanna be right upfront
about what I want from this.
Sure. Okay.
Alright. Um, as you can tell,
I'm a very serious person.
When I go out with a man,
I do so for a reason.
I don't like to waste
my time on frivolous affairs
with no future because
someone usually gets hurt.
(SIGHS)
Sounds pretty heavy.
I want a relationship built
on love and trust.
I would never do anything
to hurt him and I expect
the same from him.
So, in other words,
I'm looking for someone
who I can spend
my whole life with.
(LAUGHS)
Oh, uh, look, I, um,
I gotta be honest.
I, I, um, I don't know what
gave you the impression
that I was that
kind of a guy but --
No, no, no.
You don't understand.
I'm here because you're
just the opposite of the
kinda guy I wanna be with.
I... I think I'm confused.
You see, I think I've
become too serious about life.
And have decided that
I should do something that
I've never done before.
So I wanna have a
purely sexual relationship.
But I need to have it
with someone that
I don't really care about
and who is incapable of
being hurt by me.
(LAUGHS) And I
immediately thought of you.
So, you're saying you
wanna go to bed with me?
Yes.
And all you wanna do is,
uh, have sex?
That's right.
Nothing else.
We're not even gonna be friends?
That's the whole point.
To sleep with someone
that I don't really care about.
(LAUGHS) This is, uh,
this is really weird.
You know, I mean, um,
I don't know about this.
(SWALLOWS WINE)
Oh. I see. So, it's
okay for a man to do it.
but when a woman
wants to do it, it's weird.
Well, you know what?
Maybe you're just
the wrong guy to ask.
Don't... wait, wait,
wait a minute.
Don't, uh, you know,
I didn't say that.
Well, if you have any doubts...
No. No.
I made up my mind.
I wanna do this.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Yeah. But I just
wanna tell ya that I don't
think it's gonna work out.
I don't think you're the
type of woman who can
handle this sort of thing.
(LAUGHS) Oh, right.
See, I can if you can.
Come on. Let's go back to your
apartment.
We haven't even eaten yet.
Do you wanna...?
Why waste any time?
* (ROMANTIC PIANO MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
(CRINKLING MONEY)
* (SEXY MUSIC)
(MOANING)
(MOANING) (GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(MOANING)
-(SIGHS)
-(PANTING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(INDISTINCT BACKGROUND CHATTER)
Well, well, well, well.
What's with the flowers?
-Are they for Anne?
-Mm-hm.
Why are you wasting
your time, man?
Romance is never a waste.
Dude, she's never gonna
go to bed with you.
So you might as well
forget it. Believe me.
Troy, for your information,
these are not,
"Will you go to bed with me?"
flowers. These are,
"Thanks for last night,"
flowers.
You're lying.
Shut up.
Look at this smile, Troy.
What's it tell ya?
You you did it.
You son of a bitch!
You got her into bed?
Damn straight.
Shit.
You're not the only one
who got lucky, man.
-I did, too.
-Really?
Yeah. I got this chick eating
outta the palm of my hand.
Oh.
That's great, Troy.
I can't say who it is.
But let's just say this,
I think you're gonna
be a little bit more than
surprised when you
find out who it is.
I'm sure I will.
(LAUGHS)
What's up?
(KNOCKING)
-(DOOR OPENING)
-* (ROMANTIC MUSIC)
Good morning.
It is a good morning,
isn't it?
What are those for?
Well, they're for you.
For last night.
I already explained to you.
None of this matters.
Yeah, I know. I just
thought it'd be nice.
Just give them to one
of your other friends.
(LAUGHS) No, no.
They're for you.
(FLOWER WRAPPING CRINKLES)
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
it's time for me to change.
Oh. Alright.
Oh. (SIGHS)
(KNOCKING)
* Our ending, beginning,
our new beginning...
I have to change.
* Someone call the
love police
Oh. Okay.
(SIGHS)
Uh, you know what, there...
there is one thing.
I mean, I'd like to...
Last night, was it, uh,
Was it okay?
Was what okay?
The, uh, (LAUGHS)
you, you know.
Oh. The sex was good.
Alright?
Yeah. Okay, good. Yeah, I just,
I... I just wanted to know.
-Well, now you know.
-Yeah.
-Yeah,
-Well, thanks.
I mean, I assumed it was.
Because it was good for me.
-Good.
-Okay, sure.
Okay.
Um, well, let's just...
whatever.
Sorry to have bothered you.
I mean it won't happen again.
After all, we're not even
really friends, right?
Right.
That's cool with me.
Bye.
-* (UPBEAT MUSIC)
-(DOOR CLOSING)
(DOOR OPENING)
* (FUNKY MUSIC)
Oh, she must
really like me.
She's so scared that
I might reject her
that she has to pretend
to have no reaction at all to,
uh, what happened
between us last night.
I don't have to tell you
it was, uh, it was
pretty damn special.
Yeah, I'm, you know,
I'm sure she'd really like
to tell me how she really
feels about me but she's,
you know,
overwhelmed by her insecurity.
* (INSTRUMENTAL)
(MOANS) (KISSING SOUNDS)
(MOANS)
(KISSING SOUNDS)
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
-(LIGHT SWITCHING ON)
-(SIGHS)
What's wrong?
This isn't right.
Why?
We should've never
done it the first time.
Yeah, well,
just tell me why.
Because I care about you
and I wanna be with you.
But, you can't do that.
Yeah, but we both knew
that before we started. It...
Yeah. Well, I can't
accept that anymore.
(SIGHS)
-Just. come on.
-No. Come on.
-It hurts too much.
-(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENING AND CLOSING)
DIRECTOR: That's a take!
(HONKING EQUIPMENT SOUND)
(KNOCKING)
* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
Hi.
How are you?
Fine.
What are you doing here?
I wanna talk a little.
(SIGHS) Come on, Jack.
I already told you.
-I don't wanna --
-I know. I know.
I've just been...
Can I come in?
I've been doing a lotta
thinking about this and I've...
I've come to the conclusion
this has got to be
some kind of a game.
I mean it is, isn't it?
-It...
-(SIGHS)
No one wants only just sex.
It's unnatural.
Troy put you up to this?
No.
Or Shelly did.
Or, or Tracy.
(LAUGHS)
I said no.
(SIGHS) Think of who
else you know.
Uh, you haven't been
talking to my mother?
Okay, look. I'm trying really
hard not to be insulted here.
The only thing that's going
on is exactly what I told you.
Now, Jack, I mean,
if you can't handle it,
just... just let me know.
Me, handle it? What?
Are you kidding me?
This is the type of
relationship that I dream about.
I mean, you know,
no obligations.
Very few complications.
Just, you know, pure,
carnal lust.
I like that.
Alright, then.
We'll just forget about
this whole talk, okay?
Sure. What...
whatever you want.
Okay.
* I wanna be the
kind you don't know...
This... this your,
uh, family?
* That's what we
have to do...
Oh.
(SETTING PICTURE
ON THE TABLE)
Excuse me.
(DOOR OPENING)
Okay.
-(SIGHS)
-* (BASS MUSIC)
(DOOR CLOSING)
Do you believe her?
(SIGHS) Me neither.
I mean,
but if she wants to
play that game, that's...
that's fine, you know.
I can do that.
(FOOTSTEPS)
-Jack, we gotta talk.
-What?
-What's?
-Somebody's screwing Shelly.
Uh, what...
what gives you that idea?
Cause she's been
really nice to me lately.
Well, that's a good thing,
isn't it?
No! Somebody's doing her.
I'm sure of it.
Look, Marty.
What do you care?
You're...
you're getting divorced.
Oh, she wants to get divorced.
Not me.
Well, yeah.
Cause you were screwin' around.
So?
Look, Marty, I, mean,
you know, I don't...
I don't know what to tell you.
Keep an eye out
on her for me.
Cause I'm gonna
catch that bastard.
Okay.
(FOOTSTEPS)
Alright.
(SIGHS)
Oh, Jack. Just the
man I was lookin' for.
Listen, man,
you gotta help me.
Hey, look,
I'm in a real hurry.
No, no, no.
But, listen.
Dude, it's Tracy.
She is driving me nuts.
Oh, by the way.
I'm seeing her now, okay?
Yeah, I know.
She told me.
-Good.
-Okay.
Good. No, wait, hold on,
Jack. Just time out.
-Listen.
-(SIGHS)
I need your advice.
Okay? I need your help
on how you can
get her to like me.
You want me to
help you get Tracy?
Buddy, you are the
expert on women, man.
-(LAUGHS)
-What?
-Uh, it, uh...
-What's so funny?
Nothing. I just, uh,
I just don't know if
I should help you,
that's all.
Why not? You're perfect.
You know me and you,
you know, you know her.
(LAUGHS)
It's a bad idea.
No, Jack.
Come on, man.
I am asking you here,
man to man. Please.
(SIGHS) Alright.
Just answer me
one question, okay?
Anything.
You really care for her?
Yes, I do.
Alright, I'll help you.
You will? Yeah, man.
Okay, what do I do first?
Just do exactly what
you've been doing up to now.
-Mm-hmm.
-While I scope out Tracy for ya.
-Okay?
-Oh. Good idea.
And we'll come up with a plan
to really knock her off her
feet.
Oh, man.
That is huge.
You have no idea
how much I love you.
-I think I do.
-You're the man.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-So long.
-Yeah. ((LAUGHS)
(FOOTSTEPS)
* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
(MOANING)
(PANTING)
(KISSING SOUNDS)
(SIGHS)
* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
I'm really glad you're here.
(BED SHEETS RUSTLING)
What is it?
What? What?
What'd I do?
Nothing.
I need to go.
Well... just wait
a second, Anne.
There's something I've
gotta say to you, alright?
I really can't stay.
It'll only take a minute.
Look, it's important.
Please.
Alright.
What is it?
How'd you like to go
to dinner with me?
And then maybe
do something after?
(LAUGHS) Are...
are you asking me out on a date?
Well, it's just that we s
pend all this time together
and we don't
do anything but --
Yeah, but, I mean,
that's what we agreed to, right?
I know, but it's not like
that's all we have to do.
I mean what's the
possible harm?
I just, you know, I...
Come on.
What've you got to lose?
I mean,
I'll even pay.
(LAUGHS)
I'd really like it if
you said "Yes".
Okay. How 'bout, uh,
seven o' clock?
Seven's great.
I... I like seven.
Thanks.
(LAUGHS)
Alright.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(CLAPS HANDS)
(FOOTSTEPS)
-* (JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS)
-Peanut butter on pasta?
Yeah. It's great.
The peanut butter melts
into the spaghetti.
It's just like a sauce.
Only takes like ten
minutes to make.
Ew.
Where's your sense of adventure?
Where's your sense of taste?
You know, you are the most
obstinate person I've ever met.
Yeah. Except for you.
Of course.
-Me?
-Yeah. You're worse than I am.
You think you know the answer
to every question ever asked.
Oh. As if you don't think
the same thing about yourself?
Have you ever uttered
the words, "I'm wrong",
since the first day I met you?
I'm waiting for you
to say it first.
* (CALYPSO MUSIC PLAYS)
Alright, I'm wrong.
Sometimes I'm wrong, too.
* (CALYPSO MUSIC PLAYS)
I had a good time tonight.
Me... me, too.
Ah, see?
I told you it wouldn't be so
bad.
I guess so.
(LAUGHS)
So, could we
have dinner again?
As long as you don't cook.
(LAUGHS)
Tomorrow?
I can't. I'm busy.
Busy? Doing what?
Well, if you must know,
I'm going out.
(CLEARS THROAT) Well, I know
it's none of my business.
But, uh, do you mind if
I ask is it with another guy?
Well, yes, it is.
-(CAR SCREECHING PAST)
-Great.
No, that's fine.
You know, I mean, I, um,
actually, I was supposed to...
supposed to go out, anyway.
Okay.
* (CALYPSO MUSIC CONTINUES)
(CAR PULLING UP)
-(DOOR OPENING)
-Thanks.
(CAR DOOR CLOSING)
(CAR DRIVING AWAY)
Do you believe
what's happened?
(SIGHS) I mean,
everything was going along so
well.
You know,
we were getting along great,
then, BAM.
(SIGHS)
And it's not that I'm,
you know, really upset.
It's just, you know, after all,
we have this understanding.
I don't know.
I guess I'm just
a little shocked,
ya know?
I know you're wondering
if I'm jealous.
And, the truth is,
yeah, you know, I mean, I...
I am, I feel a slight twinge,
which is natural, ya know?
I mean,
jealousy's a primitive reaction
going back to
our caveman days.
But it's inappropriate
behavior now.
I know that. You know,
I may be a sexist, but I'm fair.
(SIGHS)
(KEYS UNLOCKING DOOR)
(INDISTINCT BACKGROUND CHATTER)
Well?
Well, what?
Don't you wanna say anything?
(LAUGHS)
I mean we are having lunch.
I don't have
anything to say.
(PLATES SETTING DOWN)
Alright.
(CLEARS THROAT)
* (JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS)
Hi.
Mark.
What are you doing here?
I came to see you,
of course.
Why didn't you call?
(LAUGHS)
I wanted to surprise you.
What?
Aren't you happy to see me?
Of course.
Of course I am.
(KISS SOUND)
(GIGGLES)
Gee, that's not much of
a kiss for your fianc
who's come 400
miles to see you.
Oh. (KISS SOUND)
I'm sorry. (GIGGLES)
Hi. How are you?
I'm Mark Fisher.
Oh, uh, hi.
Mind if I join you?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Uh, uh, please.
-Uh, uh, sit... sit down.
-Great.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Well, uh, you two must,
uh, work together, right?
Oh. Yes, naturally.
Of course.
So, tell me. How's my
girl doin' at her new job?
(LAUGHS)
Uh, excellent, Mark.
Uh, yeah, she's...
she's a very
talented person.
Uh, could you give us a...
a moment alone?
Then I'll have to be going and,
uh, you can spend the rest
of the afternoon with her.
No, of course not.
I'll just, uh,
-I'll wait over by the bar.
-Nice.
(KISSING SOUND)
Just a minute. Okay?
(FOOTSTEPS)
Look, I know this is
a big shock to you.
But if you just let me explain.
What's there to explain?
You are engaged to be married.
I mean, why should you
tell that to the man you're
just sleeping with?
It's not what you think?
How do you know what I think?
Look, I was going to
tell you about him. I --
Oh, when? After I made
a bigger fool of myself?
-You don't understand.
-Understand what?
I was... it's over
between Mark and me.
I was...
I just can't tell him.
It's you that I really care for.
-(HAND SLAMMING TABLE)
-Don't say that to me.
* (JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS)
I gotta go.
(NAPKIN HITTING TABLE)
I love
DIRECTOR: Alright, it's a take!
(LIGHTS CLICKING OFF)
(SILVERWARE HITTING TABLE)
MAN: Take.
-(SIGHS)
(HONKING EQUIPMENT SOUND)
(INDISTINCT BACKGROUND CHATTER)
* (BASS BEAT PLAYS)
Now, I want you to
understand what I'm doing
so you don't get
the wrong idea.
I know we have this
understanding, you know.
And, Anne, of course,
can go out with whomever she
wants.
But I started thinking,
you know,
and I was wondering if
maybe she might not have
pretended to be going
out with someone just
to make me take
her more seriously.
I mean,
not that I'd be angry if,
in fact,
she was lying.
You know,
the truth is,
I think it would be
quite endearing.
Well, it's been over
an hour and she still
hasn't come out yet,
so at this point I guess
you could pretty much say
that my hunch was right.
Yeah. Well, I guess
it just goes to show
that women aren't the
only ones with intuition, huh?
(LAUGHS)
Holy shit.
-* (SEXY MUSIC PLAYS)
-(BACKGROUND CITY STREET NOISE)
You know what this means,
don't you?
It means that everything
she said about just having
a sexual relationship
with me is probably true.
Yeah.
She doesn't care about me.
She's just using
me for my body.
What kind of a woman
is that, hm?
* Uh...
What if this isn't even a date?
You know, I mean,
what if this is like some
friend of hers or, uh,
or her brother, even?
You know,
it could be.
(CAR PASSING)
What if they're sitting
over there, right now,
just laughing their
asses off at me?
No, you know what?
That's it.
I'm outta here.
* Ooo... ah...
How could this
possibly happen?
You know, how...
how could she do this to me?
* Uh...
And what am I doing here?
I, I must be going crazy.
You know, I'm...
I'm Jack Westmore.
Jack Westmore.
You know?
I don't care what she does.
She can go out with whoever she
wants.
She... she can sleep
with whoever she wants.
I am way beyond jealousy.
(KNOCKING)
Open this door.
I know you're in there!
(KNOCKING)
(DOOR OPENING)
Jack.
What are you doing here?
I came to see you.
I told you I was busy
Yeah, well, I got something
I wanna say to you now.
Is it an emergency?
Are you in trouble?
Well, uh, no.
Then why don't
you call me tomorrow?
Why can't I come in?
No, Jack!
You can't.
Is there a problem?
Who is this guy, Anne?
It's alright, Steve.
I can handle it.
Would you please
just leave now?
No. No, not until you let
me in to say what I gotta say.
Hey, look. Why don't
you listen to what the
little lady has to say.
Well, why don't you just
mind your own business, pal?
This is my business.
So leave.
Oh. Leave?
You giving orders now?
Yeah, I'm --
(PUNCHING DOOR)
Ow! Ow. Ow.
-(GRUNTS)
-Ow! Ow. Ah. Ow!
Oh, you kicked
me in the shin.
Stop it.
Both of you.
Ah.
(SIGHS)
-Ah.
-Come on in, Jack.
(SIGHS)
Well, you said you
wanted to come in.
So, get inside.
* (JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(HEELS CLICKING)
Now, what is it?
Oh, well... uh,
Well, let's hear it, Jack.
I love you.
* (JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS)
What a dork.
(FOOTSTEPS)
(DOOR CLOSING)
Oh, God. How am I ever
gonna leave this apartment?
(SIGHS) How could I
have been so stupid?
(SIGHS) Have you ever seen
a bigger idiot in your life?
-(SIGHS)
-(DOG BARKING IN THE DISTANCE)
What in the world am
I gonna tell Anne?
There's no explanation.
I... sugar.
Sugar. That's...
that's it.
That... that... that's, uh,
temporary insanity brought
on by a sugar deprivation.
Yeah, I mean, they've...
they've done, like, you know,
scientific experiments where,
uh, you know,
they've proven that too
low a blood sugar can cause,
like, psychotic behavior.
Perfectly logical explanation.
In fact, I had a patient
on the show a
couple months ago.
That's exactly what happened.
She killed her boyfriend,
you know.
(LAUGHS)
That's it. That's...
ba-ba-bam.
Sugar.
She'll have to believe it.
Oh. Oh, oh.
(BALL BOUNCING)
Look, I know you
probably never wanna
talk to me again,
but, uh, no...
Okay. I...
I was completely wrong.
Um, (SIGHS) look, okay.
I'm a moron.
I'm a real moron.
(KNOCKING) Jack?
Man, you gotta help me.
Tracy wants to take me
home to meet her mother.
Well, that's... that's great.
I mean, she really likes you.
Dude, if I go
home with her,
she's gonna realize
how much I like her.
-(PHONE RINGING IN DISTANCE)
-There you go.
Then you can be completely
honest with her about,
you know,
how you feel.
Are you crazy, man?
If I do that,
she's gonna have
the power over me.
Wha -- relationships are about
love,
not power.
(LAUGHS) Yeah, right?
Since when?
Since the beginning of time.
That's great, Jack. That's...
that's your best advice, huh?
You know what, man?
I'm outta here. Thanks.
You know what
your problem is?
Educate me.
You think too much.
You know, as long
as you think that love
is a game to be won or lost,
you're never gonna find it.
I mean love is...
is a treasure to be found
only by exposing yourself and
being as vulnerable as you can.
The minute you start to
think you can outsmart
someone, you've lost.
Shit, Jack.
That was deep.
Yeah, it was.
Wasn't it?
Yeah.
Alright.
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSING AND LOCKING)
-(SIGHS)
-(BELL RINGING)
(DOOR OPENING)
-Hey.
-Hey, Steve.
-Hi.
-Hi. Could I talk to you?
Yeah. Sure.
Come on in.
Okay.
(FOOTSTEPS)
I just... I wanna
apologize for last night.
Oh, it wasn't your fault.
Nevertheless, I... I feel bad.
Why? I had a
great time last night.
'Till that nut showed up.
(LAUGHS)
Yeah. God. He was, uh,
really wacko, wasn't he?
You're telling me.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS) Listen, if you really
wanna make it up to me,
let me take you out tonight.
I can't.
(SIGHS)
Why not?
Well, it... it's about
that guy last night.
I just think...
-(FEET SHUFFLING)
-(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(BODY HITTING THE GROUND)
(DOOR SLAMMING)
STEVE: Let me in!
We gotta talk.
Jack, no. You can't
keep on doing this.
Just hear me out, okay?
(SIGHS) I guess,
under the circumstances,
I don't have a choice.
(KNOCKING)
STEVE: It's my apartment!
This'll only take a minute.
STEVE: I said, "Open up!"
No, I am not opening
this door until I'm through!
STEVE: I'll call the cops!
Yeah, go ahead.
Be my guest.
-(KNOCKING)
-What is it you want, Jack?
I wanna tell you
that you win okay?
You beat me. I mean
I don't know if I'm up,
or down, or if I'm coming,
or if I'm going.
I don't know anything.
Just tell me whatever
it is you want from me
and I'll do it.
What... what makes you think
that I want something from you?
Then why are you
torturing me like this?
I'm not torturing you.
You're torturing yourself.
What is it that you
want from me?
I want from you?
Yes. Why are you here?
I mean, what do you want?
(SIGHS)
I want... I wanna
know if you like me.
-Like you?
-Yes.
Yes. Or hate me.
Or anything, ya know.
I have no idea how
you feel about me.
(SIGHS)
I like you, alright?
(SIGHS) Since when?
I was attracted to you from
the very first day that we met.
You were? You...
Well, then what's
all this been about?
I mean... (SIGHS)
Why? Why wouldn't
you go out with me?
Because, Jack.
You stood for everything
I don't like in a guy.
I mean, how could
I go out with you?
So, I...
I decided to sleep with you.
But that just made it worse.
It did?
Yeah. It did.
Because the more
I got to know you,
the more I realized you're
not such a bad guy.
And it made me
like you even more.
(SIGHS) That's great.
I mean, that's...
that's really great, ya know?
Um, I don't know
what's so great about it.
Well, because, you and
I can have a relationship now.
You know,
a real relationship.
I don't think so.
Why not?
Because you and I are
talking about two different
things.
When you say relationship,
you mean fling.
That's not what I want.
I want something more
than just a good time.
Like what?
Like love and trust.
I want that, too.
And commitment.
Commit... commitment.
Yeah. Commitment.
You know, one person,
and only one person.
Do you want that, too?
That sounds so serious.
God, that's what I
thought you'd say.
Just wait a second,
alright?
I just... I, I need, uh,
I need time to think about it.
And I... I mean this is an
important decision, right?
Yeah.
You let me know.
* (INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(SIGHS)
-(FOOTSTEPS)
-That's the guy!
(FOOTSTEPS)
I'm going.
(HEELS CLICKING)
Uh, wait. Trace.
Hey, wait up.
-Hi.
-Hey.
Um, I need to talk to you.
Me, too.
Okay. Uh, look.
Come here.
Um, I wanna be perfectly
honest with you here.
I have tried to deceive
you and...
and fool
you into liking me.
And... and I haven't been
honest about my feelings,
or my motives,
or anything. So there.
Me neither.
-You... you haven't?
-No.
You, you either?
No. (LAUGHS) Wow.
Wait a minute.
You mean this whole time
we've been lying to each other?
Yeah. I guess so.
Oh my God.
That makes our entire
relationship make-believe.
Wow.
(LAUGHS)
I feel so stupid. (LAUGHS)
(VOCAL GUN SOUND)
No, I'm stupid.
No. (LAUGHS)
Oh, shit.
So, so, um, so what,
so what, so what should
we do about this, then?
How 'bout nothing?
-Nothing?
-Yeah.
Cause you know I,
I like you.
Yeah?
Well, I like, you know, who
you've been pretending to be.
So, if you keep doing that,
you know.
-(LAUGHS)
-It'll be good.
-No kidding.
-(GIGGLES)
Wait. You got...
you got something.
-I'm just gonna, um...
-Oh. What is --
-Oh, oh. Mm.
-Mm.
(KISSING SOUNDS)
-Wait a minute.
-What?
What do you think
Jack's gonna say?
Who listens to what Jack says?
-I don't. (LAUGHS)
-Yeah.
-No way. Mm.
-Mm.
(KISSING SOUNDS)
(MOANS)
-Wait.
-Oh my God.
-(GIGGLES)
-Stop, stop, stop, stop.
(KNOCKING)
-Yeah?
-(DOOR OPENING)
Shelly?
(DOOR CLOSING)
Can I talk to you?
Where have you been?
I haven't seen you
in about a week.
Oh, I've just, uh,
you know, I've been busy.
Have you been avoiding me?
What? No.
Of course not.
Good. Then we can
have some fun.
No, no, no. Shelly,
I can't. I can't.
Oh, yes, you can.
No, I'm serious.
I mean it.
-What?
-I can't.
Well, what is wrong with you?
I think I'm gonna
be monogamous.
You? Monogamous?
Uh, with who?
Anne.
This has gotta be
a joke, right?
I mean you're the guy
who said you could never
be faithful to anyone.
I guess I'm in love.
Oh, no. No, no, baby.
Come here.
Come here, baby.
Sit down.
You're not in love.
You're just crazy.
Did you, or did you not,
tell me that it was unnatural
for a man to
be monogamous?
-I did.
-Yeah.
And did you,
or did you not,
say that there are at
least ten women a day
that you wanna screw?
-I did.
-Uh-huh.
And did you,
or did you not,
say that you had no conscious
control over these feelings.
And that,
no matter what you did,
there was nothing you
could do to change.
I did.
Well, were you lying, Jack?
Was that all just a bunch of
crap?
No. No, you know what?
I believe that. I do.
Then it is impossible for
you to be monogamous, Jack.
(KISSING SOUNDS)
Shelly, no! I can't.
Jack, do you know
what today is?
No. I don't.
It's my birthday, Jack.
-Oh, oh, oh.
-Uh-huh.
-Oh, God.
-Yeah.
You know, I'm sorry.
I didn't... I didn't know.
You want me to have a
Happy Birthday, don't you?
Of course I do.
Well, this would make
me very, very happy.
Oh, oh, come on, Shelly.
Stop it. Just pull... put
that...
you know,
you should go see Marty.
-Marty?
-Yes.
You'd be surprised how
much you guys have in common.
Why? Does he
wanna screw you, too?
Oh, Shelly, stop --
-(DOOR OPENING)
-Surprise!
-Oh, shit!
-(GASPS)
-Oh, ho, ho.
Anne. Anne.
Anne. Anne!
-You son of a bitch!
-Oh!
-* (CALYPSO MUSIC PLAYS)
-You're screwing my wife!
I'm not your wife!
We're divorced.
-That doesn't matter.
-Yes, it does.
But I still love you.
Oh, you're crazy.
I hate to interrupt.
But I gotta go.
-(GRUNTS)
-Oh. Oh! Oh, oh. Oh.
Sorry, Marty!
You're fired, you bastard!
(FOOTSTEPS)
* (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
Anne! Anne!
(FOOTSTEPS)
Anne! Anne, stop. Wait.
Wait. Anne,
you gotta let me explain.
You got... you got...
I decided I... I wanna
have a relationship with you.
Get the hell away from me.
I was only in Shelly's
office to talk about you!
You bastard!
(DOOR SLAMMING)
Anne! Anne,
you don't understand. Anne!
(CAR MOTOR DRIVING AWAY)
Anne, I wanna
be monogamous!
Aw.
(CITY STREET SOUNDS)
INTERCOM: Flight 215 to
Los Angeles is now
boarding at Gate 27.
Well, I was wrong.
I've done a lotta thinking
about what happened and
I decided I was
really wrong.
Not that any of what
I said about man's nature
wasn't true. It... it is.
It's just that...
It wasn't the complete picture.
There's another aspect
of men that I didn't give
enough weight to.
And that's their need for love.
As for Anne, uh,
she might've been
the one person
for me, ya know?
* (JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS)
But I'm never gonna find out.
I... I can never talk
to her again, you know?
I... I've already made too
big a fool of myself already.
I mean how's... how's
she gonna believe me now?
No. Anyway, I'm splitting.
Going to Los Angeles
to look for work.
And, uh, I guess that's
how this is gonna end.
With me a sadder,
but wiser man.
Which is about what
I deserve, isn't it?
INTERCOM: Attention Passengers.
This is the final
boarding call for
flight 215 to Los Angeles.
Now departing at Gate 27.
* (BASS MUSIC PLAYS)
Wait a minute. You know,
I'm already a fool.
What difference does it make?
(HONKING EQUIPMENT SOUND)
DIRECTOR: Action!
* (SOAP OPERA MUSIC PLAYS)
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
What... what
did the crew say?
There's no sign of him.
They checked the airport
and the bus terminal.
There's no record of
him leaving town.
He just cannot have disappeared.
Well, I don't know
where he can be, Molly.
You know, I have checked
every inch of this county.
I... I just don't know
what I'm gonna do.
Oh, Matt. We... we...
we can't think the worst.
I need your help, Molly.
I'm weak. I'm so very weak.
-(SIGHS)
-(ELEVATOR DOOR DINGS OPEN)
-I'm right here, Matt.
-I know.
So am I.
Holy, she --
I mean, um, uh, hey.
Uh, Je -- Jeff. Why, why,
why you doin' here?
I decided to come back.
Uh, uh, well, that...
that's... that was not in the...
I mean they said that...
It's okay, good buddy.
I'm fine.
Just need a little
time to myself.
Oh. God.
Now, if you don't mind,
I'd like to have a few
words with Dr. Baldwin.
Uh, uh, yeah, but I...
I was, um... okay.
Yeah, alright. Just...
So, you're back?
Yeah.
I got all the way to
the airport but then
I couldn't leave.
Why not?
Because I think once
you've found what you
really want in life,
you can't walk away from it.
No matter what
the consequences
How do I know you
won't change your mind?
You seem to do that a lot.
You don't.
Neither do I.
But we'll never find
out unless we try.
And I'll do whatever has
to be done to be with you.
Just let me know
you feel the same.
It sounds so serious.
It is serious.
I'm serious.
Do you love me?
Yes. I do.
(LAUGHS)
(KISSING SOUNDS)
DIRECTOR: Yes!
That was great.
I love it. Fantastic.
It's a keeper.
Whoa, whoa. No, no, no, no.
Wait a second, you know.
That wasn't in the script.
At all. And I was...
I was... I was
gonna cry in this scene.
-Sandy, he stole my scene, man.
-Come on.
Now, don't worry, Troy.
We'll let you cry tomorrow.
You can kill off one of
your patients by mistake.
-Okay?
-Alright.
Okay. So why are we here?
That's a wrap, folks.
Let's go home.
(HONKING EQUIPMENT SOUND)
* (SOAP OPERA MUSIC SWELLS)
* (SOAP OPERA MUSIC CONTINUES)
-* (UP TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS)
-Well, I guess this really is
the end now. And everything
turned out happily after all.
I mean, Anne and I are
together and doing really well.
I mean, I don't even miss
sleeping around at all.
The truth is when you're
with someone you love,
the sex is so much more
meaningful and fulfilling.
* I'll be there
when she gets home...
I don't think about
other women. At all.
I mean, I... I barely even
notice that they exist.
* I'll be there
when she gets home...
Well...
* And I can be wrong,
And I can be right...
There was this one
today that I saw just
for a split second,
outta the corner of my eye.
* I'll be there,
when she gets home...
She was pretty good.
Nice hair.
Real short skirt.
Oh, and her legs
were like a mile long.
And her chest?
God, it was huge.
(SIGHS)
Man, she was great.
* That's right.
Oh, men.
-Aw...
-(LAUGHS)
* There's one thing
I can say.
DIRECTOR: Cut!
We're through with that.
* (POP MUSIC PLAYS)
Are we done?
-DIRECTOR: Yes, we are done.
-We're done.
Alright. We're gonna do
the credits right now
because this is such a
low budget film that we
don't have enough money
to really afford 'em.
So, if you'll stick with me,
I'd like to take you around
to meet some of
the crew members.
First of all, let's get her.
Traylor, come here.
This, of course,
is Traylor Howard.
-She played the role of Anne.
-Hi, Ed.
-Isn't she a sweetheart?
-Yeah.
Yeah, there's -- this one,
-That wasn't so bad.
A beautiful young lady
pulling all of the noodles
out of my hair is
Kimberly -- makeup.
-Frank, say, "Hello."
-Hello.
Mr. Prop Man.
Frank, right here.
-Look at you. Now you're on.
-Of course, talk to Clare.
-(LAUGHS)
-Clare does wardrobe.
Costume Designer. And her
assistant,
Andrea, Wardrobe Supervisor.
-Hello
-Guy back there with the
little Polaroid,
his name's Etod.
Around here, let me show
you some camera guys.
This would be Brian.
Say "Hello", Brian.
Yeah, there's Brian.
Over here we have the sound,
Boom Operator.
-My good friend here, Ed.
-This is Josh.
-Of course, Jay-Z right here.
-Hi. Nice to meet you.
Jay-Z pulls focus.
Riz, Art Department.
-That's Al.
-Huh?
-He's the Sound Man.
-I read lips
-This is lovely Lorraine.
-Hello, hello.
Hello, hello.
Isn't she cute?
Lorraine's also in makeup.
This guy just happened to
wander in on the set today.
This is my friend, Mike Hertz.
My old buddy from
Kansas City.
-Thanks, buddy.
-KC, alright! Keep it going!
Up top, here,
we have Lisa.
-Say, "Hello", Lisa.
-Hello.
She's the Line Producer.
-Hey, Ed.
-My main man in charge.
Our First AD, Tony Major.
-Love him. Love him.
-(LAUGHS)
And, of course,
our Script Supervisor.
She makes sure we s
ay all the right words.
That's Rebecca.
This... this would
be Lex duPont.
-Hey, there.
-Charming man.
Boy, I hope that thing's on,
is all I can say.
Director of Photography.
And a damn good one, too.
Come on outside.
I've got a few more people
to introduce you to.
-What?
-This is Carrie.
-Hi Sandy. HI everybody.
-She's the Second AD.
I got some people to
introduce to you on
the video camera. Bob.
-Say, "Hello", Bob.
-Hi, Bob.
Badass crew guy.
James Zucal.
This is Joe. Joe did
all of the set decorating.
-Thank you.
-Production Designer.
Production Designer.
-This is our Gaffer.
-Hi.
-Isn't that right?
-I Gaff.
-His name's Stanley.
-What's up?
-Jeremy's right here.
-Hello.
-Production Intern, is that it?
-Yep. Just about.
This is my main man, Don.
-Camera Operator.
-I'm not that cool of a guy.
(LAUGHS) Aw,
and here's Jason.
-Oh, yeah.
-Jason would be the Key Grip?
-That's right.
-Now that's an important title.
-Oh, yeah.
-What do you do, Jason?
-As little as possible.
-Absolutely. It shows.
He's union.
My main man, PA.
Usually a camera man
but it's such a low budget he
agreed to come on and help us.
-Is that a guy, or what?
-Just once. Just once.
Shonda. Shonda's a
young stand-in, right here.
What happened to
your trousers?
Oh, there's noodles all over.
I gotta introduce you to
someone really special.
This is Kelsey.
Kelsey, say "Hello".
-Hi.
-Isn't she a doll?
God, I love this girl.
-We got Matt over here.
-(BURPS)
That was charming.
Like I told you,
it's not always glamorous,
what we do.
Raymond works in Set
Decoration, is that right?
That's right, Ed.
Uh, so I guess that
pretty much does it.
Everybody's, uh,
here and accounted for.
But there's one
more person, actually.
Give me that camera.
-Aww.
-This... this is the main man,
-right here.
-Yay!
-Woo!
-Sandy Tung.
The Director.
Let me make sure
we got him in focus.
Sandy!