- Are you sure we should go in
there
with just the three of us?
- You worry too much.
It's a business call.
This guy's always professional.
- Yeah, but-
- Eh, don't worry about it,
Junior.
Anything goes down in
there, I'm gonna gut 'em.
- Gut 'em?
- Yeah, gut them.
- Is that what all you Brits are
like?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Well can't you just
say like a normal person?
- Like what?
- Take care of it.
- Take care of it?
- Yeah.
- What does that mean?
That's really fuckin' vague,
Grant.
My Auntie Belinda takes care of
her cat.
My mum takes care of my laundry.
If they say I'm taking
care, what does that mean?
Nobody knows.
But I say I'm gonna gut someone,
you know exactly what it means.
- Enough, gentlemen.
Enough.
- Yeah, sorry, boss.
- Yeah, Grant's sorry, boss.
- Oh, those are nice looking
knives you get there, huh?
- All right. Enough.
Now we're doing this.
And if things go south, I
trust both of you to handle it.
Understood?
- Yes.
- Capish?
- Yeah, capish, understood.
Gotcha.
- All right, let's go. Let's do
it.
Go in.
- Good evening, Mr. Schiavone.
Your guests are already here.
- Thank you my friend.
Hey, do me a favor.
Buy those beautiful
grandchildren
of yours something nice.
- Oh, oh no, Mr. Schiavone,
I'm sorry, I can't accept this.
- Of course you can.
It's my pleasure to
take care of my friends.
Otherwise you'd offend me, Gino.
You don't wanna do that, do you?
- No, I can assure you
I don't want to do that.
Just gimme a minute.
- You got it.
- Hey, why are you giving
that guy all that money, huh?
He owns this fucking
restaurant for Christ's sake.
- Hey.
Watch your mouth.
As long as I'm still breathing,
I make the decisions
and you follow my lead
and look imposing, not
the other way around.
Are we clear?
- Yeah, got it.
- Kid has a birthday coming
up soon, doesn't she?
- Jada?
- Yeah, in a couple months.
You remember?
- Sure I do.
We should talk about throwing
a party or something.
You know, 12 is a big deal.
- It is a big deal.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, I thought
these guys
were waiting for us.
What's the hold up?
- Okay.
- Good to see you, my old
friend.
- Good to see you, too.
It's been too long.
- So your mind, is it okay?
- Did I forget something?
- Well, I thought we had decided
that there would only be one
other person as a bodyguard.
- Well, forgive me.
One's just a driver.
Go wait in the car.
- Are you sure?
I'll be right outside. Don't
fuck it up.
- I won't.
- So, not to be rude, but
we're not young men anymore.
So why are we here, Rooker?
- 48 hours ago, I had a shipment
coming
to these docks from Vera Cruz.
Now that shipment by now
should be in my hands
making money for me, but it's
not.
The ship that that shipment was
on
was refused access to these
docks.
The captain had to leave before
he could unload my goods.
- So you can keep trafficking
in our fucking city?
- Your city?
- You know the rules, Rooker.
We don't traffic that
in this city. My city.
- I think the agreement that we
had
is not very equitable the way I
see it.
- Well, that's your fuckin'
problem
'cause we ain't changin' shit.
- Grant!
- I see your son still
hasn't learned his place.
- What did you say, old man?
Hey! Put it down!
I'll put a fucking bullet in
your head.
- Is this how you thought
you were gonna get your way?
- Yukio is very sensitive.
He doesn't take well to
aggression.
- Well how does he respond to
bullets?
- Put it down, son.
You were never good at
playing nice with others.
Put it down.
Now, this is how it's gonna be.
- Dad, dad.
- What the fuck happened?
Fuck.
- I need an ambulance.
My father's been shot.
- What are you doing?
Hey, hey stop, stop that.
- Please hurry up, please-
- Hey, stop!
- Hey, what are you doing, man?
- Stop. We can't call anyone.
Grant.
Grant, we gotta go.
Grant, they could be back. We
gotta go.
- Fuck you, man, I'm not
going there anywhere.
- There's nothing we
can do for him, Grant.
We gotta go, okay?
Come on, we gotta get outta-
- Ow!
- Fuck, you're hit, too.
Grant, we really gotta fucking
go!
- No, I'm not leaving him here!
- We gotta go, we gotta-
- Stop!
Stop it.
I'm not leaving him.
- Okay, Grant, it's okay.
Look, G, he's gone.
He's gone.
You'll do your father no favors
by staying here and
getting arrested, okay?
He told me to look after you
and I'm not doing that if we're
in jail.
If you want to avenge your
father...
Come on.
We gotta go.
Sorry buddy. We gotta go.
Come on, man.
- No.
- What is going on here?
- Hey, what the fuck, man?
- We gotta make a clean getaway.
Come on. Out, out.
Go on.
We gotta go. Go, go, go.
Come on, come on!
All right, here, get in.
- Sombra doesn't have friends.
- Yeah, you can keep
bullshitting me all night,
but I don't think Sombra
will appreciate knowing you're
the reason
his special delivery has been
delayed.
This is quite a selection you've
got here.
Oh, shit, you got Maker's.
It's one of my favorites.
A lot of people back
home say it's too light,
but they don't really know
what's good.
Alcohol's just so connected
to culture and environment.
You can't really criticize
until you've experienced it for
yourself.
It's the same with business.
You wanna understand someone,
if you wanna truly know them,
you have to meet them in person.
Otherwise, how do you really
know who's good or bad?
Sombra running late?
- Sombra's not coming.
- Shit, shit, he's blown.
Pull him out now.
- Get out of
there, Ray.
You're blown. Get out, now.
- At least he could
have told me to my face.
- Ray?
- I came a very
long way to deliver this.
- Dammit!
He isn't going to abort.
- How far is back up?
- Too far.
- Get in there, get
in there!
- Why did you do that?
- Oh, come on, Ray.
She just saved your life.
- They would've taken me to
Sombra.
- Jesus, Ray.
They would've taken you after
beating you half to death.
- But they would've taken me.
- You deal with him.
- Yeah, thanks to you two
my cover's actually blown.
- You're welcome.
- Can someone please explain to
me
how the hell this happened?
- We're working on that.
- It's not good enough, Al.
All right, I spent six months of
my life
developing this lead, six
months.
And now it's down to drain
because what?
'Cause this place is full of
holes?
- Is he fucking serious?
- I know you're not talking
about me.
- We don't have a lead.
- Then what happened, Al?
- Look, you think I'm happy
about this?
I could be home with my wife
having a home cooked meal.
Instead I'm stuck in Bogota
with your stupid white ass
and two of the Three Stooges.
This mission is as important
to me as it is to you.
So I need you to sit down and
calm down
and we'll figure this out.
- How?
- He's too close to this.
- Fuck you.
- Hey!
We'll figure this out.
You two, go cool off.
Hey.
I'll get you another shot.
- Hey, Ray?
Ray, are you in there?
- No.
- You got a phone
call.
- Take a message.
- It's from the
states.
He said he's your dad.
- Really?
A printed newspaper?
I can't remember the last time I
saw one.
- I can't remember the last
time I saw my son.
You all settled in there?
- Yeah. My room looks like a 90s
museum.
You know it's okay if you
wanna repurpose it, Pops.
You know, get yourself
home gym or a media room.
- That will always be your room,
Ray.
- Wow, look at these
two knuckleheads, huh?
- Inseparable knuckleheads.
You hungry?
No, I'm actually going
over to the hospital.
- You still gotta eat, Ray.
- Dad, I'm good.
- Do an old man a favor, huh?
- All right.
- He knows who did this, Ray.
- So when did he get started
working with his father?
- I'm not sure.
- Everyone knows Carmine
Schiavone, right?
You know, Grant was supposed to
be
the good one of the family.
How, how the hell did he
get sucked into this life?
- I don't know.
- Okay well what do you know,
Dad?
- He's not gonna risk anything
that the police could get
to them before he does,
that's what I know.
- Yeah, we both know that.
- How long has it been
since you spoke with him?
- It's been a while, Dad.
- He went through some tough
times when Beth got cancer.
Turned his life upside down
and...
- And what?
- Ray, you were his rock, you
know that.
You guys were like brothers.
- No, don't. Don't do that.
Come on.
- No, do what?
- Make me the bad guy.
- You had to go.
But he stayed.
He felt left behind.
- Yeah, I know.
And I wasn't there for him. I
know.
- It's not your fault.
He needed someone, something
and,
and he turned to Carmine.
- Yeah, and there's always
a catch with Carmine.
Fuckin' always.
- He's his father.
He wanted Grant to come
work with him and so he did.
The first order of business
is to find the people
that killed his father.
- Well you know if this
escalates,
it's gonna end bad for everyone
involved.
- He's gotta hear that, Ray.
Beth wouldn't want it.
- No.
No, but Carmine would.
- We have to go make him choose.
- Come on.
Give me my water, you bastard.
- Is that what they teach you to
talk like
at that fancy private school?
- Ray-Ray!
- Ooh!
Hey Jay-Bird.
Oh, wow, you got so big and
that is some attitude you got.
- I mean, it has been
forever since you've seen me.
And daddy.
- I know.
I'll do better, all right?
I'm sorry.
- You better.
Daddy said that he chose
you to be my godfather
because, "He was the most
responsible man I know
and he would protect you with
his life."
- He said all that, huh?
- Yep.
Although he was on a lot of
medication,
so he might have been high.
- Jada.
- Pops.
- Princess.
How is your father?
- Um, yeah, I don't know.
I mean every time that
we try to go in there,
Mr. Vincent makes us leave.
- Who?
- Mr. Vincent.
He says that Daddy
doesn't want any company.
- Hey, why don't you take
us to your daddy's room?
- Okay.
- All right?
- Come on.
- Jada, look, it's Ms. Carucci.
Nice to see you, Ms. Carucci.
Look who I bumped into
committing
misdemeanor assault on a water
fountain.
- No, no.
- I'll let that go since we
haven't officially met yet.
- Oh yeah?
You gonna let that go, too?
- You're a funny guy.
- Are they okay?
- Yeah, Uncle Ray-Ray's
giving them jujitsu lesson.
- Oh.
- What the fuck is going on?
Who the fuck are you?
- I'm the guy who's
wondering why his goddaughter
can't see her father?
Who are you?
- Are you a cop?
'Cause you're giving me
all kind of police vibes.
- Not exactly.
- Not exactly. That's exactly
what a fucking cop would say.
Would you do me a favor and
take a long fuck off walk
down that corridor?
- Why don't you tell him it's
Ray.
- Oh.
The infamous Ray Rose, is it?
- The one and only.
Get the fuck outta the way.
- Come on in.
- And you, you pathetic bunch of
cunts.
Honestly, I may as well have had
the fucking nurses do it!
I hope you don't think you're
getting paid
after that pathetic display.
Fuck's sake!
- Tellin' me all I had to do
is get shot to bring you home?
- Funny guy.
What'd the doctor say?
- I'm shot.
- No, shit.
Well, at least you still
got your sense of humor.
- Yeah, well they didn't take
that.
- The sooner, the better.
We've got a score to settle
and it isn't gonna settle
itself.
- Hey...
Look, I'm sorry about, about
Carmine.
Pops said the two of you
were getting close again.
- Yeah. Thanks.
- He also said you're
ready to burn the city down
looking for the guys who did
this.
- Let me guess, the cop
disapproves.
- Yeah, you'll know
when I'm talking to you.
- I'm fucking talking to you.
Are you serious with this guy?
Listen, TJ Hooker, we're
on the same fucking side.
- Well yeah, whose side is that?
- His side.
- Ray.
Look, he was my father's right
hand,
protect him with his life.
So he's my right hand now.
I'm gonna need both of you
if I'm gonna take this son
of a bitch Booker down.
- What?
You can't be serious.
Grant, let the cops handle this.
Come on.
- Is that a joke?
The cops?
The cops are another gang out
here, mate,
like they are everywhere in the
world.
Grant, they're not gonna
want to get involved
in a war unless there's
something in it for them,
you know that.
- Do you hear this shit?
War?
Is that what you want?
Look, think about Jada.
She's sitting out there
concerned for you
because Mary Poppins here
won't let her in to see you.
- Yeah, well, I didn't let her
in.
Okay? That was me.
- Why?
I don't want her to see
me like this, you know?
- So what, you let her
sit out there in the dark
wondering what's going on?
You don't think she had
enough of that with Beth?
- How would you know, huh?
You were nowhere to be
found when Beth died.
Let her in.
- You sure?
- You heard him.
- Hey, baby.
- What happened?
- This? Oh this is a couple
of scratches, couple bumps.
I'll be fine.
- You're lying.
- Hey.
- Well you are.
- Hey, Vincent. Why don't you go
home?
Huh?
Come back in the morning,
we'll get to work.
- Well, I'm not gonna
leave you here am I, right?
- Get the fuck outta here.
- What you looking at, old man?
- I'm not too old.
- He ain't worth it, Pops.
- Fuck that lot of ya's.
- Hey, baby, I'll be all right.
Especially now that you and Pops
and Uncle Ray-Ray's here, huh?
But listen, I think you should
go home with Ms. Carucci.
I need to talk to Ray-Ray.
- But...
- Jada, Jada, why don't you
come back home with me, huh?
We'll watch some movies,
have some ice cream.
It'll be nice.
- But I just got here.
- How about, how about you just
do
what the grown ups ask you to
do, hm?
I'll see you soon.
- Fine.
- Oh.
Don't hurt me, now.
I'll see you later, okay?
All right.
Ouch.
- Yeah.
You know, I don't want to hear
it.
- I haven't even said anything
yet.
- Yeah, I can feel the Ray
Rose judgment all on your face.
Now save it for somebody
who didn't just see
their father gunned down in
front of him.
He killed my father, Ray.
And now they'll try to kill me.
And they're trying to take
me away from my daughter.
Should I let that go?
- You go down this road, a lot
of people are gonna get hurt.
- Yeah, no, that's their
problem.
- No.
Goddammit, no, it's your
problem.
It's Jada's problem.
Is this the kind of man you
wanna be?
What are you teaching her?
- Teach her how to defend this
family.
How to stand up for herself
and the ones she loves.
- You have got to relax.
- You know, when my father
told me to come work for him,
I thought it was just so we
could protect his business,
make sure his legacy could live
on.
But now I, I don't know, maybe
it's-
- We gotta go.
A car load of Rooker's men
just pulled up outside.
- Well how do you know they're
Rooker's?
- Because I'm really good at
what I do.
Look, your old man trusted me
and now you've gotta trust me.
We gotta go, but right now.
- Fine.
- No, what are you doing?
- Did you hear what I just said?
There's a car load of
these days coming here.
What do you think, they're
coming in
and giving them get well soon
balloons?
- How do they know what hospital
we're at?
- Jesus Christ, it doesn't
matter
how they know, they're here.
I gotta get him out the back.
- Hey, go home. Go home and
play with your goddaughter.
- Go.
- Hey.
- Excuse me, is there
a stairwell near here?
Fuck.
- Shit.
- I'm out.
- Come on. Let's go.
Come on, up.
We gotta go.
Come on.
- Hey, that's him.
That's the guy.
Hey, watch out, Ray!
- Come on, get into
the car.
- Hey, what are you doing?
Stop!
Get in, get in!
Are you good?
- Yeah, I think I'm good.
Your wound is open.
- I'm fine.
- Grant.
- I said I'll be fine!
What are you doing?
- I'm rallying the troops.
- Hang up the phone.
- Rooker's gonna keep sending
more men.
You know that, right?
He's gonna keep sending people
until you're in the ground.
We need every man we can get
right now.
- I said hang up the fucking
phone.
How did Rooker's men know where
we were?
I mean they didn't just
know what hospital I was in.
They knew the exact room I was
in
and they came directly at us.
So, who'd you tell I was at
Mercer?
- Me?
- Yeah, fuckin' you.
- Who the fuck's talking to you?
- Hey, don't look at him.
Answer my question.
- Nobody. I didn't tell fucking
anybody.
Are you fucking serious?
- Grant.
You need to calm down.
- Stay out of this, Ray.
- You need to chill out, all
right?
I'm a fucking law enforcement
officer.
I let way too much shit slide,
I can't let you kill this
asshole.
- I'm not gonna kill him.
No.
Not while we're driving.
I'm gonna shoot his fucking
balls off.
Who'd you tell?
- Come on. No.
- Who?
- I told some of the...
Nobody, okay? Nobody.
Did you forget that they were
fucking
shooting at me, too?
Fuck's sake.
Take it easy, Grant, okay,
please?
- You better not lying to me.
- I'm not lying.
- Ms. Carucci, I remember.
Yes.
No gluten, no peanuts.
Almond milk.
Um, I think I, I'm out.
I tell you what, I'll go
pick some up, all right?
You know, I have another call
coming in.
I'll call you right back. I
promise.
- She's just gonna call right
back.
- Hey, is there anything that
you can eat?
- I can eat anything in
moderation.
- Moderation, huh?
- Yeah, too much of
anything is bad for you.
Surgeon general told us that.
- Really?
- Is there anything that you can
eat?
You are pretty old.
- What the hell is this
place?
- Rooker operates out of here
sometimes.
- All right, so what's your
plan?
- Well what's yours?
- Same as before.
You know, call the cops
and let them handle it?
- Fuckin' hell, has anyone ever
told you
you're like a dog with a fucking
bone?
Doesn't loyalty or honor or
respect,
doesn't any of that mean
anything to you?
- Yeah, you should know the
difference
between defending honor
and getting revenge.
- Shut up.
- Ray, I told ya.
If we're not down for this, then
go home.
Stop wasting your breath
trying to get us to stand down
because it's not happening,
okay?
My father's killer, he's gonna
be dead
before the sun goes down.
Understand?
- Okay, so what's your plan?
- You know my plan.
I'm gonna go in there and
I'm gonna ask a question
and then I'm gonna shoot
somebody.
And then I'm gonna ask the same
question,
if nobody answers it, I'm
gonna shoot somebody else.
And then again, if nobody
answers that question,
the same question, I'm
gonna shoot somebody else.
Okay, 'cause I'm gonna keep
shootin' until I get my answers.
- That works for me.
- Get down.
- Come on, get out
here.
Come on, come on.
- Come on.
Where you going, where you
going?
Get over there!
Keep going, get in there.
- Son of a bitch!
- Is that what I think it is?
- He's been sex trafficking
this whole fucking time.
That meeting was a fucking smoke
screen.
- My father forbid this.
- And they killed him for it.
- But this is what you
need to put an end to them.
All right, you got proof right
here.
Sex trafficking puts the
whole organization away-
- He's not still talking about
calling
the fucking cops, is he?
- No, I'm gonna handle him.
Then you can call your cops.
- So you're gonna get revenge
no matter what, right?
No matter what the cost,
no matter who gets
caught in the crossfire?
- Nobody in that house is
innocent.
Let's go.
- You're wrong.
Those girls are innocent.
- Get in there, shut up!
Get comfy, ladies.
This is your home now.
♪ Oh man I got a lot of gold ♪
♪ Stack that bread like dominoes♪
♪ Anything is possible ♪
- Don't move!
What part of don't move
did he not understand?
♪ Oh man I got a lot of gold ♪
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Hey, if you keep shooting
everybody,
who's gonna answer my questions?
- He fucking moved. What
did you want me to do?
- Come on, we're gonna
get you out of here.
Let's go.
Shh.
- Be quiet?
There's a firefight going on.
- Once you get to the road,
find the nearest person, house,
car and call for help, okay?
Go, go, go, go.
- Hey, ah, ah, ah, sit your
fucking ass in that chair.
- Sit down.
- Do not be a stupid cunt.
- Dammit, Vince, is he dead?
- All right, all right that
was partially my fault.
Only partially, though,
because you know what?
If I hadn't of shot him, G,
he would've come in and shot
you.
But you should take partial
responsibility for it.
- Me? For what?
- I don't like to criticize
you in front of...
Look, mate, honestly?
I don't think you said
don't move loud enough
when you came in.
The people in other rooms,
I don't think heard you.
I've said it now.
Look.
- Okay.
Are you listening?
Don't move or you're gonna die.
Did you hear me? Did they hear
me?
- I think you're doing it too
loud now.
There's only two of them.
- Where's your boss?
Where's Rooker?
- Wait, wait.
- No!
- What the fuck did you do that
for?
- He's down!
- He's down when I fucking
say he's down, okay?
- What are you gonna do
with that?
- Whatever the fuck I like.
Listen, you're either here to
help us
or you can fuck off,
and that's the last time
I'm saying that to you.
- Grant.
- What the fuck did you do that
for?
- I told you what was gonna
happen.
Nobody answered my questions.
Fuck 'em. They can all die.
Why don't you look for
something we can find?
Something's gotta tell us where
Rooker is.
- Hey.
How many people am I
supposed to let you kill
before I take you in?
- What's that supposed to mean,
huh?
You're gonna take me in?
- Yeah, I'll do whatever I have
to do
because you're not gonna listen
to reason.
- Well what happened to
I don't wanna be the one
to tell Jada daddy's not coming
home
to telling Jada daddy's not
coming home because of me?
- I'm serious, Grant.
Cut this shit out.
- I agree, and it will
end when I kill Rooker.
Understand?
What'd you find?
- Yeah, rather surprisingly,
I found fuck all
because you killed everybody
we were about to ask questions
to.
Like honestly mate, what
the fuck you playing at?
- What's the matter, you wanna
watch
something different, Jada?
- No, I mean, that's the
point? It's all fake anyway.
- Fake?
You never heard of a talking
fish?
Who has a friend who
can't remember anything?
Come on.
- I'm 11, you know. Not a baby.
- Excuse me.
Okay.
You wanna talk about somethin'?
- He never wants to
spend any time with me.
- Sweetie, there's no one
in the world your father
would rather spend time
with than you, believe me.
- Yeah, right.
- I know it may not
seem that way sometimes
because he's always working,
but everything he does, he does
for you,
like all good fathers do.
- Yeah, right.
- Can I ask you something?
Have you ever seen your father
cry?
I have.
- When?
- 11 years ago.
The day you were born.
- Was he sad?
- No.
He was happy, sweetie.
Probably happier than
he's been his whole life.
- Really?
- I saw him cry with my own
eyes.
- What was that?
- Well, that was probably just a
raccoon
trying to get into my garbage
cans.
I'm gonna check it out.
You finish watching the movie
and I'll get a refill on this?
- Sure.
What the fuck are you doing in
my house?
Jada?
Let her go.
- Pops!
No, no, stop, you're hurting
him!
Pops!
No, no, stop, stop, you're
hurting him!
Pops, please!
- So we think this is a good
idea?
Just sitting out here in the
open
when someone's out there
trying to kill him?
- Yeah, let 'em come.
Where the hell's the waitress
at?
I need a straw.
- Fuckin' same old Grant
Schiavone, man.
You know, your bullheadedness
is gonna get you killed
if your ego doesn't first.
- So be it.
Hey, waitress?
Yo, hello? I need a straw.
Hello?
- Dude, relax.
I'll get you a straw.
- I don't need you to get me a
straw, Ray.
- What is going on?
- Stop trying to fix everything.
Stop.
- I think he wants you to
stop pretending to be his mum.
- Yeah, we're all set.
- Eat your waffles.
- Told you you wouldn't like it.
- I'm just trying to help, okay?
- Yeah, well, I don't need your
help.
We're not kids anymore.
I don't need you to swoop
in and save the day.
- So, what am I doing here?
- Yeah, I was kind of
wondering the same thing.
Look, besides Jada,
you and Pops are the
only family I have left.
And if anything was to happen to
you, too,
because of the Schiavone
business?
No, that's not gonna happen
if you keep on insisting
being my protector.
So why don't you let me help you
for once?
Go home, Ray.
- Amen to that.
Do you need me to call you an
Uber?
Hm?
- Yeah?
Who is this?
- You've cost Mr.
Rooker a lot of money tonight
and took something from him.
- Oh, tell your boss to fuck
off.
We didn't take anything
from his geriatric ass.
We've been in the city all
fucking day.
- You should not have
interfered
with Mr. Rooker's business.
He valued those girls very much.
And since you took that away
from him,
he will now take something
away from you that you value.
- Where's Jada?
- Call Pops.
- I'll get the car.
- We gotta go.
Dammit!
All right, come on let's go.
- I'm fucking going, am I?
What use is it if we speed
and we get pulled over,
then we're not gonna get there.
- Hold up.
- Hey, get back in the car.
- I'm on a job, this is my
father's house!
- Hey.
- Get back in the car!
- Hey fuck you, man,
my daughter's in that house.
Hey, Ray.
- Hey.
What the fuck?
- Get the fuck.
- Hey, get back in the car.
- My daughter's in there!
- Hey, hey, hey, don't
you fucking touch him!
Hey.
Don't I know you?
- No, I don't think you do.
- Yeah, I think-
- Get back in the car,
take it around, the street's
closed.
Hey, hey.
- Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, listen, it's his daughter,
okay?
It's his daughter, hey, relax!
Relax.
- Hey, shh, shh.
- You need me to move the car,
right?
- Get the car outta here!
- Dad?
Dad.
Jesus Christ, what happened?
- We don't know. He
hasn't been able to say much.
Looks like a home invasion.
- Dad.
- They beat him up pretty
bad.
- They're gonna take
care of you, all right?
- Where's Jada?
- They took her.
Masks. Devil masks.
I tried.
I'm sorry, Grant.
- Hey Pops, hey Pops, I know you
did.
I know you did.
- Ray?
- Yeah, Dad?
- Family, no matter what.
Family, right?
No matter what?
- Dad, Dad?
- What's happening?
- We gotta go.
Please, just let us go.
- Fuck, things are getting out
of hand.
Where's Jada?
- Rooker has her.
- Shit.
Do you remember when your
father was getting annoyed
because cops were kept
flipping over to Rooker
because he was paying them more?
- Yeah.
- You see that guy?
He's one of them.
- Are you sure?
- I'm fucking positive.
I told you I recognized him.
We went around to all of
their homes one by one
and trust me, he's got a fucking
hot wife.
If you wanna find Rooker,
I say we stop following bread
crumbs.
- Let's go.
- Hey, where you going?
- Stay with Pops.
He needs you.
I don't.
- So what do you wanna do?
- Follow him.
- Yes, boss.
- Needs you.
- Dad, he's a grown man. You
need me.
- No.
Not he, she.
Jada.
Find her.
- Dad, cut it out, all
right? Take it easy.
- Find...
- Can we hurry up, please?
- Could this guy be more of a
cliche?
I mean he's a cop in a donut
shop.
Fucking hell.
- All right, let's go.
- We can't pick him up here,
mate.
- Yeah, let's go.
Hey.
Get in.
Now.
- Shit.
- Good boy.
Come on.
- I know you know who we are.
And we know who you are.
And more importantly, we
know who you work for.
- I work for the city of Los-
- Oh!
- I'm a fucking police officer.
Are you crazy?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Mind your manners.
- Where's my daughter?
- Daughter? Who the-
- Ah!
- Are you all right?
- He's hurt.
Clearly needs to go to a
hospital.
- Hey, do not talk unless you're
answering
some of his questions, you
stupid cunt.
Now stay down, for fuck's sake.
- You know, you're right.
I should be in the hospital
'cause I was shot, the same
day my father was killed.
And now my daughter's been
kidnapped.
Good friend's house of mine.
So I need you to listen to
me very closely, huh, huh?
Closely, 'cause there's no
scenario
where you get back into your
squad car
without telling me where my
daughter is.
And I know who you work for.
And guess what? You used to work
for us.
So, imagine all the ungodly shit
that we could pull up on you.
You're entangled with both
families.
- Why go through the trouble,
boss?
I say we just fucking pop him
right here
and then we drive to that house
of his
and we cap his kid and we
murder his fucking wife.
That's after of course I've got
her
to do some unspeakable things to
me.
- You motherfucker!
- Hey, don't fucking look at me.
Answer his fucking questions,
hm?
- Where's my daughter?
- Stand up.
Come here!
- Come!
- Smile.
- I want to go home.
- I wanna go home!
Let me go!
Let me go home!
Please.
Stop it, Jada.
Stop it.
If you're crying, you're not
thinking.
What would Grandpa do?
What would Dad do?
Thanks for that, too, Grandpa
Carmine.
- Yeah?
- Hey, hey.
I need you to run a trace
on a call, all right?
Let know as soon as you have
location.
Number is 973-415-9604.
- Okay, no worries.
Hey, Ray, is everything okay?
- Hey, I gotta go, all right?
Call me back when have
something.
- All right.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, Pops.
Take it easy, all right?
Take it easy. You want some
water?
Take it easy, all right?
- J...
Jada.
Okay?
- No.
I don't know.
Grant is out there looking
for her, all right?
What, hey, hey, what is it?
What is it?
Stop, stop.
You're gonna hurt
yourself, all right? Stop.
- No.
You...
You go.
Help your brother.
- No, what?
No, no. Grant will find her.
- You, you!
- What?
- I'm so proud of you, Ray.
- I know you are.
I know you are, Dad.
I'm proud of you, too.
Pops?
Pops!
No, no, no.
Pops.
No, come on, please don't do
this.
Pops!
- We need you to leave now.
- What is happening?
- Outside, now.
- But I'm his son.
- We're gonna do everything we
can, sir.
Ah!
- Hey!
- Hey, let me go! My dad's gonna
kill you!
- Don't make me hurt
you, kid.
My boss will kill me
if I damage the goods.
Or we find a supplier.
If you try to leave again,
you're gonna get hurt.
Don't push your luck.
- Don't push yours.
- Stay!
Or...
- You got something for me?
- Something you need to tell me?
- Just taking care of
some family business.
- What kind of family
business requires you
to use agency resources to trace
a phone?
- The important kind.
- You think I don't
already know what's going on?
- Then you know what I have to
do.
- I know what you think you have
to do,
but this is not the way, Ray.
I need you to stand down.
- Not gonna happen.
The last thing we need is for
your face
to be plastered all over the
news
being associated with a local
turf war
between two crime families.
- Turf?
You think this is about turf?
You think I would be involved
if this is about turf?
- Ray, listen.
- I gotta go.
- This is not a request.
I'm ordering you to stand down.
I can't stop you from here.
I'm ordering you to steer
clear of your friend's drama.
That's all I can do.
What you do next is completely
up to you
and the consequences are
yours and yours alone.
Do you understand what I'm
saying?
- Yeah.
You're telling me to choose
between my job and my family.
- I'm asking you to decide
where your loyalty lies
and proceed accordingly.
- Message received.
- Ray?
- Yes?
- Get in.
- Okay, Ray.
We're headed to the storage
place on Roosevelt, right?
- That's right.
- Got it.
Oh, I'm Candy by the way.
- All righty.
- Did you run a trace on
that number he gave you?
- No, sir. Not yet.
- Don't.
- Where's my daughter?
- Fuck...
You!
- Boss, are you sure you
don't want me to take over?
Or do you at least want a donut?
It'll give you like a sugar
boost.
- No, it's my daughter, it's my
pain.
- All right, they're good,
though.
- I can do this all night.
This one?
This one's for Pops.
Ah!
Where is she?
- If she's lucky,
she's on her way...
To a cartel leader's house in
Mexico.
Some big mansion where she can
be really well taken care of.
If she plays nice.
- You gonna stick to that story?
You stickin' to that story?
- Where's my daughter?
- Fuck you!
- Are you done?
Yeah?
- You sure?
Tell him, tell him.
- Rooker keeps all this girls
in the old Westfield Warehouse
while he waits for buyers.
That's, that's where they'll
have her,
if they haven't sold her
already.
If they haven't sold her
- You better pray to
God that they haven't.
- Please. Please, I
have a family too, man.
- You think I give a fuck about
that?
- I have a family, too.
- Leave him.
- Boss, what do you mean leave
him?
We gotta fucking do him, haven't
we?
- What's he gonna do? Tell the
truth?
Hm?
Yeah.
He's not gonna see in
the inside of a prison.
- You hear that, buddy boy?
You might not believe this,
but this was your lucky day.
Good luck explaining all this
shit.
How do you wanna do this?
- Well we can't go in there guns
blazing
until we know Jada is safe.
- All right, then we go in
quietly.
Get the lay of the land.
And then we go guns blazing.
- When Jada's safe, you
can shoot anybody you want.
Kill everybody if you want.
As long as we secure Jada first.
- Yeah, I know.
Come on, let's do this.
- Shit.
- Are you okay, Ray?
'Cause you look like...
I mean I can smell the
negativity
coming up off you like cheap
cologne,
which is funny because your
actual cologne is nice.
I'm fine.
- Are you sure? Because
I'm a really good listener.
You know, dropping people
around is just my side gig.
I'm actually a licensed
therapist.
- Thank you.
I'm fine.
- If you say so.
But that negative energy
needs to be dealt with,
'cause I don't have any sage in
my car-
- Ma'am.
I heard you the first time.
- Hey.
It's me.
I tracked down that number for
you.
- But Doss.
- Doss was a great agent a long
time ago,
but now he sits behind a desk
and he's forgotten what it feels
like.
- What what feels like?
- The need to right a wrong,
to fix what needs to be fixed.
And you, you're the best I've
ever seen
up close at doing that.
So, if you ask for help, I
know it's for a good reason.
The phone is at 2315 Lansing
Drive.
- You got it.
I owe you a beer when I get
back.
- And an apology.
- That, too.
- Hey Ray?
Do me a favor, yeah?
Try not to get killed.
I don't want to be the one
to explain that to Doss.
- I got it, buddy.
Thanks.
Change of plans.
Take me to 2315 Lansing Drive.
- He's coming.
- All right, I'm going.
- Take it easy.
- I'd like to apologize for what
I-
- Don't say it!
If you say my father's name,
I'm gonna come over this table
and I'll fucking kill you.
- I had great respect for your
father.
It's just a shame that his
stubbornness
and lack of foresight would not
allow us
to come to an arrangement.
- For what?
For your sex trafficking in our
city?
Yeah, we told you not to do
that.
We don't do that in our
city. You did it anyway.
So don't sit there and
act like you didn't know
this would come to a head, hm?
You knew and you knew when we
found out
that there would be blood.
- But not ours.
- Well that can be arranged,
mate.
Why don't we talk-
Take your fucking hands off me
or you're never gonna get them
back.
Hey, hey, hey!
- Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, where are you taking him?
Answer me!
- Carmine Schiavone was a good
man.
- I told you not to say his
fucking name.
- He's gone.
His demise has created
a void in leadership.
I'd like to propose a more
friendlier way
of solving our problems.
It would be beneficial for all
of us.
- Fuck you!
- Think about your daughter.
Is this a good place
to be raising a child?
You hand over your father's
business to me
and I personally will make sure
that you
and your daughter are well taken
care of.
- You think 'cause you got us in
here
and you took away our guns,
you think I'm gonna give
you my father's legacy?
- Yes, I do.
- Are you sure this is where you
wanna be?
- This is exactly where I want
to be.
- If you say so.
But you don't have nobody
tied up in there, do you?
Nevermind. Don't answer that.
Uh, we don't take cash.
- Well you do tonight.
- Take it easy, Ray.
- You jumped board and killed my
father.
I'm looking forward to killing
you.
- There is an old Japanese
proverb.
It means he who seeks only
vengeance finds only suffering.
- That's nice.
I'm gonna have to remember that.
You know what?
There was an old Italian
saying on my block growing up.
It means fuck you.
- Hey, you wanna stop whispering
like fucking school girls
and tell me when I'm gonna get
outta here,
otherwise I'm gonna have
to kick somebody's ass.
And you don't want that, believe
me.
All right.
That's it?
What the fuck too you so long?
- You're welcome.
- You had a gun the whole time?
- I had two.
- You had two guns this
whole fucking time?
You didn't feel that'd
be useful at any point?
- Where's Grant?
- He's in a packaging area,
okay?
Which is Rooker's weird ass
office.
There's a lot of people
between here and there.
- Okay.
Well what about Jada?
- I don't know.
They jumped us before we got too
far in,
but she's in the building
somewhere.
- Okay.
I'm gonna get Grant, you find
Jada,
bring her to the packaging area.
Think you can handle it?
- What's that supposed to mean?
Yeah, I can handle it.
I handled this, didn't I?
And why don't you go and get
Jada?
Wouldn't she much rather see
uncle Ray-Ray
before she sees me?
- We're doing this my way, all
right?
Get Jada, bring her here.
Got it?
- Listen, you're not in charge.
I happen to agree with the plan,
but...
He's gone. All right, he's gone.
All right, use your stealth.
Fuck, that's loud.
- Is that your cavalry I hear?
Whoever it is, they better
be bringing in a lot of ammo.
- There isn't anyone else.
- We know you have bad cop Ray
Rose.
We know all about him.
Look.
He's even on time.
Just say what we asked
you to say on the camera
then we can all go home.
Look, I know you didn't
like your father's business.
You only went to work for
him after your wife died,
and you were looking for
something
to fill your empty, useless
life.
Am I right?
- Don't you talk about my wife.
- You just don't get the
dynamic, do you?
You're in no position to give me
orders.
- Ah!
- We can put a stop to this
long evening you're having,
and I'm sure that your
daughter is ready to go home.
- Where is she?
Get away from him.
- We gotta get out there.
- What about her?
- All right, wait!
- Down on your knees.
- Ha, you must be the best
friend.
- I said get your ass down on
your knees.
- My sources told me
that you're a DEA agent,
is that correct?
- This is not talk time. This
is shut the fuck up time.
- May I ask you a question?
Are you here on official DEA
business
or is this just some
kind of personal fucking-
- Keep talking, asshole.
Keep talking.
Grant.
Come on, buddy, get up, we gotta
go.
- I think your friend might
need some medical assistance.
You know, after the night you've
had,
don't think you'd wanna
go back to that hospital.
Oh, by the way, how's your
father?
- Don't test me, Rooker.
- No. Nobody kills him but me.
- No one else is dying tonight.
You sure about this?
- Hey!
- Shoot him.
- I don't want to.
- Shot him!
He's gonna take that gun off you
and he's gonna shoot me
and then he's probably gonna
shoot you!
Shoot him!
- Stay back.
- All right, little
girl.
Give me the gun.
- Don't listen to him!
- It's not a toy.
- Jada!
He'll kill me, kill you
and then kill your father!
- Just give me the fucking gun!
- Please, mister, stop walking.
This gun is no used to you.
- Shoot him!
- I win.
- I told you that that
gun was no use to you.
- You little sh-
- Your father should not be
showing you
how to use guns at your age.
- I didn't learn it from daddy,
doofus.
I saw it on the Sopranos.
- You're all right.
Come on, let's get out of here.
I need those bullets.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Don't you fucking move.
- So, I guess this is where you-
- No!
No.
- Daddy?
- You're okay.
- Hey.
Hey, Jay-Bird.
- Ray-Ray.
- I bet you weren't even scared,
huh?
- Not a bit.
How's Pops?
- Hope you know your old man
would be very proud of you.
- Yeah, well enjoy it while you
can,
'cause we got a lot of questions
we're gonna have to answer.
- Question?
What questions are you talking
about?
Oh, I know he is not talking
about
calling the fucking cops again,
is he?
- Yeah, Vincent.
I think he is.
- Are you serious?
You still wanna play Boy Scout?
After everything that's
fucking happened here?
There are so many dead
bodies in this building,
lots of which you dropped.
Or did you forget that?
- I told you, we're doing this
my way.
- You sure about that, big man?
Huh?
- Vincent.
Hey.
It's over.
- It doesn't have to be.
- You see? You fucking
need someone like me!
That's what happens when
you don't finish a job!
- Can we go home now?
- Yeah, baby.
We can go home.
- All of you guys go.
I'm gonna stay and clean
some of this shit up.
I don't know about you, but
after this,
I'm gonna sleep like a fucking
log.
- Not me.
I'm gonna have nightmares about
devils
for the rest of my life.
- Oh, those stupid masks?
Don't worry.
There aren't any of those
guys abound anymore.
- What did you say?
- I told her the masks weren't
so scary.
- Yeah, how did you know?
- Shit.
I shouldn't have said that,
should I?
- You weren't there
when Pops told us that.
- Oh no, no, the cop told me.
The cop told me about
the guys in the masks.
G, we were there.
- The cops didn't say anything.
- He did, he told us about
the guys in the masks.
- He didn't say anything about
masks!
- Let me explain, G.
Come on.
- You're the only person who
knew what hospital I was in.
Were you a part of this the
whole time?
They killed my father!
And they took my daughter
from me, Vincent.
- Son of a bitch.
You told Rooker Jada was
with Pops, didn't you?
- Why? We treated you like
family.
- Like family?
Like family? You treated
me like a family pet.
Let me tell you something G,
you and your father didn't
give a shit about me.
The only reason I was here is
because I have no bloodlines.
You know, one thing that Rooker
had
that your old man didn't?
He paid.
He paid more! That's
how you lost everyone!
And you know what? He was
gonna give me status and power.
I was gonna run this
whole trafficking thing.
Me!
Which would've been a lot better
than being your fucking chauffer
for the rest of my life.
- You're a piece of shit.
- You know what?
I actually understand
why you feel like that.
But then you're a cop,
so who gives a fuck?
But me and you, G, we were
close.
I fucked it up.
Shit!
But it's okay, because the only
person
that really sucks for is you
guys.
- No!
Daddy!
Daddy, no.
No, please don't die.
- And for what?
For Goody Two Shoes here
who was gonna turn us all in at
the end?
Well, I got some good news for
you G,
I don't kill kids, but you know
what?
I think she's gonna end
up an orphan anyway.
And you, you fucking pig cunt.
You, I'm gonna enjoy this.
Shit.
- Daddy? Daddy, please be okay.
- I'm gonna be okay, baby.
- Hey.
- You're lying.
- I don't wanna leave you.
I never wanted to leave you.
I'm gonna have to go, now, hm?
But you're gonna be
fine with Uncle Ray-Ray.
She's gonna be fine with
you, hm, isn't she, bud?
- She's gonna be fine.
- Why'd you do that?
Why?
That bullet had my name on it.
Since when do you care about
other people?
- You're not other people,
asshole.
You're my brother.
And you've been saving my
life since I was a kid.
That's why I did it.
That why I did it, to protect
you.
I think I beat you to it.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Shh, Grant, please.
- So, what happens now?
- I don't know.
But nothing bad is ever
gonna happen to you.
- You sound like Daddy.
- Your dad wanted make
sure you're safe, okay?
But you're with me, always.
- Are we in trouble?
- No, but I have some questions
that I need to answer.
- Like what?
- Like the importance
of family and loyalty.
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪