[MEN YELLING]
[SHOUTING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
I am Sarak, soon to be
the ruler of Rotonga.
If you would live,
tell me where the priest
has hidden the sacred treasure.
No. No!
[GUNSHOT]
[MEN YELLING]
Can't we take a taxi
like normal people?
I mean, this is not
my idea of fun, guys.
Oh, Mom, this is better
than hanging out
at the airport for eight hours.
Yeah, Mrs. Campbell.
That tourist lady
at the airport said
this was the biggest festival
of the year.
Well, maybe so,
but did we have to come
by this horrible cart?
It's kind of rad.
You know, even Disneyland
doesn't have a ride like this.
Well, the next vacation
we certainly won't take it
in the middle of nowhere.
Mom, I told you we were
going to the Temple of Penchat.
Yeah. They're supposed to have
fireworks and a big celebration,
even Pencak Silat.
Pencak Silat? What's that?
It's kind of like karate,
you know?
Just jungle-style.
I don't believe
you guys conned me into this.
Of all the crazy ideas!
Oh! What an ugly... Oh!
...foul-smelling beast!
What do they do
for excitement around here?
[SCREAMING]
[MEN YELLING]
God! Is it always
so hot out here?
Oh, what I wouldn't give to dive
in a nice pool of water.
How much longer?
This ride is killing me!
I'll sure be glad
when we're on that plane
headed back to the good old
US of A tonight.
You guys wore me out.
I guess I can put up with it
for a few more hours.
Besides, it is nice
and peaceful around here.
Look! There!
The Temple of Penchat!
-Oh, at last!
-Yeah!
-Civilization!
-Yeah! Whoo!
Wow!
Tell me where the priest
has hidden the sacred treasure.
No. No!
-Then die!
-No!
Bring the other one to me!
Now,
insect,
I suggest you tell me where
he has put the treasure.
-No!
-No?
-Then die, too!
Would you die
for something
that belongs to the people?
Would you deny
the people their own?
Listen, my son,
if you will tell me
where the priest has
hidden the treasure,
I will spare your life.
Come join us.
We will take care of you.
-Uh...
-Yes, yes.
-The priest has the map.
-Yes, the priest.
-A map?
-Yeah.
A map?
The priest has a map.
Excellent. The priest has a map.
A good, good boy,
and we will take care of you.
Take care of him.
[LAUGHS WICKEDLY]
[SCREAMING]
Find that filthy priest!
I must have that map!
BOY: Look!
They're doing martial arts.
I'm going to browse around,
do some shopping, okay?
Stevie? Stevie, I don't want
you boys going too far.
Okay, Mom.
Come on, let's check it out.
[FOLK MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE]
Mahmoud, who is that?
He is our high priest, Stenda.
Keeper of all
that is sacred to us.
[HUMMING "RULE BRITANNIA"]
Oh, great. Food. I'm starving.
[IN BRITISH ACCENT]
Oh, hello!
Oh, you're not from
around here, are you?
Oh, how very observant of you.
No, I'm not.
You see, what happened was
about 20 years ago,
my ship sank not far from here,
and I've been here ever since.
-I see.
-Yes.
Well, I'm starving.
What is this?
Oh, well, have you tried
any of these native delicacies?
Right. Well, have a go at that.
-What is it?
-Chicken intestines.
Well, um, how about this, then?
A nice chicken head?
I don't think so.
Well, how about
a souvenir to take home?
Eh, is it food?
No, no, no.
I've got some nice pots
out the back.
Now, you come with me
and I'm sure you'll find
something to take home.
That food is all right,
you know?
You just got to get used to it.
You'd like a bite of this.
No. No. No. Look,
lovely things in this store.
Oh, yes. Now, how about this?
This little basket.
How would you like
to take this home?
I don't think so.
What else do you have?
-We have these rugs.
-[GUNSHOTS]
-And then we have some pots...
-What's that?
Don't worry about that, Miss.
it's nothing to worry about.
-Now...
-It sounds like gunfire.
Well, it's the rebels, miss.
They come down
from the mountains
every so often
and attack the village.
What?
Let's get out of here!
[ALL SHOUTING]
Wait a minute!
No, no, no. Just stay here.
You're much safer here,
you know?
But there's guns. I mean,
someone could get hurt.
Miss, these are mountain people.
They can't shoot straight.
[GUNSHOT]
Can't shoot straight, huh?
-I've got to find the boys!
-Miss!
Wait, miss!
Half price, just for today!
[GUNSHOT]
Maybe they're
just getting better.
I've got to find my mom.
Wait. Those guys
are still out there.
Yeah, but my mom!
They might hurt her.
I don't know, Stevie,
she was way down
at the other end of town.
Yeah. I'd say
we're in more trouble.
Oh, Mahmoud! I've lost the boys.
Yes, miss, come this way.
-I got to find them.
-Come! We will find them!
I wish we would have
stayed at the airport,
like Mom wanted to.
This is all my fault.
No, it ain't.
We all wanted to come out here.
Yeah, that's right.
Man! This has been
some vacation.
Well, it was fun
while it lasted.
You guys wait here.
No use in all of us
getting killed.
Hold it. You're not going
anywhere without us.
That's right.
We stick together.
[MEN GRUNTING]
Kill anyone
who stands in our way!
He's here somewhere, Master.
We will search this way.
Good. Remember,
I have promised great riches
to the man who
brings me the map.
Now go.
I wonder who
they're looking for.
Someone with a map.
[SOFT MOANING]
Did you guys hear that?
Please... Please...
You must help me.
Beware of Sarak.
He's an evil man.
Please...
Help me.
What can we do?
Sarak is after
the treasure of my people.
STEVIE: Treasure?
Did he say treasure?
Hey, I think he's dead.
No, he's still alive.
The map.
Here.
Take it.
Is he...
That's the map
to my people's treasure.
You must guard the map
with your life.
Sarak must never find it.
You promise!
Who is Sarak?
I think
he's really dead this time.
Let's get out of here.
What do we do with this map?
Keep it.
Yeah. We promised.
Hya!
The boys!
After the boys!
[MEN YELLING]
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
Mom!
Stevie, I've been
so worried about you.
Where have you boys been?
What is going on?
There's not enough
time to explain, Mom.
Yeah, Mrs. Campbell.
We better get out of here.
Hurry! They're coming!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Fast! Make it fast!
Oh, Mahmoud.
-Thank you for everything.
-Okay, make it fast!
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE CRANKS]
Come on, Mom, hurry!
Come on, Mom!
[ENGINE STARTS]
Throw the eggs!
[GRUNTING]
STEVIE: Come on! Keep throwing!
Flee if you will, foreign dogs!
But you will never escape
the wrath of Sarak!
I will follow you
to the ends of the Earth!
That treasure is mine!
[YELLS]
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
[CHEERING] All right. Yeah.
Come on, Alan! Yeah!
Follow through! Follow through!
Come on, get in there!
[CHEERING]
Hey, the boys are doing
a great job, aren't they?
Yeah. They worked
really hard for this match.
Now we have Stevie and Jamie.
Yeah, Stevie, go!
Look, over there.
[CHEERING] Stevie! Yeah!
Yeah. It is her, Emil.
Yes, no doubt. That's the woman.
It is them, the boys
that were with the woman.
Sarak will be very happy.
-Quiet, you fool!
-[GRUNTING]
You want to give us away?
What should we do, Emil?
Wait. When the time is right,
we will find what they
have done with the map.
MAN: Next up, Jon and Philip.
Where do you think
they keep the map, Emil?
Quiet, fool!
We'll follow the boys,
and they'll lead us to it.
Excuse me, missy.
Yes? May I help you?
What time will this be over?
Well, it's just about over now.
Another 15 to 20 minutes.
I notice
you're wearing this patch.
What does it mean?
This is our dojo patch.
It's the martial arts federation
we belong to.
We noticed
the children are wearing it.
Yes. We belong
to the same karate school.
EMIL: Hmm, very nice.
Are you interested
in the martial arts?
Oh, yes.
Yes, very interested.
Where is the school at?
Well, here's our business card,
and our address and phone number
are on the back.
Thank you very much.
Well, there's our instructor,
right there,
if you'd like to meet him.
Oh, no, no, no.
Not at this time.
-Where is the dressing room?
-Right over there.
Admirers of yours, Jackie?
Be serious, sensei.
-What did they want?
-Just asking questions.
You know, about the dojo,
the patch, and the kids.
The usual questions.
A couple
of strange-looking guys.
Yeah, I'll say.
You sure it wasn't you
they were after?
I don't think so.
But I gave them your card.
[SCOFFING] Thanks.
Hey, it pays to advertise.
Sensei,they need you
up at the judges' table.
All right.
Hi, guys.
ALL: Hi.
Hi, Jackie.
Congratulations.
You guys did a great job.
-ALL: Thanks.
-So, now what are you up to?
My mom is letting me
play for a while.
Yeah, then we can change and go.
Okay, I guess
I'll see you later.
-Bye, Jackie.
-Bye.
Bye.
Hey. Hey!
What are you doing in here?
Where are your bags?
[GRUNTING]
You know, Ken,
martial arts has been
the best thing for Stevie.
He eats, lives,
and breathes karate.
It's good for him.
It gives him direction,
it gives him focus.
Well, all I know is
it's even helped him
with his schoolwork.
And it's all because
of you, sensei.
Great. Then I take it
you're not here for a refund.
[CHUCKLING] Seriously.
These kids worship you.
Your philosophy and discipline.
I just enjoy teaching kids.
Well, as a single parent
raising a child,
I don't know what
I'd do without you.
Uh, there are no classes
tomorrow, right?
Right.
Good.
Why don't you
come over for dinner?
Okay.
-Good.
-Certainly beats me cooking.
-Well, I wonder
where the boys are.
-Uh...
I think they went to change.
Why don't you wait here?
And I'll... I'll go check.
All right, what's going on here?
I think they were robbers.
Yeah, that's it.
We caught them
trying to steal stuff.
[MALAYAN MUSIC PLAYS]
Come here.
Let's go.
[GRUNTING] Get up here.
Get up here. Get up here.
Come here!
Master. Master.
Idiots.
Why do you disturb me now?
Excuse me, master,
we have information
on the foreigners.
Yes, master, we found
the boys and the mother.
Found them?
Yes, your excellency.
Your information was correct.
Well? Did you get the map?
We had problems, O great one.
Yes, your greatness,
we had problems.
Obviously,
you did not get the map.
But what can I expect
from two imbeciles
sired by a pig and a monkey?
Thank you, your grace.
Thank you.
Yes, thank you.
If I may speak,
your magnificent.
Speak.
We can find those foreign dogs.
Here.
Martial arts?
You mean they're at this place?
Yes, your reverence.
All three boys.
All right.
This time make no mistake.
And if they do not have the map,
bring them back to me.
I will make them tell us
where it is.
Fari.
Go with these two imbeciles.
See to my bidding.
Yes, master.
Half left flip.
Go.
Keep going. Go.
Good. Go.
Go.
[SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
-All right, line up for kata.
-[BOYS SHOUT]
[ALL SPEAKING JAPANESE]
[COUNTING IN JAPANESE]
[ALL SHOUT]
-[ALL SHOUT]
-[COUNTING IN JAPANESE]
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
Okay. Grab a partner for Sumo.
[ALL SHOUT]
First two up, Brian and Alan.
[BOTH SHOUT]
Okay, bow.
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
[COUNTING IN JAPANESE] Go!
Let's go! Come on!
[ALL CHEERING]
-Yeah!
All right,
Alan is the winner. Bow.
All right, Jon and Billy.
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[COUNTING IN JAPANESE] Go!
Billy!
Okay, this side winner. Bow.
All right. [SPEAKING JAPANESE]
Line up. Let's go.
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
Okay, we have
a few things to discuss.
Remember, we leave this weekend
for our summer training camp.
ALL: Yeah!
All right, all right.
Now, because
it's rugged up there,
You won't be able
to wear your gis.
They'd just get too dirty.
So, instead...
you'll wear those.
Jackie, go ahead
and pass them down.
Hey, these are ninja uniforms.
That's right, Jon,
they're ninja uniforms.
They're comfortable.
And best of all
because they're black,
you can get them
as dirty as you want.
ALL: Yeah!
Remember, no parents.
[ALL CHEERING]
But, Jackie is coming.
ALL: Yeah!
Excuse me, miss.
Yeah?
What can you tell me
about this training camp?
Oh. Well, here is a flyer.
It has
all the information on it.
-Thank you very much.
-You're welcome.
Everyone has a lot to do
to get ready for this weekend,
so that's all for today.
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
All right, thank you.
See you later.
[SNORING]
Legend of Zelda's so cool.
I know. I got it.
You got a mutant box lunch.
[MOCKING]
Get up, you fools.
They are here!
Hey! It's that guy again!
[LAUGHS WICKEDLY]
Come here, come here!
Mom!
Help!
Sensei!
Get off me!
-Get him!
-Come on!
[BOYS CONTINUE CHEERING]
Ha!
STEVIE: Sensei!
KEN: You guys all right?
-BOYS: Yeah.
-STEVIE: We are all right.
All right, you guys,
this is the second time
this has happened.
I think you owe me
an explanation.
[ALL GROANING]
Come on, come on.
Idiots!
Again you have let
mere children defeat you.
[SIGHING GRIMLY]
What have I done
to deserve this?
To be shackled
with two imbeciles
sired by a carabao and a goat!
But, master, all is not lost.
Here we can find the children.
In the mountains, alone.
This time, dogs,
I, Sarak,
will do what you were
obviously too stupid
to accomplish.
Yes.
We will follow them
to this camp.
There in the mountains,
there will be no one
to interfere.
I will make these
little peasants wish
that they had never
seen the sacred map.
Now, go.
Your sight offends me.
Zonk, my faithful elephant,
I have need of your services.
MRS. CAMPBELL:
Thank you, sis.
Ken, you remember
my sister, Sara Jane?
Yes. How are you?
SARA: Fine. Thanks.
Nice to see you again.
Okay, boys,
what happened yesterday?
What's going on?
MRS. CAMPBELL: Stevie, tell him.
We can't, Mom. We promised.
You know,
promises are good to keep,
but not if it means
someone is going to get hurt.
Okay. It started
on our last vacation, remember?
How could I forget?
That horrid water buffalo ride.
These three conned me
into an excursion
to the far Pacific.
Ken, I told you
about the trouble
they had down there.
I never did figure out
what was going on.
I was just glad
to get out of there.
We could tell you
what happened.
What does this have to do
with the men that are after you?
Remember the promise?
Yes?
We promised a man
that was dying.
What?
Yeah. You see,
when we got separated,
we got thrown into this hut.
JON: Yeah, and we saw
a man that was dying.
And he gave us
something to hold,
and we swore not to tell.
ALAN:
Then a big mean-looking man
and a bunch of other guys
were looking for the man
that was dying.
STEVIE:
Yeah, and we didn't know
what to do, so we ran.
JON: And they chased us
all over the place.
[MEN YELLING]
All right, food.
Hey, guys, let's hide in here.
[MEN YELLING]
How about a little snack?
Jon,
give us a break.
[WHISPERING] There they are.
[YELLS AND LAUGHS]
[MAN YELLS]
Mom!
Stevie, I'm so glad to see you.
I've been so worried
about you boys.
Where have you been?
Then that's when
we saw you, Mom.
That's incredible.
Stevie, why didn't you tell me?
We couldn't, Mom. We promised.
KEN: But where is the map?
And this man said
that this would show you
where the national treasure was?
-Yeah.
Okay.
Why don't you boys
go down to the docks and play?
Ken, what are we going to do?
Look, I've got a friend
in the State Department.
Let me give him a call
and see what ideas
he can come up with.
Ken, these kids of yours
have put the State Department
in a very delicate
and awkward situation.
How's that?
Well, with the rest of the world
watching every move we make,
it's very difficult for us
to stick our nose
into someone else's business.
Here is the file
you requested, Mr. Mabry.
Thanks, Natalie.
What's going on here, Jack?
Well, since you called
I did some checking on Rotonga.
And?
The country is
in a very unsettled state.
Their high priest
was killed recently.
He was the keeper
of their national treasure.
The whereabouts of this treasure
are detailed on a map.
You mean, uh,
this map?
-JACK: How did you...
-KEN: The kids had it.
Now, will you take it
and do something about this?
No way. I've been ordered
not to get involved.
Not involved? What do you mean?
My kids are being attacked
and threatened
because of this map.
I know. But the man
responsible for this,
Consul General Sarak,
and his men are covered
by diplomatic immunity.
Diplomatic immunity?
What does that mean?
You can't arrest
or prosecute him in anyway?
There are over 400 people
in this country
with diplomatic status,
giving them complete immunity
from our laws.
So, what's the answer, Jack?
I can't have these guys
coming after the kids again.
Someone is going to get hurt.
I'll work as fast as I can.
Meanwhile, can't you take
the kids and hide out
for a few days?
We do have a Grand Canyon
summer camp coming up.
Great. By the time you get back
I'll have all the answers.
I hope so.
Well, good luck.
[BOYS SINGING]
♪ 99 bottles of beer
on the wall
♪ You take one down
and pass it around
♪ 98 bottles of beer
on the wall
♪ You take one down
and pass it around
♪ 97 bottles of beer
on the wall
♪ You take one down
and pass it around
♪ 96 bottles of beer
on the wall
♪ You take one down
and pass it around
♪ 95 bottles of beer...
♪ 55 bottles of beer
on the wall
♪ You take one down
and pass it around...
♪ 30 bottles of beer
on the wall
♪ 30 bottles of beer...
KEN: Hey, we're here!
[ALL CHEERING]
KEN:
Okay, everybody, grab your gear.
Cookie, nice to see you.
Oh, hi, Ken.
How was your trip up?
Good. Good.
Cookie, this is Jackie.
She's going to be assisting me
on this trip.
Wow. Hi, Jackie.
Nice to meet you.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Oh, I'm-I'm Cookie,
the camp cook
and the chief bottle washer
around here.
Why, if you follow me
I'll show you where
you can stow your gear.
-Just follow me.
-Sensei,can we go for a hike?
Sure. Why not?
Cookie, some of the boys
would like to go for a hike.
-STEVIE: Yeah.
-Oh, great.
Yeah, the Grand Canyon
is just right over there.
Why, I know those
trails over there like
the back of my hand.
Okay, why don't you guys
go up and change,
and I'll talk to Cookie
about the trails.
Listen, Cookie,
we had some problems back home,
so take a little extra care
in watching out for the kids.
Oh, you don't have to worry
about the wild animals
around here.
Why, there ain't any.
It's not the four-legged kind
I'm worried about.
You know, if you see
anyone suspicious,
get the kids back
as soon as possible.
Oh, you mean,
somebody is trying to
hurt them kids?
Yeah, someone is definitely out
after some of the boys.
Although,
I don't think they are
going to be able to
find them out here.
Oh, you don't have to worry
about a thing.
Why, if I see
anything suspicious
I'll bring them
back here just pronto.
Good. Thanks.
Pujo, what this?
Pine cone.
Now, quiet.
Pujo, what this pine cone?
The animals, they eat them.
Hmm.
Japanese spies
used to wear them, you say?
Wow, you guys kind of
look like The Cisco Kid
or maybe The Green Hornet.
Little ninjas, you say?
Yeah, little ninjas, huh?
Yeah. Why, I used to do
all that stuff, you know.
Just that, now I spend
all my time down in the canyon,
you know, walking and helping...
[KEN SPEAKING JAPANESE]
Good. Hold it right there.
[KIDS SINGING]
♪ Teddy bear, teddy bear,
turn around
♪ Teddy bear,
teddy bear...
♪ ...turn around
♪ Teddy bear, turn around
Amazing.
♪ Teddy bear, teddy bear,
turn around
KEN: This way.
This way. Next.
♪ Teddy bear, teddy bear,
touch the ground...
Watch. This way. That's it.
♪ Teddy bear, teddy bear,
touch the ground...
He is the one you have to
concern yourself with.
Good. Go back again.
Do it again.
Good. Switch sides.
Let's change legs. Good...
Yes, master. He is mine!
[WHISPERING] Go.
Go. Go.
♪ Teddy bear, teddy bear...
Good. Again. And go.
Good. Switch legs.
Good.
[MEN YELLING]
Stop!
Stop it! Stop!
Stop or you will lose this boy.
-Hold it.
-Fool.
You have only made this
more difficult for yourself.
You must be Sarak.
Ah, you've heard of me.
Then you know why I am here.
Bring me the three boys.
They will not be hurt.
They have what is mine.
Sorry.
The ones you're looking for
didn't make this trip.
Liar!
Go ahead. Look for yourself!
We will look,
and if we find them,
you will not be
the only one to pay.
Search the grounds.
They must be here somewhere.
We got to help them.
-Yeah, come on...
-Oh, no. Wait a minute.
You can't do it that way.
Wait. Well, look at that feller
down there with that big sword.
You'll get hurt.
They're nowhere to be found.
If they are not here,
then they must be out there.
No matter.
They will be back.
We will wait.
Take them inside. Lock them up!
[GRUNTING]
Cookie, what are we going to do?
We have to get in
and help sensei.
I don't know.
Oh, wait a minute.
You know what?
There's a doggie door
around back.
Fari, you will stand watch.
I made this doggie door.
I bet you guys can slip
right through there.
I know.
We're ninjas.
That way we can
sneak up on them.
Yeah, ninjas!
All right.
Let's go.
-Let go of me!
-No!
Quiet!
Master, we have them
all tied up.
You.
Prepare some beverages
for our pleasure.
Hey, he's coming back.
I can't look.
[IMITATES COYOTE]
Okay, the coast is clear.
Come on, Jon.
I can't. I'm stuck.
He's stuck.
Yeah. Get me out of here.
Okay, don't move.
Funny.
Ow!
[STEVIE SHUSHES]
Guys, get me out of here!
[WHISPERING] Be quiet.
Alan,
Takeshi,
go outside and push.
-I'll stay here.
-ALAN: Okay.
Hurry up!
I think I see someone coming.
Follow me.
Zonk, go.
See what the problem is.
[GRUNTS]
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
-[MAN YELLS]
-[BOYS GRUNT]
They must've got sensei
and the other kids locked up.
Yeah, let's go help them.
Yeah, let's go.
[SNIFFING]
SARAK: Idiots!
What are you doing?
Hey!
[SCREAMING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
[GROWLING]
-Ha ha!
Hey, let me down,
you big, ugly gorilla.
It's not fair.
Zonk,
after them!
Wait until I get down from here!
Oh, my God.
Sensei, what did they
do to you?
Run!
-[HIGH-PITCHED] Where are they?
-[HIGH-PITCHED] I don't know.
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREAMING]
Get me loose.
Look!
Oh, no.
Yeah.
I'm going to get you.
Ooh, that's got to hurt.
[GROANS]
[YELLING]
Alan, you see anyone?
No.
Where is Stevie?
I don't know.
We got split up.
-[GRUNTS]
-What's that?
Hey, it's Steve!
STEVIE: Help, get me up.
[ALL GRUNTING]
ALAN: What happened?
I slipped.
Those guys are going to kill us!
Yeah. Let's go get those guys.
Wait a minute.
Senseitold us
not to use martial arts
to hurt anyone.
I don't think
senseiwill mind this time.
Okay, let's go kick some butt.
Yeah, these guys are toast!
[PANTING]
[SCREAMING]
[MAN GROANING]
-Where are they?
-Huh?
[GRUNTING] Come on!
[MAN GRUNTING]
[ALAN YELLS]
Ow! Ow! Ow!
[SCREAMING]
Here he comes!
Yeah!
[IMITATING MONKEY HOOTS]
[WHISTLING]
[YELLING]
Here, Jackie,
take care of this.
All right.
Enough of this foolishness.
Prepare to die!
Where are my boys?
Where are the boys?
Sensei,look. They're back.
KEN: Stevie, Jon, Alan.
You guys are all right.
Yeah, we were worried about you.
What happened to those goons
that were after you?
We left them out there.
Kind of, laying around.
You mean, you took care of
all those bad guys by yourself?
-ALAN: Yeah.
-Martial arts.
And a few ninja tricks.
[CHEERING]
Hey, where is Cookie?
COOKIE: Right here.
Look what I found
hanging on a nail.
You know what,
as soon as I'd seen I had
everything under control,
I went down
and called the sheriff.
He'll be here anytime.
[ALL CHEERING]
Boy, you guys are amazing.
Little ninjas.
You took care of
all those guys by yourselves.
[ALL CHEERING]
NATALIE: He's waiting for you.
Here they are.
Jack, this is Chris
and the boys.
Chris, boys.
So this is our tiny
hit squad, huh?
They finished off
the goons from Rotonga?
Well, I've got
some good news for you, boys.
We contacted officials
in Rotonga
and sent back the map.
BOYS: Yeah!
Mr. Mabry has explained
how grateful the people
are from Rotonga.
You saved
their national treasure
from Sarak and his men.
Yes, you did a very brave
and good thing.
But next time,
if you have any problems,
let us know.
Mr. Mabry, what happened
to those guys?
You mean Sarak
and his gang, huh?
-JON: Yeah.
-They all got deported.
Don't worry, they're going to
get what's coming to them.
BOYS: Yeah!
By the way, I forgot to mention,
the officials in Rotonga
want you all back
in their country.
They want to throw
a big celebration in your honor.
BOYS: Yeah!
-Mom?
-Oh, no, you don't.
No.
No more water buffalo rides.
No more riots.
Forget it.
No.
No!
[DRUM MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHANTING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Your excellency,
ladies and gentlemen of Rotonga,
it gives me great pleasure
to introduce to you
our special guests from America,
Jon, Alan, and Stevie.
My country and my people
owe you a great deal,
and we will always
be indebted to you.
And to show you our gratitude,
I would like to give you
one of our country's
prized treasures.
Did you hear that, Mom?
A treasure.
[PEOPLE CHEERING]
Oh, no.
Not that. No.
[MOOING]
MRS. CAMPBELL: No.
But, Mom...
Come on, Mrs. Campbell.
ALAN: Yeah, can we keep it?
-No.
-We'll take him.
-Come on.
No.
-BOYS: Please?
-No.
[PEOPLE APPLAUDING]