♪ They told you everything
was waiting for you ♪
was set in stone ♪
♪ It's an open book,
a road in reverse ♪
♪ A brand new hook,
forget that curse ♪
♪ Rewrite, Ignite, Restart! ♪
♪ 'Cause it's your life ♪
♪ Go forward or rewind! ♪
♪ 'Cause you're a Royal
you're a Rebel ♪
♪ You're more than one
together, ♪
♪ However you go ever in... ♪
♪ Ever After High! ♪
Male narrator:
This was no ordinary day
for Raven Queen.
Female narrator:
Raven was finally mastering
her magic.
Only she wasn't using
her powers in a way
that would please
her evil mother.
Brooke page:
Well, you know what they say,
You can't judge a book
by its mother.
- Raven, I broke a nail
and gave myself a splinter!
- No problem, Cedar.
Daring Charming:
Um, I toasted marshmallows
with dragon fire
And the soot stained my teeth!
- I dropped my mirrorpad
and I can't film my mirrorcast
this afternoon!
Group of friends:
Raven, help me!
I'm next! I'm next!
Okay you guys,
as much as I would love to,
I can't do spells all day-
Apple!
Apple: Hi Raven!
I'm so late!
You-know-who is gonna
have an epic meltdown!
- Go, go, go, go!
I've got this.
- I owe you one, Apple.
- That's what friends
forever after are for.
Tiny:
The billygoats are in a jam...
and it's my jam!
I'd be happy to help.
Billygoats:
We want Raven - not you!
Lizze Hearts:
Good luck today!
Darling Charming:
And keep away
from the glass!
Raven Queen:
Thanks, guys.
Male narrator:
Visiting day:
The day Raven gets to see her
mother in her mirror prison
and Raven was nervous.
Brooke Page:
I'd be nervous too
if my mom were the evil queen.
Milton Grimm:
Miss Queen.
Sign here.
Now remember,
keep away from--
The glass.
I know, I know.
(Buzzer buzzes,
bookshelf rumbles)
(Big inhale and exhale)
(Doors open,
flames whoosh, roars)
Nevermore!
Who's a good dragon?
(Worried sound)
Don't worry,
I can handle mom.
♪♪♪
(Whimpers)
- Raven!
- Hi, mom.
- I've been waiting forever
after! How do I look?
- You look great, mom.
- How's school?
School's great, actually.
Have you been a bad girl?
Well... I...
I know you've been using
your powers for good,
helping others.
Where did I go wrong?!
- Things have changed, mom.
It's not like back when
you went to school here.
We can choose our own destiny!
- I know one thing
hasn't changed...
it's better to be feared
than forgotten.
It's true.
Everybody fears you.
Thank you!
Get me out of here,
and I'll show you the way.
We'll rule side-by-side.
We'll take over
Ever After High, together.
It'll be a great bonding
experience.
Like shopping only,
world domination.
- Take over the school?
Why would I want
to hurt my friends?
Don't you get it?
I never want to be like you!
I want to choose
my own happily ever after!
(Magic whooshes,
objects clatter)
Evil Queen:
Let out that aggression.
Go on!
Hit the glass, Raven.
(Record scratches sound)
Oh! Nevermore!
(Object clatter, whimpers)
Nice try, mom.
You want me to break
the mirror. (Chuckles)
You're not getting out
that easily.
- Can't blame an evil queen
for trying.
Milton Grimm:
Ahem. Visiting hours are over!
Oh, I'll find a way
to break this mirror.
And then ever after will be
facing a lot worse
than seven years of bad luck...
Count on it.
(Bell rings)
(Nevermore screeches)
Yeah, mom can be pretty
intense.
Poppy O'Hair:
Hey, Raven.
- Hey, guys.
- How was visiting day?
- Aw.
What happened to you, girl?
- Don't ask.
- Heh. Someone sure
needs a bath!
Raven Queen:
My mom really spooked
Nevermore.
She wound up with a bit
of a messy makeover.
(They giggle)
- We can groom Nevermore
for you!
- Sounds like a job
for Holly and Poppy.
- The O'Hair twins!
Female narrator:
There she is...
Queen of the land,
the fairest of them all,
the mother of Apple White...
Male narrator:
She's also a very powerful
royal executive.
She employs over 700 dwarves!
The one and only,
The Snow White.
(Heavenly choir sings,
birds chirp)
How is my enchanted tape
collection selling?
(Cash register dings)
Hexcellent.
My daughter will live
comfortably ever after.
By the way,
how is Apple doing in school?
(Computer beeps)
Straight A's! Perfect.
What about socially?
How are her ratings?
(Computer beeps)
Apple's popularity is down?!
And who is...
Raven is up?
This is fairy,
fairy bad news!
Set up a video call
to my daughter.
(Mirror dings)
Once upon a hi, mom!
Apple, I am fairy concerned
about you.
There's no easy way
to say this, Apple-pie,
but your popularity
is down 13%!
- It-it's Raven!
Everyone loves her now
that she's using her powers
for-for good.
Mom, it's terrible!
- You need to be proactive,
my little dove.
Remind the world
of our fairytale.
Perhaps there's some way
you could nudge Raven
toward evil?
I-I wouldn't do that.
Remember, she's still
her mother's daughter.
And so are you.
So ask yourself,
how badly do you want
our happily ever after?
Mom, you know how much
I heart our family tradition!
Sometimes destiny
needs a push, my sweet.
I'll see what I can do from
here to give you a boost.
I'll think about it, mom.
(Hang up ding)
Gather all business dwarves!
Put a task force together.
It's time to make
this Apple shine.
(Sighs)
(Door opens)
Hi Raven.
- Hi Apple.
- So... how was seeing your mom?
Are you feeling any evil-er?
- What? No!
Uh, maybe.
I don't know.
My mom makes me want
to scream sometimes.
Apple:
That's good!
That's good.
Maybe scream, and then,
um, explode something
with dark magic!
- Sounds like I'm not
the only princess
who got an earful
from her mom today.
So how's she doing?
- She's worried that
I'm not following in her
fairytale footsteps.
- Hm. That's the one thing your
mom and my mom can agree on.
(Owl hoots)
(Sleepy moans)
(Computer beeps, buzzes)
(Sighs)
(Beeps off)
Mirror, mirror
on the wall,
why is life so unfairest
after all?
Evil Queen:
I spy doubt.
And doubt makes room for the
worm to get into the apple.
(Magic whooshes)
Follow me...
- What?
(Magic whooshes)
♪♪♪
Evil Queen:
You poor thing...
Tell me your troubles.
- I can't talk to you.
- Oh Apple, we have so much
more in common than you know.
What-what do you want?
The same thing you want!
I could help you, you know.
I can restore things
to the good old ways,
steer Raven on her course
of evil
so you get your happily
ever after.
But I can't do it
from inside the mirror.
- Even if I trusted you,
I can't let you out of the
mirror - that would be wrong.
Evil Queen:
Oh, I'm sorry, I thought maybe
you were like your mother.
When her time came,
your mother embraced
her fairytale destiny.
She did whatever it took.
I am not afraid!
I will do whatever it takes
and I am like my mother!
And my destiny is mine!
(Mirror shatters)
♪♪♪
(Evil Queen cackles,
lightning strikes)
Brooke page:
The Evil Queen is free!
Female narrator:
Yes, after years of banishment,
the Evil Queen escaped...
Male narrator:
...and at Apple White's hand
no less!
Evil Queen:
Years in a mirror prison
without a single reflective
surface
to gaze at myself upon...
now that's torture.
Apple White:
I'm sorry. I need to go.
I-I- you're good, right?
Bad?
I-I can't help you.
Evil Queen:
Too late.
You want your friends
or your mother to know
you released the Evil Queen?!
Apple White:
You can't just walk into
school and talk to Raven!
What happens when somebody
recognizes you?
I'll get in trouble and--
- Good point.
I'll need to re-invent my look
to blend in with today's teens.
Let's make some magic.
From old to young,
a journey back
to fit in
would be prudent
erase what time's cruel
hands have done
make me
a high school student!
(Magic whooshes)
♪♪♪
I'll need a name.
How about Mira?
Mira Shards.
You're a teenager.
- Ready my new best friend
forever after?
Time to go back
to high school.
Let's do this!
(Lightning strikes)
- Wow, Poppy, this paint
is hard to get off.
- Tell me about it, Holly.
And we're almost out
of scale polish.
(Water splashes)
Ahhh?!
(Roars)
(Smash, objects clatter)
- My hair!
- Bad dragon! Sit!
(Flames whoosh)
- Poppy, we're gonna need
some kind of armor
if we're going to stay
in the dragon grooming biz.
- Uh huh!
(Low hum of student chatter)
Apple White:
Everyone, I want you
to meet the new girl -
my old friend, Mira!
- What's down!
- Up. What's up?
- Agh. What's up,
new friends?
- I'm Darling,
Darling Charming.
How do you guys
know each other?
- Neighbors.
- Camp.
Yeah, we went
to neighboring camps.
- Hi. I'm Cerise Hood.
what school did you--
- I was home-schooled.
- Oh, hello.
Welcome to Ever After High!
I'm Ashlynn,
that's Lizzie and Raven.
Love your outfit!
- You look wicked.
You're Raven Queen?!
You're like a spellebrity!
Daughter of the greatest
villain
in all of fairytale history?!
- Who, my mom?
Yeah, she's a queen...
a drama queen.
(Apple groans)
- Well, what do you think?
- All cleaned up.
- Nevermore!
Oh. She looks very--
- "Bow-dacious!"
(Chuckles)
- Wow, Raven,
your dragon is so cute!
(Gasps)
(Screeches)
(Flames whoosh)
Ahhhh!
(Dragon roars,
Students scream)
Raven Queen,
what is your animal doing
in the castleteria!
I'm sorry,
Headmaster Grimm.
It won't happen again!
Holly:
Nevermore! Get back here!
(Chuckles)
Hey Raven, are you okay?
- Yeah, I don't know what's
gotten into Nevermore.
She doesn't normally
spook like that!
That was unfairest of Grimm
to bust you like that.
Why didn't you blame
Holly and Poppy?
They brought a dragon
into the castleteria!
Uh, that's not
what friends do.
(Bell rings)
Well, I better get to science
and sorcery class.
- Actually, I'm in that class.
Maybe you could show me
the ropes?
- Sure! Let's go.
Mr. Badwolf:
Here are your general villainry
exam results.
Room for improvement,
miss Queen. (Snarls)
- (Sighs)
- Cast a spell on the teacher
and get straight A's.
That's what I did in school.
- Wait, I thought you
were home-schooled.
- Talking in class, huh?
Encouraging cheating?
Raven,
stick with this new girl
you could learn
a thing or two.
Coach Gingerbreadman:
Candy cane pole vault!
This old Gingerbreadman
is about to show you
how to take the cake!
(Magic whooshes)
Whoa!
(Laughing, buzzer buzzes)
- Raven Queen!
Was that you?!
- No sir!
But I kinda wish it was!
(Bell rings)
Mira Shards:
That's what I did in school.
We were saving these seats.
Sorry.
(Both groan)
- That wasn't fairy nice.
Darling and Cerise
are my friends!
- Nice will only get you
so far.
To be really popular you need
a little fear factor.
Right, Apple?
- Um, I suppose there's truth
in that.
- Um. Raven,
don't freak out,
but we were trying this new
scale polish on Nevermore
and well... she took off.
- We set up a grooming station
in the old dragon stables
behind the school.
That's the last place
we saw her.
We thought,
maybe if you call her...
- Maybe she's just hiding
somewhere and would come out!
We're sorry.
- Thanks for getting me.
Let's go.
All: (Calling)
Nevermore!!!
Raven Queen:
Nevermore!
(Echoes)
Where are you?
Apple White:
Wow! The old dragongames arena.
Mira shards:
Dragongames sound wicked!
Have you ever played, Raven?
You have a dragon!
- I know.
But dragongames
was my mom's thing
and I really don't want
to be like her.
- Why did Headmaster Grimm
close the dragon center down?
- You mean, you don't know?
Dragongames can be very
dangerous.
They say Snow White
and the Evil Queen
were the greatest dragongame
captains ever after.
Poppy:
They were wicked competitive
with their destinies and all.
- Did you know legend
is the last dragon
from that original brood?
(Dragon roars)
- That's a dragon cry.
- Nevermore!
Oh, there you are!
Daring Charming:
Something is wrong
with Legend!
(Breathing heavily)
- Body temperature seems
really high!
Daring Charming:
Does that mean
he's really sick?
Mira Shards:
News-flash, Daring.
Your trusty steed isn't a he.
She's a she!
And she's not sick...
- I think it's time...
Apple White: Aww...
(Girls giggle)
- What time?
- Ahem.
- Oh, that time!
(Fainting moan)
Holly:
Dragonpedia says,
in the wild mothers lay their
eggs near active volcanoes
to warm them until they hatch!
Apparently, it takes years.
- Dragon babies
must be so cute!
- Aw, I can't wait that long!
- I could cast a spell
to keep the eggs warm.
- Hot idea.
Incubation incantation
warm with lava imitation!
This spell could use
a power up.
(Magic whooshes)
All: WHOA!
I must have overdone it!
(Flames roar,
fire extinguisher whooshes)
Phew...
(Fire whooshes, startled gasps,
extinguisher whooshes)
(Eggs crack)
- Raven, look.
Those lighter eggs
are hatching.
- I want the cutest one!
- This is magical!
- Oh my fairy godmother!
This is exciting!
Apple White:
So cute!
Poppy O'Hair:
Oh, this one's mine!
(Licks)
Whoa!
(Giggling)
(Eggs crack,
Evil magic flares)
(Screeching)
Holly O'Hair:
This is bad.
It got too hot!
(Roars)
That can make them turn--
- Evil!
Raven, are you trying
to make evil dragons?!
- What have I done?!
Blondie Lockes:
This is Blondie Lockes
reporting live
from the dragon stables
at Ever After High
where dragons once again
roam the hallowed halls.
- (Gasp) Ow!
- It would seem the students
of Ever After
are eager to adopt
these pesky pets.
(Blows)
Though the trend seems to be
that a dragon chooses you.
- Ooh!
Cotton candy!
Ooh yum-di-dum!
(Little dragon roar,
startled gasp)
(Little squeaks)
(Blows smoke)
(Little squeaks,
flames whoosh)
All:
Agh! Whoa!
♪♪♪
Raven,
you have to try this.
Nevermore is a natural!
Woohoo!
- Who will be the next
champions of dragonsport?
(Chuckles)
Only time will tell.
Why you wicked old thing!
Welcome back.
Summon the architects!
I've just had the fairest
idea of all.
This should get Apple
back on top,
and freshen my pure-as-snow
image too!
(Low hum of chatter)
What is with
the sudden assembly?
- Hm-hm. It's top secret.
No one knows.
- I heard there's
a special guest!
- Ooh, this is hexciting!
- It is my honor
to welcome back
our most successful graduate,
our beloved Queen,
Snow White!
(Loud cheering,
birds sing)
- What is she up to?
- A little bird told me
that dragons have returned
to my beloved alma mater.
So it's time we restored
the good old ways.
Today, the dragongames are
reinstated at Ever After High!
(Cheering, applause)
The dragongames are tough,
yet elegant.
And I want my ever after riders
dressed accordingly.
I've hired the creative team
of Lizzie Hearts
and Ashylnn Ella
to design all new dragon wear.
(Cheering, applause)
♪♪♪
(Cameras flash)
Lizzie Hearts:
These looks are lightweight,
flexible and fashion forward.
Ashlynn Ella:
Not to mention fireproof,
ice-proof
and explosion-resistant!
(Flames whoosh)
Crowd: Oohhhs...
(Dragon blows)
Crowd: Ahhh...
(Cheering)
- Adorable.
Now I can't very well bring
back dragonriding
in an old dilapidated arena!
If you'll all follow me
outside...
Allow me to present the new
Ever After High dragon center!
(Applause)
(Birds sing)
Hold your applause, please.
I must admit
this was not my idea.
My daughter, Apple, thought
bringing back the dragongames
would unite everyone
with school spirit!
(Applause)
Daring Charming:
Way to go, Apple!
Apple White:
Wow! Mom... (Chuckles)
Why didn't you tell me
about all this?
Why did you say it was
my idea when it wasn't?
- Oh, you're welcome,
my little Apple dumpling.
- But mom, it's a lie.
- We discussed this!
Sometimes you've got to pull
out all the stops
and use your resources
to get your fairytale back
on track.
- Whoa. Mira was right.
We are different.
- Who?
Mira Shards: (Loudly) Me.
(Crowd gasps)
And you can't always
just buy popularity, Snow.
- Miss Shards!
Mind your manners!
- "Mira Shards."
Oh. (Chuckles)
Very clever.
Rumor has it you're an
excellent dragon rider.
For a new kid on the block.
- The rumor's true.
Snow White:
Only you're not a student.
You might've been once,
back when we were in school.
I'd know that arched brow
anywhere.
(Gulp)
I just wanted to be closer
to my daughter!
You can understand that.
- Daughter?
- And to be young again,
maybe?
- You'd have done it too,
if you could.
So I suppose now you're
going to send me back
to that awful mirror prison?
Raven: Mom?!
(Crowd gasps)
- Sorry, birdy.
Guilty as charged.
(Shocked gasps,
Ribbit)
- Yay!
The Evil Queen's here!
Said no one ever!