Captioning made possible by
lions gate entertainment
Man: I can't remember
if I had my first drink
to celebrate
my good fortune
or to grieve my losses.
I figure if I sit here
long enough, I'll remember.
How can a guy who has nothing
lose everything?
Well, I found out.
My name's Fritz brown,
and this is my story.
It all started about
a month and a half ago.
I had been working
as a repo man for bud Myers,
biggest used-car dealer
in southern California.
The whole day
just started out all wrong.
I mean, wrong
as in bad, you know?
[Laughs] Oh, shit.
Whoo!
Man: Hey, motherfucker!
Ho ho ho.
No, man, no.
Anybody moves my car--
You want
a dependable deal?
You get on down
to bud Myers.
Say hello, barko.
Come on, barko,
bark for daddy.
Fritz: I met bud Myers
back when I was still a cop.
And when I drank my way
off the force,
bud was right there
with the repo gig.
It saved my ass.
Hey, Fritz,
how's that look?
Oh, it looked great.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
What a fucking
work of art!
We ought to hire
that fucker to redo
all our waiting rooms.
[Laughs]
You like it,
huh?
"Dragon wagon."
You want
a drink, Fritz?
Yeah, give me
a regular coke.
Oh, that's right,
I forgot.
You're not
drinking this week.
Bud, you are
something else.
After all the money
that dog's made for you,
and you're
still feeding him
that dried shit?
You are one cheap fuck.
He likes it.
It's good for his teeth.
What teeth?
He's got no teeth.
Then I must
be a cheap fuck.
You said it, not me.
[Laughs]
Hey, some son of a bitch
burned solly k's down
to the ground last night.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I heard
about that.
Too bad.
One of your
hangouts, right?
Sure, it's a great place
to take...Your wife.
What are you
talking about?
I thought she
divorced your ass.
What do I owe ya?
Fritz: I never did
more than one repo a day.
Bud paid me so well,
I didn't have to.
So to keep
from going insane,
I opened the brown's
detective agency.
I had a little office
out in rancho park
where I spent my days
waiting for
a knock on the door
and, unfortunately,
on this particular day, came.
I worked 6 years
as a cop in Hollywood,
where you get
all the crazies.
And let me tell you,
nothing that I'd seen or did
could have prepared me
for what
was about to happen.
I'd thought
a little p.I. Work
would keep my mind
off drinking.
Well, that was
my first mistake.
[Knock on door]
Just a minute.
Hey, hey,
just a minute.
Can I help you?
Probably, if
you're p.I. Fritz brown.
I am.
Uh, so what
happened to you?
You lose a golf ball
or something?
A gol--[Laughs]
No, there's never
been a golf ball
that I couldn't find.
Ha ha. Can I come in?
Ha ha ha ha.
I'm Freddie baker.
You got the same
initials as me.
You can call me
fat dog, though.
Don't worry.
That's not an insult.
Everyone calls me that.
I like it.
All right,
uh, fat dog,
my fee is 500 bucks
a day, plus any
and all expenses,
and I get paid
up front in full.
Can you handle it?
I may not look
like no millionaire,
but I'm holding heavy,
trust me.
I'll whip
some bread out on you
as soon as I tell you
what it is I want.
All right. Shoot.
Um...
All right,
I got this, uh, sister,
my--my kid sister Jane.
And, um...
She's the only
family I got.
And, uh,
for a long time now,
she's been living
with this rich old
Jewish guy, right?
And he don't want her
to have nothing to do
with me.
Yeah.
Right?
And he pays
for her piano lessons.
And now Janie,
my own kid sister,
shines me on like
I'm a piece of shit.
That sucks.
Your sister,
is she over 18?
Well, she's 17,
but I wasn't looking
for no morals rap.
It's just, you know,
this guy's been
fucking around somehow,
and I want to get
to the bottom of it.
So you tail the Jew
around town,
see what he's into--
oh, and I need--
I need pictures.
You got a camera, right?
If necessary,
I have an undercover
photographer that
I work with, yeah.
Undercover. That's good.
Do you mind?
So are you going
to help the fat dog or what?
Well, I'll tell you,
if your story,
uh, checks out...
I'll give it a week.
But first,
I got to find out
a little bit
more information
on your sister.
Her name is, uh,
Jane baker.
17?
Right.
Got any pictures
of her?
Yeah.
That's her.
You can't keep that.
I need that.
Don't worry.
You'll get it back.
I see the little, uh,
resemblance there.
So, um,
why don't you tell me
a little bit more
about this--
this bad guy
of yours, ok?
His name
is sol kupferman,
and, uh...
He lives--he lives
just north of sunset
near the Beverly Hills
hotel.
And it's, uh,
the address
is 8914 elevado.
E-l-e-v--
I can spell.
Just, uh, describe
the guy, ok?
I don't know.
He's, uh...
65, skinny,
salt-and-pepper hair,
big nose.
Typical heeb.
You get the picture.
I heard a lot of stuff
about solly k.
All bad stuff,
but all rumors.
Solly k?
As in solly k's that
burned down last night?
One and the same asshole.
Any idea on the fire?
He has a lot of enemies.
I told you, the guy's
into a lot of evil shit.
That Jew bastard
made her hate me!
All right, all right.
You, uh,
you simmer down,
fat dog, and, uh...
I'll tell you
what you do.
You hang loose and
come back and see me
when you get a little
cash in your pocket,
and I'll see what
I can do about this--
you--you
want some cash?
You want
a down payment?
Here, I'll give it
to you right now.
Fritz: A lifetime in L.A.
had taught me
never to take anything
at face value
except for money.
Fat dog's a good
judge of character.
You're ok.
Here you go.
You're a caddy?
Yeah.
[Laughs]
Well,
I'll tell you what.
What's that?
I'm giving up
this job of mine
and becoming a caddy.
[Both laugh]
Hey, hey, hey,
hold on a minute.
Uh, you got
a phone number?
You know,
I move around a lot.
You can reach me
at the rustic inn.
That's a beer bar down
on Santa Monica and sawtelle.
I'll get
the message there.
Fine.
Fritz:
I ignored my first warning.
This case stunk
right from the start.
My confrontation with
brother leotis' bat this morning
left a bad taste
in my mouth.
Man, was I tired
of that shit.
Solly k and his love nest
sounded like a nice
little diversion,
and it looked like I was gonna
make some cash on the deal.
The house
was just off coldwater.
It was
a cute little bungalow,
and the his and hers
rolls royces
were fire engine red.
At least I wouldn't have
any problem following 'em
around town.
At exactly high noon,
sleepy but hot-looking
Jane baker came out
of the house.
My lucky day.
Solly k would have
to wait his turn.
I went with the girl.
Now at this point,
nothing really seemed
out of the ordinary,
except for maybe the fact
that this 17-year-old girl
was driving around
in this amazing car,
and she could barely see
over the steering wheel,
but considering
where we were,
that's not such a big deal
and not so uncommon.
[Piano playing]
I don't like people
watching me play.
Oh, sorry, I...
I wasn't watching you play.
I--i was just--well,
yeah, I was watching you,
but I, uh, I was really
looking for my teacher.
Why don't I believe you?
Well, that's, uh,
probably just your upbringing,
you know,
never talk to strangers.
That certainly
wasn't my upbringing.
So you play the piano?
Uh, yeah...
Sit. Let me hear you.
Oh, no, no.
No, I don't--
I don't play the piano.
Well, not--
no, no, not well.
I-i-I'm just
starting my lessons today.
How did you become
interested in music?
Uh, that's a long story.
You don't wanna--
you don't wanna hear that.
I--i should
probably just go.
Look who's afraid to
talk to strangers now.
Oh...ok,
if you want to hear.
Sure, I'll tell you.
[Clears throat]
Um, I was 21, uh,
my mama just died,
and I was working, uh...
Uh, part-time
as a gardener,
living off her, uh,
insurance money, um...
Anyway, I, uh,
had this job in Pasadena
trimming
a little shrubbery there,
and I heard this music
coming from the house.
Uh, thunderous
powerful stuff.
It was pretty amazing.
It was, uh,
Beethoven's eroica.
Yeah, I mean, uh,
knocked me flat on my ass,
and, uh, and, uh,
well, I've never, uh,
I've never been able
to get enough of it since.
So what happened?
Why'd it
take you this long
to take a lesson?
Uh, well, um,
I became a cop.
So you're a cop?
[Laughs]
Well, I wasa cop,
and I was a cop before,
but, you know,
that's, um, that's another
long, nonsensical story.
You don't want--
and I have
to practice, so...
You'll have
to save your story
for another time.
Yeah, I'll
look forward to it.
Fritz: I was never
any good at this stuff.
You see, it's not supposed
to go this way.
When you're
following someone,
well, they're
not supposed to catch you.
That night, I went back
to kupferman's mansion.
I had decided
to get a closer look
at mister solly k
and hopefully sneak a peek
at the young and lovely
Jane baker while I was at it.
[Muffled voices]
Ha ha ha ha.
Hey, listen...
Just come on,
baby. Come on.
We'll watch
a little TV
tonight, huh?
[Dog growls]
[Woof woof woof]
Fritz: A private eye needs
to be prepared for anything.
So I stopped off
on my way home
and bought a can of mace.
The dog didn't deter me.
The next morning,
I followed solly k
to a liquor store
down on crenshaw.
Not where you'd expect
the Beverly Hills crowd
to shop for their booze,
but I guess one bottle
of dom perignon tastes
as good as the next.
It was the rainy season,
not the ideal weather
to be driving around
in a convertible
with the top down,
but it was kinda fun
sometimes.
Fat dog wanted pictures,
so I figured
I'd take a couple of shots
just so he thought he's
getting his money's worth.
The 2 bags of booze
in his trunk,
I followed solly k
out of L.A.
And out of the rain.
I couldn't imagine
why this old guy
was driving all the way
out here.
But what did it matter?
It wasn't like I had
anything in particular
to do that day.
Finally, after 2 hours,
he stopped at
a little gas mart.
What happened next
made fat dog's story
start to make
a little more sense.
Haywood cathcart,
head of internal affairs.
The man who made an example
of me and my drinking
was accepting
2 grocery bags.
It probably had nothing
at all to do with booze.
Although I'm sure Haywood liked
the sauce as much as I did,
but he was just a little bit
more careful about it
than me, that's all.
I became his poster boy for
the new clean and sober l.A.P.D.
He pointed out my demise
as progress. I hated the guy,
and I had been waiting
all this time
for the chance
to pay him back.
Now fate had brought US
back together again
in the form of a caddy
named fat dog baker.
I had always believed
I didn't need anybody's
help staying sober.
I'd gone to a couple
of a.A. Meetings,
but it just wasn't my thing.
Sitting around with a bunch
of weak, pathetic alcoholics
didn't make
any real sense to me.
I went for my cousin
Walter's sake.
He was family, and I thought
that's what he needed.
[Whispering]
Get me outta here.
You're late, Fritz.
[Whispering] I know.
I'm on a case.
No way.
Yeah.
Who--who would hire you?
It's a long story.
Tell you all about it
later on tonight, ok?
Well, I guess that means
we're not going to lunch, huh?
Yeah, uh, sorry
about that, huh?
Here, here, here.
A little
lunch money.
That's a lot more
than lunch money.
Yeah, well,
it's a test, Walt.
You're never gonna
get better unless
you test yourself.
Hmm?
Can you do it?
We'll see about that
later, won't we?
Fritz: The rustic inn.
Must've been
the only bar in L.A.
I'd never had a drink in,
and if I had,
I didn't remember it.
What a dump.
It figured fat dog
would do his drinking here.
Get me a double bushmill
straight up with coke back.
I'm looking
for fat dog baker.
He told me I could
get a line on him here.
I ain't seen fat dog
in a week or so.
[Clears throat]
Of course, if you'd
like to leave a message...
I'll see that he gets it
as soon as he comes in.
How about any
of these other guys?
7 bucks.
They know fat dog,
where I could
find him?
Augie?!
What can you do
for him?
He loops with fat dog
kinda semi-regular.
Why don't you
go ask him?
Maybe he knows, but you
need to buy him a pitcher.
He likes coors.
Of course.
[Sighs]
[Clears throat]
Yeah. Ahem.
Ok, thanks.
Augie dougal?
How ya doin'?
I'm a friend
of fat dog baker's.
You mind
if I talk to you
for a few minutes?
You're not a cop,
are ya?
Cops are always
lookin' for fat dog.
No, no, no.
I'm not a cop.
You look kinda like one.
Well, uh...
Yeah, well, I was, but
I've traded in my badge
for a set of golf clubs.
Yeah, the fat dog's
gonna teach me the game.
Oh.
There ya go.
Well, you picked yourself
a good teacher.
Nobody knows golf
like fat dog.
Nobody can read the Greens
as well as he can, either.
You put the putt
where he tells ya,
tch, whammo.
It's in the cup.
In the cup?
Every time.
In the cup.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
That's good.
Yeah.
Sure thing.
Top that off for ya.
There ya go.
Listen, um,
here's the deal, augie.
I got this big game
tomorrow,
and it's kind of
important that I, uh,
talk to fat dog tonight.
Do you happen to know
where he could be?
Well, he's been loopin'
the bel air lately,
uh, sleepin' on this hill
out there by eighth hole--
wait, wait, wait.
Go back a second.
You're tellin' me
that he's sleepin'
outside?
Fat dog, he don't
like sleepin' indoors.
Says it's bad for him.
He has bad dreams.
I see.
What would be
the best way
I could find him
tonight?
Well, there's a gate
just off of sunset.
It's near
the girls' school,
and there's this
big statue of Jesus there.
Fritz:
I neared the entrance augie
dougal was talking about.
Jesus stood guard
over the student parking lot
at marymont school
for girls.
I waited for a while
and got lucky.
Hey, fat dog!
Got a visitor out here!
Who's that?
Friend or foe?
It's Fritz brown, man.
I gotta talk to ya.
Oh, Fritz! What's up, buddy?
Hey, the private eye guy.
You got some good shit
for the fat dog?
Well, I don't know
about that,
but I checked it
all out,
and I have
to agree with you.
I think solly k
is doing something
with your sister.
I mean, uh,
if it was my sister,
I don't know
what I'd do, but...
Don't you see
what he's doing?
He's fuckin' her,
the son of a bitch!
No, i--i
didn't see that.
I mean,
I don't know.
You don't know that
for sure, do you?
Oh, the fuckin' hell
I don't.
Man, listen, y-you gotta
look after janey, all right?
Please, just make sure
nothin' happens to her.
They're followin' me.
Who's following you?
N-No, no, no,
there's nobody followingme.
There's no one
literally following me.
No, you just told me
that somebody's
following you.
No, there's no one--
there's no one following me.
There's no--there's nobody
following me, all right?
Fine. Nobody's
following you.
Is it cathcart?
What do you know
about cathcart?
Well, solly
met with him today.
That fuckin' Jew.
I told him to stop,
you know?
I--i got money, too,
The fat dog's
got lots of money.
I-I'll give you
whatever you want, ok?
You just gotta
look after janey,
make sure nothin' happens
to my sister, please.
What does
Haywood cathcart
have to do
with any of this?
I told ya, solly's
into a lot of evil shit.
Cathcart's
as evil as they come.
I'll give you $10,000
to look after janey,
make sure nothing
happens, all right?
What makes you think
something's gonna
happen to your sister?
Don't ya understand?
$10,000 for one week!
Do you want the money
or not?
Sure. Yeah,
I'll take your money,
but it's like
I told you before--
I get paid in full
up front.
That means tonight.
Tonight. I can
give you the money.
We gotta take a ride
for the cash, though.
Right now?
Yeah.
Ok. Where to?
Venice.
Put the fuckin' top up.
I'm freezin'.
No, I like
the top down.
It's raining,
you know.
Oh, yeah.
That's why it's down.
I'm in a t-shirt.
Yeah, you sleep outside,
I drive with my top down.
[Chuckles]
So tell me your story,
fat dog.
Uh, I mean, I was a cop
for 6 years, man,
and I tell you what:
I never met anybody
as queer as you.
[Chuckles]
What can I say?
I'm the king
of the caddies.
The greatest fuckin'
looper that ever
packed a bag.
I know every course
in this town like
the back of my hand.
Looks like hard work.
Those bags ever
get too heavy for ya?
Naw, naw, naw,
not unless you're
loopin', like,
hillview
or brentwood.
Those kikes like
to pack their bags
full of cement.
I mean,
they'll throw you
some extra cash.
It's just,
you know, they like
to feel superior
while they're
torturing you.
You ever caddy
for kupferman?
No, no, no.
He's got a coon
packing his bags.
Those Jews
and niggers are
like soul brothers.
All right,
all right, all right.
Just can it, ok?
I like Jews,
and I like blacks, too.
I grew up watching
soultrain, you know.
Oh, yeah.
They had some hot babes
on that show.
So tell me, why do you
sleep outside, man?
You dig pussy?
Sure.
You ever wanted a girl
that could
give you everything
you ever wanted,
you didn't have
to worry about?
You didn't have to worry
about this chick
fuckin' other guys or--
her body is perfect,
you know?
Just like the one you've
always dreamed about,
and she's even nice
to be around
after ya fucked her.
That's how I feel
about golf courses.
They're just fuckin'...
Beautiful.
I'm back in 10 minutes.
Hey, hey, hey, babe,
I ain't lettin' you
outta my sight.
Where you go, I go.
Well, I ain't gonna show you
where I keep my stash,
so I guess we got
ourselves a standoff.
Guess so.
What's it gonna be,
cowboy?
[Car approaching]
Aw, shit!
Hey, man! You know
what kind of car
this is, dude?!
Look at this!
Where's fat dog?!
Fat who, man?!
Hey, man, he was just here
before you showed up.
God, you just screwed it up
for the both of US.
Ow!
What about
the ledgers?!
What'd he do
with them, huh?!
I don't know
no ledgers!
He just hired me
to do a job.
We know why
he fuckin' hired you.
I have one incredibly
good piece of advice:
Go back to fucking
repossessing cars, man.
[Speaks Spanish]
Fuck you, spic!
Fuck you!
Yeah, come on back!
!¡puta!
come on, huh?!
Fuck you, prick!
Fritz: What was I doing?
I should have stopped
right then and there.
This story
would have been over,
and all I would have had
was a bruised face
and a battered ego,
but the hook
was in too deep.
Seeing Haywood cathcart
got me wondering
what the hell he was up to
and whether or not I could
somehow do to him
just a little bit of what
he had already done to me.
I used to carry a derringer
back when I was a cop.
I wasn't supposed to,
but I did it anyway.
Still there...
The 2 guys from last night.
They must be working
for cathcart
or maybe solly,
I don't know.
I was starting
to feel like a cop again,
and I wasn't sure
how I liked it.
I needed some answers,
though,
and I knew just the place.
Lulu: Fritzy!
Hey, hey, hey. Lulu.
May I help you?
Yes, you may. Later.
Tell Jackie I'm here,
would you, please?
[Knocking rhythmically]
Lulu:
He'll be right out.
All right. Hey.
Hey. Fritzy, baby.
Hi. How are you?
Hey. Um...
What's with the head band?
You take up tennis?
What? Come on.
They're back in style.
Oh, yeah?
Didn't you know?
You look great.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, yeah. You get
that other face lift there?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
So how's tricks, huh?
Still got that repo gig?
Hatchet man
for bud Myers, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, more or less.
How 'bout you?
I mean, what's the latest?
Well, currently, i'm
in the escort business.
I provide businessmen
with attractive,
intelligent girls
to be seen with
at various functions.
I see. So you're
up to your old tricks.
I protest, fritzy.
My girls are all
in college.
Enough with
the bullshit, ok?
Come on. I'm serious.
I gotta talk.
Fritz: Tell me what you know
about a solly kupferman.
Solly kupferman?Yeah.
Well, I knew him.
I knew him slightly
maybe, I don't know,
20 years ago
when I had a chauffeur gig,
you know?
I used to fix him up
with a limo and a driver.
The guy was
a financial wizard.
You know, he made
a bundle for the mob.
What's he up to now?
Solly kupferman's
always up to something.
How do I know?
I mean, like what?
Come on.
You know
what he's up to.
Look, back in the eighties
before the club utopia
was burned,
this guy probably handled...
200 thou a week.
Triple that
on super bowl Sunday.
Club utopia,
as in the, uh,
utopia firebomb?
Yeah, well,
what do you got,
some whore who thinks
that solly k owes her
a shitpot
full of money?
No, no, no.
It's nothing like that.
Heh heh heh heh.
Sure, Fritz.
You're a regular
Dudley do-right, huh?
[Cell phone rings]
Yeah.
Listen, fritzy.
Do me a favor, will you?
Stay away.
These guys do things
their own way
for a reason.
Hmm. Why is that?
Because they can.
[Beep]
Yeah?
Oh, Elizabeth, baby.
Fritz: Jack was always good
for color,
but...i needed more.
Jack: A congressman?
♪ Hey hey hey
♪ hey hey hey hey
♪ hey hey hey
♪ oh, baby...
Fritz: I found myself
back in venice
around the same area
fat dog had skipped out
on me the night before.
♪ La la la la la la
♪ baby, baby, baby
Fritz: Hey, hey, hey!
You got a second?
Always enough time
and never enough wine.
You know, I can, uh,
take you in for that.
Oh, come on.
Mmm. Not that.
Singing.
Give me a break.
Disturbing
the peace.
Oh!
All right. Listen.
Maybe you can
help me out instead.
I'm looking
for this, uh,
this uh, white guy.
Big, 6'2", 6'3",
25, 300 pounds.
Uh, uh,
smelly, sweaty.
I think he lives
around here.
Yeah, I know
the shitbird.
Wears a shirt with
2 golf clubs on the chest?
That's right.
And a golf cap?
You got it.
What are you
looking for him for?
Molesting
little boys.
I knew it!
I knew it! I knew it!
You know,
one day I was sitting
on this driveway,
and this shitbird
tells me to move my ass.
Said it was his property.
He looked
a little crazy to me,
so I moved. Shitbird.
Oh, you remember
where you were?
Yeah, around the corner.
[Fly buzzing]
Fritz: Gasoline.
Fat dog knew more
about the solly k fire
than he let on.
Fritz: I headed downtown
to see Mark swirkal.
Mark was
the fastest process server
and courthouse bulldog
in L.A.
I got what you wanted,
Fritz, more or less.
The trial was short,
the transcript was short,
and the story goes
a little something like this.
In December of 1988,
club utopia,
a sleazy little
neighborhood bar
on the corner of normandie
near slauson was firebombed.
6 patrons fried to death.
The surviving eyewitnesses
described how 3 men
who had been ejected from
the bar earlier that evening
returned just before closing
and tossed a molotov cocktail
into a crowded
one-room lounge.
Yeah, yeah.
I remember the case.
Didn't they claim there
was a fourth man, though?
Give me a sec.
I'm gettin' to that.
The 3 men were apprehended
by the l.A.P.D.
The arresting officer...
Was detective lieutenant
Haywood cathcart.
77th street division.
What's this about,
Fritz, huh?
You're not still trying
to get back at cathcart,
are you?
No.
I shouldn't talk
about it.
I'm on a case.
[Chuckles]
So, uh, tell me
a little bit more
about that fourth man.
Yeah, well, the 3 men
admitted their culpability,
but claimed the existence
of a fourth man
who they met outside the bar
when they were thrown out.
They claimed he instigated
the whole thing,
but no one believed them.
Hmm. They say
what he looked like?
Yeah, it was a big guy,
a red-faced guy,
kind of grubby-looking,
real mean,
with one of those shirts
with the crocodile
on the pocket.
I mean, they say
this cat was so...
Fritz: Fat dog.
Mark went on talking,
but I didn't hear
a word he was saying.
Finally, he stopped.
What's the matter, brownie?
Hmm?
Oh, uh, nothing.
Nothing, uh...
Tell me a little bit
about the owner
of the club,
why don't you?
Yeah, well,
it was in the name
of a Wilson Edwards.
Whether he was
the rightful owner or not,
your guess
is as good as mine.
I mean, it was one
of those kind of clubs.
Huh. Yeah.
Well, hey, uh,
thanks, daddy-o.
It's on
the house, baby.
All righty.
Fritz: Wilson Edwards
wasn't that hard to find.
He had been busted
just last year
for possession of heroin.
A friend of mine downtown
supplied me
with that information
along with the address.
Go down
and wait for me.
Ok.
[Knocking]
Man: Eddie, is that you?
Yeah, it's me.
Open the door.
[Coughing]
You're not Eddie.
That's right. I'm not.
I'm a private investigator.
I gotta talk to you.
[Coughing]
You sick?
Hey, come on,
uh, you can tell me.
I'm not
gonna hurt you.
Look, look, look.
I just want to ask you
a couple questions.
I'm not sick yet,
but I will be soon.
[Coughs]
The great irony in that?
I'm fuckin' dying of cancer,
and I'm not sick yet.
Oh, why don't you
just make yourself at home?
I gotta get rid
of these shakes.
[Piano music playing]
[Tape rewinding]
Edwards: All right.
Ahem. Listen.
Make this fast.
I don't want you here
when Eddie shows up.
All right.
Well...
Ohhh.
I just want to ask you
a couple of questions
about the club utopia.
All right.
What about it?
Well, you owned
the place, didn't you?
That's right.
[Sighs]
Well, how did you, uh,
put the money together
to, uh, get a club
like that anyway?
I saved up.
[Laughs]
You saved up.
Oh,
that's bullshit.
Bullshit.
I mean, those
tracks on your arm
tell
your life story.
You've never
had a pot to piss in
except for maybe,
just maybe,
when you
were frontin'
for the real owner
of the club, hmm?
Well, things were
different back then.
I had my shit together.
Don't shit
a shitter, ok?
Look, I just
want to die in peace.
You can dig that,
can't you?
Then why don't you tell me
what I want to know,
and I'll get the fuck
out of your hair, hmm?
What do you want to know?
For starters,
who really
owned the club?
Some guy by the name
of sol kupferman,
a rich guy
from Beverly Hills.
[Coughs]
Hmm.
So you ran the place
for him then, right?
That's right.
I ran the place.
Bullshit.
Now who really
ran the place?
Who ran the place?!
All right.
Ok.
Now, you're gonna tell me
who ran the place for him,
or we're just
gonna sit here and wait
for your friend Eddie
to show up.
How's that sound?
[Sighs]
[Coughing]
[Humming]
Ralston.
Ralston who?
Richard
"hot rod" ralston.
He played
for the Dodgers
for 5 minutes back
in the late seventies.
[Coughs]
That's good. Good.
What does he do now?
Last I heard,
he was still
caddy master
at hillview.
[Coughs]
Ok, that's good.
Now, uh, tell me,
when you were working
for the club, uh,
did you happen
to run across
any bank notes, ledgers,
records of any kind?
Look,
I just ran the bar.
I ordered the liquor,
I picked up the records
for the jukebox.
I'm sick,
and I fucking don't
know anything, ok?!
Ok.
Appreciate your help.
Thank you very much.
Hey.
Fuck you.
[Door closes]
[Country music playing]
Fritz: I gotta find somebody
to help me with the fat dog.
See the guy
with the guitar
at the end of the bar?
Got him.
He's your man.
[Sighs]
Fritz: The choice
between working and drinking
is becoming harder
and harder.
I felt like just
chucking it all in
and going on
a 9- or 10-day bender.
But for 10,000 bucks,
it was worth
taking another shot
at finding the fat dog.
♪ Daddy's line of work
♪ kept US movin' around
♪ I got fond memories
of the way things were ♪
Ok.
♪ Back then...
[Whistling]
[Urinating and sighing]
Stan the man?
Police officer.
Can I talk to you
a few minutes?
Yeah.
You don't mind,
do you?
Go ahead.
Finish up.
So are you vice?
No. Why do you ask?
Well, I always
thought of fat dog
as sort of some kind
of pervert, you know?
Yeah?
He used to be
the golf ball king
of all L.A.
He used to have
3 hotel rooms.
Nothing but golf balls
in all 3 rooms.
[Both laugh]
Then he'd go sleep
on the fifth tee
at Wilshire.
I mean, anybody
that does that
has got
to be a pervert,
you agree with me?
I agree with you.
Yeah.
Listen, Stan.
I need you to take me
out to bel air tonight.
Hmm? Fat dog's out there.
He sleeps out there
these days,
and I gotta talk to him.
Hop in the car.
Ok.
Stan: Well,
fat dog's not here.
Let's get the hell
out of here.
Fritz: Well,
what about the back 9?
Heh. Forget
about the back 9.
He hates the back 9.
The toughest 9 holes
I've ever packed.
Buggy as shit.
Buggy, huh?
Stan, uh, tell me
what you know
about
a Richard ralston.
Richard ralston?
Yeah, yeah.
Richard ralston.
You know the guy?
He's the meanest
human being I ever met.
[Sighs]
Smells nice around here,
don't it?
Mmm. Yeah, yeah.
It's peaceful.
You know,
I tell you,
it's gotta
be a tough job
doing what you do.
A tough way
to make a living.
Yeah.
Looping wouldn't
be such a bummer
if it wasn't for the guys
who were looping.
Hmm.
I gotta tell you
something.
Um, i'm, uh,
not really a cop.
No, i'm--i'm
a private investigator.
You son of a bitch.
I--you--i--
I knew there was something
funny about you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I knew it.
I blew it.
I'm sorry, man.
You know, you can
hit me if you want.
But I shanghaied you
out here
all illegally and...
Sorry about that.
So how come you're
looking for fat dog?
Oh, he just hired me
to do a little work
for him.
That's all.
But mostly, I, uh,
I repossess cars.
[Laughing]
Now that's funny.
That's funny.
Yeah?
I used to steal cars.
No shit.
Did 18 months for it.
It's a hard habit to kick.
[Laughs]
Oh, I tell you,
that's, uh--
when you think about it,
that's about all I do.
Except they
don't send me to jail.
That sounds like
a hell of a good job.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, you know, it--
it has its good days.
I'll tell you what.
Why don't you
give it a try, huh?
Let me give you
one of my cards.
And, uh...
There you go.
Give me a call.
You might get
a kick out of it.
Fritz: Wally!
Come on out!
[Knocking]
Fritz: I stopped by
my cousin Walter's place.
I hadn't seen him
in a couple of days,
and I was wondering
how much of that 50 bucks
he had gone through.
Wake up, baby.
Wally, where you at?!
Hey, if you're
screwing with me again,
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Come on!
Where are you at?
[Walter coughing]
Got you!
Hey, man!
Oh, hey, buddy.
Hey, hey!
You're dead meat.
I got you.
You little bitch.
Oh, man.
Oh, you're bad.
Come on, come on.
They were
looking for you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got you. Come on.
I had to run away.
Come on.
Get up, baby, get up.
I don't
want to get up.
[Grunts]
Oh, I had to run away.
Ok, here,
put this on.
Oh, man,
I don't feel so good.
Hold on.
I haven't had
a drink all day.
What are you
talking about, man?
Do it yourself.
It's all right.
They looked like leger.
Ok.
Leger. Leger.
French cubist.
What'd they look like?
Tell me--
so what would I be doing
with a dead French cubist?
What did they look like?
I didn't see too well.
It's ok. Tell me
what they looked like.
It was dark.
I couldn't see, man.
But when
they got mad,
they were
speaking Spanish.
Fritz: Look...
I know what you want
and I know what you need.
What you want
and what you need
are 2 different things.
I know
what I need, Fritz.
And it's not a doctor.
No.
Unless...
She's, uh...
She's a, you know...
Uh-uh.
Ain't happening.
You know the last time
I dipped my wick
was August 19, 1993?
It's embarrassing.
Help me out.
Yeah. Drink it.
Yeah, it was
that cop groupie
you set me up with.
Yeah, yeah, oh, yeah.
I remember that.
I almost lost my job
on that one.
Oh, she was something.
She was something.
I know.
God.
Fritz, I'm lonely, man.
Help me out, will you?
Just do this for me.
Ok. Ok, fine.
You're gonna--
ah--
done, ok?
But ain't nobody
gonna do anything
unless you
take a bath first.
Oh, hey.
Is that ok?
Yeah. You're a pal.
Ok. Hop on.
I know a gal that'll
take good care of you
for a couple of days
at least.
Great big tits?
What, are you picky now?
Yeah, yeah.
She's got big melons.
Don't worry about it.
And you know what else?
She's gonna like you, man.
She's gonna dig you
a lot because you're
an intellectual.
She likes
the intellectual type.
Very good.
Raw tin, Fritz.
Raw tin.
That's his last--
ralston. Yeah, I know.
Don't worry.
Fritz:
The guy with Jane baker
looked kind of like
an ex-ball player.
Richard ralston.
Had to be.
What a gentleman.
Everything started
coming together
in a way
I still didn't understand.
All I knew was...
Richard!
I had to keep going.
Fritz:
I followed Richard ralston
into the hillview
country club.
I told them at the gate
that I was there
to meet solly kupferman
for a quick 9.
They believed me.
Ralston: Fat dog got himself
in some big trouble.
He fucked with
the wrong people.
You're probably not gonna
see him again, augie,
not ever.
Augie:
What did he do, rod?
Now, this is a real
heavyweight scene, augie.
Heavy-duty shit.
I mean, heavy-duty.
Did he tell you about it?
No, he didn't tell me
no heavy-duty shit, rod.
Just looping
and racetrack stuff.
Honest!
Are you sure
about that, augie?
I'm sure.
Honest, rod, honest.
Fat dog ripped off
a ledger, augie.
I needthat ledger.
Now, you know fat dog's
rich, don't you, augie?
Loaded. Heavy bread.
And guess what?
It's rightfully mine.
I want...
That money.
What do you know
about that, augie, huh?
I don't know where
he keeps his money, rod,
and I never saw
no ledger.
Ok, augie.
One more thing.
Then I'll let you go.
I got a juicy 9-holer
waiting for you.
Where do you think
the fat dog is, augie?
T.j.
Gotta be, rod.
He--he--he's been
talking about racing dogs,
and I ain't
seen him in 2 days.
You are
a good man, augie.
And a good caddy.
Fritz: "Hot rod" ralston.
Oh, he was gonna
get his due, all right.
Yes, he was.
But he'd have
to wait his turn.
I needed to find
the fat dog.
After a little
poking around,
I discovered
that Tijuana had
its own country club.
It's a giant patch of green
in an otherwise
brown landscape.
I thought maybe
I could get a lead
on the king
of caddies there.
No reembolso.
No--
no refund.
English?
You speak English?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Well, I just need
a little information.
I'm looking
for this caddy.
American guy.
Big.
6'2".
285-300 pounds.
Wears dirty
golf clothes--
yeah, yeah, yeah,
I know the guy.
He laid
some golf balls on me
a couple days ago.
Do you know where
I could find him?
Nah.
He's just a bum.
Fly-by-night.
Well, did
he talk to you
about anything
other
than golf balls?
Yeah.
As matter of fact,
he wanted to know
where he could buy
some racing dogs.
I thought he was
just shittin' me.
He didn't
look like he had
the kind of money
to be buying
no racing dogs.
Then he pulls
out a roll.
A couple of grand.
I'm like, "fuck me!"
You know, the vato's
got this kind of money
and he's selling
golf balls?
He's crazy.
He's got something
in his head wrong,
you know?
So you sent him
to the dog track?
Hell, no!
I sent him
to primo Armando'shouse.
He's got a litter
of greyhound pups, man.
Beautiful.
Why, you interested?
Uh, no, no, no.
How do I find
your primo Armandoguy?
Who are you, man?
Look, I'm a good guy.
I just want the retard
that sold you
the golf balls,
that's all.
Fritz: I went
with my newfound friend
way the hell out
in the middle of nowhere.
After 2 hours of driving,
I wasn't sure
what to expect.
By now, though,
I was ready for anything.
[Speaking Spanish]
Armando,
this is, uh--
what's your name again?
Buto.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.Mr. Buto.
Mr. Smart buto, huh?
[Chuckles]
My cousin says
that, uh...
You're trying to find
that fat gringo
I sold 2 dogs to.
That's right.
It's gonna
cost you $200.
[Chuckles]
All right, no problem.
Where is he?
I'll tell you
where he is
when you show me
the money.
It's coming.
Keep
your shorts on.
There you go.
[Laughs]
So, where is he?
You gonna
fuck him up, gringo?
Maybe.
Maybe not.
Where's he at?
Fritz: I'd had enough.
I was about ready
to blow it all,
but I held it in
and let the Mexicans play
their mind game with me.
That fat gringodeserves
everything he gets.
I got a feeling
about him.
about you, too,
gabacho.
So, I want to tell you.
You take that blue thing
up that road towards town,
look for the blue church.
You'll find him.
[Flies buzzing]
Fritz: Something was up.
I could smell it.
[Dog growls]
[Growling]
Fritz: The same stench
that lingered in the yard
doubled as I came
through the door.
[Squeaking]
It was Frederick
"fat dog" baker.
Caddy...
Arsonist...
And the one man
I thought could answer
all my questions.
The shack was empty,
but fat dog
never slept inside.
Uhh!
[Laughs]
Fritz: A thorough search
of the area turned up
Frederick "fat dog" baker's
worldly possessions,
including a bunch of ledgers
that Mr. Ralston
and the 2 Mexican guys
from L.A.
Had been looking for.
Whoever murdered fat dog
would sure as hell
like to get
their hands on these.
He deserved a burial,
but I wasn't about
to do the digging.
You can get any service
you want down here
as long as you
got the money.
[Speaks Spanish]
Keep digging.
[Groaning]
Uhh!
[Gunshots]
Ohh!
Aah!
[Rapid gunfire]
Uhh!
[Fritz drops body]
[Fritz breathing hard]
Ralston: Fat dog got himself
in some big trouble.
He fucked
with the wrong people.
Fat dog: I told ya, solly's
into a lot of evil shit.
Cathcart's as evil
as they come.
[Groans]
Fritz: Now the craving
wasn't stopping.
I couldn't resist
any longer.
As soon
as I hit Ensenada,
I stopped at the first
liquor store I could find.
Paranoia had set in.
The fire might spread,
the tire marks
at the scene
can be traced
back to me
and there were
these 4 unexplained
dead bodies.
Fear breeds fear,
and alcohol kills it.
At least it does for me.
My mind was raging,
but I was perfectly calm.
For one split second,
clarity hit
and I knew exactly what
the consequences would be.
But I didn't care anymore.
[Voices echoing]
Armando: That fat gringo
deserves everything he gets.
Fat dog: I told ya, solly's
into a lot of evil shit.
Cathcart's as evil
as they come.
[Voices echoing]
That fuckin' Jew.
I told him to stop.
I got money, too.
[Voices echoing]
[Laughing]
Fat dog: I told ya, solly's
into a lot of evil shit.
Cathcart's as evil
as they come.
Edwards: Look, I just
want to die in peace.
You can dig that,
can't you?
Fritz:
No matter how much I drank,
my mind
just wouldn't let go.
And no matter
how hard I tried,
I just kept thinking,
remembering.
It took me 2 days
to get sober,
but I finally got
my shit together
and drove back to L.A.
I'll take it
from here.
Key, please? Shh.
Bye.see ya.
What?
What the hell
do you think
you're doing?
Get out of my car!
Calm down.
My name's Fritz brown.
I'm a private investigator.
Your name
is Jane baker,
you like playing
the piano,
and your roommate's
sol kupferman.
Your big brother fat dog
enjoys collecting golf balls
and starting fires.
Now get in.
I want to talk to you.
Get in
and shut the door.
Shut the door!
[Tires screech]
It belongs to you.
How did he die?
I don't think
you want to hear
any more about that.
It was horrible?
Well, let's just say
that I'm gonna
have nightmares
for the rest
of my life.
How do you know
Richard ralston?
From hillview.
I used to tag along
when Freddy was
a caddy there.
How well do you
know hot rod?
What do you mean?
I think you know
what I mean.
Do you mean, um...
Did he ever fuck me?
What's the big deal?
Yeah, we had
an affair briefly
a few years ago.
You had an affair?
You're 17 years old.
I mean, come on.
Several years ago
you were, what, 13?
There was a time
that I loved Richard.
Well, ok.
Well, I got
some news for you.
Your lover boy
dick ralston
is responsible
for your brother's
death.
[Chuckles]
I don't believe you.
[Laughs]
Not for one second.
[Laughs] You're
just some loser p.I.
You know what,
you can believe
what you
want to believe.
But I'm telling you
it's a fact.
Richard ralston
got paid money
to give to 2 guys
to kill your brother.
Now, in my opinion,
I believe the money
came from
sol kupferman.
Fuck you!
You don't know US!
You don't know him!
I'm gonna go
tell solly.
He already knows.
[Crying]
Jane: What am I
supposed to do?!
[Jane crying]
[Knocks]
Fritz:
I went over to Helen's
place to check and see
how everything went
with Wally.
[Knocking]
Only she would've taken him
in the shape he was in.
Hey.
What a gal.
If she wasn't a whore,
I'd marry her.
Where's he at?
I've been calling you.
Calling me?
Walter's not here.
Well, where'd
he go to?
He's in the hospital.
[Monitor beeping]
Fritz: It was me
and his brother Mike
that taught him
how to drink, party,
fuck, and fight.
But Wally was only good
at one of 'em.
It was at this point
that I wondered
why I hadn't
just walked away.
And now I couldn't.
[Ralston whistling Dixie]
That's right,
Mr. Ralston.
It's a gun.
It's loaded,
but I'm not.
Next stop,
maintenance shack.
Now put your arms down
and just
walk normal, please.
Look, I want you to know
I only got $65 on me.
I lost tonight.
You'd have
done better to catch
some of the other guys.
I'm almost flat broke--
now, listen to me,
you prick.
Tonight you're gonna pay
for some of your past sins,
and you're gonna
tell me everything
I want to know.
Ohh!
Now...
I know most of it,
but you're gonna fill in
some of the pieces for me.
And if you don't...
I'm gonna
go internal on ya
and bang your kidneys
until you piss blood.
How's that sound to ya?
Look, you can do
whatever you want,
but I don't know
anything.
You don't know
anything?
Huh? How's that?
Huh? What side are
those damn kidneys on?
Do you know?!
Uhh! Uhh!
Are those
your kidneys?
Huh?!
You wear me out.
Now...
Let's give this
a try, shall we?
Come on up.
[Ralston gasping]
Stop whining!
Fritz:
Now, are you concerned
that they'll get at you
for talking to me?
Is that a yes?
Yes.
[Stops recorder]
Look at it this way.
They might kill you
for talking to me
here tonight,
but that's
an unknown factor.
Me...
I'm a fact.
I'm the here
and now.
And if you
don't talk to me,
you will die
here and now.
That's absolute.
[Chuckles]
Dig?
Good.
Now...
[Starts recorder]
Let's go.
Cathcart and solly
are working
a welfare check scam.
Fake welfare checks?
Don't those checks
have to be signed
in front of the people
paying out the money?
Yeah,
but solly's
got over 2 dozen
liquor stores
and partnerships
in a couple
of dozen others.
All the checks
get cashed there.
The ledgers
that fat dog stole,
they contain
documentation
on that, am i--
am I right?
Yes.
How did you know
about that?
[Stops recorder]
Hmm?
I ask
the questions here.
Understand me?
Mm-hmm. Ohh!
All right.
How's this scam
work exactly?
Solly forges
the applications.
Case workers submit them
for approval and--
and supervisors
working for cathcart
authorize payment.
He's even got
a guy in Sacramento
monitoring
the computer checks.
It's--it's--
it's foolproof.
How much money
do they pull in a month?
I don't know.
Hundreds of thousands.
Cathcart's filthy rich.
Who told you I was
involved in this case?
Jane baker.
We've been friends
for years and--uhh!
Don't you
fucking ever
mention her name
to me again!
Ohh!
You pervert.
Now...
[Starts recorder]
Stop whining!
Does cathcart plan
on having me killed?
Yes.
He's got somebody
after you now.
He thinks you're
holed up somewhere drunk
and afraid.
This tape...
Is going someplace safe.
If I don't check in
at regular intervals,
it goes straight
to the press.
You dig?
Yeah.
I stay healthy...
You stay safe.
Fritz:
I gave Mark the tapes,
and I told him
what I wanted.
Should I fail to contact
his answering service
once during
every 24-hour period
with the message
"crazy daddy-o,"
he should immediately
tape a dozen copies
and hand-deliver them
to the press.
I trusted him.
He was a solid, good man.
I was now officially
on the run,
but I decided to risk it
and head back to my place
and pick up a few things.
Long night?
Yeah, I'm having
the place redecorated,
and I'm staying
in a hotel.
I'm sergeant Larkin,
riverside county
sheriff's department.
Sergeant cavanah,
l.A.P.D.
Could we
talk to you?
Inside?
Yeah, why not?
[Keys jingle]
Fritz: Come on in.
[Door closes]
You have a permit
for that weapon,
Mr. Brown?
Ah, yes, I do,
and I have a permit
to carry it concealed.
I'm a licensed
private investigator.
Ooh.
Wow.i see.
Have a seat.
Do you own
any other weapons?
Yes, I own
a Browning pump shotgun.
Could we see that?
What's this all about?
Where were you
last night
between 10 P.M.
and 2 A.M.?
I told you.
I'm staying
at a hotel.
I was in my room.
You check into that.
Yeah.
Do you know a man
named Stanley gather,
a.k.a. Stan the man?
Yeah, yeah.
I met him once briefly
a short while ago. Why?
[Gun cocks]
[Shell bounces
off the floor]
Your business card
was found on his body.
[Laughs]
Yeah.
[Clears throat]
Murdered?
Oh, yeah.
Down in palm Springs
along with 2 other guys.
Caddies. Their bodies
were found
underneath
a freeway overpass.
Shotgun?
Cavanah: 6 expended
shells were found.
Their bodies
were blown all to shit.
So, how'd you
meet gather?
What was the basis
of your relationship?
Well, what relationship?
Hmm?
I met him in a bar,
he bought me a drink,
and, uh,
started telling me
about himself...
How he was a--
how he was
a compulsive car thief,
and he was doing therapy
to control
his compulsion, huh.
I told him I was
in the repo business,
and I might be able
to help him get started
ripping off cars legally.
He took my card,
and, uh--
fuck, I haven't
seen him since.
Ever met
a George Hansen,
also known
as hamburger?
Or a Robert
"Bobby" marciane?
No, no, I haven't.
Why? Are they
the other 2, uh--
that's right.
Do you know
any other caddies?
No. No,
I don't play golf.
It's not
my idea of kicks.
What is
your idea of kicks?
Great music,
beautiful women.
What's yours?
Bitch-slapping
lying scumbags.
Hmm.
Don't fuck with US,
brown.
See, I pulled up
your personnel file
this morning,
and I found out that
you're a fuck-up
and a disgrace
to your department.
Now we are
investigating
a multiple homicide,
and we don't
have to take shit
from
some repo asshole.
Well, boys,
I tell you what.
If that's all you got,
if that's all
you have to tell me,
why don't you
just leave?
Hmm?
I'll tell you
what I'll do.
I'll get
the door for ya.
Ladies?
[Chuckles]
You watch
your step, brown.
I'm personally
keeping my eye on you.
You have no idea
how excited
that makes me.
Fritz: It was
on the bottom of page one.
Not much,
but the address
of George Hansen
might be worth something.
[Doorbell buzzes]
Yes?
Are you Mrs. Hansen?
Are you
from the police?
Because they told me
I could wait
a few days
before making
my statement.
No, no, no.
My name is brown.
I'm a private investigator.
I'm here
looking into the murders
here in palm Springs
and a couple
other related things,
and I thought maybe
you might, uh,
talk to me
just for a few minutes.
Do you mind?
All right.
Come on in.
Thank you.
I'll try
to make this brief.
I believe that the death
of your husband
and his 2 friends
can be traced
directly back
to a Richard ralston
and a Frederick
"fat dog" baker.
You know these 2 men?
Um, George has been
doing business with...
Fred if you can
call it that.
They have, um,
thousands of golf balls
at some tacky
motel room
in Los Angeles.
Do you know who might
have the key now?
Well, I've got it
here somewhere.
You can have it
if I can find it.
I've really had enough
of golf balls
and golf bums.
Oh, here it is.
You know, I've been
sober now for, um...
3 years.
I've got
a higher power
in my life, so...
Here.
Take 'em.
Thank you.
How do you know
Richard ralston?
George and I
have been friends
with dick ralston
for years.
They used to
play minor league
baseball together
when they
were teenagers.
As a matter of fact,
he got, um...
George started
as a caddy,
and, um,
George and I
were foster parents
to Freddy baker and
his little sister
when they were
just children.
You were foster parents
to fat dog baker
and his sister Jane?
Yes.
When was this?
1984.
How did that, uh,
come about anyway?
A friend I knew
arranged it.
He was
a wonderful man,
an old friend,
and he knew
that George and I
wanted children
very badly and...
Couldn't have any.
He paid US really well
for taking care
of those children.
I loved them so much.
They were just...
Little orphans.
Your, uh, friend,
could you
tell me his name?
Sol, sol kupferman.
Kupferman.
I see.
Fritz: Back in L.A.,
my next stop
was at the hall of records.
Theory had been forming
in the dark corner
of my brain.
Clerk: Kupferman.
Send him
out to the car.
Come on out
to the back in here.
[Sighs]
[Chuckles]
Well, Mr. Brown.
We finally meet
face to face, huh?
Are you about to tell me
what it is you want?
What are you
gonna give me?
I'm about to honor
any requests.
[Laughs]
The great solly k
is gonna give me,
Fritz brown,
whatever he wants.
Real white of you.
I know fat dog hired you
to keep an eye on Jane,
but he attempted
to kill me.
Why would he
want to do that?
want to kill you?
Well, I
don't think he liked
the fact that i--
[chuckles]
That Jane was
living in my house.
I can't imagine why.
Oh.
He was unusually
close to Jane.
Well, I would say
that you're unusually
close to Jane,
don't you think?
Yes, well,
Jane and I are, uh--
are what?
Lovers?
Look, Mr. Brown,
I don't think
any of this
really concerns you.
Call me Fritz, ok?
And don't kid yourself.
I'm very concerned here.
You see, I don't think
little girls
should be sleeping
with their daddies.
Look, Mr. Brown, uh--
Fritz.
Jane and I are not--
be careful
what you tell me.
Your whole way of life
depends on it.
Now, the way I see it,
cathcart's
blackmailing you.
He nailed fat dog for
the club utopia firebombing,
and you didn't want your
little boy going to jail,
nor did you want
to be killed by him either,
and while
cathcart knows how
to control little Freddy,
or should I say,
knew how to control
little Freddy.
What do you want, Fritz?
I don't know.
Little revenge.
[Laughs]
Does that make me
a bad person?
Look, it's
not that simple.
Cathcart--
he's--he's
too protected.
He's beyond the law.
Cathcart--
cathcart is the law.
Let me worry
about cathcart.
You just tell Jane
to pack her bags
and get the hell
out of there.
Give her
whatever she wants.
Tell her whatever
you want to tell her.
Send her off
to a real music school,
but just get her
the hell out of that house.
Well, what if she
doesn't want to leave?
Well, then,
I'll just
have to tell her
her real last name.
Don't mess with me.
Stay out
of my way...
And nobody will ever
find out what a...
Sick, old,
disgusting pervert
you really are.
Oh, yeah.
I know everything.
Get out
of my sight...
Before I blow
your guts all
over this counter.
Fritz:
I bought a throwaway gun,
untraceable,
with a silencer.
It'll do the job.
P.A.: Announcing
the arrival of bus number 12
from Las Vegas
at gate 2.
Now boarding del mar,
departing gate 4,
del mar from gate 4,
have your tickets
ready, please.
Fritz:
I got to a pay phone.
I left my password
with Mark swirkal's
answering service.
Crazy daddy-o.
Hey, buddy.
Fritz: Then there
was nothing left to do
but the deal itself.
[Car alarm blaring]
[Alarm stops]
Fritz: You can put
that gun down now.
[Groans]
Fritz:
I figured it was all over.
Cathcart's gun had gone off,
and someone
had to have heard it.
[Man grunting]
[Footsteps]
Fritz:
I woke a bit groggy.
An hour or so had passed
and still no cops,
but I wasn't exactly safe.
Not yet anyway.
When I looked at him,
I knew he knew who I was.
Get up.
Come on.
Fritz:
He had been waiting for me,
and his kevlar service vest
saved his ass.
What did you
hope to accomplish
by coming here
tonight?
How stupid and naive
can you be?
Don't you realize
that ralston and solly k
have as much to lose
as I do?
Fritz brown.
Unbelievable.
You were
the worst scumbag ever
to con his way
into the department.
No.
I was bush-league
compared to you.
Can I get you anything
before we say good-bye?
[Groans] Yeah.
I want a $1 million
welfare check
presented to me by you
on national TV.
You do, huh?
How does it feel to know
that what you've
done here tonight
will ultimately
be judged
as the biggest fuck-up
of your fucked-up life?
On the contrary.
What I've tried
to do here tonight
is the one saving grace
of my fucked-up life.
[Groans]
How about a drink, huh?
Sure. Why not?
Brown.
You come
from good stock.
You're a big,
strong boy.
You know,
you can
still be of service.
Just a question
of, uh--
re-education,
you know?
I'll tell you
what I'm gonna do.
TV: We'll have
all of that for you
and also let you know
about the weekend.
In other news today,
veteran l.A.P.D. Officer
Haywood cathcart
died of a self-inflicted
gunshot wound
sometime over the weekend
at his fishing retreat
in del mar.
He had been
a 28-year veteran...
Fritz:
I sat in the hotel room
for 2 days,
waiting for 'em
to finally find the body.
The l.A.P.D. Reported it
as suicide.
They must have had
a pretty good idea
of what he was up to.
Eh, what the hell
did I care?
I was alive...
And free.
After a couple of weeks,
I went around
to check up on Jane.
I wanted to make sure
that this solly k guy
was living up to his side
of the bargain.
Maid told me that
she was at the hospital.
Cedar sinai.
Jane.
You all right?
You don't
have to tell me.
Fritz:
What could I do?
She made her choice.
There was nothing more
I could say.
I remembered the key
the widow Hansen lady gave me.
I decided to take a drive
out to the, uh,
la Plaza motel.
[Sighs]
[Chuckles]
[Golf ball bounces]
[Laughs]
[Sighs]
[Hums]
[Laughs]
Fritz: Just when
I thought I had found
the pot of gold
at the end of the rainbow,
Walter's condition
took a turn for the worse.
He died 3 weeks later.
He was 32.
Helen drove me
to the funeral.
I got drunk
and disrupted it.
You fuckers.
Leave him alone!
You're hurting him!
Fritz:
Well, that's my story,
most of it anyway.
Still, I can't remember
why I had
that first drink.
All I know now
is that I've got plenty
of money to buy another.
I miss Walter.
One night,
I'm gonna steal his coffin,
and I'm gonna
bring it down to the beach.
I'll have
a boat waiting there...
And I'll send him off
the right way.
He'll float out
to a fiery Valhalla.
Captioning made possible by
lions gate entertainment
captioned by the national
captioning institute
--www.Ncicap.Org--