(Frantic drum music)
(Overlapping sound effects)
(Bright dramatic music)
(Tense suspenseful music)
(Suspenseful dramatic music)
(Suspenseful dramatic music continues)
(Spaceship roaring)
(Suspenseful dramatic music)
(Upbeat country rock music)
(Upbeat country rock music continues)
(Upbeat rock music)
(Upbeat rock music continues)
- Hi. How you doing?
I'm your landlord. Remember me?
How you doin'? - Oh, yeah.
Hi, how are ya? - Hi, how are ya?
Ah, if you need anything, just let me know.
Feel free, you know, to knock at the door.
It's always open to ya.
Do you need help with anything or?
- Actually, no, I'm okay.
The box is big. Can
you get the door for me?
- Sure.
- [Woman] All right, thanks.
- There you go.
- [Brunette] I'll see you later.
- I'll see you later. Bye-bye.
(Upbeat rock music)
(Seductive rock music)
(Dark suspenseful music) (Heart beating)
(Soft seductive music)
(Upbeat seductive music)
(Upbeat seductive music continues)
(Jazzy seductive music)
(Jazzy seductive music continues)
(Dark ominous music)
- [Reporter] We interrupt
this program to bring you
a special news bulletin.
The bodies of two men
were found in a back lot
behind castcom cable company.
Police say the mo is the
same as the current killings
which have plagued our city.
Police are also dubbing this case
the vampire killer case
because of the fact that most
of the victims had gaping
wounds around their neck.
(Doorbell ringing)
Stay tuned for further information.
And now back to our regular programming.
- [Woman] Hi, can I help you?
- Hi. My name is Seth. I'm your neighbor.
I just wanted to come and
welcome you to the neighborhood.
- Well, thank you.
Why don't you come in for a second?
I don't know many people around here.
Can I get you anything?
- Oh, no thank you.
I have a roommate. Her name is Tangie.
You'll get to meet her eventually.
I'm sure we'll become really
good friends for eternity.
Do you live alone?
- Yeah, I'm divorced.
- Mmm, wow, you are so beautiful.
- Excuse me?
(Upbeat rock music)
(Energy zapping)
Uh, hi.
Um, I've got packing that I have to finish.
So do you wanna come
for dinner tomorrow night?
- [Seth] Okay, it's a date.
- Great. See you tomorrow around 7:00?
- [Seth] Yes.
- Thanks.
(Upbeat rock music)
(Birds chirping)
(Staff chatting indistinctly)
- Good morning. - [Bates] Good morning.
- You look like shit.
- Go fuck yourself.
Had a rough night.
- You always have a rough night.
What the hell do you do all night?
- Well, (sighing) I sit awake for hours
and I dread the thought
of looking at your face
each and every morning
as I come into the office.
- Imagine if we didn't like each other.
- Can you imagine that?
Hey, you got anything on the vampire case?
- Are you still insisting on
calling this the vampire case?
- You got a better explanation?
- Sure. Lunatic with an ice pick.
A nutcase with too much time on his hands.
Video tape editor who works too much.
- (Sighing) Yeah?
How about a vampire with
a terrific appetite for blood?
- Yeah, I know I got the jackets here.
Puncture wounds around the neck,
broken bones as if the
killer had super strength,
no blood left in the body.
I could give you half a
dozen reasons for that.
- Yeah, I bet you could, but
the best one is it's a vampire.
- Ain't no such thing. (Phone ringing)
Homicide. Badger.
What?
You're kidding.
Okay. Where is it now?
We'll be right down.
Check this out.
- [Bates] What do you got?
- Somebody was shooting an amateur video
the night of the last murder.
They got it all on tape.
- And where's this tape now?
- Down in the video room with herbie.
- Well, let's go down and see herbie.
- Amazing.
(Video whirring)
- Okay, herb. Show us what you got.
- Okay.
Say, has anybody seen
"spaceship explorer" last week?
- Right there, right there.
Hold that.
- Okay.
Can you move in a
little on that? Clear it up?
- I think so.
I just don't like that new show.
- Why not?
- Don't bother him now.
- But I like that show.
- "Deep space four," it really sucks.
I tell ya.
- Now wait a minute. I like that show.
- Would you please let the man do his job?
- Sorry.
(Tape whirring)
- Uh, herbie?
- [Herbie] Hmm?
- What the hell is this?
- Uh, vice had a raid
on a porno ring last night,
so I just managed to steal a copy.
- [Bates] Yeah, it looks like
the vice boys have been doing
their job again.
- I am in the wrong division.
- Right there. Hold that.
(Dark ominous music)
I could be wrong, but it sure
looks like a vampire to me.
- Oh. Maybe.
Herbie, give us a hard copy of that.
- Sure.
- If she's not a vampire, she
sure needs a new orthodontist.
- "Babylonia six" had a
show about a vampire once.
It was just terrible.
- [Bates] Herbie? - [Herbie] Hmm?
- [Bates] The video, please.
- [Herbie] Oh, yeah. Sure.
(Upbeat seductive music)
- [Woman] Oh my god.
You scared the hell out of me.
How did you get in here?
- The door was open.
- It was?
- Mmm-hmm.
- [Woman] Hey, I'm not
done with the salad yet.
- Smells delicious.
- [Woman] It's filet mignon.
How do you like yours cooked?
- Bloody.
- Okay, can you get the
champagne outta the fridge
for me while I finish cooking here?
- Okay. - [Woman] Thanks.
(Knife chopping)
Ow! Damn it!
- [Seth] What happened?
- [Woman] I cut my finger.
- [Seth] Let me look at that.
- [Woman] Mmm.
- Mmm.
I'm used to blood.
I used to be a nurse many, many years ago.
- Hey, what are you doing?
I'll get a bandage for
that. Don't worry about it.
(Upbeat seductive music)
(Seductive rock music)
(Seductive rock music continues)
(Seductive rock music ends)
(Slinky seductive rock music)
(Slinky seductive rock music continues)
(Upbeat rock music)
(Upbeat rock music continues)
- I've been waiting for you.
- Yeah, I had to get my bandaid on.
Thanks.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Hey, listen.
I was wondering, is there
anything to do around here?
Like, what's the nightlife like?
- It depends what you're into.
- Well, you know, it's been
a while since I've been out.
So I was wondering maybe, you
know, about going out dancing.
- Oh, there's a great
club called after dark,
and I think you'd be into it.
Well, it opens after midnight,
it's in the city and it's underground.
Great music. Great atmosphere.
I'll take you there
tomorrow night if you want.
- [Woman] But it's open so late.
- [Seth] Yeah, but
that's an after hours club.
That's where you wanna go, isn't it?
Wouldn't you like to try it?
- Oh, yeah, yeah. Sure.
- It would be fun. - When do you wanna go?
- We can go tomorrow evening if you'd like.
- All right. Okay.
Hey, listen.
Have you heard that thing on the news
about those two guys
that got killed last night?
They're saying something about it being
a vampire that did it?
(Creepy ominous music)
- Hmm.
Cheers.
(Creepy ominous music)
- [Woman] Anyway, can
you believe that there's
such things as vampires?
- I gotta go.
(Seth breathing heavily)
(Upbeat rock music)
(Crickets chirping)
(Dog barking)
- Come on. Don't sit down.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- [Seth] Relax. We've got all night.
Sit. Grab a seat. I wanna go.
- I wanna go. Come on.
It's been so long since I've been out.
I even put on my thong.
- I know. You look wonderful.
Just have a seat.
- What's the matter? You
don't wanna go out anymore?
- No, it's not that I don't wanna go out.
I just wanna relax for a moment.
- Yeah, well, I mean, you ran out on me
the other night so quick.
Did I do something?
You don't like my dinner?
- No, no. Everything was wonderful.
Well, I don't know if I should tell you.
- [Woman] Why not?
Did I do something?
- No, I don't think you did anything wrong.
I just don't know if you're ready for it.
- Do I need to prepare for this?
I mean, like-
- it depends. It's up to you.
Would you like to know?
- Is this gonna hurt?
(Upbeat techno pop music)
(Upbeat techno pop music continues)
- If this guy shows up,
he should have enough smack on him
to send him all the way to San Quentin.
- Well, we're homicide.
- Yeah, but he's bumped off about five guys
in the process of getting his dope.
- [John] Oh, that's why
we got this crummy detail.
- Yep, the vice boys were too busy
with a few other things, but, uh-
- yeah, they're understaffed down there.
(Tense suspenseful music)
- Can't find that pad anywhere.
- Oh my god! It's her!
- [Bates] Her who? - The killer!
- Where? - Your vampire!
- Where?
Go after her!
Well? - Did you see her?
- I didn't see nothing.
All right. You go back that way.
I'll go this way.
We'll see if we can cut her off, all right?
(Engine revving)
(Footsteps clomping)
What?
- I saw her go up that way.
- So we go up there? - Yeah.
- All right. You go up that way.
I'll go around back. All right? Go.
(Door thudding)
- The door.
- All right.
Check the rest in the backyard.
I'll check down in the basement.
- Right.
(Door creaking) (Eerie creepy music)
(Eerie suspenseful music)
(Eerie suspenseful music continues)
Oh, bates.
- [Bates] What?
- [John] Better take a look at this.
- [Bates] Yeah, all right.
- [John] All clear back there?
- [Bates] All clear.
- [John] What the,
what do you think this is?
- [Bates] I'm afraid to look.
- [John] I hope it's cranberry juice.
- [Bates] It's warm. Very warm.
- [John] Warm cranberry juice.
(Bates sniffing)
- [Bates] Blood.
- (Sniffing) Blood.
- [Bates] Yeah. - [John] Shit.
- [Bates] Looks like
someone's down a quart.
- Shit.
Let's get outta here.
- [Bates] Yeah, I'm with you.
- Check out the garage or somethin'.
(Door whirring)
What the hell is that?
- That over there is a '61 triumph.
- Nice car.
- That over there, well,
let's just say it ain't no coffin.
(Spaceship whirring)
- I've got a bad feeling about this.
(Spaceship roaring)
- [Bates] I'll be damned.
- [John] How are we gonna write this up?
- [Bates] I don't think we should.
I think this is gonna be an open case.
(Tense suspenseful music)
(Spaceship whirring)
- [Kathy] She is timeless.
This is the phenomenon
discovered by my friend,
police detective John badger.
My name is Kathy, and I am
an undercover police officer
living in Florida.
John was working on a
cut and dried murder case
when suddenly, shockingly,
all the clues pointed
to the prime suspect being a vampire.
His discoveries were fantastic,
and became even more
outrageous when he suggested
that this race of beautiful
blood suckers hailed from space.
John and his partner were
on the verge of discovering
the vampire's lair when they witnessed
a remarkable and horrifying site.
John has filed the case as unsolved,
not daring to report the
unbelievable things he has seen.
My instincts tell me that
this blood-thirsty vampire
has not fled the planet, but
is merely relocated to my city.
A recent rash of
unexplained murders involving
female prostitutes drained of blood
convinces me beyond a doubt.
This is my story.
(Seductive guitar music)
- [Vampire] You ready?
- Always.
(Seductive guitar music)
(Tense suspenseful music)
(Phone ringing) (Kathy groaning)
(Kathy screaming)
- Was just a dream.
Yeah. Okay, I'll be there.
Go back to sleep. I've gotta go to work.
- Every day, same shit.
Every day.
- It's my job.
- Then do your fuckin' job.
- [Kathy] Okay. Be unreasonable.
(Upbeat rock music)
- Who called you in?
- It's my case.
- You know, if the captain, he sees you,
he's going to suspend you.
- Well, let me deal with that, all right?
- [Detective] Another rug muncher.
- Oh, really interesting. Rug munching.
(Soft suspenseful music)
- And what the fuck is this?
- A murder.
- No, shit for brains. Kathy, outside.
You took a shot at detective
Carlos the other day.
- I know. It was dark.
It was an accident.
- I don't know what's going on with you,
but I know that it started
with unsolved murders.
Kathy, Kathy, go home.
(Upbeat rock music)
(Tense suspenseful music)
- Son of a bitch.
Ugh, no way.
Joe, she's a vampire.
- Great. Who's the vampire?
- The killer.
Well, she's a vampire.
At least she thinks she is.
- And I'm a leprechaun
knocking around never never land.
- Come on, get serious.
I'm talking for real.
- Get off the pipe.
- Look, I'm gonna catch
this bitch with or without you.
- Well, have fun.
Try not to get bit.
- Asshole.
(Upbeat rock music)
(Soft dramatic synth music)
(Soft dramatic synth music continues)
- So what's your name anyway, honey?
- Liette. What's yours?
- Cindy.
- I charged by the hour, Cindy.
- Well, don't worry about it, liette.
I have plenty of money.
(Soft dramatic synth music)
Ooh, you like to play rough, don't you?
(Tense suspenseful music)
(Upbeat rock music)
- [Kathy] Thought you
went to go find yourself
and clear your head or something?
- What's this shit?
- It's for work.
- What are you doing?
- I'm working on a case.
- "A living vampire." What is this shit?
- I told you, I'm working on a case.
"The book of nod."
- What are you being an asshole for?
- An asshole? You're being weird.
- No, I'm just doing my job.
- Well, I'll let you work.
(Upbeat rock music)
(Bluesy guitar music)
- What you want, baby?
- I don't know.
- Do not tell me this is your first time.
- Yeah, it is.
Stop. I can't do this.
- Slow down, baby.
Relax.
Not so bad, was it?
(Upbeat rock music)
(Tense suspenseful music)
- Where have you been?
- [Kathy] You creep.
What are you doing here?
- I live here.
- It's been a long night.
I really don't feel like fighting.
- The hotel called.
You left your wedding
ring in one of their rooms.
- I'll pick it up later.
- What was his name?
- Who?
- The guy you fucked last night.
- Wasn't a guy. Was a girl.
- You fucked a chick?
- Happened last night.
Guess you could say I'm bisexual.
- When did this shit happen?
- I've always felt this way.
I just couldn't tell you.
Happened last night.
Maybe if you're nice, I'll
let you join in next time.
- What? I'm not good enough.
- I didn't say that.
- Well, I'd better get outta
here before I say something
I might regret.
- Todd, wait a minute.
(Upbeat rock music)
- This is nice.
(Seductive guitar music)
(Seductive guitar music continues)
(Tense suspenseful music)
- Ugh!
- Don't fight me. You can't win.
You have a gun?
Guns can't hurt me.
- Oh, I've got something for you.
Ugh!
- I'm blind!
I am 200 years old.
Do you think someone
hasn't tried to throw holy water
in my face before?
- This will be the last time!
(Kathy screaming)
(Hammer pounding)
I win.
(Upbeat rock music)
Hi, Todd.
Yeah, sure you can come on over.
We'll have a bite. (Chuckling)
(Spaceship roaring)
(Dramatic suspenseful music)