Egypt. Temples and pyramids
recall the pharaoh's will-
- the brilliance of his architects
and the toil of his subjects.
It was a time when anything
could happen, and it did.
It was the age of
gods and demigods.
It was a time of death.
The valley was once green and fertile-
- but that was before
Im-La-Ra, Set's left hand, arrived.
With him came chaos.
It was also a time when man tried
to seek help from higher powers.
But Pharaoh's priests eventually learned
to defend themselves against the beast.
Whoever had Ra's
amulet must protect it…
...and strike at the heart of evil.
The demigod was not omnipotent.
He too was under Ra's rules.
There are always men
who prefer power to honor.
And Im-La-Ra used those men.
He tormented their bodies
as well as their souls.
The people sent their fiery
arrows under the light of the sun.
The beast was caught.
The small but mighty
amulet of Ra was blessed.
It protected them in the
ritual, but it must be buried.
When the amulet disappeared-
-so did Im-La-Ra.
Translation: Markus Svensson
www.broadcasttext.com.
PRESENT
- Forgive me for being late.
- You didn't miss anything.
- I have your stuff.
- Good. Then we'll go.
Do you really want to get
rid of your entire collection?
Much of the best is not found.
We'll do it next time.
We've already
searched a dozen times.
Three dozen!
I've been standing in the sand for two
years, and now you want to go to the beach.
- Now you are an expert.
- On what?
Finding things
buried in the sand.
But everything I find in the
sand turns out to be dangerous.
Mark, why don't you
ever talk about Iraq?
It just is.
A lot happened there
that you want to forget.
Things that change you.
- That's why I don't talk about it.
- Shall we drive, C.B.?
Very few got to call him that.
Maybe the recording director.
The producer, the big
stars, the photographer...
Everyone else called him Mr. DeMille.
Otherwise, you had to work
with western films at Republic.
With a manure shovel in one
hand and a bucket in the other.
They called it horse hockey.
One of my favorite anecdotes, Grandpa.
- Are you ready, Mr. DeMille?
- Absolutely, C.B.
How do you get this going?
- No...
- Give it to me.
I don't want to watch sports.
It's boring.
Time has stood still
in DeMille's Lost City.
The filming location is to be
excavated by Dr. Alice Carter-
- who is married to
archaeologist Jesse Carter.
Carter will excavate
and preserve this sight.
Is that your wife?
- Are you married? How stupid I am.
- We are about to separate.
- You lied!
- I'm just going to sign the papers.
I am dropping your course. If
you fail me, I'll go to the dean.
You are overreacting.
No, Alice, I'm the one
exploiting the media.
EXCAVATION
GUADALUPE IN CALIFORNIA
Here is the box. Jamie!
Jamie!
- Hang up...
- Where's Meagan with the box?
Jamie, will you marry me?
I think it's over by the water.
It looks good. Photograph and pack them-
- then we will load them
on the truck tomorrow.
Oh no... The old man is back.
He has some action hero with him.
He is sexy.
Don't forget you are single.
I can't have two newbies digging.
The students are bad enough.
But you haven't
found the good stuff.
- Sorry, what did you say?
- The throne room, the pharaoh's gate...
- It's still buried.
- How do you know that?
I have said that I
was here as a child.
- Where is it, then?
- Let Mark and I look...
...then you'll get the good stuff.
He's the only one who still knows.
What do you say, Dr. Carter?
- Say Alice.
- Okay, Alice.
We promise not to
destroy any relics.
- It's not a real excavation.
- You're not a real student.
- It is nice to work with you.
- Stop whining!
Show where you intend to look.
Shall we settle for today?
Give me ten more minutes.
This is where we've
looked the least so far.
- I promise we are close now.
- That sounds familiar.
That's what you said when I
dug up the license plate too.
- Are you in a hurry somewhere?
- No...
Now show some backbone.
Just give me ten more minutes.
Are you sure you didn't just dream
that you buried it in the desert?
That kind of talk is…
Perfect... I guess I'll have
to dig up another hubcap.
Could you please come?
The hole does not dig itself.
I told you it was here.
For 19 years, 3 months and 4
days I've been looking for that-
-and it has been buried for 80 years.
The best memories of
my life are in that box.
Are you going to open it?
It's incredible.
Grandfather!
Get me out of here!
Fast!
Help!
- Call an ambulance!
- The stories are true...
The doctor is on his way. Stay with me.
Reverse!
Where is the rest of me?
Ronald Reagan said it
in the movie "King's Row".
He looked for his leg.
Get an ambulance here!
One two three four five.
Grandfather, stay with me!
Come on now!
You couldn't have done anything.
His heart could not
handle the strain.
Do you know what might
have happened to the arm?
No.
We found some boards with nails in them.
They belong to the filming.
Maybe he got stuck on one.
- Can you tear the arm off on a nail?
- I said maybe.
It's obviously an accident.
Our movie star governor
wants us to be cooperative.
Hollywood is interested
in what you do here.
So I won't close the dig,
but don't let in any newbies.
- Okay?
- Obvious. Thanks.
I found this one.
It probably belongs to you now.
I am really sorry.
My grandfather was
really obsessed with this.
DeMille's Lost City was the
only thing he talked about.
When I got home from Iraq,
he kept talking about it as usual.
- Were you in Iraq?
- For two years.
I've seen people disappear
into the sand before.
But this was unnatural.
- I shouldn't have let you dig.
- It wasn't your fault, Dr. Carter...
Sorry - Alice.
- We had dug even without permission.
- It feels safe to hear...
Surely it is beautiful?
It should protect against evil spirits.
It doesn't seem to work right away.
I don't suppose so.
I heard the water
is coming here soon.
I have two weeks to move
things before they disappear.
The oil companies have built a canal
so that the ships can reach the refineries.
Are you moving an entire
location in less than two weeks?
- I had hoped to be able to do it.
- I'm used to that sort of thing.
- What do you mean?
- I was a logistician in Iraq.
I made sure that soldiers and
equipment arrived in time for the battles.
- Do you want a job?
- As a truck driver?
I need a coordinator.
I do not know...
I need someone with your background
to move everything. Are you interested?
This meant everything to my grandfather.
And I intend to find out what
happened to him, so yes, I want to.
When do we start?
I guess you want to go to…
- Hello, Mrs. Carter.
- Jesse, what are you doing here?
Am I Disturbing?
- No, I was still on my way.
- You don't have to go.
I thought to clear my mind anyway.
Be careful.
- A new friend?
- His grandfather just died here.
- Sorry, I didn't know that.
- It is okay.
What are you doing here?
Do you do something like this
without calling your spouse?
Former husband.
- I haven't signed the papers.
- I don't have time with you anymore.
I need you. I can't just throw
four years of my life away.
You just need an assistant.
You hate that we are equals now.
What I did was wrong. But I don't
want to just throw my marriage away.
It's not your
marriage, it's ours.
You have no place for me in your life.
I must go.
I came to help you move
"The Ten Commandments".
- I don't need your help.
- You're still angry.
I have heard of the water.
- You can't handle it.
- Do not worry.
I just want to help. I know a lot
about "The Ten Commandments".
- Yes, especially the one about infidelity.
-  Touché.
Dr. Carter, you have no
idea what we've found!
It's much bigger than I thought.
Grandpa was right.
- I dug in the wrong place.
- Now you need all the help you can get.
Doc? This looks real.
- What do you mean?
- This face...
- ...appears to be from the Middle Kingdom.
- I want to check.
I hate you!
What the hell...?
Tommy!
Stay!
- Oh my God!
- Tommy!
It's terrible, but if we stop
for a day, we won't have time.
Stop for today.
I already have too few people.
I'll send a constable
tomorrow morning.
You can probably continue
working at lunchtime - if it's safe.
Certainly. Thanks.
I didn't say anything in front of the
sheriff, but I got a strange feeling.
It hasn't happened since
we patrolled outside Samara.
It's just a mixture
of wood and plaster.
And three people
have died in two days.
What are the odds
that it's a coincidence?
- I hate this.
- What?
We shouldn't be here
considering what happened…
...Tommy and the others.
I think Carter is right.
If we focus on the job,
we'll get through this.
I guess so.
I just got a weird feeling that I
haven't been able to get rid of.
Meagan...
When I'm done with this round,
we'll be done for tonight. Okay?
Hello, little shard.
People have died to
get you off the ground.
We'll see what you have to say.
Item 312.
Part of one of the 21 sphinxes
along the road to Ramses' Gate.
The plaster is the same as
the standard used in the 1920s.
The object has suffered only
minor erosion and minimal abrasion.
Have you heard from Jamie? Keep calling.
Jimmy will be here in a little while.
Nine of your students rush
all the artifacts to location B.
We have two trucks running.
- What do we do now?
- Removes the sand from the entrance.
I was joking. I will measure
our position using the mountains.
I have already measured. Give me a
topographical map and we'll be home.
It is a bit more complicated in archaeology.
- Right?
You have saved us
half a working day.
Don't worry - I know
how dunes work.
I have dug up countless bunkers.
I have become an expert at it.
We are through.
Do you feel the cold air?
- We must preserve the place.
- Now it's just easier to ship.
- I'll take it carefully.
- Where did you study?
Fort Riley in Kansas.
Next time maybe you can take pictures?
Can you guys stop arguing?
- Here we have it.
- Everything looks so authentic.
I understand that people are fooled.
It's hard to believe
it's made in Hollywood.
- You don't think DeMille...
- ...picked it up in Cairo, do you?
I do not know.
He was a wealthy cosmopolitan.
He traveled around and found items.
Hearst Castle
is full of antiques.
- Like "Citizen Kane".
- I've never seen it.
- Rosebud is the sledge.
- Where did they get all this?
Well, what did your great
grandfather do for Cecil B. DeMille?
He was a producer.
And so he led expeditions
around the world.
We would never have
found this if you hadn't come.
We will probably need the snorkels anyway.
- Not if we hurry.
- If there are many of us, it will be done in a week.
Alice, did you do well?
- Did you see it?
- No.
Just the floor coming at me.
Whatever it was, it was already here.
What are you talking about?
There is only one way in.
Help!
- What happened?
- I saw it.
It had a face like a dog.
- It swirled around Meagan.
- What then "face"?
A cloud of sand came out of the opening,
and the head resembled a Doberman.
I heard whispers, and
then it disappeared.
My arm felt like it was on fire.
No problem.
- I don't get it.
- What?
The hieroglyphs.
They are not right. It's like a riddle.
- Look at the angles.
- They probably found it on a postcard.
It's weird.
The walls look incredibly authentic.
But they completely lack logic.
Well, Jesse, there is.
It is written as a code.
Can you read backwards?
Now I see it.
I've seen this sort of thing before in
occult texts from the Middle Kingdom.
It's like a spell.
This chamber has
a different purpose.
How?
This refers to an avenger.
Here it says to tie-
-or maybe get tied up.
- What are you talking about?
- This room...
...was built to hold something inside.
So my grandfather fell into a
trap for some kind of ghost?
If you believe in this sort of thing, something
has been trapped here for a long time.
But why do they lock something up
here with a big warning sign outside?
It basically said,
"Stay away, or else..."
What?
There is no literal translation.
"...are you drowning in
the sands of oblivion."
Don't we know an expert who
has written a book on the subject?
He's already here.
You are supposed to represent scientists,
but you are more like UFO hunters.
When a statue jumps on
you, one's worldview changes.
Good point.
My grandfather used to tell stories
of people who had died during filming.
- What do you mean?
- To scare curious children.
But now I don't know anymore.
- Scare?
- Yes...
From what I remember, people
saw things that weren't really there.
There were a lot of
strange fatal accidents.
We've had a lot
of freak accidents.
Jesse, what are you doing?
We need to move this
as quickly as possible.
- What is it?
- This is not a stage.
At least not now anymore.
It's a prison cell.
And we just unlocked it.
- Why did they choose this place?
- They didn't.
It was included in the project.
The financier owns the
land and lets us use it.
The idea was that we
would store everything here.
It would serve as a rallying
point until we were done.
Now Dr. Carter wants to
build everything up here.
It's so remote.
But it is beautiful.
Yes, but the humidity
seems to destroy the material.
At least there won't
be a flood here.
It's just weird…
...that Jamie stuck like that.
You don't think she stung, do you?
After what happened to Tommy and John?
Look at your arm! Something killed her!
Or took her or something.
Don't cry now.
Sorry, Meagan.
It's just so scary.
I know.
Sorry.
You are not alone in being afraid.
We should have stopped digging when Tommy…
I met his mother at
the hotel this morning.
- She picked up his things.
- Tommy's mother?
They take him to New
Jersey for the funeral.
That sounds reasonable.
They have come a long way now.
We'll be done soon.
Now we go back
and help them load.
- It's moving forward for you.
- So far.
It's nice to have a big
and strong soldier with us.
- I'm waiting in the car.
- Thanks, Jesse.
- For what?
- Now I remember why I left you.
I've read some of the
text, and it's not nice.
It tells of a spirit that takes revenge
on those who raid the Pharaoh's tomb.
- What is the name of this spirit?
- Im-La-Ra.
- Set's left hand.
- God of Chaos?
He turns water into sand, crops
into dust, and life into death.
- You look worried.
- If my translation is correct...
...so we have released Egypt's
old plagues in the 21st century.
Mark and I are checking the DeMille
archives. You stay and lead the work.
- What do you want to find?
- There must be something in the archive.
- Are you going to break in?
- Maybe. Don't you like adventure?
LOCATION B SANTA
MARIA IN CALIFORNIA
I've dumped a load at the beach.
Was it something else?
No. See you tomorrow.
Bye, Meg.
Meagan? Is everything
good? What did you say?
My car...
Hello? Hello?
Where are you?
Sorry.
You're not hurt, are you? Hello?
Here we have it.
His sanctuary and studio.
The archives have been
here for almost 40 years.
Shall we kick in the door?
We'll wait on that, Rambo.
- We don't want to wake Nigel.
- Who is Nigel?
I worked here for a while.
- He showed where the key was.
- So practical.
- What are you looking for?
- Specifications, invoices...
All that can tell what they took
from Egypt and buried in the sand.
- I wonder what it fetches on Ebay.
- Here we have something.
Listen: "Brother Tristan
urges me to bury everything."
"It's hidden in one of the items.
We can't risk anything."
- "Cecil B. DeMille."
- To?
Lionel Barrington. I've seen
this before but didn't get it.
Here's more. They went to Cairo-
- bought hundreds of artifacts
and shipped them here.
- Your great-grandfather was there.
- Did he bring a mummy here?
There was more to ancient
Egypt than mummies and pyramids.
The old priests could
gain power over the spirits.
Good to hear.
I didn't hit that hard.
Did it go well?
I'll probably survive unfortunately.
You snuck in.
Nigel Barrington,
former Air Force pilot.
I was in "The Bridge
over the River Kwai".
I learned a few tricks from them.
I told you what we do here.
It's still burglary.
You can be reported for this.
I didn't want to wake you up.
- This is Mark Tevis.
- I know who he is.
Your grandfather and I were friends.
But it was a long time ago.
Is it a real Maltese Falcon?
It is a replica.
Or?
You must have read father's letter. You
want to know what we took from Egypt.
- Were you there too?
- I was just a boy.
Like your grandfather, Mr. Tevis.
My father researched
shooting locations.
He suggested Guadalupe,
where you are now digging.
Tell me more.
I can show you instead.
Keep an eye on the spaces!
- Shall we weld them on?
- We have to see that they are in order.
- We only have a few hours.
- Why is there such a hurry?
If I told you, you
would run from here.
There is a message on the
panels that I must translate tonight.
Does this have anything to do with Meagan?
Yes.
Freemason...
Lord Carnarvon's group found
Tutankhamun's tomb in November 1921.
DeMille's film was
still in pre-production.
Given the excavation, it
was difficult to record in Egypt.
Besides, it would have cost too much.
In the end, DeMille succumbed
to pressure from investors.
Wait. The studio wonders-
- why it takes two weeks to film
an eighth of a page of the script.
Remember that eighth of a page?
I don't memorize the scripts. But
Mr. DeMille always thinks about the budget.
- Is this movie different?
- I thought you noted the line.
Tell. How's the line going?
"After persuading Pharaoh,
Moses led his people out of Egypt."
- Holy Toledo...
- It's actually Ramses II's city.
Now I know what 15 mil timber looks like.
- That was a good guess.
- I'm the one who pays the bills.
If every meter of timber is not
used, someone's ears will get hot.
Then take me to Mr. DeMille.
I want a thousand Israelites at…
Ira!
How was the train ride from Manhattan?
I have never been in the desert, but
now I understand the exodus from Egypt.
How fitting that you are here today.
Pharaoh's legions
await my orders.
Mr. DeMille, the delays
risk sinking the studio.
I can stop recording and call the
movie "The Five Commandments".
Don't worry - people all over
the world will want to see the film.
For 15 cents a ticket
we will be millionaires.
Besides, we'll be done tomorrow.
Come on! Now we free your people.
Listen carefully.
We have valuable stuff in the tents-
-and nothing must disappear.
We have an important scene
tomorrow, so everything has to be here.
If you fall asleep, you will be fired.
What are you waiting for? Speed ​​up.
No brains - just muscles.
Hello, sweetie.
O'Neal!
- It was hell then.
- You can't be there!
Damn.
I see you.
You picked the wrong guy to fuck with.
Lord Carnarvon was not alone
in searching for missing graves.
DeMille's men found diggers
who were actually grave robbers.
Unbeknownst to DeMille-
- the smugglers sold them priceless
antiquities of mysterious origin.
What I am about to tell is
denied by both countries.
Further up the Nile,
at today's Abu Simbel-
- there is an old city whose ruins can
be compared to those of the Giza plateau.
It is buried under the
sands of the Sahara.
Among other things, there
is an inverted pyramid here.
An antipyramid.
A hole in the ground which, according
to some, emits negative energy.
- Where did the artifacts come from?
- Yes.
It was rumored on the set that the
city was the entrance to the Duat-
- the kingdom of the dead of
the Egyptians, what we call hell.
It was one of the items we
found in the throne room.
The room was commissioned by
DeMille, to enclose the objects' powers.
- An underground vault.
- Who could build such a tomb?
Constructors of the Pyramids.
A brotherhood that created the
oldest of cities and Solomon's temple.
- Which ones?
- The Freemasons.
The angle hook, the fit
and the all-seeing eye.
- So DeMille...
- ...was a Freemason.
Lodge 16 in New York.
The rest is unfortunately
shrouded in obscurity.
Cody...
Take the sand fleas out to Guadalupe.
I've found Patrick's jeep.
Hello...
It's dangerous to be here.
Has something happened?
Get out of my mind!
Did you come up with something?
No not yet.
I started to feel quite queasy.
- Can you turn around?
- Sure.
But my testosterone protests.
I thought Nigel was
going to call the police.
Me too. It was nice
to lend the documents.
He knows I take care of them.
I hope they can give us answers.
Yes...
I liked you better sunkig.
- But you're pretty now too.
- Who is this boy?
Hang up... It's my grandfather...
...with his father.
- Moses, go ahead.
- Sorry?
Certainly.
Lord, we...
Bless this earth and watch
over it so that this boy...
...can bury his treasure chest.
- Time capsule.
- Time capsule?
Where did you get that from?
May someone one day find these things…
...and become rich like a king.
Or pharaoh.
So this is where my actors are.
What are you burying, young man?
- A time capsule.
- I don't do that.
Why don't you bury
it at home instead?
It's dark when I get home.
And I don't have Moses there.
Johnny...
And this is a special place.
In a thousand years someone
will find it and see how we lived.
Thousand years...
I have some things I like
to hide for a thousand years.
Carry on, young man.
"And a little boy herds them."
- And that's DeMille?
- Absolutely.
Where's that
damned thing, Cully?
I don't know, C.B.
I told them to bury everything.
What a waste to bury
all the treasures like this.
Now at least we close the danger.
- Shall we put up a warning sign?
- No, why draw attention to it?
Only a fool would apply here.
We could build a hundred
houses with the lumber-
- but we can't
afford to let it go.
The sands of Guadalupe
may keep our little secret.
See you in Culver City.
Johnny!
This casket...
It looks like the casket he buried.
They didn't know what they had.
It is the same.
Yes it is.
- Have you ordered anything?
- No.
- What has happened?
- I have to see the amulet.
- Your face is burnt.
- Come in and sit down.
- Do not interfere!
- I just want to help.
- You have it, right?
- No, I have it.
- Why do you want it?
- What do I gain by telling?
- Calm down.
- Stay away from my wife!
- Help me!
- Shut up!
You like her, right?
She's really cute.
- Answer!
- Yes, I like her.
Now we'll see how much.
Give me the amulet.
Okay. As long as you don't hurt her.
- He is coming.
- Who then?
Who do you think?
That thing you and your
grandfather unleashed. The Avenger.
You haven't looked into his eyes.
He hasn't been in your brain.
I have seen him.
He really exists.
Remember I don't believe in God?
He is here.
And the amulet is to him
like garlic to a vampire.
- No!
- I made a deal with him.
If I destroy the amulet,
he will let me live.
I needed to make sure.
- What's that?
- He followed me here.
- We have to knit!
- Give me the amulet!
Now!
- Drive!
- I will!
- You got rid of them.
- When you are chased by such insects...
- ...you have no choice.
- Did you see Jesse's face?
The face above the hand that
threatened you with a knife? I saw it.
It wasn't him.
I saw it in his eyes.
- He tried to kill us.
- Can you stay? I feel sick.
Think Jesse would do something like that.
You said it wasn't him.
Something has happened to him.
It must have something to do with this one.
- Is that supposed to protect us?
- Yes.
The creature wants
to destroy or use it.
What is this avenger?
One of the guardians who take
revenge on the grave robbers.
And we released it?
Buford might have some artillery.
Artillery? Buford?
That sounds like jarhead talk.
Now we take it easy. Time-out.
Your ex might get away with
it, but you should know better.
"Jarhead" refers to the Marine Corps.
But I was in the army.
You can call me
G.I., basse or soldier.
Sorry, soldier.
I'm sorry if I hurt anyone
in the Marine Corps.
- I greet them.
- Thanks.
It might be worth knowing
that Buford is a bit special.
- Okay?
- My other friends are not like him.
I'm so glad you called.
I was watching that monster channel,
and after about a dozen beers...
- ...it gets pretty shady.
- I know.
Doc and I need some stuff.
- Take what you need.
- Are you a doctor?
- Archaeologist.
- Perfect. I can't find mine.
I can only sit for four hours at a
time. I have a mark on my butt...
I am not a doctor.
I am an academic doctor.
Damn. I had hoped not
to have to go to the doctor.
They have forms
that are one page long.
But I understand you. Did
Mark tell you I was in Grenada?
You, Buford?
You have improved your range.
I take what I come across.
That's right, I almost forgot:
I have some Willie Peter.
- Seriously?
- Willie Peter?
Yes, but don't say anything. The authorities
have been and talked to my neighbors.
I'd love to have it handy...
...when doomsday comes.
- I'd love to have some Willie Peter.
- Take it for yourself.
Priscilla brings a
whole box from Idaho.
One more thing: Do you
have any rocket launchers?
Under the teddy bear.
- Who is Willie Peter?
- Willie Petey is white phosphorus.
It makes napalm look like sunscreen.
I tested a little on national day.
You should have seen it.
Okay, Buf. Now I am ready.
What do I owe you?
Well, I guess...
...that we can agree on something.
Take it easy now.
We've found most of it,
so take what you need.
Do you want me to come with you?
No.
- Some things a man must do alone.
- I understand exactly what you mean.
Nothing tells you what
kind of man you are-
-like when you stand up for something.
- Time passes.
- I know. Will you help me carry?
We've certainly had visitors.
Damn.
We probably won't get anywhere.
The car is broken.
- What has happened?
- Jesse has happened.
Has anyone trespassed?
Ninja and Buttercup
will get for not scolding.
Buford! This garbage
doesn't carry itself out.
Into the house, woman!
Download Moses and My Flip-Flops.
I will beat the rudeness out of you.
- You get along as usual...
- You have no idea.
- Do those cars work?
- This morning they did.
Choose which one you want.
Thank you, Buford. See you soon.
The garbage is out.
- What are you doing?
- I will be back soon.
Don't hurt him. He's just sick.
I'll remember that
when he wants to kill me.
Is the soldier ready
for the second round?
I should have stamped
you with my license plate.
- I'll have to do it next time.
- Then it's too late.
- Be careful.
- "Be careful."
It's a miracle
we've been married.
We can help you.
Help me?
Just give me the amulet and shut up.
Do you want the amulet?
You get it if you drop her.
So noble. No thanks.
I am a traditional husband.
Death may do us part.
Alice will be a present
for my new boss.
Take it easy.
Release her if you want the amulet.
Do not move. Otherwise, you will
soon find your thoughts on the car there.
- Give me the rifle.
- Be careful.
Mark, tell your friend
to show some respect.
The guests of honor have arrived.
Are they snakes?
You will kill us all!
Ground!
What the hell...?
You and your stupid friends and…
I probably pissed myself.
Don't tell anyone.
Run and save your girlfriend!
You always show up
when something happens.
But this time I'm ready.
Your new boyfriend is enterprising.
We'll have some company.
If they make it to the
dunes, we'll drop them!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Look!
Our ruler is here to get us!
Now he belongs to history.
It's the only thing
he's ever loved.
No... He already died when
that thing got hold of him.
I don't understand that he is dead.
It will be alright. Look at me.
Do not think about it.
Oops.
- How is it?
- We have to wait for the X-rays.
How are you?
I didn't want to miss this.
- You have the amulet, right?
- It is here.
- I had it.
- You must have lost it.
Where!
That's right.
Im-La-Ra, Set's left hand.
- Do you have any ideas?
- Not directly.
- You said the amulet protects.
- We have to take it back.
Look!
- What is he doing?
- He doesn't want to go in.
So this is like a fort.
- Like the Alamo.
- The lost.
How about Fort Knox?
If he's afraid of the
hieroglyphs, it's okay, right?
I think he's more enterprising than that.
- He doesn't need to come in.
- It's not true.
Get the grenades!
Nigel!
Hello!
I am sick of you!
Hello! Come on!
- Which end do you shoot with?
- Come on!
Do you want a cookie? Come then.
Come and take me.
Rocket Launcher! The explosive!
I have the amulet!
It's not a toy.
Come on. Hold it. He doesn't
want anyone to use it against him.
What are you doing?
Do you want it? You are welcome.
I hope you have sunscreen.
Did you know he
would melt into glass?
Willie Peter and I have known
each other for a long time.
Nigel?
I don't think he made it.
Take it easy.
The rumor of my death, etc.
I almost thought
it was out with us.
Finally the cavalry arrives.
The cavalry?
I guess they are Freemasons.
My brothers from the lodge in Hollywood.
This time we'll probably use a
little extra concrete just to be safe.
And maybe a little lead.
Don't make up nonsense now!
That was incredible.
There is one more thing
I must do before we part.
What?
We have enough time for
one more thing before we part.