That's good whiskey
you're wasting.
Been away a few days, Tom.
How'd you find me, Ranger?
Hound got your scent
back at the ranch.
Shit, I smelled you
from miles away.
Who am I supposed
to have pissed off anyhow?
Hey, you done violated
the conditions of your parole.
Like hell I did.
Assault, brandishing
a firearm in a public place.
You stole a horse, rifle,
whiskey from your employer.
You want me to go on?
That's my rifle.
What business do you have
with a 10,000-dollar
plains rifle, Tom?
Oh, saddle up son.
You're done.
Try to run, I'll kill ya.
Hunting to feed
my family, Ranger.
Too bad it ain't
hunting season.
And you're just
more trash
from Terlingua County
like me, Tom.
Stop pretending
to be what you ain't.
Tyree, you got your ears on,
buddy? Where you at, partner?
About 15 miles south
of Manse Point
over Alkali Flats.
Just picked up Tom
that stole a horse and rifle
and beat Joe Hansons.
What can I do for you, Elmer?
10-65, old Mutual Bank
over here in Mount Verde
got themselves held up
about a half hour ago.
Four heavily armed gunmen
driving one of them
off-road type rigs
came in raising
all manners of hell.
Got a 10-99 code on it.
Killed three officers.
Even put old Ben Copper's boy
in the ER,
so figured they'd be heading
your direction there, Alex.
Watch your six, buddy.
10-22, subjects are armed
with automatic weapons.
At present, no other units
are available to assist you.
10-24, we got eyes
on that 10-80.
Avenue J, outside of El Paso.
We are currently in pursuit.
10-22, to confirm,
four subjects carrying AK-47s.
Left on Avenue 245.
Whoo, they're coming in hot.
Watch it, watch it.
Ooh, this sumbitch is flying.
Come on, man,
you gonna lose 'em.
10-22, we have a chopper inbound.
ETA: 17 minutes.
Let's go. Gas, gas, gas!
Let's go!
10-24, we lost 'em.
They're heading
southbound on Terlingua.
Shit.
10-22 has broken pursuit.
Suspects were last seen headed
southbound on Terlingua Street.
One suspect has left
the vehicle.
We are going to engage.
"And there before me
was a white horse.
Its rider was named Death
and Hell...
- ...so close behind Devil."
- Shit! Gun! Get out now!
10-22,
this is 10-24. Come in.
Are you engaging the suspects?
Shane, if you're there,
answer me.
They'll make the border
before the state police
have a chopper off the ground.
Yeah, wish I was with them.
Creaky bastard like you
creeping up
on a full-blood Tonkawa.
Spot me.
Mexican police
ain't got a unit close enough
to intercede.
These boys should be considered
extremely dangerous
there, partner.
Proceed with caution
now, Tyree.
Hah. You gonna
shoot out their tires?
It's half a mile away, Ranger.
You're a good shot,
but that's impossible.
That's six feet high.
Jesus, Alex.
Goddamn! That's some
shooting there, Ranger.
What happened?
What the fuck happened?
Shattered the block
and killed the engine.
Takes a big round to do that.
Save your ammo!
You're not getting
a shot at that range.
Are they shootin' at us?
We shot at him,
so he shot back,
you dumb fuck.
I'm leaving you, Tom.
You look after the horses,
but know this,
I care more about
that horse than I do you.
I'll fire, you run,
then you cover me as I run.
Let's fucking go.
Agh! Fuck.
Agh, fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Alex.
He's a wanted criminal, asshole.
I don't care
if he lives or dies.
Thanks a lot, brother man.
You got me.
Damn! Have I saw
a shooting like that before.
Radio call said there
were four men, Ranger.
You gonna go
after the other guy?
Yeah, that other one
won't get far on his own.
Now you'll be letting me go,
huh, Ranger?
You going to jail, Tom.
I did suggest he knock first.
He was concerned since you
weren't answering your phone.
That man is Special Agent
Derby of the FBI.
British Intelligence.
I take it you're
Ranger Alex Tyree?
Major Edwards said
we could find you here.
We'd like to come in
for a chat, if that's okay.
You all right?
Give me two minutes.
British Intelligence?
We're here with the approval
of your State Department.
Special agent Derby
was tasked with making sure
I didn't get into trouble.
Well, he's lucky I didn't
shoot him through the door.
You have a lot
of enemies, Ranger?
I put people in jail.
They tend to take
offense to that.
I realize you have
a different way
of handling things here, Ranger.
And it can be quite
difficult to grasp
from a desk in London, but...
we're very aware of the elite
investigative skills
of the Texas Rangers,
and we know what you do works.
We're not some cowboy
operation, Agent Smith.
We go by the book,
just like they do in London.
I'm here because
Major Edwards said
you're the best ranger
he's ever seen,
so I've been sent to ask you
to go into Mexico
and collect a prisoner.
Federales won't allow
an official British
or US extraction,
but unofficially,
they've asked for you.
You'll be there
as a private citizen.
If anything goes wrong,
our association will be
basically deniable
in every conceivable way.
It's been nice meeting you,
Agent Smith.
Excuse me?
You got the wrong moron, lady.
Crossed the border myself.
Federales laughed in my face
when I told them I was there
to extradite a prisoner.
I'm late for work.
Carmen here will see you out.
The prisoner in question
is the bank robber
who killed the three deputies
in Esperanza County.
What is he to you?
His name is Declan McBride.
Ex-provisional IRA
wanted for a string
of terrorist activities
on and off the British mainland.
He's extremely vicious
and very resourceful.
And if we don't move quick,
he will find a way
to negotiate himself out prison.
And what's an Irishman
doing robbing banks in Texas?
Well, he's gone rogue,
charging a small fee
to rob banks
and passing the proceeds
to the worst criminal
causes imaginable.
Through his old partner,
we found out he's planning
a job on the British mainland.
I'm asking you to do this
on behalf of my country.
The English agents
insulted my intelligence
by attempting
to threaten me, Alex.
I was tempted not to give him
an extradition at all,
but then I thought of you.
I remembered you helped me
with a situation
that was very delicate.
That small act
had large consequences.
It made me indebted to you.
Today I pay you back.
The simple extradition
will be now a deportation,
and the paperwork
is already filled out.
Right.
Thanks for the hospitality.
Mexico's a lovely place.
You're welcome.
I can make it
worth your while
if you drop me off here.
Save your breath, partner.
I'm sorry
about the police officers.
Genuinely am,
but I acted in the cause
of a greater good.
How much more
of this is off-road?
Less than ten miles,
we'll be at the border cross.
Twenty minutes from there
we'll be in Nuevo Laredo.
You know who led the first
successful revolution
against colonial empire?
Huh?
George fucking Washington.
See, justice is just
your perspective, Ranger.
Elements working here are far
bigger than the two of us.
You talk more than my ex-wife.
Shame
of it is, Ranger,
I think I'd have liked
going up against you.
Good to see you again, boss.
No injuries?
Only my pride, brother.
I told you, the bank robbery
was a bad idea.
Next time I'll listen.
Go get that cop.
That's our cue, Oleg.
He's seen your face.
Choose your battles.
Two faces
that warm the heart
with memories of conflict past.
We have walked through
the dark as friends.
Which is better than to walk
through the light alone.
Yuri.
Declan. You will stay.
I have food
and Ukrainian vodka.
My men are peasants
but they raid well.
Come.
We will toast to comrades lost.
It is unwise to refuse
the generosity of Cossack,
lest they change their minds.
Appreciate the invitation.
We're on the job
, brother.
So it is business.
Mm-hmm.
So, gentlemen,
Cold War
155-millimeter-long gun.
It will fire
100-pound projectile
14 miles on good day.
And on a bad day?
On bad day,
it will be the nightmare
that ends your life
before you hear the sound.
Have your men deliver
to this address.
I'll take it from there.
You know,
I worry that you will upset
many people with this toy.
I like you, Declan.
You are like brother.
But when this job is over,
then so are we.
I expected you to look worse.
You got a lot of nerve, lady.
You've every right
to be indignant.
You were ambushed,
likely set up,
but you did your job, and
thank God you're still alive.
Thank God I'm alive.
Ranger Daniels was a good man.
He was a husband, father,
and a damn fine lawman.
He was also my friend.
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
That ain't gonna cut it.
But work with me, Tyree.
Help me bring in McBride.
You've seen him close-up,
talked to him.
You know him better than
anyone else we have.
I doubt that.
You knew they were gonna try
to spring him, didn't you?
Need to get yourself
another errand boy, lady.
If I go after McBride,
it's gonna be under my terms,
with my men, and my rules.
Just sit down, please.
Ranger Tyree, please.
You got one good reason
why I should help you?
You want a reason,
I'll give you multiple reasons.
The 1993 killings
of US servicemen in Somalia.
The '98 bombings
of US embassies.
The kidnapping of 16
Western tourists in Yemen
- that same year.
- Yemen?
All executed and planned
by a man named Aden Kashmiri.
Now, we believe Kashmiri
has retained McBride's services
for a substantial fee
to cause or instigate
a terrorist event in London.
McBride working for Kashmiri
makes him the world's most
dangerous terrorist for hire.
Keep talking.
Help me track him down.
Do what you do.
Uh, the department
would have to sign off on it,
and nothing really gels
around here that efficiently,
so...
You've already talked
to the major, haven't ya?
Right.
You remind me of my dad.
He was a police detective
in London.
We're in the East End.
It used to be a rough area.
He was killed on the job
when I was 17.
Mm.
Sorry to hear that.
It was then and there I decided
to go into law enforcement.
Ah.
Switched college courses
to criminal science,
was recruited straight
out of college by MI6.
You did all right.
He'd approve.
Don't underestimate
McBride, Ranger.
Declan is a sociopathic
murderer with a genius IQ.
Misjudged him once.
Won't happen again.
I believe that.
I should ask.
Do you plan on even
remotely trying to blend in?
I guess I could lose
the hat in London.
Section Control Geddes.
Call me Chief Control
or just Geddes.
We're informal here.
- Who's "we"?
- The agency.
We who ensure the security
of the entire island nation
of Great Britain
and it's Commonwealth.
Glad you can join us.
Alex Tyree.
Nice hat, very subtle.
I'll order you one.
If you had to give a threat
assessment number out of ten,
in your opinion, where
would Declan McBride sit?
I don't rate 'em.
Just catch 'em and brand 'em.
Mm. You actually talk like that.
This asshole got away
from me once.
I'll drop the boom
on him next time.
You've been closer to him
than any living operative,
you've spoken to him
and survived.
That makes you
a temporary asset, Ranger.
McBride is in London,
and it's our responsibility
to see to it
that he doesn't leave.
Is that clear?
Yeah, I get your drift, chief.
If you do something,
anything that reflects
poorly on the agency,
asset status terminated.
You're on your own, son.
Am I crystal fucking clear?
I'm not your son.
And I'm not your fucking daddy.
Just answer
the question, cowboy.
We understand, Control.
Thank you for accommodating us.
And we will do everything
in our power
to respect the agency's wishes
and the discreet nature
of our position.
There'll be a detective
in the lobby, 7:30 a.m.
He's your liaison.
You are not permitted to move
around the city without him.
That five-peso star
affords you no more rights
than any other guest
to this city.
Agent Smith,
you're in the UK now.
Protocol is everything.
Yes, Control.
Okay. Seven and three-eighths.
My hat size.
Yeah?
Who said you could stop?
You owe me more than that,
you lazy cunt.
Always a sweet talker.
You shouldn't have left me.
You got what
shouldn't be gotten.
I need your help, Angel.
I know.
Knew it when I saw you.
Knew it when you made love.
Know it's the only reason
you're here now.
Angel...
Kid outside worships me.
I give him kale and he'll
slice you into dozen pieces
and throw you in the Thames.
Shouldn't have done
what you did to me.
Swore if I ever saw you again,
I'd fuck you back.
So this is it?
You turned on too many
old friends, me included.
Now you can leave.
Alex Tyree, you're in room 207.
Elevator's to the left.
- Thank you.
- Wanna walk off the cab ride?
As opposed to a massage?
Luke will take
any luggage for you.
Thank you, Luke.
With pleasure, sir.
Throw it on the bed.
You call this April?
Should've listened to Carmen
and wore a warmer jacket.
So you staying at the hotel?
Well, I lived in Langley
for three years.
I don't keep a place
in the UK anymore.
Stranger in your own town, huh?
Geddes wants us to work
with his babysitter
but they won't be here
till morning.
This ain't a walk
for our health, is it?
It's a long shot.
There's a potential
intelligence source.
- Taxi.
- Ah.
Her name's Angel, ex-IRA,
and she's got a real axe
to grind when it comes
to McBride.
Let's hope
she feels like talking.
Nice company
you keep, Smith.
People looking to stay
in our good grace,
you know how it is.
No, I don't. Not really.
I'm many things to many people,
and today,
I get to call in a favor.
Mm-hmm.
Long time, no see,
you British cunt.
How are you anyway,
filthy Irish trollop.
I was all right
until yous arrived
stinking up my drinking space.
Can I join you for a drink?
Or is looking at your reflection
caused you to, you know,
empty the bar already?
You brought
your girlfriend here.
Part of the States
you're from, yeah?
Texas, ma'am.
Great state of Texas.
Well, you may want to invest
in some local wardrobe.
You stand out like
a baller in sweatpants.
I know what yous want, Smith.
Hmm. Bad news travels fast.
Get outta here.
Give us some privacy,
you fucking apes.
I'm trying to have
a private conversation.
Don't screw me around, Angel.
You know me better than that.
Sit down. Sit down.
He's here in town, for sure.
You're not gonna find him
without my help.
Why should I believe anything
you have to say about him?
You're hardly
a disinterested party.
I know what you're implying,
but anything between
McBride and me died
when he took my fucking eye.
Hmm. 'Cause I heard he saved
your life after the attack
where you lost your eye.
You heard fucking wrong.
You expect me to believe
that any animosity
you have for McBride
is motivation enough
to sully your reputation?
- I want money.
- Ah.
Cash money.
Man's fucking dangerous.
So in addition, I'll be wanting
three men released.
Not parole, but released.
These lads need a clean record
to get their year citizenship.
So much harder since 9/11.
You can appreciate that,
don't you, Ranger?
You don't have anything.
I can negotiate
a visa entry.
And arrange for leniency,
customs and immigrations
in extenuating
circumstances, you see.
You have my word on it.
You'll find McBride
when you find Oleg.
Checked in two days ago.
Room 27.
Right.
Jesus.
You sure take me
to the nicest places, Smith.
Just make sure
you stay behind me.
Ahh.
McBride finds out I'm in town,
he'll go Casper on us,
which gives us hours not days.
And time is of the essence.
What is that?
They told me to leave
my .45 at home.
You are just an observer
here, Tyree.
Study shows it's a lot
more dangerous
when law enforcement are armed.
Weren't dangerous,
wouldn't need one.
You think your sweet talking
Irish friend set us up?
That's always a possibility.
Check that way.
What a rat's nest.
Football.
This is CSI Smith.
We need backup.
223 Green Street, Hackney.
We have one armed suspect.
Automatic weapon.
He has a gun.
We are receiving fire.
You should have killed me
when you had the chance,
you motherfucker.
Stop! Stop! You fucking freeze.
Don't you fucking dare. Agh!
Fuck! You okay?
Go. Go.
Hold it! Freeze!
- You all right, mate?
- Tyree,
cease fire! Civilian!
Police! Drop your gun! Now!
No! This is MCA
official business.
We're on active assignment.
Check my ID. Check it.
Technical branch
performed a digital forensic
on the cell phone
you acquired, Smith.
Belongs to Oleg Jakovenko,
McBride's second in command,
a worthy target of opportunity.
Tragic that you
let him slip away.
If Jakovenko is in London,
then McBride's nearby.
Give me access to the data,
let me find him, Control.
An arresting officer
has already gone on record
saying that someone
in a cowboy hat
fired shots at a fleeing suspect
in a crowded area.
Even allowing for certain
quaint West Texas customs,
uh, wouldn't you agree that
that was quite reckless?
Last time I saw him,
he murdered my friend
and partner, chief.
You don't forget a man
does that to you.
Give me something that I can
take to the agency executive.
Parliamentary council
is breathing down their necks.
Nobody enjoys parrying
questions from Etonians
with no concept
of field intelligence.
They're actually already talking
about a possible scapegoat.
Any reason I shouldn't
give them one?
Ranger Tyree is the only asset
that's seen Declan McBride
in person.
We're British Intelligence.
We have considerable
assets, don't we?
Use them.
Convince me that
you are the right team
for this assignment.
I need concrete evidence
that McBride is operating
on British soil.
Ad colligenda bona.
Thanks, boss.
And I will also need
a written report, Ranger Tyree,
about yesterday's action.
I wasn't sure what
I thought of you, chief.
I'm just a simple
operative like you.
Perhaps.
I'm sure we're gonna get
along very, very well, Ranger.
Mm-hmm.
Count it.
I trust you.
Don't ever trust a terrorist.
It's just... I need
the moneys, desperately.
Mm. All men are desperate
one way or another.
During the Troubles,
the British SAS,
they had a Nemesis program
where they take Republican
prisoners into the woods
and disappear them,
never to be seen again.
I'm gonna give more to your
family than the British gave us.
Join me for a drink, Ranger?
My stomach's saying breakfast,
but a drink will do.
You got family in the UK?
Scattered to the four winds.
Mr. Smith, is he American?
Oh. Mr. Smith was my father.
Spend a lot of time in hotels,
so wedding ring's a deterrent.
- Ah.
- I don't like small talk.
Yeah. Tough to have a laugh
doing what we do.
My ex-wife always wanted kids.
I was never home long enough
to seal the deal.
By the time I was ready,
she'd already left me.
Yeah, I wouldn't have
a relationship
in this line of work.
Mm.
My father left a unfixable
void when he died.
It's not fair.
What would your next step be
if we were in Texas?
Hunt him
relentlessly.
I convinced technical branch
to share the data transcript
from Oleg's phone.
We were able to trace a number.
Initiative, Smith. I like it.
Here's to that.
Thank you
for your hospitality.
They'll have more reinforcements.
We have to move!
Get to the street
and don't look back. Go.
Come on, let's have you.
The woman shot me.
Get the fuck in.
It's gonna sting.
- All right.
- Ugh.
- You're tough.
- Mm.
- There we go.
- They targeted us.
That means we've got
their attention.
Well, if he's smart,
he'll cancel whatever plans
he has and break camp.
Then we've lost him.
You need to rest this arm.
Your system's going into shock.
You'll get sleepy,
but that's okay. I'll be here.
All right, little press.
Ah.
Hm.
You did good today.
Went against him
when he had you dead to rights.
Yeah, you saved my life.
Gave, uh, them folks
a reason to run.
Probably got yourself into
a lot of trouble with Control.
That takes guts.
With that little pistol too.
Don't knock my little pistol.
I'm gonna dig us up some grub,
Shock wears off, it leaves
a hell of an appetite.
Thank you, Ranger.
Alex.
Thank you, Alex.
Don't want you coming after me
with that little
pistol of yours.
Ah. There you go.
Here. Drink will make you
feel better.
Here you go.
Reggie, bring that down
to the man.
Good boy.
I have fond memories
of our time together, Declan,
but I can't say I'm happy
about seeing you
under these circumstances.
We need to talk.
In front of the boy?
Ah, don't worry about him.
Our special, sweet-minded boy.
God chose to touch his mind.
Declan...
what you do now,
you do for the love of chaos.
It's not what you were.
We were part of something
bigger than us.
There's a certain grace
in crusading for lost causes.
I'm finished
with lost causes, doc.
Reggie, give us
a song, will you?
"The Foggy Dew." Good lad.
I thought you said
he didn't talk.
He doesn't talk,
but he does sing.
Good lad, good lad. Well done.
Angel's been talking.
Three of our men,
prisoners in Belmarsh Prison
had their sentences exonerated.
Word on the street...
diplomatic pressure from above.
If you got something to say,
then you spit it out.
You're on your own now, Declan,
everyone is turning
against you, even her.
Even your angel.
You don't know anything.
What I did for your friend
over there
is my repayment
to the debt I owe you.
When you leave here tonight,
don't ever come back.
Bingo.
Oh.
I found us some food,
if you can call it that.
Listen.
I had a friend
dig a little deeper
- on Oleg Jakovenko.
- Oh, yeah?
Sentenced to 40 years
hard labor
in Lukianivska Prison
for war crimes.
Here, you should eat something.
I don't eat pork.
He escaped with McBride
and two other prisoners,
and during the escape,
Oleg killed the two guards
who were watching McBride.
Yeah, sounds like
a real charmer.
Oh, yeah.
Interpol alert for Northern
Ireland, Libya, Iran,
Chechnya, Bosnia, Rwanda.
I mean, the list reads like
a soldier of fortune world tour.
Look, McBride's
planning something.
But why did he break cover
to kill you?
Well, he ain't special.
I bring him in,
head down over the saddle,
just like any other horse thief.
I forget that's how
you actually speak.
I had an instructor
used to tell us,
there's two types in this game.
Those on the run,
and those doing the hunting.
And, man, McBride's a man
on the run, that's all.
Hmm.
The address on the Ukrainian
cell phone could be nothing.
Wanna go look?
What could possibly
go wrong?
I'm thinking maybe
this is McBride's safe house.
We bust enough of 'em,
think it'll get us back
in good graces with Control?
Get off the phone.
Get off the fucking phone.
- And who the fuck are you?
- Ah.
- Get off the phone.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Get up.
- What are you-- Ow!
Anya, who did you call?
Fucking Tooth Fairy.
Who do you think?
- He's upstairs.
- How did you know?
Well, he's written
"Russian gangster,
Room 212" right here.
- Seriously?
- I did not fucking write that.
Sit the fuck down.
Don't fucking move.
Fucking hell.
Yes, ma'am.
Getting that déjà vu feeling.
You wanna call for backup?
Please.
Don't touch any firearms.
Did he really write
"Russian gangster"?
No. I just wanted
to see his reaction.
This is the only occupied room.
Freedom fighting is many things,
but glamorous it isn't.
Irishman's tied
a tin can to our tail.
Fuck. Fire escape?
Nah, he'd have thought of that.
So?
We got the advantage.
How's that?
He thinks he got the drop on us.
On my mother's,
I catched him.
I won't tell him a word.
I promise.
Please, they came
bowling in here.
I didn't even get
a fucking chance to speak.
They took my phone
off me and all.
Oh, God!
Have you stopped
shooting my men?
Becoming very difficult
to find gunmen.
But after these ones,
what am I gonna do?
Put your fucking hands up!
I knew you weren't dead
when I left you in desert.
I told him it was a mistake
not to finish you.
Will you
pass me a napkin, Ranger?
Something in my eye.
Why are you
with this outfit, Oleg?
Discretion is like
the calcium in my bones, Ranger.
You could help me
bring him in.
When you're in Texas, we say,
first to talk
is the first to walk.
He's waited a long time
to see this city burn.
- Stop!
- Government agent.
I got a government agent here.
You do fine, easy fellas.
One suspect.
I have an injured suspect
wearing an IED explosive vest.
We need a bomb squad here now!
Go get 'em, fellas.
An embarrassing result.
Ah, we look good together.
Uh, perhaps not
the kind of image
the agency is hoping to purvey.
Can either of you give me
a reason why I don't punish you
to the full extent
of my authority?
We except full responsibility
for the indiscretion, Control.
An explanation will be outlined
in detail in my report.
Mm-hmm.
You've had a promising
career up to now, Agent Smith.
Expert in diplomatic
protocol and procedure.
Frankly, I am shocked
by your reckless behavior.
Having said that,
evidence we recovered led us
to a nuclear scientist
with a painkiller addiction.
It seems that he sold a quantity
of high isotope
uranium 235 to McBride.
He's making a dirty bomb?
We're putting every agent
in the field.
Intel says McBride will be
ready to strike next week.
We need to get to work then.
Eleven EOD has one
of your shooters in isolation.
He was wearing a suicide vest
that failed to detonate.
Fortune favors the bold.
Drop a logistics waiver
and get over there.
Quickish.
Information on the
prisoner's family.
Tell me
about the ordinance.
Layered PD4 derivative,
detonator enveloped
inside the accelerant.
High pressure water cutter?
There's an RDX crystal
compound on the detonator,
safeguards against tampering.
I haven't seen anything this
advanced since the EOD school.
Open the security door.
I wish to talk to the prisoner.
This guy hear us
through this thing?
I can turn on two-way
for you, sir.
McBride talked you
into blowing yourself up.
What's your family
think about that?
"Every soul shall
have a taste of death."
"But only on the day
of judgment
shall you be paid in full."
You know the words?
I do.
They are just
words to you.
Gor. Gor.
How do we find Declan McBride?
You have your mission.
Mine is to protect my family.
Full diplomatic protection.
They'll be in a secure location
by tomorrow morning.
You have my word.
He's gonna do it.
I love them.
He has left.
What?
He spoke about finding
a glass skylight,
a window from a tall building.
When? Where?
Overlooking the river.
The ancient clock.
Where you don't buy hope.
Come what may.
Today is not the end of history.
No...
Oh, boy.
RDX relay
has been engaged.
You have 30 seconds
to get out of there, Smith.
Gor...
Show them where
to find my family.
Gor, can you disarm it?
Disarm it! Gor!
- Smith, get outta there.
- Gor!
The agent needs
to exit the bomb bay now.
What a waste.
Not to his way of thinking.
Delusions of grandeur.
Hebephrenic schizophrenia.
In Texas, we'd say not enough
cotton balls on a bush
to haul a full trailer
to the gin...
if you know
what I'm saying.
Eh, he thinks
he's one of his heroes.
Michael Collins.
George Washington.
Struggling against the British.
Wants fame.
Mm, it's not much use
if you're dead or in prison.
Mm, thought process
don't work like that.
McKinley's assassin bought
a pearl-handled revolver
so it would look nice
in a museum next to his photo.
It's not next week.
It's in two days.
April 24th.
The Easter Monday uprising
against the British,
April 24th, 1916.
Ancient clock. Big Ben
near Houses of Parliament.
He's gonna launch a dirty bomb.
Not bad.
But you got there 'cause
of my comment about
Michael Collins, didn't you?
Really?
In 1954, French forces
suffered a defeat so definitive
that they withdrew
all colonial forces
and quit the conflict
in Indochina.
To surprise the French,
Viet men had attacked
from mountains overlooking
the French positions,
dismantling their artillery
and carried on bicycles
on women's backs
up into the mountain.
In front of me, Mr. Kashmiri,
is a 152-millimeter Howitzer
smuggled into the country
piece by piece.
Reassembled
and aimed directly
at the House of Parliament.
You have performed your task
remarkably, Brother McBride.
Now I must ask you
to step away.
Step away?
This is the single greatest
terrorist plot since 9/11
and you're asking me
to stand down
before the command performance?
The threat is greater
than the act.
Until it is proved that
we can do what we promise,
we can negotiate our demands.
Demands?
You're just another
fucking politician.
I am Aden Kashmiri!
Your spiritual leader!
You will do as I command
and stand down, McBride.
Stand down!
The blood of the prophet
runs in me. Don't do it!
I thought you'd quit.
Killed Protestants in the name
of the Catholic faith.
Buddhists in the name of China.
Hindus in the name of Buddha.
I killed Christians
in the name of Islam,
and now they ask me to stop.
Bloody religions.
To hell, them all.
I'll drink to that.
The ranger will be coming.
Time to finish old business.
Let's go.
Chopper unit with FLIR
discovered an off-the-charts
radium deposit.
Requires at least
50 pounds of isotope
to give off a reading
that intense.
Thanks, sir.
I served in Kyrgyzstan
and Syria, Ranger.
You don't see it.
You don't smell it.
You don't hear it.
It kills absolutely
and without warning.
I am not sending
my men in there.
- But I need to go in.
- Well, you can do as you wish,
but you're gonna have to wait
until the area's evacuated.
Evacuated?
I ordered a two-mile
radius evacuated,
and when it is,
I'm hitting that building
with a JDAM explosive missile.
I need time.
We need this guy alive.
He's our only link
to Aden Kashmiri.
A JDAM missile
will take out the entire block.
Give me two rocket launchers
on the building
across the street,
and wait for my order.
I can give you
30 minutes, Smith,
and then we're hitting
the building whether
you're out or not.
Am I clear?
We need to be careful.
We don't want McBride
triggering this thing.
We'll catch him
like a rabbit.
Cage will be on him
before he knows what hit him.
I'll take care of this guy.
I'll go upstairs,
I'll wait for you.
Security building's
been breached.
By a tall piece of piss
wearing a ten-gallon hat.
Oleg will take care of it.
Move out.
Ranger.
We're getting old,
and the men we break in
are just getting younger.
I drink vodka in the morning
to ease the pain of a long life.
Is that machine gun fire
I'm hearing, Smith?
I need more time, lieutenant,
you gotta give me something.
You have 25 minutes left.
Modern ammunition
wait for no man, Ranger.
We never finished our dance.
This is ridiculous.
Look at us.
Maybe. But you took my eye.
Each time we meet,
you get the worst of it.
Beginner's luck. Ha.
Three times?
Throw in the towel, son.
Maybe I got hit in the head
too many times, Ranger.
But to get to him,
you must go through me.
Stay down, Oleg.
Not possible.
It don't need to be like this.
Fuck.
What the fuck?
You look like you've
been hit by a truck.
- I'm just an observer, Smith.
- Only that was like
the fourth fucking time.
Just need to catch my breath.
Okay, I mean, take a minute,
- but we kind of need to go.
- I'm good to go.
You sure?
- Good to go.
- Okay, take this gun.
We've got 20 minutes.
McBride is dug in
on the seventh floor.
Right.
The raw isotope has now
impregnated the explosive.
RDD is ready for
the final mission, sir.
I don't expect allegiance from
any of you when the job's done.
I'll understand if you
and your men want to cut out.
We've spoken about it,
and we stand by you.
No one else fucking has.
Not women,
family,
even friends.
Yous the only ones that have.
Well, then,
Let's get to it, shall we?
All 11 targets painted, ma'am.
Ready to engage
at your command.
You're a hundred percent sure
you can neutralize the threat?
They have not armed
the uranium device.
We can hit them now, but the
window closes if they arm it.
We are on the sixth floor,
so just keep
that fire localized.
You may wanna brace
for this, Ranger.
Smith, you need to move.
Move now.
We have two 84-millimeter
rocket launchers
ready to fire.
Fuck!
Engage the enemy, gentlemen.
Fire!
Hit it.
Hold your fucking fire.
I'm coming out.
I'm throwing my gun.
We've got him.
Declan McBride, you're not
an easy man to find.
Why don't you show me
them hands, son?
Here's two I prepared earlier.
Shoot me. We'll salute
St. Michael together.
Get on your fucking knees now.
Careful, Ranger.
Put the gun down.
You may be suicidal.
Her? Not so sure.
No matter how far
I have to track you,
whatever it takes,
I guarantee I will not quit
until you're behind bars
or six feet under.
Well, then...
Good luck to you, Ranger.
I repeat, he's on the run.
Lost sight
of McBride, Smith.
Repeat. We do not have
eyes on the target.
McBride is Charlie Foxtrot.
Orwell said
that people sleep peaceably
in their beds at night
because rough men, and
in our case, rough women,
stand ready to do violence
on their behalf.
The world owes you both
a great debt of appreciation,
and I want to thank you
on behalf of the agency.
Agent Smith, you'll
return to your unit.
Ranger Tyree, I assume
you'll be leaving us
at your earliest convenience.
Well, I am, and I will.
Happy trails.
I'll be checking my mail.
Seven and three-eighths
cattleman.
You want boots to go with it?
Just the hat, Ranger.
You're not going home,
are you, Ranger?
Ah, things...
ain't that simple.
We're done. Good guys won.
Got your payback.
When Ranger Daniels
graduated from the academy,
married his high school
sweetheart.
At their wedding,
I promised her
I'd look out for him.
That promise ended
in the dirt,
side of the road
in Laredo County, so...
I've got to make good on that.
You're going after him?
Don't reckon I have a choice.
The DEA drone
over Sinaloa, Mexico
spotted what they think
is a smuggling outfit
led by McBride.
They have me
deep in another project,
or I would be there with you.
I'll send you all
the information we have.
Good luck, Alex.
Ranger Tyree.
You come all the way
down here for me?
It's the law of the jungle
out here.
You ready to commit
to that, Ranger?
Get your boots on.
You gonna kill all of us?
Well, I'd prefer not to.
You're all on your lonesome.
I asked you to get
your boots on.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Fine.
That was foolish.
Agh!
Don't you have a life, Ranger?
There's two types
in this game, McBride.
Those on the run,
and those doing the hunting.
Dead or alive.
Your choice.
I thought so.
Tie something around that leg.
Use it as a tourniquet.
It's a long walk.
You got this covered, Ranger?
Chief.
You're gonna find a mess
of deceased smugglers
back yonder.
Once again,
I'm indebted to you.
Many people
will not think it so.
I believe a man should always
celebrate a job well done.
Ciggaro?
I like your line
of reasoning, chief.
All right.
It might be
a better arrangement
to have the Irishman
buried with his mules.
You know, I'm right here, chief.
Might just come
to that, Ignacio.
I might suggest to stay
clear out of Mexico
for a-- a decade or so.
Adios, Ranger!
And that's all
it took to take me down?
One riot, and one
fucking ranger.
Just doing my job.