(Hard rock music)
(Loud crashing)
- [Narrator] It was the time of witches.
Innocent women and men were sentenced
to death on the flimsiest of evidence.
They were condemned by the jealousy,
avarice and ignorance of their neighbors.
The wretched ones that
were burned at the stake
died protesting their innocence.
Except one, Hepzibah Crowley,
the only real witch ever burned.
Stories had circulated about Hepzibah
months before her trial.
She had been seen
lending money to wild geese,
had performed weird
rituals with whipped cream,
and was rumored to have the ability
to converse with sardines.
The outraged townspeople brought her
before judge August loon.
They presented their startling evidence,
including the testimony
of one woman who claimed
that Hepzibah had cursed her
to have two birthdays a year.
She told of the hardship
of writing thank you notes
twice a year for birthday presents.
The judge saw great
force in their arguments
and condemned Hepzibah to
be burned at the stake until dead,
and then turned over and
burned until dead on that side.
On the Eve of her
execution, judge loon himself
lit the flame to the kindling
surrounding the witch's feet.
As the flames leap up at
her, Hepzibah cried out...
(Flames crackling)
- [Hepzibah] Judge loon,
know thee by your actions
that upon this day the blackest of curses
will fall upon you and your male issue!
From this day forward, you
and all your male descendants
will live in fear of the day
when you will lose your senses.
You will never know
when the insanity will strike.
You will come to regret
the day you were born.
You will be an embarrassment
to your family and community!
I gotta bring the curse to a close now
for I am nearly consumed by flames!
(Flames crackle)
- [Narrator] Judge loon laughed
as he really didn't believe in witches.
He just liked a good bonfire.
Witch Crowley was dead.
(Solemn harpsichord music)
In a matter of weeks, judge
loon began to act strangely.
One night, as his wife sat knitting,
judge loon jumped up from his chair
and started hailing taxis
for no apparent reason.
He began accusing their
cat of reading his mail.
And finally he insisted
on watching television
before it was invented.
He was put away in an
asylum for the rest of his life.
His sons followed him there in later years,
but not before marrying and
siring many sons of their own.
In spite of the coincidences,
the loon family refused
to believe they were victims of a curse.
And subsequently, the curse itself
was lost in family history.
(Solemn harpsichord music)
(Somber instrumental music)
(Tense instrumental music)
(Suspenseful instrumental music)
(Equivocal instrumental music)
(Tense instrumental music)
(Cheerful instrumental music)
(Pan clangs)
(Cheerful music continues)
(Pleasant instrumental music)
(Birds chirping)
(Fingers tapping)
- He's late, he's always late.
- Well, what time's he supposed to be here?
- 20 minutes ago.
Say, I don't mind honoring
the boss on his birthday,
but I can't waste no time!
I got a 1:30 hit this afternoon, ya get me?
- Hey, no lines, boss loon here yet?
(Footsteps tapping)
Hey, Blackjack Connors!
I ain't seen you since that fort Knox job.
- Hi, Ozzie.
Hey, you know I still got
that gold bullion in the closet.
Nobody would fence it.
- (Chuckles) Me too, everybody
wants to know where I got it.
Hey, I tried.
- Hey, it's been tough, you know.
It's like no one had ever
seen gold bullion before.
Hey, I even tried it in restaurants.
And they'd say to me, "don't
you got anything smaller?"
- Yeah, well, maybe someday.
Hey, this is socks Malone.
- Socks.
(Fingers snapping)
- Say, boss loon is here!
Bounce those lights.
(Footsteps tapping)
(Boss loon shouts) (Gunshots popping)
- [Boss loon] You'll never take me alive!
Eat lead!
- Happy birthday! - Happy birthday, boss!
- Oh, what a surprise!
Blackjack, Ozzie, no lines.
How are ya?
Oh, say no more.
Oh, what a beautiful cake.
Gentlemen, I am touched.
This is a great day for me.
Sit down, please.
I got something to tell yous.
This morning, I came up
with the best idea for a racket
that I've ever come up with.
This racket will make everything we do
look like nickels and dimes.
- We're all ears, boss.
- Yeah, we're always interested
in hearing a new proposition.
- This operation we're going
to start is musical comedy.
- Musical comedy?
- Sure, like we can rent an
old barn and set up chairs.
Socks, you can make popcorn and lemonade!
Like we can cast it with the
members of the flegel gang
and the purple gang and our gang.
Why, can't you just see it?
And we can get our parents
to come and our friends.
And why, there's lots of people
we can threaten who will show up.
And this morning I wrote
the best musical score
anybody's ever seen.
And even better, it's about people like us.
Listen to this.
I call it hoods and mauls.
Think of all the classy dames
we can have in skimpy little outfits.
My mom can sew the costumes.
And how about this number?
I call it, "I can duck the
law, but I can't duck love."
♪ I've been around this great big town ♪
♪ but no fears just like a clown ♪
♪ hear the little birds part ♪
♪ you put your handcuffs on me ♪
What do you think?
Great, huh?
- Can I be in it?
- Well, boss loon,
this is certainly an
unexpected proposition.
We'll talk it over and we'll let you know.
(Playful piano music)
(Tense orchestral music)
- What a surprise.
It's so good to see you again.
- Oh, the neighborhood
hasn't changed much, has it?
- Well, I guess not,
but do you know who bought your old house?
Ron Emory.
- (Gasps) You're kidding.
Why, he was the news boy when I left.
- Well, time flies.
- How's Lonnie?
I haven't seen him since we played together
in the neighborhood.
- Why Lonnie, you
remember Althea Richardson?
She used to live on river run street.
Danny was always sweet on her.
- Oh, stop.
- Yes, I suppose I do.
- Well, what are you up to now?
- What am I up to?
Why do you ask me that?
- Well, it's been 12
years since I've seen you.
How is Danny anyway?
- Oh, he's all right, so far.
Got married, has two sons and a daughter.
I want to die!
- Oh, Lonnie not in front of company.
- The only way to end the curse!
- Oh, a curse.
- You think I'm insane?
You don't understand,
tonight the moon will be full.
Do you know what that means?
- High tide?
- Tonight when the moon
is full, I'll turn into a wolf.
I'll kill.
I'll want to kill.
I might even kill you.
- (Laughs) Don't be silly, Lonnie.
I could always tell when you were joking.
(Tense music)
(Quirky music)
Lonnie, stop it.
Stop writing on my hand!
- Oh, what's the use?
Lock me in my room, mother.
- Oh, now Lonnie, you
know that doesn't help.
Besides, I can't sleep
at night with you growling
and throwing yourself against the door.
- I won't take responsibility
for what happens.
Do you understand?
- Poor Lonnie, he thinks he's a...
- Werewolf, that's right.
I think he just wants attention.
(Tense music continues)
(Suspenseful music)
(Lonnie growls)
(Suspenseful music continues)
- Well, Marge, it's been
nice seeing you again.
- [Marge] Well, I'll have to
come and see you someday.
- Oh, that'd be nice.
(Lonnie growls) (Althea screams)
(Lonnie groans)
That nut should be put away somewhere!
(Lonnie growls)
- It's only a couple of nights a month,
but it's such a nuisance.
I don't understand it.
His brother's such an angel.
(Quirky instrumental music)
(Phone rings)
- [Albert] Hello, check's.
Hold on.
June for you.
- Hello.
Steve?
Steve, who?
Oh, right.
Look, I'm real busy
now, I haven't got time.
Yeah, try to catch me later.
Goodbye.
The nerve of these insurance companies.
Hi, I'm Steve, remember me?
Try to pass themselves off
like they're your best friend.
- What are they pushing now?
- Oh, who knows.
Listen, be sure to save me table eight
for the day after tomorrow.
Jeff's coming home and
we're celebrating his birthday.
- Is he through with school yet?
- [June] Oh, yeah.
He's working in a lab down there now.
Sounded like he was gonna
spring something on me.
- Uh-oh. - I hope not.
I hate surprises.
Ah, there he is!
- Hi, mom.
Mom, this is, oh, there you are.
- I was saying hello to the cat outside.
- Oh, that must be the lindquists' cat.
- Mom, I want you to meet Kerry.
- Hello, Mrs. Coukos.
- Hello, Kerry, Kerry what?
- Grant. - Kelly Grant, you're kidding?
You must hear no end to that.
- No end to what?
- Nevermind.
I guess you're the
surprise Jeff told me about.
- That's part of it.
The rest of it is Kerry
and I are getting married.
- Ah!
- What's the matter?
- I told you it was sudden!
We should have warned her?
- Well, I thought she'd be happy.
- Oh, I am, I am.
I just overreacted.
You're a charming girl, really.
And you, oh, you.
I could just kill you!
- What, ma!
- (Cries) I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry, I'm not a psychopath.
Really, I'm not.
It's just that I'm very
upset about this news!
Oh god!
- Let's go have some
coffee and talk this over.
(June cries)
- So it was kind of fast, I guess.
- What did Jeff tell you about his family?
- Just about you and that
his father had passed away.
- I see.
But why didn't you tell me about all this?
I don't live that far away, do I?
You're only in the next state.
- I know, I know, but, well,
I was afraid if I told you
it would somehow jinx it.
You know what a bad time
I had at home dating wise.
- Yes.
Hi, is this Sherry?
Hello, this is Jeff's mother, Jeff coukos.
That's right.
I wanted to tell you
how grateful I am to you
for letting him take you out this Saturday.
I want you to know that his disease
isn't nearly as contagious
as everyone thinks.
So you'll probably be perfectly safe
as long as you don't touch him.
Kerry, you like cats, don't you?
- Yes.
- I see four or five of
them out in the yard.
Why don't you go say hello to them?
- All right, you can talk alone.
(Quirky music)
(Lips smacking)
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
- You cannot marry her.
- What the hell is this all about?
- Oh, I give up.
I give up.
Ah, it all had to come out sooner or later.
Sit down, I've got something to tell you.
This is gonna be a shock.
- Yours?
- Yeah, she's always getting away.
I've sentenced her to a life indoors.
- Huh?
- Yes, it's a private joke.
I'm the judge in this county.
- Oh, right, I get it. (Laughs)
- Oh, are you a friend of the Coukos's?
- Well, one of them anyway.
I'm Jeff's fiancee.
- Oh, congratulations.
I didn't realize he was even home.
I haven't seen Jeff in some time.
I live next door.
- His mother is different.
You wouldn't know her from
a sanity hearing, would you?
- June's a wonderful woman.
She runs the restaurant in town, check's.
Why do you say that?
- Well, she certainly
has a problem with me.
- Well, Jeff and she have had a hard time.
Husband's dead.
And then the other...
- Other what?
- Oh, oh, just other
things, I shouldn't say.
I've gotta go, nice meeting you.
- Boy, I'm sure popular today.
- [June] You have a brother.
- What?
- [June] You have a
brother, an older brother.
I never told you about him because of...
- Well, who?
I mean, where is he, dead?
- No, he's not dead.
He's still alive.
I think it's time you met him.
That'll explain things better than I can.
Can you get rid of Kerry for a while?
Oh god.
- Hello, Mrs. Coukos.
Glad to see you again.
- I had to see Jasper this afternoon.
- Who's Jasper? - He's your brother.
Dr. Fiasco, this is Jeff, my other son.
I just told him about
Jasper this afternoon.
- Your brother is the most interesting case
in my experience.
He is subject to... (Person screams)
Put that down right now!
He's been subject to many strange delusions
all the time he's been here.
That's Jasper right there.
- [Jeff] He looks okay.
- [Dr. Fiasco] He believes
himself to be a marionette.
- [Jeff] A marionette, a string puppet?
- [Dr. Fiasco] Correct.
It's very interesting.
His movements, his voice.
He gets very upset if
you tangle his strings.
- [Jeff] Ma, what is this?
- [June] Shut up, just watch.
(Fists banging)
- [Dr. Fiasco] Hello, Jasper.
You have visitors.
- Oh, well, what a happy day for me.
Hello, mother.
And who is this young man with you?
- [June] This is Jeff.
- Well, hello, Jeff.
- Hello.
- Hey, hey, hey, cut it out.
Hey, hey, you caught my string.
- I am not! - Please don't struggle.
I'll undo it.
- Jasper, I have a surprise for you.
Jeff is your younger brother.
- Oh, what a wonderful surprise.
I didn't know I had a brother.
Another chip off the old block, aye?
- I'm sorry to have
done it like that, honey.
But I had to show you,
or you wouldn't have believed me otherwise.
- So I've had a brother
in a mental hospital
all these years and didn't know it?
I mean, he must have went off the deep end
before I was born.
He can't be that much older than me.
I mean, do people go crazy that young?
- He was born insane.
- A crazy baby?
No, that can't be.
- I wouldn't have thought so either.
But it was only a few months
before he started to show it.
- Like what?
- Oh, little things at first.
Crawling backwards.
Instead of crying, he'd sing.
At least it sounded like a song.
I think it was heartbreak hotel.
And then it got worse.
He kept trying to borrow the car,
and he wanted aluminum
siding on his bassinet.
- [Jeff] He could talk in a few months?
- Oh, I told you he wasn't normal.
He climbed up into the bookcase one day
and said he was volume 12
of the encyclopedia Britannica.
Here's his picture.
- Isn't he wearing a...
- Yes, a little straight
jacket with pandas on it.
I can still see him sleeping
in his little padded crib.
- So you had him put away?
- It was all we could do.
Your father was afraid
to have another child.
I said it was just a freak thing.
Then we had you.
Then we found out about the curse.
- My god, there's a curse?
(Suspenseful music)
- Where did you get this diary?
- It was in my grandmother's
trunk in a strong box.
I never knew a thing
about it until after she died
and we cleaned her house out.
I didn't believe it at first, of course.
And I never told Jeff about
something that sounded so crazy.
My grandmother was as solid as a rock
until the day she died.
And this is definitely her handwriting.
She says that's judge
loon's diary then I believe it.
- And you buy this stuff about the curse?
- Look at all that other stuff.
The letters and the newspapers.
I had a genealogist trace
our family history back
from the 1600s.
All of the men went insane eventually,
sometime after their 20th birthday.
Some of them made it into their 50s,
but not one died a sane man.
- And no effect on the women.
- The women are the carriers.
The loon name died out because
eventually all the men died
before having more male children.
But the loon daughters
lived on and had sons.
The last name changed, of
course, 'cause of the marriages.
But it's still the same loon blood.
Well, look at Jasper,
the man's a marionette.
What more proof do you need?
- You really expect me to believe something
out of Nathaniel Hawthorne?
- All right, fine, don't believe me.
I've done all I could.
- I'm sorry, I don't mean to offend you.
It's just, you know, witch's
curses in the 20th century?
- I understand.
Well, if you'll excuse me now,
I have to go churn some butter.
- Oh, oh, wait a minute, ma.
Hold it right there.
It was you, wasn't it?
All through high school,
I never had any dates.
You sabotaged them!
Whenever I did make a date,
well, the girl would mysteriously cancel.
- Oh, I admit it.
I'm sorry, honey.
I had to keep you from
getting involved with women.
- And now I understand
why you kept suggesting
I join the priesthood, and
we weren't even Catholics!
- Well, try to understand.
I had to do these things.
You're the last male in the entire family.
If you had children, the
curse would go on and on.
I mean, think of the anguish your children
would suffer the day that
their daddy started thinking
he was a lawn sprinkler.
- I see what you were trying to do.
And I understand it was for my own good.
And I hate your guts!
(June screams)
- Stop it, you two!
I think you're both crazy, and I'm leaving!
- Wait, Kerry, wait!
Look, see, we're all right.
- I wanna meet Jasper.
- What good will that do?
- Well, maybe if I see him it'll...
I don't know, but at least
I'd be doing something!
- I think it's a good idea.
I mean, if she met Jasper,
then she's sure to believe me.
And then you could go find another man
and forget about Jeff.
- Good old, ma.
Always thinking of me, huh?
Well, let's get some rest.
We can go to the asylum tomorrow.
But I tell you, it's like
visiting Pinocchio. (Laughs)
(Quirky music)
(Mouth blows)
(Hands clap)
- My, my, my, what a wonderful surprise.
I'm the happiest puppet on earth.
Tell me, mother.
How long ago was it
when I was first carved?
- Well, you're 30 years old today, Jasper.
- My, my, that much time has passed, aye?
Where does it all go?
- Well, life's pretty crazy.
- Maybe someday, Jeff,
if I'm a real good boy,
I'll become a human
being just like you did.
- I've always been a human being.
- Well, Jasper, we have to
be getting back home now.
Happy birthday, honey.
Oh dear, you got another
big knot in your string.
There. - Oh, thank you, mother.
- Goodbye, honey.
We'll see you again soon.
- Bye.
It's nice to see you again.
Don't tell any lies.
- I'll be with you in a minute.
Jasper, do you like it here?
- Oh, yes, it's very pleasant.
- Did your mother ever tell
you about a curse on the family?
- A curse, no.
I don't know anything about a curse.
Who'd wanna put a curse on me?
I'm just a happy marionette.
- You really are, aren't you?
- Someday I hope to
live my life without strings.
- Yeah, well, wouldn't we all.
Well, it was nice to meet you.
Hang in there.
(Shoes clacking)
- Hang in there, what a nice expression.
(Quirky music)
(Car engine hums)
- Jasper seemed like a very nice puppet.
Man.
So what do you wanna do tonight?
- Look out, Jeff!
(Tires screech)
(Car horn honks)
- What are you crazy, buddy?
- Time to eat your cake, Jasper.
- That's right, nurse.
Wasn't it nice to find out
you had a brother, Jasper?
- It was one of the top thrills of my life.
Well, now let me see.
(Foreboding music)
Gee, why does I feel strange?
- What is it, Jasper?
- Quiet, maybe another change is coming.
He hasn't changed in 15 years.
- Hey, hey, you.
Hey, put those scissors down.
No, he's cutting my strings.
No, my hand.
No, hey, take it easy.
Hey, give me a break, hey.
No, hey.
No, not my head string.
No, not that!
(Tense harpsichord music)
- Where are the woods on this map?
- Oh, that's a forest where this witch
was supposedly buried in an unmarked grave.
- Is it somewhere around here?
- Some rich guy owned
a lot of land back then.
Now it's become part of
some conservation land
in northbridge.
- Are we near northbridge?
- A couple towns over.
- Where's this forest?
- So you're gonna look for her grave now?
You didn't believe me yesterday.
Oh, no, I was a pencil head yesterday.
- Oh, right, I'm sorry.
You know, after seeing
all of this documentation
and meeting Jasper,
I'm beginning to wonder.
- Oh, come on, Kerry.
Not you too.
So I've got a brother who
went insane at an early age.
That's not unique.
I don't buy this diary business either.
I think grandma coukos was off her rocker.
- How can you discount all
this proof I've shown you?
- Look, I'm a hematologist.
I know all about blood.
You don't carry insanity
around in your blood.
(Phone rings)
Hello, this is Jeff coukos.
Oh, hello, Dr. Fiasco.
What?
You're kidding, I mean,
we just came from there.
- What is it?
What's the matter with Jasper?
- [Jeff] All right, doctor,
we'll be down right now.
Goodbye.
- What?
What, what?
What?
- Jasper has gone sane.
He's found his mind.
- What, how can that be?
- Oh, let's go see him.
I don't believe this.
- Yeah, sure.
- You go ahead.
I wanna find this forest.
There's something going on here.
I was wrong.
There's something going on with this deal.
If I could find Hepzibah's grave.
(Flames crackling)
(Match strikes)
(Mouth blows)
- No, Jasper.
There's no tobacco in the pipe.
Now you can hold it,
but you can't smoke it.
- That's all right, nurse.
I don't care about the tobacco.
Fire fascinates me for some reason.
I wonder why.
- It's amazing, Mrs. Coukos.
He seems to be completely recovered.
One minute he was celebrating his birthday,
and the next minute he became agitated.
And then his mind seemed
to be clear and cognizant.
- God, what do I say to him?
I'm not used to his being rational.
Did he take up smoking?
- [Dr. Fiasco] No, he asked to have a pipe.
He just likes to hold it for some reason.
I saw no reason to deprive him of it.
It makes him feel like an adult.
- Let me try him.
Hello, Jasper, remember me?
I'm your younger brother, Jeff.
- Jeff, my long lost brother.
I'm your older brother, Jasper.
I'm completely sane now.
I'm very glad to see you again.
Don't you think I'm sane?
- Well, yes.
- Hello, mother.
- Oh, my poor crazy little baby!
(Bodies thud)
- Is this customary, I...
- You don't hold it against
me for putting you in here,
do you, honey?
- No, of course I don't.
I don't blame you at all.
It was very sane of you.
And now I'm sane, and
you're sane, and you're sane.
And I'm sane, you're sane, and you're sane.
(Head bangs)
- Sometimes he gets stuck.
- Doesn't think he's a vending
machine now, does he?
- No, he just hasn't had time
to develop like everyone else.
His recovery was instantaneous.
It's been a shock to his system.
The whole thing is really uncanny.
- And I'm sane.
(Birds chirping)
(Distant banging)
(Wind howling softly)
(Wind howling)
(Shovel thuds)
(Witch laughs)
(Kerry screams) (Ground cracks)
(Eerie harpsichord music)
- Listen, I don't need a wheelchair.
- Hospital policy.
- Doctor, do you think
he may have a relapse?
I mean, you're releasing
him awfully quickly.
- I know, but we need the bed space.
He'll still be under observation
on an outpatient basis.
But I wouldn't worry.
He appears to be just fine.
I wish I could take
credit for his recovery.
- I'll get the car.
- [Dr. Fiasco] You're going to have to be
very patient with Jasper.
You'll find his attitude and perceptions
very much as a child.
But he'll have to grow up to survive.
Superficially, he appears to be an adult,
but he's naive and
doesn't understand things
we take for granted.
He should develop a more
adult persona in a short time.
He's very intelligent, actually.
(Somber harpsichord music)
(Shovel thumps) (Jarring organ music)
(Soil thuds)
(Lightning zaps)
(Ground rumbles)
(Plaque whooshes)
(Jarring organ music)
- You see, Jasper, it's really difficult
to explain to you what's happened.
- Well, I believe you
about the witch's curse.
I read all about witches
in this gripping novel
called "snow white."
And I'll never, ever eat
apples again after that.
It was quite a revelation.
- Well, you got a head start on Jeff.
He doesn't believe any of this.
But anyway, do you understand?
We put you in the hospital
because you were insane.
And now on your birthday,
you've gone normal.
- The thing that I don't
understand, mother,
is why did the curse work backwards on me?
- Jasper, there is no curse.
I mean, don't listen to ma.
I mean, you're supposed to be sane now.
Don't tell me you believe
in storybook witches.
- Oh, yes, I do.
Mother wouldn't lie.
- Of course not, don't listen to Jeff.
He has no imagination.
And one other thing, stop that!
(Wheelchair clangs)
(Jarring organ music)
- Come inside, I've gotta
show you something.
(Lips smacking) - Where have you been?
- I've been in the
woods, I found something.
- Ah, Kerry, Jasper's home.
Jasper, you remember Kerry, Jeff's fiancee?
- Kerry!
(Kerry shouts)
- Are you okay? - What's that all about?
- I just, it's so nice to see her again.
- You mustn't knock people over.
You all right? - Look, look, look.
- Where did you find this?
- In the woods where
she's supposed to be buried.
Her ghost showed me.
- Her ghost showed you.
- I believe in ghosts.
- I bet you do.
- They come out on Halloween,
and they look like this.
Only they have two black holes right here.
And they go, whoo, whoo, whoo!
- Gotta take us there,
Jeff's gotta believe this now.
- Oh, come off it.
Some kids knew about the
legend and put it there for a joke.
- I didn't imagine a hand grabbing my leg.
- What? - A ghost grabbed my leg.
(Kerry shouts) - Jasper!
- Scared you, didn't I?
Will you give me some candy now?
- Jasper, go stand in the corner.
We grownups have to talk.
- They let him out?
Couldn't you put him in a daycare center?
- It's only temporary.
I hope.
Jeff, are you coming? - Yes, yes.
Anything to put an end to this nonsense.
- [June] Jasper, mommy's
going out for a while.
Stay in the house.
Don't let any strangers in, understand?
- This is where the hand grabbed me, ah!
- Do you, either of you, (Branch snaps)
Expect me to believe that
pure evil exists in the world?
(Ominous music)
- Hi, I'm Steve weevil
from the shakee mutual
trust insurance company.
Is Mrs. Coukos home?
- No. - Oh, that's too bad.
I told her I might be stopping in today.
- Are you a stranger?
- Well, I'm no stranger than Mrs. Coukos.
- Well, I'm not supposed
to let in strangers,
but if you're not a stranger,
you can come in and wait.
- Well, I suppose I can
give her a few minutes.
I'd really hate to miss her.
- Okay, why don't you wait in the kitchen?
She just vacuumed in here.
- Oh, of course.
I wouldn't want to get her mad.
- Where are you from?
- Shakee mutual trust.
- What a strange sounding name.
Is it in this state?
- No, I work for shakee mutual trust.
I'm an insurance agent.
Look, maybe I better get going.
- What's insurance?
- Come on.
You're kidding me, right?
You don't know what insurance is?
- No, I've been in a hospital
ever since I was born.
I'm out now, I'm perfectly
sane now, don't you think so?
- Think what? - That I'm sane.
- Well, yeah, sure.
But a really sane person
would have insurance.
- Oh, I don't have any insurance.
- You don't?
We can fix that right
here and now if you'd like.
Would you like that?
- Well, if it's the sane thing to do,
I should do it.
- It is the sane thing to do.
It's very sane.
Such as this life
insurance policy right here.
Now, if you don't understand anything,
you have any questions, feel free to ask.
I have all the answers for you.
- What's insurance mean?
- Insurance.
We insure your life
for a small monthly
payment that you can easily...
Insurance, we make certain that...
- you mean if I buy one of
your life insurance policies,
I'll live forever?
- No, no, no.
That's not it at all.
You see, the insurance
policy provides your family
with a substantial amount
of money when you die.
- I'm going to die?
- Well, of course.
- When?
- [Steve] I don't know when.
- Don't toy with me, Steve, you know.
- I tell you, I really don't know.
- But you said you had all the answers.
- I can't answer that question.
Why don't you just trust me?
You know at shakee our slogan
is "your life is in our hands."
Well, at least we'd like to think so.
Now, for an intelligent,
perceptive person like you,
you deserve the royal treatment.
Yes, the superfluous life guarantee.
This policy will guarantee you
against any conceivable thing
that could happen to you and many,
many more that will
never, ever happen to you.
And the premium, oh, it's so reasonable.
Here's the sum of what
you'll pay every month.
- Oh, that was too
fast, can I see it again?
- Sure.
- I almost saw it that
time, just one more chance.
- Okay, one more chance.
- Oh! - That's it, I'm sorry.
That was your last chance.
Now, please sign on the dotted line.
- And coukos.
- Thank you very much, Mr. Coukos.
- Jasper. - Hmm, quaint name.
Well, here's my card.
If you have any questions,
please call me at the office.
I'll be glad to help you in any way I can.
Bye now.
- This could prove very valuable.
- Big deal.
So there's a hole in the ground
where you found a plaque.
What now?
You're gonna look for a
corpse that's not there?
- It is there, it must be.
Or do you think I'm crazy too?
- You were just carried away with the idea.
My mother's crazy.
- Oh, thanks a lot.
My son.
You know, I think Jasper
made more sense when he was
in the asylum than you do now.
Have you thought of this wise guy?
Tomorrow's your birthday.
- Well, so?
- [Kerry] Well, doesn't
it worry you a little?
- No, it doesn't.
And it shouldn't you either.
And don't go out buying me a
monogrammed straight jacket.
If I do end up in one, it
will be because of you two.
And not because of some goddamned curse!
- [Together] Happy birthday, Jeff!
- Well, ma, this is really touching.
Throwing my birthday
party at your restaurant.
And you know what would make it even nicer?
- [June] What?
- If you'd sit at the same table with me.
- Well, we'd love to,
hun, but how do you feel?
- Very, very sane.
- What did you expect, mother?
I mean, after all,
we're a sane bunch of people, aren't we?
- Come on, this is silly.
Let's go sit with him.
(Shoes clacking)
- [Hepzibah] From this day forward,
you and all your male
descendants will live in fear
of the day when you will lose your senses!
(Hepzibah laughs)
- What's the matter, Jeff?
- Jasper, where'd you get that nose?
- You mean this nose?
(Nose squeaks)
- What's the matter, Jeff?
- Nothing, nothing.
Let's just cut the cake.
- Albert, would you bring
the cake cutter, please?
- Hey, where'd the balloons come from?
- Happy birthday, Jeff.
It's good to see you again.
- Thanks, Albert.
Albert, is that a new hairstyle?
- Why, yes, it is.
It's a bozo punk.
How do you like it?
(Playful carnival music)
- Ma, is this some kind of joke?
- Jeff, what's wrong with you?
- No.
No, this can't be happening.
- [Kerry] What's the matter, Jeff?
- Nothing.
I guess I'm just tired.
- Whoa, Nelly, Jeff-e-roo!
What's the matter with you? (Laughs)
- You look like you've see a ghost.
(Both laughing)
- No, this can't be happening.
It can't, it can't!
- What is it, Jeff?
- It's all right, folks.
- Are you sick?
Do you wanna go to the hospital?
- You're clowns, you're all clowns!
- Nice talk on your birthday.
- Kerry, listen to me.
The curse, it's true.
I mean, you all look
like circus clowns to me!
You act like them when I'm looking at you.
- Well, don't you like clowns, Jeff?
I do, they're very amusing fellows.
- You're not supposed to look like them.
- Listen, Jeff, we're
gonna take you out of here.
Keep your eyes closed if that helps you.
(Jeff groans)
(Somber piano music)
(Patrons laugh) (Playful carnival music)
- [Dr. Fiasco] Now, Jeff,
you've had a good night's sleep.
Would you like to try
to take the blindfold off?
- No, you'll look like a clown.
- Jeff, you've been under a lot of strain.
It's entirely possible that everything
will be all right today.
Last night may have simply
been the result of stress.
- All right, I'll take the blindfold off.
You look normal.
- Good.
Now I'm just going to give
you a little physical exam.
First, I want to test your reflexes.
Cross your legs please.
(Stick whacks) - Ow!
- Good, he's got a reaction.
- What the hell are you doing?
Stop that! - What's the matter?
Don't you like that?
- Stop it.
- Well, I guess that's normal.
Now I'm going to check your pulse.
Oh, good, completely normal, wonderful.
And I bet you have a squeaky nose too.
Yes, you do! - Stop that, doctor!
This is not funny.
- Of course, it isn't.
I can't let you leave here
unless you appear completely rational.
- I'm rational?
You're the other one out of your tiny mind.
- Now, Jeff, you must cooperate.
Don't be frightened, this won't hurt a bit.
- Dr. Fiasco.
- I was giving Jeff a physical exam,
but he's been acting very strangely.
- Kerry, don't let her
make a fool of me anymore.
- I'm afraid whenever he looks at people,
they appear to behave in a clownish manner.
I'll leave you alone with him.
You may have a calming effect.
- All right, Jeff.
Everything's gonna be all right.
- How can you say that?
The whole world's turned upside down.
My crazy brother's gone
sane and I've gone insane.
- No, no, Jeff, you just
have a slight handicap.
Please take your hands down and look at me.
- No, no, you'll act like a clown.
- Jeff, I love you.
I wouldn't do anything to hurt you.
Please.
- All right.
- What do you see?
- You've got a big red nose.
- Well, that's not so bad.
- Maybe not at Christmas time.
For the rest of the
year, you'll look silly.
- But Jeff, I don't really look like this.
It's all in your mind.
- I know, I know.
But what am I supposed
to do the rest of my life?
I mean, wear this blindfold?
What are people gonna say
when they see me like this?
(Kerry imitates western movie music)
Very funny, ha-ha.
- Whoa, Nelly, Jeff.
Don't lose your sense of humor.
- Since when do you say, whoa, Nelly?
- Jeff, the best that we
can hope for is that we can
find some way to break this curse.
We're searching for
every shred of information
to help us with this.
- Well, I know one thing for sure.
I believe in it.
I definitely believe in this curse.
- Well, maybe that's half the battle.
Just believe in us too, Jeff-e-roo!
- Jeff-e-roo?
- I'll be back as soon as I can.
(Can sprays)
Just remember, always
keep laughing! (Chuckles)
(Hand slaps)
(Shoes clacking)
- Jasper, I'm going to the asylum
to visit your brother, okay?
You just stay here and be a good adult.
- I understand completely.
May I pose you with a few questions?
- Fire away.
- Do you think Jeff will
regain his senses as I have?
Do you think he'll ever marry Kerry?
Do you think we'll find
a way to break the curse
upon this family?
Is it possible... - Jasper, Jasper.
Too many questions.
I don't have all the answers.
Believe me.
I wish I did know somebody
that did know them all.
I'll see you later.
(Door bangs)
(Phone rings)
- Shakee mutual trust,
Steve weevil speaking.
- Hello, Steve.
This is Jasper coukos.
You sold me an exciting
life insurance policy recently
and said that if I had
any questions to call you.
- Oh, sure, sure, Mr. Coukos.
What's on your mind?
- I'd like for you to tell
me how to raise the dead.
- (Laughs) Very funny, Mr. Coukos.
Anyone in particular?
- Well, it's a witch
named hepzibah Crowley.
You see, she's put a curse on my family.
And it was my thought that if we could,
well, bring her back to life,
that we could possibly talk
her into removing the curse.
- Well, Mr. Coukos,
I really don't have
time for practical jokes.
- Oh, I'm quite serious about this.
You did say I could ask you anything.
- But not about raising the dead.
I don't know that.
- Well, Steve, if that's the case,
I'd better cancel my
policy with your company
if you can't answer my questions.
- No, don't do that.
Hold on.
I'll look this up in my file.
Yes, Mr. Coukos, raising the dead.
I have that here in my
worksheet right now, yes.
Do you have a pencil?
Good, well, you take a
bottle of witch Hazel, yes.
And then dump it all over the ground.
And then you buy a book.
"The house of seven
gables," that's the book.
And you read it backwards and very fast.
Very fast and backwards.
And then if that doesn't bring
her back, well, nothing will.
- Well, that sounds easy enough.
Thank you for your help, Steve.
- Not at all, anytime.
Crazy son of a bitch.
- So Kerry also acted strangely
when you took the blindfold off.
- Right, and she had a big red nose.
- This is very interesting.
Do you see the pattern?
To you, everybody else seems
insane when you look at them,
but you feel perfectly normal.
This may be a projection
of your own insanity
onto everybody else.
Because you can't face the reality,
which is that you are
the one with the problem.
There are no clowns here, Jeff.
Logically, you know that, don't you?
- [Performer] Are you Dr. Fiasco?
- Yes.
- Happy birthday, Dr. Fiasco!
From your staff!
- What's the matter?
(June shouts)
- What's wrong with you people?
- But what is it?
- It's a clown.
- You see them too?
Then I'm not crazy!
What clown?
(Playful carnival music)
- Your people are nuts.
I'm quitting this job.
(Carnival music continues)
(Chair clangs)
- Ah.
This looks like the place.
Let's see now.
Pour witch Hazel over the grave.
And let's see.
"House of seven gables."
Halfway down a by street
of one of our new England...
Oh, backwards, I read it backwards.
I don't wanna mess this up, let's see.
And fast, yes.
Story from the house of seven gables
of a spirit's joy upon her harpsichord,
as she floated heavenwards off to kindred.
(Jasper reading indistinctly)
Bygone it seemed the present hepzibah.
From the ruinous porch
seemed to hear the bell sound
incredibly well.
(Jasper reading indistinctly)
(Witch wailing)
(Smoke hissing)
- Hey, lady, lady, what's wrong?
Where did you come from?
- Where am I?
Who are you?
- I'm Sam Lindquist, judge Lindquist.
- Judge?
Not another judge.
- I'm the only judge in these parts.
- This is not my time.
- What time?
What's the last thing you remember?
- I was burning at the stake.
Then I heard some idiot
reading something backwards.
- Come inside, I'll call
someone that can help you.
- You'll call no one on my behalf.
I trust no judge!
I'll be bound you condemned
many to death or imprisonment.
- No, not many.
Most of of my cases are
civil cases, small claims.
- I can hear your voice now.
I condemn thee to burn
at the stake until dead.
I condemn thee to hang until dead.
- I do no such thing.
Come inside, please.
We'll talk this over.
- Judges love to hear the
sound of their own voices.
How many witches did you put to death?
- Lady, there are no such thing as witches.
- No such thing as witches?
I, hepzibah Crowley, am a witch.
A most powerful witch!
I'll teach you the truth about witches.
- Lady, come inside.
Please, you need help,
everything will be all right.
- I'll fix that voice of yours.
I'll make you the laughing
stock of the county.
(Dramatic music)
(Judge coughs)
Wait, wait, come back here!
My voice, something's happened to my voice.
I've got a big case tomorrow!
- I remember all.
The loons!
(Laughs) Powers of darkness,
bring me to the last of the loons!
(Thunder cracks)
- Everything will be okay, June.
You'll see. - Oh, poor Jeff.
I warned him.
I only tried to do what was right.
Where's Jasper?
Ah, I told him to stay here!
- He'll be back.
Everything will be okay, you'll see.
(Eerie music)
- Where is the last of the loons?
(Thunder cracks)
Where is
everybody?
- Who in blue blazes are you?
- From blue blazes, I come.
I am hepzibah Crowley. - As in witch?
- It is so.
- What a surprise.
Make yourself at home.
Kerry and I were just heading out the door
to buy airline tickets.
- Airplanes, who needs airplanes?
My car has a full tank.
- Stay where you are.
Tell me where the last of the loons are.
- Why, hello everyone.
Why, who's that person there?
- Witch. - That one right there.
- Witch!
- I said which one,
that person right there.
- It's a witch, Jasper.
The witch, get it!
- Oh.
- A loon, I know it is so.
I am hepzibah Crowley.
- Oh, well this is a surprise.
I didn't think it worked.
- Then it was you who
raised me from the grave?
- Yes.
- Oh, then you have fallen to the curse.
Only a madman would
bring me back from the dead.
- No, no, I was mad, but I'm very sane now.
Very sane.
Besides, I can't take
all the credit for this.
It was Steve weevil who
told me how to raise the dead.
- Steve weevil.
My insurance man knows
how to raise the dead?
Boy, they'll do anything
to avoid paying a claim.
- Where can I find this powerful warlock?
- Well, here's his card right there.
- I'll be back for you.
- Fine, we'll brew some coffee.
Won't we, mother?
(Eerie music)
(Pages rustling)
(Steve shouts)
- Who the hell are you?
- You mean who from hell are you?
- Lady, how the hell did you get in here?
- You are the one called Steve weevil?
- Yeah, I am the one.
Which one are you?
- I am hepzibah Crowley, a witch.
You knew of the spell that
would raise me from my grave?
Just how powerful a warlock are you?
- Lady, I don't have
the tiniest, smallest idea
what in god's name you're talking about.
Now, would you please leave my office?
I'm sure you're late for
your electro shock therapy.
(Eerie music)
- Your mouth spills
forth meaningless drivel.
I shan't leave until you
answer my question.
Did you not give one Jasper loon the secret
for raising the dead?
- I know a Jasper coukos, not loon.
- Answer me, large-mouthed one.
Did you tell him the
secret of raising the dead?
- It was a crackpot I sold
an insurance policy too.
He asked me a stupid question,
and I gave him a stupid answer.
I got rid of him, no harm done.
- That spell brought me
back from peaceful death.
I had no desire to return
to this wretched existence.
But now that I am here,
I shall complete my revenge on the loons.
(Energy whirring)
- How did you do that? - You fool.
My power is in my eyes.
What an ignorant age this is.
Your mouth far exceeds your intelligence.
I will make the two equal.
Your mouth will be as small as your brain.
(Eerie music)
(Hepzibah laughs)
(Energy zaps)
So you are a loon.
Or should I say coukos?
- Who's there?
Why can't I move?
- It is I, hepzibah Crowley!
- The witch?
You're the witch that...
- yes, your silly brother
brought me back to this sphere.
Now, I can see my handiwork at firsthand.
You are insane.
But as for the other,
I know not what he is.
- He was insane, at birth.
But the curse worked backwards.
He went sane at his last birthday.
- So my revenge is not yet complete.
Very well.
The last of the loons will
suffer the same fate as I did.
Death at the stake! (Energy zaps)
- I've gotta warn them!
(Fingers punching)
- This, this is embarrassing, but my voice,
something has happened to my voice.
I wanna know whether or not my throat
is covered on my insurance policy!
(Pages rustling)
- Is it an infection?
You seen a doctor?
- What, what did you say?
I didn't catch that.
- I'm sorry, something's
happened to my mouth too.
I think it's a spasm.
I'll have to have it looked at.
- Steve, you're gonna think I'm crazy.
But this isn't an infection.
It isn't anything medical.
It's a spell!
- A spell? - Yes, yes.
This woman claiming to be a
witch cast a spell on my voice
so I would sound silly.
I didn't believe her at first.
I thought she was an escaped
lunatic, but now I believe her.
- My god, that's what happened to me too.
Was her name hepzibah Crowley?
- Yes, I think that was the name she said.
She did this to you, why?
- I brought her back to life.
- [Sam] What?
- I have this client, the coukos family.
I met this Jasper coukos,
and I sold him a policy.
He calls me one day and
asked me how to raise the dead.
I think this guy's crazy so
I just told him the first thing
that pops into my mind.
- The coukos, they're
connected with this witch?
She's a menace to the community.
We must do something.
- What are you gonna do?
You couldn't have anybody
arrested for witchcraft nowadays.
No, she needs to be treated on terms
she's more familiar with.
- You mean a lynch mob?
No, no, we can't sink to that.
- No, I'm saying that if we
treat her with regular means,
we're not gonna get anywhere.
You wanna go around
talking like a cartoon character
for the rest of your life?
- No!
- Destroy the witch, destroy the curse.
- Well, she's already legally dead.
We need help.
You know people willing to help us?
- Oh, it's never been
too difficult to find people
who would like to do this sort of thing.
(Suspenseful music)
- Here's the phone, Jeff. - Thank you.
(Suspenseful music continues)
(Buttons punching)
Hello, ma, this is Jeff.
Listen, the witch was here.
You know?
Jasper brought her back?
And he's out there.
Listen, ma, she's coming there to get him.
He's the last sane loon.
Get out of there now!
- Okay, Jeff.
- What are you gonna do with us?
- [Hepzibah] I am going to
take this one, this Jasper,
and tie him to a tree
and burn him to death.
- Well, that doesn't sound
like a very sane course
of action to me.
- We'll stop you.
You'll have to kill us too!
- [Hepzibah] Oh, I plan to.
- Stop giving her suggestions.
- But first you will help me kill this one.
- Ha!
What is this, 17th century humor?
- We'd have to be as crazy as Jeff is.
- You will gladly help.
(Eerie music)
- Of course, we will.
I haven't set anybody
on fire in simply ages.
- Yes, Jasper, it'll be fun.
Burning at the stake is so romantic.
- It sounds hazardous to me.
(Suspenseful music)
- Now, Jeff, I'm going to
prove to you once and for all
that there was no witch at your house
threatening your family.
- Doctor, I'll only be too
happy to be wrong about this.
But for now, let's just hurry.
- All right, Jeff.
(Car door bangs)
Oh, I'm sorry, Jeff.
I forgot to leave word at the front desk.
I'll only be a minute.
- No, we can't wait!
We've gotta get to my house.
- Jeff, I have other patients
who need me as much as you do.
I have to let the staff know
where I am in case I'm needed.
- No, this is more important!
- I'll be right back.
- My whole family could
be wiped out by then!
The keys.
Okay, Jeff, pull yourself together.
It doesn't matter what the car looks like,
just as long as it gets you there.
And I'm not waiting for her to come back.
(Playful carnival music)
(Car door slams)
Not bad, I can live with this.
(Car door bangs)
(Car engine revs)
(Clown chattering comically)
(Instrument clanging)
- (Laughs) Now you of the loon blood.
You shall suffer as I did.
- This is highly irregular.
- Hello, judge, it's me.
I found her, yeah.
She's just about to murder Jasper coukos.
You go get the boys,
I'll try and hold her off.
- You know, this won't
look good on a resume.
- Once you have expired,
I will be able to go back
to my grave in peace.
- Oh, please take us with you
so we may serve you in the afterlife!
- You wish to follow me into hell?
- We'll wear light clothing.
- Yes, I've got this
darling little cotton dress
I've only worn once.
- [Hepzibah] Enough,
slaves, who has a match?
- Not me.
- Me either.
- Well, don't look at me.
Personally, I think you've
gone beyond the bounds
of good taste.
- Stop, wait!
- It is you, the small-mouthed one.
- Will you permit me to speak normally?
- Oh, very well.
But briefly will I lift the spell.
(Eerie music)
- Oh, thank you, thank you.
Oh, I can speak again.
Listen, it occurred to me when you said
all the power was in your eyes
that a conscientious witch like you
should have eye insurance.
- What nonsense is this?
- Oh, I'd listened to Steve.
He sold me a great policy.
By the way, Steve, am I
covered for loss due to fire?
- I think it's time you
seriously considered
catastrophic events, such
as impaired vision, blindness,
itchy, watery eyes.
Now, with this policy, you're
covered for the following.
For the insured's accidental
loss of the following,
we pay the following amounts.
Loss of life, twice the amount.
Loss of feet.
Sight in both eyes.
One hand, one foot.
One hand and the sight of one eye.
One foot, one hand.
Loss of one eye.
On rye with Mayo on the side.
Asleep, are you?
Ah, too bad.
Mm, never underestimate
the power of boredom.
- What happened?
- How did we get out here?
- What did you do to her?
- Help me tie her to this tree.
- Oh, finish telling us
about that policy, Steve.
- Shut up.
(Townspeople shouting) (Suspenseful music)
- We're here, Steve.
- I put her in a trance, my way.
Are the boys here to do the job?
- Yes, they're ready.
But Steve, your voice, it's normal.
- Oh yeah, I got her to
lift the curse temporarily.
But don't worry, once she's dead,
everything will be back to normal.
- What makes you think
everything will be back to normal?
What are you gonna do to her?
- We're gonna serve up
some old-fashioned justice.
The right way to kill a witch
is to burn her at the stake!
Right, boys?
- [Townspeople] Yeah, yeah, yeah!
- Oh, I thought we were
going to burn her like a steak.
- Oh, I thought we were going to burn her
as one would a steak.
- I didn't bring any steak,
all I brought was fish.
- What kind of a lynch mob are you?
- Come on, judge.
We'll do the job ourselves.
- No, Steve, wait!
We can't do it this way.
This is not the right
way, we're civilized men.
Here, here, use my lighter.
- All right, ma, ma! - Here, Jeff.
- Jeff, how did you get here?
- You'd never believe me.
What's going on?
- They're gonna burn hepzibah.
- Ah, let her burn, it's been a rough week.
- We can't, don't you see?
Hepzibah being dead
isn't gonna break the curse.
We have to save her.
If she dies again, we'll
never have another chance.
(Townspeople chattering)
- Excuse me.
Mob, oh mob, may I
have your attention please?
Now you say that it's
right to burn witches.
Does that mean all witches?
- [Townspeople] Yeah, yeah!
- Yes, I'm judge and I say it's right!
- Well, in that case,
I'd like to point out
that this man is a witch.
He turned my cat into an avocado!
- That's, that's not true.
(Townspeople chattering)
- Oh, I get it.
This woman is a witch!
(Townspeople shout)
She has the power to
turn water into ice cubes!
- No, not me.
- Yes, and I happen to know
this woman plays bridge with armadillos!
- I never play bridge with armadillos.
- [Jeff] I saw this man
riding Satan's bicycle!
- I never rode Satan's bicycle!
- There's too many witches out there.
What are we gonna do?
We don't have that much kindling.
- Judge, I heard you say last
year that you'd sell your soul
for some world series tickets.
- Yeah, that's right, and I saw him there.
I saw him in the stands on TV.
- It wasn't me, I wasn't there!
- (Screams) I confess!
I'm possessed by Satan!
Recipes for quiche manifest
themselves on my skin!
(Citizen shouts)
(Townspeople chattering)
- This is getting out of hand,
maybe we should knock it off.
- Let her go, Sam!
- All right.
Listen, folks, folks!
There seems to have been a big mistake.
We wanna thank you for coming out though.
You've been a great mob, really.
Next time we need a
mindless mass of people,
we'll be sure to call you.
(Townspeople groaning)
(Townspeople chattering)
- Ah, there we are.
Hepzibah, wake up! (Fingers snapping)
Wake up, hepzibah!
- What happened?
- Well, Steve here subdued you into sleep
with some boring insurance jargon.
Well, and then this mob here
was going to burn you to death.
- Why didn't they?
- Well, we stopped them.
- You, the Coukos's?
Loon blood saved my life?
- Yes, we have.
And I must say that
you've behaved very badly.
You've behaved abominably.
And I am never going to
bring you back to life again.
- You're right.
I've been an awful nuisance
these last few hundred years.
I should go back to the grave.
- How about removing the curse?
- Very well.
From what I have witnessed,
'tis punishment enough
just to live in this age.
Loon blood, I cleanse you.
The curse is no more!
(Mystical music)
- You're all normal.
I'm normal!
- Ah!
(Suspenseful music)
Oh, there he is!
- Ma, this is Kerry, my fiancee.
- Hi, nice to meet you. - Congratulations.
Jeff's told me all about you.
This is Jeff's brother Jasper.
- Hi. - Hello, Kerry, right?
- Yes. - Hi, Jasper.
- Come on in, I've got the coffee ready.
How was your trip? - Oh, it was great.
- Oh, good. - We got a wedding to plan.
(People chattering)
(Solemn harpsichord music)