(calm music)
(majestic music)
Hi, this is Maryam Ali.
Hi, this is...
A-E-I-O-U.
Nay, nay, nah, no, nu.
Hi, this is Maryam Ali,
reporting live from Pakistan.
Hi, this is...
Hi, this is Mary.
Mary.
Hi, this is Mary Ali.
Hi, this is Mary Adams reporting live
from Los Angeles, California,
where we bring you the absolute best.
Welcome to News Live at Five.
(upbeat music)
(ball smacks)
Stay down, just butt
down, down, up, nice.
There's an arm right there,
there's a big league arm.
Nice.
Here we go.
Nice, there's a scoop.
Good feet work.
Oh, there's a hop.
Come on now.
Let's go, less crap.
Get down, down, down, down, up, down, up.
Let's go.
You got it, Zack.
(upbeat music)
[Cameron] Hi, guys, I'm Cameron.
Everyone calls me Cam, and I'm an addict.
[All] Hi, Cam.
I'm two years sober.
It's been hard as hell.
I struggle every day with the crash.
The click in the brain, it goes haywire.
We all know when the click hits.
You wake up three days
later in a California haze.
Is that what the sun feels like?
Where have you been, Cameron?
There's no sunshine in jail.
There's time and silence.
You in your head.
Words spinning around.
You think you're going crazy,
trying to battle something
that you can control.
I stand here strong
and able to talk and share with you guys.
I don't want you to be
afraid of what's in here.
Or out there.
Nobody is above anybody in here.
We're equals.
Equally human with flaws.
(bike clanks)
I've biked past here for
years on my way to school,
never thought of coming
in, but I'm here now.
I don't do drugs.
And I don't drink.
Much.
I don't like the way it makes me feel.
I mean, drink or no drink,
I'm still the same weirdo.
Butt down, there you go.
You've gotta look the ball
into your glove, all right?
Let's go, you gotta concentrate.
Mr. Walker,
don't you think you're
being a little hard on him?
I can't afford to send him to college.
Let's go.
Come on, Zack, you got it.
Atta boy!
That's a good throw.
You doing?
Are you laughing?
No, wasn't laughing.
You can pick the balls up.
(upbeat music)
Nicole, you need to focus, all right?
If you're gonna get into a good college,
you have got to straighten up.
Oh, okay, Dad, I'll just straighten up.
Go get cleaned up.
Your mother's bringing a guest home.
Guest?
A foreign exchange
student from Pakistan.
She's coming to live with us.
It's through the church.
Look, it's just for
your senior year, okay?
She can stay in your room,
you can take the guest room.
Screw that.
[Bill] Hey!
Nicole!
(Nicole grunts)
(slow music)
Nicole will be happy to give up the room
for you this year.
Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
Oh, Nicole!
Get up and go clean your room.
- No.
- Now.
Make her do it.
What is wrong with you?
So how was your flight?
It was long, but it was fine.
I'm happy to eat and sleep
tonight, so thank you.
You speak English very well.
I do detect a slight British accent.
I got an academic scholarship
to an international school.
My father couldn't afford to
send me to private school.
Oh, well, congratulations.
Thank you.
Congratulations on being poor.
Nice of you to join us.
I've only come because I'm hungry.
Have a roll.
So tomorrow is Sunday and
every Sunday we go to church.
We never miss.
You know, I think you'll
like being around this.
It's nice.
It's spiritual and they
have wonderful music.
Do they have music in Pakistan?
Yes.
Church is actually pretty boring,
just a bunch of old guys
telling women how to act,
what to say, how to dress.
So you get really sweaty in that thing?
Nicole, I'm sure it has a name.
It's called a hijab.
It's actually light.
Cool.
You like being a Muslim?
Nicole.
I love being a Muslim.
It's who I am.
I'm going out.
We just sat down.
It's early.
You still have a 12 o'clock curfew.
Do they have a curfew in Pakistan?
I just stay at home.
Home is the safest place.
You're just gonna sit there
in that stupid head thing
or you're gonna come with me?
I can introduce you
to all the shallow losers
I go to school with.
(silverware clatters)
[Bill] Have fun.
[Beth] I'm making eggs, Nicole!
Why are you yelling?
I'm right here.
Plastic straws, really?
Where are my stainless steel straws?
Protein?
I hate eggs.
I've hated them my entire
life, turtle killer.
[Beth] Then I'll eat them.
Take note, stainless steel straws.
I'm driving to school, you wanna come?
Sure.
Cool.
Thank you so much for the eggs.
Have a good day.
You too.
- Bye.
- Bye, sweetie.
Eggs were great.
Really good.
Well, thank you.
You have any left?
♪ What happened to this little girl ♪
♪ Who's living in a scary world ♪
♪ What should she wear ♪
♪ What should she do ♪
♪ If she doesn't want to be like you ♪
♪ Is anybody ♪
Unbelievable.
What is she doing?
It's my spot.
And she's back.
Took my spot.
♪ I wanna fly, fly, fly ♪
♪ And they say there's
no way you can make it ♪
♪ And I say that's a
rule I can break, yeah ♪
♪ Who are they anyway ♪
♪ Let them say what they want to ♪
♪ What they want to ♪
♪ So they say there's
no way you can do it ♪
♪ And I say that's a
wall I'll break through ♪
First day of school and
I have to get my period.
Thanks for the announcement.
Hi, Zackie.
You gonna vote for me for
homecoming queen this year?
♪ Not today ♪
♪ Today's the day ♪
Good morning.
Hey, Scarlet.
Hi, Becky.
It's Grace.
Grace, right.
Do you have a tampon I could borrow?
Borrow?
Uh, yeah!
Fellas.
- Mr. Walker.
Hi, boys.
You know I'm taking you out this year.
Oh, you are so cute, Jeff.
Well, come on.
I ask you out every year.
Never gonna happen.
Oh, like you think you
have a better shot than I do?
I'm gonna say yeah.
Well, we'll see.
Why would you do that?
Did you see the way she was
looking at me right there?
Yeah, but you totally embarrassed me.
I'm telling you, this
is my year with her.
I'm finally gonna get a
chance to take her out.
She's gonna be my girlfriend.
Not if I get to her first.
We gotta get her phone number.
Do you know someone who knows it?
Fail English?
I'm gonna fail too.
Put together a proposal
and see what we can do.
Another year of school,
another underpaid teacher.
How do you keep coming back?
I think it's obvious.
The great cafeteria food.
The jokes are getting old.
We're old.
Yes, we are.
It's coming up on 20 years, Bill.
Yep, you're still not getting a raise.
Ah.
You are getting a new
student though, from Pakistan.
Maryam Ali.
She's...
She's a nice kid.
Zack, let's go.
So I was thinking you should run with me
on homecoming court.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't know.
You're the one with all the voters.
I think that if I vote
for you, you'll be good.
All right, I'm in.
- You're in?
- Yeah.
- Okay, great.
- Might as well, let's do it.
Awesome.
Sounds good, I'll see you later.
- Okay, yeah, I'll see you.
- Bye.
You see that?
What was up with that?
(bell ringing)
A-E-I-O-U.
Nay, nay, nah, no, nu.
Hi, this is Maryam Ali
reporting live from Pakistan.
Hi, this is...
A-E-I-O-U.
Nay.
Nay, nay, nah, no, nu.
Hi, this is Maryam Ali.
Hi, this is Maryam Ali
reporting live from Pakistan.
This is Mary Ali.
Hi, this is Mary Ali.
Hi, this is Mary Adams reporting live.
This Mary Adams reporting live from...
Hi, this is Mary Adams reporting live
from Los Angeles, California
here at News Live at Five,
where we bring you the absolute best.
(toilet flushing)
How long have you been in there?
A-E-I-O-U.
Diction warmups.
I sent in my application
to California University
for journalism.
I'm gonna be a reporter on TV.
Muslim girl on TV in America.
I can see it.
Hey, brown girl.
Was your dad a part of 9-11?
ISIS called.
They're looking for
their number one recruit.
Her dad wasn't a part of
ISIS cuz it was Al-Qaeda.
Seriously, guys.
(locker clangs)
Don't be assholes.
Dude, you gotta stick up for yourself.
They already don't like you.
I'm sorry.
(bell ringing)
Hey, let's go, quiet, quiet.
Pearl Harbor.
Terrorism before it had a name.
Do I have any students
with relatives still alive
that lived through this?
My great-grandfather was
the same age I am right now
during World War II.
Was your great-grandfather
a kamikaze terrorist?
(students laughing)
Guys, settle.
My great-grandfather was
thrown into prison camp
just because he looked Japanese.
Look Japanese?
You are Japanese.
No, I'm American.
I was born here, just
like my great-grandfather.
After the Pearl Harbor attack,
President Roosevelt ordered
100,000 Japanese put
into internment camps.
More than half of the
Japanese detained were
United States citizens.
One of them was my great-grandfather,
who basically was forced
to live in a horse stall.
Okay.
So if we did it with Pearl Harbor,
why didn't we do it with
the Muslims after 9-11?
This wasn't about any security risk.
All Japanese Americans living
in the United States were
profiled as enemy.
That's racial profiling.
Maryam Ali?
Yes.
Okay, so our new exchange
student wants to talk
about racial profiling.
So, what is racial profiling?
Someone give me an example.
Asians can't drive.
Hot girls are sluts.
I am not a race.
Yes, you are.
Cops shooting black people.
Okay, good.
All Mexicans are in the drug cartel.
White guys shooting up churches?
Black people are better at rapping.
Yeah, but Eminem is still good though.
Some of these are stereotypes.
There's a difference.
There is.
So, racial profiling,
someone give me an example.
All Muslims are terrorists.
What does a white boy
from Hermosa Beach know
about racial profiling?
My dad hates Muslims.
But I don't think all
Muslims are terrorists.
And I don't think all jocks are stupid.
Listen, 9-11's coming up, so be aware.
I'm Zack.
I'm Maryam, the terrorist.
I don't believe that.
Let's leave this dumb
jock to his one brain cell.
Bye, Maryam.
Just call me Mary.
What's wrong with Maryam?
Nothing, I guess.
[Nicole] Mary?
It's easier.
Okay, Mary, what are you
gonna do with all American Zack?
I don't know.
I have an idea.
Take that thing off your head.
He didn't seem to
have a problem with it.
Oh, shit, it's America's future.
Shoot me.
Oh, shut up, weirdo.
So what's your excuse
for hanging out with this towelhead freak?
I'm not wearing a towel on my head.
Oh, I'm sorry, she meant dishrag.
It's called hijab.
It's part of our culture.
You ever take that thing off?
Yes, at night.
Then maybe people wouldn't stare.
I don't mind if they stare.
Are people's lives that
unoriginal and boring?
Well, we don't like looking at it.
Take it off.
If I were ever to take it off,
it wouldn't be because some
meathead chick told me to do so.
(Maryam screaming)
Give it back!
Mr. Walker, they're beating
up the new raghead girl
in the locker room.
Go to the field.
[Maryam] This is horrible!
All right, that's it!
Oh my god.
No, you need to go back to
wherever you came from, okay?
Oh my god, like I'm gonna-
- Hey!
What's going on?
Let's go, on the field.
You guys can beat each other up out there.
Yes, Mr. Walker.
Meathead chick?
How'd you come up with that one?
Google.
Good one, I'll see you outside.
Hey, raghead.
What did you call me?
You heard me.
I did.
It's offensive, right?
Highly.
Well, maybe if you took it off,
people wouldn't call you that.
Or you could tell the students
to stop the name calling.
That might help.
Could you please leave?
I'm changing!
(knocking)
Come in.
Hey, Dad.
Hey, girls.
What can I do for you?
Maryam was called a raghead today.
I'm sorry, what?
Maryam was called a raghead.
I apologize.
Sorry, boys at this age can be ignorant.
It was from a teacher.
I will have a conversation
with Mr. Walker.
(bell ringing)
You know, I'm thinking about
not wearing my hijab anymore.
Maybe if I stop wearing it,
then all these people would stop giving me
all this attention.
It's up to you.
Wear it or don't, I'll support it.
Own it.
Come on, own it.
I'm a Muslim.
Say it, come on.
I am a Muslim.
I'm a Muslim.
Yeah, you are!
Come on, I am a Muslim.
I am a Muslim.
- Yeah.
- I'm a Muslim!
That's right.
I'm proud of being a Muslim.
I'm so proud of being a Muslim!
Let's run into the water.
Run into the water.
Catch the sunset, into the water!
(calm music)
(waves splashing)
For once, Dad, I wish
I could just sleep in
and not be here so early.
The early bird gets the worm.
That is so fifth grade.
You know, if I want a
worm, I'll just take it.
Any time of day.
You're like a big bird.
(Bob sighs)
You cannot call an 18 year
old student a raghead, Bob.
I was just showing her an example
of why people say what they
say when she wears that thing.
It's called a hijab.
I don't care what it's called!
Sit down.
Sit.
Look, you and I both know
that bullying is a serious
problem in schools.
Ours included.
Teen suicide is real.
Now the last thing I need
is a teacher who's a bully.
The fact of the matter is,
I can't tell her to take that thing off.
Yes, you can.
They brought down our towers.
Bob, Maryam Ali is a little girl.
She didn't bring down the towers.
Extremists did.
There's a big difference.
Hijab.
Not a rag or a towel.
First off, I don't wanna bomb the school.
This thing on my head
is not a rag or a towel.
This is called a hijab.
It does not just apply to clothes,
but it is a state of mind,
behavior, and lifestyle.
It celebrates a desirable
quality called haya,
which means modesty.
We wear it so people can
see us for our personality
and not by the way we look.
I have testimony I'd like to
share with you by Nadir Osman.
"I actually started to wear it
when I was about six years old
and that was a terrible
time to start wearing it
because that's when 9-11 happened.
It was the first time I'd
ever heard the word terrorist.
I was like, 'Mom, I was
called a terrorist today
by another student.
What does that mean?'"
This innocent girl thought
that she was embracing her culture
when actually she was being
perceived as a terrorist
due to a group of men that use religion
as an excuse for violence.
Maryam, this was an
assignment on terrorism,
not personal wardrobe.
Oxford defines terrorism as
the systematic use of terror,
especially as a means of coercion.
Terror is defined as the
state of intense fear.
So when someone of any color bullies me
for wearing my hijab, that is terrorism.
[Reporter] We have a breaking story.
[Reporter] There has been
some sort of explosion.
We don't fully know the details as of yet.
[Reporter] A plane that hit-
- [Reporter] Apparently,
a plane has just crashed-
- [Reporter] Then there
was a loud explosion-
- [Reporter] In New York
City just a few moments ago.
(explosions booming)
(intense music)
(calm music)
(waves splashing)
[Maryam] I love the ocean.
Waves are wild and
restless, sometimes angry.
Are you angry?
What's the point of being angry?
Well, I like to come here and yell.
So no one can hear you?
Exactly.
(Zack yells)
Come on, try, try, try.
Like actually.
(Zack yells)
It feels good, come on, let it all out.
(Maryam yells)
(Zack yells)
Oh god, that feels really good.
- Doesn't it?
- Yeah.
Don't take my picture.
Why?
You're beautiful.
You know that, right?
Can I see you with your hair down?
Someday.
I'm cool with someday.
Where were you born?
Pakistan.
My mom was Persian, my dad's Pakistani.
Okay.
Okay?
My dad says that when he
doesn't know what to say.
Well, I've never had a real conversation
with a girl outside of Hermosa Beach.
So, I know how boring that sounds.
Do you like school?
Well, I need Bs or
higher to get into Cal U.
So I just gotta maintain that average.
They don't just hand out scholarships
to great baseball players, so.
So you're saying you're great.
I don't like compliments.
I don't like boys who don't
know how to take compliments.
Okay, give me more, please.
(Maryam sighs)
What are you thinking about?
My mother.
She died in a terrorist attack.
(Maryam sighs)
I remember that day, unfortunately.
It was a beautiful beach day.
My mother was telling me
why she named me Maryam.
Maryam means passing through the ocean
or bitterness of the ocean.
Bitterness?
But the ocean's so beautiful.
(laughs) Passing through
the ocean will lead you
to the pearl of the ocean.
There's pearls in the ocean?
Yes, and you are one of them.
You are special pearl, my
beloved star of the sea.
And I have a surprise for you.
For me?
Yes.
(gentle music)
It's beautiful, just like you.
Thank you.
I love you, Mama.
I love you.
Okay, we're late.
We have to go.
Wait, Mama?
I want to be just like you when I grow up.
No, you wanna be just like you.
We rushed to the mosque
and took our shoes off
before going inside.
"I forgot my necklace," I said.
My mother wanted to go back with me.
I said, "Mama, I'm a big
girl, I can go by myself."
She smiled as I ran off.
"Maryam, your shoes!"
She went inside.
That was the last time I saw her.
I heard a loud explosion.
Mama, Mama?
I looked back and saw a cloud of smoke.
People were screaming.
Then silence.
I couldn't hear anything.
(gentle music)
Where were you?
Beach.
Told you I don't want
you hanging around her.
She has a name, Dad.
It's Maryam.
I like her.
She's not like everyone else, you know?
Exactly.
She's a Muslim.
I got nothing against 'em,
I just don't want 'em
hanging around my son.
Do you know what casual
or unconscious racism is?
I don't need an education on racism.
I'm not a racist.
So ingrained in people,
they don't even know they're doing it.
Doing what?
Maryam is not an extremist.
There's a big difference.
And hey, we got KKK, right?
They hate Jews and blacks.
Should we hate them or forgive them?
That's different.
Why?
Because they're white people?
Hate is hate.
And Maryam is a strong,
intelligent, caring person.
And if anyone should
be angry or defensive,
it should be her.
Because she's the minority
up against the struggle every day.
Somehow she's the one who shows me
that people are just people
despite what they wear or
the color of their skin.
She uses reason instead
of violence and ignorance.
I'm just saying, why can't
you date a nice white girl?
That is so racist.
You can't let what happened
to Mom make you like that.
Don't you talk about her.
You don't even know.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean, I didn't mean to say that.
Here.
What?
What's this?
You're going to California University
on a full baseball scholarship.
You opened it?
Sorry.
You opened it.
Zack.
(bat smacking)
(bat clatters)
(waves rushing)
(glass clinking)
Hey.
So this is Fesenjan and this is Tahdig.
Fesenjan and Tahdig?
Let me serve you some of this.
So the Tahdig is the crispy rice.
It's the best part.
All right.
This is the Fesenjan.
[Zack] Fesenjan.
It's the best chicken piece.
Yummy.
This is how you eat it.
Just take the spoon.
Boom, you don't need a knife.
So easy.
Like that?
[Maryam] Yeah, just go like this.
And what's that?
Noon, or naan.
It's bread, try it.
It's like Pakistani pita or something?
Yeah, it's like pita
in Pakistan, India, Iran.
Wow, that's...
Do you, do you like it?
Yeah, it's interesting.
You know, I've never had
anything like it before.
You don't like it.
No, it was great.
I can make hamburgers, I can make pasta.
There's some on the shelf.
No.
See?
So this is kind of weird.
What?
It's like a first date.
I guess.
(Zack sighs)
So...
Nicole still pissed about
you stealing her room?
Nicole hasn't been around much.
Do you think it's because of me?
No, no.
That's just Nicky.
She's always out and about, you know?
I don't think I ever told you,
but we actually kind of grew up together.
Yeah?
She used to come over all the time
and we'd stay up all
night playing video games,
watching stupid movies and stuff.
She was like the cool
older sister I never had.
So your dad and Principal
White are best friends?
Yeah, I guess Bill is
my dad's only friend.
Pretty sad.
Yeah.
He's made a lot of stupid decisions.
Know if my mom was still around, she...
Your mom?
You know, that...
That speech, that speech
you did was great.
Thanks, I worked really hard on it.
It showed.
Students were actually
interested for once.
I hope your dad will like me now.
Yeah, I hope so.
I really don't know why
the way I look bothers him.
Just ignore everything he says.
That's what I do.
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
Are you just dating
me to make your dad mad?
Why would you say that?
It's just a question.
Stupid one.
Okay.
What your dad says when he
doesn't know what to say, right?
Okay.
(Maryam laughs)
Yeah?
So where's our next date gonna be?
Oh.
Roller skating?
Bowling.
I really wanna go bowling,
please, please, please,
please, please, please, please.
I'm a pretty good bowler, so.
You're not gonna get any compliments.
It's fine, I don't need 'em.
Maybe we should just skip all
the bullshit and get married.
You're crazy, you know that?
Love makes people crazy.
And I'm voting for you
for homecoming queen.
Stop, Zack, that's so embarrassing!
It's too late.
Be embarrassed, whatever.
You're gonna win, I know it.
(sighs) Homecoming queen.
Could you imagine?
(calm music)
[Bill] Good morning, Bob.
Bill.
I think the bell already rang.
Might wanna get to class.
It did.
Cheers.
You good?
Oh, I'm good.
[Students] I pledge
allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America
and to the Republic for which it stands,
one nation under God, indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
Do you have any plans this weekend or?
I'm free this weekend
if you wanna hang out.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna hang out
with some of my older friends.
Oh, I have a couple of older friends.
Some college kids, you know?
My parents might not be,
we can watch a movie or...
(clears throat)
Oh, hello.
Boys.
Do you know the definition of assault?
An act either criminal or tortious
that threatens physical harm to a person,
whether or not actual harm is done.
So you know better.
You tore the new girl's head scarf off.
It's called a hijab.
I learned about that in class.
Okay, I'm sorry I messed her hair up.
I'm suspending you.
What?
What about Amber?
Who told on me?
Do you enjoy being mean?
Excuse me?
Go home and think about what you did.
I know what I did.
Oh, and you're also out of the running
for homecoming court.
What?
No, no, you can't do that.
It's my senior year.
Well, maybe you should
have thought about that
before you shoved an
innocent girl into a locker.
Why is Maryam even here anyway?
Pack up your locker now and go home.
Your suspension starts today, Ms. Smith.
(Scarlet sighs)
I've come to collect my paper.
A D?
This paper was way better than a D.
I didn't think so.
What, do you think 'cause
you're diverse and different,
teachers are just gonna give you grades?
No, I study, I prepare.
I'm always overprepared.
I have work to do.
So this isn't about grades.
(student gasps)
I'm sorry.
I have never in my entire
school life got a grade below B
and I don't intend to start now
because a certain teacher has a problem
with the color of my
skin and the hat I wear.
Please address this.
I'm sorry for not knocking.
That was very rude.
I forgot my bag.
Do you believe in God?
Why wouldn't I?
Do you believe those
murderers that flew those planes
into the Twin Towers believed in God?
Those Arabs do not represent who I am.
With all due respect,
I think it would help to let the past go.
People jumping from windows
'cause that was a better
way to die than burning up.
This was an intentional
act on American soil.
Makes it personal, one
year ago or 50 years ago,
don't you think?
I do think.
I can imagine.
Oh, you can imagine?
Listen, Maryam,
I'm not interested in
letting 9-11, 2001 go ever.
Not going to be one of those Americans
that walks around feeling
sorry for himself,
but I will live on guard.
I choose to live for today and tomorrow.
Muslims aren't gonna stop being Muslims
and Christians aren't gonna
stop being Christians.
You and me, with all our differences,
is it possible that we
can just work together?
Stay away from my son.
You know what, I love your son.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
Do you really think
a university's gonna judge
his athleticism differently
if they find out that
he's dating a Muslim girl?
What do you know about losing someone?
You're white, Mr. America.
I know everything about losing someone.
I lost my wife on 9-11.
I lost my mom to a Muslim extremist.
I know firsthand, as do you.
(gentle music)
(Maryam speaking in foreign language)
May God give us peace, happiness.
(slow music)
Oh my God.
Aren't you that senior that got suspended?
Scarlet, right?
You won homecoming like every year.
What is this?
The Muslim, Maryam,
was added to the court.
Says who?
Says this flyer.
Okay, what is happening?
First she comes here and then
she takes away my homecoming?
Took away your homecoming
by assaulting Maryam.
Oh, so it was you who told on me, Zack.
What does it matter?
Still did it.
Should we tell Maryam about
what happened last summer?
It happened once.
We were drunk.
What does it matter?
We still did it.
Okay.
Why are you even here?
Tell me why I was the
only one who was suspended
and now I have no homecoming.
Jesus, get over yourself.
You won the last three years.
Why does no one get this?
This is my senior year!
It's her senior year too.
She deserves it way more than you do.
You know what, Zack?
You are the only one who wants
to get inside Maryam's pants.
I don't understand why you're dating her.
You could have anyone in the
school and you choose her?
Why?
You know what, Scarlet?
Maybe if you were nice
to one person, just one,
maybe someone would like you for you.
Instead, you're a sad,
hopeless, little mean girl
throwing all your
insecurities at everyone else.
You don't like Nicole because she's gay.
You don't like Maryam
because she's a raghead.
And now me because I'm dating her?
Is there anything you like about yourself?
First week of school and it's already old.
The hot bully.
So cliche.
Have fun being suspended.
Screw you, Zack.
Have fun committing social suicide
by dating your new loser girlfriend.
You can have the dirty Muslim!
(Scarlet groans)
(bat smacking)
I just wanna apologize
for opening up your letter.
I'm sorry.
It's just a piece of paper.
Zack, it's a scholarship.
I haven't verbally accepted.
Why wouldn't you?
You know, on Christmas,
remind me to open up all your presents.
Okay, I get it, Zack.
I'm sorry, I messed up.
I've already apologized.
I'm sorry.
So what do you want?
Well, she stopped by my classroom.
Why are you talking to Maryam?
I just want you to be careful.
Why?
Well, for one, she
told me she loves you.
I don't believe she'd tell you that.
She probably didn't mean it.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means you're young, Zack.
You both are young.
You met this girl a week ago.
Her name's Maryam.
Maryam, you met Maryam like a week ago.
It's a full ride, Zack.
It's a full scholarship.
Can't you see that?
And you're gonna throw it all away
'cause you think you're in love?
You wanna talk to me about love?
Do you know you have never
once told me that you love me?
(sighs) Zack, let me help you at least.
Just don't.
Stay away from me.
(slow music)
Hi.
I don't care what he says,
I'm not going to college.
Why?
Because that's what he wants.
I'm sure he has some good in him.
Maybe before my mom
died, I wouldn't know.
I know, he told me.
Why wouldn't you tell me that
after all that I told you?
I never even met her.
I was barely a year old.
She went on a business trip
to New York, never came home.
You know, I used to hear
my dad crying all night
from my room, talking to my mom.
Sometimes, I'd really think she was there
in the room with him.
'Cause I wanted to.
Give me some false hope
we could be a family.
Every morning after I'd wake up,
he'd be sitting in front of the TV,
empty beer cans everywhere,
screaming the most disgusting
shit about ragheads
and God knows what.
But after a while,
his screaming stopped
sounding like screaming.
All I could hear was him crying for help.
I tried to help him.
I thought I should
because he'd lost the most
important person in his life.
He never once thought that
maybe I needed help too.
Maybe I was important too.
He never gave me the chance to be a son.
I never got the chance to have a mother.
I know it sounds stupid, I...
I just feel like a boy
who never got to be a boy.
I've never seen a boy in you.
Here, Zack.
Stop, please.
Zack, please.
I'm leaving.
Come on, can't we just talk?
There's nothing to talk about.
[Bob] Here.
At least take this with you.
No, I don't want it.
Let's go.
(knocking)
Got a minute?
I need a place to stay.
Well, where's your father?
Sure.
Maybe we can invite the entire school.
Make it a sleepover.
That's a joke.
You sleep on the couch.
I understand.
I've known your dad my whole life.
I've got this.
(bat smacking)
(Bob grunting)
(calm music)
(waves splashing)
(birds calling)
Amber's helping Eddie for
your homecoming campaign.
Amber, "throw me to the locker" Amber?
Yes.
Maybe it's her way of saying sorry.
Okay.
You know I don't care about homecoming.
(Maryam laughs)
You know it's happening
whether you like it or not.
Stop.
Vote for Maryam.
And Eddie.
Yeah, and Eddie.
Eddie, I'm not gonna vote for you.
It's gonna be the best homecoming yet.
So stoked, it's gonna be awesome.
Hey, excuse me, vote for Eddie.
Thanks for your vote.
(calm music)
Any left?
Hey, I handed out all the flyers.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
You know, I'm really
glad that you're here.
And I'm sorry about detention.
It sucks.
Well, I deserved it.
Maryam didn't do anything
but wear a hijab.
And people are afraid of
what they don't understand.
I guess, yeah.
Sorry about you and Scarlet.
Yeah, we've been friends a long time.
It's just, I'm done being a follower.
I never wanted to be a bully.
It's just every time I was
with her, I would follow along,
and then afterwards I
would really feel not good.
I just don't get mean people.
Like, it takes so much energy.
Why not just be nice?
You know?
Yeah.
You blocked me, Amber?
I texted you like 10 times.
Whatever.
Here to get my stuff
because apparently I'm the
only bad guy in all of this.
I got detention, Scarlet,
and I'm fine with it.
Oh yeah?
Well, I got suspended
and I'm not fine with it.
You're helping Maryam now?
I asked her to.
This is a lot of work.
First day of school,
I lied through my teeth when
I said I'd vote for you.
You are not good enough to stand by me.
What are you doing, Scarlet?
(can rattling)
Come on, man, don't
take pictures of that.
(students chattering)
Get these students to class.
Bill!
Who did this?
Scarlet, this is too far.
Shut up, Zack.
There are a lot of cruel
people in this world
who will do far worse things
than slam you into a locker.
Consider yourself lucky.
Happy homecoming.
(slow music)
I'm sorry.
It'll be okay.
Just stop, don't.
No, no, let me go, Zack!
What?
What, you think this is funny?
You all just stood around
and let this happen?
You watched her do this?
Eddie.
There was nothing we could do, man.
Amber?
Grace.
Zack, what's going on?
You see this?
You know about this?
No.
You're all guilty.
- All right, guys.
- Who did this, who did this?
Everyone, go back to class right now.
(students chattering)
(slow music)
(Scarlet panting)
Why did you do it?
Why?
No words?
You had plenty to say the other day
when you tore the hijab off my head.
Say something!
Say something.
(Maryam crying)
When I was a kid, I used
to love playing outside.
It was my happy place.
I loved breathing in the fresh air,
pretending I was in some imaginary world.
Just a barefoot kid running around,
free as a bird.
It was beautiful.
My parents were too busy
fighting inside to notice.
Mom would cry.
Dad would hit her.
So she left.
I remember one day, I...
I chased this butterfly
into my neighbor's yard.
He was selling lemonade.
Alone.
He asked me where my parents were
and I told him that they
were inside fighting.
He invited me in his house
to cool off, so I did.
After he gave me some lemonade,
he said that he could tell
my eyes were irritated
from the swimming pool
and he offered me these eyedrops
to help with the redness.
I agreed.
Felt nice to be taken care of like that.
But the second he dropped them in,
my eyes started to burn
and the room went black
and I could feel his
hands moving up my legs.
And then,
I felt his disgusting mouth
in a place it did not belong.
After it was all over, he
told me not to tell anyone.
And for some reason I didn't.
The man still lives
across the street from me.
Just the other day, I
saw him selling lemonade.
And you were scared to speak up.
He destroyed me.
He molested your body.
He cannot molest your soul.
I want to kill him.
You can't do that.
Why not?
He killed me.
I have to go.
You should leave.
(calm music)
Dad!
It's Zack's.
I told him he could stay here for a while
until he and Bob work things out.
I told him you wouldn't mind sleeping
on the couch downstairs.
I do mind, he can sleep on the couch.
He's too big, honey.
His feet will hang off the end.
First Maryam and now Zack,
you're helping everyone else but me.
I found this in your room.
You went through my room?
That's my stuff, that's my personal stuff!
Why didn't you tell me?
Because it isn't true.
Bill, stop.
Let her talk.
I'm gay, Mom.
Why didn't either of you tell me?
I didn't wanna hurt you.
What do you expect from us?
Bill.
It's in the Bible.
It's an abomination.
It's a disease.
Funny, that's what the police said.
Honey, I think what your
father is trying to say is
we can hate the act, but
still love the person.
Act, I'm not a circus clown.
Look, it's just a part
of what makes me up.
I don't have a choice.
Yes, you do.
God gives you a choice.
I can be a Christian and be gay.
Not in this household.
Nicole!
My daughter is not a disease.
What's up, man?
Nothing, man, I'm good.
You're good?
Bro, you've been acting off lately, okay?
We've all noticed.
You're the captain of our team.
Our team.
We need you, man.
Yeah, I know, man, I'm sorry, okay?
Just a lot going on right now, you know?
Yeah, I know.
I just don't know how much
more of this I can handle.
It's your dad, huh?
Yeah, I just can't get
away from him for a second.
You know, school, baseball, years of it.
And now Maryam.
You know, I never even liked baseball?
What do you mean you
never liked baseball?
Well, my dad loves it.
You know, he played it in college
and tried out for the Dodgers
and thought I could be
something like that.
What do you, hold on, hold on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Your dad tried out with the Dodgers?
Yeah, man.
That's insane.
He didn't make it, you know.
That's like my dream,
to play with the Dodgers.
Do you know what that means?
That's insane.
Yeah.
Well, that's my problem, man.
It's not my dream.
I'd rather be on some beach in
a shack, just playing guitar.
You play guitar?
No.
Yeah, I didn't, I didn't think so.
Well, I mean, you could learn.
Yeah.
Guess I could.
Well, hey, listen.
I know your dad doesn't
like the whole Maryam thing.
Yeah.
But just know it's cool, okay?
She's cool.
And I got your back.
Thanks, man, I really appreciate it.
Yeah.
You guys make out yet?
- No.
- Oh!
And now he's back, there he is.
With a smile and everything.
So I caught you.
Yes.
Yeah, all right.
Finally.
Now stop crying.
Let's get some lunch.
- Okay, okay.
- All right, let's go.
Wasn't crying.
No, I saw you crying.
(knocking)
Can I stay in Zack's room?
Why not?
Just like old times.
Really, the whole bottle?
Parents don't care, why should I?
It's bad for your liver.
So is walking in front of a car.
Give me the bottle.
Give it.
Let's go for a walk.
God.
So what happened?
(gentle music)
[Nicole] You ever feel like an alien?
I feel like an alien all the time.
You really hate Maryam, huh?
No.
Called her a raghead.
I did.
I'm sorry.
Don't tell me.
Bob.
You know what I see when I look at Maryam?
An explosion of color and life.
She's like a beautiful flower.
If you don't wanna see beauty
in a flower, you won't.
But I see what's on the inside,
specks of green and yellow,
washes of blues and purples.
It's an explosion of life.
Can't help but stare.
So beautiful, it makes you wanna like cry.
I don't ever feel like a beautiful flower.
Not allowed to.
I'm more like a cactus.
It's cool to look at, but
you don't want to touch it.
Did you tell Maryam this?
She doesn't like me the way I like her.
You tell your parents you like girls?
I tried.
Try harder.
Straight white male is
gonna tell me to try harder
in coming out to my
conservative Christian parents?
Yeah.
It's okay to be a little different.
That's the nicest thing
anybody's ever said to me.
I do have a heart.
If you could accept me all these years,
why can't you accept Zack and Maryam?
Guess I give everybody else advice,
just can't take it for myself.
Try harder.
(clicks tongue)
Can I help you?
I'm Scarlet Smith.
Hi.
You don't remember me?
Yeah, I think I know you.
I live across the street.
Right.
Right, yeah.
Hi, Scarlet.
I've grown up now, haven't I?
Yeah, I'd...
I'd offer you some lemonade, but...
Why did you touch me?
I don't think I did that.
Yes, you did.
(gun fires)
My name is Scarlet.
I just started my senior
year at Hermosa Beach High.
I am the most pretty.
I am the most popular.
I never wanted any of this.
I just wanted someone to talk to.
(gentle music)
Mr. Bill.
Mr. Principal Bill.
I'm sorry for ripping the
new girl's headscarf off.
No, I'm sorry for ripping
Maryam's hijab off.
I know I was wrong and I'm here-
- What are you doing?
Practicing an apology.
Well, the bell just rang
and we're gonna be late.
I'm just...
I'm nervous, okay?
I've gotta go in there
and talk to Principal Bill about all this.
Well, Principal White
is not gonna come to you.
(laughs) You're right.
I'm just scared.
You know, I've never
apologized for anything.
I'll go with you.
You will?
Mm-hm.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
We're good.
Let's go.
(sighs) Okay.
(gentle music)
I have something for you.
What?
What is it?
It's a pearl from the ocean.
There are pearls in the ocean?
Lots.
Come on, let's go.
Close your eyes.
(students chattering)
An elephant or a zebra.
But think about, let's
put the tree, one stem.
Like don't think about dirt.
It's an even, it's an equal race.
Hey, guys.
Hey, everyone.
I just wanted to say that I'm really sorry
for everything I've done and
I'm here to make things right.
But of course I realize my
reputation can't just change
in one day.
So...
Can I, can I help you guys with anything?
I'd love to contribute.
These need stapling.
Okay, thanks, Grace.
Bring it in.
Okay.
[Student] So we were saying by the...
What did you say to her?
Nothing.
I listened.
[Student] It's called
literature, dumb-ass.
Oh my gosh.
See, getting cheated.
Everyone's, everyone's
always throwing shade.
Yeah, you can't go wrong.
I'm becoming more Zen.
Yeah, I found this.
Okay, cool.
Your mother was a strong woman.
Stubborn.
Which made her even more beautiful,
'cause she was usually right.
She used to wear her hair in this ponytail
'cause it got in the way of her gardening.
She would plant this
little seed into the ground
and it would turn into
this like thing of colors.
I'm not a flower kind of guy.
Death is supposed to get
easier, dealing with it.
People tell you "Just let it go."
I can't.
It's hard.
So I take it out on you.
I wish I could just let things go.
You lost your wife, your love,
but I lost a mother.
You think I sleep easy?
You think I just put that away?
'Cause I never met her?
You don't think it hurts me too?
I'm sorry.
You're stuck in my own selfish pain.
She was my flower.
Love needs water.
I guess the bucket just dried up.
Bob the racist is getting all sensitive.
(laughs) It's pathetic.
I just want a dad.
I just want a son.
You punched me in the face.
(laughs)
I know.
Felt pretty good.
Yeah, I bet it did.
Today is September 11th.
It is.
I love you, boy.
I love you, Dad.
(upbeat music)
There we go, that's a tripler.
Look at that, that's a
pro athlete right there.
Stay down, nice.
Looking good.
There you go.
That's a good right arm.
Now, gonna hang.
All right, go for a run.
(upbeat music)
Maryam.
Is this an A for apology?
It's an A for excellence.
I never was a good speller.
(upbeat music)
A-E-I-O-U, A-E-I-O-U.
A-E-I-O-U.
Nay, nay, nah, no, nu.
Irish wristwatch, Irish
wristwatch, Irish wristwatch.
Hi, hi, hi.
Hi.
No, that's too much.
Hi, this is Maryam Ali
from News Live at Five,
where we bring you the absolute best.
(snaps) Come on, come on, seriously.
Hi.
Hi, this is Maryam Ali
from News Live at Five,
where we bring you the absolute best.
(knocking)
Come on in.
Maryam, ready for you on set.
Thank you, Cindy.
[Cindy] And five, four, three.
Hi, this is Maryam Ali
reporting from News Live at Five,
where we bring you the absolute best.
(upbeat music)
♪ What happened to this little girl ♪
♪ Who's living in a scary world ♪
♪ What should she wear ♪
♪ What should she do ♪
♪ If she doesn't want to be like you ♪
♪ Does anybody care at all ♪
♪ Are you gonna let me fall, fall, fall ♪
♪ I wanna fly, fly, fly ♪
♪ And they say there's
no way you can make it ♪
♪ And I say that's a
rule, I can break it ♪
♪ Who are they anyway ♪
♪ Let them say what they want to ♪
♪ What they want to ♪
♪ So they say there's
no way you can do it ♪
♪ And I say that's a wall,
I'll break through it ♪
♪ I'm okay, on my way,
not afraid, not today ♪
♪ Not today, not today, not today ♪
♪ Today's the day I face it all ♪
♪ The tears, the fears, the angry halls ♪
♪ Try to bring me down ♪
♪ With all your words ♪
♪ You think you're cool ♪
♪ But it just hurts ♪
♪ If anybody cares at all ♪
♪ Nobody has to fall, fall, fall. ♪
♪ We can all fly, fly, fly ♪
♪ Still they say there's
no way you can make it ♪
♪ And I say that's a
rule, I can break it ♪
♪ Who are they anyway ♪
♪ Let them say what they want to ♪
♪ What they want to ♪
♪ So they say there's
no way you can do it ♪
♪ And I say that so what,
I'll break through it ♪
♪ I'm okay, on my way,
not afraid, not today ♪
♪ Not today, not today, not today ♪
♪ Whatever the world needs now ♪
♪ Love is a part somehow ♪
♪ Together we both can work it out ♪
♪ So they say there's
no way you can do it ♪
♪ And I say ♪