(dog barks in distance)
(rock music)
When are you gonna
fix my sink Bob?
When are you
gonna pay your rent?
(rock music)
(music fades)
(car engine starts)
(rock music)
(Richie) Amanda.
I don't have time for
this Richie, I'm late.
Yeah, tell me about, I've
been out here waiting for you.
Okay.
What part of we're
through don't you get?
Oh, come on Amanda,
don't be like that.
No, don't touch me.
Amanda, it's just,
I miss you a lot.
Well, you should've
thought about that
before you stole the
money from my fridge.
So you're breaking up with me
because I borrowed
some money from you?
Borrow?
You didn't borrow money Richie,
you stole my vintage
jar, my money.
10 Months worth of tips,
you stole it and
you bought a guitar.
Hey, that guitar was a
steal. I had to act fast.
I mean, would you have given
me the money if I'd asked you?
- No.
- Yeah, see.
Besides, who keeps
their money in a fridge.
You ever heard of a bank?
I don't trust banks.
Right, yeah. You
don't trust banks.
You don't trust boyfriends.
I wonder if you even trust
yourself enough to love anybody.
Look, I'm gonna pay
you back, I promise.
The band is starting
to book some gigs,
so I'll just need to
come by your place later
and you know, pick
up the guitar.
(Amanda) Don't
bother, I'm selling it.
What? No, you can't do that.
Sure I can, I paid for it.
Okay.
Okay, I get it.
I'm sorry.
I should have asked
you first and I didn't
and now you're mad at me, but
you can't sell that guitar.
It's classic.
No, this is classic Richie.
I'm not doing it anymore.
I'll give you a month,
one month to buy back the
guitar and then you can keep it.
- (Richie) A month?
- Yeah.
(Richie) Where am I gonna
find that kind of money
in a month?
I don't know. You
ever heard of a bank?
(door closes)
(tense music)
Well, well, well, look who
decided to show up today.
I know, I'm sorry.
- Mh
- hm.
Would you at least
like to hear my excuse?
Oh, I heard it.
You heard that?
- Mh
- hm.
But please, I don't
need any details
unless you're
abducted by aliens.
Were you abducted by aliens?
No.
Lucky aliens,
but really though,
this late thing is
getting to be a habit.
Keep it up and I'll
be forced to fire you.
All right.
But you'd still be
my friend right?
Oh sure, I'm
not getting fired.
All right. Hold down
the Fort, please.
I need you to run
this to the bank.
Where's Justin?
(Charlene) On a bakery run.
You know when he does that,
he takes a couple of
muffins for himself, right?
Well yeah, but I'll
sacrifice a muffin or two
for an employee that
shows up on time.
Besides, I deduct the
cost from his tips,
he hasn't figured it out.
(rock music)
Okay Mands, the
refills are done.
I'll try to contain
my excitement.
Stop calling me Mands.
Fine.
Amanda, I'm out of here.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Yep, I'm counting the hours.
Don't even think
about it Justin.
(door opens, closes)
(Lily) Excuse me.
What can I get for you?
Are you Amanda James?
Who wants to know?
My name is Lily Stevenson.
I was wondering if
you had a minute.
Unless you're selling tin
mints, I'm not interested.
Okay, then I will have a
cafe latte with skimmed milk.
Is there a place we can talk?
It's about your father.
(tense music)
I don't know where he is.
Last I heard, he was
living somewhere upstate.
I know, that's
not why I'm here,
Amanda, your father's dying.
So what?
You're here from some law firm
trying to settle his estate?
I don't want it,
give it to Goodwill.
How'd you find me here anyway?
The cafe's web page.
I hate the internet.
- I'm not from a law firm.
- Hank and I are friends.
You and my father are friends?
Yeah.
Actually, if it weren't for
Hank, I would be dead right now.
I was an addict and
he got me into AA
and just stood by me
through two relapses
until I eventually got sober.
He never gave up on me.
Lucky you.
He helped save my life.
Okay. Well, what do you want?
Your liver, just a part of it.
- What are you?
- The walking dead.
Amanda, your father
has a liver disease
and his only chance is
to have a transplant.
Look, I don't know how
it is where you're from,
but around here
asking a complete stranger
for their internal organs
might be construed as,
I don't know, creepy.
I know it's terrible to dump
all this on you like this,
but I'm desperate.
He's on the transplant list
and he's running out of time.
And you think since
I'm his daughter,
that I'd be a donor match?
He didn't have the guts
to ask me himself, did he?
He sent you.
He didn't want you involved.
He would be really upset with me
if he knew I was doing this.
Look, I won't even
pretend to understand
what caused the rift
between the two of you.
Rift?
God, that's such an
interesting way of putting it.
I don't want to be
rude, but we're closing.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm sorry for wasting your time.
Hey girl scout,
4.75 for the latte.
Of course.
Here you go.
There you go.
FYI, I never said
I wouldn't do it.
(Lily) What?
I didn't say I
wouldn't get tested.
Then you will?
I didn't say that either.
Okay, look, here's
the doctor's number
and if you do decide to do it,
then just give them a call
and they'll set it all up
and thank you for
considering it.
Thanks.
(soft ambient music)
(door closes)
(keys clank)
(soft music)
(upbeat music)
Hey stranger.
Scotch rocks?
Am I that predictable?
What are you waiting for?
Pour.
(upbeat music)
Haven't seen you
in here for a while.
The prices you charge,
I'm surprised I can
be in here at all.
Well, you still get
me to pour your drink.
I guess it's okay.
Everything okay?
Yeah, why?
Well, for starters,
you're staring at a
card from a surgeon.
You tend bars long enough
and you get pretty good at
reading stuff upside down.
It's not for me.
It's my dad.
He needs a liver transplant
and they want to see
if I'm a match, so.
Sorry about your dad.
But if you're a match,
at least you're giving him a
second chance at life right?
Good point.
To second chances.
Second chances.
(melancholic music)
(Dr. Hogan) After
the procedure,
the portion of the
liver that we remove
will automatically regenerate.
You do this kind of
thing all the time?
(Dr. Hogan) Not exactly.
You see, most of the
patients that we diagnose
with collegial carcinoma
are over the age of 50.
So finding a viable donor in
time is next to impossible.
To be completely
honest with you.
Most people die before
a donor can be found.
Oh.
However, having a family
member as a potential candidate
does increase the
odds dramatically.
So how does this
kind of thing work?
Well first, we'll do a test
to make sure that your liver
is healthy enough to operate.
You annotated here
on your history,
a high level of
alcohol consumption.
You say high, I say normal.
Well, according to the
AMA, your normal is our high,
but a biopsy will
tell us for sure.
Biopsy?
Great.
It's just a simple
outpatient procedure.
It does require a needle though.
After that, it's just a
matter of some blood tests
to screen for viruses,
a routine physical
and a psych evaluation.
A psych evaluation?
- (Dr. Hogan) Yes.
- It's just protocol.
Just to make sure
that the candidate
doesn't feel pressured
into donating.
People do that?
Desperate people will
do almost anything.
Well, you better
get back to work.
(Dr. Hogan) Absolutely.
I'm gonna have Tina out
front schedule your tests
and make sure that everything
goes well for your biopsy.
In the meantime, follow
those instructions for me.
Go easy on the sauce.
Got it.
Should have your results
in about a week or so.
And if it turns
out I'm not a match.
Then most likely your father
doesn't finish out the year.
(tense music)
(Justin hums)
Justin, Justin, Justin.
Do you mind? I'm
trying to study.
I don't get you.
Why'd you go back to school
if you don't have to?
Because I want to do something
with my life besides this.
Yeah but Law school.
Well, what are you
gonna do with that?
What do you think?
I'm gonna make cheesy
commercials, sue people
and buy Alexis.
That's cool.
I guess.
What about you, Amanda?
You're gonna fly off to
Venice and start a new life?
I'll let you know
when I get there.
If I ever get there.
Hey Mands.
Ever since you dumped Richie,
he's been super bummed out.
I've never seen him this low.
Save it for somebody
who cares, Justin.
(phone beeps)
I'm telling you,
Richie's just moping around
with that sad puppy
dog look of his.
- Well.
- You know.
No, no, I don't know.
Oh, well it's
kind of like this.
- That's not a sad puppy.
- That's a constipated one.
What do you know.
I know what a
constipated dog looks like.
And I know that guys
like Richie never change.
No man, you're wrong.
He's getting his act together.
Sure.
And maybe I'm wrong
about my ex-husband too.
Any minute now he could
walk through that door
with five years worth
of back child support
and tell me that he
actually wants to spend time
with his daughter.
I could be wrong, but I'm not.
(Dr. Hogan) I got your
test results, you're a match.
Are you sure?
(Dr. Hogan) Positive.
(tense music)
Amanda, are you still there?
Yeah, I'm here.
(Dr. Hogan) Okay.
Now I just need you both
to sign consent forms.
Then we can schedule
the surgery.
Your father's available
tomorrow at two.
Will that work for you?
I'll make it work.
(Dr. Hogan) Great,
I'll let your father know
we're on for tomorrow.
Okay, thank you.
Hey, I need you out front.
Yeah, I'm coming.
I need to take off a
little early tomorrow.
I have a doctor's appointment.
Again?
That's like the third
one in two weeks.
Are you sick?
No, I'm fine, I just
need to take off early.
Is that cool?
No, no, it's not
unless you tell me why.
I just did.
Look, the only reason
you still have a job here
is because we're friends.
I put up with a lot from
you and you know it.
So if you want a
favor, I need a reason.
Fine.
It's my dad.
He needs a liver transplant.
I've been doing tests
to see if I'm a match
it turns out I am, so lucky me.
A liver transplant?
Girl, if you're just
gonna make up an excuse.
You should definitely go with
something more plausible.
Are you serious?
I'm so sorry.
I had no idea.
Well, is this why
you needed time off?
Why didn't you just tell me?
I've known you for years.
You've never even
mentioned your family.
I don't know, like
this transplant thing.
I can finally have
a second chance
to put some things
behind me, move forward.
Got to make the
best of it I guess.
(Claire) You totally stole
that from a Hallmark movie.
(soft music)
But I got to do it.
Call me and let me
know how it goes, okay.
(soft music)
(upbeat music)
(Woman On Radio)
Love you guys.
I'm listening to you at home.
(upbeat music)
(indistinct chatter)
(soft ambient music)
(footsteps approach)
Amanda, there you are.
Sorry I'm late.
Everything okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Alright. This is
pastor Clairemont Miller.
She's gonna be joining us today.
Hi, it's nice to meet you.
Please call me Claire.
St. Francis has pastors
on call when requested.
I didn't ask for one.
No, you're right,
but your father did.
I've been counseling Hank
since he's been in
town for the procedure.
Claire will also serve
as our official witness.
Okay.
Shall we?
All right.
(tense music)
It's so good to see
you again. Thank you.
You knew about this?
Yeah.
You shouldn't have done this.
Hey dad.
Surprised to see me?
Yeah.
I hear pastor Claire's
been counseling you.
(Hank) Yes.
We've had some wonderful
conversations over coffee.
The man knows his scripture.
Yeah, it's funny.
He used to say that...
What was it?
The Bible was only made for
frightened superstitious people.
Was that it dad?
I bet you must be pretty
frightened right now.
I think we're getting
off on the wrong foot here.
Yes, don't worry, it's
just nerves I think.
(clears throat)
Any questions about
the consent forms?
So, Lily tells me
that you are sober now.
(Hank) Yes, I am.
- That's so interesting.
- And that you found God.
And in ways we still
don't understand.
He seems to have given
Hank a second chance.
I just told my friend the
exact same thing yesterday.
I think this is
my second chance.
(rock music)
(tense music)
I don't understand.
Do you want to tell
her dad or should I?
(tense music)
All these years and
you're still a coward.
(Hank) Please stop.
Why?
You didn't.
It's funny, you used
to have a power over me
and then some like
cosmic shift happened
and now I have the
power over you.
I think we need
to take a step back.
This is starting to get ugly.
(Amanda) Ugly?
Ugly. You don't
know the half of it
Lily tells me you two
are close friends.
How close is close
would you say?
Did he tell you that
when I was eight
after my mom had passed
and then I got the courage
to finally run away from home
when I was 17, that he
would come home drunk.
He would pull my nightgown
up around my neck,
pull my underwear down and
force himself inside of me.
Then all the while telling me
how much of a good
little girl I am.
And this is what
good little girls do
to please their daddies.
Did he tell you that?
Did you tell her that dad?
No.
He brushed over that part.
Amanda, you seem
upset, why don't we...
Go outside, get
some fresh air?
I'm good.
Thank you.
So now you think that
all these years later,
I'm just gonna come
in here and save you?
Look at me.
(tense music)
this is what your good
little girl looks like.
She's not gonna save you.
(tense ambient music)
Call me for the funeral.
You want to attend?
No.
There's a nice bottle of
scotch I've been saving it for.
Amanda.
Nope, whatever
cliche Bible verse
you're gonna spit out at
me right now, just don't.
(door opens, closes)
Amanda, wait.
Didn't we just do this?
You have every right
to be hurt and angry,
but this is no way to fix it.
What makes you think
I need to be fixed?
He deserves to die.
And I promise you
when his time comes,
he will be held accountable.
Accountable.
What is it with
you church people?
You know that man have been
counseling is a liar, right?
So if you want to
believe that little crap,
then be my guest.
You're right.
All I can do is take it on faith
that he's truly a changed man.
Do you have kids Claire?
- (Claire) I do.
- Do me a favor.
Next time you go on vacation,
leave your girls with my father
and see how that
works out for you
since you have so much
faith in him and all.
My faith is in God.
Where was God
when I needed Him
to save me from my
own father, huh?
What does that say about me?
That none of this matters,
that I don't matter?
Come on, pastor.
You're supposed to
have all the answers.
That's what I thought.
Keep your God.
I don't need Him.
(elevator buzzes)
(eerie music)
(upbeat music)
You might want to
slow down a little bit.
I'm celebrating.
(Bartender)
What's the occasion?
Second chances.
Oh, you mean that
thing with your father?
That's great. Good for you.
Yeah, good for me.
(upbeat music)
You know, the world would
be a whole lot better off
if more people were like you.
(phone vibrates)
A friend coming down here
to celebrate with you?
No, just me.
(upbeat instrumental music)
(Amanda groans)
(ambient music)
(upbeat rock music)
You're late.
Yeah, I know, I'm sorry.
Hey, how'd it go? I
tried calling last night.
Have you seen your dad?
He's fine.
What can I get for you?
(tense ambient music)
(instrumental music)
(soft music)
Hey, when's your
dad's surgery?
I need to schedule
a cover for you.
Man, I wish someone needed
my liver. That'd be sick.
You told him?
I'm sorry, I didn't
realize it was a secret.
I wouldn't have told you
if you hadn't forced me to.
Chill Mands, you're
gonna be a hero.
I can see it now.
Daughters saves father's life.
Shut up, Justin.
Don't you have something
you can do in the kitchen?
No.
Well, can you find
something please?
I'm just trying
to be supportive.
Okay, go support
stacking inventory.
Okay, okay, geez.
- I'm sorry, okay.
- I didn't know.
So what are the dates
that you need off?
Don't worry about it.
Well, it's my job
to worry about it.
So do you need the
time off or not?
Not.
Look, since I didn't
ask for your opinion,
then I don't have to
give you an excuse.
(Charlene) Is
everything all right?
Everything's fine.
People need to stay
out of my business.
Well, you sort of
involve me in your business
when you bring your
business into my business.
So what happened?
Can you just leave it?
No I can't, I care about you.
I never asked you to.
(soft music)
Wow.
I've got to give you
points for perseverance.
You really don't know how to
take no for an answer, do you?
You can have a career
in sales, telemarketing.
You could sell
timeshares in Florida.
Funny, snippy but funny.
If you're here to
ask me to reconsider,
you're wasting your time.
I'm not changing my mind.
That's not why I'm here.
I'm not too concerned
with whether Hank gets
a transplant or not.
I mean, we're all gonna
die of something, right?
I take it back, you're
a terrible salesman.
I would not buy
timeshares from you.
Where did you get
your pastor's license?
A box of cracker jacks?
You got something
against cracker jacks?
No.
Okay, well, if you're not
asking me to reconsider,
then why are you here?
Something you said the other
day struck a nerve with me.
For a long time, I felt
like I was damaged goods.
Sometimes I still
feel like that I am.
(Amanda) What happened?
Did your boyfriend break
up with you on prom night?
I killed my little sister.
I was 16, the ink was still
wet on my driver's license.
Julie needed paint
for a school project
and I begged my parents
to let me drive her
to the craft store.
(emotive music)
I was fiddling with the radio
and never saw the light in
the intersection turn red.
Julie was killed instantly,
me, not a scratch
on the outside.
It shattered my parents and
they split up a year later.
That was my fault.
It was my fault and I
hated myself for it.
I was in a dark place
for a long time.
I'm sorry.
Is this the part where you
found God and you changed?
I'm just trying to keep up.
I'm just saying
your past does not have to
define who you can become.
Praise the Lord, Hallelujah.
What is that?
Quote number 37 from the
Christian book of cliches.
I don't, I don't care.
I'm sorry about your
sister, I really am.
But you don't know me.
You don't know what
I'm going through.
What I'm still going through.
You want to know why I
ran away when I was 17?
I was pregnant with his.
I had a miscarriage
and it was bad
and now I can't have children.
(melancholic music)
That man is a monster.
What kind of God forgives
somebody like him?
I'm so sorry.
Look, I know you're here
because you want to help me,
but do me a favor,
go home to your kids.
They need you, I don't.
(car door closes)
(soft ambient music)
Amanda.
What are you doing here?
Oh, duh.
I guess it was too much to hope
that maybe you came to say you
wanted to get back together.
I'm gonna need to see your ID.
Seriously?
Yeah, Policy.
- Would you look at that.
- Me giving you more money.
You know, I got this job
so that I could buy
back the guitar.
(instrumental music)
Listen, I just want to say that
you know that I'm not
mad at you anymore.
I was, you know, mad
I thought you and I kind of
had something there, you know?
I mean, up until you
went all ballistic on me,
that was messed up.
That's me, messed up.
But I'm not wrong, am I?
There were moments when things
were okay between us, right?
Yeah, I guess.
Usually when we were both drunk.
Wow, that didn't say
much for us, does it?
Guess I should say thanks.
Why?
When you broke up with me,
I don't feel like
drinking so much anymore.
I'm a whole lot more
focused on the band.
So I guess that's
progress, right?
(ambient music)
(knock on door)
It would be easier
to get rid of herpes.
I was just in
the neighborhood.
No you weren't.
No I wasn't, you're right.
Well, it is technically
my happy hour.
So unless you care to join me.
Actually I would.
Okay.
(door closes)
It's funny, I didn't
know Pastor's drank.
Oh, we prefer wine.
This could peel paint.
(Claire chuckles)
Why are you here?
And no sermons.
No sermons.
An apology actually.
I'm sorry I made
you feel like a...
A reclamation project?
You brought up some deep stuff
that I thought I had
dealt with a long time ago
and I know it's not the same.
I thought I could heal
myself by helping you.
And you remembered
I can't do that.
Okay. So what is the
point of being a Christian
if you're just as messed
up as the rest of us?
I don't get it.
Like I know you
think my calling
is to run around saving
people, but it's not.
It's simply to meet people
right where they are.
And I lost track of
that and I'm sorry.
(soft ambient music)
Trust me, I am usually
much better at this.
Trusting is not one
of my strong suits.
(soft ambient music)
Well, thanks for the drink
and not slamming
the door in my face.
- Well, it was a 50
- 50 chance.
But I wanted you to have
my contact information.
I'm not gonna bother you again.
You don't even have to use it,
but if you need
anything, I'm here.
Just, here.
(soft ambient music)
(door opens, closes)
(soft music)
Bob, you have one
job. Fix my sink.
Gosh, no.
(upbeat music)
Well, don't you look.
Don't be a jerk.
Someone who needs a drink.
Yes.
Rough week?
You tell me.
I was late to work, I
got chewed up by my boss.
And I got stalked by a pastor.
(Trey) Stalked by a pastor?
Yes.
And the landlord is on my case
for rent, which I don't have.
He is too lazy to fix my
broken faucet, which I do have.
And my ex-boyfriend thanked
me for breaking up with him
because apparently
I'm the reason
that he was drinking too much.
Wow.
I mean, most people come in
here with cancer or divorce,
but you are a whole new level.
See, there you
go being a jerk.
Sue me.
(rock music)
Why is all of this
happening to me?
(Trey) It's gonna
get better, you'll see.
Are you sure?
Look at all the good
karma you're storing up.
The transplant and all.
A good deed like that
can't go unrewarded.
So, just hang in there.
Right. Hang in there.
You don't have to be so
tough all the time you know.
It's just easier.
Than feeling?
There's no way to live.
It's just me.
(upbeat music)
I'm sorry.
I have a lot on my plate.
(upbeat music)
So Trey,
I don't suppose you know how
to fix a broken sink, do you?
I'm not much of a handyman.
Hey, just call a plumber
and problem solved.
Right, problem solved.
(calm ambient music)
Hey Mands.
You don't look so hot.
I'm fine.
You want to mind
your own business?
Stop calling me Mands.
Excuse me.
I ordered a latte
with almond milk.
Okay.
This has soy.
Tastes fine to me.
Okay, but they're different.
They're different?
How so?
Do you want to explain to me
the difference between
soy milk and almond milk?
How about you just clock in,
since you seem to know
the difference so well.
Why am I even having this
conversation with you right now?
I'll make you a
new one, no prob.
Almond milk latte and a
blueberry scone on the house.
(tense music)
What was that?
What was what?
Oh, don't get cute with
me Amanda, this is serious.
You know, I've put up
with a lot from you,
let a lot of things slide.
You're late, you're angry
and now you're drunk
picking fights
with the customers.
Come on, I'm not drunk.
Seriously, you'd put that on me.
You're supposed to my friend.
Oh please, don't
play the friend card.
Friends don't treat each
other the way you treat me.
Was your dad even sick?
No, no, no operation right?
Exactly.
Wanted a little time off.
Made it all up, knowing
that I would believe you
give it to you.
Listen, I know I
messed up all right.
I'll go back in and
apologize, I won't do it again.
No, that's not necessary.
You're done.
Are you firing me?
Yeah.
I need this job.
I don't care.
You're gonna ruin our
friendship just like that?
Oh yeah, I'm ruining it.
Yeah.
It's never you, is it?
No, I guess not.
(door opens, closes)
(soft music)
You'll have your rent
when you fix my sink.
(eerie music)
Amanda, I need you.
I'm not doing this.
(ambient music)
(knock on door)
(Hank) Amanda.
No, go away or I'm
calling the police.
(Hank) Okay, I'll go.
I promise, I'll go, but I
need to tell you something.
Save your breath, you're
getting what you deserve.
(Amanda breathes sharply)
I know I am honey.
I know I am.
I let everyone think that I
had completed all the 12 steps
in recovery hun, but I
didn't, it was a lie.
I didn't complete
step number nine.
It's the one where you
make a deliberate attempt
to amend any harm that
you've done to anyone
that's out there except when
it does more damage to them.
Except when it injures
them more and you see,
I convinced myself that
trying to make amends with you
would injure you more than
what I'd already done.
And that was wrong.
That was a lie.
The truth is that I was afraid.
I was afraid to face you.
I was afraid to admit
what I had done.
Like you said, I'm
still a coward.
But I can't run from it
anymore Amanda, not anymore.
Not now, I'm out of time.
Look, you were right.
I never believed in hell but
as much as it terrifies me
to think of that.
I would go there
if I knew that it
meant that I could undo
everything that
I've done to you.
(instrumental music)
(Amanda sobs)
Goodbye Amanda.
(melancholic music)
(door opens)
(glass clanks)
(ambient music)
♪ Daggers pierce ♪
♪ It's trying to
hide inside me ♪
♪ Fortress walls ♪
♪ Building all around me ♪
♪ Can I escape the
walls enclosing me? ♪
♪ How can I love the
one who hurt me? ♪
♪ Where can I find the
strength to hope again? ♪
♪ Who can I trust to
heal this heart of mine ♪
♪ And bring me back to life? ♪
♪ Bring me back to life ♪
(ambient music)
How are we feeling?
About the same as
we probably look.
How long have I've
been out of surgery?
About 100 pages worth.
This doesn't
mean I forgive him.
I just didn't want to be the
one to let him die you know?
I couldn't live with that
guilt for the rest of my life.
(Claire) I know.
You want me to
forgive and forget.
I just can't, I can't.
Oh, you won't forget
and that's okay.
And forgiveness, that'll
come with time and with God.
I'm sorry, a little sermon.
(instrumental music)
I can't have him my life.
I'll never be able to trust him.
Amanda, Hank didn't make it.
He died on the operating table.
It was his heart.
He went into cardiac arrest.
The doctors couldn't save him.
I'm so sorry.
I guess that's it.
Like you said, we're all
gonna die someday right.
I couldn't let him die
and I couldn't save him.
What does that say about me?
(Claire) You did
the right thing.
I'm really tired.
Is it okay if I
check on you tomorrow?
Claire,
do you think he really
changed that much?
Yes.
Yes I do.
(ambient music)
(car door closes)
I don't have your rent, Bob.
I haven't fixed your sink.
(instrumental music)
What are you doing here?
I just wanted
to give you this,
it's money I took
from your fridge.
What did you do,
did you rob the store?
No, the band
booked a gig, a tour.
Can you believe it?
I know, right?
I mean, the tour,
the bus, the company,
they got a bus and everything.
It's really great.
I can go get your
guitar for you.
Nah, I don't need it.
Sell it.
Go to Venice.
All right, here's the thing.
Since I had no guitar,
we'd been rehearsing
with me just singing.
It turns out, I sound
better when I don't play.
Go figure.
Thank you.
(Richie) Sure, I
better get going.
We're leaving for Ohio tonight.
Richie, I'm really sorry
for making it seem like
this is all your fault.
It's not, I'm like
way too messed up
to be in a relationship
right now, you know?
(Richie) Yeah.
Still gonna miss you though.
(instrumental music)
Hey Richie.
Yeah?
Good luck on your tour.
(Bob clears throat)
(soft music)
♪ I feel myself sink
into reality now ♪
♪ Try to maintain the
dream, don't know how ♪
♪ I think I'm waking up,
I think I'm waking up ♪
♪ The alarm goes off and
my ears are so offended. ♪
♪ And there's no
way to avoid it. ♪
♪ Feel the light shine
your sweet vision heart ♪
♪ Fantasy ends as sun
disturbs the dark ♪
♪ I think I'm waking up,
I think I'm waking up ♪
♪ And the sight of sun
leaves my eyes so offended ♪
♪ But there's no
way to avoid it ♪
♪ I think I'm waking up,
I think I'm waking up ♪
♪ Soon the ground will touch
the bottoms of my feet ♪
♪ And I'll know I'm
not asleep anymore ♪
♪ Anymore ♪