Hey, honey. It's your mom.
I just wanted to call again.
I was hoping maybe you'd
answer.
We just haven't heard from you
in, like, six days.
We're all really,
really nervous.
Your friends don't know
where you are.
That new boy you're dating,
then you broke up two weeks
ago?
If anything happened to you,
I'd just die.
I love you so much.
Please just call.
Love you.
- This is Hera.
- Hera, it's me.
Can you please
watch Corey tonight?
I'm-- I'm at work.
Can't talk to
your sister at work?
Can you please help?
She'll just be coloring.
No, I have to work.
Tonight?
Like, just from 8:00 to 9:00?
Look, I have to go.
Fine. See you Monday. Love you.
Was that your sister?
Yeah.
Is she single?
Uh, yeah. She is, actually.
- Are you single?
- Uh...
kind of.
I have siblings too.
How many siblings do you have?
Two from my dad
and two from my stepmom.
That's awesome.
Oh. Did you guys have
the conference room booked?
No. It's fine, we're eating too.
Oh. Cool.
Have you ever been to Italy?
-No.
-Oh, my God!
You should totally go.
It's amazing.
-I would love to.
-My family and I go every year.
We go to Florence,
and then we go to Positano.
Oh, is that the place where they
have all the houses built into
-the side of the hill?
-Yes! And they have these
really special lemons.
Hera, have you been anywhere?
Oh, I don't travel much.
Neither do I.
The kids are too young,
and Mike would never let me
leave him alone with them.
Hera,
what are you doing tonight?
- I'm going on a date.
- With who?
A friend.
- Named... Zach?
- Really?
Well, if you don't say anything,
it never really happened, right?
So, have you guys
fucked in the office yet?
We got a big one, team!
$10 million account.
-Let's go!
-Yeah!
Sounds like
you owe us some champagne!
So, I had an incredible night.
Me too.
Can I come in?
No!
What's wrong? I...
You like the gift, right?
I can buy my own plants.
Not if you're only making $100K.
What makes you think
I make $100K?
Well, that's what I made
right out of college.
-I make way less than that.
-Hera, I'm not trying to brag.
Just saying, you can
come to me if you need help.
With your tests, your accounts.
And you are...
so pretty.
It sucks.
There's a glass ceiling.
Without help, it'll crush you.
-I should probably get to bed.
-Hera.
Come on, just invite me inside.
I just moved,
so I have a lot of boxes.
But you-- you could come
-another time, maybe--
-Hera. Hey.
-Hera.
-Zach.
-Zach...
If-- if you didn't
want this to happen,
why'd you let me
ask you out again?
I mean, I live, like,
40 fucking minutes away.
So I was-- I was
taking your lead on things.
I thought you liked me.
I do.
I just-- I don't wanna be
another win to you.
Well, you're making me look
like a fuckin' loser out here.
Can we talk about this later?
You could have everything.
Come on.
-Let's have some fun.
-No.
-Let's just have some fun.
-Please stop.
-Ooh, I like when you beg.
-No...
No, please, stop. Please, stop.
Just invite me inside.
No.
I don't want to.
Do you want me
to turn the handle for you?
Okay.
It's that easy. Come on.
Zach?
You've reached
Zachary Osman,
financial team lead
at Paver Financial.
Please leave me a message,
and I or someone from the team
will reach out. Thanks.
Hey.
Um, sorry I'm calling your work.
I-- I don't have
your personal cell.
Um, I just wanted to--
to call and say hi
and talk about last night.
Um...
you left your jacket here,
and, um...
and I really like
the flower you got me.
Just call me back
when you get this.
Okay.
Bye.
Can't sleep?
- Hey.
- Hey. Sorry, it's late.
I'm sure you're asleep.
You want me to come
and get my jacket right now?
Did you listen to my voicemail?
How about I come over
and you answer the door
wearing just my jacket?
I don't have it.
Is something wrong with you?
Jesus.
You know what, never mind.
Zach?
What do we think?
For work.
For Zach.
- Any plans this week?
- Oh, yeah.
- What?
- Work.
My man. My man.
-Hi.
-Hey.
You, uh, have something else
on your desk. Got it for you.
Hey, good work on
those access to capital reviews.
- You saw my report?
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Coming in late on a Monday?
Uh, it's before 9:00 a.m.
Junior analysts tend to be
in before their team lead, so.
Okay.
I'll be here earlier tomorrow.
You're very smart,
and you do good work.
Thank you.
You just have some of
the non-tangibles to figure out.
School can't
teach you everything.
I just-- I wanna let you know
that this is my dream job.
This is not a college,
and I'm not a professor.
Okay?
Trying to match your new plant?
Yeah. I don't know.
Okay, well.
You don't see clients,
so you don't need to do...
all this.
Okay.
Uh, break down these financials
before end of day.
Uh, if you see any red flags,
make sure to note it.
Okay.
Hey, Lori?
-Hey.
-What's up?
What did Borey-Lori want?
She said I shouldn't
dress like this.
What, hot?
You're stupid.
You dress like that for me?
Matched the flower you got me.
Oh.
Yeah, I get it.
Uh...
what's with the, um...
I took the condom off.
What?
Wait, did you--
-Inside?
-How did you not--
Wait, seriously?
Uh, do you wanna
get lunch today?
-Like, just me and you?
-You...
have to take the pill.
Can we talk during lunch?
I was thinking...
you could suck my dick at lunch?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I just wanna
talk about Saturday.
Sir.
I-- I can't.
I'm actually with a client--
That is
the VP of Acquisitions.
Unprofessional bullshit.
I thought we liked each other.
I do.
This is what I fucking hate.
This is fucking bullshit.
Hera?
Hera, is that you?
Why didn't you say anything?
Weirdo. Um, hey, uh,
so, got anything good?
I, um... ...I just
finished the last of mine.
I stayed up late as fuck
last night, so...
Oh, you're crying.
Um...
I was taking allergy medicine.
Uh, anyways, so, you really
shouldn't cry at work.
About work, or...
boys, or whatever.
They'll eat you alive.
Any one of them.
We're all carnivores here.
Bye.
Vicky?
Vicky, I don't like this.
90 days.
You nervous?
No. I was just
thinking about something.
An account?
Yeah.
You're nervous. It's okay.
I'm the big dog, and I'm scary.
Except I'm not.
-I hope I didn't offend you.
-Offend me?
I have some pretty thick skin.
You don't have to
be afraid of me.
If you make money, I win.
Your success is my success.
So, I just want us to be
on the same page, right?
Right.
So, tell me, what's going on?
With me?
I'm good. Yeah.
You think?
Yeah. I think I'm good.
Crushing it.
-Really?
-Absolutely.
-So this is your first job ever?
-Yeah.
I mean, I worked at a coffee
shop during college, but...
I'd love for you
to make me a latte sometime.
Yeah, sure.
I'm gonna be honest,
I don't actually know
what's in a latte.
Uh, espresso and steamed milk.
How much?
Sorry?
How much espresso,
how much steamed milk?
I'm not sure.
You must know an amount.
Even a ballpark. Any amount.
Two espresso
and a cup of steamed milk.
So, how much liquid
is in a shot,
and how much
does milk cost in bulk?
I'm not sure.
So much of what we do is
an imperfect exact science.
In order to forecast
for our client,
you need to know
what it is they do.
For example, latte.
Maintenance,
overhead, variable costs.
We need to know
what they're capable of.
I just didn't know
the measurements of the coffee--
It's okay.
I believe that you worked there.
I trust you, because deep down,
I know what you're capable of.
Risk is the possibility
of something bad happening.
And if you know the outcome,
even if it's bad,
then there is no risk.
And trust alleviates
a ton of risk.
And I trust you.
Do you trust me?
-Yeah.
-Don't just say it
because I'm your boss's boss.
-Do you trust me?
-Yes.
-Yes?
-Yes? Yes? Yes?
-Yes. Yes. Yes!
All right. You're free to go.
What?
That was me approving
your 90-day onboarding.
Congrats.
You're still on board, kid.
Thank you.
- Hey!
- Hey, hey!
- Corey! Hi!
- Aunt Hera, I missed you!
-Tell me "I missed you too."
-I missed you guys.
-How's it going?
-Good. How are you?
Aww.
Are you excited for tonight?
-Yes.
-Yeah, me too.
-Awesome.
-All right.
You know, when you said you were
making lasagna, I thought...
well, I just thought
you'd be making it.
I don't have time to cook.
Oh, yeah. I get you're busy.
You know, when I was 23,
I was pregnant.
Working, married, cleaned.
I'm in a really
competitive field.
Okay?
If I don't advance quickly,
then I'll just get stuck.
There's a glass ceiling.
You're 23, relax. You're fine.
I want to make C-suite.
I don't wanna just
have some nothing job.
When you come over next week,
I'll show you
some of mom's old recipes.
I don't even remember
what they tasted like.
It doesn't matter.
You need to learn how to cook.
And clean, for God's sake.
You moved in here,
what, three months ago?
Still looks like there's
spiderwebs from the last person.
Corey... how was school?
Did they like your pigtails?
A boy pulled my hair, Aunt Hera.
That means he likes you.
Her dad used to pull her hair.
Don't say shit like that.
Are you drawing something?
Can I see?
What is it?
A plant pod for you.
A plant pod?
Miss Deven.
She died last week.
Oh, yeah. I'm sorry, honey.
My teacher says
they put her in a bag
so her body can become flowers.
Okay, that's enough.
God, what are they
telling these kids?
Why did you draw me?
Because flowers grow.
Actually,
this lasagna's real good.
Hera.
Hey,
I should only be a few hours.
-This guy seems like a dud.
-How do you know?
You can tell by his pics.
He's cute, but he's,
like, hiking and kayaking.
But he's got a good job
and no kids, so, just drinks.
I won't feel pressure to...
All right. Well, how do I look?
You look great.
Corey?
Come out.
Corey, what are you doing?
Is this about
what your teacher taught you?
Oh, my God. No...
- Hey.
How'd it go?
Eh, you know...
I thought he was a dud.
He was.
But he was really sweet
and kinda hot, so...
we did stuff in his car.
Is that what you wanted?
Yeah. I-- I told him I didn't
think it was gonna work out,
and he was just saying
he liked me.
I don't know, it was cute,
so I told him
what I wanted to do.
He was cool with that.
Might happen again.
Corey? You ready?
I didn't do anything wrong.
I know.
I had fun. I'm allowed to.
I meant to tell you
about the guy at work.
-The higher-up.
-Oh, the higher-up? Second date?
Corey?
Well, we went out, um...
and then he dropped me off.
I'm sorry, what are you saying?
I'm just really sad
he doesn't like me anymore.
Like, he won't even talk to me.
Oh, Hera.
What a prick.
They can all be such assholes.
-You okay?
-Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Where the hell is Corey?
She fell asleep next to me.
How long ago?
-I fell asleep too.
-Oh, my--
Corey.
Corey!
- Corey, you in here?
- Mom?
I saw the tree man.
Oh, baby, it's okay.
Time to go home.
You saw a tree man?
Are you feeding
into this with her?
No more of this tree man stuff!
God, this is exactly
why I feel so alone.
I have to do everything on
my own, and what are you doing?
Come on, Corey.
- Love you.
She looks like a dock worker.
Frank, I got that email.
Tea time at 8:00.
I'm gonna whoop your ass.
Zach?
Zach.
...over our projections
for this year,
and I think as we move forward,
what we--
Hera.
Did you have
the conference room booked?
No.
I just--
I had a question for Zach.
- Sorry to interrupt you guys.
- Okay.
- Back to business, then.
- What?
What did you wanna know?
Uh...
Come on.
Center of the room.
Go on.
Ask.
Can you help me with something?
What?
Uh, I'm working on
some models for Lori.
Um, I just-- I need your help--
Hera,
what exactly do you wanna know?
Capital asset
expected return rate.
Couldn't look it up?
Risk-free rate
plus market sensitivity
times difference
between expected return
and risk-free rate.
Thank you.
You can leave now.
Sorry.
All right, let's talk about Q3.
Oh. Hey.
Don't feel bad.
It was just a joke.
Didn't feel like a joke.
I knew this was gonna happen.
I don't know why we hire women
who don't plan on becoming CFAs.
You know I want to.
Yeah, but what else do you want?
I thought you were special.
Boy, was I wrong.
You ever-- ever
think about being a teacher?
Maybe a nurse?
You could--
Oh, you could marry a rich guy.
I mean, you're hot, so...
Yeah.
Be a nice little
stay-at-home-mom.
Oh, shit.
Is that what this is about?
-I want this.
-Yeah, you aren't good at this.
Zach...
What?
Did you--
did you still want, um...
At lunch in y-- in your car?
Did you take the pill?
Yesterday.
I think it'd be weird if we...
I mean, we're coworkers, right?
So, uh...
Yeah,
and I got stuff to do today.
What, are you gonna cry?
Bless you.
Fucking women, man.
Hey, hey!
Lori, I am so sorry!
Can I help you?
I thought you were
somebody else, I'm so sorry!
Go to the breakout room. Now!
I'm so--
Hera.
-What is going on with you?
-I'm sorry.
Yesterday the dress
and today this.
And you didn't
give me a breakdown!
Ah!
-Hello?
-Um...
I know. It was late.
I was trying to, um...
-I'm sorry.
-Do not say sorry again.
Don't.
I asked Zach for help with
one of the equations.
-That's why it was late.
-Don't do that!
Ask the guys for help?
You either do the work
or you're let go.
-We don't get to make mistakes.
-Okay. I'm sorry.
That's the last time.
- Hey.
I thought you couldn't
talk at work?
- I walked away from my desk.
- Cool.
Well, I'm at the hospital,
so I can't talk long.
Hera?
I didn't know who else to call.
I-- I don't know what I'm doing.
Okay? This is so hard.
This is so hard,
I don't know what I'm doing.
Just take a breath. It's okay.
No one's gonna die
if you mess up.
It's okay.
-Yeah.
-Bad stuff happens, but...
we can't just stop
because of it.
On to the next patient,
and on to the next, right?
-On to the next.
-Good.
Okay, I really gotta run.
-Love you.
-Love you too, Demi.
Thank you.
Could you get the door for me?
Cute plant.
- Thanks.
- So cute.
I think
I'm gonna call her Grace.
Okay!
It was a gift.
Uh, I like your shoes.
Thank you!
Can you get the door for me?
Oh. You know what?
I'm so sorry. I'm meeting Zach.
Sorry.
I know.
Lasagna.
Do you want some?
Did you get a new account?
Holy shit, you've been here,
what, three months?
Ring it!
Hey, everyone! Ring it.
- I can't.
- You--
You have to. They expect you to.
You--
We have to
go through with it now.
So, what was the account?
How much was it for?
I didn't.
I just was looking at the bell.
Wha--
Why didn't you say anything?
She's got nothing.
God, you look like an idiot.
Come in.
Hera.
-Good morning, Lori.
-Mmm.
I heard you just got back
from a family trip.
I have time for one trip a year.
Too busy for family, though.
-You doing okay?
-Yeah.
Good, cool. So,
I wanted to talk to you about...
-day and a half late, but--
-I know, I'm sorry, I--
But-- Can I finish?
But you didn't
just do the report.
You did all of it.
The entire thing. Forecasting,
and your risk transfer
recommendations are spot-on.
-Yeah?
-Yes.
We need to find
a happy medium here.
You went from
prom dress to trash can.
And you look sick. Are you sick?
-I'm not sick.
-If you're sick,
you need to tell me.
I can't get sick right now.
I'm not sick.
Okay.
If you can keep doing this,
fit in a bit better,
then in a few months,
we can talk about
funding your CFA classes.
I would love that.
That's exactly what I need
to become a real analyst.
Gabe recommended you
for CFA training.
He said you've been
helping him out.
Gabe did?
Yes. Uh, go check your email.
I sent you and Vicky
some things to review.
-Vicky?
-Yes. Your little plant buddy?
Are you having trouble hearing?
Do you not hear well?
I can hear well.
Okay. Uh,
it's not, like, a sinus thing?
Because your face
does look puffy.
-I'm not sick.
-Okay.
You must have hearing loss,
then.
Because you rang
that fucking bell.
You can shut that.
Oh, hey. Come on in.
- Hey.
- Hey. Shut the door.
So Lori told me that you
recommended me for CFA classes?
Oh, absolutely.
You're crushing it.
Thanks.
We haven't worked
together at all.
Look, I'm gonna be honest.
Zach and I tag-team accounts,
so I've seen your work.
He goes in and schmoozes,
and I do
the actual heavy lifting.
Then we both win.
You're not Ivy League
like Zach, Vicky,
a bunch of people.
Ivy Leaguers play the game.
They don't put in the hours.
And...
Zach told me that things didn't
work out between you two.
Should I go to HR
about what happened?
No. Don't go to HR.
I mean, if my wife or daughter
were in your situation?
Jesus.
All right, HR's job is
to protect the company.
You go to them and tell them
that you had a fling
that went bad?
Who do you think
they're gonna take care of--
and I'm just being honest here--
a top earner,
or a female junior analyst?
I just want you to
get the help that you deserve,
because it's hard enough
being a woman in the workplace.
That's really awesome of you,
Gabe.
Us state-schoolers
gotta stick together.
Thank you.
-Jesus!
-Don't touch my plant.
Are you being serious right now?
Why do you have
the same plant as me?
Oh, well,
I went to the grocery store.
Your little plant cost $12.
I'm here now. What do you want?
Oh. Do you wanna go to lunch?
Zach and I are going to lunch.
Except...
I'm actually hungry.
Ow, Jesus!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Hera just pulled my hair.
Hera just hit me,
and now my neck hurts!
Are you okay?
I don't know!
I don't know
what is going on with you
or what kind of psychotic break
that you're having,
but I-- I'm going to sue you,
and you need to get help.
God, my neck really hurts
and I don't know--
What the fuck?
I want this to fucking hurt.
I fucking hate you!
Yeah! Whoo!
Is everyone seeing this? Whoo!
Stop.
Stop!
Stop, stop!
Stop, stop, stop. Stop--
What's going on?
I fell asleep.
You can't sleep here.
And we talked about
how you're dressed.
Do you have
a learning disability?
It's okay if you do, but we
need to talk about options for--
What the fuck is this?
Vicky, what's going on?
Did you do this, Hera?
Did you fucking do this, Hera?
I come into my office,
my plant is dead,
it's swimming in salt,
and my trash bin
is full of salt packets.
Wonder how that happened, Hera?
Hera?
-I-- I don't know.
-This is bullshit.
I'm gonna rip yours apart.
Don't.
Oh, my God!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, God!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You okay?
Is it cool if
I sit with you for a minute?
Crazy morning.
Vicky's kind of a bitch.
I get why you're mad.
She's hooking up with Zach.
It's just so shitty.
It sucks.
Plus, that stupid flower thing
he does with every girl?
-It's not stupid.
-No, no.
Yeah, I mean...
yours is great.
Do you wanna give Zach
his jacket back?
You know, uh,
I can intro you
to some other firms.
You're a talented analyst,
and they'd be down to meet.
Thanks.
You wanna get coffee and
we can talk about it some time?
Dinner?
Whatever.
Do you need money?
'Cause I can give you money.
I can give you $1,000.
It just has to be our secret.
-Is that a yes?
-Don't touch me.
-I was just--
-Leave me alone.
Why?
What am I supposed to do now?
What am I gonna do now?
What do you want?
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Do you think that
this is some kind of joke?
I know a joke.
Fuck!
Yes!
I'll kill everything,
and I'll make you watch!
I'm a carnivore too!
I hate you!
Yeah!
-All right, you stay in the car.
-But Mom--
Hera?
Hera!
Mom!
Come on...
Come on, Hera.
Please don't be dead.
Hera?
Hera, I see you in there.
Hera, let me the fuck in.
What are you doing?
I'm breathing.
Ugh!
God!
Do you wanna tell me
what's going on?
Tell me, because this is crazy.
You didn't come over
for Monday dinner.
You haven't answered your phone.
Work said you got let go
last week for stabbing someone?
She attacked Grace.
- What?
- She attacked Grace!
My flower.
Mine.
Where is it?
Or is it with the trees
you keep talking about?
Do you know
how fucking hard it is
to barely have time
to be a single mom,
and work 60 hours a week,
and take care of
an adult fucking woman?
Crap.
I have to take Corey to therapy.
-It's fine.
-Grace! Grace!
He told me to do it.
Hera?
Hera? Oh, my God.
You okay? You okay?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Hera, what the fuck?
Oh, my God.
I'm taking your keys away.
Can you help her?
Zach!
Zach! Zach! Zach!
Zach?
Zach? Zach.
Vicky.
Vicky, where's Zach?
- I don't know.
- Where's Zach?
I don't know,
he doesn't talk to me anymore!
-Where is he?
-Hera, stop! What is going on?
Please, I need Zach.
I'll do whatever he wants,
but Grace,
she's ours and she's dying!
What the fuck
are you talking about?
You need to get out of here.
It is a fucking plant!
He made me take
the morning-after pill,
but Grace, she's dying.
I need someone to help her!
Now, listen.
I'll be good to you.
I'm gonna be good to you,
but you need to leave
or I'm calling the cops
and slapping a restraining order
on your ass. Do you hear me?
Okay. Okay.
Do you wanna tell me
what the hell's going on?
Where are we going?
My house.
I wanna go home.
Why the fuck
would I take you there?
So you can make me leave work
in the middle of the day again?
The higher-up...
I didn't wanna
have sex with him.
What?
And he made me take
the morning-after pill.
Oh, Hera,
why didn't you tell me?
I tried.
Grace...
The plant.
I loved her so much.
She made me feel like
nothing bad had ever happened.
I didn't mean to hit Corey.
She's been drawing you
flowers ever since it happened.
She feels bad.
She shouldn't feel bad.
No one should ever hit her,
including me.
I'm really sorry.
I really just wanna go home,
though.
I-- I need to clean up
and-- and sleep in my own bed.
I won't do anything stupid.
Okay.
But I'll be over tomorrow
morning to check on you.
You can apologize to Corey.
Goodbye.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Coming.
- Hey?
- You good?
Are you drunk?
Uh, a couple of us
went out after work.
Figured I'd come...
check on my girl.
You-- you okay? You wanna--
-Hey, do you wanna talk about--
-No, not really.
I thought I was your mentor.
You need to go.
Gabe just dropped me off.
You want me to get a ride?
That's gonna be, like, $50.
-I could really use some coffee.
-I don't have any coffee.
Okay.
All right.
But you gotta tell me
what's going on.
What, you were crying for me
all day and now...
now, what?
You-- you won't look at me?
Have you started
applying for jobs yet?
I mean, that must have
been really embarrassing.
I could write you
a letter of recommendation,
maybe make a couple phone calls.
Hey, just-- just
as long as us hooking up
doesn't get out, you know?
Okay?
What?
I thought we had a good time--
I thought we had a good time.
What was good?
-Well, you were great.
-At?
-Getting fucked by me.
-Please let me go.
-Oh, Hera.
-Please, let me go!
Hey, hey, hey. It's okay.
All right. What-- what is wrong?
You did this to me.
What are you talking about?
You just pushed me off of you.
I didn't want to
and you forced me.
I didn't force you
to do anything.
You ruined everything for me!
My career!
Can you keep your voice down?
You raped me.
If you say that shit again--
-What, that you raped me?
-You need to back down.
See, this is why
you couldn't handle the job,
or a relationship.
You are fucking crazy.
And now you want people
to feel sorry for you?
Is-- is this a cry for help?
You are just another
dumb fucking slut
trying to whore her way to
the top of the corporate ladder.
Oh. Are you gonna cry?
You gonna cry some more? Huh?
You couldn't even take care
of a stupid fucking plant!
You can't keep a plant alive?
What the fuck?
Stop, stop, stop! Stop...
I-- I'm sorry.
Please...
let-- let me go.
I'll get--
I'll get you... a better job.
I am the glass ceiling.
You drew all these for me?
- I felt really bad about--
- It's okay.
You saw something beautiful
and you wanted it.
Next time we'll ask permission,
though, okay?
But no one should ever
hit or touch you.
Okay? And I'm really sorry.
And if anyone does, you tell me.
Okay?
Okay, Aunt Hera.
These are really good.
You know, I used to draw.
- I might start again.
- You should.
Do you wanna see something nice?
Look at that.
It grew!
Are we safe?