♪
Come on, come on, hustle!
[Laughs]
♪
[Background chatter]
Yeah, just go, that's fine!
Why would I care?!
It's what you're the best at anyway!
Again?! You're kidding, right?
[Background chatter]
Jobs out of Cleveland.
[Laughs]
[Phone ringing]
He's crazy. Do not answer that.
I don't have the time.
I don't have the energy.
[Phone ringing]
That's it.
It's, it's fine-
Hello?
[Sigh] He is a psycho.
[Lightning, thunder]
[Gasp]
[Muffled scream]
[whisper] Jonathan...
[whisper] Jonathan! Jonathan!
Hey, Caroline.
Cops were at your house.
They can't find Mina.
Your wife just called the
office and you have to-
She needs you to come home.
The cops were at your house.
She called the office.
Because something happened
and they can't find Mi-
Mina!
♪
Nelson!
Nelson, open this damn door!
Nelson, open this damn door now!
Nelson, open this door now!
Where is he?!
Release me, Edgar.
You are behaving like a madman.
No!
Madmen know nothing.
I know what he did.
You see more than you let on...
You cannot protect him!
I am doing nothing of the sort.
I have no idea where my son is.
To be suspected of this vile
crime- my son is no murderer!
Liar!
He killed her, Nelson!
My daughter!
Where is he? You know!
Impossible.
I haven't seen him in weeks.
[Laughs]
Why do you bother Nelson?
There's no way out of this.
When I find him, he's a dead man.
Who do you think you are?!
This is a society, Edgar.
You are innocent
until proven guilty.
You defend him?
You know as well as I do what
he is.
What he was capable of!
It could only have ended
this way.
Damn me for not putting an end
to it... and damn you Nelson!
You disappoint me Edgar!
I never wronged you!
Never gave you
any reason for insult!
Edgar! Edgar!
Blood?
Don't you dare!
No!
Bastard!
[Crying]
You think this is finished, huh?
I won't let you decide
when it's over.
Not until I'm satisfied.
What's this?
Spaghetti.
No. This.
It just feels empty around here.
That's all.
It's silly, I know.
Part of me thinks she may step
through our door at any moment
as if...
...it's all a bad dream.
Oh, hello Edgar.
Have a seat.
What is happening here?
You're very deep in
your own head.
You know,
I was thinking about what you
had said,
which means, you were thinking about
what you had said.
What I said?
About not letting me decide
when it's over.
As in the young man who killed
your daughter.
Not me per-se,
I'm only a representation.
Yes, I understand! What of it?!
Well, who's to decide?
You're just a sad, angry father
with no part in the events
that took place...
save being the sole witness to
my personal “execution. ”
And me?
I'm just a dead guy.
A swinging corpse.
It's all out of our hands,
really.
It's not that easy to
live with it
My wife and I wake up every
morning without our daughter.
always an empty place
at the table...
I'm not good at
feeling powerless.
So what? What can you
possibly do about it
Excuse me! How dare you after
what you've done!
Not me Edgar, I'm only a
representation of-
Yeah, yeah, right, right.
You're just- you're just insane
that's all you are.
[heart beating]
Insanity breeds insanity, Edgar.
What? What do you mean?!
[Sigh] You'll see.
[Alarm clock]
Edgar!
Hello Caroline, hove you been?
I'm fine. I thought you weren't
coming back until next week?
Why wait?
Losing my mind sitting at home.
Can't be doing my wife any good.
We just need time to ourselves.
I guess that's to be expected...
So, Lenore's doing better then?
Yes.
Edgar! Um, why don't you join
me for a cup of coffee?
No thanks Caroline.
I just need to work.
Edgar wait a second-
Why is this door locked?
Why, hello Edgar.
What are you doing in my office?
Edgar!
Pleasure to have you back!
Uh, Mister Nelson here, see, we were-
we were just using your office
to sign a few things.
I just closed the mortgage on
my estate.
Just a week shy of
my seventy-first birthday.
Can you believe it?
Yes uh, pretty old...
By the way, Edgar.
You'll be happy to know that I'm
thinking of selling it all.
Too many bad memories,
as it were.
That's a shame.
Yes, it is a shame.
My son always wanted to inherit
my land.
But, hmm... oh well.
Thank you for your business
Mister Nelson.
I want you to know your money
is always good here.
I appreciate that.
Oh, Edgar, by the way...
I never told you how sorry I am
for your loss.
Now that I understand
what that feels like.
Perhaps I'll be conducting
further business with the bank.
I hope these recent
events haven't soured our
professional relationship?
Have a good day, Mr. Nelson.
And you too, my dear.
Edgar.
What a piece of work.
Don't let him get to you Edgar.
Find something Edgar?
What is all this?
Why is this blood in here?
Why do you think
there's blood there?
Animal sacrifices? I don't...
What on earth were you involved
in in here?
Why didn't I stop you?
Have some coffee Edgar.
Maybe it was never about
stopping me.
Maybe it was more
about, helping me,
you're now thinking to yourself.
Please, you were beyond help.
What a ridicous thought.
Maybe my hand was forced?
To kill my daughter? Why?
What could she have possibly
have done to deserve that?
I don't know, I'm just
throwing things out there.
You're useless.
You were useless in life.
You haunt my mind
with your uselessness.
like some awful reminder-
even in death!
Like your father's
terrible eyeball.
He's mocking me now by the way,
your father?
He had the gall to
compare my tragedy with his.
I think you can honestly attest
to the absurdity of that.
He's frightened of you.
Did you hear what I said?!
He wants to make me suffer
for his own amusement.
He's sick!
Nothing frightens him, that's why
life is such a joke to him!
He's frightened of
what you might do.
That I might do what?
[Sigh]
You have many questions Edgar...
Enough with the rhetoric,
give me some answers
You think I have to listen to
this, to keep coming back here?
Well, I don't!
Then why do you?!
What are you afraid of?
Maybe you need to seek out
some answers, Ed?
Maybe when you're
awake, perhaps?
[Gasping]
[Sigh]
♪
GHOSTLY WHISPER:
Edgar...
[Floor creaks]
[Ghostly whispers]
[Light piano keys]
[Light organ keys]
[Steady heart beating]
[Fast heart beating]
What are you doing?
What is that?
It's driving me mad!
GHOSTLY WHISPER:
Edgar... Edgar...
Edgar... Edgar... Edgar...
[Striking calculator keys]
Mrs. Sally Winters deposited
two-hundred and forty dollars.
Two-hundred and forty...
Walter Kaegen deposited
three hundred and twenty-two dollars
and ninety-four cents.
Twenty-two ninety-four, was it?
Yes.
And ninety-four...
Caesar Benedict withdrew one-
thousand eight-hundred dollars,
Withdrew one-thousand eight-
hundred? I wonder what for?
He was never very good
with his finances.
Hmm, I couldn't say.
Finally, Mrs. Frazier deposited
fifty-one dollars
and thirty four cents.
Yes, that's the exact number.
Ah, yes Mrs. Frazier, she was
always so meticulous
You're thinking about him,
aren't you?
Pardon?
I know what you're considering!
What you're thinking, in here!
Is it the eye, Edgar?
His insanity breeds insanity.
You mustn't allow him to-
What did you say?
I need you here, Edgar.
And we need Nelson's money! You know
that, you've read the books!
Stop talking. You don't know
what you're speaking of.
You're right. Edgar,
of course you're right. I don't.
It won't be anything unsavory,
will it?
Oh, Caroline,
how are you my dear?
We've just finished here.
Good day, Edgar.
There was, yelling...
is everything okay, Edgar?
Edgar?
You knew my daughter,
you knew her well.
Yes, Edgar.
I knew her very well.
It was gruesome, the murder,
what he did to her?
Yes.
But I don't want to talk about-
He took her apart!
Edgar...
And I'm...
just putting it together now.
What are you talking about?
I just need this to be over.
Edgar, what do you mean-
it is over.
Have a good night, Caroline.
[Raven sqawks]
GHOSTLY WHISPER:
Edgar...
[Starts vehicle]
Hey Edgar, if
you're not to busy with all those
wicked thoughts going
through your head...
you mind helping me out here?
This is her blood.
You strangled her,
drove to your father's barn, dragged her
lifeless body in here and-
Then you took her to pieces.
Why on earth would you do that?
With that especially.
That looks like a pretty
difficult task for just a knife.
You sure that's it?
There has to be plenty
of more useful equipment
in this old barn.
Oh, I'm sure...
These are your thoughts,
remember?
This is all in your head.
If you wanted to find a knife-
you found a knife!
Hell, you should have
discovered a chainsaw.
Messy? Sure, but-
far more effective.
That wasn't very nice.
You were an idiot,
a complete moron.
You sure about that?
And an asshole!
Unfortunately- and I hesitate to
give the man any credit
you didn't inherit a
single trait from your father.
I can't speak to that.
Although an asshole
himself,
Nelson has always
been a gentleman.
Well, now that's true.
Quite a successful
businessman as well.
Insanely driven and determined
compulsive if you will...
manipulative even, I suppose.
Yes... manipulative...
that's just what I was thinking.
[Car horn]
What the...
Who is that?
[Sigh] Caroline...
I can not fathom what is
going on inside your head!
You have no idea.
This isn't funny!
I saw your face. Don't
tell me I have this wrong.
Have what wrong?!
Edgar, you can't harass him.
This isn't healthy!
You have a wife at home,
you have responsibilities to your-
self, to your job and to me-
Are you out of your mind?
What are you even doing
here?!
Just go away and
stop bothering me!
Nobody asked for your concern!
I'm sorry Edgar...
but this has gone too far.
This is it! We love you
but this is it!
Now get in
your car and go home!
I didn't realize.
You're right, you're right...
I'm- I'm sorry.
GHOSTLY WHISPER:
Edgar...
[Muffled yelp]
I'm sorry.
[Muffled scream]
JONATHAN VO:
Edgar, what are you doing...
Edgar, what are you doing?
Evening the score.
Now that's something.
Here I am, your daughter's
murderer,
swinging from the
gallows,
and you claim
that's not enough.
No! There's just too many
loose ends, inconsistencies.
Nothing on the surface
makes sense
as to why
you did what you did.
You'renot making any sense.
You thought you had
it all figured out.
Shut up!
[Moans]
I do have it figured out,
that's why I'm here!
What's with the mystery then?
Could it be such a far-fetched
notion
you find it hard
putting it into words?
Come now Edgar, are you
afraid it's driven you mad?
Do, not, call, me, mad!
[Grunts]
[Laughs]
Ah, but you are mad, Edgar.
You're speaking to yourself.
[Ghostly whispers]
JONATHAN VO:
So tell me,
[Ghostly whispers]
JONATHAN VO:say it out loud,
what does it all mean?
It all means, you were too stupid
to do it of your own free will.
You were a pawn. As exploited
as anyone possibly can be.
No, no, no.
That doesn't add up now does it?
How did such a simple man
like you
come up with such afar-fetched notion?
I'm not imagining it.
I've been drawn to it.
Led here one more time
to set things right.
JONATHAN VO:
Interesting, isn't it?
How a person decides
who should live or die...
So tell me, before you do
what you're about to do.
Stop talking to me, I don't
know what I'm about to do!
[Steady heart beating]
Wait.
Do you hear that?
Do you know what that is?
Mortal terror Edgar,
that's what that sound is.
Not from pain or grief but from
the very bottom of his soul.
He knows he's going to die-
just as you know,
why you're going to kill him.
I don't know why!
Oh, come off it Edgar! You've
already made up your mind.
How does he make you feel when
he looks at you?
When he stares down
your anguish, your affliction?
[Crying]
He mocks me!
Keep telling yourself that!
It's the eye,Edgar!
You know it's the eye!
It's always been the eye!
What is this? Is it my time?
No, no it can't be you!
[Screams]
No!
[Strangling]
[Choking]
[Struggling to yell]
No!
[Strangling]
[Choking]
[Heavy breathing]
[Laughing] Well what have
you got to say now?!
That's what I figured...
JONATHAN VO:
Now what are you going to do?
Shut up!
[Heavy breathing/struggling]
Just because no one saw this,
doesn't make it a perfect crime,
Edgar.
Stay out of this!
What are you going to do
with the body?
I don't know, I don't know!
[Floor creaks]
[Closes door]
[Heavy breathing/struggling]
I wouldn't do it here.
No...
They'll figure it out.
They always figure it out.
You can't be here.
You're not here!
Only in my mind!
Say what you will,
though it seems like we've gone
pretty far already..
what's a little more
crazy gonna hurt?
Yeah? If you're so smart,
what would you do with him?!
Keep it clean.
And you should probably forget what
I said about the chainsaw.
The fun part's about
notgetting caught.
The fun part?
Go to hell!
This isn't fun, it's...
It's what, Edgar?
It's necessary.
If you thought there was
no going back before, Edgar,
Well then...
I think you know that,
as well as I do.
[Chopping/heavy breathing]
[Heavy breathing/struggling]
[Heavy breathing]
[Clock strikes]
[Startled]
[Knock on the door]
Who, who is it?
State Police.
Please open the door, sir.
[Knock on the door]
A-absolutely,
just one moment officer!
Let's keep this quick I-
[sneeze]
Say no more.
Hello Officers,
how can I help you?
Are you Mister Nelson, sir?
Me? No. I, I- I'm a good friend
of his.
Well, I was called
out here by him, in fact...
although he's no
longer here I'm afraid.
I see.
And, who may you be, sir?
Me? My name is Edgar.
Well, Edgar, I assume
that's your vehicle out
there in the ditch.
Yeah, that's right,
it's a bit slippery out.
Sir, I'm Officer Mellish,
this is my partner,
Officer Starkwell.
We have two questions:
why are you here,
and where is Mister Nelson?
I was called out here, Officer,
as I've said.
But when I got
here, Nelson no longer was.
I'm not sure
where he's gone.
And why were
you called out here?
From the way that Nelson
spoke to me over the phone,
I felt he was in danger.
Is that so?
Well, It's not like him
Officer to,
to sound so
fearful over the phone.
Being that I've watched over
him over the years
I felt it
necessary to come right out.
Unfortunately Nelson seems
to have gone off by himself.
Or not by himself.
Frankly Officers, he's not been
in his right mind since his son
passed away a short time ago.
Well, you don't think
he's in trouble do you?
Is that why you're here?
Mind if we come in, Edgar?
No... no, no not at all.
I don't mind telling you Edgar
that we were called out for
the exact same reason.
Oh, is that so?
Can I ask by whom?
Anonymous.
Although, not surprisingly,
they shared your concerns.
Does Mr. Nelson drive?
No, he has a service, sir.
Well, we'll have to call to see
if he was in fact picked up.
Oh dear, you don't think he
walked off by himself, do you?
Is that impossible?
We can't afford to rule anything out
now, can we Edgar?
No, no we certainly can't,
Officer.
[Piano key strikes]
And how exactly do you know
Mr. Nelson, Edgar?
Well, I've served him for years
at the bank in town-
we've become quite close!
I've looked in on him here
and there as he's gotten on
in years- his needs-
well, he needs some help some-
times and, what with his son...
well, I don't need to tell
you his,
well, his mind
wanders a bit and,
so if he's taken to up
and walking off by himself...
it seems more possible
the more I think about it.
Uh huh. You wouldn't mind if we
took a look around would you-
That sounds like
a bad cold, Officer?
Ah, it's nothing, really.
Let me make you gentlemen
a hot pot of tea while you
look around!
That won't be necessar-
[sneeze]
Ah, no no no,
it's no problem at all.
There's definitely
something going on here.
You don't think he's going
to try and run, do you?
Nah, he thinks his explanations
are working for him.
Let's see if we can get him
to crack. I'll look upstairs.
[Whistling]
JONATHAN VO:
They know what you did.
[Screams]
STARKWELL VO:
Everything all right in there?
Uh, uh everything's fine Officer,
your tea will be ready shortly.
They're toying with you.
They're not idiots.
You made too many mistakes.
Shut up!
"He called me, we're such
good friends!" What bullshit.
You don't know anything.
What can they possibly do, huh?
Nelson's nowhere to be found,
there's no sign of a struggle,
no sign of any wrongdoing at
all, he's simply gone!
They're Officers, Edgar,
they'll search the house.
They've already seen the broken
frame to the front door.
Christ, Edgar,
they'll search the barn!
And find what?
There's nothing they can
find there I can't simply deny!
Nothing? Just wait a week.
I'm sure the house will be rather
pungent. Try denying that.
Doesn't matter!
As soon as they're satisfied
here tonight, I'm leaving.
Edgar, what about Caroline
back there in the trunk?
CAROLINE OC:
Heeeeeelp! Get me out of here!
You don't just shove someone
in a trunk
and think they're
going to keep their mouth shut.
You think she's
going to lie for you?
CAROLINE OC:
Heeeeeelp! I'm in a trunk!
It doesn't matter!
They'll never find me!
By morning I'll be gone!
JONATHAN VO:
[Sigh] Whatever you say, Edgar..
[Teapot whistling]
Your tea, Officer.
Come here and take a
close look at this, Edgar.
What do you make of it?
Huh. It looks as if the wood
has broken off around the latch.
Worn out, maybe.
Over time, do you think?
No, Edgar, I don't
think that at all.
Ah, thank you.
I could use this-
late nights, you know?
[Sips] Mmm, it's good.
[Sips] Ah...
Can I ask what you're
looking for, exactly?
Oh, anything suspicious, Edgar.
Anything that might show us why
an old man- seventies? Eighties?
Uh, seventy-one this week,
in fact.
Why such a man of his age
might up and disappear late
at night- early in the
morning, as it were.
It's a bit strange, I'd say.
Speaking of, what did he say?
What did he say?
On the phone.
He called you, remember?
[Laughs] Oh, yes! Of course...
I'm, I'm trying to recall,
there was nothing much to it, really-
it was extremely brief.
Fear, mostly, in his voice.
Asked me my name a few times,
asked if I was alright?
He asked if youwere alright?
Yes! Strange, I thought
because I'm,
I'm just fine.
Just, completely fine.
Are we sure of that, Edgar?
JONATHAN VO:
Look out Edgar!
All he's thinking about
is clubbing you across the
back of the knee and placing
his foot over your throat!
Well! I, I should
go get Officer, uh...
Mellish.
Mellishhis, his hot tea.
So. Who do you think
called them, Edgar?
[Quietly] No one!
Stop bothering me!
Let's see, your boss Mr. Singer,
he was spot on, wasn't he?
What's the word he used...
SINGER:
It won't be anything unsavory...
Oh yeah, unsavory,
that's certainly a
fine way of putting it.
He's an idiot. Totally inept!
You know, Edgar, you haven't
quite been yourself lately.
Mr. Singer's noticed,
Caroline's noticed...
Impossible...
And Lenore, well,
she's defitely noticed.
How dare you! I'm not
some maniac loose in the
night, some deranged
psychotic waiting to strike
at anyone near him!
My wife, scared to be
near me... preposterous!
Of course, and yet,
here we are, Edgar
[Knocks on door]
Oh. Come on in Edgar.
You don't think the
old man would mind if
I sit on the bed, do you?
I brought you some tea, Officer.
Yes, yes that's right...
Mm, good. Just what I needed.
Glad I can be of help.
We appreciate it Edgar,
we really do.
Have to be quite a view out here
in the daytime.
Nothing but
fields and trees, for miles it
seemed on our drive out here.
Yep, all out here alone.
Not a soul around.
‘Course, can't see much of that
at this time of the morning.
Shame, really...
hardly believe we could find
a witness to the crime.
What crime would
that be, Officer?
Just speculating Edgar,
that's all.
You see I can't help but
think of the worst possible
thing that could happen to
poor old Mr. Nelson.
Then I work backwards.
Because that helps, Edgar.
Helps me get in the
correct state of mind.
Helps me think like they do.
The supposed criminal
or criminals, that is.
I see.
Then again, maybe the poor
old bastard just wandered off.
Who knows, anyway.
Well I, I I guess I
wouldn't put it past him.
Has it ever occurred to
you to just shut up?
[Quietly] Has it ever
occurred to you?!
Of course I've considered
it,
it's just that it doesn't
seem so likely.
Why don't you join us
downstairs before we go, Edgar?
Just a few more questions.
I scoured it, I got nothing down
here. What about upstairs?
No apparent signs of a struggle,
the old man's bed looks recently
slept in, the closet's a mess...
other than that...
[Loud sigh]
Edgar, are you certain that
he called you from here?
Well, [clears throat] no,
I suppose I'm not.
Uh, I prefer to stand, thanks.
Can I ask you
Officers a question?
Of course Edgar.
Am I suspected of something?
[Laughs] Absolutely, Edgar.
Did you think otherwise?
[Laughs] Can I ask
what you base that on?
You can simply ask us,
Edgar.
You don't have
to ask if you can ask us.
It is a bit peculiar,
wouldn't you say, Edgar?
That you're the only one here.
You are the only one here,
in a house that isn't yours.
You've come a long way Edgar.
[Laughs]
Since you journeyed
into a barn.
I uh... [clears throat]
I think I'd like to have a
lawyer present if uh, you
Officers are going to ask
any more questions.
[Laughs]
JONATHAN VO:
A helpless father.
Now Edgar, you're
really not in a position to
request something like that.
JONATHAN VO:
...without a daughter.
Edgar, we could take you in
on this alone if we so wished.
Is that what both of
you want?
Is that where
this has been going?
And you somehow
managed, to take your part
in all this madness. As if
there was no other way, really.
Honestly? No, Edgar. We don't
take any pleasure in simply
arresting suspects. Because then
you have to witness the denials,
the lies and all that...
Paperwork.
Oh God, yes!
The bloody paperwork.
And everyone played their role
so perfectly.
A carefully
orchestrated three-act play.
[Low heartbeat]
And you know, Edgar, I can't
wait to see how it all ends.
[Steady heartbeat]
[Quietly] Stop talking to me!
I'm sorry?
Edgar?
Edgar, now is not
the time to go silent.
We know something about you.
We know just why you
might be here this evening.
Revenge is a tricky thing,
Edgar.
No one keeps their
hands clean for too long.
What would your
daughter say about all this?
[Screams]
Hey, easy Edgar.
Edgar...
Ah... that sound again...
pounding! Hammering away!
Tearing my brain apart!
Edgar, restrain yourself!
Edgar, calm yourself!
You're just making this
situation much worse!
Don't you hear it?! That
hideous sound?! Pounding!
Thumping the thoughts from
my brain! I can't take it!
[Laughs/cries] No!
He's losing his mind!
Calm yourself Edgar! Stop
what you're doing right now!
You're- you're villains!
Here! Here!
I'll tear the boards away!
I admit it! I admit everything!
Just make it stop!
Please make it stop!
Make what stop?!
[Loud heartbeat]
Oh my God...
Jesus!
He's hacked him to pieces!
[Laughs/cries]
No! You hear it! That sound!
It's the beating of his
hideous heart!
[Laughs/cries]
[Steady heartbeat]
[Heartbeat]