(dramatic music)
♪ Oh, I'll make you better
(Ian) I don't do this a lot.
Neither do I.
So, have you been
doing all right?
I'm sorry, that was
a silly question.
Of course not.
No, it's okay.
I've been fine, all
things considered.
Of course, it's hard with
two daughters, and...
I still miss him.
It still feels like a
dream that he's dead.
You probably don't
wanna talk about this now.
It's actually kind of
nice to talk about it.
It's been over a year, and
no one even says his name.
So...
Wish I knew him
better, you know?
I wish I got to know you better.
I mean, we barely spoke
in high school, right?
Yeah.
Crazy how we bumped
into each other.
Well, you two probably
would've been friends.
Mm.
Yeah, he was a
really great guy.
An amazing husband,
a wonderful father.
(Maya laughs)
Wow.
You know, my mom
died a few years ago,
my father before that, so I
know what you're going through.
Yeah.
This is probably
a heavy conversation
for a first date, right?
(laughs) Just a little.
So I'll see you at
church on Sunday, right?
Yes.
But I've got a babysitter
until midnight.
Oh, okay.
So guess that means I
get to hang out with you
a little longer.
Guess it does.
♪ Why so
♪ We can go anywhere
you want tonight ♪
♪ I could pull up,
tell me what you are ♪
♪ I could've held, stay low
♪ Look at my G on the radio
♪ Players running
through my bone ♪
♪ 5:00 a.m. and I'm
still not home ♪
♪ Can we go on and on,
try to keep it going ♪
♪ When it's all but gone, yeah
♪ No matter where we go, on
and on, I'mma let it flow ♪
♪ Where you going
♪ Turn it around
♪ Turn it around, we on a roll
♪ Where we go
♪ You don't know
♪ No one left, just me
and my girls, yeah ♪
♪ I was led through
something, on and on ♪
♪ And we can't
stop for nothing ♪
♪ I don't have to clarify
♪ There ain't no reason why
♪ You do what's right for you
♪ And I'mma do what's mine
Hello, Rachelle?
Are you okay if the girls
and I stay for a while?
Girl, I have had enough.
I can't do this anymore.
Okay, I will.
Maya, please.
Nope.
Don't wanna hear it.
I can fix this.
Ian, I have had enough.
I'm done.
Maya, I'm not the only
one who's fallen apart.
You've fallen apart too.
You've struggled and
I've helped you, baby,
I've helped you get through it.
Are you gonna
go there with me?
I was depressed because
I lost my husband,
but I got my life together.
You, on the other hand,
can't seem to do that.
Baby, all right,
look, look, look.
I just need a little
more time, okay?
I'll go to the program.
I'll go get help, baby.
I want to be better.
I just need a little more time.
I told you I am done.
What part don't you understand?
Baby, look, I, I love you.
I love you, and I
love your kids, baby.
Look at me.
Baby, I want to be
a real family, okay?
There's nothing more that I
want than a real family, okay?
I'm, I'm going to
go to the program.
I'm going to get help.
Baby, look at me.
One more chance, that's it.
Ian, you have
had enough chances.
What else do you want from me?
How many do you
want me to give you?
I have trust you, you
have violated my trust.
What do you want from me?
Baby, just one more, okay?
So, I was waiting
for the right moment.
The right moment never came,
so, you know, that's
all, that's all my fault.
Love you so much.
I'm sorry for everything
that I've done.
Maya, I'll go get help, I'll
do whatever I need to do,
but I can't lose you.
I can't.
Baby, I am no good without you.
I'm no good alone, baby.
We've been through
so much, so much.
Baby, please don't
give up on me now.
Please.
You don't make me regret this.
One more chance.
But you have to promise me,
promise me no more drinking
and no more gambling.
I mean it.
Okay.
I'm serious.
(kissing)
Mama.
Mama?
Mama!
Oh, God, baby.
What's wrong?
You wouldn't wake up.
Oh, Mommy's so sorry.
I must have overslept again.
Look, why don't
you head downstairs
and I'll meet you
in a minute, yeah?
Can I have a kiss?
(Maya kisses)
You got on my favorite PJs.
(Maya laughs)
Ow.
Noelle, Grace!
(ominous music)
(Ian) Maya.
Oh my God, Ian, you scared me.
What are you doing home?
I left work early.
I decided to take a shower here.
What, what are you doing?
I don't know, what does
it look like I'm doing?
It looks like you've lost it.
Funny.
No, the nanny starts today,
so I figured a little extra
security couldn't hurt.
You know, since Mama's going
back to work full time,
she needs to keep an
eye on her babies.
I get that, but, baby,
you worry too much.
All right?
Come on now, you stay with
a cop, you live with a cop.
Not to mention the sexiest
cop in the district.
Oh my God.
I'm all the security you need.
Girl, what do you
think she's gonna pull?
Well, first of all, she
was the only nanny available,
so that's telling you a lot.
And I've never left a
stranger with the kids before.
Right, I get that,
but you're still
worrying too much.
And that looks a little creepy.
That doesn't look creepy.
Baby, that, that's
a little creepy.
Can you take it down, please?
Fine.
Thanks.
(Maya laughs)
God.
Look, I'm, I'm gonna
go change, okay?
All right.
And promise me one thing?
No more weird stuff, at
least while I'm gone.
It wasn't weird.
No, that was pretty weird.
(kisses) My wife.
I'll be back.
(ominous music)
(dramatic music)
Hey, and here is the kitchen.
Oh, nice.
And here we have
Noelle, and this is Grace.
Hi, girls.
Hey, Ian.
Ian, this is Elle.
Elle, Ian.
The new babysitter.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Have we met before?
I mean, you look familiar.
I don't think we've met,
but Maya gave me
the full rundown.
You have a beautiful home.
Thank you.
What's their usual
bedtime routine?
Anything you want me to do?
We don't usually
start bedtime stuff
for another hour or
two, but if you want,
you can go with the
girls to their room
and you guys can get
to know each other.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
All right, girls,
what do you say?
You wanna show me your room?
(Noelle) Yeah.
Noelle and Grace,
such beautiful names.
All right.
How's your day?
Oh, don't you mean
how was my morning?
I've been so exhausted lately
that I slept through a
meeting with the principal.
Maybe you shouldn't go in now.
Honey.
Look, we agreed that when
the girls were of age,
I would go back to work.
You said that you
were okay with that.
I know, baby,
but sometimes I think you put
too much pressure on yourself.
You just need to take
it one day at a time.
Maybe you're right.
How's work going?
Mm.
I talked to the Chief today.
And?
And they are promoting
your boy to Lieutenant.
(Maya cheering)
Finally.
(laughs) Oh, baby.
You know, it's
not settled yet.
They still have to push
through some paperwork
and everything, but
it's safe to say
that I will be on my best
behavior for the next few weeks.
Well, you have
nothing to worry about.
(laughs) Oh, boy.
Well, I guess we gotta have
something a little fancier
than nuggets to celebrate
that big promotion.
And I could think of
one way to celebrate.
That's right, I have the
perfect present in mind.
A little prince.
A son to carry my name.
Baby, I told you I
am done with diapers.
I have a career that I love
that I wanna get back to,
and here you are trying to
keep me barefoot and pregnant?
Would you stop it?
Call me Lieutenant.
No, no, no, no.
Have you been drinking?
Oh, gosh.
Come on, baby,
it was just one drink with
the guys to celebrate.
And look, now it's our
turn to celebrate, okay?
No.
- Just one drink.
- No.
- Just one.
- No, Ian.
We know how this thing
goes, it's a cycle.
One drink goes to the
next, goes to the next,
and here we are
back at square one.
Baby, you have a big
promotion on the line.
You can't jeopardize it.
Okay.
All right, I'm, I'm sorry.
We just have to find a
safer way to celebrate.
Baby, I already told you.
I can think of another
way we can celebrate.
Come on.
(kissing) Please.
Oh, baby.
Baby, grab a condom.
Ian, honey, come on,
please, grab a condom.
(phone chiming)
You're betting again?
Oh God, I can't believe you.
(Ian) Baby.
♪ Baby, we both just
lit the candle ♪
♪ Place it up, that's
when it's stable ♪
♪ I know the stakes are high
♪ All is fair in
love and strife ♪
♪ Come
(suspenseful music)
(Elle) Oh, coffee's ready.
Thanks, Elle.
(Ian) Morning.
(Maya) Good morning.
Hey.
I gotta make a call
with the principal.
I thought you slept
through that meeting.
Mm-hmm, but he was very
understanding and we rescheduled.
Well, that was nice of him.
Look, I might be late
(kisses) coming home tonight.
They have me out on
patrol all week, okay?
(Maya) All right.
(Ian) So, I'll see you later.
Okay, I'll see
you later, babe.
Have a good day.
Oh, I can only take one cup.
I can't be late when
I'm up for a promotion.
A promotion?
Well, that's wonderful.
I'll be Lieutenant
any day now.
Well, maybe I shouldn't
get my hopes up too high
until it's official, but...
I'm sure you're gonna get it.
Maya told me you've been at the
station for, what, 10 years?
Right?
Yeah.
You're like a local hero.
Give me too much credit, Elle.
I gotta get out here.
All right?
Welcome to the family.
Grabbed your mail again.
They really should put
the boxes further apart.
Thank you.
So you have company over?
Yeah, new nanny,
my wife's idea.
Quite the looker, for a nanny.
Have a good day, Mr. Stocklan.
(dramatic music)
The cab's on its way, so
I'm having a little pre-drink.
Girl, of course I don't
drink in front of Ian.
I've got a secret bottle stashed
away for special occasions.
(Maya laughs)
All right, see you soon.
Who was that?
That was Megan.
Oh.
Oh, honey, I'm
so sorry, I just-
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, babe.
Listen, I made
dinner reservations
at your favorite
restaurant tonight.
But, honey, I told you
I was going out tonight.
Baby, I know, but I just
wanted to surprise you.
Look, I'm tired of the
rift between us, all right?
And you'd be happy to know
that I'm meeting with my
sponsor in the morning.
Baby, I just wanna be perfect
for you, for the family.
Honey, that is so sweet,
but can we do this
tomorrow night instead?
No, baby, come on.
Look, I just wanna spend a
little more time with you
before you go back
to work, all right?
Listen, we still have
a chance, all right?
You've been tired lately, and
baby, I never get to see you.
So I wanna see you tonight.
The point is, I promised
Megan that I would go.
Okay, so what I'm hearing is
that you'd rather spend time
with your little friends than
stay home with me, right?
What, are you trying
to avoid me, Maya?
I'm not trying to avoid you.
Really?
We never spend
any time together.
No, because every time we do,
all you wanna talk
about is having a son.
Honey, I have told
you a million times
that I don't want another baby,
especially not with
someone who keeps on lying
about their drinking
and gambling.
Look, Ian, you are an addict.
So what you're saying is
you'll have another child,
just not by me, right?
Honey, that's not
what I'm saying.
I'm trying to say that I don't
want another kid, period.
But what about me, Maya?
Huh?
Why do I never get a say?
You're always telling
me what to do,
but you never listen
to what I want.
Ian, I am not trying
to tell you what to do.
I'm just asking you
to stop drinking
and gambling our savings away.
And if you think that's
me being controlling,
then I'm sorry to say it,
babe, but you're delusional.
You don't get to
speak to me like that.
Calm down.
I'm going out.
Let me!
I'm your husband.
You don't get to just walk out.
Ian.
We can talk about this tomorrow.
Please.
You know what?
Fine.
Do what you want.
Oh.
(tense music)
(Maya panting)
(body thuds)
Oh, baby.
Looks like your friends
are gonna miss you tonight.
(tense music)
Oh my God.
(Maya sighs)
(suspenseful music)
(solemn music)
(Maya crying)
(officers murmuring)
(dramatic music)
All right, what happened?
Man, I left my
phone in the office.
Gotta go back inside.
All right.
I'll wait for you, huh?
Hey, I'm Liz, Deputy Chief.
Hi.
Do you need help
with something?
I was hoping that
someone can help me out
with this situation that I-
- Maya.
Hey.
Hey, baby.
What are you doing here?
I thought you were
on patrol today.
I was, but I
left my phone here.
I'm sorry.
I know how much you hate
being a traffic cop.
Oh, (laughs) I know you've
been forgetting your lunch
a lot lately,
so I decided I would bring
you something just in case.
Thank you, baby.
Okay, I'm gonna leave.
Wait, wait, wait.
Are you sure you're doing okay?
Yes, honey, I'm fine.
Wait here.
It's nice to meet you.
Ian talks very highly of you.
Thanks.
That's sweet of you,
bringing him his lunch.
It's no big deal.
Yeah.
(clears throat) My phone number.
In case you ever need it.
Are you sure you're all right?
Baby, I'm just going to
go ahead and take you home.
Chief said it's all good.
He's gonna send
someone else out.
Honey, I told you
that's not necessary.
I'm just going
over to the store.
Baby, it's no big
deal, all right?
Besides, that's for the best.
You look a little tired anyway.
I'm gonna go change, all right?
Chief'll keep you company.
His daughter's in
the music class.
What you over there doing?
You reading?
Yeah.
(tense music)
Was there something else
you wanted to show me?
Come, come.
Oh, okay you want me
to see something else?
Let's go, all right.
Oh, what do you want me to see?
Can we play with my dolls?
Your dolls?
Of course we can
play with your dolls.
Is that your doll house?
Yeah.
Show me how you like
to play with your dolls.
(Elle laughs)
All right, I'll be right
back, sweetheart, okay?
- Okay.
Stay right here, okay?
(suspenseful music)
What about your car?
I'll bike in tomorrow
and pick it up.
What were you doing there, Maya?
Can't a wife do something
nice for her husband?
(suspenseful music)
(camera clicking)
No, seriously, what do
you think you were doing,
just showing up at
my work like that?
You know, I've just been
anxious lately and I missed you.
You know, sometimes
you forget your lunch,
so I figured I'd bring
something by the station.
Elle's home with the kids, so...
Ian, I'm sorry about yesterday.
You were right, we don't
spend enough time together,
just the two of us.
It's okay.
You sure that's everything?
I talked to the principal
and he said there
may not be a budget
to where they can hire
me back full-time.
In fact, they may be getting rid
of the music program
altogether, so...
You know how bad I've
wanted this, Ian.
I was just, I was upset.
But I knew you were the
person to cheer me on.
Baby, I'm sorry
to hear about that.
Wait, I thought your meeting
with the principal
was yesterday.
Yeah, but (laughs) I let
them borrow my music stand,
so I had to go back
and pick it up.
Would you mind stopping
at the grocery store?
Elle said she needed a few
things for dinner tonight.
(Ian) Can stop by there later.
Don't worry about that.
(camera clicking)
Hi.
Hi, little lady.
I'll be back downstairs
in a second, okay?
What you doing?
I'm planning a surprise
for your mommy and daddy.
They're gonna be really happy
about it, (laughs) okay?
They're gonna be so happy.
But you have to keep
it between me and you,
just for a little bit, okay?
You can't tell
them I was in here.
A surprise?
Yeah, like a surprise party!
Right?
So, this is our
little secret, okay?
Noelle?
Is that me?
Can I, let me see, let
me see if that's you.
Hold on, let, can I see it?
Give it back, Noelle.
Give it back.
Noelle, let me, okay.
Noelle.
This isn't funny, Noelle.
Give it back.
Ow, you're hurting me!
Give it back, I need it.
I need that back.
Come here, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
You okay?
I gotta get back to work.
Babe, you need to rest.
You seem a little off.
I know, but if they
keep the program,
I've got a lesson plan due.
You wanna go play?
Yeah, you do.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go play.
Remember I showed you that?
Elle, girls.
We need to talk.
Ian, I am busy.
Babe, we need to talk now.
(Maya) God, do you not
understand what busy means?
But you have to promise me.
Come on, pinky promise
that you won't say anything
to mommy or daddy.
We don't want daddy
to get mad, right?
All right, promise.
I promise.
Nice.
What's this?
Who did you show this to?
I didn't show it to anyone.
What is wrong with you, Maya?
What's wrong with me?
What happened last night, Ian?
You wanna tell me why I've
been sleeping so much?
Why I have no idea how I
got into the bed last night?
I know that you put
something in my drink.
If you show that to someone,
you will destroy our family.
You have already
destroyed our family!
With all of the gambling and
the drinking and now this?
You didn't give
me a choice, Maya.
You're being selfish.
I've adopted your kids
and what did I get, huh?
You know how much I want a son.
A family, baby,
a son to be able to
pass something down to,
just like my dad did for me.
That's exactly what
this world needs.
Another drunk trying to
deal with his demons.
I thought you were
different, Ian.
What you have done to me,
what you have done to my kids?
I just want a son.
A perfect family, baby.
Don't touch me.
Hello, I'd like to
report a disturbance.
You disgust me.
Wait, what did you say?
You think you're the only one
to be able to
gather up evidence?
What if the wrong things ended
up in your purse or your car?
Or maybe in your system
because of a drug-laced drink.
Huh?
I am going to be a lieutenant.
And baby, you already know
the influence that I have,
the people that I know.
Who do you think
they're gonna believe?
We're married, Maya.
And I'll have
custody of the kids
if anything was
to happen to you.
And then maybe then
I'll find a real woman
who can gimme the family
that I need, that I deserve.
Baby, if you try to run,
I'll find you.
You remember what
happened last time, right?
Cops pulled you over
and they brought you right
back home to me, to Daddy.
You know it could have ended
up very differently though,
right?
You will never escape me, Maya.
Ever.
My reach is too long.
(Maya gasping)
This right here?
This is your problem
because you're always
holding on to things
that haunt our family.
(paper ripping)
He was a better man
than you will ever be.
I thank God every day that those
kids are his and not yours.
I hate you.
I want my son.
(Maya crying)
(dishes rattling)
(glass smashing)
Ian.
Mommy!
Oh, hey, baby, hey.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Maya just broke a glass.
So, baby, watch your foot.
It's okay, baby,
everything's fine.
Why don't you take
Noelle back outside
while we clean up in here?
Where's Grace?
She's in her room.
You want me to go get her?
No, no, no, I'll take her.
I'll grab Grace too, 'cause I
gotta go to the store anyways.
I'll help clean up.
Let's let Maya clear her head.
No, no, Noelle can go.
Grace can stay right
here where she is.
Here with Daddy.
Okay, I'll stay and
give Grace her bath.
(knocking)
What's going on over here?
Is everything all right?
(solemn music)
(glass clinking)
(dramatic music)
(door slams)
Hernandez, you
know there's a reason
why they refer to
it as a call in.
I'm not calling you in.
We received a call from
one of your neighbors.
Something about a disturbance.
You know, me and Maya,
we just had a little spat.
I mean, you know how it is.
No, I don't.
Can I come in?
So, where is Maya?
That's your wife's name, right?
She went to the store.
Is this really necessary?
We have to follow through
with any calls we receive.
You know that.
Liz, Liz.
Always doing
everything by the book.
(Liz) That's me.
This way.
Liz, this is our nanny, Elle.
Oh.
Are you here to chat with
the soon to be Lieutenant?
I wanted to talk
to Maya actually.
Do you know when she'll be back?
No idea.
Sorry.
Is there a problem?
One of the neighbors called,
probably heard the scream
when Maya dropped the glass.
You know how clumsy she can be.
Glass?
Right, the glass.
(radio chattering)
Sounds like it's
gonna be a long shift.
Apparently.
I gotta go.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks for stopping by, Liz.
It's always a pleasure.
(tense music)
Hey.
I'm about to put the
kids down for a nap.
Miss Grace won't sleep until
you sing the alphabet remix.
Ah, she will be coming
after your job soon.
You seen anything interesting?
Are you all right?
(Maya vomiting)
Oh, Maya, are you okay?
Here, let me, let me help you.
Come on, I got you.
Sorry.
You okay?
Yeah.
Just haven't been feeling so
great these past couple days.
Something like a stomach bug?
Yeah.
I guess so.
Hey, Elle, don't
worry about it.
I don't think Maya's gonna
be eating with us anyway.
You know, she's
not feeling well.
She'll probably be down
for the rest of the night.
Plus the kids already ate, so...
Well, I don't mind
cooking for you.
And I could eat.
Maybe we just have
dinner together,
if that's okay with you.
Sure.
All right.
Go relax.
I'll take care of everything.
(ominous music)
I did, I used to play.
I was really good.
No.
- Yes, I was.
- No, you weren't.
Yeah, you should believe me.
Don't I look like a
basketball player?
Like, look at my arms.
You don't.
I work out.
And I definitely, definitely
can shoot some hoops, so...
Don't tell Maya about this.
What?
Of course not.
Thank you.
I haven't had the chance
to get to know you yet,
so it's nice to have
a drink with you.
It is nice.
Cheers.
And I deserve it, right?
I do.
I mean, it's not like Maya's
here to nag me about it anyway.
Gosh, she worries too much.
I can handle myself.
She cares.
That's, that's what that is.
That's what that is?
Yeah.
I mean, you guys
have a good thing.
(sighs) You know what?
I've been jealous
of women like Maya.
Jealous, why?
I just, come on.
She has everything
that I've ever wanted.
A good husband.
This house is amazing.
And your kids are so cute.
They really are.
I, I've always
wanted to be a mom.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
I've always
wanted to be a dad.
Really?
Yeah.
I mean, it'd be nice to
have one of my own one day.
You know, I mean, gosh,
that's all I've ever wanted.
You know, my dad used
to always tell me,
"A man's not a man unless
he knows how to raise one."
Oh, well, that's an
interesting saying.
He had a lot of them.
(Elle laughs)
All I've ever wanted to
do was to make him proud.
Show him that I'm
my own man, right?
Like, I hope I did that.
Yeah, well, I can relate.
I've had baby fever
since I was little.
Really?
Yes, I remember my
kindergarten teacher.
She, she was pregnant
and the next year she had
the cutest little baby.
I was so obsessed with him.
I kept wanting to carry him
around every time she visited.
She was my favorite teacher.
My kindergarten teacher
was a crazy bitch.
Really?
(laughs) Yeah, my gosh.
So sorry, that's awful.
Ms. Johnson.
Still remember her name.
I will never forget her.
(laughs) Hey, where,
where'd you say you
went to school at again?
Seattle.
Hooping in Seattle.
Oh.
Yeah, I didn't grow up here.
Well, Miss Seattle,
who never played ball.
Come on.
I think you're going to
make a great mom one day.
(Elle laughs)
Cheers to that?
Cheers to that.
(glasses clinking)
You didn't drink it.
It's not real if
you don't drink it.
I'm not worried about that.
I'll...
(clears throat) I'll check
on the girls when I head out.
I gotta go to bed anyway, huh?
Look, just maybe
not say anything.
Keep this between us.
Of course.
Good night, Elle.
Good night.
Be careful.
Them stairs.
I know, I know.
(suspenseful music)
You.
You're unbelievable.
I've done so much for you
and you can't do this
one thing for me.
Just one.
But you know what?
I realize there's so
many women out there
that would love to
gimme what I need.
You know why?
No?
'Cause I'm a good man.
A damn good man.
Life would be so much
easier without you.
Why?
So you can use my insurance
money to pay off your debts?
Huh.
Now why didn't I think of that?
(Ian laughing)
(Ian kissing)
No, no, no, no.
Ian, Ian, stop.
Ian, stop!
Ian, I'm pregnant.
I'm pregnant.
What?
Are you serious?
I'm serious, I'm serious.
Baby, that explains it then.
That explains it.
Why, why you've been so
hysterical, right, baby?
Because of the hormones, right?
(laughs) Because, because
of the hormones, baby.
Baby, baby, baby, we're
gonna have a child.
Baby.
Baby, we're gonna have a child.
Oh my God, oh.
Baby, you need your rest.
You need your rest.
You need to rest,
come on, right here.
Lay down right here, lay down,
lay, lay, lay down.
Baby.
You're pregnant, baby.
You're pregnant.
Baby, I'm gonna be a father.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
(suspenseful music)
Good to see you.
Thank you.
Hey.
- Nice job.
- Thank you.
Hey.
Thanks, man, appreciate it.
Good morning, Chief.
Good morning.
LT.
You are gonna be Lieutenant
by the end of the day.
The paperwork is almost done.
Congratulations.
So proud of you.
Thank you, Chief,
it's an honor.
Hey, listen.
Me and the guys
wanna take you out
at the end of the shift, right?
So don't go anywhere, right?
- Let's do it.
- All right.
You know where.
(clears throat) Excuse me.
Emily Stocklan called again,
looking for a wellness
check on her dad.
I told you we don't have
the manpower for that.
Wait, wait, wait.
Who?
A woman wants us to
check in on her father.
Apparently he's not
answering the phone.
She's called three
times this morning.
What's the address?
What?
It's my neighbor,
older guy, confused.
Chief, you mind if I pop
in and check in on him?
I'll come with you.
No, no, it's, it's fine.
You should have
someone with you.
I said I can handle it, Liz.
Hey, hey, hey.
Both of you go.
Make it fast.
Have you seen
him around lately?
A couple days ago.
He dropped off some mail
that he grabbed by accident.
(knocking)
Mr. Stocklan!
It's Ian Flynn, your neighbor!
Let's go around back.
Oh, wait a minute, wait.
I think I see something.
(solemn music)
(Ian sighs)
Hey, Chief.
Yeah, suicide from
the looks of it.
Yeah, coroner's taking
a look right now,
but it looks like it's
gonna be pretty cut and dry.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Hernandez is talking to
the family right now.
Okay.
No, no, no, it's fine,
I'll, I'll wait around.
You know, just in case
they need anything.
All right, bye-bye.
Talk to the daughter?
Did you know him well?
Ran into him in the streets
a couple times, you know?
Lonely guy, but friendly.
Seemed nice.
It's a shame.
Yeah.
His daughter says it
came outta nowhere.
Well, I mean,
some people don't talk
about anything, you know?
That's the way it is.
Especially family.
He had his keys on him.
Your point?
His house keys, in his pocket.
Who carries their
keys around on them
when they're planning
on killing themself?
A lonely old man, Liz.
Everybody's not as
sharp as you, Hernandez.
Yeah, but something's off.
Well, we'll wait for a
coroner's report, you know,
get a cause of death.
But, I mean, it
just is what it is.
I mean, we have our people
looking at the scene, Liz.
I mean, this guy, I mean, there
was no fingerprints, right?
Nobody forced
themselves in the house.
This guy had no enemies.
Just a lonely old man
who his only family lived
hours away from him.
You know, sometimes the
answer's right in front of you.
Don't think too hard.
I'm gonna stick around.
Why don't you head back to
the station, Lieutenant?
Sure there's a party
brewing for you
that you should get back to.
Yeah, right.
(phone chimes)
(ominous music)
Are you ready for
the tickle monster?
(laughs) Oh, bedtime
already, huh?
Will you tell me
a bedtime story?
Well, the only one I know
is about a Queen Noelle.
Have you ever heard of that one?
- No.
- No?
Well, there once was a
beautiful queen named Noelle.
She lived in a magical castle
with her sister, Grace,
and their mom.
And her big crown
and her big sword.
Of course.
So when there was a dragon that
came to attack the castle...
She fought it.
No.
Queen Noelle was way
smarter than that.
She knew there were
people inside that castle
who could be hurt
by that dragon.
So instead of fighting,
she helped them escape
to another castle
deep inside the woods
where she knew they would
be safe from that dragon.
Queen Noelle wouldn't
run away from a fight.
Hmm.
Well, sometimes running away is
the smartest thing you can do.
(suspenseful music)
(hammer pounding)
(engine rumbling)
(Ian kisses)
(door creaking)
Noelle?
Maya!
Grace?
Oh my God.
Ian, why are you yelling?
Hey, baby, the,
the kids are missing.
What do you mean
they're missing?
They're not in their rooms.
They're gone, I don't
know where they are.
- Ian!
- Noelle!
- Oh my God.
- Grace!
(cars honking)
(Maya) I didn't hear
anything, I don't know.
What time do you think
you went to bed last night?
Maybe 10.
The next thing I know, Ian
is yelling that they're gone.
It's okay.
We're gonna find them.
Okay?
Now, I don't know
if Ian told you,
but I stopped by your
house the other day.
Why?
We got a call from
one of your neighbors
about a disturbance.
And I saw you guys have
some cameras set up.
Please don't tell Ian.
He has no idea
that I have those.
And what do you mean?
He wanted me to take them down
'cause he thought they
looked creepy, but I didn't.
That footage gets
downloaded to my computer,
but I have no idea what, or if
anything useful is on there.
Well, why did you put
them up in the first place?
Because I was
going back to work
and I wanted to keep an eye
on the nanny and the kids.
I know, Chief.
Right.
Give me a second.
We're gonna pull out
every resource we have.
Chief, those are my kids.
I know.
I think they're finished
sweeping your house for prints,
so you and Ian are
fine to go back.
But when you do, I want you to
plug this into your computer.
It'll give me remote access
and let me look
through the footage.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Only you would sleep
through the kidnapping
of your own children.
I can't do this.
I need some air.
Flynn!
There's something
you need to see.
Well, we're currently waiting
on fingerprint analysis.
Locks on the back
door were broken
and it looked like
nothing was stolen.
Elle.
Ian.
What the hell is happening?
Maya texted me to
come to the station.
Kids are gone.
What do you mean gone?
I just saw them last night.
Where's Maya?
I don't know.
She went to get some
air or something.
Let me go see
if I can find her,
but just call me if you
need something, okay?
Hey, can we chat real quick?
I'd love to get a statement.
Of course.
(siren wailing)
Everything good over there?
Yeah, yeah, I'll be back soon.
Oh, it's fine, I'm
using a burner.
Ian.
Something's wrong.
What?
So I dug a little deeper.
There's no one named Elle Taylor
that's even registered
in this state.
She doesn't exist.
Who is she?
Okay.
(Maya sighs)
We have facial recognition
software running.
We'll find her.
Hernandez, we
need you out here.
(ominous music)
Sorry, Chief, I
gotta find my wife.
(ominous music)
Maya!
(dramatic music)
Rachelle Turner.
(tense music)
What's going on over here?
Is everything all right?
Everything's fine, sir.
Can I help you?
Ian?
Mr. Stocklan.
Heard a commotion
coming from your house.
I'm sorry, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Are you feeling all right?
I'd like to speak
with your wife.
She's out back
taking out the garbage.
We had a little accident.
But I'm sure she'll tell you
that this was all just
a misunderstanding.
Here, let me show you.
Take you out back.
(ominous music)
I guess she'll be back.
Where is she?
She went to the store.
It's funny, she
was just out here.
I heard her scream.
I saw you hit her!
I've already called the police.
They're on their way.
(dramatic music)
(Mr. Stocklan gasping)
Chief!
So this whole time,
you've been some sort
of actress, right?
It's not what you think.
Well, correct me if I'm wrong.
I think Rachelle went
to our high school.
I think you know
that she never worked
for a nannying company.
You hired her, independently.
I think you knew that she
was using a fake name.
Hell, I think you knew
that this whole time,
she was the one trying
to kidnap our kids.
They're not your kids.
No you don't.
(Maya screaming)
(tense music)
(phone chimes)
I got you, Rachelle.
What's her name?
What's my girl's
name right here?
Hmm, oh, wow.
Good job.
That's nice.
Okay, so now we should, we
should see if the giraffe...
(thumping)
Girls, girls, shh.
Let's play quietly, okay?
Stay right here
and play quietly.
I'll be right back.
(suspenseful music)
(gentle music)
Thank God you're all right.
I was so worried he'd hurt you.
Thank you for
everything, Rachelle.
They're safe.
We did it.
We got away with it.
We're not safe yet.
He knows about you.
Noelle, Grace.
Babies, are you there?
Oh!
Oh, look at you.
Oh, I'm so happy to see you.
Are you guys okay?
Thank you for
everything, Rachelle.
You girls always had my
back, ever since high school.
(laughs) Sis,
you know I got you.
Sorry I've been
away for so long.
I still can't forgive myself
for missing the funeral.
No, what matters is
that you're here now.
If you weren't traveling
and working so much,
you wouldn't have
this beautiful ranch.
Yeah.
And we should be safe here.
If you would've told
me what was going on,
I would've left
sooner, seriously.
Rachelle, no one knew.
And I was stupid enough
to think that I could
handle it by myself.
He was keeping me disoriented,
away from my family and friends.
I was done.
And trust that he would've
tried to pull us apart.
Never.
We go too far back for that.
Everything's gonna be fine now.
I think me going to the
police station worked,
made me seem less
suspicious to Ian.
Yeah, well, I think
it was a good idea
that I brought that
stupid sandwich
and pretended it was his lunch!
You know what?
That's my girl.
Sometimes you gotta
laugh instead of crying.
Rachelle, I'm scared of him.
That man is dangerous.
And it's only a matter of time
before he figures
everything out and finds us.
That man is never gonna stop
looking for me, Rachelle.
And I guess his plan worked.
I'm pregnant.
So now what's gonna
happen to me and my girls?
Nothing's gonna happen.
Our plan won't change.
I should have left
that man a long time ago,
but I was afraid that
he would hurt himself
like his dad did.
Wait, you never
told me about his dad.
He was a cop too.
Struggled with depression
and took his own life,
right before I met Ian.
God, I put myself,
I put my girls in danger
because I pitied him.
I thought that I could save him
and in the meantime lost myself.
Girl, some things we have to
turn over to God and therapy.
You were never meant
to save that man.
Yes, but by the
time I realized that,
he threatened to set me up.
Just stop it, okay?
That's why we're here.
That's why you devised a
plan that's going to work.
We just have to follow it.
My friend will have new
IDs for you by morning.
I'll disappear with the girls
and you go to the police and
tell them everything you have.
I just told you, he's
the new lieutenant.
Everybody over there loves him.
Now, Rachelle, I'm
trying to tell you
that I don't know about
this plan anymore.
No, we're sure about the plan.
Didn't you say you
trust that lady cop?
I don't know if I
trust anyone anymore.
(phone chiming)
Someone's at the gate.
Here it is.
Here.
We have to go.
My God.
My God, we gotta get outta here.
Okay, go grab the bags.
There's only one
road in and out.
They're already on their way.
Noelle, come on, let's go
to my secret hiding place.
Let's go, let me show you.
Here's Mama.
Hey, baby.
Okay, this is yours.
I wanna stay here with you.
No, no, no, no, no,
baby, listen, listen.
We're just playing
hide and seek, okay?
I need you to hide for Mommy.
Just promise me you'll take
care of your sister, okay?
Okay, I love you so much.
Okay, you guys get
outta here, okay?
It'll be just fine,
baby, I promise.
Got it, baby?
Come on, okay.
Got it?
Alright, let's go.
(dramatic music)
Come on.
Let's go, let's keep
going, go to the right.
Okay.
Stay right here, okay?
Until I come and get you.
Okay.
Sorry.
(door slams)
Forgive me for
bringing you into this.
That's what sisters are for.
Okay?
Maya!
Baby, I know you're in there.
Elle!
Or should I call you Rachelle?
Come out, both of you,
or I will come in
and drag you out.
We're making it outta
this together, you hear me?
Come on, baby, I'm
giving you a choice!
That's how you wanna play?
You can never make things easy
for me, can you, sweetheart?
(door smashing)
(Maya screaming)
Come on, come on.
(Ian grunting)
Everything's gonna be okay.
I'll protect you.
I'll shoot if either
one of you move.
Do it, coward.
Where are the girls?
You will never
see my babies again.
(Ian laughs)
Don't you dare.
If you shoot her, I will
kill myself and your baby.
Baby, you ain't got it in you.
I don't believe you.
Try me.
(radio chattering)
No one's here.
The place is torn up.
What could he have
done with her?
If you just let Elle
go, I will go with you.
I won't hurt myself or our
baby if you just let her go.
No, no.
She'll tell everybody.
Oh, no, no, no, baby, we're
in the middle of nowhere.
She won't have time.
Honey, we will be long gone.
All right?
You, me, and our family.
'Cause we're family, right?
Yes, baby.
That's right.
Better than my old man, right?
And I never abandoned you.
I never abandoned you.
No, no, no, no, no.
You tried to leave me.
Because pregnancy
makes you confused.
Okay?
It's okay.
I promise you, we
can just leave.
We can get out of town,
and I promise you, promise you
that I will obey this time.
Okay?
All you have to do
is let Rachelle go.
Ian, come on.
You know how to
make us disappear.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Listen, Ian, she'll
just slow us down.
Just let her go.
She serves no purpose,
honey, come on,
it's just us and the family.
Elle, get outta here
before I change my mind.
Go!
It's okay, it's okay, go, go!
Hello?
Can somebody hear me?
Hello, hello?
We need help, hello.
How do I know
you won't shoot me?
Baby, I have my priorities
straight, all right?
Okay.
Just put the gun down so
I know you won't hurt me.
All right.
All right, it's
going away, okay?
It's gone, okay?
Baby, put the knife down.
Come on, put it down.
Okay.
Okay, come here.
Come here, baby.
Okay, now where did you stash
the girls over here, right?
Tell 'em that daddy's home to
come save the day, all right?
Okay?
Okay.
You can just stay right
here and I'll go get them.
How should I explain
all this to the girls?
Just, just tell 'em
the truth, baby, okay?
Tell 'em that Elle made Mommy
and Daddy fight, all right,
and now she's gone and
she'll never come back, okay?
Okay, okay.
Would you mind getting my car?
Because yours is gonna
be too easy to track.
What are you talking about?
I'm not stupid.
No, no, no, Ian, I
know that you're not-
(Maya screaming)
(dramatic music)
(children screaming)
Oh, babies, babies.
- Mommy!
- I love you so much.
Come on.
What's going on?
It's okay, baby, everything's
gonna be just fine.
Come on now, hurry.
We're fine, baby, we're fine!
Okay, Noelle, don't
hurt yourself!
Okay, Noelle, go
in the other side.
Go in the other side.
Okay, Grace, let's get in here.
(Ian grunting)
Okay.
Come on, Elle, come on!
It's okay, baby.
It's okay.
You guys okay?
(Elle) Yeah, we need
to go, we need to go!
(gun fires)
Ian, no!
Ian, the girls are in the car!
Stop it!
Oh my God, what do I do?
Elle, what do I do?
I don't know, drive the car!
(Maya screaming)
(siren wailing)
(Liz) Maya, Rachelle,
are you all right?
Yeah.
Ian, he...
Where is he?
Right there.
Lieutenant Flynn, you have
the right to remain silent.
Anything you say...
(tense music)
Right.
♪ Merrily, merrily,
merrily, merrily ♪
♪ Life is but a dream
Good job today!
Oh my gosh.
All right, I'll
see you tomorrow.
Whew, good job!
They love you so much.
They're gonna be so upset
when you leave again.
I won't be gone long.
Thanks for covering
my class for me.
Of course.
It's my pleasure.
(gentle music)
That used to be the song.
So good to see you ladies.
You too, you too.
Wow, so catch us up.
What's been going on?
Tell us about the station.
Well, it's a lot more work,
but being promoted to
Chief is a huge honor.
Are you guys gonna
drink that in front of me?
Ah, come on, we can
give you a little whiff.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, yeah, great.
Oh, did you see
today's headline?
Oh my God, everything
happened so fast.
It doesn't seem real.
Please, after all
that's happened,
he was a strain
on the department.
They were happy to wrap that up.
And I don't know
if I ever told you,
but in the middle of all this,
I thought it was you that
was behind everything.
I could have swore I was gonna
see your face on the news.
Yeah, well, if you think
she's scandalous now,
you should have seen
her in high school.
And I plead the fifth.
(laughs) You better
plead the fifth.
So how far along are you?
Ah, second trimester.
You think the third time
around would be easier, but no.
That's why I'm happy
I got my girl back.
She's gonna help me
out with the other two
while I go back to teaching.
Yay!
You know what you're having?
A boy.
Well, ain't that something?
It is.
So when is the baby shower?
'Cause that's what
I'm talking about.
How about a destination
baby shower?
I'm talking Cabo.
Look, we could go to Jamaica!
Okay, let's get up outta
here, what are we doing?
♪ And reach the stars
and then you can't lose ♪
♪ If you keep the fire
♪ So just be patient
♪ Don't let 'em say your dreams
aren't worth you chasing ♪
♪ Sometimes the silent
fear, you gotta face it ♪
♪ 'Cause this life right here
is only what we make it ♪
♪ Yeah, we're gonna make it
♪ We're warriors, warriors
♪ We're warriors,
warriors, warriors ♪
♪ I earned a couple
battle scars ♪
♪ Fighting for a way
to go after my heart ♪
♪ I never thought
I'd get so far ♪
♪ Every shot I take hits
closer to the mark ♪
♪ My failure
doesn't concern me ♪
♪ It's one more step
in the journey ♪
♪ My victory is magic and
I make the most of that ♪