- When are you gonna
tell me what's inside?
- Mary, I'll explain it to
you when you're old enough
to understand the eternal
mystery of transubstantiation.
- Please, Father.
- It's the body of Christ.
- The one we use at mass?
- Yes, indeed.
Now leave me be,
I need to finish this
homily before Sunday.
You let God out!
- Please, Father.
Can I come back in? It's
freezing!
- I'll let you sleep in the
attic
if you can recite for me
Leviticus chapter three.
- I, I can't.
- Mary, come on.
Come on.
Let's get up.
Mary?
- I just wanted to let
you know how awful it was
what happened to you today.
- Oh, nevermind that.
I'm really into this novel right
now.
You should go back to sleep.
- What happened?
- Just Father Munhauser, the
bastard.
He scolded me again for no good
reason.
- Still, neither of you have
yet to be paddled by him.
- I heard he's responsible
for that poor student's
death a few years ago.
Did he beat her to death?
I only ask because he's
known for severe abuse,
but he can only punish you
if your parents give him
permission,
like yours did.
- It was a failed exorcism.
The girl, Mary, her name
was, she started acting,
you know, demonic, possessed.
I mean, some say that she was
just going through puberty,
but he thought she was going
mad.
- Poor Mary.
I wish there was some
way we could get revenge.
Kill that son of a bitch.
- Stop, it's all just
hearsay, speculation.
Besides, I thought he was
a good guy before today.
- I know where it happened.
It was in his cabin.
He enslaved her there to
do experiments on her.
- We have to go.
How far is it from here?
- About a day's hike.
- Let's break out of
here.
How's this plot compared
to the one you're reading?
- I only read romance
and you guys can go enjoy it by
yourselves
and have fun getting locked up.
- No one's gonna be there.
It's vacant this time of year.
- Well, I guess I'd rather
be in prison than here.
- Isn't it just charming?
You know, I could spend
the rest of my life
in a little place like this.
- No way!
Why would anyone with your
ambition
wanna spend their whole life
in a place out in the country
like this?
- Nope, nope, can't do it.
It reeks of religion in there.
- Hey, maybe we'll find his wine
and tune into Dallas
playing the Super Bowl!
Oh.
- Girls, I found letters.
We have to read them.
- He tried for weeks,
every night until she cried
blood and ate nothing.
- Deliver her, be gone evil, be
gone.
I cast you out in the name
of the Lord Jesus Christ.
Be gone, be gone in the name
You are crushed under his foot.
You are crushed under his heel.
- Some say this is where
it took a darker turn for the
worst.
Everyone knows what he did to
her,
but it wasn't for selfish
reasons.
It was his final method
to draw the evil out.
- He hoped it
would flee from her body
and inhabit his instead.
But being a priest,
he didn't know the first thing
about women
except how to punish them
when they misbehaved.
- It's unclear what
happened next.
Some believe he impregnated
her and killed her
to save his reputation
at the Reform Academy.
- Let's just bury
the bird real quick.
- Hey, who the hell is that?
- Just looking for a shovel.
- Y'all trespassing.
- Uh-uh, this here's forest
land.
We know our rights!
- That may be true.
You can mess around the grounds
here,
but that there cabin is
somebody's private getaway.
- Hey, you all Manhauer's
nieces or something?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Wait, I know you.
Aren't you the janitor
from St. Catherine's?
- That's right, I'm Nestor.
I take care of the grounds.
pull weeds and such.
- You helped me untie
the knot on my shoe once.
Peeked up my skirt too.
- I get in eyefuls when I can.
Like right now.
And a word of warning,
keep away from the stinging
nettles
and don't dig in the ground for
nothing.
This here is sacred Indian
burial ground.
- Those are
my people, we're fine.
- Snazzy place.
I wasn't expecting it
to be this nice, right?
- Hey, at least he's got some
good records
because I was jonesing for a
groove.
- Oh, something weird's
happened at the neighbors.
- So what are we doing about
dinner?
- I don't know.
There's some mutant animal
parts in the freezer.
Maybe you can make a soup.
- You're sick.
How about some split pea soup?
- That will keep us warm
tonight.
- You know what else would keep
us warm?
A fire!
I'll get the kindling.
- Here, snap a real good one of
me.
- Sure!
- Jeez, Lori, you're
built like a brick house.
- Thank you.
- That's my swing.
- So very sorry.
I'm Jodi.
What's your name?
- I don't remember.
- Oh.
So you live around here or?
- I died here
and death is near you and
all you filthy whores.
- Jodi, what happened?
- It was horrible.
There was a girl there!
It was a demon, it was a demon!
- Come on now.
You're just trying to get us
in the mood for some ghost
stories.
- No, no, it really happened!
- Maybe it was an apparition?
- Uh-uh.
Sounds like someone found the
shine and it had a good sip.
- Maybe we should just
play a game or something?
- This isn't time for charades!
We need to tear this place up
for clues.
- There's no way we could
read through all the letters.
- Who do you think they are?
- Victims.
- Lori, that's not funny!
Who are you calling?
- My boyfriend, Braddock.
- Boyfriend? That's a laugh.
- You've just never met him.
He's a dream.
Wish he was here right now.
- We've already been in enough
trouble.
We don't need men.
I mean, we're already
playing hooky anyway.
- Ugh, you're right.
We're basically fugitives
already.
We might as well just leave.
Go back, face the music.
- Nestor's already seen us.
We should just ride this train
out 'til the end of the line.
I mean, we gotta find some
closure.
Besides, it's all just
rumors right now anyway.
- Not if it's written down.
I think I just found his
journal.
"I've been trying to recall the
days.
"The nights feel eternal.
"As I fail to know the
improvements
"I've made in the poor girl,
"the convulsions only
worsen a withering soul.
"Only more sickened by the
surroundings
"and the perhaps ill will
of her strange mother."
- This may take some
getting used to, Mary,
but we wanna shield you from the
evil
and the sin of this wicked
world.
- I
have doubts in my mind
about her parenting.
Forcing snake oil,
alternative medicines on her,
who has claimed she found
her recipes in dreams
where witch doctors appeared to
her
Native savages nonetheless,
I'm now convinced her secret
family potion
made of moss and elderberry
could only hasten the
subject's disposition.
- We need to speak about Mary,
dear.
- My own concerns matter little
because I'm really a humble
servant
of the Lord Jesus Christ.
But Mary, she's troubling me.
Always walking around
town like a common tart.
I wonder where she learned that
from?
- Are you referring to
me?
- And always making a
mockery during the mass,
yawning incessantly when I give
the homily
and when I lift up the Holy
Eucharist, incessant giggles.
It's, it's a mockery.
And her knees always
exposed like a temptress.
- If you weren't so cheap,
she wouldn't have such
an ill-fitting uniform.
- All right, enough.
In first Timothy, he talks about
how women
shouldn't be permitted
to speak in to church.
He should have extended
that to the household.
- Well, we need to make
a decision tonight.
- Okay, I've decided.
Mary no longer goes to school.
You could teach her at home.
- Tithes and offerings?
Holy mackerel!
- No.
I didn't know the old man was
loaded.
There must be at least $500
there.
- Try twice that.
- You know, if we had a bookie,
we could put it all on the
Cowboys to win.
- Gambling's a sin.
Also, we already
have enough bad luck as it is.
- We could change our names.
Ooh, hide out in L.A.
- Now you're talking.
We could get our nails done
and go shopping like
sophisticated ladies.
- Oh, this is perfect.
Now I'll be all ready
for that new magazine
I was telling you about.
- Hustlers?
- Yep, they're gonna love me.
- Yeah, and all the mules who
read it.
- I just have to submit some
more fees.
- This isn't you.
- It's me.
What?
- It's Mary.
Look.
- Ugh, I don't, I don't like
this one bit.
- No, no, no, no, no.
This is a good thing.
I mean, she wasn't in any of
the photos with the victims.
So this means she's here with
us.
She wants us to be here.
It definitely isn't
animal, maybe pelvic bone?
- It's her remains, isn't it?
- No, remember Nestor's warning?
It has to be a native's.
- Well, if we didn't
awaken a spirit before,
we definitely have now.
What was that?
- It sounded like a gunshot.
- Should we go check it
out?
- I think it's Lori's turn to
go.
- Fine, we'll all go.
- Someone's over there.
- Show yourself!
- Oh god, this guy again.
- Evening, ma'ams.
- Nestor, you scared us.
- What the hell are you
doing holding a gun?
- Yeah, evil spirits can't die
from that.
- Yeah, but the critters can.
I'm hankering for a gumbo.
- Something's there!
- That's the one that casts no
shadow.
- It just looks like a normal
cat.
- I think that's a bobcat.
- I'm gonna get me a $10 pelt.
That'll be 22 this year.
- No! Stop!
It's just a sweet little pussy.
- Oh my gosh, how cute!
- Yeah, that's not a bobcat.
- She wouldn't hurt anyone.
Want some milk?
- Oh, so sweet.
So demonic.
- Well, I'm bushed.
I think I'm gonna go lay down.
- Bye, baby!
- Maybe we should go talk to
Nestor.
- No, he's crazy!
- Yeah, but he might know
something about this place.
- Pssh, I do not wanna
get shot.
- If we get shot, we get shot
together.
- Uh, okay.
- Who's that?
- It's us, the pretty girls
you've been spying on.
- Oh, hello there.
- Hi.
- Oh, hold on, let me get
decent.
Okay.
- So anyway,
why do you live in the
shed like some creep
when you could be living in that
cabin?
It's right there.
- Well, this here's the
groundskeepers quarters
and I'm the faithful
groundskeeper
and I prefer staying out here
and I ain't never going
inside that cabin again.
- So you know about Mary?
- Shh!
Don't ever say her name, foolish
girls.
The more you blabber, the
more she'll haunt your souls.
- Well, that was weird.
- Maybe we should listen to his
warning.
- Ugh, you're not sleepy, are
you?
Yep, that Peg is such a party
pooper.
- I couldn't sleep a wink here.
We still have a million
questions
that need to be answered.
- That's why I brought this.
Oh, mystical magic eight ball.
Did Father Munhauser really
torture her?
My sources say no.
Okay.
Did he cause her death?
Better not tell you now.
- That stupid toy's not gonna
give us the answers we need.
We need to find something of
hers
that we can speak to her
through.
- Yet there's nothing here
but ineligible scribblings
on false teachings
and pseudosciences.
We haven't searched the attic
yet.
You take a look while I finish
combing through his journal some
more.
- Fine.
Ow!
It's okay, it's okay.
We're here to help you and
reveal the truth and all that.
- Please won't you bring
me a glass of milk?
- Yeah, yeah, I can do that.
- And it better not be
buttermilk!
You were sent here for me to
kill!
- You can sleep inside tonight.
But remember,
your father promised
to cut your tongue out
if you spoke at the dinner table
again.
- What's wrong?
- My dad cooked all the eggs for
breakfast
and made me eat them.
- Did you see my favorite
marble?
It's a yellow one.
- I'm sorry I haven't.
- Eat my mushy!
Eat my mushy!
- Repent to the Lord, I draw you
out.
- No, no!
- Say the name of the Lord Jesus
Christ.
The Lord Jesus Christ who died
and on the third day rose from
the dead
and who according to the
scriptures
is the right hand of God.
Say his name, the Lord Jesus
Christ!
in the name of the Mother
Mary, mother of God.
Say her name!
The Lord God Yahweh, sayeth
thee!
Yahweh!
- Yahweh!
- I anoint thee
in the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Spirit.
Be gone, evil spirit!
Be gone, foul spirit!
Be gone! Be gone!
- No!
Why?
- I'm sorry, Mother.
- You know the order.
First bath for father, second
bath for me.
And the last bath for you, Mary.
- No, don't make me eat
anymore.
- More moths, Mary.
- How dare
you
bring toys to the dining room
table?
- Baby was hungry too,
Papa.
Why do you have to destroy my
doll?
- Wasn't the bed of
leaves
that you raked this morning
a cozy enough bed for you?
- And what God hath joined
together,
let no man put asunder.
Nestor, you may kiss your bride.
- No!
- Okay, we sound terrible.
Let's try something else.
Oh, spirit of thy young and
innocent lamb.
Let it be known that we shan't
hurt you.
- Yes, we are here to set you
free.
- Huh?
It's working.
Lori, I can sense her sadness.
- Peggy, what the heck?
- It was horrifying!
It was like a nightmare but
real!
I swear it really happened!
- Sounds like we have a
sleepwalker in denial.
- Jodi, you know me best.
Have I ever slept walked my
life?
- Well, a lot of weird stuff
has been going on here,
so I believe you.
- Maybe you dosed us with some
good LSD.
Yep, for all I know you're
the one going around
pulling pranks on us
while she's been asleep.
- Come on, just sit down.
- Oh my gosh.
Jodi, your wrist.
- It's nothing!
- We gotta get something to put
on that.
I'll be right back.
- Oh, come on.
- Aw, hey little fella.
Aw, you're so cute.
- Girls.
Girls, I found this.
- Her stuff.
- What more could we ask for?
- This must be her diary.
- Maybe you should put on the
nightgown.
- This old thing?
- I double dog dare ya.
- Ew, gross!
I am not wearing this.
It smells like...
- Death.
- Mary, this was your
grandmother's rosary
and now that you're 16 years
old,
I think she'd want you to have
it.
- Oh my God!
She wants me to read this alone.
- Mother Mary, I haven't much
to say except I love them all.
Even if they don't understand
me.
Am I ill?
They insist I am but won't you
tell me?
It's normal for a girl
to feel sad sometimes.
It's hard to fathom the
complexity of God's love.
Help us.
- So what kind of herbal
remedies are we concocting
today?
- A little clover blossom
for the infusions.
- Hg?
I thought you used only
natural ingredients.
- Don't question my methods.
- What are you doing?
Why did she do it, Peg?
- Stop!
- Why did she do it?
- You're gonna wreck it all!
- They poisoned her, she wasn't
possessed!
She wasn't possessed, they
poisoned her!
- Who? Who are you talking
about?
- They poisoned her!
Why did she do it?
- Jodi!
- Ugh, you guys are the worst!
- Eat up, you'll feel better.
- No, I don't want any
of your stupid soup.
- Either you drink the soup
or put on the nightgown.
- Ugh, fine!
- Heal the sick, raise the dead.
Cleanse the lepers, cast out
demons.
Voices not your own-
- No, no, no, no.
I don't wanna hear this.
I know, sorry, I can't.
- Wow, is there anything
you can't make look good?
- As long as you don't ask
for another photo shoot.
- Look, look, I just found this
key!
- Ooh, let me see.
Hmm, I wonder.
- Ugh, it obviously doesn't go
there!
- Try the wardrobe.
- Can I take the nightgown off?
Feeling kind of itchy and
it's your turn to wear it.
- April 8th,
1969.
I wish I had better news.
Ruth's last batch had already
seemed to sour in the sun.
Nevertheless, she injected the
cat
with the potential remedy.
I'm grateful Ruth's findings are
complete
and have been submitted
to medical journals.
But I fear the entire scientific
community
making sport of her research.
She initially tried to create an
antidote
for early onset dementia
but when my daughter became
sullen and melancholy,
Ruth fed the formula and
her condition only worsened
and we all had to bear the
darkness,
the delirium of unbearable
deterioration
and impending death.
She concocted a tincture
of niacin and rabies
taken straight from one
of the mangy coyotes
my groundsman brought in.
I now admit experimenting on
the poor creature was cruel,
for it truly altered her
offspring for the worst.
- Well, now we know we have
access
to the seventh gate of Hell.
- How can you girls
be doing your makeup at a time
like this?
There's someone in the driveway.
- Hide!
- Father, what you's doing here?
I wasn't expecting you.
- I need solitude, Nestor.
- Wait, you's got
something you needs to know
before you ventures inside.
- What is it?
- Bad, bad infestation.
- What kind of infestation?
- You don't wants to know.
- Step aside, Nestor.
Let me through.
Who in the hell is in my house?
I'm a priest.
A prophet, a servant of the most
high God.
And you have defiled his house!
Mary.
- I've missed you, Father.
- You're not my daughter.
My daughter was pure
and innocent and sweet!
You're nothing like her.
You're an illusion.
You're a satanic illusion.
- Just what I've always wanted,
a surprise birthday party.
Can my friends stay for dinner?
- What friends?
- Fake priest!
- What kind of hell has been
unleashed in this house?
- Unholy father!
- Be gone, false spirit!
Henceforth and forever
you and all your demons!
- Don't embarrass God.
- All allegiance begone
with your father, the Devil!
The father of lies!
- You belong in hell with me!
- Fallen angel be gone with you
in the name of our Lord
and Savior Jesus Christ!
In the name of the Father and
the Son and the Holy Spirit.
- All your life's work has been
in vain!
- You have no power over me!
- Even angels mock your name.
- Be gone, foul spirit!
Be gone unclean spirit
and all your legions, all your
devils
and join your father the devil
Satan!
- You're pathetic.
- I'm filled with God in my
life.
- Soon you'll be sucking my
horns in Hell!
- You are not welcome in this
house,
you and all unclean spirits,
go back to your bowels of
wretchedness!
- Never!
- Go back to your holy Hell!
Go back to your bowels of
excrement!
- Why is your dick getting hard?
- Be gone with thee!
- I know you wanna fuck me like
Mary!
- I cast you out in the name
of my Lord's name Jesus Christ!
His power in his name, he
treads you under his hell!
A priest's role is to
offer a sacrifice unto God.
That's his true calling.
Oh, Lord.
Lord, most high.
Just as in the old covenant
when the blood of animals
was offered as a sacrifice
and the high priest offered
gifts and sacrifices for sins.
I humbly offer my life, my
offering.
I sacrifice unto thee.
- We gotta get outta here!
- Yeah, let's see.
These things in.
Ha, I won't be needing
that anymore.
Look at that.
Never again will I toil in
the hot sun like a mule.
- Nestor, what are you doing?
You can't just leave us with
that thing!
- Take us with you.
- I'll make a deals with you.
Y'all's idolatries aren't my
problem.
I ain't gonna answer to my
master no more.
Now you gonna gimme half
that cash I know you stole.
I seen yous through the window.
Then I'm off to Tijuana.
My chamber pot days is over.
- Fine, you can have it as
long as we can hitch a ride.
You can drop us off
somewhere along the way near Los
Angeles.
I'm supposed to be a model, you
see, so.
Just heat lightning,
but supposing I'm wrong.
We'd best be getting along.
Roads flood fast when the rains
come.
Best get ready 'cause if
you ain't all saddled up
in 15 minutes, I'm leaving yous
behind.
- All right, get ready.
I'll get Jodi.
Get outta the shower, Jodi,
we're leaving!
- Were you also homeschooled by
the Devil?
- No, I wasn't.
- Please, will you help me take
this off?
- Of course I will.
- We'll devour your organs in
Hell!
- No!
- Put me out of my misery.
- No, no!
- All right.
What am I missing?
Got my smokes, venison
jerky, black licorice.
Mary Joseph, don't take me now!
You're not real!
You died a long time ago!
- Jodi?
- What are we gonna do now?
- Find his keys, we're
driving out of here ourselves!
Oh, that is it!
I am ending this myself!
- It's not starting!
- Can you see me?
Can you find me?
- Lori?
Lori?
- Life is not supposed to be
good.
That's all there is to know.
Why don't you put the kettle on?
Some dandelion tea sounds nice
about now.
What's that you have there?
- It's, it's nothing!
It's nothing.
- Let me see.
You'll be punished if you
disobey me!
Punished like Mary was.
- Hello, Lori?
The door is locked!
- Won't you play jacks with me?
- Now's not a good time.
- I'm Mary's unborn brother.
She put me in the outhouse
when I was just a fetus.
All the way down.
Mother made her do it.
Do they not love me?
- That's a really sad story.
What's your name, little boy?
- I'm Aberdeen.
It must be nice to have a toilet
now.
You should hide in the closet
and don't come out until
morning.
That's when she goes away.
Are you my mommy?
- No, I'm not related to you.
But I wish I was.
Why can't all of the
spirits be nice like you?
- I like Heaven, but
I wanna come back now.
- Mother Mary, please,
wash away my sins so
that if I die tonight,
I will bask in his eternal glory
forever.
Cleanse me.
Cleanse me of,
of my indecencies and
and my naughty thoughts.
I didn't wanna be in Hustlers.
Not, not really.
I'm ridding myself of this.
Cheesecake photography.
I'm ashamed.
I'd hate for my mother to see.
You see?
Is that what you want from me?
Is it?
- Join us.
- No!
- Join us!
Join us!
- The power of Christ impales
you!
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women
and blessed is the
fruit of thy womb Jesus.
Holy Mary, mother of God,
pray for us sinners from now
until the hour of our deaths.
Amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women
and blesses the fruit of thy
womb Jesus.
Holy Mary, mother of God.
Pray for us sinners from now
until the hour of our death.
Amen.
- Peg, Peg!
You've done it again, you
wretched child.
Penance, penance will consume
the rest of your days.
You can forget about breakfast.
How dreadful of you to toil away
the morning hours in this
selfish fashion.
Are you studying to become
a nun or aren't you?
Rise from your sinful slumber.
- Mother Superior, please.
I never thought I'd be
so happy to see you!
I was trapped in the most horrid
dream.
- I know.
And it's time for you to go back
now!
- Who are you and why
are you wearing that?
- I'm Bonnie and I just
found this under the rubble.
How do I look?