- I'm so sorry!
- Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry!
My gear is malfunctioning.
Sorry about that.
Unfortunately,
the interactive features of this special
can't be displayed on this device.
But there are so many ways
you can still enjoy the experience.
- Wow!
- Just press "play"
on a newer Smart TV, mobile device,
game console, streaming media player,
web browser, or other compatible gadget
and you'll be on your way immediately.
You'll know you're on a compatible device
whenever you see this badge.
If you need assistance at any point,
just contact Netflix customer support...
- Ah!
- ...and they'll get you going in no time.
Don't miss out!
Your immersive
interactive experience awaits,
where you control the story.
Dog is awake. Good morning, Human.
It's me, the Dog, here to cheer you up.
Human? Have you seen Human?
No, you haven't, because she's gone.
Where is she, Ham? Where is Human?
All human beings
have been deleted.
The humans are gone?
Choose your player!
We're going to find Human
and fix all of this.
Let go, Dog!
You're coming with us.
Ooh. Uh-oh.
According to calculations,
the Glitch has broken the entire universe.
This is all your fault.
Gravity!
Where is Human?
She's been gone forever. I counted.
Ham can do
her dumb finding-Human thing...
...while I'm gonna do
my not-dumb-at-all thing.
- Whoa.
- No!
Should I be nice...
...or mean?
She peed her pants and died.
- Never mind who pooped whose pants.
- We've got a Code Brown back here.
We're getting really kinda high right now.
- Please, eat me.
- Wh... What?
- Come on, Pud!
- Whoa!
We're gonna go home...
...to Human
together!
I'm not a monster.
Now let's go steal a blanket from a baby.