Let's make somethin' together.
It's the king.
The king, the king,
the king, the king.
Oh, jump shot. Go on.
He's heating up.
Watch out, Sian. Move.
He's on fire.
Oh, you're on a game?
I got next.
Too late, Dru.
I already called it.
You couldn't grab us no cereal?
Do I look like your maid?
Nah. One of you farted.
Pause the game, LeBron.
I will, right after I...
Slam dunk.
Yo!
- Yo!
Oh, my bad.
It's not even funny.
That's funny.
Boys...
What...?
- Sup, Coach.
Sup, Coach. -DRU: Hi, Dad.
Hey, Coach. -Y'all get ready for the game.
I want to get to Salvation Army early.
And clean this mess up.
Yes, sir.
- Yes, sir.
Hurry up.
- Yes, sir. -Yes, sir.
Right there.
Nah, for real.
One of y'all stink.
Y'all gotta get that checked out.
Yo, no.
It was Lil Dru.
I think it was Lil Dru.
Don't point at me now.
- Nah, it was Dru.
Whoo!
That's all right, Sian.
Go get back.
Back in there.
Three-pointer, three-pointer,
take the three-pointer.
Yeah.
Take the open shot.
Yeah, boy.
- That's how you do it.
Yeah. Yeah.
I love what I see out there.
I love it, a lot of chemistry
between the team.
I like what I'm seeing.
We were losing this game,
now we're winning this game, right?
Remember, it's not how
you start the game...
It's how you finish the game.
All right,
guys, let's go.
One, two, three.
Shooting Stars!
Let's go, Shooting Stars!
Let's go,
Shooting Stars!
Let's go, Shooting Stars!
Let's go,
Shooting Stars!
Hell yeah.
When I make it to the league.
I'ma have a big ass pool in the back...
...and I'ma swim in that bitch every day,
sucker!
Sorry, Mama.
When I make it to the league.
I'ma put an arcade in my joint.
Huge 40-inch big-screen and everything.
That's gonna be tight.
We can all build cribs next to each other,
build tunnels under 'em
so we can hang out,
like, all the time.
- Why will we need tunnels...
...if you live right next door, fool.
You know, like the Batcave.
Oh, snap.
We should put a big ass basketball court...
...down there, too.
What'd we do now?
I don't know what it is...
...but y'all are gonna do something
special together.
Mm, that's right.
You know what? Y'all remind me
of a song I need to play,
something for y'all to think about.
No. No,
no. -This is a beautiful song.
Oh, you know what song we should do?
What's that song? By Biggie?
- Oh, yeah.
We should play Biggie.
There's no Biggie.
Your dad's musical taste is trash.
But when I make it to the league.
I'ma get a bunch of records...
...and I'm also gonna get a tattoo.
That'd be phat.
Don't worry, Sian,
you already fat.
Besides, tattoos are stupid.
We need to hurry before Ma get back.
Can't rush art, brother.
Heard y'all finna start high school.
Yeah. Can't wait. Buchtel.
Yeah. I went there.
Slept through most of my classes though,
but game night?
It was on.
Squad get all the hoes.
For real?
- Oh, yeah.
Sit still, dumbass,
fore this lion end up cross-eyed.
Oh, shit. Let's wrap this up
later, big dawg. -All right.
Tat?
I know you ain't puttin'
no prison ink on my son.
I'm sorry, we-we was just...
- I swear to God. Tat!
I told you about this.
Bron, get back here.
Tat!
Boy.
Gotta come home some time
and that belt gonna be waitin'!
Come on, Mama.
What's good, y'all?
- Oh, what's good, bro?
Bro, what are you doing?
That's only gonna make your arms longer.
Yo, I grew a half inch just this month,
so kiss my ass.
Whoo.
Yo, is that a tattoo?
Yeah, check it out.
What is it? -Damn.
- Is that a cow?
It's a lion. He ain't done yet.
Cause it look like a cow.
What the hell would I get a cow for?
Hey, where y'all goin'?
Heading over to Buchtel.
- Yeah, y'all should come.
Ain't nobody tryin' to go
to school in the summer, Dad.
Well, it's about to be all y'all's school,
and if anybody'd benefit from
meeting Coach Sams, it's you.
Boy, what...?
What... what is that?
A cow?
I told you, I told you.
- Yeah. -Come on.
That is definitely a cow.
Yeah, I'd cover that up with something.
Tell me that ain't Sian.
Man, that fool don't look nothin' like me.
Oh, shit.
Yo, he got them chubby cheeks
and everything.
Dang.
Relax.
Whoa.
- Whoa.
Dang.
- It's huge.
Hey.
- Yo.
That scoreboard.
Boys like what you see?
Yes, sir.
- Yes, sir.
That's what I want to hear.
1930s,
white folks moved to Akron...
...just so their kids could attend Buchtel.
They called it the Pearl of Ohio.
Everything was white and pristine.
You believe that?
But now we here.
Academic excellence...
...and we still got one helluva
basketball program.
And that's why we value all the talent...
...you boys are gonna bring to this school.
And I'm not just talking about varsity.
We need leaders on JV, too.
Wait, what? JV?
Junior varsity.
- I know what it is.
Don't worry.
We'll put some meat on them bones...
...and in a few years, few inches,
and you gonna be rolling with the big dogs.
All right, bruh.
He goes up for the slam. Bang!
Another one.
Man...
...the hell with Buchtel.
Huh?
I said forget Buchtel.
Place sucks.
Man, why you trippin'?
It was cool.
Yeah, for you. You ain't gotta
worry about your spot.
Plus Coach Sams practically
drooling over Uncle Willie.
Man, that's cause I'm raw.
You over there downloading
raw porn on his computer.
If I wanted porn
I'd just ask your mama
to mail me some more pictures.
Yo, that's not cool, bro.
She just cooked us dinner last week.
Yo, yo, yo, yeah, whoa.
Y'all hearing me?
Buchtel ain't gonna play me.
He ain't say that.
- Yes, he did.
The man ain't never seen me ball.
That's some bullshit.
Come on, man,
it ain't even that serious.
What's more serious...
...than Buchtel trying
to break up the Fab Four?
We supposed to play together.
Maybe if you stopped
wildin' out on your pops,
he'll talk to Coach Sams for you.
My pops?
Can't you see they was
both conspiring against me?
They shook hands right in front of me.
Look, if we want to play together.
Buchtel's the only school in our district.
What other choice we got?
And we'll still be
on the same team. -Mm-hmm.
Only thing is you'll be JV.
You know, ballin' with the other munchkins.
Keith Debrot?
No.
Dambrot.
Who are you?
Dru Joyce.
I just need a second, Coach.
You're on the team here?
- Nah.
Not yet.
But I could be if you're lucky.
Tryouts aren't until October.
Well, are you gonna give me a chance?
No, like a real chance.
For varsity.
Varsity.
What the hell you think you're doing?
I don't have time for this.
I-I just started this job like 45 minutes ago.
Yeah, I know.
I read all about it.
Is that right?
Yeah.
I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking like everyone else:
too short, too small,
not enough meat on my bones, right?
Maybe you go on home
and eat your Wheaties.
Maybe you'll luck
and, uh, have a growth spurt.
But what if I don't?
What if I get old and stay short,
just like you.
Yeah, well, then maybe
it's just not in the cards.
You know what, kid,
why don't you take a hike, huh?
Kind of like how coaching college...
...wasn't in the cards for you?
I checked you out.
Head coach, Central Michigan,
'91 to'93?
You were fired, right?
Somethin' you said?
No, well, that wasn't...
I mean, I-I never...
Look, look, it's all good.
I understand.
Sucks when people judge you
before knowin' you, huh?
You played against the Fab Five, right?
Greatest college lineup ever:
Howard, Rose, Webber...
I know who the Fab Five are.
Well...
Me and my boys...
...we call ourselves the Fab Four.
Let's go, Shooting Stars! -
We been ballin' with each other
since we was, like, ten.
We can win you a state championship.
Guaranteed.
You sure are a cocky
little bastard, aren't you?
Yo.
Man, where you been at?
I was at St. V's.
The Catholic school? For what?
Yeah, there's a new coach over there.
NCAA dude.
He legit.
All right, that's good for them,
but we goin' to Buchtel.
They ain't letting me play
varsity so I ain't going.
But we're supposed to play together.
Y'all didn't seem to mind
that I'm the odd man out.
I ain't wasting away on JV.
I'm better than that and y'all know it.
Yeah, we know,
but Catholic school?
They got scholarships.
If we all stick together,
maybe we could get some.
They got a lot of white folks,
too, in case you forgot.
I ain't runnin' for class
president, I'm goin' to ball.
And you serious?
Dead serious.
You really willing to walk away
from Buchtel?
They got championships, my dawg.
And girls.
I mean, what's St. V's got?
A coach who believes in me.
Bro, we believe in you.
Well, you don't set the roster.
I mean...
...what's St. V's mascot anyway?
The Irish.
So...
...we'd be the Black Irish?
Yo, that's trash.
Nah, man.
Them snow bunnies might be
hittin' though.
Man, y'all know if we do this,
our parents are gonna trip out.
Buchtel was the plan. We agreed.
You said Buchtel was the plan.
Yeah, because it'd make the most sense.
Yeah, so you can get a job there
while Bron, Sian, Willie,
they get to play varsity,
while I'm on JV. Right?
Who cares about me?
- No. No.
It's not about that.
You were the one who said...
...we was gonna do something special.
How we supposed to do that
if we ain't even together?
Let's-let's reason this out.
All of you want to go to St. V's?
We just want to play together, Dad.
Willie's talkin' to Illya.
And-and Bron,
he's talking with his moms.
Dad, Coach Dambrot,
he's a real coach.
His squad played the Fab Five.
Plus he said he'd ask them to enroll us...
...with full scholarships
if we all just say yes.
I'll talk to your mom about it.
All right, bet.
Thanks, Dad.
Come on, bro.
What are you gonna tell Coach Sams?
The truth I guess.
Does it matter?
No.
No matter what you say, we're
gonna be labelled sellouts.
This is a Buchtel town.
We just living in it.
Look at you.
Pose for me one more time.
Come on, pose, Denzel.
Mama, this ain't funny.
Shittin' me it ain't.
Oh, don't be all shy now.
You asked for this.
Go ahead.
Knock 'em dead, baby.
All right, looking good.
Stop.
Oh, my goodness, look at y'all.
Okay, now tell me.
Which one of y'all
is supposed to be Carlton?
Ma, stop.
- Is it you? Is it you?
Is it you?
- Stop, stop.
Man, with your cheatin' ass.
She let you copy off her test?
Don't hate the player,
hate the game.
'Ey. I know this is trials but
that's all just a technicality.
Be the Fab Four.
Show 'em how it's done.
Oh, shit.
Black people.
Where y'all been at?
Right over left.
So, how come we never see y'all
in church?
Chapel ain't required for varsity seniors.
Jermaine, team captain.
That's Marlon, Malik, Jake.
And back there is Chris.
- Switch.
Well, um, this Sian,
that's Bron.
Lil Dru, and I'm...
Willie McGee.
One of the best players in the city, right?
Well, in this gym,
you're just another freshman.
Dambrot recruited us.
Dambrot's a burnout.
Y'all know why he landed here, right?
I'm surprised you even came.
Heads up.
Okay.
When I was your age, I...
...well, hated being in high school...
...and now that I'm back,
I hate it even more.
So if I gonna be here,
I'm gonna win.
I don't give a shit if you started last year,
or you got a scholarship...
...or if your uncle is Michael Jordan.
If you're weak or lazy,
you ain't makin' the team.
If you're slow,
If you suck, you're out.
For everyone left,
the next four hours will tell us
who makes it and who breaks it.
Coop, it's all yours.
Everybody on the line. Let's go.
Let's move. Hustle up.
Three-point line, back.
Half-court line, back.
Baseline, back. Go!
Touch the line, touch the line!
* So what if that I'm cheatin'? * -Let's go!
Touch it with your fingers!
With your fingers!
Yo, is this tryouts or Fight Club?
Dru, what's up with your boy?
Any of you tired?
Worn out?
Fatigued?
Maybe you're hungry.
If that's the case,
get out of my gym!
Suicides. Again.
Burpees!
Again!
Come on, hustle up!
Again.
You're slacking, team!
All right, gentlemen,
bear crawl.
Bear crawl now and you stand tall later.
Yo, if that was tryouts.
I don't even want to think about
actual practice.
I'd rather quit school and join the Marines...
...then do that shit again.
Maybe Buchtel will take us back.
Oh, my God,
listen to y'all, man.
We made the team, right?
So stop trippin'.
The only reason why we here
is 'cause you a midget.
Now we all gotta suffer.
No, we came here 'cause we the Fab Four.
You think them hatin'-ass seniors...
...and coach cuckoo bird give
a shit about the Fab Four?
Dude threw a basketball at my head.
What's up, man?
I've been waiting in the car...
...for, like, ten minutes.
Oh, oh, s-sorry, man.
I would ask y'all how it went but...
All right, come on,
I can't be late for work, man.
Come on. We gotta go.
And if any of y'all want a ride,
y'all better come on, too.
Hey, listen.
Let it play out, a'ight?
It's day one.
It'll get better when the season starts.
Yo, this is some bullshit.
What'd you say?
- This is some bullshit.
Grab the ball!
How we benchwarmin' while
Romeo Travis, of all people,
gets to start for Central?
I still owe him an ass whoopin'
for stealin' my J's.
He beat yo ass. I was there.
Ha.
- He did beat your ass.
What you lookin' at, munchkin?
Yo, Coach! Yo, Coach, put me in!
I don't think coach heard you, dawg.
Jermaine!
- For the 15th time.
You keep yellin' at him,
he ain't never gonna play us.
They're not very good, huh?
- No.
Hey!
- Goddamn it!
Marlon. Marlon, come on in.
Get your soft ass down.
Uh, Willie, you're in the game.
Oh, me?
- Let's go.
Yo, yo, go, go! -Go!
Hey, yo, Unc! Hey, Unc!
Let's go, Unc!
Come on, come on, press it up.
Come on, Willie,
get over it. -Come on, Irish.
He right there, he right there!
Let's go, Willie.
- Pass the ball, pass the ball.
Give him the ball!
Hey, pass him the ball. Pass it.
Come on, man.
- Come on, man.
This some bullshit.
They ain't passing Willie the ball.
He ain't gettin' no love.
- Why you holding onto it?
Shut up, Dru.
Just shut up.
Give it to three-four!
- All right now.
Defense, Willie!
Yo, yo.
- Yeah, Willie.
There he is, yeah.
Ain't no way you ain't makin'
the rotation after tonight.
Just sayin', if they would've
put you in earlier,
we would've won.
You was the only one playin' D.
Man, if we all was out there,
we would've been blew they ass out.
So y'all got something to say?
Nobody was talkin' to you.
If you got a problem with the rotation,
go ahead and take it up with coach.
But that's right.
'Cause he don't want
to hear shit you gotta say.
We ain't come to not play.
- But y'all ain't special.
You pay your dues just like we had to,
like everybody.
And if you don't like it,
then quit.
Y'all ain't doin' nothin' else
out there other than losin'.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
What'd you say?
Oh, you heard me.
Yeah, you deaf?
Want me to say it louder,
Mr. seven points,
five rebounds, four turnovers?
The season hasn't even started yet...
...and I'm already sick of these punks.
Man, what?
- What'd you say?
Hold on. All right,
all right, all right, all right.
So y'all think you're better than us, right?
Duh.
- For sure.
So meet here tomorrow at 4:00...
...and then we'll see what's up.
Man, girls volleyball practice is at 4:00.
How do you know that?
How you not?
I mean,
Bettes Park is always open.
If y'all ain't scared.
Y'all versus the Fab Four.
Oh.
I didn't think you guys
were gonna show up.
Why?
Ain't nobody scared.
Those matchin' shirts is cute.
Well, you gotta earn these, playboy.
Hey, James Podeski.
But, uh, you can call me Jimmy.
Cap said I'm your fifth man?
First to 21?
Let's do it.
We up.
Get up. Hey!
Yeah.
- Set me up, set me up.
Swing, swing, swing. Yep.
Nah, it's mine.
Oh!
Push it!
Oh, get... take that.
- Oh, hey, Willie, Willie,
you got it, you got it.
Oh, my goodness.
- Hey!
What up, Cap?
Willie McGee.
You know I'm about to go left
and dunk this, right?
Watch this, my nigga...
You are my sons!
- Oh-ho.
Little ass freshman.
Go.
- Get up.
Oh, my God!
Wow, that kid's a freshman.
I've never seen anything like that.
Hey, what should I do?
You're doing it, man.
Keep it up.
Pass the rock. Damn, I'm open.
You don't have shit.
Man, they got us down 14-10.
Wake up.
Was that gunfire?
So what,
they shootin' over there.
We shootin' over here.
Game point.
Yeah.
Yeah, Akron style, man!
- That's what I'm talkin' about.
Yeah, yeah.
Good game, Sian.
- Yeah.
Yo, Coach.
You hungry?
Well, they obviously never get
tired of playing basketball.
What else do they do?
Oh, sometimes they play video games.
Thank you.
- Coach,
basketball video games.
Yeah, that is true.
Well, they show a lot of passion.
Especially Dru.
Yeah, my boy can be a bit of a hothead.
The other boys put him
in check though, you know.
They all kind of balance
each other out like that.
Guess I'm lucky.
What do you mean?
I was just trying to find good kids.
I wasn't trying to make the best
AAU team when they were young.
Willie...
I first saw Willie at a YMCA game.
He was amazing.
He was crossing over kids twice his size.
Both his parents...
...addicts in Chicago.
His big brother Illya took him in...
...and became his legal guardian
at the age of 18.
Saved his little brother's life.
Geez.
Sian... I go to church with
Sian's dad, um, Lee Cotton.
You know, we just wanted Sian
to work off a little bit of...
...a little bit of his baby fat.
I hear you.
My boy, Dru? Dru was born
with basketball in his blood.
I used to read John Wooden's
book to him in his crib.
Now it doesn't hurt that he was so tall,
but I picked LeBron because he had skills...
...and was a-a good kid.
His mom, she gotta work.
She can't always be there,
she gotta pull down shifts...
...so she just wants a spot
where he can be safe,
stay busy and not get in any trouble.
If they have the-the opportunity
to keep playing together,
it's gonna be special.
Listen, thank you.
Thanks for coming over
and-and checking on the boys.
Well, I should be thanking you.
I was trying to keep them humble.
Good luck with that.
We play St. V's ball today, right?
All right, all in on three.
One, two, three.
- All in.
Willie McGee voted
Mr. Basketball Youth League
Ohio Valley last year...
...gets his first start tonight.
Willie!
It's hard to believe...
...he was just an eighth grader last season.
He really contributed to St. Vincent's...
...young basketball season so far.
- Time! Ref, time out!
What? -
- Come on, come on.
Hustle in.
- Come on, boys, focus.
Jake, what's your problem?
You're not even in position,
okay? -Huh?
Uh, LeBron. You're in the game.
Let's go.
Come on, come on, play ball.
You go, baby!
There we go, they got Willie
and LeBron in the game,
they gonna kill.
This is crap!
Let's see what happens, huh?
This is ridiculous!
Jake, stop the ball!
Yeah, let's go!
Oh, boy. Wow.
Oh, that was special.
Time out!
LeBron James slams!
Ah, let's try this.
Come here.
Take a seat.
It's all right, take a seat.
Sit down, sit down. Here we go.
Lil Dru, you're in the game.
Let's go.
Come on, come on, check in.
Get in this game!
Sian, get on the court.
Let's go.
Play ball.
And Dambrot is doubling down...
...putting two more freshmen in the game.
Sian Cotton and Dru Joyce.
It's not how you start the game...!
Let's finish it!
Dambrot. Dambrot.
Dambrot! What the hell?!
They're freshmen!
- Let's go, let's go.
My son is a senior.
I want him playing.
Playing a freshman.
What is this, Hoop It Up?
We usually give more playing
time to the upperclassmen.
It-it's a policy.
Yeah, well,
policy doesn't win games.
He's a freshman! Take it out!
A steal from Cotton.
Outlet passes to Joyce.
Off the backboard
and James slams it home!
Look, I don't think I'm overstating...
...that we way be seeing the beginnings...
...of something special here in Akron.
That's how these freshman play!
Yeah? -Spencer Keizler from The Chronicle.
Well, thanks, Coach.
Um, what's it like coaching...
...the best high school
player in the country?
Who, LeBron?
Yeah, best player, my ass.
Kid's always loafing on defense.
Max Winter from The Post.
- Hey, Max.
What about you, Coach?
You thinking about returning...
...back to college any time soon?
I'm right in the middle of a
season with this crazy bunch,
so, uh...
Yeah. Hell yeah, I'm thinking
about it all the time.
This the last doughnut.
You want half?
- It's all you.
I'm good.
I'm tryin' to watch my weight.
Mmm.
Watch your weight do what?
What you mean, 'Do what,' man?
You watching your weight. What? Do what?
I'm tryin' to eat better, man.
Hey, guys!
How's it feel to be pimping for St. Vincent?
Gonna be a brick next time,
you get on the coaching staff.
Uh, Mr. Wahl?
- I'm on deadline. What?
60 seconds to run something by you?
I'll be at my office in 30 so talk twice as fast.
'After a forfeit from Buchtel,
'St. Vincent-St. Mary's finished
its undefeated season...
...with a 73-55 win over Greenview
High for the state title.'
This is high school basketball?
My old rival high school, sir.
Feels like filler for the kid's
magazine. Anything else?
The star players were four freshmen.
I think one in particular
could be the next Jordan.
Kobe Bryant's the next Jordan.
So maybe he's the next Kobe?
Kobe's too young to have a next.
Keep me posted on wonder boy.
What's his name anyway?
Hey, yo, Bron.
Check this out, my dawg.
Hmm?
- Looking like that, man.
Um... we ain't order this.
My manager went to St. V's.
Says enjoy.
It's on the house, baby.
Oh...
Yo, by all means,
this year finna be straight fire.
Facts.
- Hey.
I know y'all seen her checkin' me out.
Man, she was checkin' me out.
Y'all ain't got no game though.
Unlike y'all, I get girls.
Since when?
Melody.
Bro, y'all just hugged that one time.
Was it Melody from seventh grade?
Yo, you're still on that?
He's still on that.
- Talkin' about the girl...
...from seventh grade.
Hey, shut up.
Yo...
Oh, yo!
Nah.
- What up?
Illya'd never lets you drive his joint.
You right, but it ain't his whip no more.
You heard he got a new car, right?
Know what that mean.
We in business!
Last year is last year.
Doesn't do shit for us anymore
but put a big target on our ass.
If we don't win at all,
they'll say it's a fluke.
And it'll be a fluke.
Maybe you see some new faces here.
This is Mr. Travis,
who did us the favor...
...of getting expelled again so
that he could be here with us.
What you lookin' at, munchkin?
Lucky for him, I value good
defense over bad behavior,
so, listen up, Romeo,
pull any shit on my team,
you consider yourself permanently retired.
Oh, this here is Coach Dru.
Some of you all know him,
I think.
We need him on the schedule...
Wait, whoa, ho, ho, ho.
No, he's not gonna save you all.
Right?
We're gonna win it all...
...because you're gonna
work your asses off.
That's how this works.
All right?
Let's go.
Come on, bring it in on three.
One, two, three.
- All in!
Man, why...
Why you slide? Why you slide?
Watch out.
You watch out.
It's not that he really
broke another kid's jaw?
Man, do we even know
he broke the first kid's jaw?
Well, he here now so he had
to break somebody's jaw.
Let's go say somethin'.
Hell no.
We can't keep ignoring him.
What we gonna do on the court,
sign language?
What's wrong with that?
Man, let's just go say wussup.
Yo, stop acting scary.
- Hey, yo.
Food don't got much seasonin' on it, but...
...you gonna get used to it.
What y'all want, man?
Look, bro, we on the same team,
so we might as well talk.
You can save all that fake shit.
See? I told y'all this career criminal...
...wasn't worth our time.
You lucky you got them little
dress shoes on...
...or I'd take them, too.
Yo, I'd like to see you try.
- Dru.
Dru. Chill.
Look, dawg,
we got a good thing goin'.
All we want to know is
if you tryin' to mess it up.
I tried.
I guess, but...
You can't be serious.
See he wasn't gonna eat it.
Oh, your fat ass.
Sian Cotton!
Yeah, yeah.
Willie McGee!
Dru Joyce!
Romeo Travis!
LeBron James!
I can't hear you.
And it's a capacity
crowd here tonight in Akron.
This place is bursting at the seams...
Pass the ball.
Pass the ball, Dru.
...as defending state champions St. V's...
...takes on perennial powerhouse Massillon.
Hey, Dru!
Pass the ball next time!
He was wide open!
Yo, listen to your pop, midget.
Kiss my ass.
Can't nobody bend that low.
Ooh, Travis blocks the shot.
LeBron James grabs the rebound.
That looks like he's going coast-to-coast!
And that's what
we call a guaranteed bucket.
H-Have you ever
heard the story of King Arthur?
Yes, sir.
The boy that would be king.
Yeah, Bob, I mean,
the score is so lopsided,
the starting five are resting on the bench...
...and some of the reserves
get a go at the Tigers.
Bro, it's gonna be so many
chicks at that party.
I'm telling you.
I got two of their cheerleaders'
numbers before the game.
And their team sucks.
They want us there.
And it's gonna be packed out.
I don't know, man.
Yo, what's the point of bein' popular...
...if we just gonna hang out
all night at Dru's playin' 2K...
...and wait for Girls Gone Wild
commercials to come on?
I like Girls Gone Wild.
- Huh.
E pluribus unum, nigga.
Seize the day.
I say we go to that bitch.
All right, so,
maybe this was a good idea.
Told you.
Come on.
LeBron James.
Tequila or... vodka.
- How are you?
Vodka.
Excuse me, miss.
You was at the game tonight?
Okay, I gotta be trippin'.
I'm gonna catch you later.
Oh!
Yo, for real?!
- I-I'm so sorry.
Ya think? Agh!
Oh.
I'm-I'm so sorry.
I did not mean to do that.
- Look, it's fine.
Just leave me alone.
Here. Take it.
Please.
St. V's?
Pretty far from home.
N-Nah, it's just my boy drove... -It's cool.
I go to Buchtel.
My cousin invited me out.
Buchtel, huh?
Yeah, why?
They don't like me too much over there.
Why, you throw drinks on them, too?
Nah, just you.
Well, you got some nerve.
I'm Savannah.
I know.
Mm.
Hmm.
This is what you call...
...a hangover!
Why you yellin'?
Play stupid games,
win stupid prizes.
Okay, Don Juan.
Who's the girl?
Your hand.
Her name's Savannah.
Savannah?
Hmm.
She cute?
What you think?
I don't know,
you kinda goofy looking.
I don't know what you might attract.
Ma.
I'm just playin' with you.
You know you handsome.
Drink up.
You're gonna need it.
Can I borrow your car
next weekend to take her out?
Sorry, baby, I picked up some
night shifts next weekend.
It's okay, I'll figure it out.
I don't know why you had
to keep asking for more bread.
They told you the kitchen was closed.
They wasn't gonna do nothin'
but throw it away.
I want my full dining experience
with my leftovers.
Okay, whatever.
Let me see.
You know I got the magic touch.
You know I-I got this.
There you go.
Nice try,
but you don't get points...
...for opening my door after I already tried.
You a hater.
Yeah.
Really?
This is not my car.
It's my boy Willie's.
- Mm.
Mm-hmm.
- It sucks.
I'm sorry.
Let's just give it a minute.
And we're always in the fight!
You can't get us,
we're always in the fight!
Yeah, we are Buchtel
and we're always in the fight!
There they go.
You can't get us,
we're always in the fight!
We are Buchtel...!
LeBron is a sellout!
Who you calling a sellout, Tony?
You still owe me $100! Sit down!
Hey, fellas, let's focus.
Let's pay no mind to all this bullshit.
These the same dudes
who called us sellouts.
Same dudes who tried to put me on JV.
I ain't losin' tonight.
Period.
Come on, now!
Come on, call that foul!
You blind?
Daydreaming!
Ah, no, no, no!
Come on!
Time out! Bring it in.
Yeah, we are Buchtel
and we're always in the fight!
Taking a walk! Get in here!
You got pride.
We gonna let these people
over here disrespect us?
No, we're not.
It's a mismatch out there.
You're too small and-and the refs,
they're swallowing the whistle,
so take a break.
Sit down, Dru.
All in on three.
One, two, three.
All in.
Dru, what are you doing?
Lock in, boy.
Oh, Dru Joyce is checking into the game.
Diminutive would be
a vast understatement.
He's all of five feet,
two inches tall. -Sit down.
Dru, that's not the play!
He's not bashful
either. Those guys are on him.
They're flying at him.
He doesn't care.
No, no!
Long three by Dru Joyce.
And he stuck it again.
You almost couldn't see him
shoot it, and he stuck it.
Got to be proud of the little guy.
Oh, no, don't shoot that.
Dru Joyce gets open deep in the corner...
...and he'd done it again.
Dru Joyce has the fans
here today -He's hot, he's hot.
just in disbelief at his
ability to shoot the basketball.
This looks like the Irish...
...just want to pass it around the outside...
...and look for the...
Is he's shooting that or throwing it?
He's catching it, his feet set...
...and he just knocked it down.
That's five of them.
Here we go. Five for five.
- Five for five.
He's gonna try another one.
Check this out.
Six for six, Dru Joyce.
He had 18 points
in six minutes of court time.
Well, but he's...
he's pretty big today.
Six for six from behind...
...the three-point.
- No question about it.
18 points for Dru Joyce
to lead everyone in scoring...
...for Akron St. Vincent-St. Mary.
Good game.
Good game, guys.
Everybody on the bus.
Yeah. Rat-a-tat-tat.
Boy, you wet them fools up.
That's what I'm talking about.
Where you going? You thought you
wasn't gonna see us again.
Not gonna deal with y'all
right now, man, move.
I'm talking to you.
- Sellout ass.
Where's the rest of your cheap ass team?
Yo, that's Romeo.
That's Romeo.
- Yo, Dru, hold up.
Hey, yo, yo, yo, yo!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
What is wrong with you?
That was stupid.
- Man, what?
You out here having
Ultimate Fighting Championships...
...by yoself.
- Literally, bro.
You didn't have to do that shit, bro.
Huh. We beat they ass, though.
Oh, my God.
I know y'all seen Dru come
through with the Falcon Punch.
Yeah, but who were they, though?
Don't worry about it.
They was nobody.
Yeah, nobody till we beat they ass.
LeBron. Six-six, yep.
And he ain't even done growing.
Yes.
Special. Very, very special.
Well, just come,
come and see for yourself.
His next game is this Friday.
A-All right, now.
Yes.
Thank you. Good night.
So, who was that?
That was Sports Illustrated.
They want to do a story on LeBron.
Mm-hmm.
We have a big deal now.
Well, look at that.
My baby's a celebrity.
Yeah.
Guess you raised a baller.
Mm.
Coach, Coach. How long
you playing LeBron tonight?
The whole game? Half game?
Max, what don't you ask Coach
Dru a couple of these questions.
I got a game to win.
Hey, how you feeling
about coaching your son...
...in the championship game tonight?
I'm just an assistant,
but I think we're getting
used to the dynamic. You know?
Yeah, you're gonna have to, right,
with Coach Dambrot
going back to college ball.
Where do you get your information from?
You leaving, Coach?
No, don't listen...
- Yeah. Hell yeah.
University of Akron.
Deals done.
Tonight's the last game.
Is this not true?
What's with the questions?
Damn it.
Locker room, right now.
Let's go!
Ball!
No, he didn't touch him!
The 2001 Ohio State Championship...
...is underway and St. Vincent-St. Mary's,
led by LeBron James,
are dominating.
Will you listen?
Listen to me.
Screen, screen, screen,
back, back.
No, don't shoot that...
Okay, okay.
Okay, get back.
Yeah, the team is
playing with more individual...
...streetball style tonight.
Yeah, I agree.
There's been a lot of showboating,
which is uncharacteristic
for a Dambrot team.
Coach, why don't you try...
...and talk some sense
into one of your boys, huh?
They're not listening.
What's he doing over here?
This is ridiculous.
I gotta call time.
Dru!
Time! Time!
Time.
Dru, Dru, what are you doing?
We got a game plan.
What are you doing?
One play, not one play we practiced.
You know, you...
You got some goddamn nerve,
Lil Dru.
I got a nerve?
We ain't run not one of
your plays this whole night...
...and we still winning.
There's a game plan, Dru.
No, no, stop with the game plan shit.
We don't need you,
we never needed you.
You just been riding our coattails...
...ever since you got here.
Dru. -Just so you could get your ticket out.
Yeah, yeah, but I worked
my ass off to build you up.
Nah, Coach,
you just got in the way.
Now, if you want to leave...
...cool, leave.
'Cause I promise, don't nobody
care around here, man.
Bye. See ya. Sayonara.
- This is ridiculous.
C-Coach.
- Hey, Coach. Coach.
No, I'm not putting up with this shit.
Coach.
Coach, wait.
There's six minutes left.
It's a championship game.
Coach.
Coach... -I'm not going to be disrespected...
...by a bunch of teenagers.
What do you expect?
They look up to you,
and you're walking out on them.
So you want me to get 'em in a circle...
...and all hold hands and have a good cry?
I have an opportunity.
They'll get over this.
Most of these boys been getting over it...
...their entire lives.
Every time someone gets close to them,
they end up leaving,
abandoning them.
Every single person that matters
to them has left.
Except you.
Coach, I tried to keep them humble.
You said it was going to be hard but...
...they're so damn good and they know it.
Just make sure that
doesn't tear them apart.
Hmm?
Got six minutes.
Yeah. Heard he planned it all along.
Yeah, but what's he going to do?
Not go?
Screw that, Uncle Willie.
We the reason why he got a shot
in the first place.
Oh, Dru,
this shit not funny, bro.
It's a serious matter.
Bro, how can y'all be serious
with this comedy playin' out?
Yo, stop tryin' to act hard!
With your soft ass.
Man, stop making me laugh.
Yo.
- Oh.
Yo, what you doin'? Focus.
Stop worryin' about us.
Yo, sit down.
- A'ight.
Oh, he mad.
Hey, yo, check this out.
Check this out.
That's my foot.
How is that your foot?
I was standin' right behind him.
Man, Ray Charles could see that
that's my lean chocolate calf.
That is not your ashy ass calf.
Ain't nothin' lean about that calf.
What y'all talking about?
I see it, I guess.
Yeah. Thanks, Ms. Gloria.
Bro, you can't tell she was bein' sarcastic?
Dang.
- What...?
Hey. Stop, st-stop it.
- Get him, Dru. Get him. Hit him.
Man, you hit hard for a little man.
Ma, can we buy your car...
...so we don't have to cram
into Willie's bucket?
Sure, baby.
Yo.
Yeah. Oh, damn.
Hold on.
- Yo!
Oh, yo, this is art.
We in the front,
We in the front.
Get in the back.
Yeah, try to sit in the back.
How'd you pull this off?
I took out a loan.
They know we're gonna be good for it.
Check out your ride.
Man, this shit clean, dawg.
Wait, you got a DVD playing here.
LeBron, yo, let's ride.
Let's get out of here.
Wait, hold up, hold up, hold up.
What about my car?
Bro, no, no, ain't nobody
gonna steal that shit, bro.
Yeah, laugh now, laugh now.
Just don't forget, when y'all
needed a ride somewhere.
Who was there for y'all?
Uncle Willie.
LeBron.
He's here. LeBron.
Okay, kids, squeeze in.
LeBron.
- Hey.
You a fan of Wes Unseld?
Washington Bullets?
You kiddin' me. Of course.
This is for you.
This real?
- Of course it's real.
It's vintage, from 1976.
Now it's yours.
- Dang.
Man, thank you. Appreciate that.
Yeah, you... hey,
you mind taking a picture?
Uh, sure.
- All right, great.
Hey, would you take our picture?
Please? Come on.
Oh, thank you so much.
- Yeah.
All right.
Thank you very much.
All right, thank you.
- Hey, man, nice to meet you.
Hi. What'd you get?
Cookies and cream.
Yeah, and it's half melted.
Still good,
it's just ice cream soup.
Are you done being famous now?
Done with your little attitude now?
Maybe.
Your food's in the car.
I think it would be
a really smart choice, you know.
I'm sorry,
you said something, babe.
What I was trying to say is that
the class is only 200 bucks...
...and it's supposed to be really good...
...and you should check it out.
Okay.
What do I need to take an SAT for?
What if you blow your knee out or...?
Hey, don't put that on me.
Don't do that.
I'm just saying.
- I'm just sayin'.
I'm going to be making millions
right out the gate.
I definitely don't need college.
You don't either.
Wait, what's that supposed to mean?
It means you hit the lotto.
Oh, I did, did I?
Oh, wait, I just...
Hey, everybody,
I just hit the lottery.
Savannah, that came out.
No, no, no, 'cause my boyfriend
is LeBron James.
I mean,
I had to buy his ice cream...
'cause he didn't have no cash.
But in a couple years?
Bling, bling, hoe.
Gold diggers, stand up.
Savannah, I was just sayin'...
I know exactly what you were saying...
'cause you've been saying it
for a while now.
I mean, look at you,
you ain't even in the NBA yet,
but I can't tell.
What's it going to be like
when you actually are?
Ain't nothin' about me gonna change.
I'm still me.
Are you?
You're good at basketball.
LeBron, you're great,
but if you don't check yourself,
basketball is gonna be all that you have.
Basketball is gonna be all that you have.
Coach!
All right.
All right, all right, I get it.
Listen up.
Now, I know everybody thinks y'all are...
God's gift to basketball, right?
But we got to get ready.
I don't need to get ready
'cause I stay ready.
I hope so,
'cause this ain't last year.
We ain't playing for no state championship.
We're playing for number one in the nation.
So if you thought last year's
schedule was hard, think again.
We ran through that.
Well, now a whole country
going to be watching,
and we got Oak Hill
next month, remember?
The consensus number one team.
Basically,
it's a bunch of all-stars.
I suggest you do not let this
go to your heads.
Came to tell you, you know,
welcome to the family, dawg.
Fab Four is now officially the Fab Five.
What does La Quinta even mean?
It means you failed Spanish, Negro.
Yeah, we came a long way
from selling duct tape.
Man, jerseys sure look a lot better, too.
Y'all sold duct tape for uniforms?
We came from the struggle, dawg.
Struggle?
I had to break a kid's jaw to get here.
Y'all really believe that shit?
But I told these fools
that was some bullshit.
Man, it's the crazy eyes you got, you know.
No, but look, though,
if we beat these dudes,
we're going to be number one.
Like legit,
the best team in America.
We already the best team.
- Nah, dawg.
Like Ric Flair said,
to beat a man...
You gotta be the man!
Whoo!
Oh, shit.
Oh, what's up?
- Yo...
I just got invited to a party...
...and they said half the league
is goin' to be there.
Hey, y'all got to cover for me.
I'll be back.
Bro.
All right, bro.
The Fighting Irish are going...
...to have their hands full here tonight...
...with Oak Hill Academy.
They've been called The Hoop factory.
NBA High, and, of course,
the number one team
in America by USA Today.
And, boy, are they loaded.
Boasting a starting lineup
filled with top 100 recruits,
including the number one recruit
in the nation, Carmelo Anthony.
What's going on?
Are you all right?
Yeah, it's just the pizza from last night.
Yeah, it was pepperoni.
He was in the bathroom all night, Coach.
Well, maybe you should sit out this game.
No, I'm good.
For real, I'm fine.
Oak Hills' Carmelo Anthony...
...and St. V's LeBron James...
...are both leading their teams in scoring.
Well, we are going to see...
...both of these young men in the NBA,
and one of them is going
to have bragging rights...
...when this game comes up.
Yeah, up until this game.
St. V's hasn't really faced any adversity.
Hey, yo, steal.
Wow, Willie McGee
really picking up the slack...
...for the Irish here in the third.
With all the hype surrounding
LeBron James,
this is a bit of a disappointing debut...
...on the big stage for him today.
Go, go!
Push, push.
A great game,
but, tonight,
Oak Hill just wanted it more.
I agree.
LeBron James and the Irish...
...looked good at times,
but ultimately came up short.
Final score Oak Hill 77.
St. Vincent-St. Mary's 66.
Let me talk to you for a minute.
I want you to take today,
how you played and the outcome...
...and learn from it.
You are a special player.
The whole world already knows it.
You are going to have
to deal with distractions...
...these other boys are not going
to have to deal with.
I'm just being real.
How successful you become
depends entirely...
...on how well you manage...
...the pressure.
We're definitely blessed.
I mean, this is the third year
in a row going back to state.
And I know with these guys behind me,
we can make it a three-peat.
Listen, Dru,
take the ball back up top.
Uh, well, yeah, you know,
it-it's the chemistry we got.
I know where LeBron gonna be
before he even gets there.
No, no, no.
Run it back.
What you-what you looking at?
W-Willie flashed out to the wing.
I thought I could get it to him. -Willie?
They play ain't for Willie, son.
Well, we've been playin'
basketball together...
...since we were ten.
It's like, natural.
Uh, coming from where I'm from.
I-it's crazy to see how
tight-knit everyone was.
And then they just kind of folded me in,
made me a part of the family,
'cause that's what this feels like, family.
Coach, Rome wasn't cuttin' fast enough.
Yo, I was right there.
You just wanted to shoot that...
I don't want to hear that.
Even when we're not on the
court, we're always together.
That's how it's always been.
LeBron's this big star now,
but to us,
it feels like nothing's changed.
You acting like you don't understand...
...simple concepts!
Hello!
When the down screen come from LeBron,
give him the ball.
Great. Okay,
I think that's good.
Thank you so much, guys.
Thanks.
- Thank you.
Uh, you see that there?
That is pure joy there.
They're just taking every opportunity here...
...and spinning it into pure gold.
And they're a good team,
but this is unexpected.
The fans are going nuts.
Well, with the ten point lead...
...and growing, it's like,
no wonder.
You suck! You suck! You suck!
You suck! You suck!
You suck!
Watch out, watch out,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ball.
That ain't no foul, ref?
Ain't no foul, no foul,
keep playing.
No foul, keep playing,
Pass the ball.
You ain't gotta do it all by yourself.
Roger Bacon...!
Let's go!
Move the ball!
Roger Bacon, that's right!
That's terrible court spacing.
Ball, pass the ball.
You ain't gotta do it all by yourself.
Yo, time.
No, you didn't.
- Yes, I did.
Get open. You're no help.
I've been open this whole time.
- Get open.
Hey, I don't want to hear none of that.
Get over here.
Bro, we about to blow it
against Roger got-damn Bacon.
How we gettin' beat by a team
named after a breakfast meat?
Cut the talk, pay attention.
We could still win this game.
All in on three.
One, two, three.
- All in.
Pass the ball.
Man, play some defense.
What the hell, bruh!
Focus on your game, Dru!
Sorry, can't all be 23.
Watch your mouth.
You supposed to switch that.
I'm only helping.
You need to get back.
Shut the fuck up, Chosen One.
What'd you say to me?
You got ears.
Get out of my face, bro.
Don't be mad at me...
'cause you ain't tall enough to make it pro.
Huh?
- You stop pushing me.
Hey, hey, guys, cut it out,
cut it out, cut it out.
You gonna mess around and get a tech.
12 green.
Come on, man, think.
You're costing us the game, Dru.
Get off of me, bro.
Dru!
Get over here!
Hey, LeBron.
Damn, get over here.
Are we really gonna lose this game?
Think we might have lost more than that.
Man, this shit ain't fun no more.
Yo.
After midnight again, man.
A couple more.
All right, what's going on, man?
What's up?
When we was kids...
...I had size and skills over everybody.
But it's like...
...they got better and I just stayed the same.
What happens if nobody wants me?
Get up, man.
Let me ask you something,
why you think the boys...
...been calling you Uncle Willie
since y'all was 11?
What's that got to do with anything?
You a leader, Willie.
Just 'cause you ain't leading
down the path you thought,
does not mean you ain't on your way.
You hear what I'm saying?
You're a whole lot more than
just basketball, little bro.
What you doing here?
Nice to see you, too.
You should be proud.
You guys had a good season.
You boys are looking good.
When are we not?
Roger Bacon ring a bell?
You come here to break my balls?
Only partly.
My point guard graduates this year.
You want me to come play for you?
You're a good player, Dru.
I enjoyed coaching you.
So much you dipped out on us
first chance you got.
I wanted back in college ball.
I saw my shot and I took it.
Not going to apologize for that.
It doesn't mean I'm blind
to what you boys did for me.
Or that I forgot what I was doing...
...in this school in the first place.
It's not like I left you high and dry.
I knew you'd be in good hands.
I wanted to make great players out of you.
And I did.
Your dad wants to make great men.
That'll last you a lot longer.
Don't forget that.
Give me a call.
So we just ain't gonna talk to each other...
...for the whole season?
I got somethin' to say.
Look, I came here to play ball,
to put in work.
So while I'm here,
that's what I plan to do.
Before practice, after practice,
it's whatever.
But when we get on that court,
it's strictly business.
You feel me?
Yeah.
All right.
Well, we got Oak Hill next month, so...
So we do what we gotta do.
A high school game here in Cleveland...
...has attracted a crowd
of 10,000 here tonight.
But it's not just any high school game.
It's phenom LeBron James...
...against the number one ranked
team in the country, Oak Hill.
LeBron mania goes national here tonight.
He's one of those teenage phenoms...
...that come along in their given sport...
...and are so gifted and all I know is...
...if he's half as good
as all I've heard about him,
he is going to be one special athlete.
Good game, man.
LeBron, can we have a word with you?
Oh, no, yeah, of course.
Love you.
You've been on the cover
of Sports Illustrated.
ESPN and USA Today.
That must be a bit surreal.
What do you think?
Is it too much pressure for you?
No, no, it's never no pressure.
No, I just come in there,
play my game,
and get my teammates involved.
You know,
when I'm with my boys, man.
I'm always focused like no other. For real.
And tonight, we played the
number one team in the country.
We gave it our all, 110%,
like we do every other night.
We all do it together.
Well, congrats.
Enjoy the win.
- Thank you.
What happen, somebody die?
A bribe? That's bullshit.
It's what they're claiming.
It was a jersey
a random dude just gave me.
a vintage jersey worth $1,800.
How the hell is he supposed to know that?
Regardless, it was over
the permissible limits...
...set by OHSAA.
- It was from a fan.
Not a coach,
not a booster. A fan.
Besides, all the players get sponsored gear.
If the donor isn't a family
member, it's considered a bribe.
But it was just some random dude.
This is witch hunt, Dave.
There's been some very generous
alumni endowments...
...since these boys
stepped foot on this campus.
Don't you think we owe him our support?
The only thing that St. V
owes anyone is a good education,
and-and the look of a high school player...
...driving a Hummer doesn't help.
Please, no disrespect.
And, yes, I know what this is.
Look, it's not my call.
LeBron, you're suspended
for the rest of the season,
pending appeal.
Are you serious?
- No, you know this isn't right.
Mom.
- You can go to the games,
but you're not allowed to suit up...
...or interact with the players?
For all intents and purposes,
you're not a part of the team anymore.
He's just a kid.
Just... Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
A controversial Ohio High School
Athletic Association...
...ruling today involving
basketball phenom LeBron James.
This ruling means not only
is LeBron James ineligible...
...for the remainder of the season,
it means the Fighting Irish must forfeit...
...the big win last week over rival Buchtel.
Here's the OHSAA commissioner,
Clair Muscaro.
The OHSAA is not persecuting
one student athlete.
Rather, we are protecting every
student athlete on every team.
Bullshit.
Yo, Bron.
It's Unc checking up on you.
Illya told me to save it up.
I'm just letting you know, man,
we got your back, all right?
Yo, big dawg.
Just calling to check on you.
Um, you know, you know,
we gonna get through this.
Don't stress it.
Hey, yo, Bron,
I heard what happened, man.
That's some bullshit.
Forget Clair,
or whatever his name is.
Just hit me back, bro.
Listen up, listen up.
Y'all know who ain't here, right?
But we here. We here.
It don't matter that
everybody written us off...
...because we know what we capable of.
So, let's go out there
and show these fools...
...that we're more than just one player.
A'ight? A'ight?
More than just one player.
A'ight, all in on three.
One, two, three.
- All in!
Tonight St. V's goes
against Canton McKinley.
Both teams need this game...
...to continue to the state championship.
Yeah, and the whole
state of Ohio is aware tonight
LeBron James will not be on the court.
You know,
this is when the phrase,
'Next man up' becomes all too real.
And tonight, we'll see...
...how this St. Vincent team fares
without their centerpiece.
Let's go, green!
To Romeo!
There we go, there we go.
Come on, come on, come on.
Yeah!
Oh, yeah, Willie.
Time out.
- Time, time.
Ref!
Ooh, ooh, here we go, Bulldogs,
here we go, ooh, ooh!
Here we go, Bulldogs,
Here we go, Irish, here we go!
Here we go, Irish,
here we go!
Here we go, Bulldogs,
here we go, ooh, ooh!
Oh, hey, hey, hey,
come on, LeBron.
You know you can't.
- Come on, Coach Coop.
You'll get us in trouble,
all right?
I'm sorry, brother.
Come on, chin up.
You ain't going to say hi?
Hey, Ma.
How was the game?
What you watching?
I taped my stories.
They won.
They goin' to state.
'They'?
I ain't on the team no more.
Hmm.
Did you have friends in high school?
I had friends just like everybody else.
Nah, I mean like friends.
Yeah, I had a few.
You still talk to any of them?
Nah.
Not really.
That's just how life is sometimes, baby.
You go to school,
you got your crew...
...and you can't imagine what life
would be like without them.
Then you graduate or you move or...
The real world hits you,
gets in the way.
And you just kind of grow apart.
It happens.
It's really not what I wanted to hear.
I know.
But that don't change how it is.
What's important is that
when you look back...
...did you make the time
you had together count?
Did you give it everything you got?
Mr. James.
I'm sure you're aware that the association...
...has no bearing on your
eligibility for the NBA draft.
Yes, sir.
I have to be honest with you then.
I'm a little puzzled why we're all here today.
You're on the very brink
of wealth and fame...
...and by your own admission, you
don't plan to attend college.
I can't see how missing
one high school basketball game...
...will affect your future in any way.
It won't, sir.
You understand that presenting
yourself here today...
...puts us under no obligation
to reinstate you.
Yes, ma'am.
It's just...
...right now I'm not
thinking about the future.
I'm thinking about my brothers.
And they made it all the way
to state without me.
So this is just a vanity play...
...so you can be in
the championship game?
No, ma'am.
It wouldn't matter what game it was.
I moved ten times before I was 12.
All I had is my mom.
She's the only thing consistent,
you know?
And...
...this crazy coach...
...who kept quoting
John Wooden found me.
One of the only men in my life
that I could look up to.
He put me on the Shooting Stars...
...where I met Dru, Sian and Willie.
And, man, we'd hoop all day
except for school.
Uh... spend nights playing video games...
...and doing it all over again the next day.
It wasn't nothing special
really about it, but...
...it was special to me.
Then we went to St. V's
and met Coach Dambrot.
And, man, he was tough,
but he helped me become
the player who I am now.
People keep telling me that
my life's about to change...
...and...
...they probably right.
In a year..,.
...I might not be the same person.
So if I have to pay a fine,
change my jersey number,
do community service,
I'll do it.
Just tell me what to do.
But please...
...let me play with my best friends
one last time.
What's up, bruh?
Yo, what's up?
Hey, Bron. -It's good to have you back, bro.
I heard you cried in front of the board.
Like a 220-pound baby.
Bro.
- My boy.
What's good, bro?
- What's up, B? -What's up, man?
Look who came crawlin' back.
It's just sad when you see shit like that.
Ain't it sad, Rome?
It's definitely sad.
Shut up, y'all.
Ready to hoop?
- Hell, yeah.
Well, Bob,
it's been an absolute pleasure...
...covering four years of basketball...
...with the St. Vincent- St. Mary's team...
...and of course, the Akron phenom
himself, LeBron James.
I think everyone's hoping...
...for a storybook ending.
A low scoring game as we
come to the end of the quarter.
We now go into halftime
with St. V's down by five.
Tonight you have the chance to go down...
...as the greatest high school team
in basketball history.
But...
I want you to take a minute.
Try to grasp this thing.
This opportunity that we've been given.
I can tell you...
...when you look back
at this time in your lives,
it won't be about stats,
accolades, the X's and O's.
It's not about
winning the state championship.
It'll be that person next to you.
And no matter how you spin it,
this is my last time coaching some of you.
More importantly,
this is the last time...
...that this team will ever play together.
Ask yourselves, what are
you going to do with that time?
What's up?
Coach, I think it's time for me to come out.
'Cause it's time for Jimmy to go in.
All right.
Let's do it.
In on three.
One, two, three.
- Do it!
Get it, boy.
Jimmy Podeski!
Why they gotta play this song?
Are you cryin'
- No shit, I'm cryin'.
'Cause I got a heart
unlike you cold ass bastards.
It's all right there, big fella.
You guys ready?
Thought you guys were walking
with your families.
We are.
It's crazy.
Man, you abandoning us, Coach?
what y'all doing out here?
You know the party's in there.
Nah, last time we checked,
the party was in here.
Yeah, but you can't play
none of that whack ass music.
Whack ass music?
How have I failed you all so badly?
What do you know about this, Coach?
Y'all have to get in the back.
Yes. Y'all don't know nothing
about no music.
Hey, Willie,
what you doing, man?
Oh, my goodness.
- I got this, I got this.
Y'all stink.
- Coach, I got it.
No!
No, you ain't...
What y'all doin', baby?