- Good evening.
When we began these
specials twelve years ago,
the artist we're
going to meet tonight
was a struggling unknown.
But these days,
he is entering the history books
as the number one
singer in America,
selling more records than
Michael Jackson and Madonna.
And he's doing it
with country music.
His name? Troyal Brux.
You're at the height
of your career.
A million records sold.
And everyone looks up to
you as a country music hero.
- Hero. I mean, there's,
there's that word again.
You know, I think it's
time we redefine that word.
You know, am I a policeman
or fireman saving lives?
Yeah, in a way.
I'm saving souls with
my tight-ass voice.
- Tell us, Troyal,
who are your heroes?
- My heroes?
I mean, that's easy.
You know, the legends.
The people that paved the
way, that came before me.
You know, we're talking
about Johnny Cash,
Merle Haggard, Waylon
Jennings, Willie Nelson.
These people that marched to
the beat of their own drum.
- And if you could meet
any one of them today,
who tops the list?
- Kind of put me
on the spot there, Gail.
If I had to choose anyone,
I guess it'd be George Jones.
- And if George Jones was
watching you from home,
what would you say to him?
Bub Nelson.
It's best when shared
with someone you love,
or someone you just
like to have a good...
- Cut.
- What was wrong with that one?
- Okay, Troyal. No,
it's good, it's good.
But, uh, I'd like you to
relax a little more...
- I am relaxed.
- Well, you're about
to have a beer.
You don't have to,
they, they do want a sense
you're gonna enjoy it.
- I mean, I probably
will enjoy it.
- Well yeah, Bub Nelson.
- What do you want me...
- Just say it.
Say it with me, Bub Nelson.
- All right, I got it,
I got it, Bub Nelson.
- Bub Nelson.
- Bub Nelson, I got it.
- It's easy, right?
You got this, I know you do.
- All right, yeah,
I got it, okay.
- Great, all right, go again.
- Bub Nelson. It's best.
Uh, it's best shared.
- Cut.
- See, now you're,
you're all in my head.
You got me all messed up now.
I can't even do anything,
I can't concentrate.
Bub Nelson.
Uh, Bub Nelson, it's
best when shared.
- Cut.
- With someone.
I can get it right,
I just gotta...
- Yeah, c'mon...
- No, I'll, I'll go around.
- Yeah, let's just go again.
- Let's go again.
- Okay, all right.
- Bub Nelson.
It's best when shared
with someone you love,
or someone you just like
to have a good time with,
like me: Capitol recording
artist Troyal Brux.
- Okay.
It's good. Let's go again.
- Why would we go
again? That one's good.
That was, that was the best one.
- 'Cause
we're just warming up.
- That's the best
one we've done yet.
- Yeah,
yeah, no, it's good,
but you can do better. I
know you can do better.
- How much time do
you wanna waste?
Let's just waste all my time.
- It's not a matter
of wasting time.
- And let's waste
all the crew's time,
just because you don't
know how to do your job.
- I like, I like that
you care. Just relax.
- All right, look, I'm
gettin' a little upset
and I'm sorry about
that, all right?
- Okay, c'mon, let's
just do it again.
- All right
- No worries, man
C'mon, buddy, we got it.
- What was
wrong with that one?
- Well, you probably
shouldn't flip the can,
if you're gonna
crack open and drink-
- I like the flipping the can,
the flipping the can's cool.
It shows I can do the trick.
- But, it's not gonna work.
- It shows I've got talent.
It's not gonna work
if you can't drink it.
- The whole point
of you hiring me
is because I have talent.
- Naturally.
- Look how I can do it.
- Troyal, I think it's great.
Look, I can keep on flipping.
- 'Cause if it works,
you were, like...
- I flip it right every time.
I can juggle it.
- No, I, I, I, I don't...
- I can juggle the whole fuckin'
thing, how 'bout that, huh?
- I don't want that.
- I got ideas.
Let's just try again,
try again, try again.
Let's just do it all f...
- Yeah!
Bub Nelson.
It's best when shared with...
- Cut it.
- What the fuck was that?
- Boom in the shot.
- Yeah, boom in the shot.
He fucking hit me in
the god damn head.
He could have hurt somebody.
He could poke somebody's eye
out with that fuckin' thing.
- C'mon, let's
just take a sec, let's settle.
- Piss juice.
- Cut!
- Do you think Dad will be
home for Christmas this year?
- I don't know.
- Last year we weren't so lucky.
- Yeah.
- Maybe this year
will be different.
- I don't think so.
- Now, boys.
I don't wanna hear no guff
outta neither one
of you this year,
if your daddy can't
be home for Christmas.
- Yes, mama.
- He provides for us, tenfold.
Last thing we need is
to make him feel guilty.
These are his prime years,
and he needs to
make the best of it,
'cause tomorrow it
could all go away.
You understand what
I'm sayin', boys?
- Yes, mama.
- Nicholas?
- All right.
Now, come here, babies.
- Well, what do we
got goin' on here?
- Dad's home!
- Why don't you boys go
give your daddy a hug?
- I don't know what I
did to deserve this.
- Letter came for you today.
You didn't eat much.
You know, I worry about you
not eating enough, Troyal.
You got a long way to go,
and it's best to start
gettin' some good habits.
Earlier, the better.
Your mom and dad could
both die of heart failure
on the same day,
I guarantee you, it's 'cause
they weren't eatin' right.
This family's seen
enough tragedy
in the time that I've
been a part of it.
I just want you to see
your children grow up.
Is that too much to ask?
- Baby, do you know
who wrote this letter?
- Somebody named Jones.
- Oh yeah, somebody
named Jones, yeah.
Try George Jones.
- George Jones?
You mean "George
Jones" George Jones?
- The George Jones.
The greatest country and
western singer of all time.
- Well,
Troyal had said it,
but knew in his heart
that it was hyperbole.
It was unspoken
knowledge that the title
of the greatest country and
western singer of all time
belonged to none other
than one Roger Nelson,
who had written some
of the most unique
and thought-provoking
material of the genre.
The night before he was to
walk into the recording studio
for the first time
in the fall of 1976,
Roger was stabbed
by a homeless man
and died in a ditch with only
his ideas to keep him warm.
- Well, what'd he
say in the letter?
- He wants me to go see
him off in Nashville.
- See him off?
Where's he going?
- It doesn't matter
where he's going,
it matters where he's been.
- How old is he now?
- I don't know, he's
prob'ly gettin' up there.
One country legend to
another country legend,
wants me to come out there,
hang out with him.
Of course, it's this weekend.
- Oh, baby, this weekend?
The boys will want you
to play catch with them.
You know, we're all
just really glad to have
you home for a while.
- And I appreciate that,
and I appreciate this
whole Betty Crocker thing
we got going on here.
This Norman Rockwell painting.
- Oh, you do?
Oh, well that's good to know.
- Yeah, but I can come back
and, uh, play catch outside
with Nicholas and Christoff
any day of the week.
- Christopher.
- That's what I said.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
I got this locked down.
I make nothing but hit
records and baby boys.
- Mm-hmm.
Ain't that right?
- You do.
- Yes I do.
- But that's not the point.
- Baby, I idolize this man.
Do you understand that?
- I know you do.
But you know who
those boys idolize?
- Probably one of those stupid
cartoon characters they watch.
- No. Their father.
They idolize you, baby.
- Maybe I'll, uh, get 'em
a souvenir or somethin'
while I'm out in Nashville.
- Oh, I'm sure you will, baby.
- Probably something
big and extravagant.
George motherfuckin' Jones.
Hey, can I get more
vocals in my monitor?
Y'all ain't gonna guess
where I'm going this weekend.
- Where you goin', Troyal?
- Nashville, Tennessee.
- What you got goin'
on in Nashville?
- How about dinner and
drinks with a country legend?
- Waylon Jennings?
- No, not Waylon Jennings, it's
a different country legend.
- Oh is it, is it Johnny Cash?
- No, God.
It's George Jones.
- You gonna drink
with The Possum?
- Yeah, The Possum.
See, he knows what
I'm talkin' about.
- Whatever happened to him?
- I heard he drowned
in a bottle of whiskey.
- Nope, he got
clean, he's sober.
- All of a sudden, y'all know
so much about George Jones.
Anyway, yeah, he invited me out.
To Nashville, Tennessee.
For dinner and drinks, which
is an industry standard.
'Cause one legend wants to
hang out with another legend,
'cause we have the
most in common.
You guys will understand
when you're more established.
Bottom line is we're
probably gonna get drunk.
- Well, how come you
don't get drunk with us?
- I do get drunk with you guys.
I get drunk with you
guys all the time.
- You don't drink like that.
- That is
so frustrating.
I could drink any one of
y'all under the table,
except for Melvin.
- Well, you can't outdrink me.
- I'm talkin' about in like a
competition-type setting, Ray.
Like, if there's four or
five beers in front of us,
I get to number four,
you'll be at number three.
Which is more of a speed thing,
but I think they also
count for quantity.
- I think it's pretty cool.
- Oh, there goes Melvin.
The only one with any
sense in this band.
Of course, his playing
could be improved upon.
Let's hit it.
- One, two, three, four.
- Before you ask
me why I'm late,
you need to be askin' yourself
why I'm still messin' around
with these
bottom-feeder bandmates.
- They got a special here,
it's a pear-glazed pork
loin with basil droppings.
- Pear-glazed pork loin
with basil droppin's,
that's, that's what it's
come to now, hasn't it?
- Yeah, I better not
commit to the calories
this early in the afternoon.
- I'll tell you what,
I'll commit to whatever
calories they got,
as long as you're buying.
- Well, that's
protocol, isn't it?
- That's probably the
best thing we got goin' on
with this relationship.
- Here's what I got for you.
This weekend down in Dallas is
Governor Richards' birthday.
You're gonna go down
there, play a few songs,
shake a few hands, kiss a baby.
You jump back over
the Red River,
$25,000 richer.
That's take-home money.
That's in your pocket.
That's after fees.
That's after my fees.
The boys, they get
their minimum wage,
travel costs, all that.
- Well, that sounds
real tempting,
except for I'll be in Nashville,
Tennessee this weekend.
- You don't have anything
in Nashville this weekend.
- No, this ain't in the books.
See, I'm gonna be hangin' out
with a country and
western legend.
Maybe you've heard of him.
His name's George Jones?
- You're recordin'
songs with George Jones?
- No, we're not gonna
be recordin', man.
We're just gonna be hangin' out,
sitting across from each other.
Mind-meldin'.
- Like, talkin' 'bout
future projects?
- I don't know what we're
gonna be talkin' about, man.
We're just gonna be
shootin' the shit.
- Are you tellin' me
that you're willing to
throw away 25 grand,
to go have soup with a
60-year-old, washed-up
has-been possum?
- Well, you make it sound
better than it actually is,
but yeah.
Uh, I'm gonna have, uh,
American cheeseburger,
and this guy's gonna have
the pork loin pear glaze.
How about that, huh?
Thank you.
- I don't understand.
All right, this, this
isn't Hank Williams Jr.
This isn't Charley Pride.
This is a, this is an
old man that's washed up.
He's trying to get what you got.
- Look, I have been
a fan of George Jones
since I was a wee
little baby boy.
Now, this is a golden
opportunity for me,
and I'm definitely not
gonna let it pass me by
over some money.
- Well, that's why the people
love you, isn't it, Troyal?
It's that passion.
- God damn right.
- I met my hero once.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
It was in Boston
at a charity event.
Joltin' Joe DiMaggio.
- You met Joe DiMaggio
at a charity event?
- Isn't that something?
- Well, it's a small world.
- I walked up to him,
I introduced myself.
I shook his hand.
I thought that'd be
where we left off.
But no, we got to talkin',
we were havin' a good time.
Our ladies started talkin',
we're out to dinner,
and I got his number, and
I can call him right now.
- You can call Joe
DiMaggio right now?
- I can call Joe
DiMaggio right now.
Pick up the phone, I
can talk about baseball,
I can talk about the wind.
- See, that's,
that's the same thing
that's gonna happen
with me and George.
I'm gonna go out there,
we're gonna hang out.
We're gonna become best friends.
He's gonna be sending
me Christmas cards.
I'm gonna be sending
him Christmas cards.
Hell, we're gonna have
things to do with each other
that don't even revolve
around Christmas.
Shit, I'm gonna have a room
for him to stay at my house.
Man, I'm gonna have
a bunch of rooms,
for a bunch of country
and western legends.
My house is gonna be the,
like, the United Nations
for country and western legends.
- Wouldn't get 'em all
booked at the same time.
You know, you keep talkin'
about what you wanna do,
and hope somethin' will happen,
and you don't do it
and it won't happen.
- Well, that's a nice sentiment.
Except for in this
case, it doesn't work.
'Cause I am makin' it happen.
- Well, that's a Joe
DiMaggio quote, Troyal.
- Well, it's a good quote.
- Y'know, the first time a
reporter asked Joe DiMaggio
for a quote,
he thought it was a soda pop.
Isn't that funny?
- Kind of slow, then, isn't he?
- Well, he's not slow, he's,
he's a center fielder.
And, you know, he,
he was a rookie.
I'd like to see
your rookie card.
- My rookie card? Shit,
it'd be filled with stats.
The whole back side, just
nothin' but stats, printin'...
- Whole lot of strikeouts.
- Numbers. Well...
- They might let
you play first base.
- Baby?
- Yeah, baby?
- Why do you think George
Jones wrote me that letter?
- 'Cause he wants to
spend time with you.
Everyone does.
- There's not enough time
in the world for that.
But that, that doesn't
sit right with me.
I mean, he's an icon.
And I'm bound to be an icon.
If he's on his victory lap,
I'm, I'm on the home stretch.
- Yeah, you're on
your way, baby.
- Maybe he feels a
connection to my music,
the way I felt a connection
to his growing up.
- Yeah, baby.
- Maybe it's one great
artist reachin' out
to another great artist so
he doesn't feel so lonely.
I know what that's like, hell.
- Good night, baby.
I love you.
- Good night.
- Troyal?
- Yeah.
- I feel like we're losing you.
- Why would you say that?
- Dear Troyal,
I'm writin' to
you today in hopes
you're doin' well and
your family is thriving.
I watched your special
the other night on TV
and I have to admit, it left
quite an impression on me.
I was touched by your
words and appreciate them
more than you know.
You seem to be well on your way
to becoming a country
superstar yourself.
I would like to invite
you back to Nashville
next weekend if you are free.
I'm taking a very
extended vacation soon
and it would be an honor if
I could meet you before I go.
I understand if you're
too busy to accept.
Best, George Jones.
- Welcome to Nashville.
- Howdy doody.
They got me here a reservation
right here for Travis Wiley.
- Travis Wiley, let me see.
- That's kind a stupid name
and I didn't come up with it.
You might wanna check who
made that reservation.
- Capitol Records?
Are you a musician?
- Guilty as charged.
I'm actually a pretty
good musician. You
like country music?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well then, you might
recognize this face.
You might recognize
this shake. Huh?
- Mmm.
- I'm Troyal Brux.
- Oh my God!
Oh. Sorry.
- Shh.
Okay, listen, this is of
utmost importance, all right?
Now, I'm here for
Nashville, one night,
one night only.
I wanna be treated
just like normal folk.
Just like I was
just a normal guy
that came in here
and booked a room.
Travis Wiley. That's
why I go by that name.
That's, that's what's
called an alias.
- Of course.
We'll take real good
fuckin' care of you.
- You are a live one.
- Bullseye!
- But no, I, I do
appreciate that.
And that's why I like to
stay at this nice hotel.
This is a, this is a
real nice establishment,
and uh, you guys
are all real nice.
You treat me real well.
- Here's your key card.
It's room 1615,
and if there's anything
you need, you let me know.
- You bet I will.
- Enjoy your stay!
- Thank you.
Oh, hey, well there he is.
Head honcho, you're the
big man of security, huh?
- Hm. That's me.
- You wanna walk me to my room?
- Sure.
Now, I don't know if they
talked to you downstairs
about who I am or what
I'm doing here today.
- Oh man, I know who you are.
- Oh yeah? I didn't picture
you to be a country music fan.
- I mean,
I wouldn't say that.
We went to Stillwater together.
From '82 to '85.
- You went to Stillwater
from '82 to '85?
- Yes, sir. Played football.
- Small world. I mean,
what was the number
on your jersey?
- 31.
- 31. Well.
Was a good team those years.
- Yeah.
- Same year as I went, y'know?
Yeah.
- Well, what you doin'
here in Nashville?
- Man, just workin' in a hotel.
- That's as good a living
as any, I guess.
- You played the guitar?
- Yeah, I'd say it worked out
pretty well for me, too, huh?
What do you think?
- What can I help
you with tonight?
- Well, as you know,
I'm stayin' in this
room right here tonight.
Now, paparazzi catches wind
to this or some crazy fans
and it's gonna be hard for
a fellow to get some sleep,
you know what I'm saying?
- Sure.
- Now I need you to keep
an extra special eye
on this door right here.
Can you do that for me?
- Yes, sir.
I got you covered.
I'll guard it with my life.
- Stillwater
alumni. That's,
that's really somethin'.
- All right.
- 'Preciate it.
- It's George.
Leave a message.
- Hey, George.
It's, uh, it's Troyal.
I just, just got
here in Nashville.
I'm at the Himbassy Suite,
or the Embassy Suites.
Almost said Hilton.
Uh, it's, it's pretty cool, man.
It's kind of themed out.
They got, uh, old
concert posters.
They got a Waylon Jennings.
I'm looking at a, a Johnny
Cash poster over there.
I bet there's a,
bet there's a George
Jones poster somewhere.
I just, uh, haven't really
done much investigating as I,
as I said, I just got,
just got into town,
so, um, I guess you could
give me a call back.
Uh, you could call,
er, let me see.
I don't, I don't have a
number here, but I can,
well, let me, how can I do this?
I'll put the phone
down or, hold on.
All right. It's, uh, 1615,
that's the room number.
So, uh, 1615,
you call the front desk
at the, uh, Embassy Suites
and that's, uh, they'll
get you to 1615.
That'll be the,
that's my room number.
Uh...
Tell you what I'm gettin'
pretty, pretty inspired here.
This is, uh, this,
it's really something.
- Damn,
cocksuckin'...
- Hello?
- Clint?
- Yeah. This, this is Troyal.
- Meet me at
the Paddock Club in 15.
- Ha, I, yes, sir. Yep.
I'll, I, I can be there,
I can be there real quick.
I'll be there, just gotta...
Uh, hello?
Hello?
All right.
There he is.
Hey, I'm, it's me, Troyal.
Nah, he knows, he's
gonna meet me there.
Uh, say, don't you owe
me a couple of bucks?
Or, say, say, don't
you owe me a five-spot?
Or a cool, a cool spot? Or.
Stupid.
Hey, good-lookin'!
No, that's,
that's queer.
Hey, did, didn't I read about
you in the funny pa, yeah.
Hey, didn't I read about you
in the funny papers? All right.
- Here you are, sir.
- Thank you.
- Mr. Jones.
- Mmm. Howdy.
Have a seat.
How was your flight?
- Well, I'll let you
be the judge of that
when I tell you I
flew private, so...
- That's nice.
I hadn't left East Texas for
several years 'til last week,
and kind of forgotten
how nice it was.
- Well, I count my blessings
every day for my success.
- Do ya?
- Yeah, of course.
- Yeah, that's
right. Good ol' boy.
That's what you're
into, isn't it?
- Uh, yes, sir. I'm just a
Oklahoma boy done good, y'know?
My state's proud of me,
I'm proud of myself.
And my success is,
of course, you gotta
understand what that's like.
I mean, you gotta be
proud of yourself.
- Oh, I don't know that pride
has very much to do with it.
I've lived a long life, son.
There's been a lot
of ebb and flow.
I don't have too much pride
in my own accomplishments.
It's, I find I have pride in
other people's accomplishments.
You know, like, like you or
somethin', and not myself.
- I gotta say, Mr. Jones,
it's sittin' across from you,
you know, a country
legend like you, and,
it's pretty surreal.
Then you telling me
that you're proud of me,
that makes me feel really good.
- No. No, no, no.
I was just using
you as an example
in the sentence of
something to be proud of
that was not myself.
No. I don't know
if I could be proud
of your accomplishments anyway.
They're a little bit too much
like my own accomplishments.
Now, that'd be kinda like
arrogance, wouldn't it?
And, uh, that's not
very good ol' boy.
You get what I'm sayin'?
- Yeah, I think I smell
what you're stepping in.
- Yeah. I, I'm hungry.
Wanna go ahead and order?
- Sure.
- Waiter.
Let's skip the appetizers
and go straight to the main
course, that okay with you?
- Hey, it's your world,
man. I'm just livin' in it.
I'm gonna have whatever
Mr. Jones is havin'.
- I want the filet. Rare.
Baked potato.
- Yes, sir.
- And I'd like to amend
my last statement.
I would like exactly
what Mr. Jones is havin',
except for I'd like my
steak cooked well-done.
- Hmm. You really are
from Oklahoma, aren't you?
- I believe I am. Yeah.
- Well-done, huh?
- Yes sir, I like the
cow, uh, good and dead.
- You're
really into this
good ol' boy act, aren't you?
- Well, I mean, you put a
nice steak in front of me
or a chicken-fried steak,
I'm gonna go with the
chicken-fried every time.
That's just, that's
just how I roll.
- Yeah, but you cook the
flavor right out of it.
- I, I don't like the blood.
- The blood's where
the flavor is, son.
You know, you've
insulted the chef, right?
- How'd I do that?
- I mean, a chef will
cook a well-done steak,
but they do so begrudgingly.
And, see,
the chef will pull the
order for a well-done steak
and balk at it with the
rest of the kitchen staff.
At first, they'll, they'll
be angry as a mongoose,
but that'll turn to outright
mockery at the guest's expense.
And that means you, Troyal.
- Oh, damn.
- So they move that
soon-to-be-forsaken meat to
the hottest part of the grill,
trying to, you
know, push it along,
cursing all the while.
Then, it becomes a race
to see how many real
steaks they can cook
in the ungodly amount
of time it takes to cook
that one bastard child.
- Well, how long does it
take to cook your steak?
- Eh, two, maybe three minutes.
- Oh, yeah. Damn.
I, I can't do that.
- So just before
your steak is burned up
into a sick little lump of char,
mine will delicately and
ever so graciously emerge
as a culinary masterpiece.
Tender, juicy, and rich,
that, most of all, remains
in its God-given pure form.
- Why don't you just eat it raw?
- Well, a few minutes on the
grill is what separates us
from the animals.
- Well, I never thought about
it like that, Mr. Jones.
- Ah, well.
Oh, I'm sorry. There's the
wine, have yourself a pour.
- Don't mind if I do.
- It's a seven-year-old P & V.
It's pourin' pretty
good right now.
- Mm.
Yeah, that's, that's nice.
That's real interesting.
You know, I like to
drink. I drink a lot,
you know, beer or whiskey
or wine, you know,
whatever you put
in front of me, I,
some would say I have a problem.
Drinkin' problem, like
you, well, not like you.
Wait here, hold on.
I got something for you.
- Oh. What are you
gonna do next, boy?
Get down on one knee?
- No, these are,
these are cuff links.
They're belonged to
Hank Williams. Senior.
- Well, hell yes,
Hank Williams Senior.
Ah.
Son, maybe you, uh, maybe
you better hold onto those.
- No, I got 'em
for you, Mr. Jones.
- Oh, that's very thoughtful.
But I really, I really
can't accept 'em.
Listen. Listen, Troyal.
I know I was kind of vague
in my letter about my trip
and I'm sorry, but
I meant to do that.
It's just not somethin'
that I want broadcast.
- Well, you can
trust me, Mr. Jones.
You can, you can certainly
trust me with a secret.
- Well, uh, for starters, I'm
on the outs with Bev again.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- That kind, patient,
life-savin' woman
has finally kicked me out.
And, uh, as far
as the trip goes,
you ever heard of cryonics?
- I don't think so.
- It has to do with the freezing
and storage of a human corpse.
The idea is that resurrection
might be scientifically
possible at some later date.
- Like Walt Disney.
- Exactly like Walt Disney.
Troyal,
I'm sick.
It's my heart.
- I didn't know that.
- Yeah, some days it's okay.
And then, other days
it's not so good.
- So you're thinking
about getting frozen?
- I've done all the thinkin'.
I'm goin' in tomorrow morning.
- Well, what if
somethin' goes wrong?
What if you die?
- Everything's a risk, ain't it?
I mean, I'm just tired
of living on my past.
On my last night on Earth,
I wanted to see what
the future looks like.
And, for better or worse,
I believe that that is you.
- So you're sayin', it's your
last night on planet Earth,
and you wanna spend it with me?
- Well, I hadn't actually
put a lot of thought into it,
but yeah.
- Well, God dog.
That's wild, man. Cheers!
- Rare.
And very well-done.
- Uh, listen, real, real quick,
I just wanna say
I'm really sorry.
I did not mean to disrespect you
by asking for a well-done steak.
- I don't know what
you're talking about.
♪ Sodom and Gomorrah
wouldn't seem so bad ♪
♪ Debbie, you know, I'm tryin' ♪
- Hey, P-Wee, slow
night tonight?
- Seems to be the case.
- I was hopin' it would
be. How are you, friend?
- Doin' good, thank you.
- Got a buddy with me tonight.
You recognize him at all?
- I can't say that I do.
- Take that.
That's what I like
about you, P-Wee.
You're a classic and
you always will be.
- Only way God
made me, thank you.
- Well, god damn.
I thought I'd see you here.
- George.
How are ya?
- I'm fairly well.
- Didn't I read about
you in the funny papers?
- Troyal, I
want you to meet Juno.
Juno is a very
talented individual.
- You a musician?
- Hell, Troyal, it's Nashville.
Everybody down
here's a musician.
No, Juno's not much
of a piano player.
But he does have other talents
that prove to be very useful.
Won't you join us at our table?
- I'm ready to go
back to the hotel.
- But this is
where the country stars
come to write their
drinking songs.
- I don't see any country stars.
All I see are a
bunch of lowlifes.
I'm gonna go and start the car.
- No, just
give it a few minutes.
Have another beer.
- I don't want another beer.
I want to be clearheaded.
- Well then, go get some
pretzels at the bar. Whatever.
Let's stay a few minutes.
- Man, it is a bad place to
work for a recovering alcoholic.
I will tell you that much.
- They tell me that my
ass was coverin' the drain
so no water would go down it.
I was just lucky
that the suction
from the drain didn't gut me.
I was luckier still that
my road manager found me
just as I was gettin'
ready to turn blue.
- So, so you missed the show?
- I sure did. And I felt
really bad about it.
Back in those days, people
would drive hundreds of miles
from these little farm towns
to come see the, the shows,
and, and I'd do some
stupid shit like that.
The promoter had to give
'em, uh, a, a voucher?
For some future show.
I don't know, but the fans
still had faith in me, though.
Even to this day, I
don't understand why.
You know, I,
I would apologize to every
single one of them if I could.
I was a mess back
in those days. Heh!
- Well, shoot, I'm just,
I'm glad you're still alive.
- Well, it's not from lack
of trying to not be.
You know, I won all the awards.
I'm not braggin'.
I won 'em. I know
you won a bunch, too.
But a lot of those are ones
that just got made up
in the last year or two.
And that's just, like, the
Country Music Association,
television, whatever.
George Strait.
Straight! My ass!
Anyways, it's easier
to win an award
that just got made
up in the last year.
'Cause you just have to
show 'em somethin' new.
I mean, no offense,
it's like country
music dressin' up.
Or dressin' down, maybe.
Tryin' to be something that
it ain't and never will be.
Rock and roll.
- I like CCR.
- Now see there's a, CCR.
That's, that's a good band.
- Well, see?
Now, that there is the reason
that I don't got no friends!
That's just the way I like it.
'Cause I'd just turn around
and stab a knife in your back
some time when you
weren't lookin'.
Ain't that right, Juno?
- That's right, George.
- You son of a bitch.
But I like it like that.
You know, there's, there's
true things that are terrible
and there are terrible
things that are true.
I, I'mma tell you another story.
This is a true story
and I have never told a
living soul about this.
It was about one time
when I was in a tight
spot with the mob.
I was up in New York City,
which was probably my
first mistake.
- I don't know how
to describe this guy.
He's either a spic, Rican,
wetback, ahh, Spaniard.
He's a Mexican.
- Well, what, what does this,
uh, Mexican do for a livin'?
- He
sells drugs to children
and their mothers, his
own fuckin' neighborhood.
And with them, it's always,
he wants to kill this.
He wants to do that.
Whores up the kazoo.
- We need to put some poison
down this motherfucker's throat.
- That's right. That's right.
- Uh, alright.
Uh, but uh, what's
this got to do with me?
I mean, uh, uh, what do
you want me to do about it?
- We think you can help us.
- Now, look, you owe us
quite a bit of money.
Hey, Marty, how much is it?
- 30 big one. That's
lots of money.
What the...
- 30,000 dollars?
- I know.
I think we're crossin'
some lines here.
I'm a country singer.
I'm not a, uh, whatever
it is you think I am.
- You're nothin' but
a damn degenerate.
- Okay. But I am not a killer.
- Yeah? What'd you do
in, uh, Korea? KP duty?
- What's it gonna be?
- They had me by the balls.
I didn't have anyone
I could turn to.
Not to mention I was
dead broke at the time.
- So you
went through with it?
- What choice did I have?
- You killed a man.
- I'm not saying
I'm proud of it,
but it was him or me,
so, yeah, I done it.
I snuck in there when he was
making it with his woman.
- Sounds like somethin' that'd
be hard to keep to yourself.
Somethin' that would
eat you up inside.
- You work it out with
your music, with your art.
That's how you blow
the dust off your soul
when the world crashes
in on top of you
and tries to bury your ass.
That's how you crazy glue
the pieces back together
after somebody's
ripped your heart out
and stomped all over it.
It's why God
made us artists.
Everyone. It doesn't matter
if you are number one,
or number one million in one.
Everybody is an artist.
I believe that.
- My wife sings in the
choir every Sunday.
- Well, mine too.
- I believe in Him.
- Everybody
is an artist.
- I do too. What's your point?
- I would like brandy.
- Everybody
is an artist.
- And he will have
a glass of beer.
- Everybody
is an artist.
- It's showtime, motherfuckers.
- What about
me? Am I an artist?
- Oh, you are an artist.
I'm sure as shit you're an
artist. You're the most...
- You know, Connie
here, she's a singer.
Maybe y'all can do
a duet together.
- Oh, you're a singer?
- Yeah. Been
singing all my life,
but ain't nobody found me yet.
- So it, it's Connie. And...
- Donna.
- And that is Sueleen.
Sign of the times.
- Howdy, y'all.
- Matched trio.
Thank the Lord for
numerical coincidences.
- Troyal, you gonna
sing us a song tonight?
- Uh, hadn't planned on it,
but how 'bout a autograph?
I could do, I could do
an autograph for you.
- I think
I'd like that.
- It's like
my daddy taught me.
The world will not
let you scream,
so you better learn to sing.
- That's beautiful.
- And he underlined
the point by making me
sing on command or he'd
beat the shit outta me.
- Oh, you poor baby.
Did he beat you horrible?
- Oh, Miss Donna?
He beat me horrible.
- Oh.
- Oh, I'll, I'll pass on that.
I'll go ahead and, just...
- Come on, Troyal.
We're tryin' to have
a celebration here.
- Yeah, come on.
Don't be a sourpuss.
- Oh, no, no, no, see,
I don't, I don't, uh,
I don't mess with this.
This isn't one of my favorite.
This is, like a light beer?
Like, I can do light beer.
I can drink plenty of those.
- Now, I have
seen you up on stage,
grinnin' like an
Oklahoma jackpot.
- Ugh! Come on, Juno!
You're gonna act like a fool,
people are gonna
treat you like a fool.
You got this.
Let's go.
- Mmm.
Beans.
All right.
Oh.
Beans, two nights in a row.
Hey, that ain't bad, huh, Ma?
Uh, let's get you a scoop here,
and a scoop for me over here.
- You bet.
- Hey, Ma, guess what?
I went to P-Wee's old
place right after work.
Ran into Trey.
We get to playing
a round o' pool
and get to talkin'
about the Memphis game.
About halfway through the
conversation, I realize,
wait a minute, Trey
doesn't own a TV.
That's when he tells me
that he installed an antenna
on his roof last week.
I told him about your situation.
Trey is volunteering
to install the antenna
on your roof next week.
How does that sound?
- Sounds great, but
I've already got Jack.
- Who's Jack?
- Jack Kennedy. He does
a sound booth at church.
You know Jack Kennedy.
- Oh, the sound guy.
Yeah, he's a good man.
He's gonna come by?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, wh, what day,
I gotta tell Trey this.
- He'll have to come on a Sunday
because he works
the other six days.
- Just let me know
when he comes by, okay?
I wanna be here for that.
- Okay.
- I know how you get, you
wanna be very helpful.
You want to help out and you
end up straining something.
So, let me be that person to
strain something, all right?
- You'll just be in the way.
- I understand that. I just
wanna help you, all right?
I just wanna help you.
- You'll
be in the way.
- End o' discussion. I
just wanna help ya, Ma.
- He's full up. He's got enough.
- I just want to
help ya. That's it.
That's all. I just
want to help you.
- You'll be in the way.
You understand?
You'll be in the way.
- I would be in the
way, wouldn't I?
I always
seem to be in the way.
- I'm...
- Sorry, you'll be in the way.
- I'm always in
the way, aren't I?
- Takes all kind
to make the world, I guess.
- You'll have to
excuse me for a minute.
- Now, what's the
chance of those two,
havin' a drink, bein'
together in this bar?
- That's the whole
point, knucklehead.
They come here for this
reason. All, all the stars.
- Well, it ain't them.
- I'm gonna go get a picture..
- God damn it, Ethel,
you're gonna embarrass me.
Sit your ass down.
- But you know
who those boys idolize?
- Dad's home!
- Their father.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize there
was someone else in here.
- Anyone can be in here
as far as I'm concerned.
It's 1994.
And you know what that means?
In six years,
all these noisy machines
are gonna shut down,
and all of this
is gonna cease to exist.
- Okay?
- What's the matter?
You seem upset.
- I'm not upset.
- You say so.
You need to trust that
home is what you make it.
And you can be anyone
you want to be,
this time around.
- Troyal, Troyal, Troyal.
What would you say to a night
with a real country girl?
- I'm married.
- Of course.
All the best ones are.
- You mind if I use the phone?
- Is it gonna be a local call?
- Actually no, I'm
callin' home. Here.
I'll give you $10.
How'd that be?
- Been a lot of counterfeitin'
going on around here.
Looks legitimate, though.
I'll give you a minute.
- Thank you.
How you doin'?
- I feel like
we're losin' you.
- Thanks.
- Certainly, certainly.
- Share and share alike.
- Hey, ladies, get
that over here.
- Oh, yeah?
- Oh, we're gonna
have a party now.
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
- Ooh!
- Oh, no, no, ma'am, ma'am.
No, you, you, you can't,
you can't have a picture.
- Well, well, it's my camera.
- Just hold on a minute, sonny.
- I can take all
the photos I want.
- You're gonna have to
give me that camera.
- Oh no, I will not, I can...
- Here, let, I'm gonna
give you, I got some money.
I will give.
- It's not for sale.
- I'll give you 300 dollars.
- It's worth a lot
more than that.
- Bud. Why don't you pick
on somebody your own size.
- Those pictures, are
personal property of ours.
- Okay, this is just a
big misunderstanding.
And they just happen
to have something that
doesn't belong to them.
- Listen.
- I don't know who you
guys think you are,
with your loud shirts
and your loud talk
and all the drug use,
but this is my bar.
I own this bar. And
you ain't Nashville.
- P-Wee, hang on now.
We're, we're gonna
get this calmed down.
Just a misunderstanding.
- George, I love you,
but you've been wearin' on
me for like 10 days straight.
Ya ain't Nashville either, man.
- Now, hold on, god damn it.
- God damn it, P-Wee,
ya piece of shit.
Fuck you, P-Wee.
- Okay.
- Okay, here's
what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna go ahead
and take this.
- Oh! No!
Oh!
- Ladies,
that is our cue.
- I'm gonna go ahead
and give you this,
and I want you all to
have a really nice night.
- Oh.
- Keep buying the records.
- George.
Don't come back for at least
a week. You understand?
- Oo-wee!
- Not bad for an old guy, huh?
- What, you mean to tell
me we ain't the same age?
This night's just
nearly perfect.
I bet you can hear the
coyotes howlin' out here, huh?
- Yeah, there's more
scavengers every year.
- It's a damn beautiful
world, though.
You sure you don't feel
like stickin' around?
♪ Let me introduce to you ♪
♪ A woman with a dream ♪
- You're awful mopey tonight.
- I was just thinkin', is all.
- 'Bout what?
- 'Bout somethin' I lost.
Long time ago.
- I'm listenin'.
- I was thinking about
life and, and time.
And how weeks turn
into months and,
and months turn into years.
And before you know it, your,
your kids are all grown up
and, and you're old and wrinkly,
and everyone's
forgotten about you.
I'm sorry I was impolite
at the bar earlier.
I, I know I get like that
sometimes and I don't...
- Oh, no.
Sorry if I was.
- I was just really lookin'
forward to this trip.
Y'know, I was really
lookin' forward
to meeting my hero George Jones.
Now that I've met him, I'll,
I'll never get to see him again.
If all this cryogenics
talk is true,
which I mean at this
point, who's to say?
Y'know, you can hear
it in his songs,
but comin' face
to face with him.
That's, that's when you
really realize that,
that he's in, in pain.
- You do know that George
Jones is a piece of shit.
- Well, we're gonna have to
agree to disagree on that one.
I think George
Jones is a genius.
- Was a genius.
Now he ain't nothin' but
a washed-up degenerate.
Cryonics. Hell.
He ain't Walt Disney.
And he ain't half the
songwriter you're gonna be.
- I appreciate that, but...
- But nothing.
Appreciate what you
got and shut up.
Most people got nothin' like it.
You have no idea what all
you could have, do you?
I can do things for you, Troyal.
Things you couldn't
even dream of.
Boo!
- You all right, man?
- Imagine seeing yourself
as a different self,
living a different life,
but a life not so
different from your own.
We're talking about
alternate dimensions here.
You know, standing upon
the precipice of reality,
gazing upon a horizonless
valley of infinite cells.
Each one with its own opinion,
thought, passion, desire.
Y'know, once you're
able to glean
on this notion of
alternate timelines,
then you'll begin to
understand what it was like
for Spock to be born and
raised in a Vulcan society.
But, to put a finer point on it,
you finally understand
the leadership qualities
that it takes to captain
a Starship Enterprise.
Qualities like, uh, like
Captain Tiberius Kirk had,
or Jean-Luc Picard.
Shooting star.
You know, captains who actually
had a Vulcan mind-meld.
- Sounds like a good show.
- Oh man, yeah.
And the Vulcan mind-meld?
We're not just talking
about some fuckin', uh,
Freaky Friday situation.
We're talking about the
entire thing. Right?
Head to toe, from the
beginning nerve end
to the next, to the end.
We're talkin' about, Deni.
Oh my God, fuckin'
Denise, uh, Denise Crosby?
The fact that she went
back to those studio execs
and told her that she wanted
to reprise the role of, uh,
Tasha, of, uh, fuckin' Tasha.
Uh, fuckin', uh, Tasha Yar
on the Starship Enterprise.
I mean, the fuckin'
balls on that woman.
I mean, the fact that she
played a Romulan consort,
but also played her
own fuckin' daughter?
Fuckin' wild, man.
- I'll bet you ladies are
licensed massage therapists.
- Now, how
did you know that?
- Just a hunch.
- Troyal, have you
ever had a massage?
- Nah, I don't,
I don't think so.
- It'll change
your life, brother.
- Connie?
We should definitely
give Troyal a massage.
- How 'bout it, Troyal?
You want a massage?
- You're a star,
son. You deserve it.
Why don't you show these ladies
your fancy Nashville
hotel suite?
- Fuck it.
- So, basically.
Uh, Dr. Hammond,
uh, and he's cloning dinosaurs
on this island, right?
- This one feels real nice,
but tight in the
neck and shoulders.
- Dinosaurs.
- This one skin's
all loose like,
but his muscles?
- But that's the
whole point of the movie.
- Sure are hard.
- Like leather.
- Nah.
Like velvet.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, yeah!
The ones with all the
cute boys on the front.
- Oh yeah, who's cool now?
JTT?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I know about JTT!
You impressed?
- This is it, isn't
it? The lap of luxury.
- I mean, I guess
it's all right,
if this is what you're into.
- It's nights like this that
I am really going to miss
when I am not in this world.
- What happens if you get out
and everything's different?
- The skies could fall and
the rivers turn to blood,
but there will always
be country music!
- Yeah, but,
what if, what if everybody
just forgot about you?
- No, nobody forgets
a true artist.
They forget the, the
theatrics and the,
the glitz and the glamour.
They forget the sizzle, but
they still hunger for the steak.
And nobody cares about music
that's got no substance,
songs without a soul.
- I know you ain't talkin'
'bout my music, Mr. Jones,
'cause top of the pops,
man, my shit is legit.
- No, I wasn't
talkin' about you.
Although, I don't really know.
I've never heard
any of your tunes.
- Whattya mean, you ain't never
heard any of my tunes, man?
I thought you were a fan!
Shit, I've heard all your songs.
- Ah, I just don't listen
to much music anymore.
- That's just downright
disrespectful, man.
- Well.
Why don't you sing me something?
- Just right now, with no music?
- No, there's no better time.
I am all ears.
- All right, I can
sing somethin'.
♪ Well, I've had my
share of heartaches ♪
♪ I've lived a life of regret ♪
♪ Sadness is my middle name ♪
♪ Happiness, I couldn't get ♪
♪ Yeah, it's been a
long windin' road ♪
♪ I've traveled
through the day ♪
♪ Pop a cold one with the boys ♪
♪ and wash it all away ♪
♪ Just when you think ♪
♪ there's no end to this pain ♪
♪ God tells you to saddle up ♪
♪ And ride that horse again ♪
Anyways, that's.
What the hell are you doin'?
- What the fuck does it look
like I'm doin', peckerwood?
- Okay. All right! That's it!
- Baby, baby, you just sit back
and let me take care of you.
- No, no.
Party's over. Everybody's out.
Party's over!
- God damn it!
- You need to lighten up!
- You need to learn to relax.
- No, honey, it's okay.
No, I think it's plain as day.
This one don't like women.
Come on, girls.
- That's a bunch of bullshit.
- Fantastic. That, that
means you, come on, get up.
- Oh, shit. George, listen,
uh, we weren't
expecting any of this.
Uh,
ya got any singles, fives,
uh, anything for cab fare?
- I ain't got nothin'
but big bills.
- God damn it! Is anything
gonna go right today?
Well, I just don't
know what to do.
- Here, take that. $20.
- Troyal, you're a good man.
I'm gonna get you back.
- Nope, I don't need
to be gotten back.
Just, just leave.
- No. George will tell
you, I'm good for it.
George, tell him.
- Well, yeah.
- Okay. Just go.
- I think we're sayin' the
same thing is all I'm sayin'.
George, take care.
- Leave.
- Finally. I
thought they'd never leave.
- You just don't
get it, Mr. Jones.
I mean, you're
like a hero to me.
You invite me up
here to Nashville,
to be my friend.
I mean, that means
the world to me.
You've been an
inspiration to me.
inspiration to everyone.
But now I see you're,
you're just bullshit.
- I'm not bullshit.
You're bullshit.
- At least I'm not a liar.
- Your whole life is a lie.
- How's my life a lie?
- You're lying to yourself.
You're a god damn star and
you can do anything you want.
And you got yourself fenced
in this little tiny pod
like some pussy-ass coward.
- I'm not a coward, Mr.
Jones. You know what I am?
I'm a loyal, faithful,
good ol' boy.
Big star. What's
that gotten you?
It ain't enough!
- It's never enough.
It's never ever enough.
And who cares if it's
truth or lies?
The truth is just a last
resort anyway.
It doesn't even
really exist anymore.
Not now, especially.
Just some bullshit story
somebody told once,
and it doesn't even matter who.
Does that offend
your sensibilities?
Does that disrupt
your conscience?
Me, I ain't got a conscience.
I, I, I'm just a pipe for
fluids to pass through.
You put your heart and
your soul into your music,
and, and, people just want to,
they just want to gobble ya
up, they just want to eat it.
They eat the shit outta
your godforsaken soul!
Everybody loves the music!
And all the time they're just
tellin' you they're hungry.
More! More!
And they crowd around you.
And it's re, record
label people and,
and, and journalists
and, and managers
and this constant
stream o' women.
And they're all sayin'
more, more, more!
And, shit!
What, what kind of
a songwriter am I
when I can't even
stand my own songs?
It's god damn torture!
I'd rather have a boilin'
case of hemorrhoids
than write a song.
I thought my music could
make people better.
Nobody needs me anymore.
After tomorrow, they have to
find somebody else to devour.
And try to change people
but they, they changed me
into their image.
Ah!
The future used to be tomorrow,
and now it's today and,
and, nobody's ready.
And no one wants
to know anything!
They just wanna, to, to feed
like hogs at the trough.
- Why don't you just
get frozen then?
Maybe you'll live
a hundred years.
- Yeah, why not forever?
I could be the
wandering minstrel!
What the hell do
you know, anyway?
You, you gimme back those
Hank Williams cuff links.
You don't deserve 'em
I knew the man, god damn it,
he'd be spinning in his
grave thinking of you.
- Well, that's not really
that big of a dis, George.
'Cause I got 'em for you anyway.
- It is Mr. Jones to you.
You don't get to
talk to me like that
and then pretend
that you're my pal,
my, my
equal.
That song you sang was
just damn terrible, boy.
- Well, first off, there was
no musical accompaniment.
And secondly, I'm not
even finished writing it.
- Well, don't bother. It's shit.
- You take that back.
- Oh yeah?
Fuck you.
- Fuck you.
- Fuck you!
This is not how I wanted
to spend my last night.
- You think this is how I
want to spend any night?
- Now you're gonna tell
me I have to leave.
- Well, yeah, I do think it'd
be a good idea if you left.
- Just hang me out to
dry like everybody else.
See if I care.
- Jesus.
- You haven't learned
what it's like yet,
being up in that spotlight.
You think they can see you,
but they can't really see you.
It's so cold up there, it's
like you're walking on the moon.
- I mean, yeah, I
understand. It gets lonely.
- Ah. After tomorrow,
you won't have to worry
about seein' me around anymore.
- What do you want
from me, Mr. Jones?
- I envy you.
- You, oh, you envy me.
- I gotta spell it out for you?
- What do you mean you envy me?
- You got everything
in front of you.
You got your, your whole life,
and your whole career,
and all these
opportunities to make
great things for yourself
and I see you doin' it.
And, and I wish it was me again,
knowin' what I
know now.
Make better choices
and not fuck things up.
Put my head better on my
shoulders like I see you doin'.
That's why I'm gonna
freeze myself tomorrow,
'cause then hopefully
I can come back,
and make a strong
finish in, you know,
twenty or fifty
or a hundred years
when all the people that I've
harmed are dead or moved on.
That, and I need the rest.
- Look, look, George. You don't
need to get frozen for that.
You just need to get therapy,
rehab, somethin', shit.
Get clean, man. I'll pay for it.
- No, it's over for me.
I'm just a tired, sick, old man.
- It's not over for you.
It's not over for
anyone until it's over,
and it ain't over yet.
- Oh, God. Who's that?
Are you expecting someone?
- That's probably
your friend Juno.
- I don't want to see him.
- I'll tell him to get lost.
- Evening, Mr. Brux.
- How are ya?
- How's that quiet
evening going for you?
- Not as quiet as I'd hoped.
- Hmm. People fighting in there?
- Had, had some people
over, but, you know,
they're, they're
not here anymore.
- Just we've had some complaints
about some shouting, so...
- Yeah, like I said, they're,
they're long gone at this point,
so nothin' to worry about.
- How 'bout that old man
that came in after you?
He seemed a little
messed up on the way in.
- You know, we had some
beers out in the town,
but that's perfectly legal
in the state of Nashville.
From what I understand.
I haven't read every law book.
- Let me ask you somethin'.
You gonna break any more
shit in your hotel room?
- I'm really sorry about that.
Here, let me,
let me give you a
little somethin'.
No, no, no.
- It's fine.
- You know, I never
really got your name.
- I imagine that comes
with the territory.
- I'd sure like to know it.
- Let's just say I'm
somebody you used to know.
You have a good
evening, Mr. Brux.
- You've been a good
friend to me, Troyal.
- I believe every man
has a path to redemption.
- Mm.
Did I ever tell
you about that time
I did undercover
work with the FBI?
- I don't think I
heard that one yet.
- It's good. I can
hear everything.
- All right, George.
Remember, if you feel
like you're in any danger,
you use the code word.
You remember the
code word, right?
- Of course.
- I know this ain't easy,
but you're doing it
for your country.
It's the price of freedom.
- Let's get it over with
'fore I change my mind.
- Hm.
- All right.
All right, let's rock and roll.
So, Mr. Jones,
I cannot tell you
how pleased I am
that you've taken an
interest in our movement.
Someone of your stature.
Someone all of America
loves and respects,
young and old alike!
Oh, I want you to meet Luiz.
Luiz, do you have a moment
to meet a country
and western legend?
- Oh, yes.
- I thought so.
Mr. Jones, this is Luiz.
- Mr. Jones,
I love the country music.
Thank you for opening your heart
to the suffering of my people.
- Thank you, Luiz.
So, luckily, we were
able to get Luiz
and most of his family
out of the country,
but sadly, many of
his relatives remain.
The actions of
this administration
contributing to violence over
there have been deplorable,
to say the least.
It's a story that must be told.
And hopefully with your help,
we can bring this
abomination to the attention
of the American people
and stop this madness.
That's where you come in.
So, as most people know,
our current president has a
certain cowboy sensibility.
I'm told that he
adores your music
and admires you very much.
Our sources tell us he would
very much enjoy meeting,
as well as a photo op with you.
And then, about a
week after that,
we're hoping you
would make a statement
against American-sanctioned
violence
throughout Latin America.
People would listen
to you, Mr. Jones,
and you could help
turn the tide.
We most certainly believe
they would listen, Mr. Jones.
Your influence is considerable.
Now, if you agree to this,
we have a congressional
contact that could assist you
in getting a meeting
with President Reagan.
After you meet with him,
we would time the release
of certain CIA documents
we've managed to obtain
to the New York Times
and other press outlets.
Now, we expect a certain
amount of public outcry
in wake of these revelations.
But with your prominent support,
we could turn that
into a tidal wave
and very possibly move
the needle finally
towards some sort of justice
for these dispossessed people
and accountability for
these neofascist monsters.
You'd be doing the world
a favor. Mr. Jones.
- Tree tops.
- Tree tops?
- Fuck!
- Is that enough?
- I guess it's gonna
have to be. Let's go.
All right, this is a
raid! Everybody down!
- Is that a true
story, Mr. Jones?
- Call me George.
It's time, son.
- Hey, George.
I just wanted to say, I
still think you're a legend.
- Thank you, Troyal.
That means a lot to me.
You know, there's two ways
that you can secure your legacy.
One is have yourself
frozen in time.
The other is to completely
reinvent yourself.
Take care, son.
- Let's go.
I don't know why I wandered
into this part of Texas, drunk.
When you took me in, pitied me,
helped me to straighten out.
Married me.
Why?
Why did this happen?
- Showtime, Champ.
- I'll in be there in a second.
- You know, a man
always doing his best
becomes a natural leader,
just by example.
- Is that another
Joe DiMaggio quote?
- Yeah, that's old Joe.
- Well, that's nice.
- Hey, um,
I'm real proud of you, Troyal.
- I 'preciate it.
- Now, I know we've had
the conversation before,
but, uh, um, I thought I'd
bring it up one more time.
It's, uh, it's about
these, these gold boots.
- I told you before, I'm not
gonna wear those gold boots.
They don't go with
my cowboy image.
- Well, we did the
focus groups and they,
they're still boots and...
- Man, I don't care. I need
shit-kickin' boots, man.
You're not gonna lead a
steer to a feed trough
wearin' gold boots,
looks stupid.
- Well, I, I hear ya, um,
but you, you know, John
Fogerty wore these boots.
- John Fogerty of CCR?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, set 'em on the
counter on your way out.
Son of a bitch!
Huh! Huh!
God damn superstar.
Showtime, motherfuckers.
Well, Troyal,
everything seems to be going
pretty well in your world.
You have the number one
record in America right now,
a beautiful family, and what
looks to be a bun in the oven.
- Well.
God, He's smiled down on me.
He's, He's blessed me with
a wonderful, nurturing wife
and of course these
little fuckers.
- And we're just
really glad to have him home.
- Well, you have managed
to do something
that most artists can't
quite get a grasp on.
You're keeping your music fresh.
Now, one could say that
you are staying with
the times so much
that you've become timeless.
Now, someone as
content as yourself,
how are you able
to keep your finger
on the pulse of what
the people want?
- Well, I think the,
the important thing to,
is to stay relatable
in, in my music, y'know?
Make the material, uh, really
resonate with folks, uh,
of all, of all kinds of
different backgrounds.
You know, I do that by
just understanding them,
knowing who they are,
who, who everyone is.
- Oh! Wow! I just, I
just got goosebumps.
- Right? Well, that's what I do.
You know, that's
what I do to people.
I, I create feelings in them
that they didn't
even know they had.
That's a rare
quality in a human.
These, these
goosebumps and these,
these feelings within
people, y'know,
Jesus doesn't judge,
I don't judge.
I'm the best country
singer to ever...
♪ Every day I wake up ♪
♪ Thinkin' 'bout somethin' now,
everyone's walkin' this way ♪
♪ And then the
night time comes ♪
♪ I'm lookin' now, hopin' now ♪
♪ Much I'm gonna lose to faith ♪
♪ Beneath the rings,
these better days ♪
♪ And you know I owe
it all to you, baby ♪
♪ Blowin' in the wind
is the only way to win ♪
♪ When I'm tryin' to
be straight with you ♪
♪ I got a friend and I'm gettin'
rid of all these promises ♪
♪ We ain't got nothin' to lose ♪
♪ Against the tide,
I almost died ♪
♪ I want to give it
another try, baby ♪
♪ Dealin' hands that
don't cost me a thing ♪
♪ And there's a world
outside of this fame ♪
♪ I put my hat on
and fool today ♪
♪ Travelin' on the highway,
my way of lovin' you ♪
♪ Doesn't mean a single thing ♪
♪ Unless you look
right back at me ♪
♪ Happy as a stray dog eatin'
out of somebody's hand ♪
♪ What's the plan,
I wanna understand ♪
♪ That I'm gonna do what
I can for you anyway ♪
♪ Dealin' hands that
don't cost me a thing ♪
♪ And there's a world
outside of this fame ♪
♪ And what you want
from me, baby ♪
♪ Must be some kinda change ♪
♪ Some kinda change ♪
♪ Every night I go to sleep,
dreamin' 'bout a hole in me ♪
♪ You got the love to feel it ♪
♪ Yeah, you got the
love to feel it ♪
♪ Dealin' hands that
don't cost me a thing ♪
♪ And there's a world
outside of this fame ♪
♪ And what you want
from me, baby ♪
♪ Must be some kinda change ♪
♪ Some kinda change ♪