[MUSIC PLAYING]
NARRATOR: Seems like everywhere
you look, love is all around.
But make sure you look very
closely because true love is
nearly impossible to find.
You doing all right, sir?
Yes, I'm fine.
In fact, how you doing?
Excuse me?
What's your name, beautiful?
Uh, sorry.
[SCOFFS] Now see,
that's just wrong.
Hey, we can't all be lucky
enough to find Mr. right.
True.
Take a look at [INAUDIBLE]
coming through the door.
Ooh, mm.
Now that's what I'm
talking about right there.
Woo, mm. [CLEARS THROAT]
Is he looking at me?
He probably is, to
tell you the truth.
Do you know of him?
Actually, I do.
You know, I have
never met a couple
as fascinating as Chante and
Harper, college sweethearts who
broke up after college but
then got back together,
as fate would have it.
As a matter of fact,
tonight is the anniversary
of their second first kiss.
Oh, that is so romantic.
Let's just say that Harper's
romantic side is definitely
going to cause a scene tonight.
How exactly do you know them?
It's my job.
Let's just say I help
women find true love.
So you're one of
those matchmakers.
Not exactly.
I'm a little more
hands on than that.
I help women find
out if their guy is
a Prince Charming or
just another toad.
Well, I'd say you
definitely helped her out.
What's that?
Confirmation of
whether Harper's
a prince or a pretender.
Hey, Jennifer, can you run that
to table two for me, sweetie?
Thanks.
I gotta go.
Here's my card.
Call me if you ever
need my services.
Nice to meet you.
What is that?
Oh.
Thank you.
Another one?
It's not from me.
What?
What's wrong?
(UNDER BREATH) Oh, shit.
All right.
Let's do this.
Hold on.
Uh, whew, I just... I just
want you to know that
if I... if I don't make it
out in one piece, I love you.
You know, you say this to me
every time that we do this.
And I just keep thinking to
myself, wow, you're stupid.
You're stupid.
OK?
Can we go in and
do our job, please?
[BREATHING QUICKLY]
Wow.
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING]
KENT (OFFSCREEN): Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Coming through, coming through.
What's up, man?
Hey, young, got an ID?
You look young.
You seen him?
Hold it.
Chris Brown.
Hey, candy girl.
Hey, Kent.
Long time no see.
Where you been?
Oh, just trying to
stay on the truck.
Mm.
I see.
Well, if you decide you
want to get into some,
you know where you can find me.
Mm-mm-mm.
Kent.
Huh?
Yeah.
Why you still standing here?
Waiting for the clock.
Come here.
OK.
Who... who... who
are you right now?
Dude, we're still on the clock.
Dude, whatever happened
to what they don't know
don't hurt them philosophy?
Come on, man.
I'm just trying not to
fall of the wagon, dude.
[CHUCKLES] You can't
fall off the wagon, brah.
OK, hell, let it run you over.
You're not married, man.
Come on.
Well, that might change son.
[CHUCKLES]
Y... you for... you serious?
What you trying
to say, B Pumper?
Huh?
What's up?
What's up, baby?
You... you throwing
in the towel, huh?
You waving the white flag?
Stop it.
Kid, come on.
Look, you... you don't know
anything about monogamy, OK?
You wouldn't know monogamy
if... if your name was Adam
and her's was Eve.
Wow.
And Brooke is not the one
to be turning your card for.
Oh.
That's a sign.
Oh, so sorry.
I guess I don't know
my own strength.
But thanks.
These things have been
falling out all night.
It must have been because of
all the bouncing and jerking,
I guess.
So do you like what you see?
Absolutely.
Oh, no. [STAMMERING] Oh, man.
Hold on.
Is that a siren?
There's... there's an emergency.
There's a lady about
to jump off a building.
We gotta go.
That's right.
Exactly.
Let her die.
No.
Look, what is your name?
Uh-uh.
No.
That accent is
sexy as all get...
Come on, we gotta go.
I know.
Get off of me.
KENT (OFFSCREEN):
She's Australian, too.
Kent, what are... what are...
What are you doing, brah?
What... dawg.
Look, first of all, don't try
to play a player, brah, OK?
Because I see it.
I see it in your eyes.
You still go the itch.
Yeah.
You still [INAUDIBLE].
No.
My itching days are
over, all right?
DOUG (OFFSCREEN): Yeah, right.
KENT (OFFSCREEN):
At least they gonna
have to be if I'm gonna
ask Brooke to marry me.
Wow.
You are serious.
Yeah.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I don't even know
what to say to you.
I don't know if I should
congratulate you or start
making plans for your funeral.
Doug, it's not
the death penalty.
No, it's life without the
possibility of parole ever.
Man, is Brooke that bad, man?
OK, OK, OK, OK.
Look, don't... don't
get me wrong, OK?
I like... I like Brooke.
But you gotta ask yourself
two very important questions,
all right?
One is, do you
really want to marry
somebody that doesn't
trust you at all?
And two, my brother,
more importantly,
are you ready to give
up all the power?
Wow.
Thank you.
How you doing?
- Wow.
- You feel me?
Really?
Yeah, it's like that.
No one man should
have all that power?
No, not at all.
Wow.
You know what?
I'm gonna be in the truck.
I'm gonna let you do your thing.
All right.
It's all good.
What's up, ladies?
How you doing?
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Someone's feeling
frisky tonight.
Yes, I am.
Mm.
Does work have my
baby stressed out?
Mm, yes it does.
Will you make me feel better?
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Ouch.
Oh.
Eeh.
Oh, I'm sorry, baby.
Damn.
It's OK, baby.
You women and your
bra malfunctions today.
Mm.
And what does that mean?
Uh, no... nothing.
Actually, it's... it's
a really funny story.
See, I was at work...
At work.
Today.
And... yeah.
And this go-go dancer...
She was dancing.
A go-go dancer.
And had a tassel
hit me in the face.
In the face.
And... when she
lifted up her blouse.
And see, it was
a freak accident.
A freak is what it was.
No.
She... she was a freak.
She was a freak.
But it was a freak accident.
It was not an accident.
I'm doubting, ladies' man.
Oh, no.
Reformed ladies' man.
The jury's still
out on that one.
Oh come on, baby.
It... it was nothing.
Hmm.
I was at work.
If you don't believe
me, ask Doug.
[SIGHS] Doug is not a great
character witness, Kent.
Come on, baby.
I... I don't wanna fight.
I'm sorry.
It's not you.
I'm just... ugh, I feel
so wound up, you know?
I mean, tomorrow's only the
biggest interview of my career.
Come on.
You acting like
you're not the best
candidate for the promotion.
I mean, I could be the
first female marketing
director in the
history of our company.
I mean, that's huge.
I know.
If I could just... ugh,
if I could just get a
read on Mr. Godfrey.
Yeah, what's up with that guy?
I don't know.
But I've never not been able
to impress one of my bosses,
and I'm not going to start now.
That's right.
Yeah.
That's my baby.
Mm.
You're my biggest
supporter, you know that?
Mm-hmm.
I love you.
I love you, too.
You stay here.
OK.
What's going on?
[GIGGLES]
What you doing?
Hopefully something you like.
What?
You know, you spend all your
time at those nasty clubs.
Uh-huh.
And you got your own
woman right here, right?
Yeah, you about to get nasty?
Yeah?
That's right.
OK.
Play some music.
Let me put something
on for you to dance to.
Wait a minute.
OK.
[RAP MUSIC PLAYING]
No way, baby.
No, no, no, no.
That's it, baby.
That's that primary bass.
No, no, no, no.
I want something
sexy and really...
Sexy?
OK.
[R&amp;B_MUSIC_PLAYING]
Slow jams, slow jams.
I like that one.
That's it?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm. k
We'll make it official.
I'm gonna make it rain.
Yeah.
It's magic city time.
Yeah, this is
gonna make it rain.
Get it.
I can't see.
Make it rain.
Oh.
Oh!
Baby!
Oh, damn.
Baby, are you OK?
I'm so sorry.
I... I... just thought
you would like it.
Why do you even have
all those singles?
I... I thought you
would like that.
Sorry, I'm just
not a professional
like the ones you're used
to making it rain on.
No.
No, no, no, no.
Don't... don't leave, baby.
What are you doing?
Come on, now.
No.
No, don't be embarrassed.
I need... I need to go.
No, it happens to the
best of them, baby.
Baby, don't leave.
No, what are you doing?
Stop.
Baby, finish your dance.
Don't be embarrassed, OK?
It happens to the best of them.
Strawberry at the club... she
was twerking it out one time.
She fell back, hit
her head on stage.
It happens to the
professionals, baby.
It happens all the time.
Just don't go.
Please.
Baby, I'm not a professional.
So I don't... I just...
I just need to go.
No, no, no.
But understand this.
I don't care.
You don't have to do that, OK?
That's not why I'm with you.
All right?
It... it doesn't change
the way I feel about you.
Please, don't leave.
You're kind of awesome.
You know that?
You're awesome too.
I love you.
Don't leave, OK?
OK.
Mm, I'm so tempted.
But I gotta go.
I do.
I need to focus for tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
What?
Rain check?
Come on, cheerleader.
I'm cheering.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Damn.
Woo.
Great shot, sir.
Thank you.
Good to see you, Mr. Godfrey.
Good to see you.
This here's for you.
What is this?
Come on.
I already know your work.
I don't need to see that.
I know you're brilliant.
Thank you, sir.
But to be the
director of marketing
requires more than brilliance.
Yes, it takes someone who
is completely organized,
highly knowledgeable,
and in complete control.
And someone who's willing to
listen just as much as they're
willing to talk,
someone who's flexible.
(WHISPERS) Yes.
Someone who has a
willingness to learn,
and someone who's
open for suggestions.
Am I right?
Yes, sir.
Definitely.
Listen, Brooke. k What
we're trying to do this year
is tap into the young market.
Oh.
So we need someone who
resonates with these younger
clients we're trying to
bring in, someone who, uh,
thinks outside of the box.
Well, I, sir, can definitely
think outside of the box.
I assure you that.
You can?
Yes, sir.
Well, let's just see.
If you make this
putt, you get the job.
Can't we just... just do
the interview, please?
It's just a putt, Brooke.
Sir, I don't think that
my getting this promotion
should be based on
me making that putt.
It should definitely be
based on my abilities.
[CHUCKLES] Really?
Yes, sir.
You can't do it, can you?
I didn't say can't.
All right.
Thank you.
Take your time.
Most definitely.
Let me get my shot lined up.
Now see, one great putt,
one great marketing director
coming up.
Great.
All right.
So let me get this right.
You putted for your
promotion, babe?
I had to.
You know how bad
I want that job.
What?
You know what a move up
like that would mean for me?
For us.
So he challenged you.
Yes, he challenged me.
Ugh.
All right.
What happened next?
Well, after
embarrassing myself... OK,
he tells me that he
knows me well enough
to know that I wasn't
going to back down
from a challenge, right?
So then he says, I'll
give you a second chance
with this new product launch.
Sounds kind of interesting.
What... what kind of product?
A clothing line
they want to target
after a younger audience.
So my mission is to think out
of the box, whatever that is.
[SNAPS_FINGERS] You
know what you should do?
What?
You should do a
throw back function.
You know, like... like
these old school parties.
You know what I'm saying?
I think people would
really like that.
That's what you think?
Yeah.
That's a cute idea,
and you're cute.
But I don't think that'll work.
I don't wanna bore the kids.
You know what I mean?
I wanna attract them,
not bore them to death.
But I love you.
All right.
Cool.
[PHONE_RINGS]
Oh, I gotta go.
But listen, I took the liberty
of booking us reservations
at Le Bistro to
celebrate later on, OK?
OK.
What are we celebrating?
I didn't get the promotion.
Well, no.
We're gonna celebrate.
We're gonna celebrate,
um, you and me.
Aw, there you go with
that sweet thing again.
Give me cheek.
Mm-hmm.
Mm, I hate seeing you go.
I know.
But I got to.
I love you.
I love you, too.
All right.
Whipped cream tonight.
That's what we're doing.
I hope you're ready.
Did you enjoy dinner?
Yeah, tonight was a good idea.
Thank you.
I needed that.
[SIGHS] Celebrating
us was a good idea.
I appreciate that.
Mm-hmm.
That dress is off the chain.
Thank you.
You look good, baby.
No, you look good though.
Mm-hmm.
I love you.
Kent.
Kenton Hughes, is that you?
It's me, Kim.
Uh.
[SNAPS FINGERS] Oh, yeah.
Kim.
Yeah, uh, how you doing?
Good.
It's been a long time
since I've seen you.
And we... it's been a long time.
Yeah, yeah.
Whew.
Hey, Brooke.
Brooke, this is Kim.
How nice.
Kim, this is my
girlfriend Brooke.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Wow.
It's been a while.
Yes, yes.
Don't act like you
don't know Kent and Kim.
Kent and Kim.
Like an after school
cartoon or something.
That's cute.
It was the Kent and Kimmy show.
Kent and Kimmy.
That's so cute.
Cute, Kim, and Kent.
Good, good, good.
Good, well, it was...
Are you chipping in on
the bill or anything?
I mean, you sat down
like you were offering.
Uh, she... no.
She's a comedian.
Yeah, she... she is.
We just doing our thing.
It's all right.
You know what?
I'm not going to interrupt
the romantic evening
you guys are having.
Thank you, thank you.
But it was good
seeing you, Kenton.
Yup, it was good
seeing you too.
Have a good evening.
Bye.
Nice meeting you, Brandy.
Brooke, Brooke.
Her name's...
Your butt's falling out.
- Stop.
- It is.
I mean...
Don't do that.
It's fine.
Clearly, she's from the
skanky area of your past.
Why?
No, just chill out.
Just relax.
Why do you have to be so...
That was rude.
She sat at our table.
WAITRESS (OFFSCREEN): Hi.
Hey.
Flowers for the lady.
Thank you.
Good save.
I love orchids.
Me too.
I wish my man was half
as romantic as yours.
Oh, sweetie, is
something in your eye?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
You might wanna get
something for that.
Check please.
I guess we'll just
wrap everything up here.
We'll take the check please.
Yeah.
No problem.
Look, I'm... I'm sorry, babe.
To... tonight wasn't
supposed to go like that.
Don't worry about it, baby.
It's OK.
I... I didn't know she was gonna
be coming through with that ass
and... and...
Whoa, with the what?
Not the ass.
With no class.
It was... it was... it was totally
just... I don't know what to...
I got to get out of
here, like, ooh gosh.
I'm ready to go.
Can you... can you...
And your check.
You gonna pay?
No, I am not going to pay.
No, I'll take...
Oh, I just...
I'll take care of it.
WAITRESS (OFFSCREEN):
She looks so strong.
She's strong.
No, no she is.
That I am.
Everything's inside.
BROOKE (OFFSCREEN):
Drop that on the table.
Wheel it back a bit.
Thank you.
I'll be over here
if you need me.
OK.
Bye.
Thank you.
OK, OK, OK.
Goodbye to you and your butt.
Time to go.
Can you just stop?
Can you help me work out
this gratuity please?
No, I will not.
You good with the math.
You... you do that.
Use your brain on that
instead of thinking about...
Use my brain?
No.
- Now is not the time.
- Your mind is everywhere.
Now is not the time, Kent.
Just put it... oh, god.
All right.
DANIELLE (OFFSCREEN): Ooh,
you know what we could do?
We could do high
mimosas, not high tea.
Mimosas?
DANIELLE (OFFSCREEN): Yes.
You always want a cocktail.
No, honey.
Today we are having
tea and crumpets.
OK.
Romantic restaurant,
your favorite flowers,
and dessert on a silver platter?
Hello, honey.
Sounds to me like you just
ruined a perfect proposal.
I didn't ruin it.
Those girls ruined it.
But Brooke, you don't have
anything to worry about.
I mean, if Kent is as
perfect as you say he is,
he'll propose again.
I'm not worried, Danielle.
Yeah.
No one ever is, Brooky.
I mean, look at me.
I never would have
believed it about Tony
or Lloyd or Clarence.
Oh, my gosh.
Or Mario.
[LAUGHING]
DANIELLE (OFFSCREEN): What?
Nothing.
Well, I don't have to worry,
because Kent is reformed.
Ugh, face reality, Brooke.
All men cheat.
Uh-uh.
Wait, hold up, honey.
All men do not cheat.
They don't.
OK?
And I think Kent
is one who doesn't.
Thank you.
Well, I mean, at
least I don't think so.
Oh, well, thank you.
SOPHIA (OFFSCREEN): Come on.
It's the truth.
Well, there's one way
that you can know for sure.
You could give him the MS test.
And what is that?
Why do you think that
I am still single?
Well, there's a lot of reasons.
I mean, it could be because
you're a little bit of a picky
bitch, but...
Stop it, OK?
We're going to be nice today.
No, Brooke.
It's because all my men
have failed the MS test.
Like multiple sclerosis?
I'm not understanding.
Keep it up.
Girl, I don't like ugly.
Get to the MS test please.
What is it?
It's not what.
It's who.
She's called the man stealer.
[CHUCKLES] And she is one woman
you do not want anywhere near
your man if you want
to keep him, that is.
Now, none of her clients
have ever seen her in person.
But I'm willing to
guess that she's
got the body of a
Victoria's Secret model
and the face of a goddess.
You know, wherever she goes,
men lose their freaking minds.
You know Stacy Shaw?
BROOKE (OFFSCREEN): Mm.
DANIELLE (OFFSCREEN): She said
her ex certainly lost his.
And apparently, a lot
of men fall for her
because her website
boasts a 99% success rate.
It bring out the
inner Fido in all men.
You know the 1%?
Yeah, they're probably gay.
But whatever she looks like,
one thing's for certain.
Only men with true love in their
hearts can pass the MS test.
Well, in that case,
Kent would ace the test.
[CHUCKLES] Well, there's
only one way to find out.
Are you challenging my love,
my four year relationship?
SOPHIA (OFFSCREEN):
Brooke, careful.
Careful.
Don't go looking
for trouble, OK?
Because people that go
looking for trouble...
They normally find it.
To the perfect couple.
That would be me and William.
Here's to you and Kent.
BROOKE (OFFSCREEN): Thank you.
Cheers.
What do we have here?
What are we celebrating, ladies?
Uh, OK.
I see what this is.
Y'all must be talking
about men, huh?
DANIELLE (OFFSCREEN):
You know it.
In that case, um,
let me excuse myself.
DANIELLE (OFFSCREEN):
Wait, wait.
Not so fast, brother-in-law.
You know, maybe you
can help us out.
All right.
What, what, what?
Lay it on me.
Brooke.
All right, William.
This is about Kent.
And we want to know if
you think all men cheat.
Well, that's an
interesting question.
Yes, it is.
Mm-hmm.
I think they got a
show called "Cheaters."
It might give you some insight.
Answer the question.
Well, well, since you guys
are going to just drag me
all up in this mess, I mean,
Kent seems like a cool dude,
you know?
But, uh, you know what they say.
Once a player, always a player.
Preach.
Watch it.
On that note, deuces.
[SIGHS]
No.
Trust.
Never.
I got things to do.
OK.
Nope.
Just walk away.
OK.
[WHISPERS TO SELF]
It won't hurt.
OK.
You're not going to do this.
Nope.
I'm better than that.
I am so much better than that.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, that... that
concludes our tour.
And, uh, like I
said before, here
at the African-American
museum at Station Number 30,
we are dedicated to preserving
the legacy of African-Americans
in the fire service.
And with that, thank
you for coming out.
Thank you.
It's really cool that
you guys have this place.
To tell you the truth, I
never even knew it was here.
Do you guys work
here full time or...
Oh, no, uh, Doug and I
are actual LA firefighters.
But, uh, we just come
here from time to time,
you know, to
volunteer, give back.
Great.
Yeah.
Appreciate it.
Hey, man, I appreciate you.
Thanks for coming out.
No worries.
Nice to meet you.
All right.
Cool.
Take it easy.
You too.
A real American
hero in the flesh.
Just like GI Joe.
Well, Joe, it looks
like your friend here
needs a little help.
[CLEARS_THROAT] Doug?
Y... yes?
Yes?
KENT (OFFSCREEN):
I didn't know we
were doing safety
training today.
Well, Kent, you...
You know me, right?
I mean, you can never
put in too much overtime.
I mean, you know, you
can never be too safe.
Oh, and I don't mind.
I like seeing you handsome
black men working hard.
You know what?
Let's... let's go this way.
It was nice meeting you.
All right.
Well, hey, take care of
that thing I told you about.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, I pretty much run
this place, you know.
Yeah, I mean, you know, without
me, this would fall apart.
Kent's like my little sister.
Oh, so you working
hard and in charge, huh?
I like that too.
Yeah.
Why don't I show you
some other, you know...
I'd love to see
whatever you have.
After you.
So where'd you say
you were from again?
Um, well, just like
down the street.
He's pretty funny and
quite the ladies' man.
You have no idea.
So what can I do for
you, Ms. Photographer?
I'm looking for Kenton Hughes.
Oh.
That's me.
I'm Kenton Hughes.
You're Kenton Hughes?
Yeah.
You're the reason why I'm here.
I work for the "Daily
Breeze," and we're
doing a segment
on local profiles.
And Kenton Hughes made the cut.
Damn.
I guess I was drawn to you.
Uh, what do we have
to do for this profile?
Basically, I need
to follow you around
at work and play and
everything in between.
Is that all?
Yes.
Oh, and I'm on a
really tight deadline,
so we should get started ASAP.
How about tomorrow?
Uh, tomorrow?
That's good.
You know what?
The sooner we finish
this, the better.
Yeah.
I'm really looking
forward to it.
Damn.
Woo.
You only smile like
this when you're
about to drop the
hammer on another chump.
Not true.
I smile at a lot of things.
Uh-huh.
So who's the unlucky
toad tonight?
This guy, likes brunettes,
frequents gentleman's clubs,
loves Italian food.
Ah.
And, uh, where might
I be meeting you?
Spaghettini's.
And don't be late this time.
Hey, don't worry.
Me and my camera will
be laying in wait,
reading to catch the
next idiot in the act.
[SIGHS] They man
not all be idiots.
Mr. Kent didn't respond
like the others.
I've never heard you say that.
I know.
Game on.
I'm saying, why are you
acting all nervous though?
No, dude, every time, like,
we go out... thank you, sir.
Every time we go
out, you always gotta
bring me into an environment
where there's, like,
a lot of estrogen,
like a lot of chicks.
Like, how come we just
can't go to an environment
where there's an even mixture?
It is.
It's just...
Why would you even want that?
Because I... look, that
doesn't even matter.
It makes no sense at all.
I just need you to be
my anchor today, OK?
Don't even trip, homie.
I got your back, homie.
I'm serious, Doug.
All right.
I got you, man.
I got you.
All right?
Relax.
You're all nervous.
I... yeah.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hold on.
This is Brooke.
That's why I'm nervous.
Hello?
Hey, sweetie.
How are you?
I'm good.
Oh, I didn't tell you I
was having lunch with Doug?
Yeah.
We're having lunch with
that photographer too.
No.
Is she pretty?
Hell yea, she's...
No, no.
She... she all right.
I mean, you know, whatever.
But you ain't got
nothing to worry about.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah.
I know.
OK.
Well, I'll... I'll
see you later on.
All right.
I love you, too, baby.
Bye, baby.
I'm terrible.
I cannot believe I let
you talk me into this.
Oh, come on.
This is the only way you'll
ever know the true Kent.
Was that the warden?
No, man.
It was your mother.
You know, me and her have
been hanging out a lot lately.
You know, I never knew
she was a freak like that.
Your mother's special.
Wow.
That's right.
I'm playing.
Look, I... I just need
you to just sit here
and have lunch with
us and be cool.
I will Dude, I
already told you.
I got you, all right?
I mean, but personally, I
don't... I don't even understand
why I'm here.
I mean... I mean, to
be honest with you,
I certainly wouldn't invite
you to be a third wheel if I
was having lunch with, like,
Miss December or somebody,
you know.
I mean, not unless, you
know, she wanted it that way.
Does... does she... does
she want it that way?
Did you ask her?
I'm... I'm saying, like,
you know, she... she wants...
Hey, Kent.
Hey, Doug.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I interrupt something here?
No.
No, not at all.
Absolutely not.
As a matter of fact,
I was just telling
Kent I am really
sorry I will not
be able to join you
two for lunch today.
Yes.
Yeah.
Booty... duty calls.
You got that, right?
All right then.
Uh.
What a jerk off.
So what's up?
How you doing?
Oh, I'm good.
I'm good.
I'm glad you could come out.
You're... you're out.
Absolutely.
You're really...
And thank you for having me.
No problem.
Gotta love Doug.
He's so dedicated to the job.
I get the feeling you
are just as dedicated.
I'm sorry.
Would you like
something to drink?
Coffee, tea, water,
maybe some wine?
Take the edge off.
Hey, what, you trying
to get me drunk already?
No, it's OK.
I never drink when
I'm on the job.
I'll take a water.
Speaking of job, why'd
you become a firefighter?
Oh, to rescue, uh,
damsels in distress.
Oh.
Thank you.
No, I'm just kidding.
It's a little firehouse humor.
I... I guess I just
wanted to help people.
Oh.
So how long have you
been rescuing damsels?
[CHUCKLES] All my life.
No, no, uh, I've been on the
force for about eight years
now, eight proud years.
They look really cozy
together, don't they?
Ooh, I wonder what
they're saying.
(HIGH PITCHED) I wonder
what they're saying.
You're too happy for this.
Mm-hmm.
Well, you know there's only one
way we're going to find out.
What?
What are you doing?
Well, I'm going to
see if Mr. Wonderful's
as perfect as you say he is.
He is, Danielle.
Are you always this charming?
Let me get another
one of these.
Excuse us.
Excuse me.
Ooh, duck.
Duck.
And here you've got candles,
some lingerie, you know?
You work that out,
girl. [INAUDIBLE].
Danielle, this is silly.
If we just get a little closer,
we can hear their conversation.
Please.
All right.
Look, I just wanna
see who this woman is.
[SIGHS]
Come on.
Sorry.
So the hours are grueling, huh?
Gosh, it must be hard
for your... girlfriend?
The readers want to know.
Trust me.
It makes for a better profile.
Oh.
In that case, uh, yeah, I guess
it's kind of tough on her.
I have to spend a lot
of time away from her.
Brooke.
That's her name.
Oh, he said your name.
He said your name.
Aren't you
interested in jotting
all this juicy info down?
Oh, honey, trust me.
I've got a mental file
like a steel trap.
So it's, uh, tough for Brooke.
Keep going.
Um, yeah.
It's kind of tough on her.
I mean, um, matter
of fact, we were
supposed to have
lunch together today.
Oh, no.
Did I get you in
trouble or anything.
Or...
No.
No, no.
OK.
It's OK.
Brooke is cool.
See?
We gotta go.
Oh, gosh.
Let's go, please.
Right.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
No, we haven't
seen her face yet.
I'm gonna get busted.
Let's go, Danielle.
All right.
God.
(SLOW MOTION) [YELLS]
I am so... I'm so sorry, ma'am.
Let me help you clean that up.
Can we get a wet nap over here?
I'm so sorry... that was my bad.
It was... I'm sorry.
Let me get that for you.
[INAUDIBLE] Pray.
[INAUDIBLE]
Can we get a
napkin or something?
That's crazy.
I know.
Wow.
Wet nap?
What kind of restaurant
y'all running?
You guys work hard.
What do you do for fun?
(MAKES BUZZER SOUND) Brick.
Look at this no game-having...
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
I hear you talking.
You can talk a good game.
Can actually play it?
You don't want none of this.
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
That's my assistant,
Natalie, over there.
She's going to get some
shots while I school y'all.
Oh, and get a shot of Jordan.
This is baby Jordan.
Boo-ya.
Make or take it.
In your face.
You OK?
I just wanna make
sure you're cool.
Yo, yo, put your hand
in her face or something.
I ain't gonna put my
hand in her face, man.
She don't even know
how to play the game.
Hey, kid, right here.
We right here.
I'm looking at you.
I'm gonna teach
you a thing or two.
What?
Hey.
Yo.
Two to zip.
You disappoint me, kid.
Come on.
No, I'm gonna go
ahead and play now.
DOUG (OFFSCREEN):
It's embarrassing, OK?
Oh, thank you.
See, now we talking.
Now we talking.
Let me get my LeBron on, man.
What's wrong with you?
OK.
All right.
Take a picture of that.
MANDY (OFFSCREEN):
I let you have that.
You got that?
My D got you on lock.
Now, you said your Ds.
Your... your D?
Oh, all right.
Whatever.
Play the game.
Here we go.
Focus.
Oh.
I said, take it to the right.
All right.
Take it to the right.
Can you?
Or you gonna fake?
That's classic AC [INAUDIBLE].
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
Oh, OK.
Nice.
That's game.
Let me take you to school
and show you something.
You and all your
subliminal comments.
Man.
You didn't tell me
you were a hooper.
Hey, I tried to warn you.
I grew up as a
tomboy, so... I have
two older brothers
who love basketball.
I didn't have a choice.
Huh.
So how'd you go
from being Candace
Parker to being Beyonce?
I know your brothers
weren't really feeling that.
I guess I sort
of grew out of it.
Or more specifically,
I grew these.
[CHUCKLES_NERVOUSLY]
I had a girlfriend
who convinced
me to try out for cheer-leading.
So I traded in my
kicks for pom-poms.
I never really
liked cheerleaders.
No?
Why not?
Were you nice to Mr.
Most Likely to Succeed?
Yes.
No.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
The only time y'all
nice to me is if you
needed help with your homework.
Plus, you know, light-skinned
brothers was in back then.
Oh, what are you talking about?
Come on.
You know what I'm talking about.
That's all y'all wanted,
Mr. Al Beat, Mr. Cool J.
Yeah.
Dark-skinned brothers weren't
even in the rotation then.
OK.
I'll give you that.
But that was then, you know.
This is now.
So what do they say?
Like, the darker the berry,
the sweeter the juice.
Is that how it goes?
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Oh, damn.
I'm on fire.
I mean, something's on fire.
You know what?
[SIREN]
Another time, another place.
So many things.
But I can't, all right?
I... I gotta go.
Oh, my god.
Your leg's so soft.
Oh, ooh, ooh.
Ooh, I gotta go.
That's a first.
Yeah.
It's gonna take a little
more effort than I thought.
Yo, hurry up, hot lips.
Leave it alone, D.
What, man?
She looked like she was trying
to get traded to your team,
and you weren't
trying to stop her.
Man, I wasn't gonna kiss her.
Right.
I wasn't.
Stop saying that.
Right, right.
So?
So what?
Uh, look, don't make me
cut you, Miss MS Test.
OK?
I understand you two had
quite the undercover operation
yesterday?
Mm-hmm.
She was hilarious.
You should've seen her,
with cake all on her face.
Shh.
You didn't.
Keep it down.
He's in the other room.
It wasn't that funny.
I can't even believe
I'm doing this.
This is ridiculous.
Oh, please.
It is not ridiculous.
And you know what?
We're gonna find
out soon enough.
Mm-hmm.
I know that's right.
You know what?
Maybe I should try
the man stealer test.
For what?
Exactly.
You know.
BROOKE (OFFSCREEN):
So she can rub
more of how perfect
everything is in our face.
I mean, come on now.
You know he's perfect.
- He's not perfect.
BROOKE (OFFSCREEN): We know.
Your man, your boo.
No, what does she call him?
Her chocolate hive.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You know what she calls him?
What?
Mr. Always Right.
[INAUDIBLE]
No, seriously, if Kent was
as perfect as William is,
I'd be pregnant, knocked up,
happy, all those good things.
So let's hope he
passes this past.
Yeah, the whole situation
was crazy, right?
I mean, Tiger was a freak.
He had stripper after stripper
coming out, porn stars.
Bang, bang, bang, bang.
Man.
Yeah, man.
It's like your
man [? Tee Howe?]
Said in that flick, ain't
nothing better than a woman.
So the new woman.
Oh.
Yeah, man.
You know, I bet you
know all about that.
I bet you they be
throwing it at you
like you skinny
Luther or something.
No, no.
I'm cool, man.
I'm trying to stay on
the straight and narrow,
do the husband and
wife thing like you.
You know what I'm saying?
Look, but don't touch, right?
Yeah, man.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, baby.
Hey.
That looks good [INAUDIBLE].
You know it does.
Mm.
BROOKE (OFFSCREEN):
You all right?
[INAUDIBLE]
What?
He's a great role
model, isn't he?
All right.
So I didn't put a lot
of cheese because we're
staying the night.
Oh.
Oh, cool, thanks.
I don't like a lot of cheese.
It's a little Frisbee, huh?
All right.
This is my forte.
I see.
You gonna show me what you got?
You like games?
I love games.
I play them all the time.
Oh, I bet.
All right.
You just gotta stay
focused, nice and easy.
Oh.
Beautiful.
Let's see.
Wow.
All right.
OK.
Oh, God.
Oh, wow.
That's... do the second one.
OK.
That happens.
It happens.
All right.
Let me show you.
OK.
Grab it right there.
Mm-hmm.
Good.
Back up into it.
Yeah, don't be shy.
OK.
Oh, yeah.
You know what?
I need to freshen up a bit.
Where is the little girls' room?
Um, just over there.
That way?
Yeah.
OK, great.
Hold that for me, sweetie.
OK.
You be back now.
Whew.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yo, yo.
Hey, babe.
No, no, no.
That's the TV.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
All right.
I'll see you.
I love you too.
Mm-mm-mm, you dog.
I hope you're ready
because this guy's a loser.
Oh, just like the rest.
I don't know.
Kent seems to be different.
Mandy.
What?
Do you like Kent?
Hell no.
He's just different.
Uh-huh.
Be careful, Mandy.
Don't get involved.
Hey, it's 99% success, not 100%.
Just let this one go.
OK.
I'm already planning on calling
his girlfriend and telling her
we're off the case.
All right.
Now let's go save another girl
from heartache because this wig
and these heels... child, please.
Woo.
All right.
Let's go.
OK.
Don't forget to show
me that ring, girl.
You know, I never
meet clients here.
But in your case, I
thought it was necessary.
You?
You're the man stealer.
Yup.
And I've got a 99%
success rate to prove it.
The reason why I called you
here is because I think Kent
could go in the other 1%.
So I'm pretty much done.
Oh.
Wait, you're done?
MANDY (OFFSCREEN): Yup.
Something wrong?
Uh, well, yeah.
I, uh, paid you for a service.
And it's only been a few days.
I thought you'd be happy.
Isn't this what you wanted?
No, it is.
Trust me, it is.
It's just I really
need to know for sure.
I... I need you to do
a full investigation.
You don't know Kent, OK?
He hasn't always
been squeaky clean.
So I just really
want to make sure
that he's changed, truly
changed into this, uh, 1%
that you speak of.
And, um, don't take
this the wrong way.
But you don't strike
me as the kind of girl
that he would actually
really be into.
OK, Brooke.
Let me help you out here, OK?
Go back to your man
and be thankful for who
he is because as
wonderful as you
as think you are
compared to me, you're
not unlike many of my
clients who let a good man
slip through their
pretty little fingers.
Listen, whatever your name is.
It's Mandy.
BROOKE (OFFSCREEN): Oh, Mandy?
Hmm.
Listen, Mandy.
I don't know who
you think you are.
But Kent, my man... he has
a great taste in women.
And you are far from perfect.
You're right, Brooke.
I'm not perfect.
But what a man like Kent sees
in me is pretty damn close.
Ha.
Yeah, you don't know him.
You're right.
I don't.
But what I do know is that
if you keep testing him,
he will end up
like the other 99%.
Is that a threat?
I'm just saying,
you have a good man.
Start appreciating him
before he gets taken.
Listen, honey, I take men
from their women every day.
It's my job.
But Kent... Kent, I just
might take for myself.
So listen, walk away from this.
Huh.
I never walk away from anything.
OK.
If this is what you want, I
will gladly take your man.
Gladly?
Well, then I guess it's on.
Hmm.
Well, I guess so.
We should keep this between us.
Not a problem.
We're done.
We're done when
I say we're done.
Oh.
[SIGHS] I'll win.
Music, huh?
Likes neo soul, basketball.
Favorite body part, legs.
Thank you, fellas, for
letting me tag along.
I really got some
good information.
Oh, it's no problem.
It's all good because
you brought us gifts.
(WHISPERING) Stop.
[MUSIC PLAYING FROM CAR STEREO]
What is it with today's music?
Hey, tell me about it.
It's like you come
up with a wack saying
and add a dance to it, you can
just get on the money boat.
I know, right?
All I need is some
good neo soul.
Give me some 'Gel,
India, I'm good.
Shut up.
You don't know nothing
about no neo soul.
What?
Girl, that ain't no
cheerleader music.
Oh, OK.
Hold on, wait.
We gonna test her.
What you know about
this? [HUMMING]
[HUMMING ALONG TOGETHER]
What?
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, don't test the kid.
Don't test the kid.
I'm trying to tell y'all.
All right.
I tell you, stay with the
kid, you'll learn something.
Oh, for real?
Yeah, music soul job.
Why you gonna go there though?
Why you even gotta go
there on me like that?
Hold on, hold on.
For real, for real.
All right.
All jokes aside, you might
wanna hang back a little bit,
for real, because she
might not handle it.
Because you know it can
get dangerous inside.
What he means by
dangerous is we
going into Southern
Girl Desserts.
Southern Girl Desserts?
Ooh, that sounds good.
Yeah, you never had it?
No.
It's off the chain.
Come on.
Hold up, hold up.
Ladies first, man.
I got the door.
Just chill.
Hey, there's my boys.
Where y'all been?
I take it y'all are regulars.
Uh, something like that.
Oh, honey, these are my boys.
You know, they can't get
enough of these cupcakes.
Boy, wash your hands.
Actually, I think
it's just their excuse
to come by and see me.
What?
Are we that obvious?
Some feelings, you
just can't hide.
[COUGHING, _CHOKING]
Come on, baby.
Come on.
Get back.
Take a deep breath.
[WHEEZING, _COUGHING]
Are you OK?
Just calm down.
It's OK.
Thank you so much.
It's no problem.
Get some water.
It's OK.
Good work.
Good work, baby boy.
Yo, let's, uh...
Let's keep this here.
You know what I'm saying?
Between brothers.
This stays here.
You dig?
Yeah, yeah.
I got you.
Ha ha, my dude.
Baby boy.
Take care.
You need some air.
You OK?
She OK.
She just needs some air.
Come on.
Let's get you some air.
Take some deep breaths.
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
Y'all come back, OK?
Yeah.
Take care.
You see this?
[WHISPERING]
Wow.
Saved the day.
Hey.
That's what we do.
OK, Doug.
Thanks for agreeing
to meet me here.
I think.
Yo, to be honest with you,
uh, I almost didn't show up.
I didn't think you were serious.
But then I thought to myself,
hey, what kind of friend
would I be not to
make this sacrifice?
Doug, I have never
been more serious.
Yeah, I see that.
Kent told me.
He said, Brooke would never
set foot in a place like this.
And here you are.
Yeah.
That's saying something.
It is, isn't it?
OK.
Before we get all
warm and fuzzy,
OK, I'm here for my boy Kent.
That's all.
I'm just looking out for him.
Of course.
And I'm here for my man, Kent.
So...
OK.
Well, yeah.
There it is.
All I need you to do is
just tell me what to do.
OK, well, first things first.
Repeat after me.
- OK.
- Ready?
Mm-hmm.
Lighten.
The.
Hell up!
H...
Lighten up.
You know what I'm saying?
Relax, exhale, put
your shoulders down.
They are down.
No, they're not.
Thank you.
Yeah, loosen up.
Do something
unplanned, you know?
Unexpected.
Like what?
You ever fart in front of Kent?
See?
No.
You're boring.
Yeah.
I got it.
Unlock your inner scripper.
My inner what?
Your inner scripper.
Oh, yeah.
I tried that.
It... it didn't go too well.
It's probably because you
ain't do my man's favorite move.
You know, he got this
little move he like when...
Kent has a favorite move?
Oh, yeah.
Didn't he tell you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Baby... as a matter of fact,
baby girl in the other room was
doing it right
before you came too.
She was like like,
bak, bak, bak.
Yeah, it's called
the red snapper.
Well, if there's gonna
be somebody freaky moving,
it's gonna be this woman.
So it's gonna be move.
If anyone's gonna freaky move
with Kent, it's gonna be me.
Girl, what the
hell are you doing?
Give me the information.
Come on now.
Give me the scoop, brother.
I'm down.
Don't you want to sit down?
No.
Seriously, come on.
OK.
Cool.
You come to the jungle.
You play.
That's right.
So first, you want
to limp to the side.
OK.
Kind of like your
leg was broke.
Oh, OK.
That's... no, that's... that's
what's I'm talking about right
there.
Yeah.
And then you want to shake.
OK.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, and kind
of twitch, kind of like you
smoking.
OK.
Yeah, yeah.
[CHUCKLING]
What?
You're an ass.
You are an ass.
Ah.
First you gotta
limp to the side,
kind of like your
leg was broken.
[LAUGHING]
Yo, for real though, don't ever
do that again, ever in life.
Ha, ha.
Of Can we help me now please?
I'm serious.
I... I need your help.
All right.
All right, Brooke.
Look, you have to stop
being so judgemental.
You gotta cut that out.
Stop it.
All right?
No man wants to be critiqued
about he everything he does.
I do that?
OK.
Next lesson, stop
debating everything.
Everything is not a
debate, unless you
trying to tell me
that those are real.
Don't no man... and
I mean no man... want
to be challenged
about everything,
everything, especially
from his woman.
Does Kent say that about me?
Doug, what else does he say?
Is he falling for Mandy?
Doug, hello.
What?
Gosh, doesn't that get old?
Hell no.
How could it get old?
So many [INAUDIBLE].
What I do know though, Brooke,
is you were Kent's choice.
All right?
Now, I don't know.
Oh, god.
Uh, you've got to tell
me what to do then.
Well, specifically,
Brooke, only you know that.
What I do know
though is you... you
could do something to keep
your man's full attention.
I guess we're done.
Uh, full attention,
full attention.
ANNOUNCER (ON TV):
Second shot opportunity.
Fisher!
Ooh.
Now, that's how you
run a triangle offence.
For real, triangles.
Mm.
What about yours?
I don't know, D.
I mean, I didn't
know it was going
to be this hard.
You know?
I really thought I was done.
I figure I just put a ring
on Brooke and be happy.
But now...
Now what?
Oh.
Oh, I see.
You figure you take your
talents to South Beach, huh?
There you go.
Man, it's serious.
I don't know.
What if meeting
Mandy was a sign,
showing me that
Brooke's not the one?
Man, shut your crying.
You sound like a girl.
(HIGH PITCHED) Oh,
is Mandy the one?
Is Brooke?
Who cares?
They're both hot.
Brooke hot.
Mandy hot.
You know?
What's the... what's the problem?
No, but it's not just
about the physical thing?
Well, what is it about?
The metaphysical, huh?
Yo, hey, I think you
got company, my man.
Hey.
Brooke?
Baby?
I'm looking for my man.
[STAMMERING] W...
What are you doing?
What are you doing
dressed like this?
What... what's going on?
What?
You don't like it?
Yeah, Kent.
No, no, no.
I... I... I do.
I do.
But what are you trying to do?
I'm trying to watch
the game with you, sexy.
Mind if I stay?
Uh, um, I don't...
I don't think...
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Why not?
I thought you wanted me to
watch the game with you.
No, I... I do.
But you should... we
should... we should just
go back to... to my place
and look at the game.
Why?
All of your friends are here.
Yeah, um, we're all here.
Hey, man.
Hey, chill out, man.
You ain't gonna be my friend for
too much longer. [STAMMERING]
No.
Stop it.
Come on.
Let's get a coat.
Hey, Doug.
Doug, look after her, OK?
You see this, what's
going on with my baby?
Absolutely.
This is... I don't
know what you're doing.
I don't know what this is.
Doug.
Nice move.
Oh, don't you worry.
I've got plenty more.
Ah, I'm sure you do, Brooke.
Listen, are you sure you want
to keep doing this because...
Are you sure you want
to keep doing this?
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah?
Because I never lose ever.
Good to know.
OK.
Oh, ho, woo.
Hey.
Hey, I see... I see
you ladies have met.
We did.
You know, I was
just telling Brooke
how great our
interviews were going.
I'm getting such
good stuff with you.
Really?
What kind of good stuff
are you getting, you know,
hanging around
other women's men?
Oh.
It's funny you should ask.
I think we should get going.
I feel a cat fight
cat coming on. [MEOWS]
Uh, Kent, you... you leaving?
You guys are laving?
Yeah.
Yeah, Kent, you can't leave.
The game is starting
to get really good.
Oh, really?
Then baby, we have to stay.
Hey, Brooke,
[PATS KNEE] you can
sit right here, if you want.
Hey, look here,
partner, I... mm-mm.
[STAMMERING] You see what I'm
dealing with here with, man?
Come on, man.
You gotta help me get
this under control.
Uh, you gotta love
they're trying.
Oh, Doug, damn it.
This is serious.
I need your help,
D. Come on, man.
Look at that D, Kent.
He's got the boy on lock.
Oh, the playoffs are going
to be bananas this year.
What are you doing?
Well, which one is Shaq?
Huh, baby?
I can't see him.
Uh, uh, he's... he's
not on the team, babe.
Yeah, he got traded
out, and the team
is so much stronger without him.
They just fit, don't
you think, Kent?
Yeah, well, they won
championships with him.
Right, baby?
Yeah, but everyone knows
that Kobe was they young star.
They traded out the old model
for something new and improved.
Oh, well, everyone thought
Kobe was Mr. Wonderful.
Then he got caught
with his pants down.
True, he was accused.
But the charges were dropped.
Yeah.
But he lost a lot behind that.
Well, he still has the team.
I guess when you get
right down to it,
he was just the better package.
Oh.
No, Brooke.
Baby.
You don't have to leave
on my account, all right?
I thought I was doing something
that would make you happy.
But clearly, I was wrong.
No, it's... it's...
It's not like that.
It's always like that, Kent.
Why is she even here?
You invited me to come
see the game with you.
God, you think William
would do this to my sister?
Oh.
You know what?
Don't follow me.
All right?
You just stay your ass here.
Aw.
Oh, shit.
Drive it to the hole!
Penetrate!
Ugh.
The playoffs are
gonna be good though.
There's some good match ups.
Yeah.
Yeah, it looks like it.
Wanna sit down?
Yeah.
That's cool.
That was a good game, right?
You see that three
pointer at the buzzer?
[WOOSH] That was hot.
Yeah.
Definitely.
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah, sure.
Is everything OK
with you and Brooke?
Off the record?
Off the record.
It could be better.
Oh, gotcha.
Brooke sure is a lucky girl.
Somebody should tell her that.
You don't think she knows?
I think Brooke sees
what she wants to see,
and that's unfortunate.
That's not a
Brooke thing, Kent.
That's a woman.
Trust me.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
But, I... I just don't know
what got into her today.
I mean, wilding on me like
that and then storming out?
I... I just... I don't know.
Well, speaking from
experience, women just
want to know that their
Mr. Right is really
who he says he is.
I mean, the last
thing you want to do
is come home two nights
before your wedding
and find your man in the
shower with your roommate.
True story?
Yeah.
That guy's an idiot.
Tell me about it.
Most are.
And maybe that's what
us women are afraid of.
But I haven't done anything.
And I mean, I keep on
getting tested, you know?
I'm just beginning to wonder
if it's even worth it anymore.
Really.
Well, call me sappy.
I mean, even with all the
craziness I've been through,
I still believe in soul mates.
What about you?
I believe people mess
things up all the time,
but you can't...
You can't hold it
over somebody's head forever.
You know what I mean?
It's just too much...
(BOTH) Pressure.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've... that pressure
thing can be really tricky.
It can make you think
in ways and do things
you wouldn't normally do
but maybe you need to do.
Have you ever felt like that?
Yeah, but, uh, you should
never act on those urges, right?
No, you should.
You just... you
shouldn't fight it.
Um.
Look, uh, uh, I can't.
I can't do this.
I... I gotta go, OK?
I gotta go.
It's a shame.
I mean, I shouldn't
be this good.
You know what I mean?
I mean, come on,
man, nothing but net,
to the bottom of the
net, with my eyes closed.
[SIGHS]
Yo, Kent, what's
up with you, man?
You're right.
What is wrong with me?
I... I think Brooke's
right, though.
I... I don't see how
she could trust me.
What'd you do, K?
What'd you do?
KENT (OFFSCREEN): Nothing.
What'd you... don't...
You dirty... you...
No, your mind is in the gutter.
You... you was here wit your...
No, no, no, no, no.
Yes, you did.
Yes.
Did you pound it like
this? [MAKING NOISES]
No, no, no.
Hell no.
DOUG (OFFSCREEN): Yes, you did.
None of that.
Hey, Doug, can you,
um, give us a minute?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
(UNDER BREATH) Stop.
Stop.
Stop it.
He's an idiot.
You already know that about him.
That's just what he does.
So, um, what's up
with the cold shoulder?
Nothing.
I just... no cold shoulder.
It's all right.
Look, Kent, if this is about
the other day, I'm sorry.
I just... I got caught
up in the moment.
It didn't mean anything.
Really?
It didn't mean anything?
No, of course not.
We didn't do anything.
Look, I have everything
I need for the story.
So let's call it a wrap.
I'm taking you out tonight.
We're celebrating.
Oh, no, no, no.
Let's just do a
rain check on that.
Nope.
Not a chance.
Geisha House, nine o'clock.
Hot sake and a beer.
And quickly, please,
before I die of boredom.
Sake, huh?
I thought you didn't drink
when you were on the job.
Who said I'm on the job?
Oh, no.
They have karaoke tonight?
You're in trouble.
MAN (OFFSCREEN):
Hot sake, ma'am.
Thank you.
Nice.
Enjoy.
Oh, I will.
And we're going to
need two more of these.
Two more?
Ooh.
Hmm, yes.
No, no.
Drink up.
It's hot.
You know that's
like 100 degrees?
Damn.
Sure you don't want this?
No, no no.
I'm good.
Appreciate it.
Fine.
Wow.
You, uh... you really going in.
Ah, that's some stuff.
Ooh.
Actually, make that four more.
Oh, Jesus.
Damn.
That's like the seventh one.
OK.
Hey, be careful now.
Oh, my god.
[SIGHS]
Ladies and gentlemen,
this next song
is dedicated to
that sexy chocolate
brother sitting all
alone in the back.
Kenton Hughes, this is for you.
[R&amp;B_MUSIC_PLAYING]
Oh.
[MIC FEEDBACK]
Damn.
Can't tell, right?
No, you can't.
I mean, you can
tell me if you're
like some kind of Pointer
Sister or something.
Oh, I shouldn't have done that.
I really should
not have done that.
No, no.
You actually were really good.
I liked it.
See, this is why I don't drink.
Do I have a knot?
No, I think you'll be OK.
Well, I would really
be OK if I could...
If you could what?
Man, you better...
What'd you say?
Cut it out.
If you could what?
No.
How long have you and
Brooke been together?
What does that matter?
Stop.
Oh, my god.
You wilding.
I'm not.
I'm serious.
My head is hurting.
I think I maybe had
a little too much.
No, man, you had
like five sakes.
You went in.
I did not have that many sakes.
Yes, you did.
OK, maybe I had a little bit.
But my head is
really hurting now.
All right.
You have some kind of,
like, headache medication
in the kitchen or something?
I do.
I'll take that.
Where is it?
No.
Where's your
headache medication?
It's over there.
It's in the... it's
over that way.
Oh, god.
Where?
Your room?
No, it's in the top
shelf on the left.
Find it.
Well... What?
Target?
What?
What is... Is He True?
The hell is this?
Likes basketball, neo soul.
Wow.
[SIGHS]
Oh, man.
What?
[SIGHS]
[DOOR CREAKING]
You know, I didn't
call in a favor
and shut this place
down for you not to eat.
You know I don't
like surprises.
Oh, then you're
gonna hate this.
It smells good.
Mm, you should eat.
What do you have
up your sleeve?
Oh, nothing.
Just calm down.
You have something
up your sleeve.
You ladies remember
each other, right?
Mandy, I'm so glad you're here.
Please, have a seat. please
Thank you.
Mandy, Brooke.
Brooke, Mandy.
Wait a minute.
Babe, I got something for you.
Baby, open this please.
It's for you.
(UNDER BREATH) How you doing?
Gentleman test?
Yeah, that's what
I just call the way
you used to test
me to, you know,
see if I would
open doors for you
or offer my jacket to
you if you were cold.
You know, chivalry stuff.
And I was honored to be your
knight in shining armor.
Honesty test.
Oh, yeah.
You remember that
one, don't you?
This girl is so crazy.
You were so obsessed
about me telling you
the truth all the time.
Yeah.
And I... I didn't mind, either.
I mean, even when you
went behind my back
to verify my stories.
But I passed that
test too, didn't I?
You sure did, baby.
You sure did.
Let's see here.
Yeah.
And there was the...
There was the career
test, financial responsibility
test, family man
test, sense of style test.
Damn, that's... that's a
lot of tests, isn't it?
But... but I endured them
all because, in my eyes,
you were worth it.
OK.
You know what?
This is...
No, no.
Mandy, come on now.
Relax.
It's all good.
Chill.
I want you to see this.
I tried this before, but
it didn't go so well.
But, uh, this time I
think I got it right.
So let's lift our glasses.
Mandy, please, lift your glass.
Here's a toast.
Here's to no more tests.
Come on, Mandy.
No party pooper.
Mm.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, one more thing.
I got one more surprise for you.
This is the kicker.
You are going to love this.
OK.
All right-y.
What have we now?
Unbelievable.
Yeah, you both fail.
Brooke, uh-uh.
You know, I know I wasn't
perfect in our relationship.
But I was faithful
to you, even when
I had to face temptation
that you sent to me.
And the ironic thing is that
the... the one guy that you
compare me to, the one
person that you think
is just totally perfect,
Sophia's Mr. Wonderful...
He couldn't even pass this test.
Good evening, ladies.
How did he get this, Mandy?
Mm.
Sophia?
I'm in here, honey.
You know, we were
expecting to see you
last night seeing as though you
thought Kent was gonna propose
and everything.
Yeah, well, I was
wrong about that.
Girl, don't worry, honey.
That man is gonna
propose because I
can see how much he loves you.
No, Sophia.
I was really wrong.
What happened?
Kent found out that I
hired the man stealer.
Now he won't speak to me.
Wow.
Yeah.
Anyways, it was pretty dramatic.
I'm sorry, Brooke.
But you know what?
I can't blame him.
I'm sorry, honey.
People don't always
want to be tested.
Look.
OK, baby, look, OK,
you made a mistake.
OK, people make mistakes.
It happens.
But love... love can
cover up all the hurt
that we cause other people.
Well...
What?
Kent said something
about William.
[SCOFFS] What?
He said that, um...
What?
Something about he didn't
pass the test himself?
What?
You know what?
Don't.
Don't even go there, OK?
Because it's not
about me and William.
All right?
And whatever you think
you know, you don't.
OK?
Sophia.
What, Brooke?
What are you saying?
Sophia, come on.
You and William are
like the ideal couple.
OK, so what?
Yes, we have problems.
We do.
Oh, gosh.
You have to stop
comparing yourself to me.
Be you, honey.
Do you.
Just because we
have problems... that
doesn't mean that you and Kent
are going to have problems, OK?
People put too much
demand on love and this
and that and the other, OK?
If you love that man,
then be with that man.
But stop testing that man.
Call him.
I don't know how much
good that's gonna do.
Listen, honey.
Call him.
And you tell him you're sorry.
And even if he's
not listening, you
keep telling him over and over
and over, until he does listen.
But you gotta be
ready to change.
And you gotta be ready to trust.
You hear me?
I hear you.
Stop comparing yourself to me.
Hey, baby.
Oh, let me guess.
Y'all must be talking
about men again.
[CHUCKLES]
You know it.
All right, baby.
I'll be in here if
you need me, OK?
OK.
And, uh, you know, thanks
to Mr. Hartsfield Jr,
who is well into his 90s.
And to this very
day, every Saturday,
he still comes here
and volunteers.
Yeah.
He's a great guy, too.
Real cool.
Um, but if you
look over here, we
have examples of
some of the equipment
that they used, like, in
the '30s, '40s, '50s, '60s.
Uh, somebody die?
On your way to a funeral?
He doesn't want
to see you, Mandy.
So...
Oh, no, no, no.
It's OK, man.
I mean, unless she here to do
something for your profile.
Mandy, right?
That's your name?
Mandy?
Is that her?
I just came here
to apologize to you.
I'm really sorry,
Kent, for everything...
No, no, no.
You don't have to apologize, OK?
'Cause we're done.
Kent, I said I'm sorry.
I mean, was it some kind
of game or something?
A challenge?
Does it really matter?
Hell yeah.
(WHISPERING) I put myself
out there like that.
You get that?
I understand, Kent.
You know, I... I felt things too.
I feel things for you, things
I didn't expect to feel.
I... at the end of the
day, you are not mine.
You're hers, and I get that.
And to answer your question, no.
It wasn't a game.
But if you want my advice,
don't take the easy way out.
Forgive Brooke.
Stop it.
And rejection has never been
something that has bothered us
or deterred us,
ever, especially me.
I was not expecting
to feel like this.
[SIGHS] What was I thinking?
Wow, you really liked him.
I... [KNOCK_ON_DOOR] Who's that?
Hmm.
Hi.
Uh, Mandy?
Can I come in?
Sure.
Are you... are you good?
I'm good.
OK.
I'll... I'll call you later.
Thanks, Nat.
NATALIE (OFFSCREEN): Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Look, if you're looking for a
fight, Brooke, this is not it.
No, I'm not.
I... I'm here to say that
you were right, sort of.
Have a seat.
This test... it was
a bad, bad idea.
I don't know.
I was hoping to find
something horrible about Kent.
I just found something
horrible about myself.
Well, for whatever it's worth,
this has never happened before.
And I could tell when
I met Kent that this
was gonna be different.
He really is a great guy.
Yeah.
1%, right?
You said it.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's a... he's a
great guy, isn't he?
It took me too long
to realize that,
and now he won't speak to me.
So...
You're not the only
one he won't speak to.
He'll forgive you for that.
You know, it's not your fault.
Me, not so much.
Look, Brooke, to be
honest, I could have
and I should have stopped it.
But with the bet between
you and I and Kent
being such a challenge, I just...
I wasn't thinking straight.
Me and my challenges.
Mandy, you were
only doing your job.
Me, not so much.
You know, I haven't
been a good girlfriend.
So I don't blame
Kent if he never
wants to see me again or
give me another chance.
And honestly, I don't
deserve another one.
So, um, I guess you
won on a technicality.
Well, you did gift wrapped
him and sent him to me.
You don't have anything
to worry about, Brooke.
He's coming back to
you, return to sender.
Yeah, well, we'll
see about that.
Does your fee include
a... a drink on the house?
I think I can make that happen.
Woo, thank you.
K. K, have you been listening
to what I'm saying, brah?
I brought you here to
get you out of your funk.
Look around.
Booty, booty, booty,
booty rocking everywhere.
What's up, baby?
Come on.
Look around you.
Look... at all these
women in here.
Look at that one.
She got low self
esteem right there.
That's good for you.
You want somebody
in your lowly state.
You know what I'm saying?
To get back in the saddle,
if you know what I mean.
No, it's not gonna happen, man?
Why not?
Why not, Kent?
Huh?
Why not?
You got eye problems?
Look around.
Eh.
I'll pass.
Who are you, and what have
you done with my friend Kent?
Stop it, OK?
Stop it.
I know seven dudes
right now that'd
give their left one
to have your problem.
What is wrong with you?
That's just what it is, though.
It's a problem.
It is not.
I don't what to do.
It is not a... both of
them, at the same dang
time, a menage a three,
menage a four if she a Gemini.
Look, do it.
Oh, man, damn.
You play too much.
This is serious, man.
Kent, Kent, hold on.
Hold on.
All right.
Let's talk.
No, let's talk.
All right?
Wow, I'm Not.
Really good at this,
so I'm just going
to give it to you straight.
Um, you acting
like a girl, dude.
This is your idea
of being serious?
Excuse me.
Oh.
So you are serious.
What's up?
What's up is that
your... your choice
really isn't that
confusing, K. It's Brooke.
Yeah, look.
I know.
I know I've been rooting
for the visiting team.
But I'm saying, over the
last couple of weeks,
man, she showed me something.
Yeah.
Hey, I guess that's
the problem too.
Like, I know what I'm
getting with Brooke.
But I'm kind of
wondering what it
would be like to get with Mandy.
Right?
Stop wondering, OK?
Stop, OK?
Stop.
We got a purpose in life.
God put us here
for a reason, OK?
Mine... [POUNDS HANDS
TOGETHER] Stop.
You really need
to make that sound?
That's me.
This... yes.
Stop, don't run.
Wow.
- Don't run.
- Wow.
That's me.
All right?
You the one that thinks
with his big brain.
Not according to Brooke.
Look, brah, I know
Mandy is hot, all right?
I'm saying she's sexy.
She's got junk in the trunk.
Legs be all smooth
looking, and toes
be just thicker than a $4
milkshake and grits on Monday.
I'm telling you, baby...
Where was I going?
I don't know.
But I like where you were at.
Stop.
Stop, stop, stop.
The point... the point
is, yes, Mandy's hot.
But dawg, she's a fantasy, man.
And trust me.
I know a thing or
two about fantasies.
You don't wanna end up
like me, chasing fantasies.
All right.
So what are you trying
to say, Confucius?
Well, grasshopper,
what I'm saying
is the grass isn't
always greener.
Tend to your own lawn.
Keep watering the
grass you've been
watering for the
past four years, man.
Brooke loves you,
K. She loves you.
So what?
She made a mistake.
Big deal.
OK, everybody makes mistakes.
You too.
Stop playing.
Stop sitting over there,
acting like you... you all Mr.
Innocent, like you
ain't... come on, son.
Stop.
You know?
I mean, dawg,
without forgiveness,
how this love thing gonna work?
That's deep, man.
Run that back.
Say that again, the...
The forgiveness thing.
Oh, I... I said
that, you know, how
this love thing gonna
work without forgiveness?
(UNDER BREATH) That's so nice.
Stop.
(UNDER BREATH) That's nice.
- Stop.
- (UNDER BREATH) I like that.
You know what?
Stop.
I mean, I...
Brah...
I never knew.
Brah, I said I'd watch you.
I never knew it was there.
Really?
And you went there.
Don't.
Stop it.
Don't touch me.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I got to admit, I... I was... I
was a little skeptical coming
to a company that was as
old as yours, understand.
I didn't think you guys knew how
to market us in a relevant way.
But I am impressed.
Taking the old school and
then flipping it to classy?
That's... that's what
we're all about.
That's great.
I... I gotta be honest.
I didn't know what
to expect at first.
But, um, I have total
confidence in Brooke's abilities
and her instincts.
Thank you, sir.
I mean, we are
Phoenix Marketing.
So we rise from the
ashes of the old.
And what do we do?
We make something new.
See?
You like that?
That's what I'm talking about.
- There it is.
- Yes.
It's right there, right?
Yes.
You gentlemen excuse me.
I'm gonna mingle a little bit.
OK.
- And we'll talk a little later.
- All right.
- All right?
- Come back.
All right.
I definitely will.
She's one of the best.
Yeah?
Yeah, she's one of the best.
I didn't think you'd come,
but I'm really glad you did.
Hey... hey, Doug.
Yup.
Yeah, I didn't think I
was gonna come either.
But, uh, old friends gotta
support friends, right?
Right.
Right, right, right.
I don't mean to interrupt
all the pleasantries,
but is that Danielle?
Yup, that's her.
She's Sophia's
eyes on the ground,
seeing as how she's letting us
use her house and everything.
So...
Right, right.
You good here?
Yeah, yeah, I'm good.
OK.
Not that you would
care, but fine.
Same Doug, huh?
Yeah.
Same old Doug.
It's really nice seeing you.
The place looks awesome.
Um, man, I can't
believe your sister
let you use the house
for all of this.
Right?
I mean, her and William
are away on this couples
counseling thing.
So the house has been empty.
That's good for them.
Yeah, it is.
Seems like everybody's
having a good time, though.
I mean, damn, who
would've thought
people were so into
'90s throw back parties?
Who would've thought that?
I wonder.
Yeah, well, I could
fill this entire place
with the things I don't know.
I took the advice
from an old friend.
And, um, here we are.
Wait a minute.
You... you took someone's advice?
Oh, damn, you must really
feel guilty about something.
I really do.
And I'm really sorry.
Look, uh, this isn't
the time or place
to discuss that, you know?
Let's just, um... just
try to get through this
the best way we can, OK?
Sure.
Of course.
Uh, would you like a drink?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Yeah?
A little thirsty?
Yeah.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Can I have this dance?
In front of all these people?
It's OK.
Come on.
Trust me.
OK.
You know how they
do in Chicago.
OK.
Hit it just like this.
- OK.
- Come on.
It's called stepping.
I just learned this too
when I went to travel.
Literally stepping.
Yeah, literally stepping.
This is how you do it.
Just do what I'm doing, OK?
OK.
Just relax.
I'm relaxing.
All right.
Cool.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna put
you in a spin real quick.
You ready for this?
OK.
Hold on.
Here we go.
Oh.
Ah.
That's real good.
I like that.
That feel good?
Yeah, that feels... feels good.
OK.
Hold on.
One more spin.
Here we go.
Oh, ooh.
Now you see what
happens when you let go?
Yes.
You see that?
All right.
Let me try this.
OK.
Do the dance move, OK?
All right.
Cool.
Let's see.
Oh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sorry.
You thinking all
the way out the box.
Oh, my gosh.
OK, OK.
So much for style points.
Yeah, for real.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, I uh... I'm
really happy I came tonight.
Me too.
Look, Kent, I know you
don't want to hear it.
But, um, I just want to tell
you that I'm very sorry.
No, seriously.
I'm sorry for hurting you.
I'm sorry for all the
tests, all the doubt,
all the comparisons that haven't
been fair to you, all the fear.
I'm sorry for trying
to change who you are.
You know, it's just... I
was so focused on trying
to have the perfect man and
the personal relationship
that I never stopped and
realized I had all that.
Um, and I totally
understand if you never
want to see me again because
after that Mandy fiasco,
I don't deserve another chance.
So that's it.
Um, and have a good night.
Wait.
You passed, Kent.
I failed.
Hey, I remember you.
Hey.
Are you here to
cause more fireworks?
Something like that.
Kenton Hughes and Brooke Moore
represent some of my best work.
They love each other a lot.
They've been together
for about four years,
and they just needed a
little help remembering.
Thanks for coming.
You know, I like pork chops.
Hey, listen, these
last few weeks
haven't really been anything
to write home about.
And, uh, there's
still some things
that we definitely
need to discuss.
I mean, you're saying that you
don't deserve another chance.
But it's not about deserving.
I mean, who can say I...
I deserve your love?
Without forgiveness, this love
thing doesn't stand a chance.
Look, um, about that test,
I, uh... I owe you an apology.
No.
Kent, this isn't your fault.
And I can't sit here and let
you apologize like it is.
Are either of us perfect?
No.
And we never will be.
But I put us in this position.
And baby, if your heart...
If it's big enough to let me
back in, Kent, I promise
you I will do my part
to fill your heart with
everything that I have,
all of me.
I promise you that.
I like that.
There's something else.
[CLEARS THROAT]
What?
I love you, Kenton Hughes.
I love you too, baby.
Will you have me?
You know, that... that's funny.
Um, [CLEARS THROAT]
I was about to ask
you the same thing.
Will you marry me?
Yes, baby.
Yeah?
My goober.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Put this on.
Make it official.
Ah, perfect.
Waitress, champagne please.
We are celebrating.
That's for you.
Perfect fit too.
I know, right? [INAUDIBLE]
I love you.
I love you too, baby.
Jennifer, sweetie, can you
run this over to table four?
Thank you.
Brooke and I learned
a couple of things,
mainly that love is
not about pass or fail.
It's about honesty and
commitment and trust.
I learned a few other too,
girl, but we won't go into that.
But you look good, Brenda.
It's good to see you.
You too.
Thank you.
Can I buy the lady a drink?
That depends.
On?
Tell me my drink.
Hmm.
That would be a pearl
lemon drop martini to go.
Yup, babe, my
work here is done.
Yeah, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
If you ever need my
services, call me.
I will.
Who's gonna call
whose parents first?
I don't know.
Girl, you probably should
because your dad doesn't really
like me.
No, he'll love
you, just like I do.
Oh.
Thank you.
Congratulations, you two.
You did it.
It's from Mandy.
Oh.
Right?
That's nice of her.
That's great.
And we did do it.
Yes, we did.
[MUSIC PLAYING]