(dramatic electronic music)
They're calling him
the Jackson Strangler.
Who is he?
Where is he?
(static crackling)
We have a little
bit more information
from the neighborhood's
pastor wife.
Yes.
If you know anything,
this is a tragic incident.
(static crackling)
And this is not the
time to be silent.
This is a very
tight-knit community,
and we need you to come forward.
Jackson Strangler needs
to be brought to justice.
Have you heard that,
Jackson Strangler?
We're coming for you.
I'm Michelle Mitchell,
and you're watching
Channel 10 News.
(static crackling)
Neighbors in the
community say that
the crime is typically
extremely low.
That's why they were
caught by surprise
when informed that the Jackson
Strangler has struck again.
(static crackling)
Yeah, it's, uh...
That's unfortunate.
You know, um, this hit me hard.
You know, I-I used to see her
around the neighborhood a lot.
(sighs) Didn't think it was
gonna happen here, you know,
this Jackson Strangler thing.
It's, um,
it's gotta stop.
It's, it's, it's too much.
Like, when, when do it end?
(singer vocalizing)
♪ Boy, you got me in my feelings
♪ Feels so unreal
♪ Said you'd never do this to me
♪ Never thought you'd be
the one to break my heart
♪ Said I loved you
from the start, babe
Yes, the Jackson
Strangler is at large,
and the manhunt has begun.
Now, police say there
are no witnesses.
He's believed to be a
Caucasian in his mid forties.
If you have any
details or information
regarding the attacks
that have been occurring,
you're asked to call
the police immediately.
Look, I'm gonna be honest.
Long as buddy don't
come around me and mine,
I'm good.
This one right here,
this my heart and
soul, you feel me?
♪ So many ways you
broke my heart
♪ So many ways disappointed me
♪ You lied, you cheated
♪ Ran out on me, and it's over
♪ It's over
♪ So many ways you
broke my heart
♪ So many ways disappointed me
♪ You lied, you cheated
♪ Ran out on me, and it's over
♪ It's over
♪ Over
♪ Ooh, it's over
♪ You broke my heart
♪ You lied to me
♪ Thought the world of you
♪ Ooh, it's over
♪ My blinds eyes can see
♪ Ooh, it's over ♪ It's over
♪ It's over
♪ Over
(thumping dance music)
Why you on these
dating sites anyway?
What up with old boy John,
you remember John
with the crusty feet?
He had crusty feet,
but he was real good to you.
First of all, I'm not
a little girl anymore.
I am a grown woman.
I'm trying to find a man,
I don't need you
telling me what to do.
Sylvester, you need to
find you something to do.
Okay.
[Bartender] Hi, what
can I get for you?
To my girl Tanya,
who just so happens to
finally gotten a real job
(chuckles) making some
real money downtown.
Thank God!
(friends laughing)
Maybe now you can
finally stop dancing.
Whoo-hoo!
Let me borrow a dollar.
Girl,
can I please get
my first paycheck
before you get to begging?
I should be asking you for
some money, Miss Lawyer.
Well, as long as
you're not asking me,
because the last time I checked,
I think you still
owe me 30 bucks
from the last time we hung out.
(Tanya mutters mockingly)
(friends laugh)
Jessica,
girl, it's like that old saying.
[Both] Long as I owe
you, you'll never go broke!
(both laughing)
[Jessica] Why do I
always feel so broke?
I don't know.
Probably because I
owe you money too.
(friends laugh)
That's a good one!
Girl, what's up with you?
That guy over there.
Do you see him?
Well, yeah, he's
right in front of us.
No.
Do you see him?
Girl, what are
you talking about?
I don't know.
He looks real familiar.
I think he's a killer.
(Elaine coughs)
A what?
Ooh, a killer.
Maybe he's got a gun, girls.
No.
Seriously.
I've seen that face on the TV.
(gasps) Wait.
I think she right.
I think that's the
Jackson Strangler.
No way.
Girls,
I think maybe you've had a
little too much to drink tonight.
First of all,
I don't drink.
And second of all,
I'm calling the police.
[Elaine] Mm-mm, no.
You can't do that.
[Tanya] And why not?
Because!
If that's the guy
we think it is,
this guy ain't no joke.
They can't find one
witness on this guy.
They all either come
up missing or dead.
Then that's a risk I'm
just gonna have to take,
now isn't it?
(Elaine sighs)
All right, but don't
say I didn't warn you.
You never listen.
(smooth R&B music)
(quiet hip hop music)
(metal rattles)
Man, how long we gotta
keep making these drop-offs?
Till my kids turn 18, goofy.
Well, how long is that?
(Pooch chuckles)
Man, why we keep going
through this every month?
How many kids do I got?
10.
From those 10, how
many are from my wife?
None.
Exactly.
Man, Pooch,
that's a long time.
I don't think I could do
that many deliveries, man.
How about you?
You wanna make 'em?
- I can do it.
- You wanna do 'em?
- Yeah.
- Go on, get the money
from this dude, man,
since he don't want to.
- You sure?
- Man, I got this.
Oh, you know what?
Fall back, fall back.
Check this one out.
You don't wanna make
the deliveries no more?
It's not a problem,
you just let me know,
all right?
We'll take care of everything.
'Cause anything can
happen to you, you know.
You can get shot
on the expressway,
come up missing.
But at least you
gave me a heads up
so I can find somebody
to replace you.
[Crew Member] Man, come on...
I got this, bro.
Come on, Pooch, you
would kill me, man?
Look, man, we got four
days to make these drops.
Some of my baby
mamas ain't nice.
Do me a favor,
count the money.
(low tense music)
(door thunks)
(door thuds)
[Dennis] It took
you long enough.
I had to get the rope.
What rope?
You said get the rope.
I didn't say get the rope.
I already put 'em
in the rug, man.
If I was gonna wait
for you and the rope,
she would have
turned like a mummy.
(scoffs) All right.
Who car is this?
Who you think it is?
It's that chick, no?
She's a nurse.
What, you think I change
profession overnight?
Stop asking these
dumb questions.
You know what?
Hurry up and get
her outta here, man.
I got a lot of stops to make.
Right.
Aren't you gonna help me?
I already did.
I get the bitch,
and you dump them.
And the trunk is open
for you, Cinderella.
Hurry up, man.
I always get the
short end of the stick.
(Dennis laughs)
You rather be like
the chick in the back
and be the short
end of this knife?
(both laugh)
Wait a minute...
Get the body outta here,
dump it in the river.
I gotta go.
I ain't got all day.
(door slams)
(Dennis sighs)
Hey!
She's not even wrapped up, man!
Okay, do it!
She heavy!
Hey, I need some help!
Jesus, man.
(door clunks)
(alert dings)
Gotta do everything myself.
(door slams)
You...
Man, you didn't
even wrap her, man.
You want me to
put a bow on it?
Come on, man.
This is your first time?
I mean...
(low tense music)
(door slams)
What's up?
He with you?
[Rashaad] I got him.
This guy's certifiable.
I can't get him to say a word.
Put him in the car,
I'll make him talk.
(door slams)
So what'd you do with the body?
What body?
Man, you gonna play stupid?
Who said that I was playing?
Okay, look, we gonna
do this one of two ways,
the hard way or my way.
You do the picking,
but either way,
you are gonna lose.
I got four witnesses that put
you at the scene of the crime.
Three.
What?
Yep.
As of right now, you
only got three witness.
The fourth witness is dead.
Say what?
Yo, Jacobs!
How many witnesses we
got in the Jackson case?
Well, we had four.
They found one of the ladies
beaten to death in her closet.
Husband came home,
put up his jacket,
found his old lady
(shutter clicks)
hanging there instead.
Oh, and get this,
they found the same
rope around her neck
as the others.
All signs lead to Dennis.
How is that possible?
He was in custody yesterday.
Well, your guess
is as good as mine.
(Rashaad sighs)
Hey, guys,
I know people.
You really think
it's just one of us?
(chuckles) I got a team.
And as of right now,
you only have one
body on your watch.
Do you wanna make it two?
Man, get this
animal outta here.
Yeah, it's about time
I get outta this car.
(door slams)
(deep dramatic music)
(phone chimes)
Hey, baby, I'm sorry.
(sighs) I got a
big case at work.
Yeah, I kind of figured.
But you could have called,
I've been waiting forever.
Hey, I'm sorry.
(Rashaad chuckles)
I'm sorry.
Did you order yet?
No, I was waiting for you.
Oh, okay.
(phone rings)
Hold on.
Okay, I gotta, I
gotta take this.
Just a second. Hello?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, slow down.
No, no, you are not
going to make that call.
Why would you?
(deep tense music)
Look, I'm trying to protect you!
And you...
Hello?
(Rashaad exhales sharply)
Look, baby, I-I gotta go.
Rain check, okay?
Rain check what?
You just got here!
And now I gotta go.
You can't.
But I will.
I need you!
I have to go home to my wife!
(insects chirping)
(door knocks)
No, I'm not as happy
as a caged bird. Free!
(Tanya laughs)
Hold on one second. Hold on.
(door squeaks)
(alarm beeps)
(Tanya laughs)
Say what?
(door thuds)
(scoffs) You know how I do.
(envelope rustling)
Hm.
(Tanya chuckles)
Yeah, well, look, when
the boys are away,
and it's just me
and my lonesome,
trust me, it's gonna
be a good night.
(Tanya laughs)
Girl, they went with my
mama to some oldies concert.
You know she always trying
to put 'em up on the dusties.
(laughs) Yeah.
What you mean,
"What about Alex?"
He's at Bible study.
But guess who finally
got the nerve?
(Tanya laughs)
Guess who finally got
the nerve to stop?
I'm tired.
Yeah, well, it's what's
best for me and my boys.
(Tanya laughs softly)
But I wouldn't have been able
to do it without you, girl.
You've been my rock.
(Tanya laughs)
Yeah.
I know.
(deep ominous music)
(phone thuds)
What are you doing here?
(intense dramatic music)
(Tanya screaming)
[Rashaad] Hey, baby.
Hey, babe.
Mm.
How you doing?
How was your day?
Bad. (laughs)
All on account of the
Jackson Strangler.
The Jackson who?
Strangler.
The guy, it's been
all over the news.
Oh, I've been swamped.
All right, so a
guy walks into a bar,
picks up random women,
two or three hours later,
they find 'em strangled.
- Wow.
- Mm-hmm.
And that's not the kicker.
This guy's been on the
run for three months.
No witnesses.
Dang, none?
Not one.
Hmm.
Wow.
(low soft music)
Where's your ring?
Huh?
Your ring.
Ah, it's...
I think it's...
I-I think my hand got
all sweaty at the office,
and I took it off,
and I just threw it on the desk.
The office?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, you,
you said you were working
in the field today,
said you weren't
going in the office.
- Huh?
- Said you weren't going
in the office.
- Huh?
- You said you weren't going
in the office.
Yes, I did!
No, no,
you said you weren't
going in the office,
and that was today
'cause I specifically
remember you saying today.
No, no, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
No, I didn't.
- You did!
- No, I didn't.
(Angie sighs)
Look, no, I didn't!
I mean, it could have
been today, yesterday,
could have been last year.
What difference does it make?
Can I just finish the story?
Okay, okay,
fine, fine, go ahead.
[Rashaad] Without
being interrupted?
Yes, please, do finish.
Please finish.
Okay.
Yes, go ahead.
Where was I?
Um...
No witnesses.
No witnesses, right.
Up until four ladies
come out of a bar
and see a woman getting into
the car with the suspect.
Okay, so you do
have some leads?
That's good.
No, it's bad.
Well, no, it's bad
because (sighs)
one of the women ended up dead.
- What?
- Yeah, the woman,
husband comes home,
opens the closet,
she's strangled.
So now we're down
to three witness.
And the funny thing is,
this murder has the same MO
of a guy we have in custody.
Okay, well,
but how can he be involved
if he's, he's in your custody?
I said the exact same thing.
(phone rings)
[Angie] (sighs) Weird.
Hello?
Hey, Jacobs, what's up?
What?
Where?
Lexington and what?
All right.
All right, all
right, I'm on my way.
Babe, I gotta go.
What is it?
What is it? W-wait, what?
- They found another-
- Wait, what?
They found another body.
You said Lexington?
Lexington and what?
(Rashaad sighs)
Rashaad, Lexington and what?
It's Lexington and Sixth.
Sixth?
Babe,
that's where Valerie
and Tanya lives.
I know, baby.
I know. I'll be back.
(deep unsettling music)
(camera shutter clicking)
I don't get it.
I was just on the
phone with her.
What did she sound like?
All right, I guess.
I mean, she was in a good mood.
Her, her kids were away,
she was enjoying her time.
She was happy to finally
be breaking off things
with this guy.
[Detective] Really?
Yeah.
Unfortunately, it
didn't go as planned.
Wow.
Is there anything
else you can think of?
(sniffs) Look, I just
need a moment, all right?
I'm Detective Williams.
Private Investigator Tony.
What do we got?
Well, no signs
of forced entry,
but this is
definitely a homicide.
[Rashaad] Hm.
We had blood that we sent
to the lab for processing.
Vic's in her mid
twenties, cute girl.
She lives here with her mother.
Her mom was out to a concert
and came home and found a rope
around her daughter's neck.
Daughter's name is-
- Tanya Griffin.
Oh, so you know her?
Yeah, um,
it's my wife's cousin.
Um,
Val, her mother, took my
wife in when she was a kid
after her mother had died, so...
They're, they're real close.
Oh my gosh, I can't imagine.
Wow.
Okay, I'm gonna keep a
close eye on this case.
- Okay.
- Okay?
And I want you to give
my regards to your wife.
I will, I will.
Okay.
We're gonna find
out who did this,
and when we do, it's
not gonna be pretty.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh.
I gotta get going.
Uh, my husband and I are
celebrating our 20th anniversary,
and I wanna get home quick
so I can celebrate
the 21st with him too.
So, but I'm pretty sure you
can handle all this, right?
Yeah. Yeah, I got it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey, take care of yourself.
[Rashaad] I will. You too.
[Tony] Okay, thanks.
(door squeaks)
(alarm chimes)
(door thuds)
(Angie breathing shallowly)
(tense somber music)
(Angie cries)
Angie,
what are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
I assumed you
weren't gonna tell me.
This is not the time or
place for this, all right?
I will talk to you
when we get home.
You get-
- You want me to
go home and wait
so someone else in my
family can get murdered
and you not tell me?
Babe, look, listen to me.
Now, don't do-
Do not call me babe!
You are wrong.
You knew she was a
witness in this case,
and you didn't do anything!
You didn't do anything!
Look...
Hey, Val.
Oh, auntie.
(Valerie cries)
(Valerie mutters indistinctly)
Oh, my baby girl.
They took my one and only.
(Valerie cries)
Somebody help me. (crying)
(Angie shushing)
It's all right.
It's okay.
It's okay. We'll
get through this.
Hey.
You know, Val, I
wish I could have...
(hand slaps)
You shut it.
I looked through her cell phone,
and I saw all the text
messages that you sent her.
What?
Oh yeah.
Your husband
knew that my baby
girl was in danger.
Oh, but he wanted
to play Mr. Columbo.
What is she talking
about, Rashaad?
Via text, and I'll quote,
"Don't worry about it.
I'll protect you."
How dare you try
to protect someone,
and you can't even
protect your own wife.
Look, Auntie Val, I-
- Only by marriage.
Ms. Thomas,
we need you to come with us to
go over some of the details.
Okay.
Listen,
I don't know what
you're gonna do,
and I don't know how
you're gonna do it,
but you better find out who
did this to my daughter.
Do you understand me?
Yes, ma'am.
(Angie sighs softly)
I'll see you at home.
Why?
(Dennis laughing)
Why not?
Look, man,
now, you hit that one girl,
and it's like, "Okay,
I'll take that one,"
but now you messed
with my family, man.
And why you gonna
mess with Tanya?
Why are you gonna
Tanya ain't done
nothing to anybody.
She, she's a good girl, man.
Who?
Tanya!
Man,
I didn't tell them to
knock off no Tanya.
And let me tell you something,
I took a lot of lives
off these streets,
but Tanya was not one of them.
But, uh,
I really like the name,
maybe I should have.
Well, if you didn't
do it, who did?
If it was my job to find out,
I would be the one
wearing the badge,
now, wouldn't I, my brother?
I ain't your brother!
It looks like you got
a lot of work to do.
Jacobs!
Take him, man.
(sighs) Here we go again.
(door slams)
(tense mysterious music)
I took a lot of lives
off of these streets,
but Tanya was not one of them.
[Rashaad] Hey, Val,
I wish I could've-
(hand slaps)
- [Valerie] You shut it.
I looked through her cell phone,
and I saw all the text
messages that you sent her.
[Dennis] It looks like
you got a lot of work to do.
♪ I'm praying
♪ And I won't get up
'til you answer me
♪ Establishing, solidifying
♪ 'Til you answer me
♪ Your relationship with
God through prayer
♪ I'm praying
♪ And I won't get up
'til you answer me
♪ Establishing, solidifying
♪ 'Til you answer me
♪ Your relationship with God
♪ Lord, I'm down
here on my knees
♪ Praying, Lord, please
hear my high pleas
All right, so you counted
it, it's all there, right?
- Yes, sir.
- All right.
Yo, am I gonna
get my shot or what?
Shut up, man!
Be smooth.
Man, shut up.
Be easy, be easy.
Give it to her, make sure
she know it's from me.
Put in one of them
little white envelopes
or something, you know.
I got you, boss.
All right.
All the time with you two, huh?
Ask him, man.
(Pooch sighs)
Come on, Pooch, you're
always blaming me, man.
♪ I'm praying
She will definitely be missed.
We're praying for
you, Mrs. Griffin.
Thank you.
Is everyone here?
I'm waiting for my
niece and her husband
and a few more close friends.
Okay.
Well, we'll be starting shortly.
Okay. Thank you,
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
Hey, sis.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
We are definitely praying
for you and your family.
If you need anything,
let us know.
We're here to serve
you today, okay?
God bless you.
Thank you. God bless you, too.
I cannot express
enough how sorry I am.
Please accept these condolences
and on behalf of your family.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you, baby, for coming.
Ma'am, may I extend
the condolences
of Officer Rashaad, myself,
and our fellow officers.
We are truly sorry
for your loss.
Thank you so much,
I appreciate it.
Thank you, thank you.
Ms. Griffin,
my wife and I are truly praying
for you and your family.
Your daughter spent a
tremendous amount of time
along with Brother Alex
doing anything and everything
to bless the house of the Lord.
And I am so happy
that she made it right
before she left us.
So if there's anything at all,
and I do mean anything,
we're here for you.
Please don't hesitate to call.
Thank you so much.
We're praying for
you, Ms. Griffin.
[Valerie] Thank you.
So sorry for your loss.
This is from Poochie.
(Valerie mutters)
I'll be right back.
[Pooch] Everything cool?
- Yeah, everything good, man.
- She done?
- Yes, sir.
- All right, what's up.
Yo, Pooch,
(tense hip hop music)
what you doing here, man?
(Pooch chuckles)
It's funny, I could
ask you the same thing.
Really?
Yeah, really.
See, I'm surprised to
see you here at all.
Especially considering
you the reason she dead
in the first place.
See now, when she was with me,
she had it made.
Nice cars, jewelry, all the
money she could ask for.
Then when she got with you
and joined this church,
that's when her
life spiraled down,
giving all her
money to that God.
Well, you know what
the good book says?
It's better to give than
to receive, my brother.
Yeah, well look
where that got her.
(Alex chuckles)
Pooch, you got it all wrong.
When Tanya got with me, her
life changed for the better.
(chuckles) It was
all in God's plan.
See, he allowed her to
get with a scum like you
so when she got with me,
she would know what a
real man looks like.
(Pooch chuckles)
I got you.
You and your goons can leave.
(deep somber music)
Baby.
You haven't said
anything to me all day,
and something's gotta give.
I mean, can we talk?
No, Tevin Campbell, we cannot.
We have nothing to talk about.
Oh.
Okay, because I thought
we would want to catch up,
seeing as you haven't talked
to me in a week and a half.
Why should I?
So you can leave the
important stuff out?
No, so that we can
be adults for once.
Yeah, right.
Coming from the
biggest kid I know.
Look, I know how
much you loved Tanya.
Okay? I was just
trying to protect you.
Protect me?
(low tense music)
How?
You were just trying
to protect yourself!
(Angie stammers)
Please, explain,
how in the world were
you protecting me?
Okay, this is a very
high-profile case.
Very high!
This isn't some hit-and-run
or some pickpocketing fiasco.
This man has a
14-person body count!
And unless you want to be 15,
you need to trust my judgment.
Trust?
Let's not,
let's not even talk
about trust right now.
Because you and I both know
that honesty is not exactly
your strong suit now, is it?
(Rashaad chuckles)
So this is what
this is about, huh?
Yes, and you
thought it wasn't?
(chuckles) No, I thought that
I heard that you forgave me.
Forgiven, yes.
Forgotten?
No.
No, well, they both
sound the same to me.
Yeah, right, well,
I guess you need to hear
a little bit better.
Go get your ears checked.
And you know, this
is not the first time
you kept something
major from me.
And every time I think the
last time is the last time,
guess who comes
out with the remix?
You got all those people
at that job fooled,
but I know you
very well, Rashaad.
No, no you don't
because if you knew me at all,
you would know I
was a changed man.
Changed where?
You couldn't change the
tire that's on your car
if you wanted to.
Besides,
I have proof of your infidelity.
(chuckles) No,
you have accusation.
And that's exactly
what you're gonna have
if you keep going like this,
nothing.
Mm-hmm.
You're right. Nothing.
That's what we've had
for the last 10 years.
Ever since you messed it up
with that thing from work!
And it's not my fault that you
haven't been able to fix it.
So will you please
just leave me alone?
Angie.
Angie! (sighs)
(Rashaad exhales sharply)
Ms. Griffin, what exactly
brings you in to see us today?
Well, the other day at
my daughter's funeral-
- Um, homegoing.
I'm sorry?
Um, when believers pass on,
we call it a homegoing,
not a funeral.
The saints, they returned
back to the Father.
And it is my understanding,
although Tanya always went
back and forth with God,
she got it right in
her final moments.
Yeah. Oh, whatever.
I know you told me
that if I ever needed anything,
not to be afraid to ask.
Oh yes, definitely.
We're always here to help,
especially for those
who were so generous,
such as Sister Tanya
was to our ministry.
Well, when I heard
you speak on her giving,
I got to thinking about
how much she really gives,
whether it's her
time, her energy,
her money.
Hmm.
I forgot all those countless
days she spent up in here
serving in the food
pantry, the bookstore.
Oh yes,
and I didn't mention
the prison ministry.
(laughs) Oh my goodness,
she was such a blessing.
Her and Alex used
to get up earlier
and minister to the imprisoned.
Always giving from the heart
and never asking for a dime.
I'm asking for it.
Oh?
(low tense music)
Yes.
I'm here to collect.
Um, to collect what?
Oh, you know!
All the money you owe her.
You see, my daughter was
not as much a businesswoman
as I am.
That's why you were
able to get over on her,
you'll find up until her death.
Um,
passing.
Excuse me?
Well, again,
believers don't die.
According to John 3:16,
"In him, we have
everlasting life."
We don't, um,
die, we just pass on.
Uh, yeah yeah.
Well, yeah,
as I said,
you'll find, to the exact date,
a list of all the days
she served at the church.
Um...
I'm confused.
Oh, don't be.
Each date is marked to a T
I even highlighted
a couple for you.
Um...
Ms. Griffin, (chuckles)
I think that we might have
some type of misunderstanding.
Here at Fellowship
Christian Church,
we pride ourselves in making
sure that each and every one
of our people are
well taken care of,
whether it's
financially, physically,
and especially spiritually.
[Valerie] Oh, well-
- Our members are in
full understanding
that they served in
a voluntary basis
and that the fruits from
their seeds are sewn
and manifested in heaven.
I do understand.
But I'm not a member,
my daughter was,
even though I begged
her not to join
and waste her time with
all this foolishness,
especially with her mother
being a proud atheist.
Oh yes,
that's right.
I don't even believe in
this so-called God of yours.
I don't know, what time is it?
- Um, this-
- Oh, that's all right,
I gotta go.
Go ahead, look over
those documents.
My QuickPay information is
right at the bottom there.
Oh, and by the way,
as long as you get everything
paid in full by next week,
there'll be no reason for me
to get my legal team involved.
You have been so kind.
Thank you for your time.
You have a wonderful day.
[Jessica] Mrs. Jones.
Yes?
Is your husband around?
Who are you?
I was actually, um, a really
good friend of your cousin's,
and this is my friend Elaine.
We both were.
She's a little too nervous to
come with me today, though.
Um,
anyway, we think we know
who killed your cousin,
and it's not who
everyone thinks it is.
What do you mean?
Listen,
I gotta go.
Both our numbers are on here.
You call me later,
and I'll be able to talk
to you about it then.
Okay?
Uh, wait a minute,
why didn't you just
go to the police?
It's really complicated.
We know how much you
loved your cousin,
and we wanted to tell you first.
I'm sorry, I gotta go.
(deep tense music)
Listen, I don't
know what's going on,
but some strange woman just
rolled up on me on the street
and said that she knows
who really killed Tanya.
[Rashaad] What do you
mean who killed Tanya?
The Jackson Strangler did it.
Are you serious?
Yes!
Now, to be honest,
I thought she was one of
your little girlfriend
at first, but-
See,
see, now you're playing around.
Stop playing.
I'm being serious. Come on!
[Rashaad] Okay, what
exactly is she saying?
Did she even mention the
Jackson Strangler at all?
Well, she says she
doesn't even think
the Jackson Strangler had
anything to do with it.
[Rashaad] What?
Are you serious?
That's ridiculous.
He had everything to do with it.
Who else could it be?
That's what the woman said.
[Rashaad] Okay, someone
like her is pretty dangerous
by herself.
We better put her in
witness protection
before she ends up dead too.
Okay, well, she did
give me her number,
so I'll text it to you.
[Rashaad] Yes, text
it to me right away.
And hey, stay safe out here.
These people are crazy.
Of course.
[Rashaad] You never
know who's trying to get
to you to get to me.
Okay.
[Rashaad] I mean it.
All right, bye.
♪ Never thought you'd be
the one to break my heart
♪ Said I loved you
from the start, babe
♪ So many ways you
broke my heart
♪ So many ways disappointed me
♪ You lied, you cheated
♪ Ran out on me, and it's over
♪ It's over
♪ So many ways you
broke my heart
♪ So many ways disappointed me
♪ You lied, you cheated
♪ Ran out on me, and it's over
♪ It's over
♪ Over
♪ Ooh, it's over
♪ You broke my heart
♪ You lied to me
♪ Thought the world of you
♪ Ooh, it's over
♪ My blinds eyes can see
♪ Ooh, it's over ♪ It's over
♪ Oh ♪ It's over
♪ It's over
♪ Over
I miss you.
I miss this.
Yeah, whatever.
Angie, what do you
want from me, huh?
I want the truth.
I want the truth
from my husband.
Do you want the truth
or do you want to hear
what you want to hear?
Because I can give you either,
but you and I both know
that you're only going to
accept what you want to hear
'cause you're too immature
to accept the truth.
B-but, I'm immature?
(low dramatic music)
(Angie laughs)
Yes.
Are you serious?
You're immature. All right?
I mean, look at
how you're acting.
Look at,
look at you.
You barely talk to me.
You're not cooking.
We're not even intimate
anymore at all.
You're fussing,
y-you're cussing,
you're moping around like
you're a little baby.
Now, if that's not immature,
then I don't know what is.
It's called a
woman that's scorned.
No, it's called a
woman that's selfish.
H-how am I selfish, Rashaad?
Because I want my
husband all to myself
and not sharing him with half
of the women in the city?
It ain't half!
O-oh...
Then what is it?
As a matter of fact, um,
what is this?
- Oh, look, Angie-
- Oh. (stammers)
That's right.
You stand there, and
you think real hard
about the lie you
got for this one.
- Angie-
- Don't,
don't touch me.
(singer vocalizing)
♪ Boy, you got me in my feelings
(Rashaad coughs)
(door slams)
Hey, baby.
Shouldn't you be at work?
Hey.
I didn't go to work today.
What, you not feeling well?
(chuckles) I'm fine.
Actually,
I'm feeling the best
I've felt in years.
Right.
So, why aren't you at work?
I told the partners
it was moving day.
(both laughing)
Moving day?
I mean, I saw a truck outside,
but I didn't think
it was for us.
Oh, it-it's not for us.
It is for you, though.
(laughs) Oh, it's for me?
Oh yeah.
(deep dramatic music)
You didn't think I would put
up with your mess forever,
did you?
Now see, girl,
why you wanna go
even start anything?
Oh, no, no no no no.
Because you, you want to cheat
and have all kind of babies
outside of this marriage.
Oh yeah.
Mm-hmm.
All the baby mama drama
and the comma going on.
You know what?
Your clothes are in that
suitcase over there,
and my brothers are here,
and they will help you
pack the rest of your crap.
Now, how'd Jarvis get a key?
I gave it to him,
silly. (laughs)
O-oh, I forgot to tell you.
Jarvis, hey, bro.
What's up?
He's taking your room.
You know that man
cave you love so much?
Yeah.
Him and my other brother,
they gonna just move in here
and enjoy this big,
beautiful house with me
until I get a real man who
will help carry the weight
that you were supposed
to be holding.
Girl, you better tell me
what's going on right now.
I just did.
You're out, he's in.
Okay, you're crazy,
and if you think for one second
I'm going to go nowhere.
You know what?
Jarvis, handle that.
Jarvis, handle that!
- I ain't going nowhere!
- [Jarvis] Man, go to sleep!
(Jarvis grunts)
(blow thuds)
(Rashaad snoring)
Y'all take him
out to the truck
while I finished
packing his stuff.
Oh wait!
(Angie sighs)
Baby,
those are the
divorce papers, okay?
Make sure you sign
them when you wake up.
Get him outta here.
[Jarvis] All right, let's go.
(deep dramatic music)
Live from Channel 10,
we're bringing you
the latest details
on the disappearance
of the mother of three,
Jessica Turner.
Police say that
she was found dead
just two and a half
miles from her residence.
Now, if you're not familiar
with who this woman is,
let me catch you up.
Jessica is a key witness to
the Jackson Strangler murder
and also has information
on the death of her friend,
who's also a key witness.
Now, with Jessica, there
is foul play involved,
and the autopsy reports are
waiting to be confirmed.
If you have any information
about this case,
please contact your local
authorities as soon as possible.
I'm Michelle Mitchell,
and you're watching
Channel 10 News.
(tense unsettling music)
Hey.
[Elaine] Hey, you hear
about what happened?
Yeah, I just saw the news.
[Elaine] Look, I'm just
trying to keep it all together.
It's just so much, you know.
I'm so sorry.
[Elaine] I'm so
sorry for tearing up.
No, no, no,
don't apologize for crying.
- Look,
- It was your friend.
[Elaine] if there's
anything I can do to help out,
an end to this.
I'm just so tired of
murders, you know.
I just want-
Listen.
We need to talk, face-to-face.
[Elaine] As a matter of fact,
I have an idea of
what's going on here.
I was thinking the same thing.
[Elaine] Can you have your
husband meet me at the station?
Yeah.
[Elaine] I'm ready to talk.
Okay.
[Elaine] Please, have him
meet me as soon as possible.
Okay.
[Elaine] Okay. Goodbye.
(tense dramatic music)
(Rashaad coughs)
Rough night?
You could say that.
So I understand you were
the last person to talk
to Ms. Griffin.
Yes.
It wasn't exactly the greatest
experience, but, of course,
I am one to believe that
everything happens for a reason.
(Rashaad laughs)
Yeah, that's what they say.
I just wish I understood
the reason for this one.
Maybe I could have done more.
Tell me more.
You want the long version
or the short version?
(scoffs lightly)
Well, whatever.
I got water, I'm good.
Well, Tanya,
she always had a
thing for married men.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't know if it was,
like, obsession or what,
but she always talked about
it like a fantasy, you know?
Then, one day about
nine years ago,
she put it into action.
They met at a club,
- Mm.
- Had drinks,
exchanged numbers,
now the rest is in the air.
Nine years later,
a couple STDs,
two kids.
So, no divorce?
Right.
My girl always fell
for the okie dokie.
He always promised
to leave his wife,
but he never did.
Okay, (sighs)
but what does this have to
do with the other night?
A lot.
You see, she had met
this new guy, Alex,
a good man.
Worked 9-to-5, church guy.
They hit it off quickly,
and she was finally starting
to leave Mr. Married Man alone.
Mm-hmm.
That night,
she had to see him one
last time to cut all ties.
She had been hinting at
telling his wife everything.
You know, since she
changed her life,
she wanted to make
everything good.
So how did you feel about
her dating married guys?
I hated it.
Ah?
(low intense music)
I knew she deserved better.
She knew she deserved better.
Well, did you ever
express that to her?
Absolutely.
Plenty of times, but never
really ended too well.
(thumping dance music)
(Tanya laughing)
Girl, when do you
get enough of this?
Girl, enough of what?
Being that man's secret.
(Tanya laughs)
Girl, bye.
What she doesn't
know won't hurt her.
But it will
eventually hurt you.
(laughs) Girl,
I am in love.
You do remember what
that feels like, right?
Or have you been single
for so long you forgot?
No.
I'm waiting on God
to send my husband,
rather than take someone else's.
I'm waiting.
You do remember what
that feels like, right?
What?
Waiting.
Or have you been easy
for too long you forgot?
(Tanya laughs)
This is why we wear these,
to remind ourselves
what we're waiting for.
Girl, whatever.
He's my sons' father.
No, he's their mother's trap.
And I promise you,
if you don't let Christ
free you from that snare,
the only end will be death.
Is that a threat?
No. That's a prophecy.
And you better take your heed.
Your kids don't even
know who their daddy is.
[Tanya] What do you know?
I know enough.
(Rashaad sighs heavily)
Wow.
Kids never knew their father?
Mm, that's cold-blooded.
Yikes.
(Rashaad moans)
What's wrong?
I just...
I-I hate guys like that.
Sounds like a POI.
POI?
Person of interest.
You think so?
I mean, yeah, man
cheating on his wife?
You know, sounds like
highlights from my life.
I mean, except for
the kids, you know.
My wife didn't want
'em, I didn't either.
Um, it's a typical case.
Guy wants to whack
off his side piece
just to get a clean slate.
Wow.
I never thought of that.
You don't get paid to think.
I do.
Do you have a
description on this guy?
I don't.
Wait. (scoffs)
What? You said they were
together for nine years.
Yeah, she was, not me.
I never even seen the guy.
I wouldn't have even
thought he was real
if it wasn't for the kids.
That's the thing with Tanya.
She kept this man top secret.
Victoria's Secret classified,
if you know what I mean.
Hmm.
Well, did you ever
meet the "nice guy"?
Alex?
Of course.
Every Sunday, we all went
to the same church, and...
Well, I mean, me and Alex did.
And then, one day,
he ran into her,
and they clicked, and she started
coming to church with him.
(Elaine chuckles)
It's kind of funny
how it all worked out.
Like the Word says,
some plant,
others water,
but God gives the increase.
I was planting.
Alex was watering.
(deep hip hop music)
Hey, let me holler at you.
Boy, bye.
I got a man.
First of all, I didn't
even ask you that.
So what you want?
(Alex laughs)
Look at you.
You so used to someone trying
to take something from you,
you're not used to a brother
trying to give you something.
And what is it that
you want to give me?
My number.
(scoffs) Boy, bye.
I do not have time for this.
No, no, no, no,
I'm, I'm just joking.
I'm just joking.
Unless you really want it.
See?
(laughs) No, for real though.
For real, for real.
My church is a
couple of blocks up.
You should pop in
on us one Sunday.
No, I'm good.
Come on, it'll
be good for you.
Look, I ain't been to church
since I was, like, five.
I doubt I got anything to wear.
I gotta go.
Can I at least get your name?
Well, I guess
she saw him again,
and he kept asking,
and one thing led to another,
and next thing you know,
they were like glue.
You never saw one
without the other.
(Tanya sighs)
So, what are we calling this?
(chuckles) What?
This.
Us. (chuckles)
What are we, uh,
what, are we dating?
(Alex laughs)
Nah.
See, a real man?
A real man don't date.
He courts.
Oh.
Well, then I guess
you consider yourself
to be a real man then?
Well, yeah.
Tanya, when you think of a date,
you think of the
calendar, right?
Yeah.
Okay, and if there's
something on that date
that doesn't fit your schedule,
what do you do?
You try to find one that does.
Exactly. You
adjust your schedule.
Tanya, I don't have
to adjust my schedule
because I found you.
That's deep.
No, baby girl,
that's favor.
Tell me something.
What is it that you see in me?
Hmm. Honestly?
I see a sweet,
beautiful,
intelligent,
and wonderful woman of God.
(Tanya laughs)
She's laughing at me. (laughs)
What's funny?
It's just...
That's not what I see
when I look at
myself in the mirror.
Really?
No.
You see, I see a
woman that's broken,
torn,
not worthy.
Plus,
I have a past.
It's time you
forget about the past.
You know the story
of Hosea and Gomer?
(chuckles) I told you I
needed to brush up on my Bible.
Well, let me enlighten you.
You see, um, Gomer
knew a lot of men,
but Hosea had
married her anyway.
He accepted her for her.
He forgot about her past.
When a man loves a woman,
I mean truly loves a woman,
there's nothing he
won't do to be with her
and only her.
Can I be desperately
honest with you?
I wouldn't have
it any other way.
I know we've been
talking for a few weeks,
and I like you, I really do.
I mean, you're really dope,
(laughs) but-
- You're seeing
someone else, right?
Yeah.
Tanya, I'm not stupid.
So what, you stalking me?
Well, not stalking
you exactly.
But I have seen him
around with his wife.
You realize that's not who
God has for you, right?
Look,
he says he's gonna leave her.
(laughs) Yeah.
And you believe that?
Look, all I'm saying is this,
pay attention to what's
right here in front of you,
right now.
Okay?
All right, well, hey, let's eat.
We got a picnic, right?
So I assume the two of
them still stayed together?
Well, yeah.
I mean, Poochie had
a problem with it.
Poochie?
Wait, who's Poochie?
Granny, I'm hungry.
Okay, let's see what they
have over here for us, okay?
Okay.
Thank you, ma'am.
Really do appreciate
what you're doing
for the community here.
Yeah, we appreciate it.
Thank you.
God bless you.
Thank you so much.
You know, this is exactly what
we need in this neighborhood,
people that actually care.
Not like these low-life that's
passing around this poison
to our babies.
Well, the Lord provides,
doesn't he, Mrs. Gunther?
Yes, he does.
He does more as well.
He provides, he guides,
and he keeps us.
He's a good God. Yes.
- That's right.
- He's a good God.
- Amen, yes.
(Alex chuckles)
All right, y'all keep
doing what you're doing,
all right?
We will.
- We will.
- All right. Come on, baby.
You know what, baby?
I'm gonna go inside
and see if there's some more
juices and water, all right?
- All right, baby.
- Okay? You good?
- I'm good. I'm great.
- Fellas,
hey, hey, watch your mama.
- A'ight.
- Watch her.
Hey yo, Slim?
Slim!
Come here.
What do you want, Poochie?
Man, that's how you greet me?
What you want me to call you?
My baby daddy?
(Tanya laughs)
My bad.
Were we still keeping
that our little secret?
Or did your wife finally
put two and two together?
You know, it's only
been, what, nine years?
I think it's about
time she knows.
Don't you think?
You better not.
(laughs) Well, why not?
You know,
you didn't send your
drop off guys this month
to keep it quiet.
I thought that was a sign that
you were ready to come clean,
dirty.
My money been kind of tight.
Really?
Well, I wonder how
tight it's gonna be
when your wife
finds out about us.
You know, them attorney
fees can get real hefty.
Then when I come forward,
it's like a domino effect.
All your other baby mamas, gone.
Listen here.
(deep ominous music)
You ever wonder why
they call me Poochie?
Hm?
'Cause that's the name of
the guy that killed my mama.
Real cool, easy-going,
'til you mess with him.
Then people end up dead.
(chuckles) See,
I'm just like him.
See, on the streets,
they called him Poochie,
but at home, we
called him Daddy.
I got no problem taking
my baby mama out either.
Boys!
Tanya!
What are you doing?
Yes, ma'am?
Come here.
There's somebody I
want you to meet.
This is Mr. Edwards.
He's your mom's good friend.
Say hi.
What's up?
- Hey.
- How you doing?
Hey, mister.
Hm?
What do you know,
we got the same last name.
(Pooch chuckles)
Nice car.
Yeah?
Maybe your daddy'll buy one
just like it for you one day.
Sir,
we don't have a daddy.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
what'd I tell you
about that, huh?
Don't ever say you
ain't got no daddy.
Okay?
What'd I tell you?
He's just like the devil, right?
He's always there,
even if you don't see him.
Hey, baby!
Hey, um,
we didn't have any more
juice or water, okay?
But we got a bunch of chips.
(Alex laughs)
Who's this?
This is, um, (clears throat)
this is him.
- Him?
- Him.
Oh! (clears throat)
Him! Okay, okay.
How's it going?
All right, well,
I better get going.
(engine revs)
So that was the last
they heard from Poochie?
Not exactly.
[Tanya] Alex! Alex!
(door banging)
Alex!
(tense dramatic music)
What is going on?
- Alex!
- What is going on?
Let me in, hurry
up! Let me in!
Hurry!
Baby, baby,
what, what?
Baby? What is going on?
I think he's following me.
What? What are
you talking about?
Who's following you?
Poochie! He's
trying to kill me.
What?
Look, I've been,
I've been trying to tell him
ever since I started
over with God.
And I've been trying to
come clean with this wife,
but I gotta tell him first.
Tanya, what are
you talking about?
Alex, I don't know
who my sons' father is!
L-Listen,
first of all, calm down.
No one's gonna lay
a finger on you
as long as I'm around.
I'll die first.
Come on, come on.
[Tanya] Hide me, please.
(Alex shushes)
(door knocking)
Who is it?
[Pooch] You know who
it is, man, stop playing.
(Alex clears throat)
Can I help you?
Not unless you
work at Popeye's
and got two breasts
and a thigh from me.
(Pooch laughs)
Come on, man, I'm
looking for my lady.
Your lady?
(low tense music)
Yeah, my lady.
I'm sure she told
you we had history.
You know what it is, come on.
Hey, man, you can
check this whole house.
You're not gonna
find her nowhere.
I know she in here
(sniffs) 'cause I can smell her.
(lips smacking) Come here, baby.
Come on, Slim.
Where you at, girl?
(phone rings)
Hello?
Spence, what's up? And
this better be good.
What?
All right, I'm on my way.
All right.
(deep dramatic music)
[Alex] Man, stay
away from us, Poochie.
Oh.
(elbow thumps)
Man.
(door thuds)
You heard what I said!
You heard me, right?
Yeah, you gonna see me again.
Yeah, but I'm not so
sure you want to see me.
Get, get outta my house.
Well, looks like it's time
for me to pay Mr.
Poochie a visit.
W-wait, but don't you want
me to finish telling you
about the married guy?
Wait, I thought
that was Poochie.
Oh no, they're two
totally different guys.
Remember, I told you she was
fascinated with married men.
She was running game on both
of these guys at the same time.
Really?
Oh yeah.
As a matter of fact,
I know I told you I couldn't
describe what he looks like,
but I do know what
he sounds like.
Okay.
It's actually funny, though,
because that's how
everything adds up
to the night she was murdered.
I heard his voice too.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
I was talking to Tanya
when he walked in,
and then she dropped the phone
in shock when she saw him.
The thing is,
the phone never hung up.
Yeah.
(tense ominous music)
(Tanya laughs)
(phone thuds)
(sharp menacing music)
What are you doing here?
You know exactly
what I'm doing here.
You think I'm just gonna
let you, quote, unquote,
"lay it all out on the table"?
Tell my wife about me and you
and let you get away with it?
No, no, no,
you know I'm smarter than that.
Shut up!
Save it for the birds.
Yo.
(alarm chimes)
What's going on?
(chuckles) My man,
you're right on time.
Hm.
Hey, baby,
tell Marvin Gaye what's
going on. (laughs)
Baby?
Oh, what, you didn't know?
Baby girl's been
playing both of us, dog.
No, no, I was playing you.
I do not live that life anymore.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I forgot.
She all saved now.
See, she started
dating the choir boy,
and she all sanctified.
Yeah, but she been
playing us, dog.
Oh, and by the way,
I'm them boys' papi.
What is this
dude talking about?
Dude? Oh, hold on, one
second, my name ain't dude.
I'm Officer Rashaad.
And that might
make a difference,
but it's not in the
next couple minutes
'cause you're gonna be dead.
But, long story short,
I've been giving her the loving,
and she's been getting
the money from you.
I mean, I liked
that deal, honestly,
but all good things
must come to an end.
Yeah, like you.
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey now, wait.
Hold up.
Don't do anything stupid.
So lemme get this straight.
You invited me over here
so that you can tell me
that the kids that
I've been paying
for you to keep quiet from
my wife aren't even mine?
And you thought I'd
be okay with that?
I tried to tell you, Poochie.
You owe me $300,532.23.
Wow, that's a lot of money.
Now, I thought you said
you didn't love this dude.
Wait, what?
Mm-hmm.
I never said that.
Don't listen to him, Rashaad.
Those words never
came out of my mouth.
Yeah, you remember,
that night at the club.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait a minute.
- Yeah.
- What?
No.
(Rashaad stammers)
I said I didn't love you...
I didn't love you like that,
I-I wasn't in love with you,
not that I didn't love you.
Oh.
Okay, so let me
get this straight.
You've been lying to him
about me then lying to me
about how you feel about me.
(intense ominous music)
It's not like that.
It's just, it's just a
big misunderstanding.
No, no no, it ain't.
I think I understand
everything perfectly.
(alarm chimes)
(door slams)
Now we're alone.
Come here, I wanna
tell you something.
[Tanya] No...
(stammering fearfully)
No, I just wanna talk to you.
- Rashaad, I'm sorry.
- No, no, no. (shushes)
(sharp menacing music)
Come here!
[Tanya] Rashaad!
Rashaad!
Rashaad, please please please!
(Rashaad yelling)
(Rashaad laughs)
Well, it seems like you
solved this whole thing
just by hearing my
voice on the phone.
That, and you introduced
yourself to Poochie
when he walked in.
Mm.
Dead giveaway.
I know you tried hard to put
this on the Jackson Strangler,
but what's done in the
dark always comes to light.
(chuckles) Yeah,
always does.
Guess I'm gonna just
have to kill you.
[Officer] I wouldn't
do that if I were you.
(low tense music)
Breaking news.
We've just been
told by authorities
that they have taken into
custody one of their own,
a 22-year police veteran.
Rashaad Williams was arrested
for the death of Tanya Griffin,
who was found dead
in her apartment
that she shared with her
mother and two children.
(Angie sighs)
We need to talk, face-to-face.
So how long have you
known about this?
Girl, let's
start with forever.
Wait a minute, why didn't
you just go to the police?
It's really complicated.
I wanted to look
out for my girl
because I knew they were dating.
We know how much
you loved your cousin,
and we wanted to tell you first.
And I wanted to prove to her
that there were other women
besides you and her.
It just so happens she didn't
get the chance to see them.
Guess they were meant for you.
Williams is also
linked to the murder
of one of Tanya's best friends,
46-year-old Jessica Turner.
More news at 10:00.
Hey, listen,
I hate that you had to
find out about your husband
and your cousin this way.
No, no, look,
(chuckles) I would've
found out eventually.
I'm just trying to figure out
how we're going to
prove all of this.
Oh, trust me,
I have the perfect setup.
I see y'all got him.
Whoo! I'm so glad.
'Cause I don't carry
this around for nothing.
(singer vocalizing)
♪ Boy, you got me in my feelings
♪ Feels so unreal
♪ Said you'd never do this to me
♪ Never thought you'd be
the one to break my heart
♪ Said I loved you
from the start, babe
♪ So many ways you
broke my heart
♪ So many ways disappointed me
♪ You lied, you cheated
♪ Ran out on me