Hello?
Fear splits a glimmer of hope
in two,
like lightning
strikes an old me.
Beyond it, a vision of futures,
dreams realized.
Dancing like golden ghosts,
we emerge
from behind a veil of fog
on the horizon.
Thank you.
Ramy!
Uncle Hani.
Good to see you.
You made it.
This is your room.
Make yourself at home.
I'll make us some tea.
So...
Medical school, huh?
It's a tough university
to get in to.
Yeah I suppose so.
You made it this far.
Your dad must be very proud.
I guess he is.
But it's mainly for my mom
that I'm doing this.
Hmm.
Oh, Alya was a loving lady,
filled with so much life.
What a loss.
I'm glad you're finally here,
really.
Thank you, Uncle Hani.
Fear splits a glimmer of hope
in two,
like lightning
strikes an old me.
A glimmer of hope
strikes fear in two,
behind a veil of smoke,
on the hori--
Tamer?
Uh, heard there was an infidel
takin' over my digs!
The fuck?
What's up, cuz?
Cuz!
Yo, man,
sorry to drop in on you so late.
I uh, I lost my keys on tour.
Oh,
and I didn't wanna wake up dad.
Fuck.
It's your room.
Yeah, yeah.
It's uh,
it's nice to see you, cuz.
Same here.
-So, you like it?
-Quite a bedroom.
Really. Do you speak any French?
Haven't had a chance
to learn it.
I went to
a British private school
where mom used to teach.
A British school!
Fuckin' hell, mate.
Ain't we proper jammy?
You like those?
I'm not familiar with them.
The classics.
Thanks.
What, they didn't teach you
about the Pistols
in English class?
Afraid not.
Shit, what kinda English
do they teach over there?
Yo, I want you to listen this,
okay?
And tell me what you think.
What do you think?
It's a bit like spicy food.
Takes getting used to,
but once you're there,
it's like a--
a whole world opens up.
That's it.
You fucking nailed it.
Tabarnak!
What are you doing Saturday?
I'm recording a video
at a cool club called "L'Esco".
You'll love it.
You should come out, hang out.
Meet some people.
I'd love to.
You know about Montréal girls,
right?
What?
Hmm.
Thank you.
Of course.
Mmhmm.
Hi, what's his name?
It's Phénix.
Phoenix?
Hi.
Sorry, I don't speak French,
but that was
an incredible performance
you just gave there.
Was it?
A performance
you couldn't understand?
Perhaps I was simply
reciting my grocery list, no?
Well, I aspire
to perform poetry one day.
Like you.
Ooh, like me! Is that so?
And what is stopping you?
I don't know.
I mean...
I'm gonna give you
the best piece of advice.
You see, one needs to go
into the dark void.
Have his soul crushed.
Burned.
Chaos. Disorder. Anarchy.
Then rise again
like a phoenix from the ashes.
You have to live
and breathe poetry.
Sometimes you won't even
have a dime in your pocket,
but your heart is on fire.
Why?
Because it's been stepped on
a thousand times
and can only exist
by bursting into flames
every second of the day.
Forget it.
It's no life for
Have you ever even loved?
With the fire of a dozen suns?
Follow the sheep, boy.
You'll be much happier that way.
Okay, this is gonna be a take.
Raise the energy, everybody!
Action!
Hi!
Sorry?
Do you work with the crew?
No. Why?
Oh, never mind.
Do you want one?
Sure.
Alright, do you like reds,
darks, or blondes?
Your beer.
Whatever. You decide.
Here you go.
Two blondes
for the price of none.
Désirée.
Ramy.
Enchantée.
Nice to meet you.
Wooh!
- Cut!
- Thank you, thank you.
Beautiful fuckin' people!
Alright, this next one's
dedicated to my cousin
who's new in town
and lookin' for a good time,
ladies.
Ladies, he's right back there,
Doctor Ramy!
Uh, if you're feeling hot
and bothered,
the doctor's in town
to check you out!
One, two, three four!
Your cousin?
He's a legit
fuckin' cheese ball.
But he's family.
So, is it true?
What?
Are you Doctor Feelgood?
I'm working on it.
Santé.
Have fun.
Amazing! And cut.
You had fun at the bar?
It was quite an experience.
Okay, so, who--
who do you like best,
us or them?
Can't tell the difference yet.
Oh, everyone's a critic!
Everyone's a critic now,
did you know?
Hey, guys!
Madam. Yazzie.
Where you've been hiding,
beautiful?
You guys know each other?
Cuz, everyone knows me!
I'm a local fuckin' legend!
This is my friend, Yasmina.
She's a band promoter,
sometimes models for me.
My partner in crime.
Pleasure to meet you, Yasmina.
You can call me "Yaz".
Okay, shots for everybody!
Okay, I'd like to
propose a toast to Doctor Ramy
for pretending
he likes our music
and for being a good sport.
Okay.
- Wooh!
- Cheers.
He said our music is like uh--
what did you say?
Spicy food?
It goes down tasty,
but it comes out burning your--
What was it?
So, he's got
a sense of humour then?
Either that, or he knows
what he's listening to.
Oh! Pain!
Hey, are you tryin' to say
we're crap, Dési?
Look, Punk is dead.
I hate to break the news to you,
you're not even
fashionably late.
Okay, God forbid,
you take one of these girls
to a respectable club.
Nobody appreciates culture
anymore.
I'm with Ramy.
I think it's like spice.
Too much and you lose the taste.
You need just the right amount
to make something delicious.
Too much or too little
and you've lost everything.
God, you girls.
- You're so bad.
- You have no idea.
This party is getting so lame.
Please entertain me, Ramy.
Well,
Dési is definitely having fun,
isn't she?
Shooter! Wooh!
This is burning my throat.
- Yeah?
- Do you need an inspection?
Do you need another one?
Uh, sorry about that, officer.
Okay, everybody, time to go!
Thanks for coming.
Time to go, party's over.
Go, go, go!
Come on, fuck out!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Out, out!
- Come. Let's go, Ramy!
Sorry about that.
Do you always walk girls home,
Ramy?
I couldn't let you girls
walk alone at night.
I need water.
Come on, we're almost there.
He's such a gentleman, isn't he?
Oh, my--
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Ow. Okay, here we are!
Are you coming in?
Habibi?
Wait you're gonna pull me.
Hey.
Big pockets.
Oh, so you like tickles, really?
How about you?
Oh, my gosh, don't even try.
Yeah, she's totally--
Okay, I'll be right back.
So, Ramy, what's your story?
My story?
In three sentences or less.
Medical student-to-be.
Hmm.
Aspiring poet.
Mmhmm.
Missing dead mother.
Hmm.
And what is your story?
I know nothing about you.
Well, maybe
that's what turns you on.
Why ruin it?
Your lips are nice.
With a little bit of training,
you could be a good kisser.
You are so unusual.
Why is that?
You seem so carefree, I guess
So unpredictable.
I've never met a girl like you.
Enjoy it then.
My neighbours
are allergic to fun.
So, what did I miss?
Mm, you smell so nice.
Whoa, what kinda desperado
calls you this late?
No one.
Oh, I have to go.
Come on, are you sure?
Why don't you stay over?
I can't.
Come on.
We could show around town
to Ramy tomorrow.
I have to go. Come on.
You want to share a ride?
Sure. Call it.
- Ramy, are you coming?
- The sun is rising.
It's been fun. Thank you.
Yeah, let's hang out.
Sure.
Bye.
Sir, you can drop me off
at La Ruelle.
Um, just-- just here.
Thanks for the ride.
I'll text you.
Sure.
So, let's begin.
This one-year
preparatory curriculum
will prepare you
to excel in the medical program.
Can you do it?
I have faith that you can.
Hard work, dedication,
and listening.
So, you are here,
because your passion
for medicine and science,
and your dream
to become a doctor
are your life's mission.
We're here to help,
we're here to give.
Let's do this together.
Welcome to your first day
of pre-med.
This is the start
of your future.
Now, you'll have courses
in molecular biology,
physiology, metabolism,
cell biology.
Also, we operate courses
in humanities
and social sciences.
Then, you'll be able
to move forward
into the main program.
But-- it's a big but.
Humanities and social sciences,
but-- and this is a big but,
you must maintain a 3.5
cumulative grade point average.
When your mother passed,
your father
became completely closed.
I used to ask him
how he was doing,
and he would answer,
"I can't afford emotions."
Can't afford.
Always balancing the books.
Perhaps he was trying to--
to protect his sanity
or his heart.
Your mom, she had a good soul.
She always insisted
on emotional honesty, always.
If she were here today,
she would demand it
just the same, hmm?
My own son
doesn't think he needs me.
But I want you to know
that if you need to talk,
I'm here for you.
Isn't she pretty?
Yaz, hey, did you get any sleep?
Ramy.
- Yo, cuz!
- What the fuck?
Oh, don't tell me
I caught you jerkin' off.
Can't you knock?
You tryin' to traumatize me?
How come you're still in bed,
man?
What is that?
This your idea of porn?
She's hot. Not my type.
Terrible tits.
But to each their own.
To each their own.
Funny.
-What you got there?
-Nothing. Verses.
Really? Can I read 'em?
They're not finished yet.
- Come on.
- You know, I write poetry, too.
Check this out. New lyrics.
You're a lowly fucked disgrace.
Blow it out your ass.
I don't like your fuckin' face.
It's called "BIOYA".
Does that stand for
blow it out your...
Ass!
Correct.
Okay, now, let me read yours.
Okay, just...
Shit...
Huh! Ooh.
Your emerald eyes
sparkle in the desert moon.
Rosewater scents surround us
as we kiss under kh--
The fuck is that?
It's a bit obscure.
Not sure
about the translation yet,
but it's you know,
the bear constellation.
It's an expression.
The back of the bear.
So you're kissing
under a bear's ass?
Come on, what is that?
Blow it out your ass, seriously?
It's political.
I don't have to explain.
Anyway, it sounds a lot better
with music.
Trust me.
Yeah, at least
we agree on one thing.
What's that?
We're both ass men.
When's your next show?
Oh, you wanna see us again?
Already hooked on the spice,
are we?
- Mmhmm.
- I'm flattered.
Uh, we play in a few weeks.
Will Yaz be there?
Oh, you snake.
And this whole time I thought
you liked my song writing.
Look at you.
Trust me, Yaz is a lesson
you don't wanna learn.
Fuck, that's a good line!
That girl is a lesson
you don't wanna learn.
Hey, did you get any sleep?
Hi Desiree, do you
wanna hang out?
Hey.
Hey, Ramy!
-Nice to see you.
-You made it.
Yeah, sorry,
I was lost somewhere around.
I didn't know
there was another viewpoint.
Yeah.
But this view looks far better
Yeah,
I hike up here all the time.
It centres me.
What's that for?
I'm collecting portraits
for a photo exhibit.
Let me show you
my favourite spot.
Sure.
Let's go.
Thank you for bringing me here.
So, young doctor,
besides carousing
with Montréal Girls
on your spare time,
what else do you do?
I write verses.
Oh, let's hear some.
I'm not sure I'm ready for that.
No, some on. Don't be like that.
Own it if you care about it.
Otherwise what's the point?
You're right.
A glimmer of hope
strikes fear in two,
like lightning
splits an old tree.
Beyond it, a vision of futures.
Dreams realized
dance like golden ghosts,
behind a veil of smoke
on the horizon.
Nice.
Hmm.
I got a few others in there.
check that out.
Ever had a muse?
Not sure.
How would I know if I had?
You would know.
Something...
...or someone...
...who just perfectly embodies
that vision
that you're striving
to give voice to.
Beckoning you,
like a star that's pulling you
into its gravity.
You can't explain why.
It just happens that way.
And you follow,
sometimes blindly,
hoping that by being near them,
by grasping their essence,
you might find the perfect way
to say what you want to.
Your poem reminds me of Rumi.
"The soul which cannot endure
fire and smoke
won't find the secret."
What's the secret?
Wow!
That's up to you to figure out.
Did we really just
get the same text?
It looks like it.
You'll love Bloodshot Bill.
Are you going?
Yaz is the promoter.
Alright.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This next one, we're gonna do
it
for all you Montréal girls
out there, here we go.
Bloodshot Bill!
- That's so funny.
- Are you serious?
Yaz.
Hi.
Ramy.
- Where's Dési?
- I don't know.
She got the invite
like everyone else.
Did you get my texts?
Oh, shit.
Excuse me man!
Ètienne Tremblay!
Alphonse Legrand!
Mm.
I've never seen you around, huh?
What are you drinkin'?
Adios motherfucker.
What?
That's what I'm drinking.
Excuse me there!
Two adios motherfuckers, please.
Yeah, two.
Doubles.
Oh!
- Thank you so much.
- Have a great night.
Wooh!
Oh, my God.
I think I have too much blood
in my alcohol system
Well, you might need
to do a blood test.
-Oh!
-Here let me give you a shot.
What's that?
Uh, you wanna make out?
I'll be back.
I'll be here.
Hey, guys,
anybody wants some poutine?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, man.
Gotta roll, man!
Why!
-Need a ride home, huh?
-Hmm.
Better that than to ride
with him on his tiny moped!
Mopeds... They're fun, huh,
until your friends see ya
ridin' them
Just ignore them, Ramy.
Come on, Etienne.
What?
Don't be so immature.
Oh.
Fast. He's fast.
Are you always this forward
with girls?
A girl spying on a boy.
Isn't that called "stalking"?
Well, I came here to save you
from that rousse Marie-Claude.
That chick's like Chiclets.
Sweet on the outside,
but she'll stick to you
like bubble gum.
Is that what you want?
You've got pumpkin lipstick
all over your mouth.
This isn't a Halloween party.
Who's that pervert Etienne?
A friend of yours?
Friends don't know the way
that I taste.
Are we more than friends now?
I don't know, you tell me.
You have reached
the voicemail box of...
Ramy Salama.
Salut, Ramy!
Sorry, I can't come out tonight.
I was working late.
I just booked
two photo exhibits.
The first one opens
tomorrow night, 7:00 p.m.,
at Gallatin Island
I'd love you to come.
I-- I really hope you can come.
Okay, bye.
- What the fuck?
- Etienne. Etienne!
- Stop!
- Etienne!
Yaz!
I guess
you're not havin' poutine.
You must have a poet's heart.
You're so easily seduced
by fantasy.
Hello.
Check.
- Ramy?
- Ramy.
- Ramy!
- Mama.
Saw Yaz last night.
Uh-huh, and?
She vanished.
Of course she did.
She's a fuckin' mirage.
Cuz, cuz, cuz, listen to me.
Don't let me catch you
hangin' over Yaz.
Those chicks,
they're like buses.
You miss one,
you catch the next.
Do you understand?
Okay.
You know, Tam, before mom died,
I promised her
that I would study hard
to become a doctor.
And now, she's gone.
And I wonder,
"Does any of this
even matter anymore?"
I don't know, man.
Nothing really matters.
We're just germs
spinning on a rock
in the universe,
and we have to get jobs
on top of it.
That's bullshit.
Sometimes I feel
like I'm wasting my time.
I love the old stuff, you know?
The classics.
But music now, it's just shit.
I mean the older stuff is
like...
...like a tiger in the wild.
It's dangerous,
and it's exciting,
and it's everything
you could ever hope to be.
But then you see the tiger
in the zoo
with the fake landscape,
and it's not the same.
The stripes
and the teeth are there,
but it's just not the same.
Sometimes
I feel like we're the zoo tiger.
I don't know.
It's better to die
from delusions of grandeur
than from reality and boredom
I guess.
Hey, this is Yaz.
Don't leave me a message.
I don't check 'em.
Beyond the black
velvet futility,
like glimmering watchtowers
in the distant cosmos,
the signal fires
from your eyes
arrive burning
like a dozen stars
after the journey
of light years
to ignite the heart's lantern.
The flame of the muse,
dancing, eternal.
Ramy.
Ramy?
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
Do you happen to have some time?
Yeah, sure. Come in.
Well, so typical of her.
But I don't understand.
I mean she was so...
So what?
I thought she was open for--
you know?
Open for business?
But even you and her...
Don't worry about me and her.
Besides what of it?
You know, you have the audacity
to come here
and inquire about Yaz
when you didn't even
return my phone call?
What phone call?
Crap.
I never check my voicemail app.
Désirée, I'm so sorry.
Are you serious?
Do you think
that I am Yaz's pimp?
That I can just go around
and you know,
make an arrangement for you
to get in her pants?
I have my own life,
my own interests,
and who Yaz is
or isn't gonna sleep with
is not one of them.
Look, I have to get ready
for my chakra workshop.
I really have to get ready.
Can I--
Can I at least give you this?
Open it, please.
Give it to your muse.
For you Yaz, Ramy.
Sorry,
I don't understand French, sir.
This is
the Saint Lawrence River,
the Fleuve Saint-Laurent, okay?
It's a sacred river.
See?
It's like our vein,
you know what?
You can throw it your sorrows
if you want,
but not your garbage.
It wasn't rubbish.
It was a poem I wrote actually.
A poem? Oh!
But maybe you're right.
Maybe it's just waste after all.
A poem of love interest?
Don't let tears of sorrow
inundate your thoughts,
young man.
They are like the--
the river current.
The more you resist
the stream of life,
the more it makes you drown.
When I moved to Canada,
I apprehended the new world.
Your mom was a foreign student
at McGill.
She wrote this poem
as a welcome gift
and to soothe my fears.
As water ventures forth
down a mountain,
it dreams not of its origins
as a fountain,
nor fears its destination
across the plain,
but breaks free
from all self-imposed restraint.
Simple, and effective.
Your mother excelled
in English.
She was
a terrific language teacher.
Keep it. It's now yours.
A secret treasure.
As water ventures forth
down a mountain,
it dreams not of its origins
as a fountain,
nor fears its destination
across the plain,
but breaks free
from all self-imposed restraint.
Will there'll be
sleepless nights?
Absolutely.
Will there be hard days?
Will there be days
where you think
you're gonna have to give up?
100 %.
But that is when you depend
on yourself.
But-- it's a big but.
You must remember
that you have to maintain
a cumulative grade point average
of at least 3.5.
Dear Baba,
this is perhaps
the most difficult letter
that I will ever have to write,
but there is something
I must confess.
I couldn't find the courage
to call you.
I was afraid
of your immediate reaction.
I trust that you will
respect my decision.
Your son, Ramy.
-Hi.
-Hey. That was fantastic.
Thank you for coming.
It's nice to see you here.
Hey!
Oh, the little pigeon
has returned.
Ramy.
Sophia.
Sophia is the editor of Poetzia,
the reference site for poetry.
She has immaculate taste...
...in everything.
Enjoy your night.
Yaz, I haven't heard from you.
Everything alright?
Uh, your father called.
Really? What did he say?
He was really angry.
Are you sure
about this decision?
I mean you've worked very hard
to get here.
Have you even thought
about your future?
Yeah, aren't you gonna
lose your chance
to residency status here
and shit?
I'd rather lose my status
than my mind.
Hmm, makes sense.
Okay, Dave's here. I gotta run.
Thanks for dinner, dad.
I'll be back Wednesday.
Hey, Tamer, tonight's your show
at L'Esco, right?
Yeah.
Will Yaz be there?
Are you mentally exhausted?
Okay, listen, man, I'm gonna
tell you something straight up
and you're not gonna be
happy with it, alright?
I nailed Yaz
more than a few times, okay?
We were drunk,
and it was something to do.
And I'll tell you right now,
she's the biggest
pain in the ass
you'll ever meet, okay?
You get hooked on that chick,
she's gonna make you wanna walk
into the Saint-Laurent
with concrete boots on.
It's a catch. Want to go?
Stay here.
Is everybody having a good time?
Ladies?
Ladies, come on!
Ooh!
Give it up for Dave on drums,
Arno on bass!
Do not feel like a Dirt bag!
Come on!
Wooh!
Yeah, yeah.
And more to you after party.
Ramy.
I wanna talk to you.
I'm busy.
Ramy.
Ramy. Hey! Oh, but-- dude!
Why do you keep giving me
the silent treatment, Yaz?
Is that what you're here
to discuss?
Are you gonna be boring?
Did you read what I sent you?
The poem? Yeah.
And?
I thought it was nice.
Clever.
What are you hiding from then?
Fuck you, Ramy.
I don't need your inquisition.
I'm not
one of your research projects.
I felt something with you.
Something new I've never felt.
Sorry if that makes you feel
like an experiment.
So you want me
to be exclusive to you?
Is that it?
Why should you
get special treatment?
Because we're
from the same culture?
The same background?
I've been running away from that
my whole life.
I'm someone else here.
Mysterious, exotic Yaz.
What will she say?
What will she do?
Everyone wants to know.
It's a full time job playing me.
You ought to know.
You're playing a role, too.
But at least I'm the one
who is in control.
Nobody owns me or tells me
what to do.
Don't be so naïve, habibi.
Here.
I wanna make you feel better.
Let's take a trip together.
I've already taken two of these.
Kiss me, Ramy,
or I'll swallow this one, too.
What the fuck are you doing?
Can't you tell
she's playing you,
like she does
with everyone else?
Daring you
with these dramatic games
to gain the attention
she so desperately craves.
Mind your own fucking business,
Désirée.
All you care about
is getting your own way.
All you want are free headshots
and...
...friends, like Rami and I.
This is not a contest
between one or the other.
And you, Ramy,
I thought you had
a bit more consciousness.
Depth maybe.
Sense enough not to be lured in
by an illusion
of your own imagination.
Désirée. Désirée!
It's not what you think!
Hey, Dési.
- Stay away from me.
- Wait. Wait!
Leave me alone.
Rami, is that you?
What's goin' on with you?
Where were you all night?
If you knew where I was...
All good.
Just met some people.
Hmm.
Doctors failed
to save my mother.
At least if I fail at poetry,
nobody is goin' to die.
Why you're speaking to me
in English now?
You're coming back home with me.
No. I'm not.
What did you dare say to me?
I'll be staying here
to study literature.
Literature.
This is your life ambition now?
To be a vagabond?
I'd rather be a vagabond
than a coward like you.
Being a doctor was your dream,
except you were too afraid
of failure to pursue it.
And so,
you chose safety instead.
And when mom was dying,
it was left to me
to comfort her,
because you were too afraid
of your own emotions.
Woo-hoo!
Yo, cuz. Presentable?
You've got mail.
Getting high
after havin' been low.
Never too early to start,
you sly dog.
Thanks for letting me stay
in your room all that time.
Yeah, well you owe me big time.
Listen, I um, need your help
with some lyrics.
Yeah, since you've been in
your whole nuclear anarchy mode,
you know what,
I'd like for you
to write me some
before you get
into any further trouble.
Really?
Yeah, really.
And uh, you can stay here
as long as you want.
Dad could use the company.
Dear son,
in the journey of life,
find eternity in an instant.
Live in wonderment as an infant.
Allow your voice
to become your freedom
and your intuition your path
to wisdom.
In the presence of time,
surrender to nature.
Death and birth
cohabit in a cycle.
This is not my goodbye,
just a farewell.
And even though
one day we will be apart,
always remember
to follow your heart.
I will forever love you.
Phoenix?
Hey, you again.
My real name is Félix
by the way.
What happened to you?
What?
Uh. Yves St. Laurent. So what?
Call me "petit-bourgeois"
and I'll kick your ass.
What do you want?
I'm late for work.
I'm having a reading tonight
at Quai des Brumes.
You comin'?
Wow! Bohemian life.
Poverty, deviance, uncertainty.
Freedom.
How extraordinary.
I gotta go to work.
Uh, break a leg.
Ramy?
- You're early.
- We open in 20 minutes.
This is fine work.
Thank you.
I was hoping you'd come.
Even without an invitation?
I'm sorry. I was mad.
Désirée,
I think I found the secret.
What do you mean?
I've discovered
that I'm not meant
to cure bodies with medicine,
but hopefully to heal souls
with my words.
Désirée,
I came here to thank you.
I'm so glad you came.
I would not miss this
for anything.
After trying
to cling desperately
to some artificial sanity
imposed by
your own sense of dread,
you realize
that the only way
to stay sane and survive
is to let go of that construct.
To fire the architect of fear,
to stop building walls
that prevent you
from living life,
however mad.
To not fear angels or demons.
But instead,
to invite them both in for tea.
You might learn that the angel
is really a demon,
or that the demon
is really an angel.
Or maybe
that it doesn't really matter.
'Cause it's the chaos,
the anarchy,
the disorder
that sometimes makes you feel
like you've lived,
and that perhaps
you've loved.
I would like to dedicate this
to my muses.
Wooh!
It's my cousin.
It's my-- it's my cousin.
It's my fucking cousin!
I'm so proud of you.
Look at you! Look at you!
Check it.
Hmm.
You know what else is awesome?
- Me.
From Doctor Feelgood,
with love.
Of course you're awesome.
Proud of you.
You're fucking legend.
Taught you well.
Thank you.
From Doctor Feelgood, with love.
You might learn that the angel
is really a demon,
or that the demon
is really an angel.
Or maybe...
That it doesn't really matter.
'Cause it's the chaos,
the anarchy,
the disorder
that sometimes makes you feel
like you've lived,
and that perhaps
you've loved.
Well,
it looks like you've got a fan.
You ready?
Your immaculate verses
are as brave
as your poet's heart.
Who?
Her. Her. This chick.
What you doing? Get up!
Go, go!
Excuse me.
Hey! Excuse me!
Sophia?
Did you write this?
Yes.
And I meant every word of it.
Along the dark span of time,
souls come and go,
appearing from nothing,
sharing tears, sharing laughter,
then vanish again into nothing.
But a thread of light
holds us together,
Binds our souls across
the delicate void of cosmos,
constructing a memory
that shall never die,
but will always live
in our heart forever.
You've given me life,
and have freed my being.
For all eternity,
I'm forever grateful.
Here I am,
standing humbly before you
with bursting love,
a new being.