All right, you monkeys.
Today we will learn an exercise
called a squat thrust.
We will learn how to do this exercise
in the proper manner,
or I will personally chew
some asses off.
All right,
on the whistle blow.
♫ Now here's a little song
about a thing called rage ♫
♫ And you're wondering
just how it feels... ♫
Squat, thrust.
Squat, thrust...
Mr. Noland, what the hell
is going on back there?
Those were the lamest squat
thrusts I have ever seen
in my entire 10 years of high-school
gymnasium class coach.
Get your ass up
your front center, pronto.
Pronto, damn it.
Now you will do
a squat thrust
in the proper fashion,
in front of the entire class.
On the whistle blow.
Squat, thrust.
Squat, thrust...
♫ Don't let them get you down,
don't ever lose your glory ♫
♫ 'Cause the world's doped up,
and you're part of the song ♫
♫ So, let's all get in key
and we 1! all sing along ♫
♫ Yeah, we 1! all sing along ♫
♫ Yeah-ah... ♫
Squat, thrust.
Squat, thrust, squat--
(whistle blows)
Get up, you pathetic turd.
Get up.
Now I will demonstrate the proper
fashion in which to do this exercise.
Hold my clipboard,
if that's not too much to ask.
♫ Ain't got no daddy, my mama's
living off of government mail ♫
♫ But she is the one
that will decide ♫
♫ What's best for me,
while pills are keeping her high ♫
♫ Vlﬁth her and the school board
against me ♫
♫ They gave me test to see
just what they might see... ♫
Observe-- you're down,
extend, retract,
you're here.
You're down, extend,
retract, you're here.
Give me that clipboard, boy.
- Now do it on the whistle blow.
- Can't you give me a break?
Give you a break?
Son, I never got any breaks
in life raised in Alabama.
12 years in the military,
I never got any breaks.
64-70 pick-up,
no breaks.
Now repeat after me--
I had a damn fine
gymnasium class coach.
I had a damn fine--
I had a damn fine
gymnasium class coach.
Now, then,
you will demonstrate
30 squat thrusts in the proper fashion,
in front of this class.
On the whistle blow.
(bell ringing)
I am the head
of the guidance department.
And my name...
is Mr. Korn.
Now, hold on.
I know what you're thinking.
You are thinking to yourselves,
“Oh, man, with a name like that,
this guy had best be down
with where my generation
is coming from, huh?
Otherwise, he is whack!“
( laughs )
Okay...
well, I'm gonna be taking over
this class for the next two weeks.
And I'll just be here to talk to you
about stuff
like college, and jobs...
and fun things like that.
Now i have an assignment for you.
i want you to write a paper.
it'll be due
at the end of two weeks.
But that's not your homework
for tonight. I know, I know.
Hold on! Let me get
a word in here, please.
Boo, grown up homework stuff.
I want you to help me out.
i want you to jot down some ideas
for tomorrow's class.
Like, where do you
see yourselves in 10 years?
Are you gonna be married?
Single?
You got kids?
What's your job like?
Are you gay? Straight?
Hooked on drugs? Sober?
Just give me the whole Iollapalooza.
( chuckles )
- Hey.
I was looking for that book.
Are you gonna check it out?
Maybe.
Okay.
I'm trying to find a topic
for my career paper.
Whatever.
Well, it was nice
talking to you.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Check this out, baby.
Very impressive.
Mr. Grimaldi made me do
30 squat-thrusts today.
That's the advantage
of being in Special Ed.
We don't have to take gym. It makes it
up for being with the retards all day.
Next year I'm gonna sign up with
the “retard" classes with you, but...
No, you don't wanna be doing that.
We got all the lame chicks.
You guys get all the hotties,
like that Sasha
you're always talking about.
Sasha seems like she's
into murder and stuff.
She was wearing a Charles Manson
t-shirt today in the library
and reading a book about killers.
So I got a bunch of them.
Chicks love these guys.
The Night Stalker, Richard Ramirez,
Ted Bundy--
they both married fans
while they were in prison.
I think you might be on
to something here, man.
(scream, explosion )
- Hi, babe.
- What are you cooking for dinner?
Very funny.
- So, how was school?
- Fine.
You got any tests or papers
coming up, Case?
You gotta get your grades up
if you're gonna get into a good college.
- Not this again, Mom.
- Just keep me posted, okay?
You never cared
before Dad died.
Now it's myjob to make sure
you get everything done.
So just give me a break, okay?
♫ She swam to me, yeah... ♫
TV host:
Hi, I'm J. D. Rock.
You may remember me as the host
of the game show Fun House.
You wanna make more money?
Heck, we all do.
Call now for a free brochure
and how to earn a degree in auto
mechanics, real estate, or computers--
Worried about not having your high-
school diploma, but you like to travel?
Why not call JWA Transport?
And we'll get you
driving the big rigs.
When I graduated from high school,
I knew college wasn't for me.
That's why I went to the Tech Effects
Institute for Computers.
Police this morning found the body
of a local high school student.
He was with his girlfriend,
who officials claim is still missing.
Police have yet to release
the names of the victims,
but our sources tell us
that authorities are now considering
the recent murders to be the work
of a single serial killer--
Narrator: Theodore Robert Bundy
considered himself to be a predator.
He preyed on young women.
He murdered
at least 30 of them.
He told me, “I decided
to take the shortcut to be...
powerful and well known
and to be--
to make my mark
on the world.“
- I'll meet her.
- Man: They're all my children.
Anybody that's ever seen me
has followed my footsteps.
How else could they do
anything else?
♫ Toot-toot. ♫
I know my mind.
And I trust the very
same person that you do.
And the very same person
that you do.
I trust the only person
left to trust--
me.
( dog barking )
( barking continues )
Shh!
Would you please be quiet?
Shut up!
Shut the fuck up!
♫ Hey, you,
shut the fuck up! ♫
♫ Shut the fuck up! ♫
Goddamn dog.
Hey, I got those stickers
you asked for.
Oh, great.
This is gonna be awesome.
Man, you look burnt out.
Old man Cruder's new dog
woke me up again last night.
That goddamn dog
barks every night.
I mean, I know where--
I can get you some C-4,
we could shove it up
that puppy's ass
and blow that fucking mutt
to Delaware.
- Have you gone postal?
- No, but check this out.
Last night, I'm watching
the Jenny Jones Show, okay?
They got these supermarket employee
makeovers. Are you following me?
They take these fat ugly chicks
and turn them
into fat ugly chicks with makeup.
I mean, fucking those are
the people you gotta kill.
Yeah, that's not a bad idea.
Somebody's gotta clean up the crap.
- Man, just kill those motherfuckers.
- I hear you.
Hey, check this shit out.
Holy shit!
- That's disgusting.
- Serial killers struck again.
I've got the pictures to prove it.
Show and tell, baby.
Having a dad
as a police photographer
must make you the coolest
kid in Special Ed.
Nah.
Actually, this one chick's dad
is a drug dealer.
It kind of sucks.
♫ i needed you then,
i needed you then ♫
♫ i bet you know
i don't need you now ♫
♫ We were good friends, yes,
you know, we were good friends ♫
♫ But you know
you lost me somehow ♫
♫ it's a beautiful life ♫
♫ it's a world of delight... ♫
Okay, now if you'll all just pass
your outlines up front,
- we can read them aloud.
- Oh my God, how embarrassing.
Thank you,
and thank you.
Okay. Well, let's see
what we've got.
- Hey, Mr. “Pekela.“
- That's “Pekala.“
Mr. “Pekala.“
“In 10 years, I see myself
as a gynecologist,
because I feel
it's important for young girls
to have someone
to help them with their...
vaginal problems.“
That's “vaginal," Mr. “Picalla.“
Very funny.
Let's see... voila. Okay.
“In 10 years...
I will be the CEO of Revlon.“
Marni Greenstein.
Well, that is very interesting,
Ms. Greenstein.
And I can see that clearly
you are off to a very good start.
You're so money.
You do know it.
Let's see what else
we have here.
Ah, Mr. Casey Noland.
“In 10 years,
i see myself
on death row...
convicted...
of being the most notorious
serial killer in history.
They caught me after
i decapitated my gym teacher. "
Ew, what a psycho!
I don't find this very funny,
Mr. Noland.
And we're gonna wrap
about this after class.
All right.
We've read enough of these.
We 're gonna be
handing you out
the Life Goals Evaluations Test.
And this should give you
a pretty good idea
of the sorts of careers
and vocations
that will best suit you
and your personal ambitions.
You will need a #2 pencil.
Please don't go
outside the circles.
(crowd cheers, applauds)
Mr. Noland, you should know
that the use of CD players
- during school hours is forbidden.
- I was just listening to--
And you will excuse me
if I relieve you of this toxic--
pardon my French--
crap as well.
( bell ringing )
So, you like
Marilyn Manson?
- Yeah.
- Me, too.
I liked your career choice.
Thanks.
I'm gonna return that book
to the library this afternoon,
if you wanna check it out.
It'll be in.
- Yeah, thanks.
- That's no problem.
How cute.
Two freaks in love.
Thank you.
Mr. Noland...
I didn't find your paper
very amusing.
Killing people
isn't the bomb.
- It's just not funny.
- Depends on who you ask.
Now you listen to me.
If you want to pass this course,
you're gonna hand in another paper
besides this one and do it
properly this time. Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
And by the way...
thanks for the diet tip.
Oh, Marni.
Someone seems to have left
their jacket behind.
Would you do me a favor
and run it over to Lost and Found?
- But I'm gonna be late for gym class.
- Thank you.
Hello? Hello?
- ( screams )
- What the fuck are you doing here?
I am lost. I am trying
to find Lost and Found.
No, no, wait, wait.
Here, we keep that shit in here.
What you got there,
pretty girl?
Oh, it must have been expensive.
You are a pretty girl.
You wanna sit?
- I've got some beer in the fridge.
- No, thanks. I have to get to class.
Wait!
Where are you going?
The kid will learn his lesson, huh?
( spits )
They're ungrateful.
They're all ungrateful bastards
and bitches.
What you're gonna want
to ask yourself today,
is, “Can I hurl the plastic disc
in a fashion
that will please Mr. Grimaldi,
or will i hurl it
in an improper fashion
and displease Mr. Grimaldi,
thusly receiving a boot
upside my buttocks?"
I think you'll choose
the first option.
Take the disc
and hurl it to your neighbor
in the other line.
On the whistle blow.
And...
Good throw.
Good catch.
Good throw. Good catch.
Good throw.
Good catch.
Good throw. Good catch.
- Good--
- ( whistle blows)
Mr. Noland, what the Sam hell
is wrong with you, huh?
You can't even throw a plastic disc
like you don't squat to pee?
Try it again. And this time
throw it like you got a pair.
On the whistle blow.
And...
Did you try to hit me
with that plastic disc? Did you?
Did you try to express
your hatred for Mr. Grimaldi?
Well, if you did,
try it again.
And this time, throw it
like you got a pair of nuts.
Take the plastic disc.
Throw it at me. Do it.
Do it.
You pathetic turd.
I cannot believe
that you throw like a woman.
Well, We gotta get somebody
to teach you how to throw like a man.
Ms. Barman,
get your ass up here.
Take him over in the corner
and teach him how to throw like a man.
Do it now!
The rest of you
resume the activity.
You know, Mr. Noland,
if you continue in this fashion,
you'll be the first student
to ever fail gymnasium class
in the history of square buildings
with wooden floors.
The rest of you continue
on the whistle.
♫ At least the monkey
was my own I
♫ i let him go because
We grown... ♫
These kids are maggots. Fucking
tater tots all over the lunch room.
Goddamn kids.
Where are their fucking parents?
( alternative rock music playing )
♫ Although you think
you're very clever:
♫ Long ago i was alone ♫
♫ But i had
my monkey on my back ♫
♫ Now my monkey's
gone away ♫
♫ it's worse this time,
l'm aware of life every day. ♫
That's disgusting.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
I don't feel good.
I can't do this.
Mr. Horror Movies
is grossed out by a dead pig?
- I don't believe it.
- Can I go to the nurse?
Well, I have to fail you
if you don't complete this project.
Can I make it up
with extra credit?
Well... we'll work something out.
Yes, go. You go. Go ahead.
- Thanks, Mr. Rabino.
- It's the second door on the right.
No, the third door.
Mrs. Prisano.
Ah, she can handle it.
Keep cutting.
Very good.
♫ Let's do it. ♫
What you reading?
“The Psychosis of Murder.“
So, I guess you're really
into this stuff.
You know, I never met anyone
that wanted to be a serial killer.
- It's pretty cool.
- Thanks.
If you're serious about this stuff,
you're gonna need some help.
- Help?
- Yeah, look at all these books.
It's gonna take you weeks
to get through all this information.
Unless you had someone
who can do the research with you.
- Like who?
- Who do you think?
Then what's in it for you?
Hmm... let's just say I share
a personal interest in this topic.
I help you become a serial killer
and you let me be your first victim.
- What?
-Yeah, you heard me.
-You wanna die?
- It's not a question of dying.
It's a matter of fame.
“Sasha Fitzgerald,
the first victim
of serial killer Casey Noland.“
Yeah, it does have
a nice ring to it.
Yeah, I wanna be
the Sharon Tate of the '90s.
So, do we have a deal?
- ( knock on door)
- What?
What did you do now? You and I have
a little meeting tomorrow after school,
- with your guidance counselor?
- That guy is a jerk-off.
I didn't take his stupid
aptitude test seriously.
He said something
about killing people.
I told him that I wanted to be
a serial killer when I grow up.
Very funny, Casey. Come on, you can't
kid around like that in school.
Come downstairs.
I got “Taco Hell“ for dinner.
- Mrs. Noland.
- Mr. Korn.
Thank you for coming by.
Casey, come on in. Have a seat.
Okay.
Well, let's get down
to the business at hand.
- Has Casey shown you this paper?
- Ah... no.
Well, evidently,
your son finds it humorous
to joke about death
and murder.
Mr. Korn, Caseyjust has
this really odd sense of humor.
Yes. Well, I'm sorry, but I don't find
mutilation and dismemberment
to be an appropriate topic
for a paper.
I'm gonna fail him
if he doesn't change the subject.
All right. Well, I promise
I will help Casey pick a new topic.
in addition,
I gave Casey
a career profile survey,
which incidentally
I had to mark by hand.
(sighs)
He is qualified to be either...
a parking meter maid,
a night security guard,
or a toll booth operator.
Not very ambitious
careers, are they?
Mr. Korn,
Casey's a bright kid.
He just hasn't
found his niche.
Well, Casey,
give me “the McCoy.“
When you graduate
at the end of this year,
- what do you wanna do?
- I don't know.
- Toll booth operator sounds good.
- Mrs. Noland: Casey!
Casey, you're not dissing me.
You're dissing yourself.
Because in six months you will have
graduated from this high school,
and you have no plans
for your future.
Listen, i know
it must be very tough
for a young man to start
his senior year at a new school,
but this behavior...
is abnormal.
Incidentally, I took this from Casey.
It's a band called
Marilyn Manson
and I don't know whether or not
you are familiar with their lyrics.
No. It's not exactly
my kind of music.
Well, in this song, they are
talking about eating cake
and sodomizing
each other and...
that date rape
is a kind thing to do.
They are clearly
glorifying Satan.
They are proclaiming
themselves to be the gods of--
- the gods--
- Fuck. Gods of fuck.
Casey, stop it!
This is what I'm talking about,
Mrs. Noland.
Ah, Ms. Lindon. Very nice to see you.
Thank you for coming by.
Mrs. Noland, Casey, this is Ms. Sally
Lindon, the school psychologist.
It's nice to meet you.
Sorry I'm late.
Ms. Lindon and I have talked it over.
We feel it would be extremely helpful
if Casey would start
counseling twice a week.
- What?
- Excuse me.
No offense, but...
I don't know
if I'm exactly thrilled
- about my son seeing a shrink.
-Yeah, me neither.
Of course Casey doesn't have to go
to counseling with Ms. Lindon,
but if he doesn't,
I'm gonna fail him on his paper.
- ( sighs )
- Ms. Lindon: it won't be that bad.
Instead of going to the gym,
you come spend that period with me.
Cool.
Mrs. Noland, Casey shows many
of the troubling signs we associate
with... mentally disturbed adults,
but if we can nip it in the bud,
we can help Casey become
a respectable, responsible,
- contributing member of society.
- ( sighs )
His father passed away
a year ago and...
We're aware of that, Mrs. Noland.
But it's time for Casey
to start moving past his grief.
- Ray, there's been another--
- ( flatulence)
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Mexican again?!
- Another what?
- Another murder down at the park.
You'd better hurry up.
The press is already down there.
Press? Press.
You have no idea what you're
gonna do with the rest of your life.
Well, have a look at this paper.
Look at this survey.
You know, quite frankly...
I think the only thing you're qualified
to be is... a serial killer.
You know what?
You're absolutely right.
This is not psychologically
normal, Casey.
Casey, will you stop
killing your teachers?
Honey, you are never
gonna graduate!
That was stupid fresh, Casey.
Maybe this is
the right career for you.
( barking )
( dog barking )
Casey:
Mr. Grimaldi?
Why aren't you dressed
for gymnasium class?
I have to meet
with the school psychiatrist.
Ms. Lindon?
What in the hell for?
Well, they say is that I don't have
enough direction in my life.
Casey...
what you need in your life
is more discipline.
I think you know that.
The kind of discipline
that it can only be found
here in gymnasium class.
Casey, if you allow this class
to be something in your life,
it can be a warm, nurturing,
embracing nest.
Like chickens have
in a hen house.
You know what I mean?
I'm gonna go. I'm gonna be
late for... Ms. Lindon.
Another thing...
if I find out it was you who put
those bumper stickers on my van,
I'm gonna squash
your nuts into oblivion.
And tell those boys from home economics
to stop calling my house.
- How about this one?
- The blob.
- What does this look like to you?
- The sequel.
- And this one?
- A vagina?
- Casey, do you remember your dreams?
- Sometimes.
- Tell me about them.
- Well, last night, I had a dream
that I took I really big knife
and Iopped off Mr. Korn's head
and then I threw
the knife in your skull.
Then Mr. Korn's decapitated head
told me I'd be a good serial killer.
You know, Casey,
this would be
an excellent
extracurricular activity for you.
it would give you an opportunity
to be of help in the community
and to socialize
with kids your own age.
“Adopt a grandparent?“
You've seen the signs
in the school, haven't you?
Yeah, but old people?
They're so... old.
I think you'll find spending time
with the elderly
to be very rewarding.
Listen to this: “Everything serial
offenders do and think about is directed
towards assisting and fulfilling
their otherwise inadequate lives.
This book says
that the most crucial single factor
in the development of a serial killer
is the role of fantasy.
Edmund Kemper's fantasy involves
sex and death.
He had to completely
possess his partner,
this meant possessing her life.
So, what's your fantasy?
I guess I don't have one.
Well, it also says
that Kemper was like this
because he was trying to rid himself of
his domineering and abusive mother.
So, what's your mom like?
Is she cool?
Yeah. Yeah,
my mom is great.
Things have been kind of tough
on her since my dad died, though.
- Sorry.
- Yeah. He was a cop.
Some scumbag shot him.
We moved out here to start over.
Your dad was a cop.
Why be a serial killer?
Sally, I wanted to talk to you
about Casey Noland.
Sorry, I meant
to send you a note.
He's gonna be
meeting with me twice a week.
Oh, really? Missing
more gymnasium class, will he?
You know,
he's failing as it is.
Casey has a number of problems
to work through.
- Oh, yeah. Like what?
- That's too complicated to get into.
Sally, I'm concerned about
Casey Noland's welfare
just like you are.
Casey wants
to become a serial killer.
(laughing)
- Really?
- It's really not funny, Vince.
It's a little funny.
Listen...
I know you've got your psycho
mumbo-jumbo business going on,
but that's not gonna give him
the proper discipline that Casey needs.
That discipline can only be found
in gymnasium class.
The only thing he finds
in gymnasium class are more problems.
Serial killer, huh?
Shut up, Frank.
- How are your grades?
- Why?
It looks like a lot of these guys
are really smart.
Like Edmund Kemper,
he had an IQ of 146.
So, how did you do
on your last English exam?
- I didn't study for it at all.
- What was your grade?
A D+.
Look, if you wanna be
like these guys,
you're really gonna have
to start doing better in school.
You're also are gonna have
to start dressing better.
What's wrong
with the way I dress?
I mean, I like it.
It's cool, but...
it's not the way
these guys dress.
You gotta be more conservative.
Look at this.
Ted Bundy--
he was a young Republican.
And when they catch these guys,
the neighbors always say, like,
“Oh, he was
such a nice man.
We had no idea.
He was such a quiet man.“
You know,
you have to blend in.
- Blend in?
- Yeah.
- I don't even know where to start.
- I do.
- So, what do you think?
- Very nice.
You look like J. Crew's evil twin.
- lf anybody's got any information...
- Hey, check it out.
...about the murder of Michael Berman
or Tara Bolasky, who is still missing,
notify your police department.
Tragic.
Here's Chuck with the weather.
Tragic?
I'll tell you what's tragic.
I just got my new car washed
and we're expecting rain, rain, rain.
Wow.
I bet with all the information we have,
we could probably catch this killer.
- Yeah, maybe.
- I wish I could talk to him.
You know, see what it's like,
get some pointers from him.
I don't think he'd be
too interested in chatting.
Yeah, so what's in the book?
Anything interesting?
Yeah, it says you first need
to pick a type of a victim.
Like Ted Bundy liked
to kill teenage girls.
I don't think I could
kill teenage girls.
I like 'em too much.
How about ifl kill old people?
Put them out of their misery.
Maybe even terminally ill patients.
Yeah.
You could be Casey Noland,
the Dr. Kevorkian of serial killers.
I like that.
Okay, now you need a type
of a pattern, like the Zodiac Killer.
How about I kill every time
one of those infomercials come on
- for the Psychic Pals Network?
- No, it's on too often.
How about a weapon
or a special way of killing?
Okay, but I wanna be original.
I wanna use something
no one's ever used before,
so it guarantees me
a place in history.
- How about a baseball bat?
- That's too athletic.
- A chainsaw?
- That's used in too many movies.
Jeffrey Dahmer once drilled a hole
in a victim's head
while the guy was still alive
and then he poured acid inside.
Mrs. Noland:
Dinner!
- Mom...
- Mmm?
- ...this is Sasha.
- Mmm.
Excuse me.
Well, hello.
Pleased to meet you.
( laughs )
Casey, look at you.
Mr. Clean Cut, huh?
Looks like you're
a good influence on him.
Thanks.
So, anyway,
you wanna stay for dinner?
No, thanks. I don't eat meat.
I can whip you up
a salad or... cereal?
That's all right.
I gotta go.
Okay.
It was nice
to meet you, Mrs. Noland.
You too.
So, I got tickets
to that Marilyn Manson concert
on Thursday night,
if you wanna go.
That concert's sold out.
Well, I know, but my dad's company
was able to get tickets, so...
Yeah-- no,
I'd love to go.
Cool. Great.
I'll see you in class tomorrow.
- Bye, Case'.
- Bye.
Case'.
( laughs )
Don't even start with me, no.
I'm not gonna say a word.
Well, she's-- she's cute.
Oh, man, look at it.
Junk mail and more bills.
- Man: Maylhelp you?
- Actually, I can have a little...
help.
- Oh, but these are nice over here.
- Oh, yeah-- yeah, I like these.
Yeah, they're 7 1/4-inch
"dinanite carbicle" T-saw blades.
Then you're gonna have to buy
one of these big babies here.
- No, I'll just take the blades.
- Just want the blades?
All right, fine.
Movin' right along.
Oh, it's here-- you're gonna need
one of these for your tools.
You've got so much stuff,
a little tool belt for you.
Let's see. One of these,
one of these.
One of these,
one of those, and two of these.
Good. Turn.
- Is this a good grass blower?
- Ah, yeah, yeah. That-- it blows.
It blows well, actually. The problem is,
they're not very dangerous.
What if something sharp
got stuck in it?
Like those giant drill bits.
What if somebody took one of those
and shoved it in there
and started it?
Ahh, ooh--
yeah, that would hurt.
See you later.
Toodles.
Weird guy.
- Yeah.
- Hey, can I come in?
-Yeah, come in.
- Whoa, awesome tools.
- Yeah.
- How'd you pay for all those?
Dad's insurance.
I couldn't decide on just one weapon.
There's just too many of 'em.
That's okay, you can be the hardware
store murderer or something.
I brought some books--
they might help you out.
- Cool.
- What's this?
Oh, that's my dissection program
for biology class.
Oh, cool.
I got this great stuff
off the internet.
The psychological profile
of a serial killer.
Let me see.
Let's see.
“Body disposal:
Hide the body, dismember it,
display it, throw it away
or a combination of any of the above.“
I don't think
I have space to display it
and I don't think my mom's gonna be
very happy with dead bodies
hanging on all over,
so I need to throw 'em away.
It would be easier if you
dismembered it and then trashed it.
I guess, but I'm not
gonna be too comfortable
with chopping up dead bodies.
I can't even dissect a fetal pig.
Okay...
“Take a souvenir or trophy from
the victim, like a ring or a necklace.“
Yeah, it lets you relive the kill.
These guys would give them
to their girlfriends or their wives--
it would reassert
their domination and control.
I guess I'm not gonna have anybody
to give a souvenir to.
“Postmortem sex.“
- Sex with an old dead lady?
-Yeah, a lot of the killers do it.
I think I'm gonna pass
on that one.
Okay, so you're not
into sexual experimentation.
Okay...
the killer is a male.
Check.
The victims' race will be the same
as the killer's. Check.
- Usually single?
- Check.
And middle class.
Check.
- Resides away from the crime scene.
-You know, that's not a problem.
There's an old age home
half an hour away from here.
- What kind of car does your mom drive?
- A Taurus. Why?
According to John Douglas,
the Volkswagen Beetle
was a serial murderers'
car of choice.
That's weird. You know who has a VW?
That crazy janitor at school.
- Maybe he's a serial killer.
- That guy is a freak.
I mean, he walks around
all day at school,
mumbling to himself,
mopping the floors.
I heard they hired him off some mental
institution program or something.
( barking )
That fucking dog
keeps me up all night long.
You know, Edmund Kemper once said
that the true measure of a psychopath
lies in the quality
of his animal torture.
Ithink you should
kill the dog.
I was thinking about that, but I thought
I'd be better off killing people.
You should take this one step at a time.
You don't wanna rush into anything.
I think you need to start small.
- Kill it.
- Fine.
I'll kill a fucking dog.
You know what?
You should do it after the show.
- We gotta go.
- Okay.
( crowd screaming )
What's this about women in the army?
What kind of a military is that, huh?
I'll tell you what, I think
those guys are all a bunch of fags
and they like to put on
their little green uniforms
and parade around,
am I right? Ha!
You are such a dickhead.
Pull up your pants.
You're talking out your ass.
I was in the military.
And I worked with a lot of women.
And not one of them was a fag.
- Jesus, Vince, man--
- Hey! Can it, boy!
I didn't know
you were in the military.
Military was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
You know, I was raised up in Alabama
by a one-titted whore.
Whoring for a living,
what my momma was doing.
Whenever she played out on me,
my grandma and my grandpa raised me.
They died when I was 16
and then I went to the army.
- I didn't know, I--
- Well, now you know.
- I'm sorry.
- Fighting in Granada for the US of A,
storming the medical campus,
hand-to-hand combat
with Mexican medical students.
That's so shitty.
It's a good thing,
that army training.
I pass that on to my gymnasium
class students, too.
- I'm sorry, Vince.
- Oh, shut up.
You're not a man. You're a prancing,
little ball, a sissy thing.
Look, Vince,
I didn't know you were--
Oh, I'm just funnin' you.
I'm just funnin' you.
Casey: Oh, wow.
- Great Marilyn Manson concert.
- Casey: Yeah.
- You left your keys in the car.
- Oh, shit.
Do you have anything
we can break in with?
No.
We gotta call a locksmith.
- How are you doing, Vince?
- Hey, Ray, how are you doing?
- Good, good, good. How's work?
-You know how it is.
Little bastards don't appreciate
nothing that you do for 'em.
Wipin' their asses one day
and their noses the next.
How is it going
with that serial killer?
Between you and me,
we got a few suspects.
We 're looking
for a younger man.
Because lots of these psychos,
they look for victims their own age.
Uh-huh. Well, if you're
looking for a young guy
that has the wants and desires
of a woman trapped inside a man's body,
you oughta talk
to Pessin over here.
- Jesus, I said I was sorry.
- Yeah.
You know, speaking of...
that serial killin' business,
I got this kid
in my gymnasium class
who says he wants to grow up
and be a serial killer.
-You are kidding me.
- I'm not kidding.
He's in therapy for it.
I mean, you ask me,
he couldn't kill a housefly
if his head was shaped
like a swatter.
But somebody believes him.
They got him in that counseling.
All right.
- What's this kid's name?
- Noland.
- Casey Noland.
- All right.
- I'm on it.
- Good.
- ( pager beeps )
- Goddamn it.
All right.
I'm out of here.
Get everybody a drink on me,
except for Pessin.
Casey Noland.
- Thanks for the ticket.
- No problem.
Who else was I gonna ask--
it wasn't a date.
You know what, Sasha,
I'm kind of embarrassed about this,
but... I really like you.
( car door shuts )
Grimaldi:
You called for a locksmith?
Mr. Grimaldi?
Well, corn hole me
at the Saturday dance,
Casey Noland, my favorite
gymnasium class student.
- You're a locksmith?
- I am a locksmith, Casey,
on weeknights and weekends.
Gotta work a second job,
you know?
Well, with the economy
being what it is...
quite frankly, the working man's place
in the work force is always at risk,
being usurped
by foreign influences.
But I don't have to tell you that.
You probably know what I mean.
Maybe not.
What do we got going on here?
I-- I locked
my keys in the car.
All righty, then.
I'll justjump right in,
have this worked out
in two shakes of a Iamb's tail,
have you and your little
pretty friend out of here, double time!
Thanks, Mr. Grimaldi.
Your name's... Sasha, isn't it?
Yeah, I had you
sophomore year.
( laughs )
You sure did.
There you go, Case'.
Thanks, Mr. Grimaldi.
How much-- how much
do I owe you?
You can give me Sasha
and we'll call it even.
Ha! Just funnin' ya.
No charge tonight.
You two kids run along.
- Thanks. That's really nice.
- Yeah, thanks.
Now, don't tell anybody
at high school.
I wouldn't wanna ruin
my reputation as a hard ass.
Sure.
Drive carefully!
Good night.
Sleep tight.
Ah, enough of this shit.
I'm gonna go see the real thing.
I still can't believe that dick
had to be the one to help us.
i don't know why
you hate him so much.
He seems like a really nice guy.
- I had a good time tonight.
- Yeah, me too.
Thanks for going
with me.
Good night.
I-- I'll call you tomorrow.
( muffled screams )
- ( squeaks )
. He-.
(grunts)
(toy laughing)
Let's get messier.
( laughs )
How groovy!
No, that's too “Evil Dead.“
Time to carve some puppy?
Fuck it!
Let's get over with it.
( squeals )
(engine sputters)
- ( engine humming)
- ( shot fires)
(yelps)
( squeals )
Hygiene isn't just about
“Hey, get the germs off me, man.“
But it's also very important
on a job interview...
- Did you do it?
- No, I couldn't do it.
- He was too cute.
-You couldn't even kill a dog.
I just--
Now, it's also very important, when
you're going on thatjob interview...
Did you hear what happened
with Marni Greenstein?
- No, what happened?
- She disappeared last night.
There were cops swarming
around her house all morning.
- Are you through?
- Yes.
Are you sure there's nothing you'd like
to share with the class?
- No.
- Okay.
Now, teeth-- brush 'em.
You don't wanna go to that interview
with your breath smelling like “booty."
Today we're gonna play
a little word association.
I say a word and you tell me the first
word or two that comes to mind.
Gotcha.
- Red.
- Blood.
- Boy.
- George.
- Girl.
- Boy George.
- Casey!
- Me?
- ( sighs )
- What?
You know, you've really been
improving this past week.
You cleaned yourself up.
You're dressing better.
Your grades are improving.
I'm really proud of you.
- But why can't you ever be serious?
- ( knocking on door)
Come in.
- Ahh, Ms. Sally Lindon?
- Yes?
I'm Detective
Raymond Berro. I...
I'm looking for one of your students.
Casey Noland?
- Is there a problem?
- No, ma'am.
There's no problem.
Nothing's wrong.
But I would like
to talk to him alone.
- Well, I'll be right outside.
- Fine, thank you.
So, hot shot,
I hear you wanna be
a serial killer.
Yeah, so?
So, I have
a missing girl here
with your name
written all over it.
You know this girl?
Yeah, it's Marni Greenstein.
She's in one of my classes.
I understand
you don't get along very well.
Yeah, she was
a stuck-up bitch.
- Where were you last night?
- I went to a concert.
- Yeah, what did you do after that?
- I went home and I went to bed.
- Well, I--
- What did you do?
- Okay, I admit it. Ijerked off.
Hey!
( loud whistle)
Don't become
a smart ass with me.
- Ray.
- Yeah.
Excuse me, but there's--
there's something you should see.
You don't go anywhere.
We interviewed
a teacher named Korn.
He claims he sent the girl
to the lost and found.
So, we go
to the lost and found...
it's in the boiler room.
So, we searched
the place, right?
And we find this,
Marni Greenstein's notebook.
- Who's this guy?
- He's the janitor.
Custodian.
Head custodian.
Custodian. Excuse me.
Not only that, he's got a very keen
interest in young girls.
I think this is our guy.
I say we take him down to the station
and see if we get him to talk.
All right.
But in the meantime...
I wanna keep my eye
on this kid.
Brad, bring him in.
Wait a minute.
This thing is way
too damn loud.
I'm surprised
you didn't get caught last night.
You know, Frank, the janitor?
He was arrested.
Yeah, I know.
They got the wrong guy.
He even doesn't
fit the profile.
They must know something
we don't.
They don't know anything.
They're stupid cops.
No, they questioned you.
We gotta be careful now.
What does it matter?
I couldn't even kill a damn dog.
- I am a failure.
- Relax.
You just need
to kill a real person.
After your first,
it's not supposed to be that tough.
I think I'm gonna go and kill
one of those old people first.
Just to practice.
I promise, ifl ever get caught, I'll
tell everyone you were my first kill.
I hope I am your first.
We should scope out
the old age home tomorrow.
- You wanna go?
- Yeah, sure.
♫ in a peril-act world... ♫
- Casey, what are we looking for?
- Someone who looks senile.
- How about that one?
- Let me see.
- Casey: oh-ho, per'lbct.
- So, what are you gonna do?
I figure I'll find a good time
to go up there
and grab one of these old farts
and carry 'em away.
Do you think
that's gonna work?
They're so dazed,
they don't know what's going on.
I'll drive her
to some secluded spot and kill her.
Unbelievable! That old bag's been
walking in circles for hours.
I never wanna get old.
They look so bored and hopeless.
Yeah, God,
I hate retirement homes.
it's like you can smell
the death inside.
Hey, wait, listen to this.
There's more
Volkswagen stuff in this book.
It says that a lot of the serial killers
own VW Beetles,
but then they switch to a van.
“Because unlike a car,
in the back of the van you can do
whatever you want and not be seen.
You have in effect
a mobile murder site.“
- You know who drives one of those?
- I almost forgot...
they let Frank, the janitor, go
last night. They said he had an alibi.
And that the police think that the
killer had some kind of special tools,
so that he could sneak into these homes
so easily. They're calling him--
The locksmith killer.
Sasha, it's Grimaldi!
Oh, come on.
I agree there are a lot of similarities,
but I refuse to believe that a high
school gym teacher is a serial killer.
He is a war vet. He's probably killed
many people. Plus, he drives a VW van.
You're insane. Just because you don't
like the guy, it doesn't mean--
Look, all these victims are
young girls, high school girls.
Have you seen “Silence of the Lambs“?
We covet what we see every day.
This guy is surrounded
by hot chicks in short shorts.
Casey, that's a movie.
It's not real.
Grimaldi is the killer.
I'm gonna prove it.
- Hit any?
- Three for three.
Cool.
I need a favor.
-You need some C-4?
- No, no C-4.
I need some information. Can you go
to the police station with your dad?
Yes, I could go there.
He's going there tonight.
Can you see what you can dig up
on Mr. Grimaldi?
Yes, I will bring a shovel.
What do you need it for?
Ijust have a hunch.
Good to go.
Time to kill.
- Come on, it's time to go to bed.
- Charles, is that you?
- No, my name isn't Charles. Come on.
- I know that's you, Charles.
Oprah, come meet my grandson Charles.
He just stopped by for a visit.
What a lovely surprise!
So nice to meet you...
Charlie.
Come on, it's time to go in!
- Time to go in. Good girl.
-You know, I think-- I think...
- Charlie is gonna come with us.
- Oh, shit.
- Aren't you, Charles?
- Yeah.
What are you doing, Amil? You're not
messing up my computers again, are you?
- No, I'm just playing some games.
- Where's your dad?
He is in the dark room.
Losen
Hey, everyone.
This is my grandson, Charlie.
Nice to meet you, son.
We've heard so much about you.
Look at those dimples.
He's adorable.
- Now, what's with all those tools?
- He's a big-time carpenter.
Just look at that punum!
He's got your looks.
So, where's the girlfriend?
You're not one of them faggots, are you?
Holly shite!
Whoo-oo!
- Have you constructed big sky rises?
- Do you build mansions?
Now, with all those tools,
you must be a busy boy.
Jesus Christ!
I'm not a carpenter!
I'm an undercover detective.
Yeah, I'm currently tracking a serial
killer who goes after young girls.
Wow, how do you do that?
First, I draw a psychological
profile of the murderer.
I figure out his motive, his weapons,
any pattern that he may be killing.
How do you know?
Many serial killers,
they fit a particular lifestyle.
They're very charismatic,
although they lack soul.
Thank you for coming
to see me, Charlie.
You know I don't
have much time.
I've been telling my friends
about you for years.
They started to think you don't exist.
I'm so proud of you.
When you were younger,
you were such a loose cannon,
but you've become
such a respectable young man.
I love you, Charlie.
I love you too, Gram.
Mr. Pekla, what job experiences
do you have?
- I worked in a fast food restaurant.
- Mm-hmm.
They fired me.
I pissed in their shake machine.
Dude, please.
Try to take this seriously.
( bell ringing )
What's wrong?
I had another bad fight
with my parents last night.
- And how'd you do?
- I bonged.
That old lady thought
I was her grandson.
I'm gonna give up.
This is getting really ridiculous.
You're not giving up.
Tonight.
You and me at the park.
You want me
to kill you tonight?
Yes, I still wanna be
your first victim.
- Are you sure you wanna die?
- Yeah.
Yeah, definitely.
Tonight...
at the park.
Yes, ma'am.
Uh-huh.
The kid was by the Palms
nursing home last night.
I want you to stop by later
and see what he was up to.
Hold on, please.
Ray, I'm following three other leads--
Do it.
Go ahead, please.
Were your parents related
before they were married?
Get your ass up that rope.
Mr. Grimaldi,
I have a meeting
with Ms. Lindon today.
Another one
of those stupid meetings.
Casey, when are you
gonna learn?
The discipline
that you need,
the help that you need,
is right here in gymnasium class.
You're right.
If I could just climb that rope,
- my life would be wonderful.
- Listen to me,
you pole-smoking
“Playgirl" subscriber.
You will treat me
with respect in my class.
Do you understand me?
Repeat that!
I will treat you
with respect in your class.
Get the hell out of here!
Tell me about your childhood.
Well, Ms. Lindon,
it was kind of tough.
I was a bastard child.
And my mother told me my father
was probably a sailor she met one night.
Then, when I was seven,
she remarried a man named Mike...
Mike “Cock-In-You.“
And he used to tease me.
He used to send me to school in dresses.
He said I wasn't manly enough.
If that wasn't bad enough,
he left my mother when I was 14
and by that time,
I had a nine-year-old half sister.
And my mother was afraid that I'd
rape her. So, every night, before bed,
she'd lock me up
in the basement and I spent...
many nights planning
my revenge on that bitch!
- Are you finished?
- No, wait.
I didn't tell you
about my uncle Bob, Bob Booey.
When are you gonna grow up
and start acting like an adult?
You can't spend
the rest of your life goofing off.
I'm 17 years old. Why is everyone
in such a hurry for me to grow up?
Everybody else your age realizes
it's time to start planning their lives.
You know, I don't wanna be
like everybody else.
Well, if you're not,
you're gonna be left behind.
Everybody else will be married
and in good steadyjobs,
while you're still trying to decide
what you want to be.
- Do you wanna be some kind of freak?
- A freak?
Why am I a freak?
Look, every time somebody
wants to do something different,
you shrinks
classify them as crazy.
Half the kids my age say
they're gonna do something
and they're not gonna
end up doing it.
The ones that are gonna do it,
they're not gonna be happy.
- That's not necessarily true.
- Are you happy?
We're talking about you, Casey.
And I'm not saying you're crazy.
You know what?
I am crazy.
I am a fucking psychopath
and I'm proud of it.
I have no ambition?
I have ambition.
- I wanna be a serial killer.
-You're not a killer, Casey.
- It's not something you can become.
- Yeah, we'll see about that.
I just wish that you could take all this
knowledge about murder and death
and apply it
to something more positive.
Positive? Positive?!
We live in a world where a man kills
his wife and gets off scot free.
Teenagers are having babies
and throwing them in dumpsters.
My father is getting shot
by a bank robber.
- How positive do you want me to be?
- Casey! Casey!
Yo, Casey,
where have you been, man?
- I've been looking for you everywhere.
- I got to get the hell out of here.
I've got that information
that you asked for.
Vince Grimaldi lives
in a small apartment
on Gayhouse Lane with his mother.
Twice he tried to become a cop,
but he failed the examination.
Twice. You know,
that is not that unusual.
A lot of people fail
that psychological stuff.
But this,
this is unusual, man!
- Check this out!
- What is it?
See, this is some information
that you did not ask for.
You see, I dug a little deeper
and came up with this shit right here.
Grimaldi was in a mental institution
when he was a teenager.
- Oh, shit!
- Yeah.
This motherfucker
killed his grandparents?
Yeah.
How can they let him
become a teacher? It doesn't--
I know. His mother, she convinced them
to seal his file when he turned 18.
I guess they thought
they cured him.
- How did you get this if the file was--
- Don't worry about it, man.
I just get into the mental health
main frame using a CIA hub.
I just hack that shit.
So, it's no big deal.
- I owe you one... seriously.
- I know how you can repay me.
Take some C-4
and blow this motherfucker up.
Fucking boom! Fuck!
C-4, man.
That's the shit, man.
I've got the skill to kill.
I've got the urge to purge?
Fuck!
- I can't do it.
- Why not?
- You're just sitting there.
- What do you want me to do?
I don't know.
- Run away from me, I guess.
- Okay.
What's wrong?
Amil dug up info on Grimaldi.
This guy's a psycho, Sasha.
- He's killed people before.
- Oh, come on.
They wouldn't let a murderer
be a high school teacher.
They don't know.
His files were sealed.
All the research we've done
points directly to him.
- So, what are you gonna do?
- I don't know.
Don't do anything
stupid, okay?
Why don't you call that cop?
That guy is almost about as big
as an asshole as Grimaldi is.
I'm kind of exposing myself.
If there's one person I could kill,
it would be Grimaldi.
You know, it's getting late.
We really should go.
- What is this?
- It's nothing.
You tried
to commit suicide?
Why didn't you tell me?
It's nothing I like
to brag about, okay?
- What-- I mean--
- I screwed it up.
- The first time...
- The first time?
I swallowed a--
a bottle of pills.
And then a month ago,
I slit my wrists.
And I screwed it up.
Why?
I just get depressed.
And I don't have anyone to talk to.
My parents are always out
making money or something.
It's not like I have all these friends.
I'm not some pom-pom cheerleader.
- So, this was all bullshit?
- No, Casey--
You couldn't kill yourself, so you had
to get me to do the job for you?
All the research, the practice,
you were just manipulating me
to get what you wanted from me.
You lied to me, Sasha.
This whole thing was a lie!
- Well, it was a lie at first--
- I trusted you!
Yeah, “Let me be your first victim
so I can become famous.“
I can't believe
I listened to that bullshit!
Casey, wait!
- Ray, Ray...
- Yeah?
You are not gonna
believe this.
Rose Wyman was found dead in her room
at the Palms nursing home this morning.
Okay, that's sad, but guess
who was the last person to see her?
- I'm on it.
- Ha!
( knock on door)
-You're Mrs. Noland?
- Yes.
Detective Raymond Berro.
A woman died
in an old age home last night,
and it seems that your son was
the last person she spoke to.
You can't possibly think that Casey
could have something to do with that.
Hey, looks like she died
of a heart failure.
But I still need
to question your son.
Grimaldi's got Sasha!
Let's go!
- Go where?
- Where? I don't know-- his house.
You think he takes girls to kill them
at his mom's crappy little apartment?
Where would he go?
How the hell am I supposed to know?
You're the one that did the research.
- Casey: Shit!
- He's not here.
- He's probably at the neighbor's.
- Which neighbor?
- The Feldmans, next door.
- Mm-hmm.
All right. Umm...
There was a guy named Beswick
and he used to take his victims
to the basement of his factory.
- So?
- The school! Go to the school!
Hey, kids!
I hope we're not too late.
Shit!
It's locked.
Stand back.
What the hell is that?
C-4.
I told you it'd come handy.
- What? You carry it around with you?
- Never leave home without it.
You militia fuck!
Is it “blue to red“
or “red to green“?
( laughs )
- ( clock rings)
- Oh shit!
Shit!
-Amil!
- Blue to yellow.
It was blue to yellow.
- It was awesome.
- Probably got to get you to a hospital.
No, no. I'm fine.
- I'm fine. Just go save Sasha.
- All right.
( gasping )
The office.
- What happened, kid?
- It was beautiful.
Okay, I put about
350 pounds on here.
- ( grunts )
-You know I'm gonna kill you later.
But at least you'll have
the firmest buttocks in the morgue.
Well, well...
if it isn't my favorite sissy boy,
Casey Noland.
What the hell happened
to your southern accent?
My southern accent?
I just decided...
to stop doing it.
Take care now.
Casey?
Casey, what are you doing
with all these tools?
This ain't “Home Improvement,“ boy!
Casey?
Casey! Casey!
Don't let me catch you!
Casey.
Did you fall down?
You know, it's a shame
I'm gonna have to kill you.
I was looking forward to you
being the first student ever
to fail gymnasium class.
I dug up the papers
about your past.
- Everybody's gonna find out about you.
- Not if you're dead.
- Put down the knife, Vince.
- Ray!
I am so happy you're here.
You know, I caught the kid red-handed,
and he tried to kill me.
- He's full of shit.
- Vince...
I need you to put down the knife.
No problem, Ray.
You know me,
law-abiding citizen, huh?
- Casey: Look out!
- Ah!
Nothing personal, Ray.
Ouch!
Casey, did you say goodbye
to detective Berro?
Casey, stop.
See, now that you've run away,
I'm just gonna have to cut
your heart out,
show it to you
and make a hand puppet, huh?
Casey?
Casey,
you forgot to say good night
to Detective Gurgling-on-his-own-blood.
( laughs )
Casey!
Just show yourself, you idiot.
You know I'm gonna find you.
Case'!
Well, you get an “A"
for rope climbing skills,
but an “F" for hiding places.
You stupid imbecile,
did you actually think
I wouldn't see you hanging from a rope
in the middle of a big, empty room?
Get your ass down here.
Casey! Get your ass
down here!
(coughing)
I gotta hand it to you,
Colombo.
That was a pretty impressive
detective work on your part.
-You killed a cop. You're finished.
- Oh, I'm finished?
You think they actually are going
to suspect their drinking buddy?
You asshole! You're the one
that's been bragging for two weeks
that you wanna be a serial killer.
Who do you think they're gonna believe?
You could teach me
how to be a serial killer.
What!?
Casey, you're a girl.
You have to be a man
to be a serial killer.
I know everything. The bodies,
you turn them into furniture.
You depersonalize them--
inanimate objects.
You wanna feel
like you own these girls.
Like-- like they're
your possessions.
Possessions?
God damn it!
You have completely bought
into this touchy-feely horseshit
that they're teaching you
in psychotherapy.
i don't want 'em as possessions.
I'm just trying to rid society
of some of its filth. That's all.
Yeah, I took a shotgun and killed
my grandmother and grandfather,
but! was doing them a favor.
And then I get sent off
to a mental hospital,
where they thought
they could cure me.
They didn't do
a very good job.
No, they didn't,
'cause I don't have a disease.
I'm the one who's healthy.
It's the rest of society
that is diseased.
Look at these girls
in gym class...
with their breasts bulging out
and their tight little shorts on.
They're just gonna
grow up to be whores
and sluts,
and real estate agents.
You've been rejected
by girls your whole life.
What teenage girl wants to be
with some lame-ass gym teacher?
First of all, fuck you.
Second of all,
this conversation is over,
'cause I'm gonna
kill you now
and turn you
into a piece of furniture.
( saw whirring stops )
( laughs )
You are so pathetic.
You bring a power tool
to kill your gym coach
and you don't get good batteries?
What do you intend to do with that?
Scratch me to death?
Huh? You can't throw it.
You throw
like a fucking girl!
Not anymore.
I had a damn fine
gymnasium class coach.
Good throw... bad catch.
Sasha.
It's over.
Grimaldi's dead.
Yeah. I'm all right.
How about you?
I'll be okay.
Did he touch you?
No, but he said he wanted
to make me into a coffee table.
After this, you still don't wanna
kill yourself, do you?
No.
I don't think I'm cut off
to be a serial killer.
It doesn't matter.
- What do you think?
- This is so good.
God, I wish
your dad was here.
He'd be so proud of you.
So, ifl have a problem with Mr. Korn,
you're gonna back me up?
You bet. You're
on the right track now, guy.
Thanks, Mom.
I love you, honey.
I simulated the whole fetal pig
dissection. It's totally interactive.
Casey, this is great!
I can use this in all my classes.
So?
I'm giving you an “A.“
It's great to see you
take more interest in school.
Killer.
I believe the next individual to go up
and speak would be Mr. Casey Noland.
This should prove to be
very interesting, Mr. Noland.
Because your grade
in this class hinges on this paper.
My paper is entitled,
“Serial Killing for Dummies.“
“A serial murderer
is like a hunter,
he must always be
on the hunt,
looking for the victim, the opportunity,
who is most vulnerable.
As an agent in the FBI's national center
for analysis of violent crime,
I will have to put myself
in the position of a hunter
of a serial offender.
I've got to be able to profile
my potential prey,
determine what
his next move is...
...detectives and crime scene analysts
take a number of unrelated clues
and turn them
into a coherent narrative.
They're telling a story
that victims can no longer tell.
As John Douglas explains,
if you want to understand the artist,
you must look
at the paintings.“
That was fly, Mr. Noland.
You got yourself an “A.“
Motherfucking kids!
Killing the goddamned
teachers.
( laughs )
Un-fucking-believable, yeah!
And you know...
who's gonna have to clean up
this fucking shit, right?
The head...
fucking custodian,
that's who, yeah.
Fucking tater tots,
and blood,
blood, and tater tots.
Jesus Christ!
( sighs )
I gotta see some titties later.
I got titties on my mind here.
Yeah, what do they care?
What the fuck, huh?
Sure, sure, sure.
They just make fun
of me, right?
Make fun of the job.
I'm just a dummy.
“Look at the dummy clean it up.
The dummy will clean it up.“
Yeah, well.
Fuck them, huh?
I'm gonna kill
all those fuckers. Yeah.
Yeah, serial killing, uh-huh.
(laughs)
Yeah, that's for dummies.
( laughing )
It's for dummies.
♫ Buried my own head ♫
♫ Buried my own dead ♫
♫ Buried my own brain ♫
♫ And met her
in there yesterday ♫
♫ Hiding my own fears ♫
♫ Hiding all these years ♫
♫ Hiding my own brain ♫
♫ And hiding my yesterday ♫
♫ Whatlknow,
yes, what i know:
♫ Can't you see
l'm trying to believe in you? ♫
♫ So please believe in me ♫
♫ And what i am is
what i am-- ♫
♫ Burying my own head ♫
♫ Well, truth are lies and lies
are truth, so what do you believe? ♫
♫ l'm trying to believe in you,
so please believe in me ♫
♫ And what i am
is what i am, it ain't easy ♫
♫ Burying my own head ♫
♫ Bury, bury, bury, bury,
bury, yeah ♫
♫ And l'm hiding, hiding,
hiding, hiding, hiding ♫
♫ l'm buried:
♫ l'm buried, oh buried ♫
♫ And I'm hiding ♫
♫ l'm hiding, l'm hiding ♫
♫ What i know is
what i know ♫
♫ Because you'll see
l'm trying to believe in you ♫
♫ So please believe in me ♫
♫ And what i am is
what i am, and it ain't easy ♫
♫ And hiding my own-- ♫
♫ Well, truth are lies and lies
are truth, so know what you believe in ♫
♫ l'm trying to believe in you,
so please believe in me ♫
♫ And what i am is
what i am, and it ain't easy-- ♫
♫ Bury, bury, bury,
bury, bury, yeah ♫
♫ And l'm hiding, hiding,
hiding, hiding, hiding ♫
♫ l'm buried:
♫ Buried, oh buried ♫
I And l'm hiding,
l'm hiding... ♫
( screams )
♫ Buried my own head ♫
♫ Buried my own head. ♫