WOMAN:
Life isn't fair sometimes.
Most of us live with that.
But tomorrow,
my three daughters and I
have a chance to right a wrong
that started
seventeen years ago.
We have a chance to confront
face to face
the man
who changed our lives.
A chance to ask him
questions that,
frankly, we're not sure
we want the answers to.
My daughter Andrea,
she's stronger and
doing better than she thinks.
I'm worried about
Marcia though.
Can I call you daddy?
Would that be okay?
WOMAN: She's young
and so sensitive.
And Christine, my oldest.
She doesn't know it yet.
But in the end,
I think she might be the one
to hold us all together.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SLOW INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
My mother used to say
life is like the weather.
Sometimes it's sunny and
other times it's
filled with rain.
But when it's windy,
things just get blown around.
looking back at my life,
I realize,
my mother was one smart lady.
[DOG BARKING]
[PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
And I'll never forget
the first time I saw him.
♪ You ask how much I need you
♪ Must I explain
♪ I need you, oh my darling
♪ like roses need rain
♪ You ask how long
I'll love you
♪ I'll tell you true
♪ Until the twelfth of never
♪ I'll still be loving you
♪ Hold me close
♪ Never let me go
♪ Melt my heart
Like April snow
♪ I'll love you till
The bluebells
♪ Forget to bloom
♪ I'll love you
Till the clover
♪ Has lost its perfume
He was so handsome.
We were so much in love,
but that's when the weather
started to turn.
SOLDIER: Hey, Greg.
WOMAN: Hey.
What're you doing?
GRIFFIN: Mad dog. Mad dog.
Private Griffin reporting Ma'am.
For a matinee.
Mrs. Griffin.
Yeah.
The marines have landed.
But we need a beach.
Here, right here.
Here's our beach.
These are for you, Patsy.
And this is for me.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
GRIFFIN: What?
Now come on, Patsy.
No secrets between us.
Remember.
PAT: I just can't
believe you love me.
I love you.
And we're really married.
We're married.
My sweet, shy, Patsy.
I love you so much.
I hate it when you're not here.
I'm right here.
I mean, when you go back
on duty at the base.
And I'm all alone here.
I can't wait until we go on
back home to Virginia.
When you get out,
and I can take care of you.
And you can go back to school.
I just want to fly, Patsy.
Just want to fly.
And we're going to have babies,
lots and lots of babies.
Just the two of us.
Like this.
Together.
Always together, Patsy
Just the way we are, now.
-GIRLS: Hi, Mrs. Griffin,
Hi, Andrea.
-Hi.
Do you think I'll ever
look like that again?
CHRISTINE: Daddy, Daddy, Daddy.
Yes, my little angel.
Can you take me flying?
My angel wants to go flying?
Let's go flying, come on.
Ready?
One.
Uh, two.
Here we go, taking off.
GRIFFIN: There's my
little angel flying.
MIG, six o'clock, take it out.
[MIMICS GUNFIRE]
-Everybody, for the landing,
come on little angel.
-[BABY CRYING]
How was that for flying?
You know one day,
you're really gonna fly.
Tommy?
Fly Andrea too.
[ANDREA CRYING]
Pick her up.
Wanna watch tv with Daddy?
Watch movies, come on.
[ANDREA CRYING]
Want to taste this?
GRIFFIN: It's good, huh?
Honey,
honey...
Why don't you
want to touch Andrea?
Why don't you want to touch me?
You never touch me.
Baby,
I love you.
I don't know what's happening.
All our plans and
all our dreams...
Your plans, Pat.
And your dreams.
You were always on me about
school and families and having
babies.
Yeah well, I didn't want
any of this.
What?
All I ever wanted to do, Pat,
was to fly a damn plane.
And stay the way we were,
just the two of us.
-Forever.
-But we wanted a family.
No.
No, you wanted a family, Pat.
Like I had anything to say
about you getting pregnant
all the time.
My little angel, Christine,
she was enough for me.
[ANDREA CRYING]
Doesn't that ever stop?
All day and all night.
-I'm sorry. I'll get her.
-[CONTINUES CRYING]
[ANDREA CONTINUES CRYING]
MAN: Come on.
PAT: Oh, that wasn't it.
Can't wait to get my hands
on a double fudge.
WOMAN: Sounds good.
Christine, honey, sit down.
WOMAN: Sit down sweetie.
You think I'm fat?
I think you're pregnant.
I know that.
I always am.
Now what's that
supposed to mean?
-You want some money?
-No, got it.
Is there something else?
Where's Tommy?
This is Tommy's car, isn't it?
Where is he?
Kevin, you want a cookie?
Pat, what are you doing?
Will you stop doing this
to yourself?
Did you hear the
way she said his name?
Tommy.
Like she knew him.
Like she'd been with him.
Come on.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Must be Vi.
Hello.
My name is Marjean Stewart.
I'm sorry to bother you
like this, Mrs. Griffin.
But I had to talk to you.
Come in.
Uh, Pat, why don't I
get the kids and get out
of here for a little while.
[BABY CRYING]
WOMAN: It's all right,
we're going to go outside.
We'll be right outside, Pat.
Mrs. Griffin,
I,
Tommy and I...
I'm pregnant.
MARJEAN: I thought Tommy...
I really thought
we'd be together.
I didn't know that...
You...
How far along are you?
Two months.
But the doctor says,
I can still get rid of it.
I have no money.
I have no place to go.
I have no one but Tommy.
PAT: How much?
What?
How much money do you need?
I don't know, but Tommy
doesn't have any.
This isn't coming from Tommy.
No.
I can't take your money.
Do you want to have his baby?
I don't know.
Well, you think about it.
And let me know.
Mrs. Griffin...
I'm sorry
[SLOW INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRYING]
Hi, Honey.
What're you still
doing up?
Waiting for you.
Okay, well, I'm here.
What a day.
I had a visitor today.
Oh, who's that?
A girl by the name of
Marjean Stewart.
Who says she's pregnant,
with your baby.
And you believed her?
Yes, I did.
Did she ask you for any money?
No.
But I was going to offer.
Oh, Patsy.
Sweetheart,
that's the oldest scam
in the book.
It used to happen to us
on the base all the time.
I mean, these young girls would
scout out he married men
and then they'd go to
their wives, and give
them a story
about how lonely and pregnant
and how broke they were.
And by the time
the husband got home,
that girl was long gone.
-With about
five hundred dollars of cash.
-But she knew your car.
I took the kids for ice cream,
and she...
-GRIFFIN: Where? Bunny burgers?
-Um-hmm.
Well, sweetheart, I take
the girls there all the time.
And that's where she
probably saw me.
It's not true?
No.
No, sweetheart.
It's not true.
You're my girl.
I love you.
Shy, innocent, little Patsy.
Ah, too long.
[TV PLAYING IN BACKGROUND]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Hi, honey.
Look at your nose.
Here you go.
Go play on the slides now.
Be careful, though.
Don't get hurt, Kevin.
Hey Pat...
Pat, what's the matter?
What is this?
I found them in...
From his jacket.
What are you going to do?
I don't know what to do.
Help me.
Tell me what to do.
Well, talk to him,
Confront him with it.
I can't.
Why?
I'm afraid he might leave.
If he leaves I don't know
what I'd do.
Pat, stop that.
Listen,
you're holding on to something
that doesn't exist.
This man isn't yours anymore.
Why should he be?
Look at me. [GASPS]
I'm a mess.
Honey...
Maybe if I...
If I fixed up a little,
you know,
put some makeup on
and fixed my hair.
-Made really nice dinner.
-Pat stop.
Stop it.
Pat, romance and makeup
are not going to fix this.
You're not the
problem, Pat. He is.
Aww.
[CLOCK TICKING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Where have you been?
Don't you never ever
ask me where I've been.
You understand me?
-You do not have the right to...
-I am your wife.
-I have the right...
-You have the right to nothing!
Because you do not own me, Pat.
I guess not.
Not judging from these...
I found them in your jacket.
We are barely getting by,
and you spend our money
like that!
Tommy.
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
-Hi!
-Hi.
It's kind of hard. Um...
Could I borrow some cereal,
and maybe some milk
-from you?
-Of course. Come on in.
No, no.
I just haven't been able
to get to the store.
Why? What's the matter?
Tommy went out for some cereal,
and he hasn't been home for
a couple of days.
-[PATSY SIGHS]
-Don't you say another word.
Tommy...
PATSY: Tommy!
[BABY CRYING]
-Hi, angel.
-Tommy, Tommy, honey.
Talk to me.
Tommy, just talk to me.
[BABY CRYING]
Tommy, please don't.
Don't do this.
Don't... Don't leave us.
Tommy.
I'm sorry. I'll... I'll do
anything you want me to do.
I'll be anything you want me to
be. Just don't do this.
Don't leave.
Please don't.
Tommy, just don't
leave us. Please,
honey, don't do it.
I... Honey, don't.
Tommy!
Tommy, no!
No!
No! [GASPING]
-No! You can't leave us!
-[BABY CRYING]
[PATSY SOBBING]
[ANDREA CRYING]
[ANDREA KEEPS CRYING]
-Please get up, mommy.
-Oh.
[DOORBELL CHIMING]
Hi, Pat.
Where's Tommy?
Tommy? I haven't seen him.
His car's right there
in the driveway, Bill.
I know he's here.
I want to talk to him.
It's okay, Bill.
What's the problem, Pat?
Hi angel.
Hi, daddy.
What do you want?
I want you to come home.
Already been there.
Tommy, for God's sake.
I don't have any money.
I don't even have any food...
-Pat, I will help you out when
I get back on my feet, okay?
-What about
the baby? And Christine,
she adores you.
You're just gonna
run out on her?
-Want some ice cream, honey?
-Where are you going?
-Taking them away from you, Pat.
-What?
You think I want her
to grow up
to be like you, huh?
Get in the car, doll.
I'll get some ice cream.
Come on.
-Tommy.
-I'm taking her away from you.
-I'm gonna get custody, and you
ain't never gonna see her again!
-Stop it!
Stop this.
[CHILD CRYING]
Christine, open the door honey.
Sweetheart, open the door.
Honey, open the door!
Tommy. Stop it! Stop it!
[CAR SCREECHING]
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna call the police!
[CAR SCREECHING]
-We just went for a little ride.
-PATSY: A little ride?
This time.
PATSY: Give her to me!
Gimme her!
Christine! Give her to me.
[GASPING] Tommy!
Don't you ever do that again!
Ever!
[SOBBING] Oh. God.
Oh. How are we gonna live?
Don't worry about it, Pat.
Look, your folks will help
out, until I can kick in.
Pat, you're not going to starve.
Daddy loves you, honey.
Hey, Bill!
Oh!
[GASPING]
[BABY CRYING]
Yes.
My baby. My baby.
[PATSY CHUCKLES]
[BABY CRYING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Pat?
Tommy.
What was it?
It's a girl.
Another one?
Did you name her?
You picked the
other girls' names.
Do you wanna name her?
Why don't you just err,
pick one out of the phone book.
[SIGHS WEARILY]
Why are you here?
-See what you had.
-We had, Tommy.
We had.
Did you know we're on welfare?
Did you hear me?
Your children and I,
are on welfare.
How does that make you feel?
Where's Christine?
She and Andrea,
are with my folks.
Well...
I guess that's it then.
There she is.
[VOICE OVER PA SYSTEM]
Attention. Visiting hours will
be over in 15 minutes.
Oh, my God.
Sweetheart.
Hi, baby. How you doing huh?
Ah, good.
Patsy...
Look, hon. Uh...
What do you say we
take a little walk, okay?
-You want to see her?
-Of course. Yes, yes.
She looks just like Christine
when she was born.
-You remember?
-Yeah.
[OVER PA SYSTEM] Doctor Bartman,
please report to Radiology.
Doctor Bartman...
Honey, I want you
to sit over here.
Oh, I'd be happy to.
Careful.
-You all right?
-Yeah.
Uh,
Tommy's gone.
He took everything.
What?
He emptied out your
bank account.
He defaulted on the car loan,
and they repossessed it.
-He even had
the phone disconnected.
-[PATSY GASPS]
-There's nothing left.
-Oh, God.
Oh, God, This can't be
happening. [SHUDDERS]
How could he do that to us?
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
[GASPING]
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
[BABIES CRYING]
[SERENE INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
That's my sister.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I keep telling you, Patsy,
it won't be so bad.
-You'll get a job, you'll see.
-What kind of job?
Well, maybe you could work
in the drugstore,
in Harry's drugstore
A couple of hours every day.
Mom, I keep telling you.
I can't get a part time job.
If I do that, I lose
my welfare benefits,
and I make more on welfare,
than I would on a job like that.
I'm just stuck.
Now, don't talk like that.
It's just a temporary thing.
And there's no shame in taking
a little help, now and then.
I just wish your dad
and I could help
-some more.
-I know, ma.
I just expected
more from my life.
I'm not prepared for this.
I don't know how to do anything.
I'm... I've no training. I...
My life has come to a big
dead end, all of a sudden.
I just wish...
Wish I could go back to school.
To school?
You've got two years
of junior college.
Isn't that enough?
No. I need to go back
for another two years
and get a degree.
Maybe then I could
get a decent job,
and I could support my kids.
You really want this,
don't you?
Yeah, I do. I
really, really do.
I don't know...
I mean, I don't even
know if they'll let me
go to school on welfare.
Besides, what would
I do with the kids?
Honey,
what are grandmothers for?
Would you take care
of them sometimes?
Of course I would.
You're still my baby.
Ma, I'm so scared.
I know, sweetheart.
I know.
Look, the Welfare Department
has never supported
the idea of a recipient
going to college.
Why not?
What's wrong with wanting
to do something with my life?
If you go back to school,
we have no way of knowing
where your money's going.
The only chance that I have,
of getting off of welfare,
is to go back to school.
Look, I'm... I'm not
getting child support.
I don't think I ever will.
[SIGHS] My husband hasn't
paid me a dime. I don't
even know where he is.
I don't know.
Why don't you make
me a test case?
Nobody's ever asked this before.
Please. I just want to
be able to take care of
myself and my family.
Doesn't that count for anything?
I don't think my supervisor
would approve this.
Ask.
Just ask. Okay?
I'll think about it.
Thank you.
[SOMBER INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE]
[PHONE RINGING]
Good one.
-Whoop!
-Pat! Pat! Jerry, wait.
PATSY: Jerry!
[EXCLAIMS]
-Open it.
-I can't! I can't!
[EXCLAIMING IN JOY]
And the winner is...
PATSY: I can't believe
it's straight A's!
[ALL CHEERING]
-[CROWD CLAPPING]
-[TRIUMPHANT INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
RUTH: Welcome to the IRS.
Now, the coffee boy is
the most important person
to know, of course.
and you'll get your manuals
later on this afternoon.
Let me introduce you to Grace.
-Hi.
-Bob, Julie.
-This is Pat.
-Hi.
-Hi, Pat.
-Any questions?
I don't think so.
Now, you'll start here,
and you'll work your way, all
the way down there to the end.
-To an office?
-Hard work. Dedication.
It's yours if you want it.
Welcome aboard.
Thanks, Ruth.
-But let me know if
you need anything.
-I will.
Good luck, Pat.
[FAIRGROUND MUSIC PLAYING]
Ooh!
Hey! There they are.
-Thank you.
-Christine is having a ball.
-Did you see who's here?
Eddie's Lin and Uncle Crankwood
-I was so surprised.
-Do you have some cake?
-It was wonderful.
Oh, good.
-Hi, Lorraine!
-Pat, free cake.
Where'd you get it?
-I made it.
-Come on.
Who taught her everything
she knew?
[EXCITED CHATTERING]
-Looks good.
-Yes.
LORRAINE: Oh, it's terrific.
I love it.
So good to see you
laughing again.
Yeah, we're still broke,
but it's a start.
[GATE OPENING]
There's Bill.
What's he doing here?
Hi, Bill.
-Pat, I'm sorry to interrupt
your party like this...
-Well, what is it?
It's about Tommy.
What about him?
He came back, didn't he?
Bill, did he? Is he back?
No, Pat.
Tommy's dead.
How did it happen?
Tommy's foster mother
called me this morning.
-He was killed in a plane crash.
-Oh, my God.
[SOBBING] Where?
I don't know exactly.
A friend of Tommy's in Atlanta,
phoned the Griffins.
Are they sending him back here?
They haven't found the body.
-Oh.
-[CHRISTINE CRIES]
It's all right, honey.
-[CRIES]
-Sshhh.
[CRIES BITTERLY]
Oh, there you are.
Girl, I was looking for you.
Your exemption case is here.
Divorced mother.
She's got proof she was
the sole support of the child.
Okay, great. I'll be with her
as soon as I can.
[CHUCKLES] Girl, it's been
like that all day.
Hello?
LADY OVER THE PHONE:
Mrs. Thomas Griffin, please.
-This is she.
-This is Blanche Payton.
I got your name and number
from my husband's sister.
I need to speak with you.
It's about your ex-husband.
What do you want?
I...
Look, I don't have to say this,
but I think...
that the man I married
seven months ago
is your husband.
My husband is dead.
He died in a plane crash
more than three years ago.
I don't think he's dead.
His sister's name is Carol.
She told me how to find you.
Where are you?
I'm at a pay phone
at a restaurant
called Birdie's.
-On Fourth?
-Yes.
I'll be right there.
Mrs. Griffin.
Bennett, it's Pat Bennett.
-Bennett?
-My maiden name.
I met him a year ago.
He told me his name was
John Douglas Payton.
My husband's name was Griffin.
Thomas Griffin.
He lied to me.
We were only married
a short time.
And then two weeks ago,
he walked out on me.
Without a word, he just...
He just left
and he didn't come back.
Do you have a picture of him?
No, I'm sorry.
Well, how do I know
you're telling me the truth?
How do I know this isn't
some kind of...
scam to get money from me?
He's all I had.
Oh, I was so...
I was so crazy in love with him.
He'd hold me and he'd tell me
stories about how...
All he wanted was to fly.
And be with me.
Just him and me.
That's all he wanted.
And I would've done anything.
I would have been anything
he wanted me to be.
How did you find me?
I looked through his things
and I found his sister's
phone number in Miami.
She told me that,
that he'd been married to you.
And we thought that when
he ran out on me,
that he might have
come back to you.
So I was hoping that,
I'd find him here, with you.
You never divorced?
We thought he was dead.
Wait, you have,
you have children?
Three.
You have any pictures?
He told me he didn't want any.
Not with me.
That son of a bitch.
For three years...
I have lived in the mourning
thinking he was dead.
Thinking I would never have
a chance to see him again.
Never have a chance to confront
him with any of this.
Now, I find out he's alive,
but my girls still don't have
their father.
What kind of man does this
to his family?
Well, you know what I think
of him?
Are you going to
tell the girls?
No, I am not going to tell them.
You're going to let them think
that he's still dead.
Lorraine, I don't want them
hurt again.
All these years,
he has manipulated me.
Every time I cry, I thought
my heart would break, he won.
Every time my girls were alone
and hungry, he won.
I am not gonna let him win
anymore.
I am going to take back my life.
Why me? Why me?
I don't need this in my life.
This is disgusting.
-It's... Woah!
-[CHUCKLES]
What are you doing?
It's my Saturday.
I really don't want to be here.
Take the rake, and rake it
and put it in the bag.
CHRISTINE: Mother!
Mom, Lorraine is on the phone.
Christine!
Lorraine, I'll call you back.
She'll call you back.
Christine, the phone is not
gonna reach.
Think a little bit.
[CAR HONKS]
PAT: Come on,
just keep raking all right.
Bye, mom. See ya later.
Where are you going?
-She's going with Tony.
-Tony?
Tony. You know...
[LAUGHS LOFTILY]
Mom, do I wash this in
whites or darks?
Because this isn't dark.
No, honey. Not white. Not dark.
They're colors.
That pink goes with the colors.
Okay, I'll do it.
Okay, bye, honey.
See ya later.
[BELL RINGING]
[TYPING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello.
WOMAN ON PHONE: Mrs. Bennett?
-Yes, this is Miss Bennett.
-About your daughter Marcia.
Yes?
This is Miss Campbell
at her school.
Marcia has been truant for
three straight days.
And it's not the first time.
I think you'd better
come over here.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Well, why haven't I heard
about this before?
Why haven't you called me?
If you look through her file,
you'll find...
dozens of written excuses
forged in your name.
Oh, she wouldn't do that.
But she did.
That's her pattern.
What are you saying?
I'm saying Marcia needs help.
What kind of help?
We have a program for kids like
Marcia who need more attention.
I recommend that we transfer her
to a special class,
but I need your approval.
[DOOR OPENS]
Just, what in the hell
is going on here?
Have you ever wondered
why Marcia ditches school?
Why Christine never goes out?
Or why Andrea can't even keep
a boyfriend
for more than a few weeks.
-Christine!
-Tell her.
Yes, tell me.
Well, I guess I feel like
I'm not good enough to like him,
and then I just suffocate
whoever it is I'm with.
And then, what?
They leave.
Honey.
You don't have to do that
to keep a boy.
I know, but, I just get
so panicky.
CHRISTINE: Have you ever read
any of Marcia's poetry?
Poetry?
She writes about pain
and wishing she was never born.
Oh, honey. Marcia.
Is that true?
Oh, honey.
I've always tried to be there
for you girls.
I think we needed a father, too.
You never let anyone get
close enough to take his place.
Dad really messed us up, Mom.
I never even knew you thought
about him.
CHRISTINE: Yeah.
Yeah, it's like this family
should come with its own
warning label. "No men allowed."
MBA and promotion.
How does it feel?
Good.
-Feels good.
-Uh oh.
What's going on with you?
It's my kids.
Marcia is in all kinds
of trouble at school,
and I never even knew about it.
And Andrea...
I don't think I ever really
realized the effect
not having a father
has had on them.
You've done your best, honey.
Kids get into trouble.
Even in the best of families.
It happens.
On top of everything else,
I get a letter
rejecting my request for Tommy's
social security death benefits
for the girls.
They say, I can't collect, even
though nobody has heard from him
-for more than ten years.
-But why not?
I thought the state of Virginia
declared him legally dead.
They did. Doesn't mean anything.
Just makes his disappearance
legal.
He's out there, Ruth.
He is out there.
I'm gonna try and find him.
I'm gonna make him answer
to those girls.
They're entitled to that.
They're entitled to
child support.
After all he's done, that is the
least he could give them.
Take it easy, girlfriend.
Now, you deserve a break.
Why don't we celebrate your
promotion?
I've been given two tickets
to Congressman Henderson's
fundraiser, this Saturday.
-We're going.
-Ruth, I don't...
Every eligible man
on Capitol Hill will be there.
It'll be fun.
You owe it to yourself.
Saturday.
[PLAYING HARP]
Some nice-looking men here,
don't you think?
-Ruth, stop!
-I just want you to be happy.
-Please.
-Mingle. Talk to people.
Why don't you talk to that
nice, young man over there?
Good to see you again.
Oh. Did you want one?
One was all there was.
And I got it. I'm sorry.
[MUNCHING] Um, Richard.
Pat.
Can I buy you a drink?
Sure.
It's a nice party, isn't it?
I work for the IRS.
I want to say
that right up front.
It usually scares people.
-See ya.
-[LAUGHS] Wait a minute.
What do you do?
Who, me?
Um, I'm an investigator.
Really? An investigator?
What kind?
Private.
-Really?
-Really.
Why? You have something for me?
-Maybe.
-For the IRS?
No. No. Me.
-Ugh, stop it, Pat!
-What?
I promised myself I wasn't gonna
do this tonight.
Come on. Come on.
What do you have?
No. Uh.
What could you possibly have?
Except a pair of
very beautiful eyes?
You had to ask, didn't you?
Well...
An ex-husband that
I'm trying to track down.
[SIGHING] Not another one.
How far have you got?
Well, through his former wife
I tracked him to San Antonio,
but then I ran into a dead end.
He's not there anymore.
Do you know where he worked?
I think he was
an insurance adjuster
for a company called
Transworld Fidelity.
They have one in San Antonio?
Yeah, that's what I called
but he transferred out.
Call the main office.
What if he doesn't even work
for that company anymore?
Well, he still got
to be licensed.
Each state has
only one licensing office.
Fifty offices, fifty calls.
Better than going through
ten thousand
city telephone books.
What if I hired you?
[CHUCKLES]
Ooh! Then we'd have to see
each other again.
Look, you don't have to hire me.
You could do this yourself.
-But I'll tell you what.
-What?
Here's my card.
If you need me,
you give me a call.
Okay?
Thanks.
Okay, Tommy, where are you?
Yes, he disappeared
ten years ago.
At that time, he was working
for you in San Antonio.
Can you help me?
MAN ON PHONE: Privacy laws
are very strict.
All I could do is confirm
or deny.
Look, he's my ex-husband.
Actually, he's disappeared
twice.
He left me alone
with three kids.
What's his name?
Then it was John Douglas Payton.
Do you have a file on him?
Anything?
We have a file for
a John D. Payton.
Do you have his
Social Security number?
-No, I don't.
-Describe him to me.
Uh, six-one.
Brown hair, blue eyes,
about a hundred eighty pounds.
ANDREA: Mom?
Mom, I need five dollars
to go to the movie.
-Who are you talking to?
-Nobody that you know.
My purse is on the table,
in the kitchen.
-I'm going to stop
at Judith's later.
-What?
I'm going to Judith's later.
Can you hold on one second,
please?
You call me when you get there.
-Mom!
-You know the rules. Go on.
Did he leave
a forwarding address?
I can't tell you that.
Well, can you give me
a Social Security number?
I'm sorry, I can't help.
[PHONE DISCONNECTS]
WOMAN: Florida State
Licensing Department.
Yes, I'm looking for an
insurance adjuster by the name
of John Douglas Payton.
John Payton. I'll have
to look him up,
Can you hold on a moment?
Yeah.
Yes, we show a John D. Payton
insurance adjuster in Tampa
at 4682 Ayrshire Drive.
You have a John Payton
in Tampa?
Isn't that who you wanted?
Yes. Yes, it is.
Hold on one second.
Give me that address again.
Uh, that's 4682 Ayrshire Drive.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Whoo!
I've gotta go out.
You finish dinner.
What? Me?
-I'll be back.
-Why is it always me?
-Help your sister.
-Cook, Marcia.
-Clear, Marcia.
Make dinner, Marcia.
-Okay.
-Help your sister.
-What do you--
What are you making anyway?
Bread!
Mr. Frowming. Mr. Frowming.
Richard.
-Pat, what are you doing here?
-Hi.
Your secretary told me
you just left. Guess what?
I found him.
-Great.
-I actually found him.
My ex-husband Tommy
in Tampa, Florida.
-That was after four days
and 32 phone calls.
-Very good.
Now I just have to find out
if this John Payton
which is the name
he's going under,
really is Tommy.
So I want to hire you.
I do. I want you to go down
there and follow him to a
restaurant
and get his fingerprints.
And what would
I do with these fingerprints?
Well, take them to the FBI,
so they can track him down.
Sure, then I'll call you on my
secret decoder ring
with the results, right?
I think you've been watching
too many detective movies, Pat.
I think I have.
Look, I really do have
to find out if it's him.
Look, slow down a bit.
What I can do is
I go down there,
get some photos of him.
if it's Tommy,
you'll know soon enough.
Okay. Great.
Hey, you want have some dinner
or something?
I can't.
The girls have dinner
waiting at home for me.
But I need some more information
about Tommy in Tampa I mean.
Oh, right. Well, listen.
Why don't you come home
with me and have dinner
and we'll talk about it?
Okay.
-But just business talk?
Absolutely.
-Yes.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Richard back already?
Good luck.
MARCA: I'll get it, mom.
-Hi.
-Mom, it's Richard.
-Thank you.
Thanks, honey.
Excuse me.
Here.
[EXHALES]
That's him.
Changed?
A lot.
But you're sure
it's Tommy?
Yeah.
That's him.
You're not gonna
get him back here.
Grant won't sign extradition
orders for cases like this.
Grant?
He's the Common Wealth attorney
for the state of Virginia.
Well, what should I do.
You're gonna have to hire
an attorney in Florida.
And from everything
I know about cases like these,
it could take a year.
A year?
God, not another year.
I know some people down there.
I can't afford an attorney.
I don't have that kind of money.
RICHARD: Don't worry.
I can make some calls.
We can get you somebody good.
Thanks.
Will you take these?
Yeah.
I better tell the girls.
I don't know how they're gonna
take this. I don't know...
what they're gonna do.
Call you tomorrow?
Richard...
Thank you.
Okay.
Are you sure that it's daddy?
I mean, Thomas Griffin.
Actually, years ago,
I found out there was a chance
that he was still alive.
What?
Why didn't you say anything?
Because I was afraid
it might be a blind alley and...
I didn't think it was worth
upsetting our lives.
Well, don't you think
that was up to us?
Yes, but you were all so young.
So what are we gonna do now?
I'm gonna go to Tampa.
For what?
Now that I have proof
that he is actually alive,
I'm gonna try and
go after him for
the back child support
he owes us.
Girls, It's enough for you all
to go to college and then some.
So I'm gonna go down there
and I'm gonna file a petition.
Can we go with you?
PAT: What?
-Can we go too?
-Oh, no.
We have a right to see him.
MARCA: I don't want to see him.
He's never seen me.
He doesn't know who I am.
I don't want him to
know how I feel.
-It's none of his business
-Marcia?
What if he sees me
and he doesn't want me
all over again?
What if he still
doesn't love me?
What will I do?
Marcia?
I know how you feel
You don't, how could you?
Because he was
my father too
He abandoned me
just like he did you.
At least he stuck around
while you were born.
So? He was never there for me.
He was never there
for any of us.
But I still want to meet him.
I want him to know who I am.
[SOBBING]
Come on, Marcia, I wouldn't
want to go without you.
Come on, Marcia.
Girls.
Girls, look
I don't know what's gonna happen
when I get down there.
I don't know how
he's gonna react.
I don't want you
guys to get hurt.
Mom, we have a right
to make this decision.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
I've always want to ask
him why he left us.
I know, so have I.
Me too... me too.
[AEROPLANE LANDING]
Check this out.
Wow.
-Pat? Yeah.
-You must be Frank.
-This is my daughter Andrea.
-Hi, Andrea.
There you are pay the driver.
That's my daughter Christine.
Hi, Christine, here let me
help you with that.
-That's Marcia.
-Hi, Marcia.
Hi, nice to meet you.
If I knew the girls were coming,
I'd have gotten another room.
That's all right, We'll put in
a cot or a pillow.
Doesn't matter. I don't think
we're going to sleep much
any way you know.
Where is the beach?
Where do you think?
Out there.
-Come on, let's get
you checked in.
-All right.
CHRISTINA: Here's your soda.
-PAT: Diet?
-FRANK: Which one's the diet,
that one?
Thank you.
-See you later
-Thanks, guys.
-Take care. Bye.
-Okay, girls. We will.
If we simply file a petition
here in Florida
to accept Virginia's decree
of forty two thousand dollars
in back child support,
Tommy will be notified.
That means he can run again.
He could, but even if he didn't,
this will never get to court.
Then his daughters
would never get to meet him.
We could ask the court
for a writ of ne exeat.
Ne exeat, what's that?
This would allow the sheriff
to arrest Tommy without notice.
Hold him until
he can post bond.
It's rare.
Judges hate to deal with it...
but we could get lucky.
What if we don't get lucky?
What's the least
you want to get
out of all of this?
Five thousand dollars.
That would cover
my expenses so far.
But the most important thing
is I want him to promise
that he'll meet his girls
face to face so that
they can talk to him.
I'll do the best I can.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[LAUGHING]
Don't splash me.
I'm so wet.
So what are you going to
say to Thomas Griffin
when we see him?
I'm gonna ask him
why he didn't love us
enough to stay around.
I think he did love us,
I remember...
What do you remember?
Come on, Chris, you're older.
You had more of him then we did.
He'd be sitting on the couch
and I'd run to him
and open my arms
and he would grab
me and hold me.
He'd let me sip his beer
and then he'd pick me up
and fly me so high,
and so fast,
he'd call me his flying angel.
I'd just go, daddy, daddy.
[LAUGHS]
Daddy.
So, what are you gonna say?
I sorta wrote a poem.
What is it?
Let's hear it
Can I call you Daddy?
Would that be okay?
I dream of loving moments
when I know just want to say.
When I don't feel sad or guilty
for being here today.
Would you and Mommy
still be happy,
and as one,
if had never been born...
if I could be undone.
Can I call you Daddy?
Forgive me if I pray.
Just to have you hold me.
If only for one day.
It's okay. It's okay.
Richard.
What are you doing here?
RICHARD: Ah, well, I was in
the neighborhood.
-Hey, Frank.
-Richie, long time no see.
Yeah. I thought I'd keep an eye
on Tommy until you got
all the paper worked out
He's got a nasty
history of running. So...
It'd be a shame if he got
wind of this and skipped.
Hey. Thank you.
It's okay.
You got this far, right.
Well, I'm going to go
out to Tommy's and
make sure he stays
until the sheriff gets there.
-Do it, Frank. Yeah.
-Good luck, Richard.
FRANK: Your Honor,
we ask the court
for a writ of ne exeat.
I order that John Payton
be arrested.
Ordered he stay in Florida
to attend a child support
hearing.
Is there any reason why
a bond should be more than
one thousand dollars?
Your Honor, if the court sets
the bond to low, Thomas Griffin,
alias John Peyton
may pay on the spot and flee.
Then ten thousand.
And good luck, young lady.
Thank you, Your Honor
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Officer?
What can I do for you?
Let's see what do we got here?
Pick up a deadbeat dad
over in Luths.
He lives at 4682 Ayrshire drive.
Well, that part of Lutes
isn't in Hillsborough County.
That's over in Pasco County.
That's out of our jurisdiction.
What do you mean?
What do we do?
You have to go see
the Pasco County Sheriff,
Jim Marsee.
That's twenty five miles
from here.
Well, you better hurry.
His office closes at five.
We'll never make it in traffic.
[TIRES SCREECH]
Sherriff Marsee!
-OFFICER: That's him
-Sherriff, wait, wait!!
Here.
[PANTING]
[CHATTER OVER WALKIE]
Where are they?
Maybe they couldn't find him.
Maybe he wasn't home.
Pat...
Relax.
Come on.
Everything's on schedule.
Sit down
[SIGHS]
I'm not sure
I really I want to see
him right now.
I'm not sure I'm ready.
I'm gonna go call the girls.
[DOOR OPENS]
You bitch!
You okay?
Keep it together.
It's okay.
Where is he?
Did he get here yet?
We didn't miss him, did we?
He's here.
[DOOR UNLOCKING]
Your daughters are outside.
They're asking for you.
Would you like to see 'em?
[MUMBLES]
Well, he won't see you
and I'm sorry.
Please, They just want
to talk to him.
He's got his rights
and he says no.
Can you at least give
him some pictures?
I brought my scrapbook
for him to see.
I guess I can give him
some pictures.
This too, please.
Okay.
Mom, I'm scared.
-I know.
-I don't want to see him.
It's all right.
JOHN: My lawyer here yet?
Your kids sent these to you.
[CALM MUSIC PLAYING]
-I just talked to Frank.
-What'd he say?
One back payment of $5,000
and $200 a month
until Marcia turns 18.
Will he see us?
No.
So I told him no deal.
He must really hate us.
Honey...
Hey, sweetie.
Marcia, come here.
Honey, I don't think
he's capable of hate
any more than I think
he's capable of love.
So he abandons us?
-It's no excuse.
-Of course, it's no excuse.
There is no excuse for
what he's done.
I just think there's something
missing from him.
He sounds so sad.
I know. You know,
we gotta remember
something here.
There's nothing wrong with us.
It's him.
Okay?
-Okay.
-[CHUCKLES]
We lost.
What?
Judge Evans vacated the writ.
Tommy is free to go.
Why?
The writ was issued
in Hillsborough County.
Served in Pasco County.
Gave the judge an out.
He didn't have to deal
with the real question.
So, we can't see him today?
He's already left the courtroom.
I'm sorry, Pat.
What we can do is file an appeal
in Pasco County right away.
Please don't get discouraged.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
PAT: But, Frank,
I don't understand.
Now, what's the problem?
The problem is, Pat,
Judge Kalis is known
for letting these guys go.
He's not sure he can enforce
this as a debt.
-They're treating it as a loan
-It's not a loan.
I know that. Pat.
Look, he's not sure
this is a matter
for the civil court.
Now we've got five days
to file the briefs.
That's ridiculous!
-Mom?
-What?
Thomas Griffin just called.
He wants to see Christine,
Marcia and me.
[AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's split up and see
if we can find him.
Come on over here.
Let me have a look at you.
Come on, sit down.
I'm Andrea and Marcia.
Um Christine couldn't make it.
She's sick in the motel.
We, have to talk.
You look just like your mom.
Did you love her?
Yes, I did.
ANDREA: So why did
you leave her?
Why did you leave us?
-These things happen.
-These things happen?
You just walk out on your wife
and your three children,
that's all?
I didn't ask you here
to discuss this.
I asked you here to make a deal.
A deal?
What kind of deal?
If we can settle this
out of court...
I'll make it worth your while.
I'll see you through school.
I'll buy your clothes.
I'll put money
in your pockets.
Just like a father
You tell your mother...
that if she doesn't stop
harassing me,
she's not going to see one dime.
Now, you tell her that!
This whole thing is beat.
-Let's get out of here.
-That's it?
Would you have anything else
you want to say to me?
Yeah.
How about goodbye.
[SLAMS]
[AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARCIA CRYING]
[BOTH CRYING]
RICHARD: Here you go.
Thanks.
[SIGHS]
So what now?
File the appeal, and wait.
Why isn't Frank filing?
He's done everything he can,
and I can't ask him to keep
working for nothing.
-Where will you file?
-Here in Tampa again.
And if I win the appeal,
I'll have to argue my own case
in front of the court.
Okay, Perry Mason.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
One person at a time.
REPORTER: Are you arguing your
own case ma'am?
No more questions, please.
BAILIFF: All rise.
Court in the state of Florida,
County of Pasco
is now in session.
The honorable Michael Curtis
presiding.
We're here to determine
the ability of John Payton
to pay child support.
Let's proceed.
Your Honor, I would like
to call John Payton to
the stand, please.
BAILIFF: Please raise your
right hand.
You do solemnly swear
that the testimony
you shall give in the cause
now pending before this court
is the truth,
the whole truth and nothing
but the truth, so help you God?
I do.
Please state your full name
For the record.
-John Douglas Payton.
-Please be seated.
Mr. Payton...
isn't it true that after
your arrest last year,
you transferred your share
of co-owned property,
cash certificates of deposit
and ownership
in a duplex apartment?
That all belongs to my wife
and her family.
Didn't you spend more than
$20,000 in home improvements
last year,
including the purchase
of a wide screen TV
at a cost of $3200?
I object, Your Honor.
Really, a television set?
I am trying to show
that he has been
hiding cash all along.
Answer the question, Mr. Payton.
The truth is, Your Honor,
I'm stone broke
and deeply in debt.
I don't even have
a bank account.
Right after Tommy's...
Right after Mr Payton's arrest,
he and his wife closed
their money market account
of fourteen thousand dollars.
And we have canceled checks
from his employers
for more than $ 30,000.
LAWYER: Now we're getting
a lesson in accounting.
Your Honor, I must object.
Please move it along,
Ms. Bennett.
Yes, Your Honor.
One last question.
You met your daughters,
Andrea and Marcia
for the very first time
just recently, is that correct?
No, that is not correct.
Excuse me.
For the first time
since Andrea was a baby.
I don't believe you
ever didn't meet your
daughter Marcia.
Whatever.
Do you know who
this young woman is?
[AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
No, I don't.
PAT: That's very sad.
That's your daughter.
That's Christine.
You don't even know who
your own daughter is.
PAT: Your honor,
this man has not seen
his children for 17 years.
He has changed his identity.
He has committed bigamy
and he has failed
to support his children.
He has showered
himself with luxuries
while his children were forced
to live on welfare.
LAWYER: Your Honor...
Your Honor, if a man
were brought before you
who had abused and
beaten his children,
this court would have
no problem in condemning him.
While my children may look...
perfectly healthy
on the outside,
but on the inside...
they are bruised
and scarred for life.
And there is no amount of money
that is ever going to make up
for the emotional damage
that has been done to them
by not having a father
all these years.
This pattern of allowing men
to simply run away
from their responsibility
as fathers has got to stop.
And it could stop right here
and right now,
if you find this
one father in contempt
for failure to pay
child support.
Show these people
that the system
really does work.
I want my girls to be able
to walk away from here
with some sense of dignity
and some hope
for the future.
Please, Your Honor.
Please.
Hearing the testimony, the court
will take a short recess.
You'll have my decision
in one hour.
[KNOCK]
BAILIFF: All rise.
Having heard the testimony,
the court finds John Douglas
Payton's failure
to make payments
of back child support,
willful and premeditated.
Mr Payton, in addition
to making payments
of back child support
in the amount of $ 106,500,
you are remanded
into the custody of the
Pasco County Jail
for a period of not less
than thirty days.
Relax, you're not gonna
do any time.
JUDGE: In addition,
you'll be forced to pay
back interest,
bringing your total sum of debt
to $146,200.
Ms. Bennett,
you're a very brave woman
and an inspiration
to millions of other women
out there suffering as you have.
Good luck to you.
This court is adjourned.
[ALL CRYING]
PAT: You know, the pain
never really goes away but
we've learned to live with it.
Our life is so much better now.
Somehow resolved, peaceful.
The girls are growing into
wonderful young women
right before my eyes.
And believe it or not,
I'm in my second year
of law school.
As for Tommy,
well, two hours after the
hearing, his wife
bailed him out of jail.
Then, four weeks later,
he began missing his
weekly payments.
But he caught up quickly
when I threatened
him with jail again.
He still sends me and the girls
a hundred dollars every week.