(film spool spinning)
(projector clicks)
(film flapping)
(crickets chirping)
(haunting music)
(man singing)
(men grunt)
(pickaxes thudding)
♪ Ah, ah-ah, ah ♪
- Hooh!
(pickaxes thudding)
♪ Oh-oh, ah, ah-ah ♪
(men singing)
(pickaxes thudding)
(men grunt)
♪ Ah, ah-ah, ah-ah, ooh ♪
Huh!
♪ Ah, ah-ah, ah ♪
♪ Well, I ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Hooh!
♪ Been in trouble since I ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Huh!
♪ I-ah was born ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Hooh!
♪ Been in trouble since I ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Huh!
♪ I been born ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Huh!
♪ Here I'm nothin' 'cause I ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Hooh!
♪ Born to die ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Huh!
♪ Here I'm nothin' 'cause I ♪
Hooh!
(car rattling)
(haunting music)
(haunting music continues)
(rim rattling)
(shutter bangs)
(rim rattles)
(hinge creaks)
(crow caws)
♪ Jimmy crack corn and I don't care ♪
♪ My master's gone away ♪
♪ The mule, he run, he jump,
he pitch ♪
♪ He threw my papa in the ditch ♪
♪ He died, the jury wondered why ♪
♪ The verdict was the blue tail fly ♪
♪ Jimmy crack corn and I don't care ♪
♪ Jimmy crack corn ♪
(box lid creaks)
(box snaps)
(Amelia sighs)
♪ And I don't care ♪
♪ Jimmy crack corn and I don't care ♪
♪ My papa has gone away ♪
♪ He's buried 'neath a 'simmon tree ♪
(Amelia exhales)
♪ The epitaph, for all to see ♪
♪ Beneath this stone
I'm forced to lie ♪
♪ The victim of the blue tail fly ♪
(haunting music)
- Mornin' Ben.
Mornin' Jake.
- Mornin'
- Mornin' Miss Amelia.
You reckon it be ready in 21 days?
- I reckon, ma'am.
If they stay with it.
- Looks all right.
- Thank you, ma'am.
(gentle music)
(gentle music continues)
(Amelia whistling)
(pestle clanking)
(birds chirping)
(pestle clacks)
(Amelia whistling)
(liquid pouring)
(gentle music)
(Amelia groans)
- My man hauled off and whacked me
across the side of the face.
- Suzanna, you keep this onion on.
Got exceptional drawin' power.
And you whack your husband
when you get home tonight.
- [Suzanna] I will Miss Amelia.
(crying) I will.
(gentle music)
- He been sick three days
like this now, Miss Amelia.
I'm real worried.
- (sniffing) And he got worms.
Well give him this.
Wrench loose the bowls,
but it's sweet tastin'
- Thank you, Miss Amelia.
- I tried it myself.
- Thank you.
- What's wrong with you, Marilee?
(door thuds)
- What's goin' on here?
- What is it, Grandma?
- What is this?
- Miss Amelia!
Oh, no Miss Amelia,
not the sewin' machine.
- [Amelia] I'm takin' it
in lieu of the $2
you owe me!
- I will pay!
I, I swear I will!
- [Amelia] Get outta my way.
- Just gimme two weeks, Miss Amelia.
Just gimme two weeks!
(dramatic music)
- You can't do this!
You're takin' everything we got!
You hear me? Everything we got!
(dramatic music)
(dogs barking)
♪ And he walks with me
and he talks with me ♪
♪ And he tells me I am his own ♪
♪ And the joy we share ♪
♪ As we tarry there ♪
♪ None other has ever known ♪
- Just pay attention the
word of the Lord here.
Let me see if I can get
through to you people today.
Old! We become old.
And it has been a long, long climb.
There will not be much more of this.
And then, then we shall rest.
No sorrow, nor sweaty,
nor aching back,
nor sickness, nor pity, nothin',
nothin', do you hear me?
Nothin' will take or touch us more.
Nothin', not thunder,
Not the rustlin' of worms,
not the scalding kettle,
nor the weeping child,
no, shall rouse us,
rouse us from our rest.
(people chattering)
- Everybody!
Listen here! It's time!
(people chattering)
(feet scurrying)
(train whistling)
(engine chugging)
(engine chugging louder)
(train whistling)
(frogs croaking)
(water babbling)
(insects droning)
(water stirring)
(wings fluttering)
(crickets chirping)
(gentle music)
(creature buzzing)
(birds chirping)
(gentle music)
(water stirring)
(crickets chirping)
(gentle music)
(birds cawing)
(forage rustling)
(crickets chirping)
(haunting music)
(water splashes)
(bucket thuds)
(haunting music)
(crickets chirping)
(barrel creaking)
(metal echoing)
(liquid splashing)
(bucket thuds)
(lighter snapping)
(flames roar)
(whistle blares)
(train chugging)
(feet crunching)
(gentle music)
(wood rubbing)
(coins clanking)
(jar thuds)
- Thank you, Miss Amelia.
(coins clank)
(coins rattle)
(jar thuds)
(coins clank)
(palm slaps)
- You too young.
(dramatic music)
(cicadas droning)
(bird calling)
- It is smooth liquor.
I have never known
Miss Amelia to fail.
(haunting music)
(man gulping)
(dogs barking)
(haunting music)
(dog barking)
(haunting music continues)
- I see somethin' comin'
(frogs croaking)
(dogs barking)
(dramatic music)
- Calf got loose.
(feet crunching)
- No, it's somebody's youngun.
(dramatic music)
(dogs barking)
- (panting) Evenin'
(dramatic music)
I'm huntin' for a Miss Amelia Evans.
- How come?
- 'Cause she is kin to me.
(dramatic music)
- That's me. How'd you mean kin?
- (pants) Because my
mother was Fanny Jessup.
She come from Chehaw,
and I remember hear tell
that she had a half sister
named Martha.
And back in Chehaw today, they
tell me she was your mother.
And if Fanny Jessup and
Martha were half sisters,
and I'm the son of the
third husband of Fanny,
that means well, here.
I have a picture
of my mother and her half sister.
- This could be any old picture.
- Let me see it.
(gentle music)
- Where do you come from?
- I was travelin'
(Lymon crying)
- Sho' is a cry baby.
- He is afflicted.
There is some cause.
(Lymon continues crying)
(gentle music)
(cork pops)
- Drink. It'll liven your gizzard.
I don't know your name.
- I'm Lymon Willis.
- Well, there's supper in the stove.
Come in, you can eat.
(feet trudging)
(door shuts)
(fork scratches)
(fork clacking)
(Lymon chews loudly)
(gentle music)
(fork clacking)
(Lymon chews loudly)
(gentle music)
(gentle music continues)
- Don't turn off the lamp, Amelia.
(gentle music)
Leave the door open, please.
- There she is.
She's washin' her head under the pump.
- So? She does that every mornin'
- Is this brokeback, he
claimed kin with her?
With Miss Amelia?
- He did. Said he was her cousin.
His mother and her's were sisters.
- I don't see no brokeback.
- Well maybe he left.
Maybe she threw 'em out.
How do I know?
Now where's my pail?
- Oh, she's goin' back in the house.
What's she doin'?
Are you sure you saw
this here brokeback?
How much liquor you had?
You just been seein' things?
- Weren't just me saw him.
He was there alright.
Just like I said, and
carryin' this old suitcase,
tied up in rope.
They went in the house together.
- Then where is he?
What's she done with him?
- What was he doin' up there?
- Well I don't know.
- Have you seen him?
- I ain't (whispering)
Oh, shh.
Mornin' Miss Amelia.
(horse clopping)
- Ya ask me, all that business
'bout kin was trumped up.
- Takin' that creature-
- Ya ask me,
Amelia got no kin.
(people chattering)
(cicadas droning)
(bird whooping)
(men chattering)
- I wonder where in the hell he is.
- I can't say.
- Hey, I know what Miss Amelia done.
I said, I know what Miss Amelia done.
- Yeah? What's she done, Merlie?
- She murdered that man for
somethin' in that suitcase.
- Miss Amelia would not kill anyone
for just a few pieces of junk.
- Well how you know it's junk, huh?
How do you know?
- So what's she done with the body?
What's she done with it?
- She chopped him up and
buried him in the swamp,
that's what she done.
- Murdered?
- That brokeback?
- He's buried in the swamp.
- Well, if she has kilt him,
they'll come and arrest her.
- You're crazy.
- No, I ain't! I ain't crazy.
- Miss Amelia has murdered him.
- They will take her to Atlanta.
- They will electrocute her.
- It's wild and foolish
talk that you're doin' here.
And it does none of ya,
none of ya, any credit.
- Where is he, Reverend Willin?
- Good question.
- Come on!
- Yeah, right.
(men chattering)
(dirt crunching)
(intense music)
(feet thudding)
(clock ticking)
(gentle music)
(feet thudding)
(fingers slap)
(Lymon laughs)
(fist thuds)
(Mert laughs)
(Lymon laughs)
- Why that's Miss Amelia's snuff box.
That belonged to her daddy.
- That's so.
(clock chiming)
- Where'd it go?
- Just a trick I learned out east.
Where you from?
Who are you anyway?
- Well, he's Merlie Ryan.
He don't mean no harm.
He's got three-day malaria.
- Merlie, go fetch those ladies
in here.
They're gonna hurt their noses
the way they're pressed up
against the window like that.
- Y'all, ladies, please come in.
- [Lymon] Evenin' ladies. Come on in.
We was just talkin' about you.
(Lymon kisses hand)
(ladies gasp)
You know,
anybody that could ever do this?
Know anybody in your life
that could ever do this?
Tell me the truth.
You ever seen anyone
one that can do this?
(crowd laughing)
♪ Ya ever hear tell of
Sweet Betsy from Pike ♪
♪ Who came 'cross the
prairies with her lover Ike ♪
♪ Two yoke of oxen
and one spotted hog ♪
♪ Two shanghai roosters
and one yeller dog ♪
♪ Singin' hoo-rack-rack,
soo-rack-rack, so-rack, hey ♪
♪ That's soo-rack, soo-ran,
hah, soo-lay ♪
(Lymon claps and gasps)
(Lymon barks)
(Lymon laughs wildly)
(crowd laughs)
(breezy harmonica music)
(Lymon claps)
(crowd gasps)
- [Woman] How'd he do that?
(crowd laughing)
("Sweet Betsy From Pike")
(women whispering)
(upbeat harmonica music)
- [Mert] Work call comes at
five in the mornin', boys.
Come on, Mama.
- [Lymon] Well, you don't
haveta go yet.
- We got to go.
- Well go ahead
and stay a little while.
(people chattering)
Good night.
It was a pleasure havin'
ya, don't be a stranger.
See y'all.
(people chattering)
Hey Edith, good night.
It's been a pleasure.
(women singing)
(people chattering)
(laughs) Good night, don't
let the bedbugs bite, Harlan.
(people chattering)
Good night.
It's been a pleasure ladies.
(Amelia clomping and clapping)
(people chattering)
♪ Bringing in the sheaves ♪
♪ We shall come rejoicing ♪
(dog barking)
- I remember when my
Big Papa was alive.
Ah, those days I slept.
I'd go away just as the lamp
was turned on, and I'd sleep.
I slept like I was drownin'
in more mounds of grease.
And then Big Papa'd walk in,
and he'd put his hand on my shoulder,
"Get stirrin', Little," he'd say.
- He called you Little?
- Yeah, and then he'd holler
up the stairs from the kitchen
while the stove was hot!
(clock chimes)
It's 3:00. "Fried grits," he'd yell!
White meat and gravy, ham and eggs!
And I'd rush down the stairs,
and I'd get my clothes by the stove
while he'd be washin' out by the pump.
And then off we'd go to the still.
- Those grits we had
this mornin' was poor.
Fried so quick that the
insides never heated.
- Mm-hmm, when Big Papa
used to run off the liquor,
in those days, why you just never saw.
(fire crackling)
(Lymon crying)
What is it that ails ya, Cousin Lymon?
You want me to rub some
liquor on your back?
- No.
(fire crackling)
- What is it then?
- I just don't like the nighttime.
I don't like starin' into
the dark, that's all.
(Lymon cries)
(chair creaks)
♪ Baby, baby ♪
♪ Where has my baby gone ♪
♪ (singing in a foreign language) ♪
(tongue clicking)
(chair creaking)
(fire crackling)
- We were destroyed. I'll
tell ya we were destroyed.
It was terrible.
Never had it so bad.
Mornin'
- Miss Amelia, mornin'
- This here is my cousin.
This is Lymon Willis.
This is Jack.
- Pleased to meet ya.
- At your service, sir.
- Amelia?
That nigger boy there's sloughin'
He's lollygaggin' Ain't
no lollygaggin' now!
(bird chirping)
(turkey yelping)
(turkey gobbling)
(birds chirping)
(wings beating)
(gun blasts)
- Whoo!
(ax chopping)
(Amelia whistling)
9, 5, 14, 18,
19, twine, (claps) 19.
Corn, pine.
- Amelia.
You know what?
Get some tables in here.
- Tables. Cousin Lymon, whatever for?
- So folks could sit down to drink.
- Why do they need to sit down?
- Oh man, Amelia, you can
make those tables yourself.
Look, you could clear out a space.
And then we could have
company every night.
You know I like company.
You know that, Amelia.
- Yeah, but-
- And you can start
sellin' liquor by the glass!
Make more money that way.
And we could brin' that
piano in from outside.
- Well that piano ain't
been used since my ma died.
- That piano would liven
things up, Amelia.
The piano would liven things up!
(Amelia laughs)
(doors bang)
(piano rolling)
Over there!
Over there.
No, no, over there!
(upbeat piano music)
(people chattering)
Well, come on in.
I told you this here's a cafe.
You know, you ever see a cafe before?
Amelia!
(upbeat music)
(people chattering)
- He callin' for Amelia.
- Come on down here, Amelia.
We got guests!
(upbeat music)
(feet clomping)
(people chattering)
(everyone laughing)
- Anyone want serving?
- My, Miss Amelia, that
sure is a pretty dress.
- My ma's dress.
- I know. I remember.
I'm so pleased to see you
wearin' it, Miss Amelia.
- You want servin'?
- (laughs) What have you got?
- Liquor.
- Cold bottle drinks,
- 5 cents a glass.
- 5, 10 cents.
- 10 cents a glass.
- And cherry juice.
- 1 cents a glass.
- Penny a glass.
- I'll have some cherry
juice, thank you, Miss Amelia.
- Liquor for me, if it's
all right, Miss Amelia.
(upbeat piano music)
(bottle clinking)
- You see the color of that dress?
She's wearin' a scarlet dress.
Y'all know what that means.
She's livin' in sin.
She's livin' in sin
with that brokeback!
That's what it means.
(people laughing)
(crickets chirping)
(keys tapping)
- What you doin', Amelia?
- I'm writin' a story.
- A story.
You're writin' a story. What about?
- Ah, ah, I don't want you
to see it yet.
- Why not?
What's it about? Tell me.
- It's about foreigners
and trapdoors, and
millions of dollars.
- (laughs) Wow. Millions of dollars?
What else?
- I ain't decided yet.
- I like stories
with gangsters in 'em.
(paper rustling)
You got gangsters
in this story Amelia?
Mm?
(crickets chirping)
(exhales) Maybe.
(upbeat fiddle music)
- How much?
- $75.
(Lymon gasps)
- 75?
- 75 even.
- What is it?
- Cousin Lymon, it's a car.
I bought it for you.
- I wanna drive it.
I ain't never driven
a car before! (laughs)
(horn blares)
- You can't, Cousin Lymon.
- You can!
(upbeat fiddle music)
Let's go to Chehaw.
- [Amelia] Whatever for?
- We could go to the pitcher show.
- Whatever for?
- [Lymon] It would be fun!
- Ah!
(upbeat music)
(clutch grinds)
- [Amelia] Whoo-hoo!
- [Lymon] Ya-hoo!
(horn blares)
(both laughing)
Whoo-hoo, Chehaw,
here we come! (laughs)
Two for the picture show.
- Upstairs or downstairs?
- Upstairs.
- What?
- We'd like upstairs.
- That'll be 30 cents.
- [Narrator] The democratic candidate
has spoken forcefully and insistently
of the need for a change, a New Deal.
And on election day, Franklin
Delano Roosevelt is confident.
(upbeat music)
- Some guy.
(sirens blaring)
(tires screeching)
(weapons blasting)
(explosives booming)
(weapon firing)
(chalk rubbing)
- Hah!
(children screaming)
(feet scurrying)
(upbeat piano music)
(people chattering)
(people laughing)
(glasses clinking)
(people chattering)
(people laughing)
- Ah, Merlie.
- All right.
- Move it, Merlie.
All right.
On my way over here,
we's havin' and go by a house,
woman naked standin'
right in the front window!
- Well, who was she?
- Your wife! (laughs)
- These is my neighbors.
I ain't never seen 'em
like this before.
Never before my whole
life, and that is a fact.
- Like what?
- Hey, I ain't one for words
Miss Amelia,
but I know everythin' useful
in life's got a price,
and can only be bought with money.
And that is the way the world is run.
Ain't that right, Miss Amelia?
- Maybe, maybe so. So what?
- [Customer] Thank you, Miss Amelia.
- Well, you know, not
havin' to think about it,
the price of bale of cotton
or a quart of molasses.
(people laughing)
(people chattering)
Human life, it ain't
got no value put on it.
Seems like you work and you
slave and you try all your life.
All you're tryin' to do
is just to fend off death.
(Lymon laughing wildly)
(people chattering)
Look at these people,
and maybe they forget.
- Two liquors.
- Maybe they forgettin' they
ain't worth much in this world.
It's just like me, Miss
Amelia, I ain't worth much.
I never was worth much.
I never could be worth much, but.
Right now I feel good.
(people chattering)
(people laughing)
(upbeat piano music)
(water bubbling)
(crickets chirping)
- Whoo, this is fun!
(both laughing)
When we gonna get there?
- It's far as there around the bend.
- I'm so thirsty.
- A lot of liquor up by the still.
- Ho-hoh.
- You just love that liquor.
- I can't wait.
- Gonna have to.
- Ah, you are always so slow, Amelia.
(thunder crashes)
(corn tapping)
(rain splashing)
(upbeat harmonica music)
(Lymon laughing)
(rain splashing)
(tree crashes)
Amelia!
(Amelia laughs)
(Lymon laughing)
(thunder rolling)
(rain pouring)
(clock chiming)
- (sighs) Did I ever
show you Papa's acorn?
- Nope.
(clock ticking)
(rain splashing)
(thunder rolling)
(clock ticking)
What does the acorn signify?
- Oh, it's just an acorn.
(laughs) It's just an acorn
I picked up
in the afternoon
Big Papa died. (laughs)
- How do you mean?
- I mean, it's just an acorn I
spied on the ground that day.
I pick it up and put in
my pocket. I dunno why.
- Hmm, what else you got in here?
(treasures rattling)
What are these stones, Amelia?
- Oh, they, they're not important.
- Then why do you keep 'em?
- Well, they're my kidney stones.
I had this pain years back.
The doctor in Chehaw cut 'em out.
I never felt such a pain
in all my life.
That's why I keep 'em.
To remember the pain.
(clock ticking)
(rain splashing)
(bird chirping)
(cane banging)
- Where'd ya get that cane, Amelia?
Good sugar cane's green in color.
Any fool knows that.
(cane thudding)
S'mornin' I went up to
Rotten Lake to fish.
- Yeah.
- Steppin' over this fallen tree.
Straddled right over it, and
it suddenly started to stir.
I looked down, (laughs) I'll
be damn if it wasn't a gator,
as long as from here over
there to that there door.
And as thick as a hog.
(hog grunts)
- Miss Amelia said you
been in bed all day.
Sick with the stomach quinsy.
(fly buzzing)
- I snuck out.
Amelia don't know half of what I do.
- [Man] Who's gonna work
and where (indistinct)
(men yelling)
- [Man] And are we gonna stand
by and watch the black races
take our wives, our
daughters and our sisters?
- [All] Hell no!
- [Man] Brothers, I'm
tellin' ya that today
if we allow a nigger to address
a white woman on the
streets, he will rape and-
- If you don't wanna end
up hangin' on that cross,
you better git!
- We don't want you around
here, runt! Get out!
(Lymon thuds)
(men yelling)
- [Man] Our women and
our sacred white race.
What is the way?
(men yelling)
(easy piano music)
(people chattering)
(chair scrapes)
(chair creaks)
- I got a letter from my brother?
(easy piano music)
- You are welcome to it!
- He's on parole.
He's out of the penitentiary.
- Who?
(palm bangs)
- Why?
- Because Marvin Macy is a,
(Amelia hisses)
He belongs to be in that penitentiary
for the rest of his life! (slams palm)
- What's he done?
(Amelia bangs table)
Well, what's he done?
Well he's on parole
from the penitentiary!
He musta done somethin'
What's he done?
You all know! Somebody
tell me what's he done?
- He robbed a couple of
fillin' stations.
- Is that all? What else has he done?
- Why, he's lower than a
snake belly in a wagon rut!
He will not set his split
hoof on my premises.
- Who is Amelia? Who is he?
What's he done?
Why are you so riled, Amelia?
What he done to you?
Marvin Macy, Marvin Macy, who is he?
- That loom-fixer I was married to.
- Married? You never
told me you was married.
Why you never told me that?
What happened?
Somethin' musta happened!
Please, Amelia, tell me what happened
between you and Marvin Macy.
- I don't ever want you
to mention his name again,
Cousin Lymon.
I don't even wanna hear it again!
That loom-fixer's nothin' but a
(pounds fist) mm!
He's an evil man, Cousin Lymon!
He's evil! (pounds fist)
- He loved you Miss Amelia.
- Huh!
(gentle music)
- I must be in love with her.
- No, no, no, I know you
Marvin Macy. I know you.
You may have somethin' good in you,
but I ain't never seen it.
You lead a wicked life.
Your heart, your heart is as
hard as the horns of Satan.
- Well that ain't my fault.
- Yeah wait, wait.
Wait, wait, come on back.
Come on back. Sit down here.
(gentle music)
Sit.
Yeah well, maybe I was wrong.
Ya see, all of us are sinners,
each and every one of
us in the eyes of God.
- Well, I can change, Reverend Willin.
I know I can.
(water splashing)
(doors bang)
- What are they for?
- Well, for you, Miss Amelia.
Just want flowers and chitlins.
(sack rustles)
And uh. .
I want you to have this.
(gentle music)
It was my mother's ring.
I come
(gentle music)
to ask you to marry me, Miss Amelia.
(bell pealing)
- She's comin'! She's comin'!
- Okay, everybody pay attention.
We're gonna sing now.
"What a Friend We Have
in Jesus," all right?
(bell pealing)
(feet crunching)
♪ What a friend with have in Jesus ♪
♪ All our sins and guilt to bear ♪
♪ What a privilege to carry ♪
♪ Everything to God in prayer ♪
♪ Oh, what peace we often forfeit ♪
Okay, that's enough.
We're done, everybody.
Sit down!
(people chattering)
- [Woman] She's looks funny
in that thing. (laughs)
(person shushes woman)
- Friends, we are gathered
here today in the sight of God
to bind this man
and this woman together
in holy matrimony.
Don't stand there lookin'
at her. Give her the ring.
(gentle music)
Well, I now pronounce
your man and wife.
(crickets chirping)
(Amelia chomping)
(Amelia clears throat)
(watch cover clicks)
(watch ticking)
- Miss Amelia.
- Hmm?
- It's gettin' late.
Maybe we should, uh,
you know, go to bed.
(gentle music)
(Amelia clears throat)
(feet clomping)
(gentle music)
(Marvin thuds)
What you doin', Miss Amelia?
Miss Amelia, you can't do this.
You can't do this to me. Miss Amelia?
Miss Amelia, a man who can't
sleep beside his own wife,
he's no kind of man at all,
Miss Amelia.
He is only a laughin' stock.
(suitcase bangs)
Miss Amelia!
(crickets chirping)
(haunting music)
- In accordance with
the wishes of my client,
I am hereby instructed
to say the followin',
"I, Marvin Macy, bein' of sound mind,
hereby give over to Miss Amelia
Macy all my worldly goods.
10 acres of timberland up
by the Fort Falls Road. "
This here is the paper transfer
on the ownership, Miss Macy.
(gentle music)
(door shuts)
- Get out.
- Miss Amelia.
- You get outta my house.
(door slams)
- She's gonna get a lot of trouble.
- [Henry] That man's real dangerous.
- Well, lookit right now.
Reckon she broke his heart.
(people chattering)
(metal scraping)
(dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
(Amelia spits)
(Marvin spits)
(crickets chirping)
(bird whoops)
(Marvin breathing hard)
(weapon clicks)
(dramatic music)
(door bangs)
- Amelia!
Amelia!
(dramatic music)
- Marvin Macy,
you broken into my store!
- I wanna be in here.
I belong in here with you!
- You git!
- You can't do this to me, Amelia.
It ain't right!
- You git outta my house.
I'll have you arrested.
I'll have you locked
up in the penitentiary.
- I love you, Amelia.
- I'll give you 10 seconds.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5,
6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
- Don't come no closer.
I'm warnin' you!
- You think I'm scared
of you, Marvin Macy?
Well, go on, shoot.
- But you're my wife.
Amelia?
- Git! (slaps)
Git, git!
- Quit it. Quit!
Quit, Amelia!
Quit!
(dramatic music)
You quit!
Jesus Christ!
Jesus Christ, Amelia!
- You leave my house, Marvin
Macy, and you never come back!
You hear? Never!
(Marvin grunts)
(weapon fires)
(dogs barking)
(weapon clatters)
- I ain't finished with you.
Just you remember that! I
ain't finished with you!
(gentle music)
- Amelia?
Amelia?
(door opens)
(clock ticking)
(metal clattering)
- Cousin Lymon!
Cousin Lymon!
(paper rustles)
- "WANTED MURDERER. "
(door opens)
(stomps feet)
- Cousin Lymon,
I got some business to do in Chehaw!
Will you come with me?
- Naw! I'm fine!
- Are you sure?
- Thank you, Amelia. I'll stay here.
- I'd like you to come
with me, Cousin Lymon.
- Well, I'm not comin'
(Amelia sighs)
- I'll be back before dark.
(engine sputters)
(car horn honking)
(metal clatters)
- "WANTED MURDERER
CAUGHT IN TOURIST CABIN. "
"Marvin Macy, wanted for
robbing three filling stations,
suspected murderer of," whoo.
"Found drunk on the
floor of a tourist cabin
with a guitar beside him and
$57 in his right-hand shoe. "
Marvin Macy. Marvin Macy.
(car honking)
(haunting music)
(engine roaring)
(engine sputtering)
(haunting music)
(haunting music continues)
(cicadas droning)
(children chattering)
(slow sliding music)
- Who is that runt?
- Lymon Willis.
He cousin to Miss Amelia.
She cares for him.
- She cares for that brokeback.
- Why did you come back, Marvin?
- This is my home.
(crow cawing)
- Marvin changed himself,
that time he loved Miss Amelia.
Well, it seemed like
he changed completely.
He was, he was good to me
and to Henry.
You remember that, don't ya?
- I remember that, yeah.
- Why'd she throw him out?
Why'd she marry him
and then throw him out?
Why?
- I don't know.
All I know is,
and it takes two people to be in love.
It takes the
lover and the beloved.
But these two, they come
from uh, different countries.
And sometimes the,
the beloved is the cause for all the,
all the stored-up love
that's layin' in the
heart of the lover
for such a long time.
And every lover knows that
deep, deep in his soul.
He knows that his love is a
lonely and solitary thing.
(laughs) And the funny thing is,
the object of that love
can be anybody, and it
just don't matter one whit.
That's why, I guess most
of us, we'd rather be
the lover than the beloved.
I mean, because the state of bein'
beloved is intolerable.
See, and then after awhile
the beloved gets to hate the lover,
because the lover's
always tryin' to strip,
strip, strip bare the beloved.
See that's because the, the lover,
(gentle music)
he craves that love,
even though he knows that that love
can only 'cause him pain.
(gentle music)
(dirt crunching)
- Did you have a good time
in the penitentiary? (laughs)
(knife snaps)
(horn honking)
(car door slams)
(haunting music)
- What ails this brokeback?
What, is the runt throwin' a fit?
(hand slaps)
(Lymon groans)
That'll learn ya, brokeback.
(dramatic music)
- Oh. (groaning)
- Why?
(Lymon crying)
Why, Cousin Lymon? Why?
- Oh, Marvin Macy,
he's been to Atlanta.
- Goin' to Atlanta does him no credit.
- Oh, he's been on a chain gang.
He's been to the penitentiary.
- Been to penitentiary?
Why, that trip ain't no
travel to brag about.
- Marvin Macy.
- Blessed are the meek for
they shall inherit the earth.
Blessed are the children.
(door bangs)
In Jesus-
(crickets chirping)
(apple crunches)
(people chattering)
(crickets chirping)
(haunting music)
(table bangs)
(people gasp)
(chair thuds)
- Can I fix you somethin',
Marvin Macy?
You want somethin' to eat?
- Get outta my way, runt.
(Lymon yells)
(people chattering)
(Lymon gasps)
(clock ticking)
- Maybe Marvin Macy would like
some of your fine liquor, Amelia.
(crickets chirping)
(clock ticking)
(glass clinking)
(haunting music)
(bottle clanking)
(Marvin gulps)
(bottle thuds)
(haunting music)
- Nice place you got here,
Miss Amelia.
(birds chirping)
(Lymon coughing)
(Lymon panting)
- How come you never sweat,
Marvin Macy?
How come that is?
You wanna see somethin'?
You know what these are?
These are Miss Amelia's kidney stones.
You ever heard such a thing?
Miss Amelia's kidney stones. (laughs)
(birds chirping)
(watch cover clicks)
(watch ticking)
- This is my watch, runt!
She stole it from me.
How come you got it? Huh?
- Miss Amelia gave it to me.
Honest Marvin, it was a present.
You can have it, you can keep it.
(watch lid clicks)
You wanna know somethin' else?
You wanna see Miss Amelia's still?
- Maybe.
Where is it?
- Just up a piece.
I'll take you there if you wanna go.
- So you mean to travel,
loom-fixer? (laughs)
(cork pops)
(liquid splashes)
(tongue clicking)
(Amelia whistling)
- Marvin Macy's gonna be
visitin' a spell with us.
(feet thudding)
(haunting music)
(Marvin laughing)
(Lymon chattering)
You know, when you shot those guys.
You shot their eyes-
(Marvin laughing)
(Lymon laughing)
(Lymon chattering)
(Marvin laughing)
(haunting music)
(cutters snip)
(gentle music)
(pestle chomping)
(dramatic music)
(slow sliding music)
(people chattering)
(Marvin laughing)
(Marvin continues to laugh)
- Bust a gut!
♪ Sweet, Peaches ♪
♪ Where ya been all day ♪
♪ Love your peaches, Mama ♪
♪ Wanna taste your peaches ♪
♪ Why you stay away ♪
(easy music)
♪ Mm-mm, Peaches ♪
♪ Where ya been all day ♪
Bust a gut!
- Everythin' you holler at
me bounces back on yourself.
- Is that so?
- Yeah. That's so, Miss Amelia.
(Amelia grunting)
Go get me somethin' to eat.
I'm hungry.
(clock ticking)
- Oh, look at how scared they all are.
Oh, you really are somethin',
Marvin Macy.
(forks clanking)
(clock ticking)
(silverware scraping)
- What's wrong?
- I ain't so hungry after all.
- What you mean?
- I mean, maybe you poisoned it.
(customer gasps)
(Amelia chewing)
(knife sawing)
(Marvin laughs)
(people chattering)
(Amelia heaving)
- Why don't you fight him, Amelia?
I thought you was goin' to.
What's the matter? You afraid?
(people chattering)
You scared to fight him, Amelia?
- [Woman] I think she's chokin'
- [Lymon] Well, you said
you were gonna fight him.
You said you were gonna fight him!
Why don't you fight him!
You gotta fight him!
Come on, fight him!
(rooster crowing)
(people chattering)
(fists pounding)
(Amelia grunting)
- Now Miss Amelia'll win, I reckon.
Y'all remember what she done
to that Fort Fall's lawyer
who tried to cheat her.
Beat him up so bad he
was three quarters dead
time she got through with him.
- That is so.
- Hell.
And she can make 'em terrifyin' faces
and fierce noises.
Whoo! Scare me outta my wits. (laughs)
- [Man] Well you ain't
got no wits, Merlie Ryan.
(Merlie laughing)
(crickets chirping)
(haunting music)
- Look at that buzzard.
That buzzard call for Miss Amelia.
- Hey Lil, come out here.
Look at that fella.
(haunting music)
(bird screeching)
(people chattering)
(haunting music)
(bag thuds)
- Fight's on.
- That's right.
(haunting music)
- You gonna fight today, Marvin Macy?
You fightin' Miss Amelia today?
(haunting music)
(fork clattering)
(both chewing)
(wind wailing)
(wind roiling)
(haunting music)
(wind whirling wildly)
(wind moaning)
(clock ticking)
(haunting music)
(cicadas droning)
(frogs croaking)
(people chattering)
(wagon creaking)
(horse clopping)
(people chattering)
(feet thudding)
(basket thuds)
(clock chiming)
(people chattering)
(metal banging)
- Come on in.
No knives.
No weapons.
(Mert pats Marvin)
Okay, shake hands
and come out fightin'
(crickets chirping)
(clock ticking)
(fists slam)
(both grunt)
(people chattering)
(Amelia breathing heavily)
(Amelia breathing loudly)
(Marvin slapping Amelia's fist)
(people yelling)
- [Man] C'mon, Miss Amelia.
(people chattering)
(Marvin thuds)
(people yelling)
(fist whooshes)
(fist pounds)
(Marvin grunts)
(people cheer)
(Amelia thuds)
(people chattering)
(fist pounding)
(people yelling)
(Marvin grunts)
(Amelia grunts)
(fist slams)
(both grunt)
(fist thuds)
(Amelia grunts)
(people chattering)
(fists pounding)
(people yelling)
- Stop that!
(Marvin groaning)
(fists thudding)
(people yelling)
Stop that! (crying)
(clock ticking)
(people groan)
(fist slams)
(Marvin groans)
(fist thuds)
(people groan)
(fist slams)
(Marvin thuds)
(people chattering)
(Marvin slams)
- C'mon, Miss Amelia.
Get him.
(people chattering)
(both grunting)
(both groaning)
(Lymon groans)
(both panting)
(Amelia groaning)
(Marvin groaning)
(haunting music)
(Amelia grunting)
(people groan)
(Marvin groaning)
(people chattering)
(Marvin choking)
(haunting music)
- Aah!
(people yelling)
(Amelia thuds)
(fist slams)
(Amelia grunts)
(music intensifies)
(fist thuds)
- Ah!
(Amelia thuds)
(Marvin panting)
- Give me that bucket of water.
(water splashes)
(crickets chirping)
(Amelia crying)
(Amelia wailing)
(haunting music)
(Amelia wailing loudly)
(haunting music continues)
(Amelia continues to wail)
(feet scuffling)
(haunting music)
(switch clicks)
(dramatic music)
(tires crunching)
(glass crashes)
(music intensifies)
(items crashing)
(glass breaking)
(intense music)
(glass crashing)
(items crashing)
(flames crackling)
(intense music)
(fire explodes)
(intense haunting music)
(Lymon cackling wildly)
(flames roaring)
(both cackling wildly)
(intense haunting music)
(haunting music slows)
(shudder slams)
(pickaxes thudding)
(men singing)
(men grunt)
(pickaxes thudding)
♪ Ah, ah-ah, ah-ah ♪
(pickaxes thud)
- Hooh!
♪ Ah, ah-ah, ah, well ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Huh!
♪ Been in troubles and I ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Hooh!
♪ I was born ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Hoo!
♪ Been in troubles and I ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Hooh!
♪ I been born ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Huh!
♪ Here I'm nothin' 'cause I ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Huh!
♪ Born to die ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Hoo!
♪ Here but nothin' 'cause I ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Huh!
♪ Bound to die ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Hooh!
♪ (indistinct) ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Hooh!
♪ Ah, hah-hah ♪
(pickaxes thud)
(men grunt)
♪ Puttin' in my time and I'm ♪
(pickaxes thudding)
Huh!
♪ Goin' on home ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Hooh!
♪ Gonna make my time, but I'm ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Huh!
♪ Goin' on home ♪
(pickaxes thud)
(men grunt)
♪ Gonna make my time, and I'm ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Hooh!
♪ Goin' on home ♪
(haunting music)
(pickaxes thud)
(men grunt)
♪ Gonna share this song, and I ♪
(pickaxes thud)
Huh!
♪ Take no more ♪
(pickaxes thud)
(haunting music)
(haunting music continues)