(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(BUZZER BUZZES)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Mr. Russell?
You know the routine.
OFFICER: Place your hands
on the wall for me.
DONALD: See you, eh...
And when you're done,
let's talk.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
DONALD: In accordance
to Texas State Department
of Corrections
maximum status release,
you've met the three month
mandatory contact standard.
It's my determination
that you are in compliance
with the conditions
of your parole.
You've found employment,
passed all mandatory
drug screenings
and are attending the required
group therapy sessions
for violent offenders.
This is all noted
in your personal file.
Mr. Russell,
how would you say things
have been for you
since your return to society?
(TENSE MUSIC)
(KNOCKS)
(SNIFFLES)
(GRUNTS)
I know what to fucking do.
(TENSE MUSIC)
MAN (ON RADIO):
We're about finished here.
Clear the exit.
All clear.
(TENSE MUSIC)
It's time.
MARCOS: We're on, baby.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
WES: Don't move!
Drop the fucking bags!
- Drop the bag!
- (BAG THUDS)
GABE: 30 seconds!
WES:
Turn around! Hands on your head!
- Move!
- (INDISTINCT SPEECH)
WES: Get on your fucking knees!
- Set!
- MARCOS: Moving!
GABE: Cover!
MARCOS: All set!
GABE: Moving!
All set!
GABE: I'm moving.
WES: No!
Come on!
Let's get the fuck out of here!
- MARCOS: Let's go, let's go!
- WES: Come on!
GABE:
What did the fuck did you do?
- MARCOS: Hey, hey, hey!
- GABE: Fuck!
Heads up! Heads up!
GABE: Ah, shit!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Just drive.
(SIRENS WAILING)
Hey, babe. What's up?
What? Define knife?
All right. Well, yeah,
I can't talk
about this right now.
Well, right now is work.
Okay. We'll talk about it
when I get home.
It's okay. We'll figure it out.
All right. Well,
tell baby girl I love her.
I love you, too.
Fly in the ointment?
Matthew, took a knife to school.
JORDAN: A knife?
Is he 14?
SOLOMON: He's 15.
JORDAN: Are they expelling him?
Well, I don't know.
Sure hope not.
Private school ain't cheap.
Well, education isn't cheap.
I'm still paying off
college loans.
SOLOMON: Huh. Yeah, maybe
you could borrow some money
- from this crew.
- JORDAN: No shit.
Evidence response team?
Ah, no. Actually,
we're just looking for a place
- to get some lunch.
- Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
I'm Special Agent
Brett Solomon. FBI.
Good to meet you.
Special Agent Angela Jordan.
- Pleasure.
- Major Crimes Division.
We appreciate the assist.
Dan Pogue. Sheriff.
So this is what the FBI
looks like now, huh?
Times are changing fast
over there.
Well, not fast enough
if you ask me.
So, what's the M.O.?
Well, we had three gunmen
wearing masks.
Carrying ARs.
Couple of Glocks.
Lord knows what all.
SOLOMON:
You wanna walk us through?
Well, the, uh, the guard,
he came out of the bank
carrying the money bags.
The gunmen ambushed him
from a SUV.
One of the gunmen shot
the guard.
Driver witness it?
Whole deal. Everything.
SOLOMON: And where is he?
She. Indoors.
Let's go.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
That's the roundup, eh?
Yeah.
Well, little brother,
you got, uh,
270 grand.
So, get him clean cash
from the back.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Just a quick question.
What the fuck happened
out there?
It's on me.
No doubt about that.
When the Feds are up
my fucking ass,
that's on you too.
We all knew there was a risk.
Look, I could give two shits if
you whacked a fucking pig, okay?
I'm talking about
the cowboy shit, all right?
And if that shit,
comes back on me,
there's gonna be
fucking hell to pay.
What are you saying?
It simply means that
if you back me
in a fucking corner,
and you leave me one option.
Okay, different tact.
Give me a word that's not
coming back on me.
16 years inside, motherfucker.
That's my word.
RADER: You're just
temperamental as your old man.
How is Ruben?
GABE: A fucking prick.
You should go see him.
Okay.
So I'm gonna go with God
and your word is good.
What about the, uh...
What about Superboy?
Superboy?
What are you talking about?
Your brother.
GABE: What about him?
You vouch for him?
He's my brother.
That gives me so much solace.
You want a drink?
Give me a minute.
'Cause I just... I found
something that I thought
you might be interested in.
It's a bank job.
Weekly cash delivery.
Uh, armored car.
Here's the thing.
It is mid to high.
Six figures.
And my inside guy, Devland.
He's the bank manager.
He just wants to meet you.
When?
Next week.
You interested?
We sit down.
Talk about the particulars.
Yeah?
- Yeah, I'm in.
- RADER: Good.
Before I forget,
it's good to have you back.
SOLOMON:
All right, what can you, uh...
Can you tell us about 'em?
Um, what?
What do you wanna know?
Well, how did they come in?
I mean, were they fast?
Did they... did they seem like
professionals?
They... they moved like a...
A SWAT team.
SOLOMON: Okay. Sounds tactical.
Maybe military.
Mm-hmm.
Anything stand out?
Any tattoos
or distinguishing marks?
I mean, one. One spoke Spanish.
Well, that narrows it down
to about
one third of the population.
The one... the one that, um,
held his... his gun to me.
Uh, he... it...
He was the leader.
He just had this, this look.
What...
How could you tell
he was the leader?
Oh, you... you could just...
Just tell.
Fair enough.
Anything else you can remember?
One of the others, um,
shot... shot Philip.
DAN:
Local PD found the drop car.
Okay.
Just give us a minute, okay?
Be right back.
(TENSE MUSIC)
Make it quick.
SOLOMON:
Let me guess. Extra crispy?
You got it.
A good Samaritan phoned it in,
thought some honkies
blew a meth lab.
- We're running the plates now.
- JORDAN: Much likely stolen.
SOLOMON:
Where'd they find the car?
Sending smoke signals
a county over.
It's probably a waste of time
against my better judgment.
But let's check the car
for prints, DNA, hair,
anything that can lead us
back these guys.
Then let's check the vin
against any previous owners
and title.
- You got it.
- Okay.
One of my team will get back
in touch with you.
(TENSE MUSIC)
We're very sorry for
what happened to your partner.
Thank you.
Look at me.
I'm gonna get 'em.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Where is he?
WES:
What the fuck took you so long?
Did you go see Daddy?
No.
Don't smoke in here.
That's for you.
MARCOS: Gracias.
Hey. Where's mine?
Checked the last one?
WES: I motherfucking checked.
Frisk the guard!
That was your one job!
WES: I did, motherfucker!
How am I supposed to know
he had a fucking ankle piece?
We don't shoot people.
When someone pulls
a fucking gun,
you be prepared
for when it goes off!
Spare me your military bullshit.
It doesn't even impress me,
- motherfucker.
- That's fucking bullshit.
Fucking true,
a rule I fucking live by!
There's one rule.
We don't get caught.
I didn't see
the gun either, Gabe.
I didn't.
Fuck out of my face.
I fucked up. There you go.
That what you wanted to hear.
Hm?
What about that fucking
bullshit out there?
Do you think that's not
gonna get us jailed up?
- That's my fucking car.
- MARCOS: Gabe is right, man.
You know the Shop
doesn't pay big wages.
We gotta make this look good, baby.
Yeah, whatever.
You better hold on
to your share.
Until it cools down
or until you grow the fuck up.
Hold on. Come... come again.
My fucking daddy now?
Paying me an allowance?
It's my money!
What happened to the 85
from the Southlake job?
What happened to the 70
from the Flower Mound truck?
Casino or strip club, motherfucker?
Just shut the fuck up already.
Fuck off my back.
Did, uh, Rader mention
he had any more work?
I don't need Rader for jobs.
I want you to stay away
from him.
Why? I didn't do time for him.
I did.
Stay out of his bar.
That clear?
You know, uh,
I deserve to be part
of the brotherhood too, right?
Stay out of his bar.
I'm serious.
- Fuck you!
- (DOOR SHUTS CLOSE)
MARCOS (SPEAKS SPANISH):
You were just like him once.
Just like that.
Adios.
(CAR ENGINE REVVING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
JORDAN:
Armored car driver was right.
SOLOMON: Mm-hmm.
It appears they've taken
a class or two.
(PHONE VIBRATES)
JORDAN: Need to take it?
SOLOMON: Ah.
No. I'll call her back.
She's just trying to plan
Chloe's birthday party,
trying to figure out
what we're gonna do with my son.
- Did you talk to him?
- (CHUCKLES)
No. When was the last time
you talked to a teenager?
Think I'd have more luck
breaking into a bank vault.
Hey whoa, whoa.
Pause that for a second.
You see that?
Someone has a conscience.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
CHEF: Order up.
Here you go.
Do you need anything else?
- CUSTOMER: Okay, thank you.
- Okay. Just let me know.
EDDIE: Hey.
- Talk to me.
- Let go of me.
Look at me.
I'll tell you
when it's time to let go.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay.
Let's go.
Why do you keep coming
over here for?
I just wanted to see you.
What do you want?
Could you take a break?
Maybe sit down.
Some coffee or something.
What happened?
He do that?
Don't act like you care.
Still your dad.
You don't deserve that.
You know, how about I tell you
what I deserve?
It's better than you
and it's better than this.
But it's all I've ever had.
Eventually, you just get
fucking used to it.
You remind me of your mom.
She died a long time ago.
Just like you did.
Order something or leave.
I know I haven't been there,
but I'm trying to change...
DAWNETTE: Order something
or fucking leave.
I'll take some coffee.
I don't wanna see you again.
JORDAN:
Here we got our Spanish speaker.
Trigger man.
Crew leader.
Mm-hmm. I like it.
Crime lab came back
on the robbery SUV.
It's clean. No prints.
- No DNA.
- SOLOMON: Yeah, you were right.
- Plates were decoys.
- And the wheel goes round.
But we were able to trace
the vin number of the SUV
back to an owner out of Dallas
who reported it stolen
two days ago.
Okay.
Well, let's subpoena the owner.
Bring him in for questioning.
See if they have any priors.
Anything that'll link 'em
to the other robberies.
And, uh,
let's check with local C.I.'s.
See if there's anything
on the ground. Okay.
Thank you, Roberts.
Good job.
ALBRIGHT: Agent Solomon.
The man, the myth, the legend.
Oh, you're the only legend
left here in this bureau, Dick.
I was referring to your father.
But that is a nice tie
you got there.
Thank you. Yeah.
Daughter picked it out.
She has good taste.
Yeah.
Why are you referring
to him for?
You know, seeing you in your
father's shoes right now.
He'd have been proud.
Yeah, some bitter lessons
were learned at Waco.
And, uh,
he shouldn't have punished
himself for other people's sins.
Yeah.
$2 for a bottle of water.
You believe that?
Highway robbery if you ask me.
So, did you really come
all the way down here
to be nostalgic?
You know, Intelligence Division
- keeps me busy enough.
- Hmm.
Takes a lot of work keeping
things hush, hush, you know.
Silence is the language of God.
Indeed.
So, ah, why don't we
just cut the shit
and you tell me really
why you're down here.
I heard you took on
a robbery crew.
And there's a lot
of publicity in it.
Just wanted to know
if you have any leads?
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, we're...
We're close actually.
Yeah, uh-huh, well.
Good to hear.
Let me know if I can do
anything to help at all.
- Anything.
- SOLOMN: All right.
You know, and obviously, Dick,
if... if Intelligence
has any information on the case
that would be beneficial,
you'll...
You'll be sure to let me know
as well, right?
If I hear anything at all,
I'll be sure to let you know.
But can I offer some advice?
Some, uh, advice
your father didn't take.
Yeah.
And what advice would that be?
It's okay
if you don't win this one.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, that is terrible advice.
I can understand why
he didn't listen.
The day ain't over yet.
Typically,
you don't catch Texans
trading in their spurs for skis.
(CHUCKLES)
Look.
I just want you to know
that I appreciate
what you did for my cousin
while you were on the inside.
And as we discussed before,
all you need is 5 percent
earnest money
to show commitment.
You got the money?
Well, I'd say
that's a whole lot more
than 5 percent.
How much is it?
It's 250,000 dollars.
I'd ask where it came from.
But asking is for lawyers.
And as long as I get
my percentage,
we got a deal.
There will be a $60,000
remaining balance.
I just need you to sign below.
Next to the X, pal.
Good.
I will draft a cashier's check.
I'll overnight it to ensure
they receive
this in a timely manner.
This check's gotta be received
within five days
of the binding agreement date.
It is a competitive market
out there.
You don't wanna waste a moment.
You're all set.
Pleasure doing business
with you.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
What do you want?
(MUSIC ENDS)
The boy's lost to me.
- Did you know he took him?
- RUBEN: I did.
I know what you did, too.
What do you know about me?
It's all over the morning news.
Yeah, that went south.
You should cut ties. Walk away.
That's what you did.
I'm not talking about me!
(RUBEN COUGHS)
Yeah, you never did much
talking back then.
The past ain't never where
you think you left it, boy.
I've accepted what I've done.
Have you?
(COUGHS)
You should talk to a doctor.
Ain't no doctor could cure me.
I'm an old man. Old men die.
You're a reformed man.
(RUBEN CHUCKLES)
RUBEN: Reformed.
(CHUCKLES)
(SPITS)
RUBEN:
That what you call yourself?
Doing what you think is right
ain't the same as doing
what's right.
Yeah, there's never been
anything right
about this family.
I guess being a criminal
runs in ours.
You know, it's a good thing
your mother ain't around
to see how we all turned out.
You got a choice, boy.
Look where mine led.
(COUGHS)
Rader won't stop.
GABE:
What makes you think I won't?
You're like me, he knows it.
You don't know me at all.
You can't trust him.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
What's up, Brandy?
BRANDY: Hey, baby, how are ya?
I'm good. You doing okay?
BRANDY: I'm doing awesome.
Good. You know where Mandy's at?
Right upstairs waiting on you.
- Hey, man.
- Doing good, my bro?
- Yes, sir.
Take care of yourself,
all right.
(MUSIC LOWERS)
(INDISTINCT LYRICS)
♪ Hey, you say
♪ Hey, you say it
(HIP-HOP MUSIC BEGINS)
MANDY: Fuck off.
♪ Because I will be high
all the time ♪
♪ Would you stay
♪ Hey, stay...
♪ Because I'm you (INDISTINCT)
all the time ♪
Hey.
I'm the last one.
Where you been?
Doing man shit.
Hmm.
Man shit.
You know me.
How you been?
Better now that you're here.
All right.
(MUSIC ENDS)
(HORN BEEPS)
(IN SPANISH)
Bring me the light and a drill.
Can I get a new one
when this is over?
No.
Smart folks
keep the old ones running.
Hey.
Do you care
if I score some early cash?
- Yeah, I do.
- Before I leave.
Yeah, I do.
Uh, I actually, I mind.
If you're not gonna do
the fucking job,
you're not getting paid,
all right?
What the... Come on, dude.
I already stocked
the shelves and shit.
Uh, I got everything
done already.
- Come on.
- And now?
I need you to sweep the floor.
You fucking kidding me?
No, I'm not.
Do I look like
some little grunt bitch?
Make one of the...
One of those little
chicken shits do it.
- Come on, man.
- Remember kid,
I didn't fucking want you here.
Your brother did.
You know what? Fuck you, Dallas!
DALLAS: Get control
of your brother, Gabe.
WES: Bitch-ass motherfucker!
(SNIFFLES)
(IN SPANISH)
Start you piece of shit.
Engine is shot, man.
Yeah.
I'll take you home.
MARCOS: (IN SPANISH)
There's the love of my life.
Gracias.
No problem, brother.
(IN SPANISH) What happened
to your truck my love?
MARCOS: (IN SPANISH)
It didn't want to start.
In the shop.
Gabe gave me a ride.
(IN SPANISH) Why don't you
invite him for dinner?
MARCOS: Hey, Gabe!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
MARCOS: (SPEAKS SPANISH)
Gracias.
No.
MARCOS: (IN SPANISH)
Mija. Get this plate.
Are you finished
with your plate?
Thank you.
(IN SPANISH)
Does he look like his father?
He does.
Yeah, he does.
MARCOS: I plan to teach my son
how to fish.
Just like my father taught me.
Did you do much fishing?
Cerveza just for you.
Thank you.
- (SPEAKS SPANISH)
Long time ago, I did.
When I uh...
My mom used to leave my old man.
Every couple of years,
she'd always come back.
One year, she took, uh,
me and Wes up north.
She came from...
Her brother had a boat.
Wes and I spent
the whole summer on the lake.
It's the best memory of my life.
You should go back someday.
CAMILLA: (IN SPANISH) My love,
I'm putting the baby to bed.
MARCOS: Okay.
(IN SPANISH)
Good night, my love.
GABE: (IN SPANISH)
Thanks for dinner.
(IN SPANISH) You're welcome.
How the fuck did you score that?
- (CHUCKLES)
- I know you, motherfucker.
See man, uh,
when you got locked up,
I went back to Mexico,
lay low for a little bit.
But when I met Camilla,
I knew that she was the one.
Hm-mm.
She got pregnant with my son.
We decided to come back
to America.
Wanted to give him the best,
you know.
Anyways, man, how is Dawn?
She oughta be in her 20s by now.
She hates me.
I earned it.
It was pretty fucked up.
I wasn't there for her
when her mom died.
I don't think she ever really
had a chance.
You know what I mean?
Is there a way
to turn that around?
None that she'd like.
I shouldn't have never brought
you back into this shit.
MARCOS: No, man.
You know, Camilla wants to bring
her family out from Mexico.
She wants them to be involved
in the children's life.
But it costs money
to bring them over.
And even more to keep 'em here.
And this job
and the shitty wages,
you know that ain't enough.
And being illegal.
- Yeah.
- MARCOS: I...
I mean, need some help.
I really need this money.
It's one last job.
It's gotta be smooth.
We can't fuck it up.
I guess, we play the game
till we don't.
This one we can't lose.
Money's how we keep score, baby.
LORI: This is KOTW Channel 5's,
Lori Lambert here with...
Turn that up.
LORI (ON TV):
Following the armed robbery
that happened last week
in broad daylight
where three masked gunmen
violently robbed
an armored car at a city bank.
The armed security guard
Philip Davis, pictured here,
has died from his wounds.
(SLOW ROCK MUSIC)
MANDY: It's not the first time
some guy has eye-fucked me.
- Okay?
- Hm.
Just go get us some beer.
You mind not eye-fucking
them back this time?
Hey, Monty. Two beers.
LORI (ON TV): And we are
right outside County Medical
with breaking news following
the armored car robbery
- that took place...
- Could you turn that up?
LORI (ON TV): last week.
Devastating news
coming just hours
after doctors were hopeful
given several surgery attempts.
But at this time,
it is confirmed by medical
staff that Philip Davis
is pronounced dead.
Fuck, fuck.
Turn that shit off.
Give me a bottle, would you?
I said a fucking bottle.
Wrong place, wrong time.
Wonder if these guys know just
how much shit they're in.
Capital murder.
They're about to.
Oh, let's go.
Is the FBI officially investigating
Phillip Davis' death?
I'd say
that's a fair assessment.
- Do you care to comment?
- JORDAN (ON TV): Not right now.
Thank you.
LORI (ON TV):
What would you like to say
to those responsible?
The past is about
to catch up with you.
LORI: Well, there you have it.
Straight from the FBI.
They are officially investigating
Philip Davis' death.
What is your name, chula?
Mandy.
- Like...
- Like candy.
CHAVA: Are you asleep, Mandy?
MANDY: I can be.
CHAVA: Hmm.
What the fuck?
- CHAVA: Hey, calmate.
- WES: Fuck you, dude.
- Take it easy on me.
- Get your fucking hand
- out of my face.
- CHAVA: Calmate, amigo,
why don't you just get us
another round of beer?
Who even knows what the fuck
you're talking about?
Well, I'm speaking English,
- so you'd better understand.
- WES: Fuck you all.
Do I look like your bitch
or something?
Who the fuck are y'all?
What the fuck is that
you're compensating for?
Hey.
Hey!
That's my girl.
- Well, she's everybody's girl.
- What'd you say?
I said she's everybody's
fucking girl.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
HISPANIC MAN 1: (SPEAKS SPANISH)
What are you even saying?
Tiger King, fuck off!
- CHAVA: Listen to me.
- WES: Fuck off.
Go fucking fetch us some drinks
and get the fuck out of my face!
What, I look like a fucking
bitch right now?
- Yes, you are.
- Huh?
Yes, you do.
You're very tough, aren't you?
HISPANIC MAN 2:
Go to the fucking bar.
- Get some fucking drinks.
- (GRUNTING)
Back up!
Back the fuck up!
Bunch of little
fucking bitches huh,
when someone pulls a gun.
Get your fucking hands off her.
CHAVA: Nah, I like this girl.
Get your fucking hands off her!
Fucking pussy-ass bitch!
MANDY: Wes, come on.
Let's get out of here.
- Come on.
- Yeah, come on, Wes.
What you waiting for?
(SPEAKS SPANISH) Do it.
I dare you.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
Do it! Come on.
Do it. What you waiting for?
Chava! Stop!
This is my fucking bar!
And everybody, it's closed. Go.
PIKE: Move your ass!
And you too, sweetheart.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- MANDY: Back off!
Get your fucking hand off me!
Who the fuck gave you
permission...
These pricks think they can
fuck with me, man!
Get the fuck out of here.
- Fuck 'em up.
- Back the fuck off.
- Listen, listen, listen, listen.
- I got back up.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
- Seriously, listen. All right.
- CHAVA: Put the gun down.
- It's down, all right.
- Move!
Everybody shut the fuck up!
He didn't mean nothing.
Get the fuck away.
He fucking meant it.
He fucking meant
to listen to me.
I tried to give him a chance.
You understand?
I said... (SPEAKS SPANISH)
You see this? Aranas latino,
- motherfucker.
- MAN: That's right.
CHAVA: Do you know
what this shit fucking means?
He disrespected me
in front of my people, man.
RADER: Oh,
I'm so sorry about that.
But you see this?
And that's not from listening
to gangster rap.
I'm asking you man to man.
He's a fucking moron.
I'm asking you,
have a drink with me.
- All you all, alright.
- WES: Fucking waste of alcohol!
- Shut the fuck up, asshole.
- MAN: (SPEAKS SPANISH)
CHAVA: I'm talking
to you. Look...
I don't want
your fucking drink, okay?
I wanna fucking kill
this motherfucker.
Okay, okay, okay. I'm asking you
to have a drink with me.
I'll deal with him later.
Please? Alright? Simple.
I don't want your fucking drink!
You hear me?
I want to fucking kill him!
- Oh, whoa. Whoa.
- CHAVA: You hear me?
I want his fucking blood.
Okay, you can have
his blood, okay.
Let me just get out of here.
You see, motherfucker?
You see? You see, huh?
When you pull out a fucking gun,
you see what happens, huh?
You see that? You see that, huh?
You see? You see
what the fuck happens!
We're fucking killers now?
This is not the way
it was supposed to happen.
The FBI, Gabe?
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
This changes nothing.
They don't know shit.
We stick together,
we finish this.
Then we cut ties.
And everybody gets
what they want.
I don't know, man.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
I gotta go.
MARCOS: (SPEAKS SPANISH)
No, I got it. Here,
thank you for the beer.
WES: I do my thing.
I do my dirty work.
RADER: (INDISTINCT)
can you tell me about?
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- WES: I did.
He came in, all guns
blazing and shit.
RADER: I didn't...
I didn't come in guns blazing.
WES: Wasn't a grand entrance.
I gotta protect my stints.
RADER: So you done
and fucked up.
- WES: That was hot. That was...
- RADER: Oh.
WES: And you put a fucking
- revolver in my head.
- RADER: Oh shit
The party killer's here.
He's here.
WES: Hey, where'd the fuck
you come from?
Come on, man. Come on.
Pick... come on.
Take a seat right there and have
- a drink with us, right?
- Let's go.
RADER: What's the fuck
wrong with you, man?
I'm just damn proud of him.
He's part
of the brotherhood now.
We got Ruben, Archangel Gabriel.
And we got Superboy,
and we got one motherfucking
family, right, Pike?
Get in the truck.
You never did know how
to have fun, did you?
You should be like your little
brother more, you know?
He's a little bit more loose.
You wanna know
something? (CHUCKLES)
You used to be my hero
when we were young.
- RADER: (CHUCKLES)
- Get in the truck.
Used to be the hero.
Used to be.
What the fuck is you...
What's wrong with you?
As I... as I recall,
you were the one who told me
you won't take care
of this shit.
You know? You vouched for him.
I'm just having a drink
with him.
And you know what?
Your word, your precious word
don't mean shit to me no more.
And you got nothing
to say, do you?
Your brother comes in here,
pulls out a gun in my place
and I got three
fucking bodies to bury.
- Give me a fucking shovel.
- RADER: (CHUCKLES)
Seriously, you're still
a man of few words.
Give me a fucking shovel. Yeah.
You know, seriously, you know
what your fucking problem is?
Is you actually think
that you're silence
bought you favors with me.
And you could not be so
motherfucking wrong.
Set up the bank meet.
Stay the fuck away
from my brother.
Hm.
Sprout some wings,
Archangel Gabriel.
(RETCHING)
Get in the truck.
Come on!
(ENGINE STARTS)
I told you to stay
the fuck away from Rader.
You think it's a fucking game?
WES: Fucking game.
GABE: Do you think
this is a game?
And you love
playing a game, bitch.
Fucking little brother
fucks shit up,
big brother cleans it up.
It's fucking merry-go-round shit
that you get off on.
Just drive.
(DOG BARKING)
(ENGINE STOPS)
That some more shit
you steal from the old man?
Shut your fucking mouth, man.
You don't know
what it's fucking like.
Why don't you fucking tell me?
(CHUCKLES)
You wanna know about Iraq?
- I don't give a fuck about Iraq.
- Huh?
You wanna know about
all the explosions and shit!
I wanna know why
you fucked up my job!
Let me tell you something.
Over there, I had my team.
I had my unit.
I had my brothers!
And they had my fucking back!
Every fucking day,
I put on a uniform
that showed me
the respect I earn.
Yeah, you don't wear
that uniform anymore.
No, I'm not!
You know what I am doing?
Sweeping some fucking shop!
Is that the best I got
to look forward to?
Been home eight months!
The best I got?
And fucking my cigarette.
You know, when we hit
that armored car,
most alive I have felt
since coming home,
can you believe that?
Hm?
I just thought
Wesley fucking Russell,
you come back to your hometown
where your daddy
and your big fucking brother,
the same brother
who was your super hero,
when you were a little boy.
You could be just like then?
You can be a part of something?
I came back thinking
that I could...
I could belong
to something, too.
Can't you see
I'm trying to protect you?
(CHUCKLES) I don't need
your fucking protection, motherfucker?
I think I can take care
of myself, right?
This shit gets in your blood.
Takes over, makes you think
you're involved, but you're not.
Neither am I.
I'm trying
to look out for you, man.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
You know
what's really fucked up?
Is whenever I shot
that armored guard,
I don't feel
a fucking thing, man.
I'm no better than some
fucking Hadji overseas.
You need help.
You know what would help me,
is the bank job
that Rader mentioned.
- No.
- WES: Hm.
We're done.
What are you talking about?
No, fucking no.
GABE: You gotta get
clean, brother.
And I can't save you.
Get the fuck out of my house.
The fuck out!
(PHONE RINGS)
We'll be in touch, thank you.
Just got off the phone
with the owner
of the stolen car.
Did we clear him?
Roberts is working on it.
But get this,
the owner discovered
the keyless entry FOB
stopped working
prior to the robbery.
- Okay. Is that a crime?
- JORDAN: No,
but whoever had
access to the car
traded it out
with a lookalike FOB.
Wouldn't raise questions
with the owner.
Well, did they mention
who had access prior?
JORDAN: Two weeks ago.
Clemens Garage
and Wrecker Service.
There's something else.
Crime lab found
a tracking device
underneath the steering column
that survived the fire.
(TENSE MUSIC)
You gotta be shitting me.
Here's my theory.
Owner takes the car in
for repair.
Someone at the shop,
trades out the real FOB
with a fake one.
Give me some
of those duplicates.
JORDAN: Then one of them plants
a tracking device in the car.
They wait a few days.
They track the vehicle with GPS.
Almost there. Keep going, Gabe.
JORDAN: Locate the vehicle,
grab and go.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Interesting skill set.
Eliminate street thugs.
And they'd have complete access
to the vehicle at the shop.
That's good.
Alright um,
let's... let's question
the other owners
of stolen cars, okay?
See if they visited the shop.
See if they'll testify to it.
Then I want any documentation
they have.
Alright. Receipts, phony key
FOBS, phone calls, okay?
They got a new carburetor,
I want to know the part number.
And let's expedite it, right?
I want to be there the next time
these assholes
think they can take
a score in my city.
(ENGINE STOPS)
GABE: What's the take?
It's a $100,000
between two tellers
at the front counter.
There's an additional $100,000
right behind them
at the drive-up windows.
Every Wednesday,
at 11:00 AM sharp,
Wells Fargo delivers.
Now they deliver cash
for that week's payroll.
They're also picking up
any deposits
that were put in the bank
that week.
But that's about $400,000
or $500,000.
You mix that
with the bank's money
and you're leaving with at least
half a million dollar take.
What about security?
No security. Wells Fargo guy
will come in, he'll drop off,
he'll pick up, and he's gone.
- What about cameras?
- Yeah, there's cameras.
But I'll have them disabled
for the day of
for scheduled maintenance.
So, what's your end?
My end?
It's 10%.
Why does a bank manager
rob his own bank?
ROSKAM: You trust the bank.
Banks are like the streets, man.
You keep your eyes open,
you look both ways every time.
You gotta be present
on the day of.
I'll be there.
Devland,
I pray to God
that you completely understand
what will happen
if this comes back on us.
Yeah, I know.
Get the schematics?
Yeah.
Everything you need
is right there.
- SOLOMON: Looks perfect, honey.
- ALLISON: Thank you.
- SOLOMON: Great job.
- ALLISON: Okay.
- Go get Chloe.
- Okay.
- (PHONE BUZZING)
Actually, one minute.
I gotta take this.
- It's the office. They...
- ALLISON: Seriously?
They know it's an important day.
- ALLISON: Right now?
- They wouldn't call me
if they didn't find anything.
One... one second.
Hello? Better be good.
Hey.
Grounded. Room.
Now.
Yeah, one minute.
Let's go.
Don't bug your sister.
Alright.
Callin' me at home
on my daughter's birthday,
it better be good.
Check your email.
- SOLOMON: Okay.
- Per your request,
I set up a meet
with the C.I. Remy.
He wants to meet tonight.
(CHUCKLES)
My man, Remy.
- Brett!
- Yeah? Uh.
Yeah, one minute.
Honey, one minute, okay. Just...
- What am I looking at?
- Open the attachment.
They're connected.
All stolen vehicles
visited the shop two weeks
prior to the robbery.
And we cleared the owners?
Ran into a problem.
What kind of problem?
Two of the owners have priors.
The others think
we're implicating them.
- Refuse to testify.
- Well, alright.
We can force a deposition.
Either way, we know these guys
are involved.
We need to move on this.
Alright listen, I want
to know everything there is
about this shop. I want
about the people
working there, alright?
They got any records.
See if they've ever
employed felons before.
Let's get surveillance
on them, ASAP. Alright?
Right. Got it.
Thank you.
Okay.
(BLOWS PARTY HORN)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(CAMERA SHUTTERS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Oh yeah. Thanks.
Is uh... is Dawnette
working today?
What happened?
Hey.
- What can I get you?
- DAWNETTE: I... I don't
wanna talk to you right now.
Do you feel like you can
drink or eat anything?
I don't need your help, okay.
I made it this far without you.
I'm... I'm fine now.
- I was trying to help.
- DAWNETTE: It is my fault.
You wouldn't understand.
Help me understand.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
IN BACKGROUND)
DOCTOR: How are you feeling,
Miss Russell?
Like shit.
How is she?
DOCTOR: Luckily,
there's no broken bones.
Just external abrasions.
The good news is,
as of right now,
the fetus hasn't miscarried.
But that could change anytime
in the next 24 to 48 hours.
There's just no way to know
yet what might happen.
It all depends
on how your body responds.
Okay.
DOCTOR: I'd, uh, like
to keep you another day
to run some more tests.
In situations like this,
the hospital provides
a Case Manager,
that I'd like you to, uh,
speak to.
They'll be over soon.
You should go.
How far along are you?
Two months.
I already told Eddie about it
and he flipped out.
Um, he thought I was trying to
trap him or trick him
or something I guess.
I don't know, maybe he's right.
Was that Eddie at the diner?
DAWNETTE: Yeah.
You gonna say something?
I'm leaving soon.
I've got a place
and I want more than anything
for you to go with me.
We can start over.
I can't... I can't
just pick up and leave.
I mean
it's not that easy for me.
I don't have any money.
I don't even know
how I'm gonna pay for this.
Let me worry about that.
Just think about it.
I do need one thing from you.
What?
I need to know
how to find Eddie.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
WES: Who is it?
GABE: Me.
Yeah.
What do you want?
I've got a problem.
You're asking me for help?
Yeah.
Alright.
Why didn't you fuckin' say so?
(TENSE MUSIC)
(SPITS)
Alright, there's no back door
and only one way in.
You got a gun?
I don't need one.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
EDDIE: Who the fuck is it?
WES: Jehovah's fucking Witness,
open the door.
Wes.
- WOMAN: (SCREAMS)
- EDDIE: (GRUNTS)
Jesus.
- (GUNSHOT)
- (SCREAMS)
Look at me, motherfucker.
Pack your shit
and get out of town.
I don't ever want you
to talk to Dawn again.
You hear me?
Fuck you.
(GRUNTING)
Hey.
Hey!
Let go of me.
WES: Come on.
You done.
Done.
Whoo! (CHUCKLES)
Pretty boy got fucked up.
Hey.
We're all over the place.
Pull over.
It's fine.
WES: Pull the fuck over.
Come on, slow down.
Right there.
(SIGHS)
Is my niece alright?
Is she gonna be okay?
Yeah.
She's gonna be.
I'm proud of you.
Thanks for being there.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Hmph.
If you want in, you're in.
WES: You know what's funny
is for the first time
I think I want out
of this place.
By the looks of it,
think you do, too.
GABE: Let's go.
SOLOMON: Hey, Remy.
(RONNIE BREATHES DEEPLY)
Well, what's up, Remy?
Flat broke, man.
Run... run outta money again.
Need a little help
from my friends.
I got you right here.
What, are they trying
to bring you back
into the fold, huh?
Oh, no, no, no, man.
I told you,
I'm through with that shit.
I'm not going back.
Well, but is that life
through with you?
Once you cross over,
you don't really come back.
Quit fucking with me,
Super Agent man?
Just tell me, what...
What the fuck you want?
You heard about this crew
that's been hitting
these armored cars?
Yeah, I heard about 'em. So?
Well, I was kinda hoping
a little birdie
might have told you something.
Yeah, it's a...
It's a big city, Remy,
but it's a small,
organized crime underground.
Yeah. I don't know who
these motherfuckers are, man.
But they're grabbing
their shit quick.
They jerking it off the streets.
Shit, they're trying
to beat your record.
Ain't nobody gonna break
my damn record, man.
You know,
I was trying to get out, man.
Your line of business
does have a shelf life, Remy.
You want my opinion?
Mhmmm.
These boys are gonna grab
their money.
They're gonna pay
all their damn bills off
and then, they're gonna
disappear, man.
And money gone, you ain't never
gonna see 'em again.
Plus, I think
what's gonna happen,
they're gonna stick
their goddamn toes
in some sand
and laugh at your ass.
So you don't recognize the M.O.?
I don't recognize anything.
Hmm. Why?
'Cause you would have heard
something by now?
I swear to God, man.
I think somebody's
taking care of 'em, man.
They'll take care of them
as long as they want to.
And then at some point,
just like me,
they get stuck.
And when they're stuck,
they're fucked.
Yeah. You know,
I just gave you a whole
lot of money there, Remy.
You haven't really told me shit.
What the fuck you want?
Well, who do you know
that can move
that quantity of money?
I mean, besides a casino?
RONNIE: There's only one
motherfucker I can think of.
Yeah, who's that?
It's gotta be...
goddamn Whitman Rader.
(MUSIC ENDS)
DAWNETTE:
So, what happens now?
Come with me.
Don't make promises
you can't keep, okay?
GABE: No, listen.
Two days.
That's all I need.
Why two days?
Because I've got
some loose ends.
Pack a bag.
Just enough to get out of town.
Meet me Wednesday night.
We can leave from the diner.
Can you do that?
I won't let you down again.
SOLOMON:
Okay, what have we got?
Wesley Allen Russell.
Served eight years in the Army.
Five in the Rangers.
Ran him. No priors.
Discharged after popping hot
for cocaine
after a two week recce in Iraq.
Been employed at the shop
ever since his return.
And most recently,
became the proud owner
of a new Roush Mustang.
Guy thinks he's Magnum P.I.
What I wanna know is,
how does someone afford
this car on minimum wage?
- Well, that's our position.
- SOLOMON: Mmhmm.
He'd also have knowledge
of weapons and tactics.
The plot thickens.
SOLOMON: Hm.
Rader, what do we know
about him?
Owns a local dive
outside of town.
But get this, 25 years ago,
Rader was running organized
crime in Dallas County.
Has a jacket as long as my arm.
Goes off the map in about '04.
Been clean ever since.
And how does Wesley
track with Radar?
Word on the street
is that he frequents his bar.
Okay. Let's run
through Intelligence.
See what they find out.
What about this guy?
- JORDAN: Big guy?
- SOLOMON: Yeah.
- We're not sure yet.
- SOLOMON: Okay.
- And?
- JORDAN: Shop foreman.
And the Spanish guy?
JORDAN: Too many to track.
The shop employs mostly
Spanish speaking personnel.
What's our move?
Where is this
Wesley Russell now?
Surveillance tracked him
to a dance club.
What, strippers?
Could be washing the money.
Let's bring him in.
I want to talk to him.
(HORN HONKING)
FBI AGENT 1: Mr. Russell?
- FBI AGENT 2: FBI!
- FBI AGENT 1: In the car!
In the fucking car!
WES: You got me.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
SOLOMON: Has he said anything?
Not a word.
Oh, good.
We'll let him sweat a little.
JORDAN: Don't spook him.
We don't need him to lawyer up.
(SIGHS)
Well, let's keep it simple then.
Mr. Russell.
WES: Finally.
Do you have a cigarette?
- No.
- No. I'm Agent Jordan.
This is Agent Solomon.
That's fucking great.
Am I in trouble or something?
Well, not unless you're married.
Got a little glitter
on your shoulder there, bud.
We just have a few questions
for you.
How long have you worked
at Clemens?
Uh, few months I guess.
Yeah, give or take.
What's the pay like there?
Pay? Fucking pay.
You know what? That's exactly
what I was saying.
Right, we were just talking
about this.
I mean, a Ranger, right?
Sweeping floors at a garage.
That's grunt work.
It can't pay more
than minimum wage.
I ain't no fucking grunt.
SOLOMON: Okay, okay.
I gotta, uh, a kid,
he's about to turn 16.
My wife and I were about
to get him a new ride.
But, uh, you know,
they're not cheap.
Cars these days.
And I noticed
that you got a new car.
So, I was just wondering,
how does someone afford
something like that
on minimum wage?
Hazard pay.
From the shoot 'em up,
Army days.
SOLOMON: Army left you
a hazard pay.
Of course, they probably left
you with some other things.
Right?
Weapons training?
Hostage tactics?
Maybe, uh, a chip
on your shoulder?
Where's this going?
Look, Mr. Russell,
explain to us...
How do you know Whitman Rader?
You look like a nice lady.
Is this one of those moments
where I need a lawyer?
SOLOMON: Well, well,
I don't know.
You know it's not a bad idea, right?
But, usually,
in our line of work,
if somebody needs a lawyer,
uh, they have something
to hide so...
I don't know
a fucking Whitman Rader.
Okay. That's weird.
That is weird though,
because the word on the street
is you frequent his bar
quite a bit.
- Solomon.
- What? We're just talking.
We're just talking here,
all right?
Just... just... just tell me
how you know the guy?
Yeah, and that's my cue,
I'll take uh,
a get-out-of-jail-free card.
I'll take that, uh, that lawyer.
Listen, I, uh, I apologize.
Shit. I'm sorry.
We got off
on the wrong foot here.
How about this?
I'll make you another deal.
You tell me who this is
and, uh, you're free to go.
GABE: Moving, cover.
WES: Shot!
Moving!
Cover!
- MARCOS: Shot.
- GABE: Moving.
- Shot!
- MARCOS: Shot.
GABE: Moving. Shot!
Taught you fucks well.
Get a few rounds in?
No. What do you want?
You look like shit.
Yeah.
I wanted to see you.
We're meeting tomorrow night.
The fuck's wrong with you?
We need to talk.
GABE: So how'd they
pick up on you?
WES: The Roush.
What'd you tell 'em?
- WES: Nothing.
- No. No, look at me.
What did you tell them?
Nothing, man.
I didn't tell them shit.
Okay, I swear.
MARCOS: Do they know
about the bank?
No, but they're...
They're curious about Rader.
Wanna know how
I figure into things.
They know about me?
Yeah, this F...
This FBI dude Agent Solomon,
he's smart.
Do they know about me?
He fucking knows about you!
Okay?
It's the FBI!
We play this game
until we're done, Gabe.
Gotta call it off.
It's over, baby.
Gabe, what are we gonna do?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(MUSIC ENDS)
(WHISTLES)
Damn.
That's a nice shop.
That's what dirty money
gets you, huh?
Huh.
You must be, uh,
Ruben Russell's son?
Ran narcotics for, uh,
Whitman Rader back in the '90s?
Gabriel Russell, right?
That's right. Who are you?
Oh, sorry.
Agent Solomon.
You know, Gabriel, I had a...
A really nice chat
with your brother.
Told me all about you.
I mean, he only had
nice things to say, of course.
In fact, I think he looks up
to you, if you ask me.
Can I help you with something?
Well, actually
I was gonna see if...
You know, maybe if I showed you
some photographs.
If you could answer some
questions about 'em for me?
I'm pretty busy.
Well, just take a minute.
Does that ring any bells?
Oh, come on, buddy.
That's not your barbeque?
Oh, wait.
Let me show you my favorite.
This is great.
You guys left that
underneath that last car.
(SOLOMON CHUCKLES)
Thought you were
smarter than that.
No idea.
Nothing, huh?
Hm. Well, that's all right.
Federal Agents are actually
combing through your place
right now as we speak.
(YELLS)
ROBERTS: FBI!
Got a warrant.
Check those cabinets.
Check that room.
Turn this place upside down.
- Clear.
- (CLATTERING)
You know I read your file.
You spent 16 years in prison.
Because you wouldn't
give up information
about your criminal associates.
Yeah, I don't betray
my brothers.
SOLOMON: I love it, you guys
and your brotherhood
criminal bullshit.
So many secrets.
Speaking of brotherhood though,
what about the, uh,
the hit they put out on you?
Man, I heard you put that guy
in the hospital for a month.
I mean somebody put
a green light on you, Gabriel.
Somebody must have thought
you were gonna talk.
Is that why your father
stopped working with Rader?
FBI OFFICER 2: Clear!
Just... just answer me one thing.
Just... just tell me why?
Why, what?
Why take down scores again
for your own boss?
You must be confused.
I don't do that anymore.
Time changes us.
Well, that's where
I think you're wrong.
I think time,
for people like you,
is a weapon.
So, I guess it's just
a coincidence, huh?
That every owner
of a stolen vehicle
has visited this shop
before the robberies.
What a mystery.
Hm. The odds?
(CHUCKLES)
You know, you and your crew,
you killed that guard.
For that, you're gonna burn.
It's over for you, Gabriel.
You know what's coming for you.
Whatever's over for me,
came a long time ago.
Glad we agree on something.
Have a nice day.
Hey, Wesley. Good to see you.
(MUSIC ENDS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(GRUNTS)
Hi, baby.
(PHONE VIBRATING)
SOLOMON: Oh, shit.
Hello?
What?
What happened?
(MUSIC ENDS)
GABE: You have them?
MARCOS (SPEAKS SPANISH):
Looks good.
WES: Hey.
For good reason.
I don't think
anybody here can argue,
$640,000 for one day's work.
Not too bad, right?
So, the accountant
will be at the site
to exchange the cash
as soon as you arrive.
We're ready.
10:55 sharp we're at the bank.
Park on the side, but coming
strong through the front.
Upon our entry, I separate
the tellers from the alarms.
Control the counters,
and the window.
I'ma manage all the bank guests
and communication devices.
Tablets, cell phones, I got it.
Once we're in,
the world is ours.
No panic buttons, no calls out.
Get the bank's money,
we wait for the armored car
to arrive.
When it does, guard walks in,
we take him down.
Frisked, zipped,
nobody gets hurt.
Nobody dies.
And we're back here
tomorrow morning, 10:00.
Got it, bro.
Gabe. Wait.
Yeah, I got this, uh,
sneaky suspicion
that you... you gotta
tell me something.
Or you got something
to say to me?
So, just say it.
I got nothing to say to you.
You got nothing?
Then I'll see you tomorrow.
Good.
All good?
Yeah, we stick with the plan.
Let's go.
SOLOMON: What happened?
JORDAN: We lost 'em.
- What does that mean?
- It means that somehow
they evaded our surveillance.
It's a rhetorical question,
all right?
I know what it means.
What about, uh,
what about Wes' car?
Well, it's still
parked downtown.
He never came back for it.
Okay. Well then, yeah, easy fix.
Right? We focus on his brother.
Same with Gabriel.
His truck is still
at the garage.
And we didn't find anything
at Gabriel's place.
It was clean, Solomon.
And we have cars
outside their homes right now.
- Correct? Right now?
- JORDAN: We do.
They're not there.
I mean, it's...
It's two common thugs, guys.
I mean, what...
What about their father?
What about, uh, Ruben?
Off the grid. No known address.
All right, well...
Fuck it.
We'll contact Gabe's PO.
We don't have a case yet, Solomon.
If the PO catches wind
that we're onto him,
he's gonna arrest him
for parole violation.
He's gonna serve out
his remaining sentence and walk.
That what you want?
Are we not the FBI?
Figure it out.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
RUBEN: Come to make your peace?
I am.
I'm leaving.
I'm taking Dawn with me.
You know what to do?
Yes, sir.
Then let this be it for us.
I'll hold the space
for you, son.
(MUSIC ENDS)
Hey, can... let me call you back.
This is the remaining balance
on the property
and some start-up cash.
Can you put the deed
in someone's else's name?
I sure can.
Can I trust you?
Of course.
Thank you.
You're welcome, Gabe.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
Hey.
Go ahead.
Tell me some good,
we got anything?
No, we got nothing.
(SIGHS)
Can I help you?
We're actually closed.
Hello.
Who killed my little brother?
Oh.
Well, information costs money.
At least,
in my neck of the woods.
Hm.
MANDY: Baby?
WES: Yeah?
MANDY: I'm packed.
- MANDY: Baby!
- WES: No!
(GUNSHOTS)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(PHONE RINGING)
(SNIFFLES)
Yeah?
How are you?
Um, better.
Everything's gonna be
all right now.
New beginnings.
(SNIFFLES)
Are you there?
Uh, yeah.
New beginnings.
Be ready tonight.
I will.
Okay.
MARCOS: Hey, Gabe.
We can't wait for him, man.
We gotta go.
(CAR ENGINE REVVING)
RADER: Where's Superboy?
I don't know.
- RADER: You don't know?
- Do you?
How the fuck would I know
where he is?
You're the one
who vouched for him.
Superboy probably skipped town.
PIKE: Mm-hmm.
Which is probably for the best.
So, it looks like
you're gonna need a third man.
Would you do me a favor?
Go with him?
No, fuck that.
He's not going with us.
Well, he knows the workups.
And uh, he can control the room
better than even I can.
All right.
By the way, you don't have
any time left.
You're out of it.
So, don't even think about
disagreeing with me, all right?
You make me proud, okay?
- I got you.
- Throw him the ropes.
Give me the fucking vest.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
POLICE OFFICER: All stations,
can I get a sit rep?
Baker 218, to Adam 12,
we are on stage and location.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
Parking lot secure.
Stay off the radio.
What do we do?
GABE: It's time.
Everybody get down on the floor!
Get down on your knees!
- Get down on your knees!
- MARCOS: Get on the ground.
Hands up! Hands up!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Hands on your head!
- MARCOS: Listen up, listen up.
GABE: Everybody, be calm.
Everybody, be calm.
PIKE: You wanna sit
the fuck down!
GABE: Take out your cellphones.
Put them on the ground.
Do it! Quickly!
Loose bills.
Just leave the cash.
No dye packs. You understand me?
See this little boy out here.
He wants to go home today.
- MARCOS: Your turn.
- PIKE: Nice and easy.
Get the fuck down.
You! Get out here!
On your knees.
- Who the fuck are you?
- I'm the bank manager.
- PIKE: Bullshit!
- Don't you fucking lie to me.
- Where's Devland?
- I told you.
- PIKE: I'm warning you.
- MARCOS: Everybody, out.
Let's go.
- GABE: On your knees.
- Everybody's doing great.
- Come on.
Everybody, be calm.
PIKE: Hands
on your fucking heads.
- GABE: Right here.
- PIKE: On your knees.
On knees, come on.
Break this down!
GABE: I need you to give this
to Agent Solomon.
Do you understand me?
PIKE: What's going on?
MARCOS: Ho, ho! Ho!
What the fuck is going on
with you, motherfuckers?
What do you got going on?
GABE: Whoa, hey!
Hey! What are you...
Look at me. Easy. Easy.
MARCOS: Hold on, Pike.
What the fuck do you think
you're doing?
Put the gun down.
PIKE: Fuck this.
- GABE: We don't do this.
- PIKE: Uh-uh. This is my show.
MARCOS: Easy, Pike.
Right here, hey.
(SPEAKS SPANISH) Calm down.
PIKE: What are you doing?
Fucking me?
GABE: Hey. Look at me!
I ain't going down
like this, son.
- MARCOS: Put it down.
- Get over there, motherfucker.
Move! Over here!
You get over here, motherfucker.
Get the fuck o...
Uh-uh.
You're not looking at him.
I'm right here.
GABE (SPEAKS SPANISH): You set?
MARCOS (SPEAKS SPANISH):
I'm set.
Uhh.
(GUNSHOTS)
MARCOS: Gabe!
- Gabe.
- GABE: Hey, it's okay.
(INDISTINCT SPEECH)
We got this.
(MARCOS BREATHES HEAVILY)
GABE: Let's go.
(GRUNTS)
GABE: Give me your keys!
WOMAN: In the car! In the car!
(GRUNTING)
SOLOMON (ON RADIO):
Where are these guys?
We got fucked here, man.
What do you wanna do?
Get Rader on the phone.
Find out where the fuck
these guys are.
Right now!
- (MARCOS COUGHING)
- GABE: Stay with me.
Hey. Stay with me.
The hospital's right here.
MARCOS: They're gonna be
looking for us there.
It doesn't matter.
MARCOS: We play this game
until we don't.
Hey, we're past that.
You hear me?
It's gonna be okay.
MARCOS: Tell Camilla...
(COUGHS)
And the kids that I love them.
You're gonna tell 'em yourself.
You had that baby boy, man.
I don't want them to know.
- I don't want them to know.
- Hey. Hey.
We got this.
Breathe. Just breathe.
Hey, brother?
Marcos?
Mar... Marcos?
Marcos!
Hey! Hey! Hey.
Hey.
Fuck! Fuck!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(DOOR CREAKING)
RADER: Gabriel?
You look like you're coming out
of ether there.
Where's Pike?
GABE: You're an informant?
RADER: Informant?
What's this?
- Where's my brother?
- RADER: Brother?
Calm as a motherfucking bitch.
(GUNSHOT)
You fucked me, didn't you?
Guess you won, huh.
Man...
GABE: I told you to stay away
from my brother.
RADER: No, wait, wait.
Please, wait, wait.
- Please.
- (GUNSHOT)
- Are you Agent Solomon?
- SOLOMON: Yes.
He told me to give this to you.
Who did?
The robber.
ROBERTS:
Found the escape vehicle.
Torched.
And Solomon,
they said one of the robbers
was inside.
JORDAN: And somebody
got to Rader.
He's found shot dead
in his bar 15 minutes ago.
Mmm. (CLEARS THROAT)
You sons of bitches
got some explaining to do.
SOLOMON: Sheriff, what are you...
What are you talking about?
DAN: Any reason why the FBI
might be coordinating
with local PD on a bank job
behind my back?
- What bank?
- Frontier State Bank.
You all got an Agent
on that deal.
JORDAN: What is the hell
is Albright doing here?
ALBRIGHT: Hey.
Funny seeing you here.
- I've been meaning to come...
- ROSKAM: Oh! My man! Yo!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- I'm gonna give you some advice.
Don't run an undercover bust
during my fucking investigation!
Prick!
You all right?
GABE: How you doing?
GAS STATION ATTENDANT:
What can I get you?
GABE: I'm three out there.
I got this.
Fuck!
(GUN CLICKS)
(GUNSHOT)
Hey. We're closed.
Um, no, I'm actually
waiting on someone.
There's nobody here.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Goodnight.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(GABE COUGHS)
(SOMBER MUSIC)