[WONDROUS MUSIC]
[GENTLE BIRDSONG]
[WATER FLOWS]
NARRATOR: From time immemorial,
the ancient Ukrainian forest
has harboured amazing
secrets and mysteries.
Behind the Dark Mountain,
in the forest's heart,
the Source of Life is hidden.
It provides the forest
and its dwellers
with their power, their spark.
But one winter,
while the forest
was fast asleep,
with the guardian
alone watching over it,
a human broke into the forest
through the passage
in the Dark Mountain.
It was the owner of the sawmill.
He needed at least one drop
from the Source of Life
to save his dying
newborn daughter.
But then he returned and
brought an army with him,
hoping to take over the
entire Source for himself.
And so a terrible battle began
that left no winners.
Only losers.
All humans who had trespassed
behind the Dark
Mountain vanished.
The Forest Guardian
lost all but an echo of
his ancient strength.
And when the forest
creatures woke in the spring,
they were greeted by the
horrific consequences
of the humans' treachery.
Look at what our
enemies have done.
For this reason,
no human shall set foot
behind the Dark
Mountain ever again!
This is the new forest law.
- [BOULDER RUMBLES]
- [SOMBRE MUSIC]
Many years have
passed since that day.
[GENTLE MUSIC]
[YAWNS] Another winter is over.
Oh, I've slept so long.
I was having the
loveliest dream.
But this is better
than any dream.
[MUSIC LIFTS]
[CHUCKLES] It's finally spring.
[SQUEAKS, PURRS AND CHITTERS]
[SNIFFS]
[SNEEZES, THEN GASPS]
[CHITTERS]
MAVKA: Swampy!
It's the best part of
the best day of the year.
Time to wake up the forest.
[WONDROUS MUSIC]
[ICE CRACKLES]
[WATER GUSHES LOUDLY]
[GRUMBLES]
[MAVKA GIGGLES]
[SWAMPY PURRS]
[TRUMPET BLOWS]
[BURBLES]
[NYMPHS SIGH CONTENTEDLY]
[MOOSE LOW]
[BIRDSONG]
Hark! Hush, the master
of sounds, approaches.
Happy spring, Mavka!
Hush! You can fly?!
That's kind of huge news.
They'll call me Hush,
who conquered the sky!
Just don't tell Lesh.
He'll think I'm
stork-raving mad. [LAUGHS]
[WONDROUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
- HUSH: Whoa!
- [BIRDS TWITTER]
[VEHICLES RUMBLE AND RATTLE]
[HORN BLOWS]
[VILLAGERS CHANT AND
PLAY UPBEAT TUNE]
[RECORD SCRATCHES]
[CHANTS]
- [PLAYS HIGH-PITCHED SOLO]
- [VILLAGERS CHEER AND APPLAUD]
VILLAGER: Yeah! One more! More!
And the fans go wild!
We are so ready to
conquer the world.
Settle down, kid.
Hometown crowd.
Everybody knows us here.
Wow, I'm just so nervous.
What if things don't
work out in the city?
There are so many
other musicians there.
You have to believe
in yourself, Nina,
and let the music
show us the way.
Whatever that's
supposed to mean.
- [HORN HONKS]
- [VILLAGERS GASP]
VILLAGERS: What was that?
[GRUNTS]
[READS] "Big money
for an important job?"
Hm, not for a soon-to-be
musical legend like me.
But maybe Uncle
Leo can use this.
Lucas, your uncle,
he's not feeling well.
They called the
healer and everything.
Get home, quick.
Hopefully we'll see
you at the fair later.
[VEHICLE HISSES AND SPLUTTERS]
- Hey, look!
- What is it?
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
- [DOOR LATCH UNLOCKS]
- [VILLAGERS GASP]
[DARK MUSIC]
Greetings,
after so long, my
dear fellow villagers.
It is I, Kylina,
the daughter and only heiress
of the late sawmill owner.
The one that got burned
up by forest demons?
Yes, my father died tragically
in a forest wildfire,
but it had nothing to do with
your quaint superstitions.
After dear Daddy's death, my
mother and I left this place,
but soon I became an orphan.
- [VILLAGERS SIGH]
- Oh, poor thing. What a shame.
How positively tragic!
[VILLAGERS SIGH]
But now I am back to make
our village prosperous again.
I'm offering you all a job.
You'll have so much money
that you'll never
have to work again.
Not working is my dream job.
I'll rebuild the sawmill.
We'll start selling our
timber all around the world.
Aren't you all good and ready
to become rich and happy?
- Yeah!
- Absolutely.
- Yes!
- What do you want us to do?
All you have to do is pop
over the Dark Mountain...
- [VILLAGERS GASP AND MUTTER]
- VILLAGER: What?
Oh, she's cuckoo.
Ugh, just like her father.
But I'm talking huge money.
You can't buy another life.
Tell the evil spirits I said hi.
- [WARBLES]
- [GULPS]
[CHUCKLES, THEN GASPS]
- [FAINT WHIMPERING]
- What's that?
[CHITTERS]
[CROAKS AND SNIFFS]
[GRUNTS]
[ROARS]
Easy, easy.
[SNARLS]
[SNIFFS]
MAVKA: What's the matter?
- [CUB WHIMPERS]
- [GASPS]
A trap!
Probably left from
the old times.
[GRUNTS]
Huh?
[CUB WHIMPERS]
[CHUCKLES]
[EXCLAIMS JOYFULLY]
[LYNX PURRS]
[SWAMPY CHITTERS]
[CHUCKLES]
Huh?
[SQUEAKS AND SPEAKS
FOREST LANGUAGE]
The guardian is calling us.
- LUCAS: Uh, how is he?
- [BARKS]
He's holding on, but my
herbs can only do so much.
Leo needs real
medicine from the city.
But... it's not
going to be cheap.
Uh...
"Per-du-cabri-co-carum"?
Just give this to the
pharmacist in the city.
He'll understand.
Thank you. Sincerely.
[DOG BARKS]
Great news, Uncle.
A little perdi-caca-something-um
and you'll be good as new.
Lucas, what are you doing?
You can't waste
your money on me.
I'm old and I've
had a good long run.
Spend it on a nice girl,
get settled down...
[SIGHS] ..so your old
uncle can die in peace.
[WHIMPERS]
Nobody's going to D-word.
I'll find the money
some... where.
[CHUCKLES]
Uncle, you'll be
fine. I've got you.
- I've got you!
- [DOG GRUMBLES]
[DOG BARKS]
[WHINES]
[JOYFUL MUSIC]
[HORN HONKS]
SERVANT: Oh, madam, it's
your family mansion.
How... rustic.
KYLINA: Ugh, it's just
a revolting hovel.
A bunch of pathetic cowards!
All my plans are at risk
just because this primitive
mob is terrified by the forest.
- Move it, Frol!
- [FROL GROANS]
Oh, ma'am. Right
away. Just a second.
Do me a favour and get
these peasant rags off me.
How can they wear
this hideous stuff?!
Ugh, I hate it. Get
rid of it right away.
What a terrible piece
of tasteless trash.
Stupid, uneducated,
superstitious mob.
[GASPS]
- Frol!
- Oh, my God.
This is so old-fashioned.
[INSECT WINGS FLUTTER]
Don't get me upset, Frol.
It's bad for my complexion.
Oh, sure, madam.
- [FOOTSTEPS THUD]
- Oh!
[GLASS SMASHES]
[BOTH GROAN]
[GASPS]
Clumsy idiots!
Inside this case is... [GASPS]
Just be careful with it.
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
Mm?
What is it?
Uh, about this job offer...
Oh, forget it.
KYLINA: Who's there?
Frol!
Oh, about THAT job offer?
Please come in.
Hi. My name's Lucas.
It says you'll pay well.
KYLINA: Hmm.
Hmm.
I will.
If you're up to it.
Uh, I am.
I can do any job.
Good.
Eric, Derek, you go with him.
[BOTH GRUNT]
So... what do I have to do?
Find me the tree with this leaf.
Uh... Huh!
In the forest behind
the Dark Mountain.
Hmm.
FOREST-DWELLER: What happened?
The guardian is
summoning everybody?
This hasn't happened
since I was a sapling.
- I'd rather take a nap.
- The guardian?!
[UPLIFTING MUSIC]
Greetings upon the new spring,
my fellow forest-dwellers.
[ALL EXCLAIM SOFTLY]
Is everyone here?
Mavka, did you
wake everybody up?
[FOREST-DWELLERS MUTTER]
She's probably frolicking
through the crocuses
with Swampy again.
- [FOREST-DWELLERS CHUCKLE]
- I'm sorry I'm late, Guardian.
I was helping the lynx cub
get out of an old trap.
- How terrible!
- An old trap.
I thought they were all
removed after the battle?
Nymphs.
You are the forest's
armed forces.
Which one of you missed this?
Good job, Mavka.
You've embarrassed us in
front of the guardian.
[WONDROUS, ETHEREAL MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
Now, then,
listen, forest-dwellers.
The Supreme Spirits of Nature
whisper that dangerous
times approach.
Therefore, at midnight tonight,
in the heart of the forest,
the spirits shall
choose a new guardian.
Lesh, but what about you?
I have so little strength left.
The guardian's burden
has grown too heavy for me.
Lesh won't be the
guardian anymore?
Will the humans attack us again?
- Who else can protect us?
- HUSH: Hark.
Hush the sky conqueror
can become the guardian.
Guardian chatterbox?
Yeah, just what we need.
HUSH: I heard that.
But really, anyone can
become the guardian.
You mean like even you?
No, no, no, Mavka.
You may be the sweet,
pure soul of the forest,
but for this job you
are just way too nice.
No, I'm not.
Ooh. I feel unwell.
Ondina, are you alright?
See? So gullible and nice!
LESH: Enough!
All will be decided at midnight
in the heart of the forest.
[FOREST-DWELLERS MUTTER]
LUCAS: People say that
behind the Dark Mountain,
the water nymphs and tree
spirits can tickle you to death.
Uh, you're laughing and laughing
and then bleugh!
We don't believe in
monsters of the forest.
Where do we go from here?
I think through this way.
[GASPS]
[WONDROUS MUSIC]
[FIRE FIZZLES OUT]
Uh... [GULPS]
Uh-huh.
I didn't think we
came here to hunt.
This isn't hunting.
This is fun. [CHUCKLES EVILLY]
- Yeah.
- [GUN FIRES LOUDLY]
[BISON BELLOW]
- [OWL HOOTS]
- [GASPS]
[SWAMPY CHITTERS]
Impossible.
Today of all days.
[BISON BELLOW]
[LUCAS CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
It was an accident. I tripped.
I am extremely clumsy.
My childhood nickname
was Clumsy Lucas.
We'll make you Clumsy
Black-and-Blue-cus.
[GULPS AND LAUGHS AWKWARDLY]
DEREK: Mm-hm.
My brother thinks you
should go on by yourself.
[LUCAS GROANS]
If you find the tree,
mark it on the map.
OK.
I was gonna suggest that anyway.
[FAINT RUMBLING]
[BIRDS TWITTER FRANTICALLY]
[ANIMALS GRUNT FEARFULLY]
[HUFFS AND PUFFS]
I feel their fear.
[RUMBLING INTENSIFIES]
[FRENZIED MUSIC]
[BISON BELLOW]
[ETHEREAL MUSIC]
[BISON GROANS]
[SCREECHES]
[FRENZIED MUSIC FADES]
Quiet down.
Everything is fine now.
[SWAMPY CHITTERS]
What scared you so much?
[SNARLS AND BELLOWS]
Humans? Here?
I have to tell the nymphs.
Wait.
Come on, Swampy.
I'll deal with
the humans myself.
Let's show them how 'nice' I am.
[GROANS FEARFULLY]
[GRUMBLES]
Argh!
[SIGHS]
Where in the haunted
heck is this tree?
[RUSTLING]
Believe in yourself, Lucas.
Let the music show you the way.
[SIGHS] Whatever that means.
[PLAYS MELODIC FOLK TUNE]
[GASPS]
[FLUTE MELODY FADES]
[ETHEREAL MUSIC]
Ohh!
It's so beautiful.
Oh, thanks. I...
Uhh...
Argh!
- [SWAMPY GRUMBLES]
- Argh!
Forest demon! [PANTS]
Argh!
Is the human dead?
- [GROANS FAINTLY]
- [SWAMPY CHITTERS]
Is this some sort
of human magic?
HUSH: Mavka!
A lot of weird,
whistly, raspy sounds
coming from this
exact area and I...
- [GASPS]
- Uh, Hush.
You already learned how
to dismount the stork.
Nice.
I am on high alert.
Our forest has just been
incursion-ated by...
Argh! THE HUMANS!
I'll watch him. You
go get the nymphs.
Oh, no.
I say we can drive the human
out of the forest on our own.
So I would be Hush, the
first kicker-outer of humans?
Oh, I like that very much.
- Argh!
- [GROANS]
[CHITTERS]
Uh... Argh! Evil spirits.
Keep back, I'm warning you.
I... I'm a... borscht
belt in combat polka.
[HUSH SPEAKS IN ECHOED
TONES] Pathetic little human!
You violated our
sacred forest...
Huh?!
..and tried to harm
these noble bison.
No! Super no.
That was the bouncer brothers.
In fact, I saved
the bison from them!
MAVKA: What is this, then?
Oh. That's my flute.
I, uh, play my music
on it... with it.
'Music'?
And you were doing this
to try and magically
enchant me in some way?
No! Well, sure.
Music is kind of magic, but...
Wait, so you liked it, then?
You do not question
me, little human!
Why have you trespassed here?
A strange lady offered me a big
reward to find a special leaf.
Aha! You hear that? A reward!
I knew that all humans
were selfish and greedy!
- Why you little...
- [SWAMPY YOWLS AND HISSES]
- Ouch.
- [BELLOWS]
[ALL EXCLAIM]
HUSH: You see this!
Human treachery!
Huh?
Wow!
You are the most
amazingly beautiful demon
I have ever seen.
Your eyes.
I am not a demon.
I am Mavka, the
soul of the forest.
Well, I'm Lucas.
The soul of... myself?
Look, I can explain.
I need that reward to buy
medicine for my uncle Leo.
No. I have been warned that
humans are skilful liars.
You have broken the law of
the forest and I expel you!
No expulsion necessary.
I'll leave myself.
Just let me find
this silly leaf first
or else my uncle...
..dies.
How awful. I'm so sorry.
- [SWAMPY CHITTERS]
- Whargh!
[LAUGHS] Hey there, little...
What are you?
This is Swampy, the
last of the kittyfrogs.
LUCAS: Awww!
It's so cute how
much he hates me.
- [GROWLS]
- Oh!
You want something super yummy?
[SNIFFS]
[LUCAS LAUGHS]
Had a feeling you'd like that.
You're very different
from the evil humans
in all the forest legends.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
[OWL HOOTS]
[WIND HISSES FAINTLY]
[NYMPHS CHUCKLE]
[BROTHERS GRUMBLE]
- [FAINT RUSTLING]
- Huh?
[SQUEAKS]
Huh?
[GROANS]
Derek, hold my boomstick.
Derek?
[OWL HOOTS]
ERIC: Derek? Where are you?
HUSH: I'll teach you,
you filthy human!
Hush, what are you doing?
Swampy, spit it out immediately!
This grotty fleshbag is
trying to poison you.
Hey! It's my mother's recipe.
HUSH: Oh, Mommy
poisons folks too, huh?
[LUCAS AND HUSH GROAN]
MAVKA: Hush, stop!
Lucas, leave him alone.
- Huh?
- You gave it a name already?
[HUSH WARBLES AND TRUMPETS]
- [LUCAS GROANS]
- [GRUMBLES]
Lucas. Stop it right
now! [VOICE ECHOES]
[THUNDER CRACKS]
Well, he started
it. He has to leave.
I need the leaf.
Fine, here's a leaf. Now leave.
Not this one.
Are all humans this picky?
Lucas. It's not the
leaves you really need.
You need to heal your uncle
and I'll give you
the cure he needs.
LUCAS AND HUSH: Really?!
Oh, thank you. You are so nice.
Hey, hey, hey.
Do you really want
to break the law
to help a human on such a day?
You heard him.
He saved the bison,
and for some reason...
I believe him.
- [INSECT BUZZES]
- Urgh!
After all, the
soul of the forest
must help all the living
creatures in the forest, right?
And Lucas is a living
creature who is in the forest.
- Huh?
- Therefore, I have to help him.
And you will help me help him.
Me?
No way! Never!
Never, never, never,
never, never, never, never!
- No!
- [BIRDS WINGS FLAP]
When will I learn that I'm
incapable of saying no to you?
Don't worry, Hush. We'll make
it before the ceremony starts.
I'll give Lucas the cure
for his uncle and...
And then he'll leave
the forest forever.
I promise.
Hmm?
[ONDINA'S VOICE
ECHOES] Come to me!
Don't be shy. Come closer.
Ahhh!
[FROG CROAKS]
[ONDINA CHUCKLES]
[COCKS GUN]
[CHUCKLES AND GASPS]
Huh?
[SCREECHES]
Argh!
- [SCREECHES]
- [SHRIEKS]
[MUMBLES]
How did I...
Curses!
[SCREECHES]
- [HICCUPS]
- [SCREECHES]
- [WATER BUBBLES]
- Uh...
Oh.
[HICCUPS] Mm.
Huh?
[DEREK GROANS AND SCREAMS]
Mavka, how can I thank
you for your help?
Just tell me and I'll
do it with pleasure.
Maybe you could play
your music for me?
Oh. Sure thing.
[DISTANT SCREAMING]
No, no, no, not now.
Nobody can know you're here.
No, let him play.
The nymphs will hide him
safely in the forest,
one piece here, one piece there.
MAN: ♪ Wonder, I pray
♪ The star you trace
♪ Here is our land
♪ Only tightly hold my hand
WOMAN: ♪ Ask me
and I'll tell... ♪
- [MAVKA GASPS]
- ♪ How in love I fell
♪ Flying, flying
♪ Keep flying with me
BOTH: ♪ My world, your world
♪ No, we do not need the words
♪ Two hearts but one history
♪ Always beat in harmony
♪ My world, your world
♪ Flash of everlasting love
♪ Two hearts but one history
♪ Always beat in harmony
♪ Talking, talking,
talking to the wind
talking to the wind... ♪
[GRUMBLES]
WOMAN: ♪ Learn the language
♪ Of wind and rain
♪ Listen, listen
♪ To know me well
MAN: ♪ Cherish your will
♪ Your song, your magic skill
♪ Keep flying with me
BOTH: ♪ My world, your world
♪ No, we do not need the words
♪ Two hearts but one history
♪ Always beat in harmony
♪ Talking, talking,
talking to the wind
♪ Talking, talking, talking... ♪
You know, humans are not
actually as terrible
as you've been taught.
We have a lot of nice things.
Like music. It's so lovely.
You must be the guardian
of music in your world.
[LAUGHS] Not yet.
But my dream is to fill
my whole life with music.
As soon as my uncle gets better,
my musician friends and I
are leaving for the big city.
"The big city".
What is the big city?
It's a place where everything
is made of bricks and stone
and there are as many buildings
as there are trees
in the forest...
HUSH: Hurry up, hurry up. Move!
LUCAS: What are you
doing? Back off, shrubby.
Hush! Mavka!
Are you the ones
making all this noise?
[GULPS] Too late.
Nice knowing you, Mavka.
Up until today, anyway.
Lesh, how's it going?
Busier than I'd like.
Who is your guest?
Uh, I'm... Hush's...
cousin. [LAUGHS SHEEPISHLY]
Yes, dropped by for a
visit from overseas.
[CHUCKLES] Right, Hush?
[CHUCKLES] Uh-huh.
A very, very
many-times-removed cousin.
Shmucas is his name.
Ah! Welcome, friend Shmucas.
[CHUCKLES] Come quickly. The
ceremony is about to begin.
Oh, great. What do we do now?
Do you realise how
illegal this is?
We just need to keep our
distance from the new guardian.
As soon as the ceremony is over,
I'll come up with something.
FROL: You look just like
your parents, madam.
Hm, much better now.
Yeah. Lovely portrait.
Totally... horridness.
Hmm?
[BROTHERS MOAN]
Hmm. Did you find the tree?
So what stopped you?
Bunnies? Squirrels?
The forest demons?
[HICCUPS AND CHUCKLES]
FROL: Knuckleheads.
Totally useless. Oh!
Stop being such fools.
You are stupid idiots.
What am I paying you for?
And where is the boy?
[GRUNTS]
Oh!
- Out of my way.
- [EXCLAIMS]
Oh!
Oh, damn!
I'm running out of time.
And where is this peasant loser?
[FOREST-DWELLERS MUTTER]
Ohhh! Oh!
[CHITTERS IN FOREST LANGUAGE]
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
- Hey.
- [MEOWS]
Shhh!
It is time.
Hmm!
Oh! That's the...
The Supreme Spirits of Nature,
I summon you.
The One Who Dwells in the Earth,
I call on you.
The One Who Moves the Waters,
The One Who Flies
with the Wind...
..the One Who Sits
on the Rock...
..I call on you.
Those who protect us,
those who help us,
those who dwell at
the Source of Life,
please choose the new guardian.
[INTENSE MUSIC]
[GASPS]
Mm.
Hmm?
SPIRIT: The guardian is chosen.
[GASPS] Huh?
- Her?
- Me?
What's happening?
Is it good or bad?
Please close the knothole
on the front of your face.
Lesh, why me?
I can't possibly
be the guardian.
I have to tell you something.
The Supreme Spirits are wise,
and they know who is capable
of protecting our realm.
Now the Supreme Spirits
will bestow their powers
on the chosen one.
[WONDROUS MUSIC]
[WIND WHISTLES]
[WONDROUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOREST-DWELLERS
GROAN AND EXCLAIM]
[GENTLE MUSIC]
- Incredible.
- Perfect.
So how do we "keep our distance
from the new guardian" now?
Mavka, you are now granted
the powers of the Supreme
Spirits of Nature.
It is for you now
to always remember
that our enemy -
the humans - are out there.
Defend this fragile,
sacred place
with your very life.
Please welcome our new guardian
of the Source of
Life and the forest.
[WONDROUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
That was just... whoa!
Our little Mavka is
now the guardian.
I always knew this would happen.
[SCOFFS]
There has got to
be some mistake.
Why did the spirits not
choose the strongest one?
With her as guardian,
our forest is more
in danger than ever.
Hey. Easy there, friend.
Who are you supposed to be?
Me? I am, uh, Hush's cousin.
You... [SNIFFS]
You stink like a human.
Yeah, he stepped in some
human on the way here.
Uh, Cousin Shmucas.
If he's a noise keeper,
I'm the new guardian
of the forest.
And we all know...
- ..I'm not.
- [FOREST-DWELLERS GASP]
- [GASPS]
- Uh... oops.
Human?!
Run. Move your footsticks.
You treacherous human.
You have tricked me!
- Human?
- Oh, no, he's a human.
Don't let him get away!
Am I the only one here
who's completely confused?
LESH: Hush!
You've got a great deal
of explaining to do.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Argh!
[SPLUTTERS]
- Huh?
- [SCREECHING]
Argh!
[FOREST-DWELLERS MUTTER]
[SIGHS]
[SNARLS]
Argh!
[NYMPHS SHRIEK]
Argh! [SCREAMS IN SLOW MOTION]
Argh!
- Mavka.
- Get on, quick.
The lynx will take you home.
Whoa! Sounds safe.
[CHUCKLES] Nice... kitty.
Take this.
It will heal your uncle.
Thank you.
- Huh?
- [FOREST-DWELLERS APPROACH]
There's no time. Go...
and never return.
Death is the only thing
for a human to seek here.
- Go!
- Wait!
I promised I'd play for you.
Where is he? Where's the human?
He got away.
What? How did he...
You helped him?
You have the powers
of the guardian
at your disposal,
you could have -
no, you should
have - stopped him.
The guardian doesn't
need your help
deciding how and when to
use her powers, Ondina.
Mavka,
this human is no different
than all the others.
He will betray you.
And when he does, we
will all pay the price.
Hmm.
Frol!
Yes, madam?
There's something
about this boy Lucas
I don't trust.
Watch him.
I'm not so sure
he came back from the
forest empty-handed.
Me?!
Madam, I am a fashion
tsar in the making,
not a spy.
Oh, that's too bad.
If I get what I want,
I could establish you
as the number one fashion god...
..in the world.
With my own Soul of Frol
Manly Lace Boutique?
With a global chain
of whatever insane
thing you just said.
Then, if you need a spy,
why, Frol is your guy.
[CHICKENS CLUCK]
Ugh. Uh!
Silks, ribbons and laces
don't have to be disgraces.
That's the Soul of Frol.
[CHICKENS CLUCK]
No. This really happened
to me. Last night.
The forest is full of -
not demons - but creatures.
And they are not
fond of us at all.
Except Mavka. She is very nice.
Danger or no, I have to
go back to the forest
to Mavka, to thank her.
Lucas, look, if you've been at
the village fair all night long
and plan on going back,
you can just tell me.
Busted. You know me.
Party animal.
Best carnival ever.
[HEN AND ROOSTER CLUCK]
[ROOSTER CLUCKS ANGRILY]
- [KNIFE BLADE RINGS]
- FROL: Mmm!
[CLUCKING CONTINUES]
So how is this,
uh, perdi-caca-something-um
supposed to work?
I have less than no idea.
- [MUSIC DISTORTS]
- Huh?
[WHIMPERS]
Uncle?
[WHIMPERS QUIZZICALLY]
Whoa!
Hah! And no pain.
I haven't stood this
straight in 20 years.
It's a miracle. [LAUGHS]
[SQUEALS]
It is a miracle.
It's a miracle of
perdi-caca-something-um.
I've got so much energy.
Now I'll be Hercu-Leo.
Hey, let's take up curling.
- [DOG BARKS]
- [LEO CHUCKLES]
[GROANS]
[GASPS]
[CLUCKS QUIETLY]
[FROL LAUGHS EVILLY]
[GIGGLES TRIUMPHANTLY]
- [ROOSTER CLUCKS]
- [KNIFE BLADE RINGS]
[GULPS]
- [ROOSTER CAWS]
- [SCREAMS]
FROL: Cock-a-doodle-doo.
Cock-a-doodle-doo.
Yeah, it's bit more
complicated now.
But, Swampy, think for yourself.
How can he play his beautiful
music without his flute?
We have to return this to Lucas.
What if something happens in
the forest while I'm gone?
What if nothing
happens while I'm here?
You're absolutely right.
I'm the guardian now. I
can't leave the forest.
Humans are enemies.
I somehow managed to live
without Lucas before.
Or his music.
Or his eyes.
Or his smile.
Or this feeling
that now lives right here.
[SIGHS]
[PLAYS SINGLE NOTES]
[GRUNTS]
[EAR POPS]
- [SIGHS]
- [FINGER SQUEAKS]
Hmm. Mmm.
Madam! Madam! Where's Madam?
- [STAMMERS]
- [GUNSHOT BLASTS]
- [CHANDELIER THUDS]
- [GRUNTS]
[SPITS, LAUGHS]
- [BANGS PIANO]
- [GROANS SOFTLY]
[GASPS] Madam is
probably upstairs.
- [WARDROBE CLATTERS]
- Gah!
[LIVELY MUSIC]
Madam! Madam!
Madam, you were right!
[PANTS, GULPS]
[SPITS] Eugh!
- [EXHALES]
- [ATOMISER SPRAYS]
That icky boy lied to you!
Here.
[GASPS]
Oh. [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Lucas was at the Source of Life.
The heart of the forest.
And I also found this.
Finally it will be mine!
[GASPS]
But... but there is
nothing marked here!
Now think! Did Lucas say
anything about the tree?
[STAMMERS] No!
Nothing about the tree,
but he just said he will
go into the forest again
to see the nice forest.
The magma! Boy, what a fool.
It doesn't make sense.
The nice forest magma?
Yeah, that's what he said.
He probably wants to keep
the source to himself.
- Frol.
- Yes, Madam?
- Keep an eye on this boy.
- [CLICKS FINGERS]
When he decides to
go to the forest,
we need to keep him
company by all means.
[SINISTER MUSIC]
[BIRDS SING]
MAVKA: But on the other
hand, as the guardian,
shouldn't I learn as much
about our enemies as I can?
If Lucas isn't evil, maybe
other humans aren't evil either.
[CROAKS]
Oh, stop croaking about
the law of the forest!
Maybe it's time for
things to change
so that the forest-dwellers
and humans could live in peace.
Oh!
[ROOSTER CROWS IN DISTANCE]
[DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE]
[SWAMPY CHIRPS]
[ENCHANTING MUSIC]
[BISON LOWS]
[SIGHS]
Uhh, no! I can't show
up looking like this.
- [PURRS]
- Hm!
- [GIGGLES]
- [SCREECHES]
Huh?
Gotta find something
a human would wear.
[ROOSTER CROWS IN DISTANCE]
[PURRS]
[LAUGHS]
[CROAKS, YOWLS]
[CHIRPS]
[PURRS]
[SQUEAKS]
[WHINES SOFTLY]
- [CROAKS SOFTLY]
- [WHINES CURIOUSLY]
[GROWLS, SNIFFS]
- [CROAKS]
- [WHIMPERS]
[BARKS]
[CROAKS]
Hey, boy. I'm making a gift.
[BARKS]
Yes, Dot, Mavka is
going to love me.
Uh, it! It.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
- [SCREECHES]
- [DOT GROWLS]
And... done.
[BARKS]
[WHIMPERS]
- Hey, where are the pies?!
- [WHIMPERS]
[SWAMPY LAUGHS]
[CHUCKLES] Pie-demolisher!
- [WHINES SOFTLY]
- It's fine.
I'm not perfect either.
For instance, I'm about to
break my promise to Hush
and the forest law
in order to keep my
promise to Mavka.
- [GASPS]
- [MAVKA GASPS]
Mavka, are you here?
Your hair! How are you here?
Aren't you happy to see me?
No. I mean, yes!
Heart-burstingly happy,
which is a thing I probably
shouldn't say out loud.
[GIGGLES SOFTLY]
Oh, is this your nest?
[CHUCKLES] I prefer to
think of it as a cave.
Is this for making music too?
[LAUGHS]
- [TOOLS CLANG]
- Uh, no. [CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
Those are regular instruments,
not musical instruments.
I've come to return your flute.
It was broken, but I...
Here.
Thank you.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC]
Now you can go to the stone
forest and follow your dream.
Just play for me one last
time and then I'll leave.
No. No, don't leave!
Uh, I have an idea.
I'll play even
better music for you.
There's a festival in town and
my band is playing. Let's go!
- Uh...
- [CHUCKLES] Don't be afraid.
It'll be good for
guardian of the forest
to know more about
us humans, right?
Uh...
- You're gonna love it.
- [GIGGLES]
[DELICATE CHIMING]
[COW MOOS IN DISTANCE]
[ENCHANTING FOLK MUSIC]
[PIG SNORTS]
[VILLAGERS CHATTER INDISTINCTLY]
[GASPS]
Huh?
[GIGGLES]
Mavka, let's find you
an outfit that says,
"I am a non-alarming
local human."
What's wrong with this one?
Well, it kind of screams,
"Howdy, I'm a barely
disguised forest demon
"from behind the Dark Mountain."
[GASPS]
Oh!
[ELECTRONIC FOLK MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
[ELECTRONIC FOLK
MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MAN GASPS]
Oh.
- [GOAT BLEATS LOUDLY]
- Oh!
- Hm?
- [BOTH LAUGH]
- [BOTH GRUNT]
- [KNUCKLES CRACK]
[PURRS, MEOWS]
[CROAKS, PURRS]
- And this is my uncle Leo.
- Oh!
He's the one you
saved with your gift.
[HAMMER CLANGS]
[SCULPTURE HISSES]
- [STOMACH RUMBLES]
- [GASPS]
Hm? [LAUGHS]
[BOTH GIGGLE]
[GASPS] What have you done?
[BAND PLAYS LIVELY FOLK MUSIC]
Oh! Those are my
friends playing.
[MUSICIANS SING]
- [MAN TRUMPETS MELODY]
- [WOMEN TRILL RHYTHM]
[LUCAS LAUGHS]
[LIVELY FOLK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MAVKA GIGGLES]
- [MUSIC STOPS]
- [VILLAGERS LAUGH AND CHEER]
This music, the dancing
- how delightful!
But you still play
better than anybody else.
MARCO: He was born that way!
So, Lucas, Uncle
Leo is recovered.
He looks better than you now.
Isn't it time to show your
talent to the big city?
Um, well...
Or has the music shown
you a different way?
A very beautiful way.
Well, your call, Romeo.
We're always happy
to have you with us.
Pack up. We gotta go.
Oh, that's right, it's
late. I must go too.
Thank you for the wonderful
time and for the gift.
Wait! I haven't
fulfilled my promise yet.
[PLAYS MELODIC FOLK TUNE]
[DELICATE CHIMING]
- Look! A demon from the forest!
- [VILLAGERS GASP]
[GASPS]
- She's glowing!
- Green hair!
An evil spirit from
behind the Dark Mountain!
WOMAN: What shall we do?
She's come to kill
our lovey ones
and destroy our food crops!
No! It's not true!
FROL: This lad is trying
to protect the demon.
She has bewitched him.
- She'll put a curse on us.
- [VILLAGERS GASP]
Get her!
No! She won't hurt anyone.
[VILLAGERS GASP AND EXCLAIM]
[MAVKA GASPS]
- Lucas!
- [LUCAS GASPS]
MAVKA: No!
- [GROWLS] Hm...
- Argh!
[VILLAGERS GASP]
- [LUCAS GRUNTS]
- [SHOVEL THUDS]
- [GROANS]
- [SHOVEL CLANGS]
[SHUDDERS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOW THUDS]
MAVKA: Let me go! Lucas!
What do we do?
- Burn her, right?
- No, they drown witches!
Let's do both!
My fellow villagers,
I was wrong.
The evil spirits of the
forest are very real.
And now I see that it was her
kind that burned up my father,
the goodly sawmill owner.
MAN: How dare she!
But fear not!
My eyes are open now
and I will find out what the
demons have in store for us,
be it plague...
- [VILLAGERS GASP]
- ..drought...
- ..famine, fire or flood!
And where the Source of Life is.
[DELICATE CHIMING]
- [TORCH HISSES]
- Oh!
- [VILLAGERS GASP]
- What is this?!
- What's happening?
- Black magic!
[YOWLS]
[SCREECHES]
[MUFFLED YELLING]
- [BOTH GROAN]
- [MAVKA GASPS]
- Argh!
- [HISSES, YOWLS]
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[BLADE RINGS]
KYLINA: Don't let her get away!
[GROWLS]
[PANTS]
- [CHIMING, CREAKING]
- [VILLAGERS GASP]
[LESH GRUNTS]
- Lesh!
- [ROARS]
[VILLAGERS SCREAM]
[LESH GROANS]
- [SWAMPY SCREECHES]
- [LESH GROANS]
[VILLAGERS EXCLAIM]
- MAN: Where'd he go?
- WOMAN: Is he gone?
All is lost!
My strong silks, my robust
ribbons, my manly laces,
the Soul of Frol - gone!
[BOTH GROAN]
Oh!
It isn't over yet,
my whiny little pet.
My poor, dear, terrified
fellow villagers,
we underestimated
the demon's power
and the results were tragic.
- [STALL RUMBLES]
- [VILLAGERS GASP]
But this is not the end.
They'll soon be back!
- Oh, no! What do we do?
- Oh, this is terrible!
There's only one way
to stop this evil.
Strike first!
[THUNDER CRACKS, RUMBLES]
[SOBS] Lesh, how
did you find me?
Hush told me everything.
I don't understand what's
happening. Those humans...
Calm down now.
Those humans obviously conspired
to lure you into a trap.
I love how no matter where you
look, you see goodness, Mavka,
but you have made the
same mistake I made once
in trusting a human.
Lucas would never do that.
I'm sure he can
explain everything.
[GROANS]
- Mavka!?
- [MICE SQUEAK]
[GRUNTS]
[MICE SQUEAK]
[GROANS]
Now, Lucas,
be a good boy of limited
intellect and integrity
and mark the Source of Life
on this crudely drawn map.
Never gonna happen, lady.
Somebody found a backbone!
Let's see if we can't just
melt it like meringue.
Ooh, I'm peckish.
[MUFFLED CRIES]
Oh, no!
[DELICATE CHIMING]
Don't touch her!
The source...
- [WHIMPERS]
- ..or she dies.
[TENSE MUSIC BUILDS]
Now let Mavka go!
Sure thing, ding-a-ling.
Oh, Lucas! Smooch,
smooch, swoon!
Oh, you saved me! You saved me!
You're so, so dumb. [LAUGHS]
No! Kylina, you won't
get away with this!
- Ah! Ah!
- [KYLINA LAUGHS]
Really? Guess I'll
just stop, then.
Have a nice swim, sweetie!
[PIPES CREAK]
So much water has flowed
past since that fateful day,
the time has come for me
to tell the full truth.
The battle all
those winters ago -
I've never told anyone the
reason why it happened.
[WIND HOWLS]
The sawmill owner
came to me in tears.
He was begging me to save
his newborn daughter...
..and I believed
in goodness in him.
I gave this human
a drop from the
Source of Life itself.
Soon, he returned with...
..well, with an army of humans.
They wanted the Source
of Life for themselves.
So, I called for the Supreme
Spirit of the Underworld,
the One Who Sits in the Rock,
to give me the Spark of Rage.
And, may all those
I love forgive me,
he did.
Everything good in me was
replaced by sheer rage.
I burned and the world burned.
Humans and the forest alike.
Fire and hatred without end.
Have you seen Lucas?
Have you seen my boy, Lucas?
[CONDESCENDINGLY] Oh!
Your boy's been taken by
the evil forest demons.
- Huh?
- Stings, right?
But you can still save
him if you join us.
Take the weapon, old man.
I'm on a schedule here!
You stay here and make sure
nobody finds the boy...
..unless you were just
dying to be in the battle?
[CHUCKLES CONDESCENDINGLY]
This is for our home!
[QUIETLY] And my youthful skin.
[LOUDLY] Now let's go
eradicate those demons
for the good of
all we hold dear!
- Yes!
- Yes! Death to the demons!
Start the forest killer!
[POWERFUL MUSIC]
[ENGINE ROARS]
[ALL CHITTER IN FOREST LANGAUGE]
Humans are preparing
to attack the forest.
Uh!
Hey! Somebody! Anybody! Hey!
[SIGHS]
[MICE SQUEAK]
[GRUNTS]
[DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE]
Dot? Dot, is that you?
[BARKS]
Good boy!
Run! Find someone
to help me! Hurry!
[BARKS]
[CHAINSAW BUZZES]
So, that's it. War is here.
The sawmill owner's daughter...
[GASPS] I know what to do!
What? Decorate their
axes with flowers?
I know what we all
need to do - fight!
No! There's another way!
I am the guardian and this
is my call. Wait here.
- [SCOFFS]
- Don't look at me.
She is the guardian.
[ENGINE ROARS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[VILLAGERS SHOUT
OVER EACH OTHER]
[DELICATE CHIMING]
[WIND WHISTLES]
[KYLINA GRUNTS]
[FOREST KILLER CREAKS]
What's going on?
Whoa!
[ENGINE RUMBLES]
MAVKA: Please stop!
[GASPS]
Hm.
I might've frightened
the people at the fair,
but the forest means
no harm to humans.
We can live in peace and
even help each other.
"Help each other"?
A long time ago, the
forest gave a drop
from the Source of Life to
the owner of the sawmill
so he could heal his
sick newborn daughter.
The forest saved you!
What? Nobody ever told me!
It is the truth.
[LAUGHS]
The truth?
The truth is the sawmill
owner never had a daughter,
but he had a beautiful wife
that came up with a tragic story
about a little sick daughter.
My husband was
obedient but weak.
He only got me
the one lousy drop
that kept me young and
fit for all these years.
But how does this
make us enemies?
Oh, you'll never understand
this. Look at you!
You're Nature's queen,
glowing and gorgeous forever!
You don't know nothing about
crow's-feet, turkey neck,
back fat.
You'll never get old and
saggy and shrivelled.
But I can give
you one more drop.
That is so nice of you,
but, see, if I get hold of
the entire Source of Life,
I will not only be young
and beautiful forever,
but it'll also make me
the richest, most
powerful woman ever.
But without the Source of
Life, the forest will die.
It's gonna die one way
or the other, honey,
so why not just
get out of my way?
Hm.
[TENDRILS RUMBLE]
Not all humans are as cruel
and selfish as you are!
Oh, you're thinking about
that lad of yours? Lucas?
Huh?
[TENDRILS CREAK]
Do you have any
idea where he is?
- [GASPS]
- [CHIRPS]
I... [GASPS]
I'll tell you another
truth, sister.
I paid Lucas very well so
he would find the source
and lure you into the village.
- Huh?
- He took his money and left.
To the city?
Exactly.
Oh.
- [VILLAGERS EXCLAIM]
- [TENDRILS RUMBLE]
And one more thing.
Lucas told me it was
almost too easy to fool you
because you're just so nice.
Oh.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Now get out of my way
and take your freaky
woodland zoo with you!
[SAW GRINDS, CLAW CLANGS]
[MAVKA SCREAMS, GRUNTS]
[HUSH AND SWAMPY GASP]
Mavka! I knew we couldn't
trust that Shmucas!
I got it so wrong, Hush.
Humans really are
all evil. Lucas is...
HUSH: Huh! Huh!
[BEASTS ROAR]
[SCREECHES]
[VILLAGERS SHOUT]
[NYMPHS SCREECH DEMONICALLY]
[ROARS, GRUNTS]
[CHAINSAW BUZZES]
[STUMP GROWLS]
- [SCREAMS]
- [TREES ROAR]
[BARKS]
[WHIMPERS]
[SAW SQUEALS]
Who are you, friend?
[BARKS]
You're saying Shmucas
didn't betray us?!
[BARKS]
- Do you believe him?
- [CROAKS]
Then I have an idea.
Mm! Frol Style! Madam
is going to love it!
- [SIGHS]
- [EAGLE SCREECHES IN DISTANCE]
Huh? [GASPS]
[DOT BARKS]
[STORK CALLS]
Well? Where's our hero?
- [HUSH GASPS]
- [SCISSORS CLICK]
Hm! Hm!
Go get Shmucas and I'll
deal with this one.
- [GRUNTS]
- Huh?
Hm!
[GRUNTS]
Argh!
I will slice you into
robust little ribbons!
[PANTS]
- [CROAKS]
- [BARKS]
LUCAS: Dot? [BANGS ON DOOR]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[WHINES]
[MEOWS SOFTLY]
Get back here, you
rotten cabbage!
[YELLS]
[BOTH GRUNT]
FROL: Oh-ho-ho! You have
awakened the beast now!
Knock, knock! Anybody home?
[BELLOWS]
[SNORTS]
[GRUNTS]
Ooh!
[STUMPS GROWL]
[LAUGHS COCKILY]
[GRUNTS]
[CHAINSAW BUZZES]
- [VILLAGERS CHEER]
- [LYNX ROARS]
[PANTS]
[GASPS]
[WHIMPERS]
- [CHATS SWEETLY]
- Hm.
[DOT GROWLS]
[AIR BUBBLES RUMBLE]
[BAR SCRAPES]
[WHINES]
[WHIMPERS]
[WHINES, BARKS]
- [YOWLS]
- [GROANS]
[GASPS] Am I glad to see you!
[GROANS]
Ooh!
[BREATHES WEAKLY]
Oh-oh-oh!
Huh? Oh!
- [VILLAGERS SHOUT]
- [GASPS]
- [BISON BELLOWS]
- [CHAINSAW BUZZES]
- [VILLAGERS SHOUT]
- [NYMPH HISSES]
[MOOSE BELLOWS]
[BOAR SNORTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Hm.
[DELICATE CHIMING]
[GROANS]
[TENDRILS CREAK]
[SIGHS]
[DELICATE CHIMING]
[GROANS]
[PANTS]
[SIGHS]
[ROARS]
So, that's where you're
hiding, you rotten old stump!
[LAUGHS]
[GRUNTS]
This is all my fault.
I have to stop this.
[DELICATE CHIMING]
Supreme Spirit,
the One Who Sits in the Rock,
I call on you!
No! Mavka, don't!
[THUNDER CRACKS]
[ETHEREAL MUSIC]
You have called me, Guardian.
I beg you, give me the
strength to answer my calling.
I need the Spark of Rage
to protect the forest.
The Spark of Rage has its price.
The price paid by
the previous guardian
was his enormous strength.
The rage burned him
out from the inside.
And you,
the Spark will
cost you your life.
You shall enter the
Nothingness for eternity.
I agree, for this
treacherous feeling here,
now it brings only pain.
As you wish, Guardian.
Ondina was right.
I was too nice.
- [SPARK ROARS]
- [GRUNTS, PANTS]
[THUNDER BOOMS]
[POWERFUL MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
[FLAMES ROAR]
- [TORNADO BOOMS]
- [VILLAGERS SCREAM]
Whoa! [GRUNTS]
[FLAMES CRACKLE]
- [CHAINSAW BUZZES]
- [FROL LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
I forgot to mention...
I've got you now, weed-face!
..I'm allergic to chainsaws!
- [GROWLS]
- [WAILS]
[LUCAS GRUNTS]
[FROL GRUNTS]
Hush, you alright?
Oh, Shmucas!
I'm fine. Got some yellow
spots, but, overall, fine.
- [FROL SHRIEKS]
- Huh?
[SHRIEKS]
[WAILS]
This village has the worst aura!
- [CHAINSAW BUZZES]
- [WARDROBE CRASHES]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
Hush, please, I
need to find Mavka!
What the hometown
hurricane is that?!
It seems that IS Mavka.
[POWERFUL MUSIC]
[VILLAGERS SCREAM]
Oh! [SCREAMS]
[PANTS]
[GROANS]
- [POLE CRACKS]
- Whoa!
[LUCAS AND HUSH PANT]
Mavka!
It's me, Lucas! I'm here!
Argh, I've got to get closer!
I might be able
to help with that.
[STORK CALLS]
Thank you, dear cousin.
Ha! They'll call me Hush,
who first befriended humans.
Uh... uh... Whoa!
- [BLEATS]
- Whoa!
Mavka! It's me!
Please! You have to stop!
Aah!
[GRUNTS]
Whoa! Aah! Oh!
- [GRUNTS]
- [STORK TRILLS]
- [BLEATS]
- Oh!
Where are you going?
You're gonna die!
I don't care. I
have to save her.
There's nothing you can do.
She can no longer understand
your words. Do you copy?
What did you say?
I said she can't
hear your words! Run!
Hush, you are a genius!
Finally I can scratch hearing
that off my bucket list!
She can't hear my
words, but what if...
[PLAYS MELODIC FOLK TUNE]
[GROANS]
[HOWLS]
I got it! I got it!
They need our help.
[VILLAGERS SING TO MUSIC]
We should all do this together!
[GASPS]
[DELICATE CHIMING]
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
[BLAST HOWLS]
[SOFT ETHEREAL MUSIC]
Mavka, it's me.
Hear me, please!
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
[MEOWS SADLY]
[SIGHS]
Come back to me. Please!
[SORROWFUL MUSIC]
[SINISTER MUSIC]
[THUNDER BOOMS]
MAVKA: Is this what
Nothingness feels like?
SUPREME SPIRIT: This is the
place of no phantom dreams,
where no songs are
carried by the wind.
The fire of hate and
rage does not burn here.
MAVKA: Rage doesn't burn
in my heart anymore.
I heard his voice and now I
know he never betrayed me.
SUPREME SPIRIT: You have chosen
to spare the lives of the humans
who have caused
you so much pain.
MAVKA: But they also
gave me something
I've never felt before.
SUPREME SPIRIT: We have
made the right choice
making you the new guardian.
You have bridged the
gap between the humans
and the forest-dwellers,
but now you have to
pay the promised price
and remain in the
Nothingness forever.
For eternity.
[SILENCE]
MAVKA: No.
I'm alive and I
will live on forever
because now my heart is full of
something that will never die.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
[ALL EXCLAIM]
Through the darkness,
I heard your music.
It filled me here.
Your music is the real magic.
No.
The only magic
humans have is love.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC]
[VILLAGERS AND FOREST-DWELLERS
EXCLAIM SOFTLY]
[GENTLE FOLK MUSIC]
Uh? [CHUCKLES GENTLY]
SONG: ♪ Sing me your
woodland ballad... ♪
- [CROAKS GLEEFULLY]
- [HOWLS, BARKS]
I think it's time
to end our feud.
Peace?
♪ And let there be
endless pride... ♪
- [TRILLS HAPPILY]
- [LAUGHS]
♪ Let the star
rise and shine... ♪
Peace, friend.
[VILLAGERS CHEER AND LAUGH]
♪ Be on my side
♪ Fly as the wind, my only dream
♪ Here's our home
♪ And here's our will
♪ Pure love, pure love
♪ Save us from the dark
♪ Only love, only love
♪ That keeps our souls alive
♪ So, let the dawn fires
♪ Keep burning
♪ Warming and lighting
♪ Our hearts
♪ And olden times
♪ Sacred knowing
♪ Lead us the way to a new start
♪ And olden times
♪ Sacred knowing
♪ Lead us the way to a new start
♪ Faith and fate now
♪ Be on my side
♪ Fly as a wind, my only dream
♪ Here's our home
♪ And here's our will
♪ Pure love, pure love
♪ Save us from the dark
♪ Only love, only love
♪ Fly as a wind, my only dream
♪ Here's our home
♪ And here's our will
♪ Pure love, pure love
♪ Save us from the dark
♪ Only love, only love
♪ Let there be endless pride
♪ Let the star rise and shine
♪ Faith and fate now
♪ Be on my side
♪ Fly as a wind, my only dream
♪ Here's our home
♪ And here's our will
♪ Pure love, pure love
♪ Save us from the dark
♪ Only love, only love
♪ That keeps our souls alive. ♪
I've found it! I've
finally found it!
[LAUGHS]
[DELICATE CHIMING]
[LAUGHS ROUGHLY]
It's finally mine! [WHEEZES]
Yes!
Mmm!
Take that, ravages of time!
Fresh and firm forev...
Huh? What? No! No! No!
[WAILS]
[GIGGLES]
[LAUGHS]
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]