No!
Mom.
This is stupid.
Look, four nights.
We get in, we pack,
we're out Monday.
We're four days away from
putting this whole place
behind us for good.
Besides...
Liz'll be there.
If you get sick of us,
at least you'll have
somebody your own age
to be moody with.
Great. Just great.
-Aden.
-What?!
Okay.
Aden, baby.
It's gonna be okay.
Can you go any faster?
It's not gonna
do us any good
if I drive off the road.
Everything's gonna be all right.
You're safe now.
Spread your legs.
Hey.
Hey, hey!
Hey!
Aden, no, don't
touch that. Don't touch that!
- Whoa, whoa.
- Don't touch that.
Really, Mom?
It's just a gift basket.
- Right.
- Come on.
People give stuff to folks
that are grieving.
All right, just-- Okay.
Just let me take care of it.
Get inside.
Aden?
Hey!
You ready for dinner?
Jesus, Mom.
- Fuck!
- Jesus, Aden, are you okay?
Just get out of here, just--
just leave me alone, please.
Okay. Just try
and take a deep breath.
All right, baby,
now name five things
you can see in the room, okay?
Um...
table.
Um, candle holder.
My dead fucking dad!
Hey, hey, hey! Baby, come here.
Good job.
Okay, breathe, breathe.
Hey, look at me. Look at me.
I'm not going anywhere, okay?
I'm right here, okay?
I'm sorry.
Hey, I'm not going anywhere.
I'm not going anywhere.
I remember this one.
This was really good.
- Hmm?
- Hey.
Can you--
can you make this tonight?
-Earth to Mom?
-Uh, yeah.
I think so.
Cool.
- Hello?
- Hey.
I think we took a wrong turn
at the tractor pool.
Can you meet us in town?
Of course.
I'll meet you at the diner.
Which diner?
There's only one.
Aden?
Yeah?
I'm headed into town.
Do you wanna come?
I'm good.
Okay, I'll bring back lunch.
Be safe.
Hey, Sarah.
Oh!
So, is cow-tipping
a favorite pastime around here?
Mama, you know you can't
actually tip a cow, right?
But we can tip our waitress.
What do you want,
daughter of mine?
The menu hasn't changed much.
I could probably
recommend something.
Yep. No more wobble.
-Hi.
- Where's Aden?
- Back at the house.
So you're getting crickets
and your daughter's eating ants?
Sour cream and onion crickets.
- Oh, my God, no!
- They're pretty good.
You're sick!
Fresh.
Really?
Well, I expected it
to be a little more farm-y.
-Oh, you got a little, uh--
-What?
Is it a tick?
Is it-- What is it?
Oh.
Hey.
Why don't you take
your stuff upstairs, guys,
and there's a picnic table
in the back
where we can eat,
and I will get us some wine.
Oh, did I forget to mention
there's no service?
Just a couple of days.
You'll be fine.
He sacrificed
everything for you
so you could become a man.
I know this has
been hard on you.
Hey, hey, hey!
What are you doing?
-Why are you talking to him?
-Oh, hello, Sarah--
No, no.
You don't get to talk to me.
- Sarah, I--
- Stop. You can't be here.
-He was just helping me--
-Aden!
- I only want--
- Now please leave!
- I only wanted to--
- Stop!
I asked you to leave.
Now get off my land.
You mean... his land?
Leave us alone.
And if I ever
see you here again--
-Mom!
-Aden, inside! Now.
It's all right, Aden.
We can talk later.
Shut your mouth.
You shut your mouth right now!
She told you to leave.
Who was that?
Aden?
Aden.
Talk to me.
He told me.
About Dad.
Your father...
Josef...
I thought he loved you.
I thought he loved me.
And I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
He wasn't a good person.
Am I?
Am I a good person?
Of course you are!
I'm hurting, doc.
- What do you got for me?
- No, uh-uh.
Your feelings are getting
nowhere near my notepad.
I would never.
Jordan, your wife is
as compassionate as always.
-Damn right.
-Mm-hmm.
Hey, so, uh, how's Aden doing?
I wish I knew.
I'm gonna go
get us some more wine.
Sarah, hold up.
We should really get to work.
Hey, I wouldn't
say no to more wine.
Wine she found in exchange
for days of cleaning.
- Babe.
- Hey, come on.
It feels like
I'm back in the Navy.
Liam, you were an officer.
The only thing
you had to keep clean
were those fancy rank boards
and your choker whites.
Well, can we, like,
go look for Aden or something?
He'll be back when he's ready.
Well, we all know
what boys like to do
in the woods.
- Gross.
- Yes, gross.
What? It's natural.
What's natural?
Mom, look at this.
One, two, three!
Oh, my God, it's coming,
it's coming, it's coming!
-Holy shit.
-We did it.
We got that down!
Hey.
Thanks for giving
my moms your room.
Yeah. Course.
Who was that old dude
you were talking to?
Uh...
he...
he was a friend of my dad's.
You mean like
one of the crazy ones
our parents think we can't
hear them talking about?
They're not crazy!
Okay, calm down.
I'm just saying
the adults talk like they are.
They were our family.
Really?
Yeah.
Hey.
Taking a break?
I've earned it.
Can I have one?
A break?
Or a drink?
-Just don't tell Aden.
-I think he knows you drink.
Not whiskey straight,
no, he does not.
Hmm. Our little secret.
So, Aden,
anything interesting
out in the woods?
I guess.
Like what?
Hmm. Well, there was a stream.
Um... oh, the ring of trees.
I don't know. Nature.
He's always loved being outside.
Yeah,
not where we live now.
Why not?
-Too good for city life?
-Liz!
It's just... dirty.
This place is dirty.
- Not when Dad was here.
- Aden.
What?
Come on. I wasn't that young
when we left.
I remember
how things used to be.
It sounds like your dad
ran a pretty tight ship.
Yeah, I mean, he did, but...
he always made time
to spend with the family.
I was the one
who kept our house.
Mom, I...
I better take care
of these dishes.
I can dry?
So.
Yeah?
Didn't see you at my party.
Party?
I didn't invite you.
I should have.
I'll make sure
you know about the next one.
Thanks.
I don't, um...
I'm not big on parties.
Why?
Well,
anyways,
it was a pretty lame party.
Awful, really.
Why?
There was a boy
I wanted to come,
but didn't.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Not you, stupid.
Yeah.
And moms came back early.
Kind of ruined the whole thing.
Not really selling
the whole party thing.
How about...
if I ever throw a party...
you can be the guest of honor.
All right, cool.
Maybe you could
have it out here.
Kind of pretty.
What the hell?
Do you have any idea
what fucking time it is?
Kill that fucking engine before
I get up there
and do it for you!
Come on, you crazy asshole!
You hick bastard!
You ought to see a real machine.
I got one out front!
Aden, Aden.
Wake up, wake up.
What the--
Whoa, whoa, what's going on?
You have to see this.
He really is an ape.
Yes, he is.
Hey, guys,
breakfast is gonna be ready
in just a-- Aden!
Put a shirt on!
Mom...
Oh, Liz, um,
would you like to help me, um,
come fix up some breakfast?
Sure.
This is a case
that has a lot of events,
but it's really
a crime of revenge.
-It all came...
-Hey.
-You're up early.
-I've been up for a while.
This one's your dad, yeah?
Do you wanna keep it?
I'm gonna go get a shirt.
Circumstances have
immediately indicated to us
that something else
was happening.
I'll have you know,
I make an amazing cup of coffee
and an even better Bloody Mary.
Just because
you put pickles in it
does not make it food.
No, no she's right.
Hey. So, last night.
Dinner was weird, right?
It's none of our business.
- Come on, she's our friend.
- Exactly.
So if she wanted
to talk about it,
she'd tell us.
We're just here
to help her clean her house.
They just really seem
to be having a hard time.
Yeah, I can't imagine
what a toll this must be
taking on their family.
Really digging
deep there, Rachel.
You know,
you don't have to be so...
clinical about this.
I have been perfectly
helpful this weekend.
Right, but you just
have to make sure
I know you're unhappy about it.
I could've come by myself.
I would never
let you do this alone.
But of course I'm not happy
about it. Why would I be?
It's a beautiful weekend that we
could be spending as a family,
and I'm stuck here with a sulky
daughter and a preoccupied wife.
And I have to watch Liam
puppy around after Sarah,
who doesn't have time in her
life for another damaged man.
It's-- it's--
-What?
-There's a man outside.
- Was it Liam?
- Is everyone okay?
We're fine.
Just take a break, babe.
And we'll finish up in here.
Whoa.
Aden, come look at this.
- Oh!
- Are those real?
I was wondering
where these went.
Is it-- is it locked?
- Oh-ho-ho-ho!
- Hell no.
Mama!
Aw, Jordan, come on. Be cool.
How 'bout we dust this off and
teach these kids how to shoot?
It'll be just like
gun call day on the ship.
And afterwards
I'll take 'em to town
and get rid of 'em
at the pawn shop.
All right. Okay.
You know, sometimes
you're actually pretty cool.
Sure. I'm teaching them,
but you're the cool one.
Always.
He's really good at... stapling.
May I?
After you.
She's a bit more
seasoned than I'm used to.
Shooting's just like
riding a bike.
Sights must be off,
or something.
Yeah. Sights are off.
You got this.
So, I'm on the paper.
Mm-hmm.
What?
You think you can do better?
Hey, hey, I didn't say that.
Come on, big shooter.
Let's see what you got.
That's weird.
Sights seem fine to me.
Don't say it.
-You shoot...
-Shut up!
-...just like an officer.
-Don't.
Oh, my God.
He never asked me
if I could shoot.
He's trying to bond with you.
Great.
I mean, he didn't do
a very good job,
but at least you'd know
who'd win in a fight.
Wanna see something cool?
Sure.
-Surprise!
-Maddy.
Can't I surprise
my big sister?
Of course you can.
Because you sure
surprised me by coming here.
It's complicated.
Seems pretty simple.
Explain it to me.
Sarah, have you seen Liz--
Oh, hello, Madelyn.
Hi, Rachel.
What is it?
It's old.
Duh. You found this place?
Years ago.
Before we left.
Does your mom
know about this?
I don't know. Is it safe?
Hmm.
Seems fine to me.
Come on. Don't be scared.
All right.
Madelyn. Nice of you to join us.
Eat shit, Liam.
How did you let this happen?
Me? She's your sister.
Yeah, don't I fucking know it.
Where the hell is Aden?
Why are you always
missing school?
I don't want
people to talk.
Nobody talks about you.
I won't tell anyone.
I see someone.
Like a shrink?
Kinda.
Wanna know a secret?
Sure.
I see one, too.
Why?
I hate it.
It makes me feel like there's...
something wrong with me.
Aden, that's not--
There's nothing wrong with you.
My dad
used to tell me a story.
That if you had a weakness...
a sin...
that you had to live with...
it wasn't always your fault.
It was separate from you.
And it could be removed...
if someone
would take it from you.
It might be willing,
but it didn't have to be.
It could be an animal,
it could be...
someone else.
You could give them your sin.
Somehow.
Give me my sin again.
Yeah, it's...
not quite Romeo and Juliet.
This...
sin eater...
would absolve you
of whatever you did.
Then they would be sacrificed...
protecting you
from your mistakes
in this world...
and the world to come.
Can I get
a pair of hands in here?
Can you grab me the paprika?
I thought you didn't want
anything to do with him.
-I don't, I just--
-Hmm?
Aden asked for one
of the meals in there.
So what?
Just leave it be, Maddy.
Frankly, Sarah, no.
I didn't help you
escape this place
just for you to come back.
Josef is gone...
and I know what I'm doing.
Sarah, do you remember
what you were like
when I took you in?
Yes, you never let me forget it.
Then why?
Why didn't you let me come?
-Everybody else is here--
-Because I didn't want
my little sister swooping in
to take care of me again.
I just don't understand.
Why are you here?
I need the money.
- I can lend you money.
- You don't--
you don't get it.
I know that
you think that you do,
but you don't know
what it was like.
Nobody knows what it was like.
Ah! I don't even know
what it was like.
I can't remember everything
and I just...
I just want to know
what happened to me here.
-Bad shit.
-Wow! Thanks, Maddy.
That's really helpful.
You have a child.
Stop acting like one.
Mom?
Is that Aunt Madelyn's car?
Aden!
Aunt Madelyn.
I thought you couldn't make it.
I pulled some strings at work
as soon as I found out
you guys were here.
I guess your mom just
couldn't wait to get started.
Aden, why don't you take
your aunt's bag upstairs?
She'll stay in my room.
-Why not?
-Lead the way, kiddo.
What was that?
So, did you get all those guns
from the basement pawned?
Yep, I did.
Oh, you didn't want to
take one home to practice?
No.
Does everybody have
something to drink?
Mm-hmm.
So, after dinner...
are we gonna take
a couple more loads out?
I was thinking
that we might have a fire.
I like it.
Great.
You deserve a break.
Lighten up, Madelyn.
Yeah, you just got here.
Whose fault is that?
Sarah, this is a lot of meat.
So, Aden.
Where'd you learn to shoot?
Oh, um, Dad used to
take me hunting.
Why?
Would have been good to know,
like when I said
we'd teach you how to shoot.
Yeah, great idea, by the way.
I didn't even touch one, Mom.
Yeah, Liam really
had a monopoly.
Hey, Mom, maybe he could show
you how to use that little
-pea shooter in your purse.
-Aden.
Actually,
maybe I should show you.
-Dude, you're really pushing it.
-You're not my dad.
Yeah. I wouldn't let you
behave this way.
My father was ten times
the man you are.
Yeah, was.
Sarah, I am so sorry.
Go apologize to my son.
-Sarah, I didn't mean to--
-Please.
Yeah, of course.
Excuse me.
Come out here
to insult my family some more?
- No, I'm sorry--
- No, you're not.
I just lost my temper.
No shit.
Can I be honest with you?
Yeah.
I don't need a new dad.
Every guy that comes around
and just sees us as these two...
broken things...
that they can protect...
and fix.
I don't need to be fixed.
Kid, I can't even fix myself.
And I'm not trying
to replace anyone.
Aden...
I really like your mom.
Can you give me a chance?
Why not?
Hello?
So imagine, okay,
she scared
the bejesus out of me.
So there's Liz, four years old,
crying her eyes out.
She's covered
in spaghetti sauce.
I mean,
just dripping with the stuff,
all because she wanted to try
making a pasta smoothie.
Mama.
We're still cleaning it up.
And that is why
we don't cook anymore.
It would be nice
to do a few meals at home.
to have a refill.
Nice. Real nice.
Moms of the year up in here.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Oh, my goodness.
Is all quiet
on the western front?
- We're facing south.
- Oh.
So, why aren't you at the fire?
You're not either.
I miss you, you know.
- What?
- You and your mom.
She shouldn't have
brought you here.
- It's fine.
- It's not.
I know you're putting on
this tough guy face,
but when your mom
was in recovery,
it was just you and me
for the whole year.
I know you, kiddo.
Mom...
she doesn't know
what she's doing.
She thinks that
getting rid of this place
is gonna fix everything.
But I know better.
Don't say that.
I care too much
about the both of you
to let you take this on alone.
I love you.
I know you do.
We're gonna
have to carry them in
when they're finally done.
I know.
You want some?
What?
Have some with me.
Well?
Okay.
I-- I never did this before.
You were gonna shoot a gun
and you don't know
how to shoot a bottle rocket?
I read the manual.
For the bottle rocket?
For the peashooter, stupid!
Do I need
to give you a safety glass?
No. Give me the lighter.
-Give me the lighter, please!
-No, no, no.
You hold the bottle.
Steady, steady.
All right,
don't point it at me.
- No.
- All right.
Is it gonna--
Wait.
- Oh!
- Hey, hey, hey.
Ooh! Ooh!
-Told you, you can't do it.
I should've never doubted you.
Damn right!
I have to get a refill.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, are you drunk?
Good night.
Shh, we're good.
Night.
Do they still want--
Oh, yeah, go for it.
Go for it.
- Come on.
- You sure?
Mm-hmm.
Shh.
-Oh, sexy!
-Yeah?
Oh, sorry.
No, no, it's okay.
This is what these freaks do.
They leave freaky baskets.
This is, like...
a shit-ton of food.
I don't care what they do.
As long as
they stay away from Aden.
Who? The freaks your husband
used to hang out with?
Ex-husband.
Sarah.
He was-- he was part of this,
like, intense religious group.
Like a cult?
Beyond that. It was like a...
a generational mini-society...
that you're born into.
And they live here?
I was so young.
And before I knew it...
we were married.
Then my whole life
just became, um...
family.
Family.
And everything else was, uh...
choked out.
And they were all
that I had left, so...
God.
Can you believe
I thought I was happy?
I'm so freaking stupid.
Hey, Sarah--
No, because if Aden
had never gotten sick--
Hey.
You did what you could.
You got out.
Then I came right back.
Hey!
What-- what are you doing?
Are you insane?
Are you?
They brought this, didn't they?
-Stop it, Maddy.
-No, stop it.
Hey!
When were you
gonna tell me about this?
It-- it's just some baskets.
Look, it's nothing threatening.
Sarah. What were you thinking?
I just-- it was an easy way
to keep everybody fed
this weekend.
I will go into town
and get us some fucking pizza.
Stupid bitch.
So fucking creepy.
One more day, babe.
Are you sure
you don't want to take him home?
At this point, I'm not sure
I want to take you home.
Look how cute he is.
I'll be back soon.
Hi, Officer.
Got you going
pretty fast back there, ma'am.
Yeah, I'm not from around here.
Hmm. I bet.
License
and registration, please.
Yeah, of course.
Ma'am, I'm gonna need
you to step out of your vehicle.
Wait, why?
Please! Help me!
You sons of bitches!
Anything?
It's voicemail again.
She said she was just going
to get some groceries.
Yeah, I know.
If it makes you feel any better,
I can go into town
and see if I can find her?
I mean, there's only one
grocery store, right?
Thank you.
Please tell me
Liam went to get food?
Who died?
It is getting late.
We need to feed these two.
I'll just order something.
No one will deliver out here.
Let my wife work her magic.
So, Mom, how'd you do it?
A magician
never reveals her secrets.
I'm gonna try calling again.
Don't worry, Mom.
They'll be back soon.
Yeah, definitely.
Let's get these kids
to bed, huh?
No, don't. Please!
Stop, stop, stop, stop it.
No, no, no, no, no
you don't have to do this,
please.
No, please.
-Shh!
-What are you doing?
-They're in the house.
-What?
Come on.
You need to get out of here.
What about my moms?
Liz, wait!
- What the hell is going on?
- Quiet.
-We gotta go. Now.
-No shit.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
This way, come on, come on.
Sarah?
Sarah? Sarah? Sarah!
Jordan, they're coming.
Mom!
There's no time!
Damn it.
I know you're in here.
I can hear you breathing.
Aden, Aden, stop.
- Aden!
- We have to keep moving.
What about my moms?
They'd want you to keep going.
-I can't leave them.
-You have to.
Hey, Liz, Liz,
look at me, look at me, Liz.
When did you have time
to put shoes on?
You're hurting me.
You better run!
Sarah. Sarah.
Thank God you're awake.
- Where's Aden?
- I don't know.
- What's going on?
I've been alone in here
for hours.
Aden?
-Aden?
-Sarah.
Nobody can hear us.
No, no, no, no.
This can't be happening.
I told you
not to come back here.
I just wanted my life back.
You had it.
You were free.
This whole
coming back here thing?
It's sick. You're sick.
I'm sorry.
You should be.
Where's your gun?
They took it.
-Where are we going?
-Not much further now.
What the--
- Shh!
- Aden.
Are you ready?
Hey.
Liz, look at me.
This is why we're here.
What are you talking about?
Liz.
This is my party, Liz.
And you're the guest of honor.
Aden, what are you doing?
Help me!
Help me, please.
Please, let me go.
Please, help me, please,
I just wanna go home.
Mom!
Why-- why are you doing this?
Please! Please stop!
Please! Please!
Why?
No, no, no.
Drink.
-No! No, please!
-You have been chosen.
The families
have gathered for you.
Are you prepared?
Yes.
Wait here.
What?
Your life will be better.
You have been chosen
to be one of the family.
The ritual can begin.
She has been chosen.
Chosen. Chosen.
-She has been chosen.
-She's been chosen.
Are you-- wait...
You are starting down the path
to become
one of our sisters.
Chosen.
She has been chosen.
She's been chosen.
You've been chosen.
We will prepare you
your first steps.
She's been chosen.
This is your path,
as it was ours.
The family will care for you.
She's been chosen.
You will come
to love and trust the family...
as we all have.
For the family.
Are you nervous,
young?
A little.
There's no reason to be.
Your time preparing
was well spent.
We've arranged everything.
Though, we were disappointed
to have a few
unforeseen ends to tie up.
I'm sorry, I--
didn't know
my aunt Madelyn was coming.
Or the girl.
Other arrangements have been
made for your guest of honor.
Aden.
Your father would be proud.
Young.
Your life
as a member of this family
resumes now.
Your mother tried to weaken you.
She did not succeed.
I will not fail the family.
Prove it.
Hey, big shooter.
Aden? What's going on?
I'm joining my true family now.
Aren't you glad
you could help me do that?
I saw you kiss her.
-Aden. You all right?
-Aden. Help us.
Aden, honey?
Aden, what the hell?
Hi, Mom.
I know you tried.
You've always wanted
what you thought
was best for me.
And for the longest time...
I was afraid I'd...
never be the man
Dad wanted me to be.
Who gives a shit about him?
She's your mother.
Stay out
of my family's business!
You show up uninvited to what?
Huh?
Steal me from my family again?
Aden, let us go.
You let us go or--
Please, please.
- Sarah! Sarah!
- No! Maddy!
Maddy! No!
Maddy! Maddy!
Family doesn't give up...
that easily, Mom.
Family doesn't run away.
Family also forgives...
Mom.
- Aden, no--
- Mom.
They're forgiving me for you.
For Dad.
And I couldn't have done it
without your help.
Thank you.
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, it's okay.
You brought me back.
You did everything you could.
Now...
Liz and I will pick up...
where you and Dad left off.
Aden, you can't. Aden.
Don't do that to that girl.
No, Aden, just look at yourself.
No.
Aden, Aden, Aden, Aden.
It's almost over.
-Let's go.
-Wait!
-We need to think about this.
-We can't wait.
What? Jordan, no! Wait.
Jordan, wait.
-Liz!
-Liz! Help!
Are you okay?
I'm fine, it's nothing.
Rachel.
What's wrong?
You just shouldn't have
revealed your secrets.
Don't.
Go save our daughter.
I love you.
I love you, too.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Aden. Where's Liz?
You fought very hard.
You could have escaped,
if you'd just left Liz alone.
She's my daughter!
Where is she?
-She's safe.
-What did you do to her?
She's part of
my family now.
Don't worry.
In all the generations
we farmed this land,
we've never had a poor harvest.
You're gonna make
an excellent hunt this year.
Your blood
will fertilize the lands
that feed your daughter.
A mother's place
is to sacrifice
for her children.
Don't you think?
We begin this year's ceremony
with a renewed sense of joy...
knowing that our family
will once again be complete.
Tonight, we restore our lost son
to his rightful place.
Our forefathers,
they knew that the sacrifice
of one's life for another
is the greatest show of devotion
that man can reach.
Thus, we've always
honored the tradition
of the.
On this night...
your father
gives his life for you.
Now...
honor your father's sacrifice.
Praise the family!
I present to you
our first sacrifice,
representing planting,
the first seed and hope.
May his blood
fertilize our lands.
For the planting!
After the planning...
the seed grows and is nourished
and the weeds...
that threaten
the sprouting plants...
must be ripped from the earth.
As the sacrifices
of our ancestors
cultivated this land...
so too will yours.
I remove this weed
that has choked our family.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
For the cultivation!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The harvest must be reaped.
The wheat separated
from the chaff.
For the harvest!
I'm not going anywhere.
The harvest ceremony
is complete.
We now join
Elder...
in welcoming his bride.
We celebrate their binding
as it strengthens
the future of our family.
You'll come to love it here.
I promise.
With your commitment
to the family...
and to our future...
I bind you
in love and protection
of the seven families.
I bless your thoughts.
May they be pure...
and wise.
I bless your bodies.
May they be strong
to serve the family.
Lastly, I bless your lips.
May only praise...
ever be uttered from them.
They have taken
the honored position
of service and marriage
to each other.
We, the family...
will support you and guide you
on your journey together.