[dramatic music]
[tense music]
- [Doctor] It's stage
four pancreatic cancer.
It's metastasized to your
liver and your kidneys.
You have a few options, but
it'll just prolong life.
- It's been pretty long already.
What are we talking?
- [Doctor] Four,
maybe five months.
- I feel fine.
- [Doctor] The pain will come.
- I'm used to pain.
[people chattering]
- [Man] Yo, Max!
- [Man] Max!
- So how'd it go?
- I've been worse.
- Well, you gonna get an
operation or something?
- Something.
- You need anything?
- I'm good.
- [Ezra] Mom.
- Yeah.
- This is not Frosted Flakes.
The cereal is literally
making my mouth burn.
- Okay, I get it,
the cereal sucks.
Here.
- Half?
- I'm sorry, babe.
We're gonna have to stretch
'em out, just for a little bit.
- [Ezra] We need
better insurance.
- Well, why don't you put
all your complaints on paper
and I will talk to management.
- Wait, ask Dad for the money.
- All right, I'll handle it.
That new hot water
heater didn't help,
but I got extra shifts this
week, so we'll be fine.
- Well, if I have a
seizure, it's your fault.
- What?
Hey, hey, hey.
Stop that, I don't like
that, that's not cool.
Go, go, go.
We're gonna be late.
[upbeat music]
- [Radio Announcer]
Excessive heat warning today,
Las Vegas expects
to see temperatures
into the 105 to 110 range.
Not only today,
but also tomorrow.
Pahrump Valley, 103 to 107
and Roseland, 110 to 117.
So this is just the beginning.
We do have a chance...
♪ Work it out, maybe
we can work it out ♪
- [Ezra] What's for my lunch?
- I made my famous peanut
butter and tiny bit of jelly.
But I made it with love.
- Mom.
- What?
- I'm not a baby anymore.
- You're my baby.
Your friends aren't
even looking.
- Those douchebags
are not my friends.
- Hey.
Go on, get outta
here, go be smart.
- Love you, Mom.
- Love you more.
- [Boy] Yo, dickwad!
- [Boy] Hey, twitcher!
- I'm so sorry, sir.
I'll get you one
without cilantro.
- [Customer] Hey,
waitress, excuse me.
- I'm gonna be
right with you guys.
Are you good for
drinks right now?
Your order's just-
- Okay, thanks.
- Okay, be right back.
I didn't forget you.
I'm getting your salsa.
- [Restaurant Worker] Maxine,
veggie tacos, table eight.
- And here's your extra cheddar.
No such thing as too
much cheese, right?
- Warden wants to see you.
- Now?
- No.
Christmas 2025.
Let's go, boss.
- Okay, I'm gonna
refresh your water.
- Hey, Maxie.
Hey, hey, hey, you got a second?
- What are you doing here?
- What?
- No how are you,
nice to see you?
You look great, babe.
- What do you want?
- I just need a sec, okay?
I wouldn't be bothering
you if it wasn't important.
- You want money?
Because I don't have any.
- Jesus Christ, no,
I don't need money.
I need to see my son.
- Okay, my manager
just got back, so go.
Go.
- Look, why do you
always do that?
You always make me
look like an asshole
in front of everybody.
Huh? I just need a sec.
- Everything okay, Maxine?
- Yeah, everything's fine.
I'm just trying to
talk to my wife.
- Sorry, he's just leaving.
- No, I am just leaving, Tom,
just as soon as my wife here-
- I'm not your wife.
- Do I need to call the police?
- No, no, no.
- Call the police?
What for, asshole?
- Okay, sir, I'm gonna
need you to leave.
- You need me to leave?
- What are you gonna do, huh?
- Stop it!
- What are you gonna do?
- Somebody call 911.
- Oh, call 911?
Oh, no, oh, no, Tom.
- Hey, hey, why
don't you just go?
You need to leave.
- Okay, no problems, Tom.
This is your fault.
- What the fuck
is wrong with you?
- I wanna see him.
- [Tom] What a fuckin' asshole.
- I know he is, I'm so sorry.
Tom, I'm so sorry.
- I gotta let you go.
Sorry.
- Oh, fuck.
- You have any family, Max?
- No.
- I know you have a daughter.
- Then why did you ask?
- You know, you've
done a lot in here
with helping these
guys get sober.
I mean, you've been pretty good.
I've already spoken
to the parole board.
Now, if your
daughter is willing,
you can live out the
remainder of your days
under house arrest.
Well, I can make this
happen pretty quick for you,
but your daughter's gonna
have to agree to it.
- Well, I haven't spoken to
my daughter in a long time.
We're blood, not family.
Not anymore, anyway.
[phone ringing]
- [Maxine] Hello?
- [Woman On Phone] Hi, this
is the principal's office.
We're gonna need you to
come pick up your son.
- Fuck.
- We have an issue.
- Okay, I'm on my way.
- He did have an altercation
with a few boys at lunch today.
- A few boys?
- Yeah.
The other boys have
been suspended,
but this will go
on Ezra's record,
and he will have detention
through next week.
- For what, getting beat up?
- Sorry, my son got attacked
and he's getting punished?
- I'm sorry, these
are the rules.
- Well, your rules suck.
You know he has epilepsy.
What if he'd had a seizure?
What would you do then?
Expel him.
- We can't make an exception
just for one student.
- Oh, this is such bullshit.
Now he's gonna have a mark
on his record for nothing.
- [Principal] We have a strict
policy against fighting.
- He wasn't fighting.
My son is an exceptional
student who has had
a really hard time
because his mother
has made some stupid mistakes.
Not him, me.
The rules state...
- Your head is rammed so far
up your bureaucratic ass,
you can't see you're
hurting an innocent kid?
- Is this really the
example that you want to set
in front of Ezra?
- Actually, yeah.
Yeah, it is.
Come on, let's go.
- That was kind of cool, Mom.
- [Maxine] You should
have walked away.
- What... I did.
- Well, you should've
walked faster.
- Well, are you mad at me?
I didn't do anything!
- No, but you could
have done something
to get yourself
outta that situation.
- Here you go.
- Okay, that's very thoughtful.
- You're welcome.
- Go to your room.
- I was planning on it.
- Wait, wait, wait.
[phone ringing]
Could you get that, please?
- Oh my God, up or
down, make up your mind.
Hello?
- Hello.
Is Maxine there?
- Wait, who is it?
- I don't know, they
called you Maxine.
- Hello?
- [Max] Hello.
Maxine?
- Yeah.
- [Max] It's Dad.
How you been?
Is that your boy?
- [Maxine] What do you want?
- [Max] Well, I just wanted
to see how you're doing.
- Bullshit, you want
something, what is it?
- I'm getting out soon.
- [Maxine] And I
give a shit because?
- Oh, maybe this was a bad idea.
- [Maxine] Yeah,
you got that right.
- Oh, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
- I'm sick, Maxie.
You there?
- Yeah.
You're sick.
So what?
- I don't have a
lot of time left.
And anyway, the warden
has made me an offer.
- Look, I don't have a lot
of time to play catch up,
so say what you wanna say.
- In the time I have
left, I would like
to spend it with you.
- Really?
- Well, the warden says
if you sign for me,
I could spend my last days with
you, outside of this place.
Compassionate release.
You still there?
- You have the nerve to
call me after 12 years
to tell me that you
wanna live with me?
- [Max] I just thought maybe...
- Well, you thought wrong.
Don't call here again.
- [Max] Okay, okay.
Don't hang up, please.
I'm sorry.
- I'd just like
to know one thing.
What's his name?
- Ezra.
- That's a good name.
I bet you're a
great mother, Maxie.
Maxie?
[insects chirping]
- All right, I'm going to work.
Call me if you need anything.
Feel weird or something, okay?
And no TV.
I'm serious.
- What?
- Especially that
Vegas crime show, okay?
I don't want you
watching that anymore.
- Why?
You afraid I'll see Dad?
- Kiddo.
I'll see you in the morning.
- I mean, it's the only way
I get to see him, right?
[upbeat music]
- Come on, Vic.
Let the lady do her job.
- How'd it go tonight?
- A mess.
New girl couldn't even
bevel 'cause of bunions
and then face planted.
- It happens, trust me.
I've had quite a
few crappy nights
on that same stage myself.
Hey, any extra shifts
I could pick up?
- Sorry, Maxie, not this week.
Hey.
Why don't you get that sexy
ass of yours on the pole?
Make yourself some
serious money.
- Why don't you get
your ass on a pole?
Get outta here.
[solemn music]
- Come on, Hammer.
I don't want those
fucking chemicals
flying around inside me.
- Oh, like you
haven't put anything
worse in your body than that?
- Yeah, okay.
- Hey, is it true?
- Yes.
I banged your sister.
- Yarek says he owes you.
Whatever you want.
- A new pancreas.
- Okay, I will ask him.
- I'm kidding.
Tell Yarek we're all good.
- He wants to make sure.
- Everything dies with me.
- Thank you.
[machine beeps] I'm
sorry, it's been declined.
- Well, could you try it again?
- Sure.
[machine beeps]
- Yeah, nothing, I'm sorry.
- Okay, well, how much is it?
- It's 171, please.
- Look, is there any way that
you could gimme some of it?
Like say 20 bucks worth?
It's for my son,
he has epilepsy.
- Yeah, you'd really
have to talk to
the pharmacist about that.
[guitars strumming]
- [Tyler] Maxie.
Look it.
Hey, listen to me.
That manager provoked me.
- Okay, thanks.
You got me fired.
I need money, Tyler.
- All right.
20.
That's all I got.
- You have money for some
bullshit band, but not our son?
- Well maybe if
you let me see him,
I might be a little
more generous.
- Here?
You're squatting with
a bunch of losers.
- It's an artist co-op.
- Oh, okay.
Get yourself cleaned
up and get a place
with a real bedroom
for Ezra, and then
maybe I'll think about it.
In the meantime, he's
out of medication.
- What medication?
- I give up.
- What?
- He's antiseizure medication.
For his epilepsy.
- I know.
Look, hey, hey, I got
a gig coming up, okay?
I can get you some cash then.
- A gig?
That's a joke, right?
- I'm trying, babe.
- Great job.
I smell Father of the Year.
[phone beeps]
[Maxine sighs]
[knocking on door]
- [Guard] Message
came in from Admin.
Call your daughter.
- Hi, I got your message.
- So that thing you asked me,
I'll do it on one condition.
You have money?
- I've got some.
- You pay me rent and you
cover all your own expenses.
Food, toilet paper, everything.
- Maxine, is everything okay?
- Do you want it or not?
Every month on time
for as long as...
- Sure.
- I already signed the papers,
so you can be released today.
- I appreciate this.
- Don't make me regret it.
- If you ever need me to
take care of anything,
your daughter,
whatever, when I'm out,
if I get out, I'll do it.
- I appreciate it.
Keep up with the steps.
- One day at a time.
I love you.
Don't ever tell
anyone said that.
- Watch your step.
- My God.
You're still so beautiful.
- I'm not interested
in making you
feel better before you die.
I need cash, that's
why I'm doing this.
You're a tenant.
That's it.
As far as Ezra's concerned,
you're my uncle or something.
You can't tell him
you're my father, okay?
You do that, you're out.
- Oh, come, Max.
- No, I am dead serious.
Don't test me on this.
- [officer] You have a 50
yard radius from the house.
You take it off or you
mess with it in any way,
it's gonna go off,
and we come get you,
which means you'll
be right back inside.
- I understand the
meaning of house arrest.
- If you have a
doctor's appointment,
we need to know in advance.
Don't make us come back here.
He's all yours.
[door closes]
- Been ages since
I've seen this place.
Hasn't changed much.
- Well, it's a dump,
filled with bad memories.
- Not all bad.
- How would you know?
You missed everything.
- I'm not that guy anymore.
- Okay.
If my ex didn't bury us
in debt, I'd sell it.
I'm upside down on it.
- How did that happen?
- I don't know.
Maybe since you were in
jail most of my life,
I didn't have anybody giving
me any fatherly advice.
I have to pick up Ezra.
You can take my room.
- I can't do that.
- Well, it's either
that or the couch,
and I'd like it if you spent
as much time outta sight
as possible, so.
I'll sleep in Ezra's room.
[Max groaning]
- [Max] Shit.
- How bad is it?
- It's fine.
Oh.
This is my gate money,
and whet I earned inside.
I'll have more soon.
- Okay, but I don't want
you bringing your past
in my house, and no
drinking or drugs.
- I havn't had a drink or
touched a drug in 12 years.
- Okay, I'll be back in an hour.
Try not to break the law.
[gentle music]
♪ It's a long, warm summer ♪
♪ A cruel way to live ♪
♪ All the lovers
walk hand in hand ♪
♪ All the world to give ♪
♪ All the days on my own ♪
♪ All the nights
I've spent crying ♪
♪ It's hard to say
if I'll ever escape ♪
♪ But man, I keep trying ♪
♪ I take note of
my shortcomings ♪
♪ It makes perfect sense ♪
♪ How a man ends up so alone ♪
♪ When he builds such a fence ♪
♪ All the days on my own ♪
♪ All the nights
I've spent crying ♪
♪ It's hard to say
if I'll ever escape ♪
♪ But man, I keep trying ♪
- [Ezra] Who's he again?
- He's kind of like my
uncle, but just not by blood.
- Confusing, but okay.
How come I've never
heard of him before?
- Because we're not that close.
Where are you going? Ezra.
- It's fine.
- He's probably sleeping.
- He isn't sleeping.
Are you hungry?
How come I've
never heard of you?
- Hey, don't be rude.
- I'm serious.
You've never mentioned
Uncle Max before.
- I've been away.
- Like where?
- Okay, ease up
on the questions.
Max is probably tired.
- How'd you get that black eye?
- Why don't you finish
your pizza in your room?
- I thought I'm not
allowed to eat in my room.
- Well, this is an exception.
- Mom, a little
consistency would be nice.
Nice to meet you, Max.
- You too, Ezra.
Smart kid.
- Too smart.
[door closes]
- I know you're mad at me.
- Okay, I'm not mad.
I'd have to give
a shit to be mad.
- Don't you want
to know anything?
- What happened?
- I know what happened.
You're a criminal.
You're violent.
And I know you got
paid to hurt people.
Max, if I wasn't so screwed,
you wouldn't be here, okay?
So just drop the
father-daughter bullshit.
It's not us.
I don't have room in my heart
to make you feel better.
I have to go to my night job.
Stay in your room.
[pensive music]
- There you go.
How's the cereal?
- It's really good.
- Less radioactive?
I'm happy.
- [Max] Morning.
- I have a question.
- For me?
- Mm-hmm.
What was my grandfather like?
- Ezra, Max just woke up.
- Your grandfather?
- Yeah.
He died before I was born.
Was he nice?
- I'd say he was nice.
Your grandfather had
his share of problems.
He did have a hard time
showing his feelings.
- All right.
Come on, we're gonna be late.
- Please, okay,
Mom, are you PMSing?
- Mister, you have
three seconds-
- I'm going, I'm going.
Mom says I remind
her of him sometimes.
The good parts.
That's why I asked.
- The good parts, huh?
- Yeah.
That he used to make her
laugh when she was a kid.
Okay, see you, Max.
- See ya.
- Used to make you laugh.
- Yeah, well, I had
to tell him something.
Look, I have to find a job
today, so eat what you want.
You can square up with me later.
- You must be exhausted.
- Hi, yeah, I'm
calling about the...
Administrative
assistant position.
I just, I can't see
where to email my resume.
- [Woman On Phone]
The job requires
at least two years of college.
- Minimum two years of college?
- [Woman On Phone] Just
send your transcripts.
- Yeah, of course.
- [Woman On Phone] Ready
to write this down?
- Sure.
- [Woman On Phone]
You got a pen?
- Yeah, I have a pen.
- M-A-T-T-I @CasinoCleaners.com
- Okay, thank you, I'll
email that right away.
- [Woman On Phone] Great.
[phone buttons beeping]
[phone ringing]
- Hey, babe.
- What?
- Get that, will ya?
- Hank's.
- Is Hank there?
- He's busy.
- Tell him it's
Max, he'll take it.
- Some guy called
Max on the phone?
- Am I dreaming?
- Another ball-buster, huh?
- Well, you tell me.
She's a pain in my ass,
but she's good to me.
How are you, my friend?
When'd you get out?
- I didn't really get out.
- You escaped, didn't you?
Holy shit!
- Don't get too excited.
- Max.
Come by.
- Listen.
I'm not doing so good.
- Yeah, well, we're
getting old, buddy.
- Look, that seed
money I gave you
100 years ago for the gym.
If you got it, I could use it.
- Shit, Max.
If I'd known sooner...
It's pretty bad right now.
Most of these fighters
are training for free.
Haven't had a
contender in a while.
- Say no more.
I just thought I'd ask.
- [Hank] I'm an asshole.
I should have been putting
something away, I know, but-
- I gave you that money.
You don't owe me shit.
- Max, if it wasn't for you-
- Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Save it, save it.
- I'll come by and
say a proper hello.
- Oh, I'm at the old house.
- [Hank] Okay, I'll see you.
[phone beeps]
- What's up, twitcher?
Probably deaf as well.
- Nope, I can hear you.
- Oh!
He speaks too.
- And you walk upright.
Amazing.
Evolution.
- Aren't you smart?
- A little, yeah.
It's too bad I can't
say the same about you.
- You want another beating?
- I have a feeling that's
a rhetorical question,
but the answer would be no.
[tense music]
- Oh.
Guess you don't have a big
mouth now, do you, twitcher?
[Max coughing]
[car approaching]
- Yarek?
[car door closes]
The infamous Max MacLeary.
Did you get Botox?
- Fuck you, lots of men get it.
- I told you, boy, we're good.
- Max, relax, I just
wanted to see you.
- You know, our
past dies with me.
I just wanna make that crystal.
- Of course.
Max, you could have
said a lot of things
to make your life
easier, but you didn't,
and that kind of loyalty,
that doesn't exist anymore,
so anything you
need, you just ask.
- Actually.
Your cousin still
do construction?
- Yeah.
Really, that's what you want?
All right, have a
crew here tomorrow,
make you a nice man cave.
Mirrors, bar, the whole thing.
- I have epilepsy.
- That some kind of superpower?
- Yeah.
They call me the Twitcher.
- Aren't you supposed
to be in school?
- That would be correct.
This kid wants to kill me.
- Did you know I was a boxer?
- I didn't even know you existed
until like a few days ago.
- Come on.
Is this the same kid
that beat you up?
- Same one.
He's hated me since
like first grade.
And then he pulled
a knife on me.
What would you do?
- What I would do and
what you should do
are two totally
different things.
- Seriously.
- You fight him.
- But he has a knife.
- Trust me, he won't use it.
How old is he?
- 12, and trust me.
Have you not seen
the news lately?
- Okay, okay.
Stand up.
Do me a favor,
get your hands up.
You always have to
protect yourself.
Chin down, hands up.
Yeah, like that.
And whenever the punch comes,
your fists take the brunt of it.
You might get clipped, but your
hands are always, always up.
That's good, good, good.
You got it, you
got it, you got it.
Good, good, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go.
Wow.
I think I need a popsicle.
- Shit, she's home.
- Oh, you came home early?
What happened?
Are you okay?
Did you have a...
- You can say it, Mom.
I didn't have a seizure.
Just my stomach was hurting.
- And what have you
guys been up to?
- Just talking.
- Okay, go wash
up before dinner.
You didn't say anything
to him, did you?
- No.
I'd like to, but since the
kid thinks I'm dead, you know.
- That's my fault?
- He was just showing me the
backyard, you know, the roses.
They must be, God, 30 years old.
I remember when your
mother planted it.
Yeah.
You know...
What are those?
- It's a Rice Krispy treat.
- Rice what?
- Krispies.
- Oh.
- Yeah, try one.
- No, I don't think so.
- You know Max was a boxer?
No, I mean, he was on the
phone and he was saying-
- Are you lying to me?
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
- It wasn't his fault.
We got to talking.
- Did he tell you he
was one of the top
amateur fighters in Nevada?
- He was?
No.
- Go to my room.
- Wait, am I grounded again?
- No, goofy boy, my room.
There's a photo
album, third drawer.
[Max sighs]
- Hey.
- I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah, it's
fine, I'm sorry.
He came home, and he
asks a lot of questions.
- I know, it's nonstop
with the questions.
He can't just sit
in silence, I guess.
- Oh, he'd make a good lawyer.
You know, you remember when
you wanted to be a lawyer?
Get me out of prison.
- I was seven.
- Oh yeah, but you were smart.
- Aww, look at the baby.
- [Ezra] My first recital.
- Wow.
Cher.
- Yeah.
- Oh, you danced at Caesars?
- Yeah, that was a
short tour because I got
pregnant with somebody
who's sitting on this couch.
[Ezra laughs]
- Oh.
- [Ezra] I haven't
seen this one before.
- Give it back.
- Did you know my grandma?
- A little.
- Mom never talks about her.
Mom never talks
about growing up.
- Because there's
nothing to talk about.
Here.
- When was this taken?
- I think I'm gonna
have to lie down.
[Max groaning]
- Are you okay?
Get my phone.
Ezra!
Call 911!
You're okay.
You're okay. [siren wailing]
- What's wrong with you?
- Max is sick, Ezra.
- Well yeah, I can see that.
Calling the ambulance
kind of gave it away.
- I have cancer, pal.
- Is he gonna die?
- I'll let your grandfather
explain his conditions.
- He's my uncle.
- [Paramedic] Sir, I
think we should take you
to the hospital to
get checked out.
- I'm dying.
Nothing's gonna change that.
- If you're
concerned about this,
we can just call
your parole officer.
- I am not going
to the hospital.
End of story.
Thank you.
Much appreciated.
- What is this?
- Oh, that, that's my new PS5.
- Seriously, what
the hell is going on?
Are you really dying?
- Yes, I am.
[solemn music]
- [Maxine] You do that?
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm feeling a bit better.
Figured I'd take advantage
of the good days.
I've been thinking.
Maybe I should go.
- No, no, no.
You don't have to do that.
- It's just, you
know, Ezra, you...
- Max, I heard you throwing
up in the bathroom.
So gross!
- Good morning.
There's my son.
- Give me a break, Mom, I'm 12.
I don't understand half the
stuff that comes outta my mouth.
- Yeah, I don't buy that.
Since the same kid corrected
my grammar on a school note.
- Who ends a sentence
with a dangling modifier?
It's pretty
straightforward stuff.
- Dangling what?
- No, no, no.
Don't ask, you'll
be here all day.
- Careful.
It's hot.
- [Ezra] Thank you.
- Okay.
So listen, I have
something to tell you.
- That Max is your father?
Which would make
him my grandfather,
who you told me was dead.
I'd say you have
something to tell me.
[pensive music]
I'm still trying to wrap
my head around all of this.
- [Maxine] You sure
you're an honor student?
'Cause I've explained
it like four times.
- Why did you lie to me?
- It's complicated.
- Can I use that
same excuse next time
you ask me if I'm lying?
- No chance.
- Is there anything
else I need to know?
Because if I ever do like
a 23andme at some point.
- Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Watch where you're
going, asshole!
- Dad!
- Ezra, stay in the car.
- Oh, hey, boy, you good?
- Yeah, I'm good!
- Ah.
Man.
- I've missed you.
- Come on, you're gonna be late.
- Mom, five minutes, please.
- Okay, you have until the bell.
- Oh my God.
Are you growing?
You're so tall.
Hey, Mr. Licorice.
Hey, hey, hey.
Check out what I found.
It's my old band's t-shirt,
man, isn't that sick?
- It's amazing.
- You want it?
- Yeah, it's awesome.
- You remember this, Maxine?
- Come on, let's go, it's time.
- [Ezra] It's fine.
- Hey, yo, I got you a
1964 Ludwig drum set.
It's all set up at my
house ready for you
to come and stay with me.
- Can I, Mom, please?
- Yeah, we'll see.
[bell ringing]
Okay, it's time go.
- I'll get the second bell.
Okay, when can I
stay at your place?
- [Maxine] Come on, you can
see your father another time.
- It's fine.
- Say goodbye.
- Mom, I haven't seen him.
- I'm gonna walk you in myself
if you don't go now, okay?
I'm not kidding.
I'll hold your hand.
- Yeah, she makes up the rules.
You know this, all right?
- Can't stop me from seeing him.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- I fought the law and...
- The Lord won.
- No, the law won, son.
I love you, buddy.
- Okay.
Bye.
- Go get in there, you genius.
- You can't show
up here like this.
- Relax.
Why do you always treat me
like an asshole all the time?
- Stop being an
asshole all the time.
A new drum set?
- What?
- You're high, Tyler.
All this bullshit pretending
you care about him,
it's not about him.
- I do care about him.
- Well, if you care,
then you'll get clean.
- You can't stop
me from seeing him.
- No?
Watch me.
I'm not putting him through
your bullshit again.
[engine starts]
- Max.
- Took you long enough.
- Between the broad and
these pussy-ass fighters.
- What the hell?
You lost like 40 pounds?
- 48, been sober five
years, eating oatmeal.
- Oh.
Well, I know the
world's going to hell
if you're eating oatmeal.
- Tell me about it.
Look, best I could do.
- I told you it was fine.
- Oh, that's bullshit.
I had to sell a few
things, but here it is.
I owe you, Max.
- I can't take this.
- Fuck you, take it.
If I can scrape together
some more, I will.
- Thanks.
- What's going on here?
- I called in a
favor from Yarek.
- Ah, that's a name
I could live without.
- Oh, we're square.
- Yeah.
Look, I gotta go,
teaching a boxing class
with some old white women.
I'm sorry about your, you know.
- We're all going to
die, Hank, even you.
- Oh yeah.
- No, not me.
Uh-uh, never me.
[both chuckling]
See you, Max.
- See ya.
- What the hell's going on?
I come home, there's
guys working.
What do you think you're doing?
- Oh, just fixing
up a few things.
- You should have asked me.
- I wanted to surprise you.
- Okay.
Well, I'm surprised.
- Hey, did I ever tell you
why we called you Maxine?
- Because you have a giant ego
and you really wanted a boy.
- No, no, it was your mother.
We were young.
We didn't know any better.
But she said you were a natural
born fighter from day one.
- Look how far that got me.
I asked you not to
bring your shit here.
- I'm not.
I promised your mother
years ago that I'd
finish that little
apartment, never did,
I'm doing it now so
you can rent it out.
- Oh, now you wanna keep
your promises to Mom?
You're unbelievable.
What's that?
- This is for you.
It's all I have to my
name, and it's yours.
- I don't want your dirty money.
- It's good money.
- Bullshit!
Knowing you, somebody
got hurt for that money.
- It's clean.
Stop being so
stubborn and take it.
I've also lined up a
job interview for you.
- You what?
- A job, a real job.
A friend of mine.
He's got a bunch of
businesses, I got you in.
- Why?
Why?
Because you're my kid.
It's the least I could do.
- Okay, stop.
- Oh, I'm a piece
of shit, I know.
- No, you don't
get off that easy.
Now you're trying to
take responsibility?
Now you wanna keep
your promises to Mom?
I had to sit in this
house and watch her
drink herself to death.
- Your mother had problems.
- Yeah, no shit
she had problems.
You didn't have to wake
up at three in the morning
to her screaming, lying on
the kitchen floor, here.
Right here.
Drunk off her ass,
knife in her hand.
She was cutting her arms.
She was too fucked up
to even kill herself.
And then when she saw me,
she started screaming,
"I hate you, I hate you.
You've ruined my life."
You didn't have
to deal with that.
I did.
I would wait for her to pass
out, drag her ass to bed,
clean up the blood,
and go to school hungry
because she'd spent
all her money on booze.
I had to deal with that.
And where were you?
I'll tell you.
You were off in Miami
doing some messed up shit,
or you were in prison.
Mostly in prison.
But I'll tell you
where you weren't.
You weren't here.
- Maxie, please.
- But I stayed right to the
end, because that's what you do.
So don't come in here now
like you're some kind of
fucking hero, 'cause you're not.
- You have every
reason to hate me.
I'm sorry.
I really, really don't
know what to say.
- Well, there's nothing to say.
- I fucked up, I know.
The shit I had to do
to protect you guys.
- [Maxine] Stop,
stop, I can't, please.
- Maxie, please.
I know, I know.
None of this will make up
for who I was or what I did.
I know that.
But you're my daughter, and
what I should have done then,
I didn't, and it kills me
every day that I didn't.
But please, Maxie.
Please.
I'm asking you.
I'm begging you.
Please, please, let me
be your father for once.
Please?
[Maxine crying]
Look, there's nothing
wrong with this money.
Nothing.
It's as clean as it'll get.
And it's yours.
Now you take it.
You could use it
for Ezra's college.
- He's not gonna be
anything like you.
Or his father.
Or me.
- You're not so bad.
- Hey, baby.
- I'm not your fucking baby.
[door slams]
- Will you tell me how many people
are coming to your birthday?
Because I have to
preorder the pizza.
- No idea.
- You want anything
special for your birthday?
- Yeah.
A set of balls.
I'm tired of being
picked on all the time.
You don't get it, Mom.
- What's to get?
You're letting a bunch
of idiots run your life.
- 'Cause they can run my life.
I mean, come on,
Mom, look at you.
Do you have a job?
- I had two jobs, smart mouth.
And I'm looking, so
drop the attitude.
- What, some minimum wage jobs?
What do you do, clean costumes,
work at Nachos Fully Loaded?
- I'm not gonna
apologize for that.
We have food on the table.
We have a roof over our heads.
- You're three months
behind on the mortgage.
I can read, Mom.
Really well, actually.
- Since you read
so well, read that.
What does that say, hmm?
That says all paid up.
- It actually just says "Paid."
- You're being a
little shit right now.
- I want to see my dad.
- I know.
I want that for you too, I do.
Your father made his choices.
- You kicked him out!
You never gave him a chance!
- I give him plenty of chances.
You have no idea.
He's not trustworthy.
I'm sorry, Ezra.
He's not careful with you.
He does bad things.
- Oh yeah, just
like your father?
No offense, Grandpa.
- None taken.
- Don't talk about your
grandfather like that.
- Why?
He literally just
got out of jail.
- Kid's got a point.
- Shut up.
- You're such a hypocrite!
- Hey, get back here, Ezra!
I do everything for that kid.
Everything.
Tyler doesn't do
shit, he never has.
Ezra like worships him.
- Let me talk to him.
[knocking on door]
- Go away!
Go away doesn't
mean open the door.
You're invading my privacy.
- Take a breath, kid.
Let me say something.
You want the kid version
or the man version?
- Don't care.
- All right.
All right.
I'll give you the kid version.
- Give me the man version.
- Your father, that
you love so much,
is a loser, plain and simple.
He's a drug addict who cares
about no one but himself.
If he cared for
you, he'd get clean,
give money to your
mother, come see you,
and stop banging whores.
- Wow.
- I know you love him.
He doesn't deserve your love.
Trust me.
I can write a book
on shitty fathers.
Your mother loves you.
- A little too much.
- Hmm, you should be so lucky.
She works hard for you.
- That kid from school
almost beat me up again.
- Oh, you look fine.
- I'm scared, Max.
I did call him a
dickhead, though.
- Let me guess.
You feel it here.
- Yeah, I'm shitting myself.
- When did you start
using those words?
- Honestly, ever
since you arrived.
- So you're scared.
Be scared.
- Then what?
- Then you fight 'em.
I'm gonna take you somewhere.
Show you how to really fight.
- I wish I met you sooner.
- Me too, kiddo.
Me too.
Listen.
I want you to
understand something
while you're still young.
If somebody offers you
something all bright and shiny,
and it seems too easy, it is.
Look what happened to me.
Go on.
Apologize to your mother.
She didn't deserve that.
[solemn music]
- [Maxine] Hey.
- You can't sleep on the floor.
Take your bed.
Hank had an extra futon.
- It's not even finished.
- Where I came from,
this is the Four Seasons.
I'm fine.
Plus Ezra snores.
- And farts.
Good night.
[muffled rock music]
♪ If you only love me
when I'm out of control ♪
♪ Easy come, easy go ♪
[muffled singing]
- Just don't be mad at me.
- [Maxine] [sighs] You okay?
- Yeah.
- I'm not gonna be mad.
I'm too tired to be mad.
Come on, show me.
What is that?
Let's watch it.
- No.
- Let's watch it.
Open it.
I'm not gonna be mad.
[muffled rock music]
I was at that show.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
He's pretty good.
- He's amazing.
He's so amazing.
- Okay, slow down.
- Can I ask you something?
- [Maxine] Uh-huh.
- Why did you fall
in love with him?
- It was really weird.
So I walked into this bar.
He was on the stage playing,
and I saw him and I just,
it was weird, I knew I
was gonna end up with him.
And then I met him after
and he was a total jackass,
but it was a done deal.
Plus that hair.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, Look at it.
And I was an idiot too, so.
- What's changed?
- Hey!
- I'm sorry.
I can't help it,
you make it easy.
- Oh, I got my room back.
So you're gonna have to
do without this idiot.
- Yay!
- Oh my God, okay, your armpits
smell like hamburgers again.
- Hamburgers are good.
You smell like cheese.
- Not anymore.
I was fired, remember?
Go to bed.
- Maxine?
- Uh-huh.
I mean, yeah, yes.
- This way.
We have three shifts, 24/7.
[machinery whirring]
We handle the laundry
for all the major hotels.
The Cosmo, Bellagio, Caesars.
It will be general
admin work at first,
but once you learn the business,
you'll move to payable
and receivables.
Starting salary's 42.5.
- Sorry, how much?
- I know it's not the greatest.
Your desk is right over there.
Health insurance as well.
I know you have a
boy, so I was told
we have to work
around your schedule.
- Sorry, I'm a little confused.
That's it?
I'm hired?
- You're in the door.
But it's up to you
to keep this job.
You screw up, it's on you.
You need to learn QuickTotals,
and you start next week.
Yeah, we're done.
- Thank you.
- You can go.
- Oh.
[pensive music]
- I told you, he's
a friend of mine.
I can't leave because
of this thing.
Trust me, he knows
what he's doing.
[horn honking]
- This the kid?
- Yeah.
My grandson.
- Ah, he looks pretty tough.
You sure he needs training?
- Wouldn't hurt.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Don't go easy on him.
- Do I ever go easy on 'em?
- Hey.
- Bye, Grandpa.
My name's Ezra.
- Good.
You need a name.
[hip hop music]
Yo, are you ready for this?
- Do I have a choice?
- Not really.
Keep punching.
Come on.
There you go, keep punching.
There you go.
Oh, come on.
Keep punching, there you go.
There you go, there you go.
Ho, there you go, ho, ho.
Come on, come on, keep punching.
Ha, ha, ha, come on.
There you go, there you go.
Punch it, come on.
- Just give me a sec.
- Don't stop, keep...
- You think this punk
ass gonna give you a sec?
- How is it gonna help me if
he has a knife on me, huh?
- Take that shit off.
Okay.
Here's what I want
you to do, all right?
You sure you got the
balls for this, kid?
Hmm?
You got the balls, huh?
- I think so.
- Either you do or you don't.
Now say it like you mean it.
- I fucking do!
- All right.
You didn't have to
swear, but okay.
Now listen, when you see
this punk ass, all right?
You gotta be a little
bit crazy 'cause people
are scared of crazy
folk, all right?
Walk right up to him,
grab him like this.
Is that funny?
Don't wince, don't wince.
- I thought you
were gonna hit me.
- I know, I know,
but don't wince.
Gotta keep your eyes
open, all right?
Okay, now.
It's your turn.
When I tell you to come
over, I want you to
grab me by my shirt
and punch right here.
Don't let go of my shirt, okay?
Be crazy!
Okay, now really
see this sucker.
Visualize him.
Okay kid, take his head off.
You go there, there
you go, keep punching.
Keep punching.
That's it, keep punching.
- Oh my God, sorry.
- Don't say sorry, okay?
I'm going to teach
you how to box.
But now you got to be a fighter.
- See you in the morning.
Hey, what happened here?
- It was just, Max was
teaching me how to shave.
- It's a little
early for that, no?
- It's cool, Mom,
it's guy stuff.
[Max groaning]
- [Maxine] I could call in sick.
- He's not gonna
die tonight, Mom.
- I know, I just...
Thanks for today.
- When do you start?
- Next week.
I got a lot to learn.
- What's up?
- Oh, your mom
got a new day job.
Through a friend of Max.
A desk job.
- Nice, Mom.
- Yeah.
Are you sure?
- [Both] Go.
- You know lying
is wrong, right?
- I'm not the one with
the ankle monitor.
- Point taken.
- I'm not five, you
don't have to tuck me in.
- I missed the last 12 years.
Can I do some
catching up, please?
- Can we just watch one episode
of "Vegas Crime Zone?"
- Your mother said no TV.
- She also said no fighting.
You know, "break the cycle
of violence" and all that.
Didn't stop you from
teaching me, did it?
- She actually say
"cycle of violence?"
- Please, just one episode?
- All right.
Just the one.
Let me use the can first.
[indistinct chattering on TV]
[urine trickling]
[Max breathing heavily]
[toilet flushing]
- [Man On TV] This
is the police.
Come out with your hands up.
[indistinct chattering
on police radio]
- Why did you go to jail?
- Wow.
You go straight for the jugular.
- What, you're gonna die soon.
I'm sorry.
I look smart, but
really I'm not.
- Don't worry about
it, it's all good.
So, you wanna know
why I went to prison.
Which time?
- Wait, how many times
did you go to prison?
- More than I care to remember.
- Wow, okay.
Well, let's start
with the last time.
And give me the man version.
- I told you I was a boxer.
Instead of fighting
to my potential,
being the best I could be...
I took shortcuts.
- What kind of shortcuts?
- I made it easy for people
to beat me for money.
You understand?
- You cheated.
Well, what's that gotta
do with you going to jail?
- Give me a sec, I'm
working up to it.
You know, I didn't
have much education.
The skills that I had,
well, you couldn't
put it on a resume.
- You beat people
up for a living.
- I worked for a
couple of bad guys,
and when things didn't
go their way in business,
they sent me to negotiate.
Which is why I went to jail.
- You spent the last 12 years
in jail for negotiating.
Yeah, that's not
the man version.
- Well, that's the only
version you're getting.
There are some things you
don't ever need to know.
I wish I could
forget them myself.
- You killed
someone, didn't you?
You know what, it's fine.
I don't wanna know.
You know, I saw my
dad on this show once.
- Sounds about right.
[pensive music]
- Fucking QuickTotals.
Yes!
[Max groans]
Are you okay?
- Not so good today.
- Ez, breakfast.
Listen, I was thinking, maybe
you should consider treatment.
That might give
us some more time.
- Yeah, well, I don't
deserve any longer.
- Okay.
You might not, but we do.
You think about it?
- Ah, fuck it.
You know it's
gonna be 107 today?
When did you last go swimming?
- God, I don't remember.
- Yeah, well,
Yarek's out of town
and said we we could
use his pool today.
Let's go.
- Now?
- Yeah, yeah.
All of us.
Ezra, you, me,
let's have some fun!
Hey, morning, slugger.
What do you say?
- Hey, kiddo.
We're not going to school today.
Really?
- Yeah, it's too hot.
We're going swimming.
- Okay, this would
qualify as a bad example,
but I think you're awesome, Mom.
Okay, I'm gonna get dressed.
- You were gonna fight
him today, weren't you?
There's always tomorrow.
- That's what I'm afraid of.
[bangs table]
- Let's go.
Go, go, go!
[cheerful music]
♪ Every day I wake
up and wonder why ♪
♪ I'm alone when I
know I'm a lovely guy ♪
♪ Birds come down
from the sky so blue ♪
♪ See all the beautiful
things you do ♪
- What'd you tell the cops?
- I told them I was sick and
had to go to the doctor's.
We have at least three hours.
- Lesson number two for the day.
How to evade the cops.
- Go!
♪ Pray to God that one day ♪
♪ I can be your man ♪
♪ Birds come down
from the sky so blue ♪
♪ See all the beautiful
things you do ♪
♪ Why can't I just get with ♪
♪ You'd be my only
friend in the world ♪
♪ Or you could just be my girl ♪
[woman speaking
foreign language]
- Time to go, kids.
- I thought we had
permission to be here.
- Yarek, yes, his
wife, not so much.
- Oh my God.
- Go, let's go.
- Go honey.
Oh my God, what time is it?
- Oh, shit!
Oh, God.
[indistinct chattering
on police radio]
- It's not his fault.
We had a flat, we
tried to call you.
- I'm sorry, ma'am.
We have to take him in.
- Maxie.
- No, no, no, no.
- It's okay.
- What's happening?
[phone ringing] Is
it gonna be okay?
- Yes, yes.
- [Man On Phone]
Correctional Institute.
- Hello, this is
Maxine MacLeary.
- [Man On Phone]
How can I help you?
- Hi.
Yeah, I need to speak
to the warden, please.
- [Man On Phone]
One minute, please.
- [Warden] Maxine, I have
already heard about it.
Now put the officer
on the phone.
- Could you just
talk to him, please?
I have him on the
phone right now.
- Hello?
- [Warden] Put him on the phone.
- Yes, sir, here he is.
- Hello?
- [Warden] Max, you got yourself
in quite a situation there.
- A little bit, but
I'm not gonna lie.
It was kind of worth it.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, this is the first
and the last time.
I don't have any more
strings to pull for you, Max.
- Right, right.
Thank you.
- Put the officer
back on the phone.
- Hello?
- Let him go.
- [Officer] Yes, sir.
I got it.
[pensive music]
- [Maxine] Oh, thank you.
Thank you, thank you so much.
- Wish me luck.
- Luck.
Wow.
- I'm scared.
It's my first day.
- Luck.
You got this, Mom.
[bell ringing]
♪ It goes around, goes
around, goes around ♪
♪ If you only love me
when I'm out of control ♪
♪ Easy come ♪
♪ Easy go ♪
- Told you it wasn't over.
[Ezra grunting]
- Fight him!
Take him down!
Fight!
- Kick his ass, Ezra!
- [Kids] Fight,
fight, fight, fight!
- Get outta the way.
- All right, that's
enough, Ezra.
Get off of him, that is enough.
Break it up, break it up.
- No, no!
[people chattering]
- Why don't you guys like me?
Can we just call
it here, right now?
- Oh shit, I'm dead.
- Really?
- It's my first day.
I'm not losing my
job just because
you are letting some stupid
little assholes ruin your life.
You do that?
Both of them?
- Yeah.
- How does it feel, you little-
- No, Mon, we're good.
- Back again.
Right this way.
- Did Ezra's mom just
call us assholes?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Slow down.
Put that on.
- Just don't be
mad at him, okay?
If it wasn't for
Max, I'd probably
spend the rest of my
life running for cover.
- Violence doesn't
solve anything.
- Well, I think today
proved that wrong.
Okay, I hear you.
And I hated it, to be honest.
I never wanna do it again.
- Okay, but you're
still grounded.
And what kind of parent would
I be if I didn't ground you?
- After my birthday party?
You know- - Okay.
- I have friends coming.
- Oh, you do?
- And a girl.
- A girl, tell me.
- Okay.
- It's ready.
[gentle music]
Keep your eyes closed.
- Oh, I can't see a thing.
- That's the point, okay?
In you come.
Okay.
Now...
Open.
Yeah.
You know, I called
in a lot of favors
over 20 years for
this, best I could do.
- [Ezra] This is sick!
- Yeah, yeah.
You could get a great
rent for this, you know.
I would say, well,
at least a grand.
- My God.
[phone ringing]
- I'll get it.
- Grandpa, it's amazing.
Thanks.
- Hey, hey, put that ice
pack back on your hand.
- Oh, don't be mad at him.
- I hate to admit it,
but I'm proud of him.
- Yeah, I knocked him down.
- [Tyler] What?
You knocked him down?
That's awesome, kiddo.
- [Ezra] Max is showing
me how to fight.
- Max?
Who's Max?
- He's just my grandpa.
Okay, wait, are you
gonna come on Saturday?
It's my birthday party.
- What, you mean
your mom's dad, Max?
- Yeah, he's been
living with us.
Wait, Mom's coming.
Okay, just try to come to my
birthday party on Saturday.
Okay, bye.
- [Maxine] Who was that?
- It was Dad, okay, but
Mom, before you freak out-
- Did you tell him
about Saturday?
- I'm not gonna lie.
Okay, I was gonna lie,
but I did tell him, yes.
- Okay, next time
your father calls,
just give me the damn phone.
- I wanna see him, Mom.
He's my dad.
- I've got to get
rid of that landline.
- Maybe you should
think about it.
- Oh, don't you start.
- Well, it's just,
Ezra's a big boy.
Try to make it work, that's all.
[drum beating]
- Big Daddy Bulldog's
in town, huh?
You think that's a good idea?
- Actually, it's the best
thing that's happened to us
in a long time.
Do you think you can stop
using for your son's birthday?
- Maxie, I got it under control.
- Okay, stop, stop.
Can we just be
real for a second?
You're an addict, Tyler.
- Do you think I
want to be this way?
- This is about Ezra,
and he's gonna hate me
if I don't let him see you.
- What do you
think's gonna happen?
Huh?
Just let me teach him how
to play the drums, huh?
It's the one goddamn
thing I'm good at.
It's the one thing.
- I know.
Just stop using
for one day, okay?
That's all I'm asking.
[cheerful music] [kids
laughing and chattering]
- Oh, wow.
- Hey, Grandpa.
I was telling them
how you used to
beat people up for a living.
You went to prison.
- Somebody actually paid
you to beat people up?
How much?
- What are you, a cop?
- [Maxine] Okay,
who wants pizza?
- Oh my gosh.
- [Maxine] Oh, oh.
- You don't have to
touch every slice.
- I'm gonna lie down for a bit.
Call me when it's cake.
- Okay.
- Is Grandpa okay?
- Yeah, he just
wants to lay down.
Happy birthday, baby.
- Hey!
- Dad!
- Bottom of the ninth,
here comes raw daddy-oh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, happy birthday, man.
We got beer.
Look at that
baseball glove, huh?
That's real leather, man.
- [Ezra] Okay, thanks, Dad.
- What, okay,
"okay, thanks, Dad."
How you doing, Maxie, huh?
- Can we speak for a second?
- Hey, hey, buddy Mommy
and Daddy need to talk.
- Okay.
- I asked you for one thing.
You're not clean.
- Look, I'm trying to be
a part of my kid's life.
Isn't that a good thing?
- No, you've gotta go.
- No, no, whoa, hey, wait.
Will you quit breaking my balls?
All right?
I'm hanging with Ezra.
It's the birthday party.
Oh shit, yo, whoa,
whoa, we got pepperoni.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Whoa.
Oh.
- I got it.
- No, no, I got it, I got it.
I got it, I got it, chill,
chill, chill, chill.
Bro, I got it.
- I got it.
- No, that's what
the ground's for.
- [Maxine] It's fine.
- Come on, no party foul.
No way.
See?
- Dad, stop.
- Mm.
Oh, come on, what?
Come on, man, you want
me to stay, don't you?
Come on, tell your mom
you want me to stay.
- I do, but you're not...
You just knocked
over everything.
- It was an accident.
Was she brainwashing you, man?
Did you tell my kid
I'm the bad guy?
- It's fine.
- No, I'm his father!
- I'm his father!
- Stay, okay?
It's fine.
Stay here.
- You're fuckin-A
right I'm staying.
It's a party.
Fucking-A, right.
I'm staying, I'm
fucking staying,
we're gonna have a party.
- Okay, kids.
Why don't we go
into the front yard.
- Come on, let's celebrate.
Hey, hey.
Gimme a beer.
Where's the candles?
Bring the cake!
Don't be a fucking bitch!
I'm trying to have a good
fucking time, are you?
- Maxie, everything okay?
- [laughs] Great.
Oh, look who just decided
to show up and play daddy-o.
- Well, you know
about that, don't you?
- Max, please, go inside.
We're fine.
- Yeah, yeah.
You better get your
old ass back inside.
Hmm?
- Look, you can see
Ezra another time.
- Oh, now you're
trying to tell me
when I can and can't
see my son, is that it?
What are you gonna do
about it, tough guy?
Huh?
- Look at him.
He's embarrassed.
Be smart for once in
your fucking life.
- You better get your ass back
inside before you get hurt.
- I'm gonna ask
you one last time.
- Or what?
- Tyler, you know
me, you know I'm not
a fucking around kind of guy.
[Tyler chuckling]
[Tyler grunts]
- Tyler!
[Tyler grunting]
Dad!
Stop it!
Ezra!
[Ezra gasping]
[tense music]
It's okay.
[Tyler groaning]
Get away from him!
All of you!
Go!
It's okay, baby.
It's okay.
I got you.
[soft keyboard music]
[Maxine sighs]
- Was that a birthday party
or was that a birthday party?
- Jesus Christ.
This fucking family.
[both laughing]
- I get it, Mom.
Dad's a drug addict.
And a very angry
man, by the way.
- I don't know how you do it.
You are an amazing kid.
- How do you think?
It's you.
[gentle music]
How's Grandpa?
- I don't know.
I should go check.
- I love you, Mom.
- I love you more.
- [Max] Ezra okay?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry, Maxie.
I lost it.
- Yeah, story of your life.
- He'll hurt that boy one day.
You too.
- That doesn't
give you the right
to beat the shit out of
him right in front of Ezra.
- I behaved like a pig.
You deserve better.
- Does the pig need a lift
to his appointment tomorrow?
- No, no, no, Hank's got me.
Maxie.
I just want to
thank you for this.
For all of it.
[solemn music]
- [Doctor] Max, let's talk.
- You were right about the pain.
What do you think?
Too late for treatment?
- [Doctor] Normally,
I'd say yes,
but you're a tough
son of a bitch.
- What kind of time
am I looking at?
- [Doctor] It's hard to say.
Maybe an extra month.
Why don't you think
about it, Max?
At least let me write you a
prescription for the pain.
[knocking on door]
- Get that, would you?
- [Ezra] I'm brushing my teeth!
- Is there any chance we
won't be late one day?
- [Ezra] Probably not.
- What are you gonna do, Maxie?
- Stop it, Tyler!
Stop!
- Let me in.
Let me fucking in!
- Do me a favor.
When I'm gone...
- You're not gone yet.
- When I'm gone, pop in from
time to time, check up on them.
Maybe hire Ezra part-time.
- Okay.
- How bad was I?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, how bad was I?
The truth.
My head's so fogged up, I don't
know up from down anymore.
So.
- You were bad, Max.
Ain't nobody around to
tell how bad you were.
I'm sorry, but you
wanted the truth.
[engine starts]
[baby crying] [dogs barking]
- Maxie?
Ezra?
Maxie?
- [Maxie] Tyler,
you're scaring him.
- You guys home?
- [Tyler] If you weren't
such a selfish bitch!
- Jesus.
- [Maxine] Tyler, think
about what you're doing.
- Maxie?
Maxie?
- Tyler!
[tires squealing]
- Maxie.
- Tyler, please pick up.
I promise I won't call the
cops, just bring Ezra back.
- Maxie.
Where's Ezra?
Oh, jeez.
- I tried to fight him off.
- This is my fault.
And I promise you, I
promise you, I will never,
never let that piece
of shit harm you again.
Wait here.
- I just want him back.
Please, that's it.
- When I send him out, drive.
You hear me?
Don't look back.
Don't think, just drive.
Give that kid the
life he deserves.
- I love you, Dad.
- I love you too, Maxie.
Never stopped.
[tense music]
- We're gonna go camping, it's
gonna be fucking great, man.
It's gonna be me and you, bro.
We're gonna be going down there.
Gonna go down to
fucking Tijuana,
gonna be getting
some fucking ladies.
Me and you, man.
- Where is he?!
- Where's who?
- Listen to me, you cunt!
Where the fuck is he?!
- Grandpa!
- Don't you fucking touch him!
- Ezra.
What are you doing?
I'm your dad, not him.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Get over here!
- Go.
Your mother's waiting for you.
Just go.
- Promise me you won't hurt him.
- I promise.
- Get back!
[men grunting]
[Tyler] Ezra!
- Come on, baby!
Are you okay?
Did he hurt you?
- I'm fine, Mom, I'm fine.
[tense music]
- You're a joke!
[men grunting]
- You come into my
house, you take my boy!
- And what are you gonna do
about it, tough guy, huh?
[Tyler groaning]
Here.
[bat clatters]
Pick it up, dickhead!
[men grunting]
Come on.
Show me your fucking face!
Bye!
[Max grunting]
Fuck you.
Get the fuck back.
[sirens wailing]
[pensive music]
[solemn music]
- My father wasn't
the greatest guy.
He wasn't the greatest
father, either.
We all know what he did.
Maybe life never
gave him a chance.
Maybe he didn't want it.
I don't know.
But what I do know is I
look out at all these faces
I remember from
when I was a kid.
So he must have done some
good, 'cause you're all here.
I'm not gonna make
excuses for him
now that he's gone, and
he wouldn't want that.
This one time I was,
I was really young,
like eight or nine, and we
were visiting him in prison.
I spent a lot of time there.
And this guard, he pointed
me out to another guard
and he said, "that's her?"
They knew my dad.
Who didn't?
And this guard said,
I'll never forget it.
He said, "that's his daughter?"
And it was so weird, because...
It was like a guy
that bad, that mean,
could possibly be my father.
And then they brought Max out.
And he lit up like a kid on
Christmas when he saw me.
He always did.
And yeah, I'm his daughter.
Proud of it.
♪ Did you hear the one
about the shotgun clown ♪
♪ He left his heart at
the lost and found ♪
♪ Some say the day
that he skipped down ♪
♪ Was when the whole wide
world turned upside down ♪
♪ The whole wide world
turned upside down ♪
♪ Now you don't
want to wake up ♪
♪ Take off the makeup ♪
♪ When that shadow you've
been running from ♪
♪ Keeps chasing you around ♪
♪ You don't wanna wake up ♪
♪ Heaven forsake ya ♪
♪ You're shaking when
you find the strength ♪
♪ To put your shotgun down ♪
- Ezra, my paddles.
- Okay, got it.
♪ It's a shotgun clown ♪
- Thanks.
♪ Have you ever seen
a fella disappear ♪
♪ When the cloudy eyes
seem crystal clear ♪
♪ 15 minutes served
in 50 years ♪
♪ We all fall down, but
he stayed down there ♪
♪ All fall down, but he ♪
♪ Now you don't
want to wake up ♪
♪ Take off the makeup ♪
♪ When that circus you've
been running from ♪
♪ Keeps chasing you around ♪
♪ You don't want to wake up ♪
♪ Heaven forsake ya ♪
♪ You're shaking when
you find the strength ♪
♪ To put your shotgun down ♪
♪ It's a shotgun clown ♪
[woman vocalizing]
♪ You don't wanna wake up ♪
♪ Take off the makeup ♪
♪ When that circus you
been running from ♪
♪ Keeps chasing you around ♪
♪ You don't wanna wake up ♪
♪ Heaven forsake ya ♪
♪ You're shaking when
you find the strength ♪
♪ To put your shotgun down ♪
♪ It's a shotgun clown ♪
[people vocalizing]
[pensive music]