Please, let me go.
No!
I don't think so.
It's such a beautiful,
beautiful day, Mia.
You know, it reminds me
of the day you were born.
The flowers are blooming.
The birds are singing.
The sky is so perfect and clear and blue.
It's so peaceful and quiet.
There is so much hope
for better days ahead.
Shut up, mother!
That's it.
I have had it with you,
you ungrateful little brat!
I have done everything for you
and this is how you treat me?
How bout I shoot you right now?
What are your last words, mom?
All right, all right,
everybody calm down.
Take a deep breath, Mia.
If you shoot me, I shoot her.
So stay out of it.
This is none of your
business, Detective Asshole!
It's Detective Ross.
Only my ex and my daughter get
to call me Detective Asshole.
Now Mia,
I want you to move your gun
and point it towards me.
Don't worry, she's not
gonna shoot me or anyone else.
She hasn't followed through with anything
a day in her damn life.
You see what she's doing?
She's begging me to shoot her!
Alice, you're not
helping here, all right?
Mia, focus.
I want you to move your gun over here.
Mom's not going anywhere.
We're gonna talk this out.
No!
That's it, that's it.
I have had it with you, Mia!
I have done everything for
you and you're so ungrateful.
You ungrateful little brat!
Alice, just shut up!
I'm gonna shoot, I mean it!
No!
- Oh my God.
- I'm so sorry.
Oh my, oh my God, baby.
Oh my God, mom.
- I love you so much.
- I'm so sorry.
You could have been killed.
That man could have killed my baby.
- I'm sorry.
- My baby's alive.
Oh my God, oh my God.
I'm so happy you're still alive.
You almost killed my daughter.
You monster, how could you shoot her?
I shot her gun.
You're alive, she's fine.
I hope your daughter
doesn't get treated like this.
Come on, please, I need a signal.
Oh no.
Not here, not now, no.
Oh, come on, come on, come on.
Pick up, pick up.
Daddy, I messed up.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have come here, it's so shady.
But it's worse than that, I'm in trouble.
They're coming from me.
They can smell the blood.
They're going to-
Where do you think you were going, Faye?
No, please, let me go.
Who do you talk to?
No one.
Please, why won't you let me go?
Dr. Pavor has big plans.
Let's go, let's go.
No, no.
Please don't take me
back to Dr. Pavor, no!
Dr. Pavor, do you want to
know what happened to Faye?
Is she still alive?
Yes, but you should
have seen what I did.
Not now.
Can you see that I'm busy here?
Last chance to change your mind.
Cheap surgery across the
border is never a good idea.
I've heard the place
has some decent reviews.
Heard it from who?
Doesn't matter.
We got a week off our classes
and just enough money to pull this off.
We're doing this.
And you really think
Bobby's gonna believe
you suddenly went from a
B cup to a D in a week?
Yes.
Bobby believes everything that I say.
I mean, he's really sweet,
but let's be honest, he's kind of dumb.
Which by the way, is
what I like about him.
Okay guys, we're doing this.
Like what's the worst that could happen?
Are we supposed to have this much blood?
Oh, the surgery was a success.
You two clean up.
Mm.
What are you doing, Anna?
Are you crazy?
Crazy, what do you mean?
It says we're supposed
to drive for four hours
where no one lives,
then hit a small town near the border
where we meet in a bookstore.
That doesn't sound sketchy to any of you?
Madison, just get in the car.
Come on.
Well, at
least the drive is scenic.
I'm gonna be
scenic after my surgery.
Was that a joke, Skylar?
You don't usually joke
when driving a long ways.
I'm happy, is that crazy?
You're happy?
Can I drive your car then?
I'm not that happy.
Come on.
You can use a brake from driving.
You're not
driving my car, Madison.
This is it, pull over.
Take a picture, it lasts longer.
Damn, he actually took a picture.
Do something, Quinn.
I got this, babe.
Hey, are you Tony?
That's me, I'm Tony.
Wait, so you're the guy
we're supposed to meet
to find out where the surgery center is?
I wouldn't call it a surgery center.
What would you call it then?
I think of it more as a big house.
It's a short walk from here.
Walk?
No cars allowed.
You guys walk to the house from here.
I didn't bring any hiking shoes.
How long is this walk?
Uh, about a mile or two.
The website didn't say anything
about walking two miles in the desert.
Look, it's a shaded path.
Woods, not a desert.
This is how we cross
the border undetected.
Follow a stream,
you reach a storm drain
and there's a tunnel.
Dude, this is crazy.
You want the cheapest
plastic surgery performed
with high quality and under the radar.
You know what I mean?
I, I get it.
No taxes, no paperwork,
no malpractice insurance, low overhead.
Yes, you get it, amigo.
Dr. Pavor is the best, you know?
I understand the business plan,
but we were fully expecting
a shuttle, not to hike there.
It's the only way.
No one even knows you're there.
You save thousands.
But if you guys want to cancel,
I have to contact them.
Dr. Pavor is expecting you today.
Uh, I vote for turning back.
We're going, we're gonna do this.
I'm sure the place is safe.
Brenda, is that you?
I can't get the restraints free.
Well, you didn't get out when I did?
They caught me.
I didn't make it in time.
I left a message for my dad.
He'll find us.
I don't think we have a lot of time.
I can barely walk.
We need to get out now.
Hey, what's happening?
Dr. Pavor wanted me
to bring Faye to him.
Will you help me bring her to him?
Liar.
No, no, no.
You suck.
No wait,
I suck.
Run, Brenda!
Faye, I really don't appreciate you
grabbing my uniform and wrinkling it.
I only have one and I hate ironing.
I'd really like to punish
you and to drink your blood,
but Dr. Pavor has big plans for you.
Detective Ross.
Oh Susan, what's up?
No, I haven't seen Faye.
You know, I barely see her anymore.
We don't have the best relationship now.
You think she's missing?
Well, why?
When was the last time you talked to her?
She said she was going to
Mexico for spring break, really?
Ah, yeah.
So she shouldn't back
like what, two days ago?
All right, listen, calm down.
I'm sure she's gonna be fine,
but let me look into it.
All right, bye.
Daddy, I, I messed up.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have come here.
It's so shady, but it's worse than that.
I'm in trouble.
They're coming for me.
They can smell the blood.
They're going to-
You look like a-
- Jesus.
- Shh.
Where is he?
I don't know.
I can't tell you.
I don't know where he is, I swear.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Hey Joe, what's up?
You busy?
Uh, never for you, uh, I still owe you.
What's the problem?
Faye's missing.
She went down to Mexico for spring break
and she hasn't come back.
She's left this phone message
which scared the hell outta me.
I think she's been abducted.
What can I do?
I need you to help me find her.
You got it.
If you guys are gonna
leaving for the clinic soon,
it's getting late,
and you guys should not be
walking around there at night
because you won't find it.
We just need another minute.
I need a word with my friends.
We're going, what's there to talk about?
We need another minute.
It's getting late, guys,
and you guys don't wanna
be walking on the path
when it's dark.
So you keep saying.
She said give us a minute,
so give us a minute.
Fine.
I know I keep saying it over and over,
but this all really sounds crazy.
Hiking in the woods through a tunnel
to cross the border illegally
just to get cheap surgery?
I don't like the hiking part,
but the rest is what I expected.
Me too, babe.
I can't wait till you
get that tight kitty.
Careful, you
can get lost in there.
Not for long.
Speaking of not long.
That won't be an issue
either, after the surgery.
Will you two quit feeling each other up?
There are ladies present.
You know, Maddie,
I bet Dr. Pavor performs sex changes too,
if you're interested.
Mm, I'm good.
My sexual preference is not a problem.
Besides, one dick on this trip is plenty.
You guys decided yet?
I'm going.
Me too.
Well, if you're all going, I'm going.
I'm going even if I
have to hike in heels.
Hold on guys, hold on.
- Thanks babe.
- Okay.
Guys, if we keep stopping,
we won't make it before dark.
So what happens then?
I don't know, werewolves.
Guys, I think he means
that it would be really
hard to stay on path.
And he only gave us one flashlight, so.
How was I supposed to
know I need hiking shoes?
Yeah, they didn't really
mention on the website.
March on, Maddie.
Daddy, I, I messed up, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have come here.
It's so shady, but it's worse than that.
I'm in trouble.
Talk to me, Steve.
She's somewhere in Mexico.
She must have stopped before the border.
The cops are working on that now.
You think the cops down
there are gonna help me?
Give me a break.
Okay, I'll keep looking.
She's my daughter.
I need to find her, damn it.
I'm on it.
All right, you know what?
I'm gonna get in my car and
I'm gonna start heading south.
Just call me when you got something.
It's worse than that.
I'm in trouble.
They're coming for me.
They can smell the blood.
They're going to-
If I'm reading this
right, that's the tunnel.
We should go in.
You want us to go in your tunnel?
Ow.
The tunnel's really dark.
I wonder how long it is.
Yeah, I'm not gonna touch that one.
Low hanging fruit.
Please let me go!
I won't tell anyone what goes on there.
I promise.
And I am supposed to trust you?
Yes, you probably never have
much reason to trust anyone,
but you can trust me.
I, I'm sure you've had a hard life,
but maybe just once by
trusting just one person,
by trusting me, your whole
life can change for the better.
No!
I don't think so.
Thank you for your service.
Well, we made it.
We're in Mexico.
We need to pick up the
pace before it gets dark.
Stop looking at me.
Just leave her alone.
I'm 100%, absolutely totally sure
we'll make it before it gets dark.
Okay, okay, sorry.
Actually we're almost there,
so no one loses their shit.
According to the map, we're here.
Looks more like a home than a hospital.
That's what the freaky
dude that the bookstore said.
When Tony said it was under
the radar, he wasn't kidding.
Last chance to turn back
and make a run for it.
Don't be such a pussy.
Meow, bitch.
Speaking of a bitch-
- Don't say it.
- Ow.
Aren't, aren't they expecting us?
Maybe it's after hours.
We were supposed to get here before dark.
Please, come in.
Fuck me.
Keep it in your pants, perv.
That is, if you can find it.
Hi, I'm Skylar Winslow.
Dr. Pavor is expecting me and my friends.
We were expecting three of you.
Who's the other?
Uh, her and I, we're,
we're here for some work.
I'm here for moral support.
Excellent.
We sometimes lack of morals here,
so your visit is greatly appreciated.
You're the surgeon?
Yes, I'm Dr. Pavor.
And all your questions will
be answered soon enough.
But for now,
just follow Maria Angela to
your rooms and get situated.
Follow me.
Are you checking out her as?
I have eyes and I am not dead.
Shh, shh, shh.
I understand there was some excitement
in your room earlier.
What happened to Brenda?
Oh, no, no.
Don't you worry your little
pretty head about Brenda.
Maria Angela is taking care of her.
Now, no more thoughts about leaving, okay?
Please.
Please what, my dear?
Please let me die.
No, no, no, no.
You are not going to die.
You are going through
the transitional phase.
No.
You are going to feel
much, much better now.
No, don't.
Please, please, I hate needles.
Well, that's unfortunate.
Then you're really not gonna like this.
Hey Steve, I found Faye's calendar.
It looks like she's
headed to some bookstore
north of the Mexican border.
I'm heading there now.
I'm gonna text you the address.
So hopefully you'll meet me there
or maybe you can even get there
before me and check it out.
There's nothing wrong with your breasts.
So you told me a million times.
I just wish I could
have talked you out of it.
I feel like such a lousy friend.
Well, you're here, so that's not lousy.
Madison, follow me.
Hell no.
You ever think about getting into porn?
You got the body for it.
I prefer nursing.
You prefer nursing?
Sign me up, I'll nurse from you.
So do you assist the doctor
with some of his procedures?
Yes.
So do you know much
about vaginal rejuvenation?
Yeah, what do you
know about the vajayjay?
The doctor will answer
all of your questions now.
Please, follow me, Alana.
Just Alana for now, Quinn.
You'll be next.
So is this where we'll
be staying tonight?
Sleep now.
You don't have to leave.
I mean, if you want to hang out,
we could get to know each
other a little better.
What's with the face paint?
You, you don't say much, do you?
Personally, I, I think
talking is overrated.
You ever see "The Little Mermaid?"
Well, the chick in that film
doesn't talk much either,
and I had the biggest crush on her.
She was hot for a cartoon and,
and pretty naked too at one point.
You know what?
I think that's the first time
I realized I liked girls, and fins.
I used to imagine Ariel grew
up to be Jessica Rabbit.
Probably, because they were
both redheads, just like you.
Great job, Maddie.
Scared off another one.
Welcome, Ms. Roberts.
Tell me about yourself, Alana.
You have my file, right?
I just wanna know more about you.
Like for example, how many
of your friends and family
know that you went to Mexico
for a plastic surgery?
Hmm, just my friends that are here.
And what type of work do you do?
I'm a porn star.
Well, no, I should say I'm a porn actress,
to pay my way through school.
I'm not a star, yet.
But hey, if you're willing
to gimme any discounts,
I can give you the full star treatment.
What sort of work do you do?
Well, I'm a student
and undeclared major.
But, uh, don't worry about
paying for the surgery.
I have a little inheritance
from my grandma.
What sort of work do you do?
I'm a student.
So far I'm an accounting major.
Hey, maybe I could do
your taxes for a discount.
It's not that I think
there's something wrong with them,
it's just that I want
'em to be a little more.
Bigger, down there.
On top.
You heard of the Grand Canyon?
Well, that's what it's
like between my thighs.
Miss Roberts, have you
had a a baby recently?
God no.
I'm not ready for that nightmare.
Well, it's just that you're
rather to vaginoplasty.
Have you ever seen a porn, Doc?
Male talent is huge.
Plus, I've done my share of gang bangs.
You are not alone, Miss Winslow.
You know,
breast enhancement is one of
my most popular procedures.
Now, do you have any
size or shape in mind?
Um, maybe a cup or two bigger.
Definitely noticeable,
but natural looking.
I really want, like when I'm a
small business owner one day,
for clients to see my photo
and wanna come in and be my customer.
You know what I mean?
You know, penile
implants are not as rare
as what you think.
They're just less discussed, you know?
So have you heard of the
penile map procedure?
Well, the process can take about an hour
and it comes in three different sizes.
It comes in large, extra
large and extra, extra large.
I've tried kegel exercises,
rejuvenation cream.
It's not working.
I really think I need some
tightening up down there.
Um, though, I'm kind of
worried about sensitivity.
I was reading that some women
tend to lose some
sensation in their breasts.
I assure you that there
won't be any numbness.
You know, my surgeries have more to do
with manipulating blood, flow.
Will it still function normally
even if I got the extra, extra large?
Yes, yes.
I mean, look,
I'm just gonna make a small incision
at the base of the abdomen
and then I'm gonna insert
the silicon cylinder
in the shaft at the top so it
won't obstruct the passages.
As a matter of fact,
my procedures will increase the flow
and it will help you maintain stronger,
longer, and harder erections.
I always wanted a bionic dick.
Gentlemen, we can rebuild them.
We have the technology.
We can make 'em better, stronger, faster.
Healthy three to four inches, Doc.
Most women already think I'm a dick,
might as well be a big one, right?
Wow, I have nothing to lose.
No, no, it's just a matter
of what you're gonna gain.
I like that.
I'm gonna sign right here.
Oh, any chance you
could bleach my asshole
while you're down there?
All the porn stars are doing it.
It's been a slow week.
Nobody seems to buy books here anymore.
I actually make more
by sending people to
Dr. Pavor's as clients.
What the hell, buddy?
You're open rather late, aren't you?
So what is it to you?
I'm looking for a girl.
Keep it in your pants, man.
I just sell books here.
Her name is Faye, she's missing.
I know she came through here last week.
So what?
I get a lot of people
that come through here.
You do?
I can't help you.
Get outta here.
I know 42 ways I can injure
you to the point of death
and all you'll feel is pain.
You'll beg me for death,
but I'll just hurt you more.
Okay, geez.
Now,
this girl.
We'll try this once again.
Was she in here recently?
I have not seen her.
See if this helps you remember.
Ow!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, stop, stop.
Yes, yes, she was here a few days ago.
See, now that wasn't so hard, was it?
Yeah.
No, it's me.
No, I'm here right now.
The pen is mightier than the sword,
when it's a poison pen.
That room is off limits.
Sorry, I um, thought
I heard someone crying.
Do you think you're
the only patient here?
This is a painful recovery process
and you need to respect
the privacy of others.
Of course.
I, I'm sorry.
Your friends should be done
with their consultation by now.
I'm sure you can find
them in the kitchen area.
No worries.
What are you doing, Anna?
I don't answer to human cows.
I won't be human for long.
Oh yeah?
Dr. Pavor needs somebody
to go out into daylight.
Now what did you do with Brenda?
I took care of her.
The wolf will do the rest.
Huh, leave now.
Why?
You think because Dr. Pavor
drinks you, he trusts you?
No, he trusts me.
You are the only one he punish
with that ridiculous face.
Anna, is that you?
Please, untie me.
No one will know.
What, what are you doing?
I'm thirsty.
Ah!
And if I were you, I'd, shh!
Have you been drinking blood again?
What are you gonna do, report
me to Vampire's Anonymous?
Back off.
Who are you?
I'm the owner.
I'm a detective.
I just need some answers.
Why the gun?
Seems to make a strong point.
I'm warning you,
the cops down here will not care
if you're a big shot detective.
Why you uh, have a lot of books here.
Sell any of them?
That's your question?
You wanna know about my books?
Yeah.
And what are you doing here in the dark?
It's none of your business.
It is my business.
Geez, take it easy.
You don't have to point that thing at me.
I'm looking for a
young woman, name's Faye.
She was here sometime last week.
Did you see her?
I don't know who she is.
Here take a look.
Wow, what a looker.
That's my daughter!
I never saw her.
Did a man named Steve come here tonight?
No, nobody was here.
Can you please leave?
Listen dick face,
I know this place is up front
for a shady plastic surgery center
somewhere south of the border
and the clients come here first.
Let me ask you again.
Have you seen my daughter?
Come on, that sounds ridiculous.
Oh!
Oh man, that wasn't cool, man.
You think I'm joking?
One more lie and I'm gonna
shoot you in the leg.
Yes, uh, they, they were here.
They were here a few days ago, but all,
all I did was draw them a map.
What map?
Uh, this map.
Hand it to me.
Hey, hey.
That was stupid.
Now you're gonna have
to draw me another map.
Come on, we both know
you're not gonna shoot me.
Are you testing me?
Okay, I'll draw you a new map.
But I need to get my
special pens over there.
What?
I gotta get my special pen.'
Hey, back off.
I'll get it.
You killed Steve.
Last chance, where's my daughter?
Look, I will draw you a new map,
but I know you're not gonna shoot me.
You're right, I didn't
shoot you, asshole.
So, how'd it go?
Great.
I'm going to spread my
legs for the doc tomorrow.
So what's new?
Shut up.
You're spreading, too.
Yeah, you're finally
gonna grow to be a big boy.
Where's Sky?
Oh, she's upstairs unpacking.
You guys are sharing a room.
They have Quinn and me bunking together.
What did you guys
think about those nurses?
I'd do 'em.
Me too.
As long as I got my
standard girl/girl rate.
But like what's with the
naughty nurse uniforms?
My perv radar says
it's all about Dr. Pavor,
but who cares?
As long as the rate isn't even a 10th
of what it'd be in Beverly Hills?
Yeah, I don't think
we should judge them.
They're professionals,
they deserve our respect.
Wait, so you're saying
you wouldn't do 'em?
No, I, I didn't say that.
It's just, nevermind.
I think we should all get some rest.
We all have a big day
tomorrow, and I do mean big.
So what time do you go under the knife?
He's doing me at noon.
10:30, and can you
please not put it that way?
Why are you getting scared stiff?
Actually, just the opposite.
Good, then I will
get some sleep tonight.
Oh, there you are.
I was wondering where you were.
Yeah, just checking out this
place, this surgery center.
Oh, I was sure that you were somewhere
hitting on Miss Face Paint Nurse.
She's kind of hot, for a mime.
I think I scared her off, so.
Oh no.
You didn't tell her about your
sexy tune obsession, did you?
You know that's fucking weird, right?
Okay, I screwed up.
Drop it.
So do you think your
boobs are in good hands?
Well, we'll see.
The procedure's tomorrow at 9:00 AM.
Damn, he's doing all three
of you in the same day?
Yeah.
The way Dr. Pavor explains it
is that he doesn't actually
have to insert any implants.
It's more about channeling the blood flow,
so the surgery goes by quick.
What?
He compared it to,
you know when a woman's breasts
fill up with milk after pregnancy?
Something like that.
Hey, whatever.
If it works, you know?
You don't think that sounds
like a little dangerous?
No, I trust him.
Plus he said that it's gonna go by quick
and that they're gonna
look really natural.
Tell you the truth, I can't wait.
Whatever, I think all
three of you are crazy.
You are fine just the way you are.
Well fine is not perfect.
Nobody is perfect.
And that is why we are here.
What has Pavor told you
about drinking the product
time and time again?
Do you remember what he
did to you last time?
No thanks.
I don't want white mime
paint burning to my face.
Dr. Pavor, are you okay?
Just need a little nourishment.
What's going on there?
Anna was dipping into
the supplies again.
You fool.
You know that I need
my stress for tomorrow.
If I pump out anymore
from her, she will die.
What about the girl who
is not here for surgery?
She was snooping around earlier.
I bet you can fit on her tonight.
No, I had other plans for her.
Oh, she reminds me of-
No!
Thanks to your indiscretion,
I now must go out tonight.
You know,
I really hope Bobby
appreciates what you're doing.
I'm not doing this for Bobby.
I'm doing this for me.
Hey, why don't you get
something done while we're here?
Like what, longer legs, a butt tuck?
I mean, hey, if you can't
bounce a quarter off it, right?
Fuck you.
What about that tattoo that you hate?
I'll pay to get it removed.
My gift to you for coming with us.
That's what friends do.
They support each other
through dumb decisions like this one.
Do you have something against Dr. Pavor?
I've never even met him.
I have nothing against him.
Okay, I know maybe
he won't be your type,
but I don't know.
There's something really
comforting about him.
He reminds me of my grandfather.
Sounds dreamy.
Madeline, it is you.
You'll come back, soon, soon.
But now I must feed.
Beautiful weather, right?
Lovely.
I'm glad you liked dinner.
I did not realize that
you were such a good cook.
You really surprised me.
I'm gonna show you something special.
Check this out.
It's a tree.
Yeah, it's a pomegranate tree.
I grew it from a single seed.
Wow, you're a cook and a gardener?
Well you, you're very beautiful.
Wait, wait, it's barely our first date.
Come on.
You know you like me and I like you.
I don't get it.
How do I make my fangs show?
I just think about something
that makes me really angry.
I usually think about my father.
That's it.
What did you think about?
How hard it is to get
a long-term relationship?
That makes me mad.
Well, maybe you wanna rethink
that whole long-term relationship thing
because vampires live a long time.
Can I crash here for a while?
No, that wouldn't be a good idea.
My boss is really grumpy.
He's very persnickety.
In fact, you should leave now.
I wanna stay a while.
We had so much fun last night.
We did have fun, but I have work to do,
so now it's time for you to go.
Are you sure it's okay
if I leave in the daylight?
Of course you can.
That's just a myth.
Vampires can totally
go out in the daylight.
Well, what about the other myths?
Well, the other myths are mostly true.
Well, I wanna see my
fangs in my reflection.
No, you absolutely cannot
look at yourself in the mirror.
That myth is true, but I
assure you, you look very sexy.
Come on, trust me.
Well, okay, I'll trust
you since you're my maker.
Okay, well, it's time for you to leave.
Are you sure I can leave
though without any problems?
Of course.
Okay.
Too clingy.
You know, Maddie,
this is your chance to talk to Dr. Pavor
in case you want anything done.
Last chance.
You sure you still wanna
go through with this?
Damn, Maddie, you gotta
stop asking me that.
I know.
Well, sorry, I'm nervous.
I'm so sorry to keep you both waiting.
Okay.
Dr. Pavor, you look different.
Well,
it's amazing what a good
night's sleep can do to you.
How did you sleep yesterday, my dear?
Good, very good.
Maddie's a nervous wreck though.
So you are the one
here for moral support.
Mm-hm.
Too many morals though,
not enough support.
My name's Madison.
I am Dr. Pavor.
Doesn't Pavor mean dread in Spanish?
Very good.
But there's nothing to
dread in here, my dear.
I told you.
Are, are you from Mexico, Dr. Pavor?
Oh, my family's from
California, you know,
tracing back many years,
but now I call this
beautiful country my home.
You're really striking, my dear.
See, even the doctor
doesn't think I need
to have any work done.
Well, I didn't say that.
You know, improvements can always be made.
I bet, but, but I'm,
I'm cool the way I am.
Except for that tattoo.
Oh, tattoo removal is a little
beneath my skill, you know?
But after I finish with your friends,
I will be more than happy to
touch you up, free of charge.
Well, but first things first.
Are you ready to become voluptuous?
Yes, I am.
These twins have been
just waiting to grow up.
Hey!
Hey buddy, stop!
Stop!
Hey, thanks for stopping.
I could use a little help here.
I'm looking for this surgery center
and just got this crappy little
map and no cell reception.
Can you tell me where the clinic is?
Where'd you get that map?
Why?
So you're the one that killed Tony?
So you know Tony?
You know, he killed my friend, Steve.
And then he tore up this map.
This is all I got.
So how do I get to this clinic?
You know, I suggest that you
turn around now, head home.
Otherwise, you're a dead man.
I'm not going anywhere.
How do you know Tony?
We work for the same employer.
Yeah?
Yeah, who's that?
You don't know?
Come on, who is it?
The cartel.
Cartel?
Can't have to do with drugs.
What's really going on here?
Cartel doesn't want anybody
to mess with the doctors,
so either you leave alive or in a box.
Your choice.
Faye's not doing anything with drugs.
What does the cartel out with my daughter?
You know what?
I'm tired of this shit.
On your knees now.
Hey, hey.
On your knees!
On your knees.
She's my only kid, all right?
Hey, my ex is gonna kill me
if I don't bring her back.
Huh, you got kids?
Oh, I'm tired of
listening to your bullshit.
Say your prayers.
Listen, can you,
can you at least point me
in the right direction so I,
I know I was close to her, please?
"The right direction."
You have no idea how close you were.
It was right over there, that way.
Let us begin.
Aren't you gonna gimme anesthetic?
No, something better.
What is it?
Oh, it's a special cocktail.
Just drink it and look into my eyes.
Let us begin.
You, you want me to drink this?
It's just
a special cocktail.
Just drink it and look into my eyes.
Let us begin.
It's a special cocktail.
Just drink it and look into my eyes.
Reading up on your bartending?
Your surgery's done already?
What do you think?
Shit, Sky, um,
do you remember what you told
me your worst nightmare is?
Okay, let's see it.
Yeah, whip it out.
Just a little peek though, okay?
All right, but you
ladies better stand back.
Where is it?
Oh my God, there's nothing there.
He turned you into a mannequin.
Is, is it over?
Am I okay?
Almost,
but I need you to push.
Really push harder.
Why?
What the fuck, I'm pregnant?
Yes, and the
baby's trying to come out,
so I want you to push, like really push.
There's a problem.
I tied the bandana too much
and the baby can't come out.
Really push harder.
- I don't understand.
- Push!
Push!
Oh God.
What is it?
Push!
- What's inside of me?
- Push!
Welcome back.
Nice nap?
What happened?
We're done.
Was there a problem?
None whatsoever.
You just need to rest so your
body will accept the changes.
I dreamt I was having a baby.
It was really the
opposite of having a baby.
Sky.
Is anyone gonna get the door?
Who are you?
I, I'm, I'm a friend of
a patient of Dr. Pavor.
Oh my God, what happened?
I, I need to talk to
Dr. Pavor right away.
It's an emergency.
Dr. Pavor!
Oh my God, Dr. Pavor!
What's all the commotion?
Oh, close the god damn door.
What are you doing here?
We got a serious problem.
Hey, Maria Angela,
help Mr. Smites back in,
into the operating room,
and can you assist your
friend back into her room
because her body needs to rest.
That was strange.
Yeah.
How'd it go?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I, I think so.
I just feel very, very...
Is it worth it?
Guys like it tight.
Plus, I don't plan to do porn forever.
You planning on having
some kids someday?
God, no.
I'm gonna have an affair
with some wealthy, big ass politician,
and then blackmail him
for every cent he's worth.
And then I'll retire in luxury.
Whatever.
No, oh no.
No, no.
What happened?
He's coming be for you and the girl.
Who is coming?
Anna, stop that right now!
She's always hungry.
Now we won't have answers for hours.
Give me the hand.
I will reattach it while he's unconscious.
Hey, hey.
You speak English?
Yeah.
I'm Detective Joe Ross.
And there's a, I'm looking
for a surgery center.
It should be close to here.
You need to stay away from there.
Bad things happen there.
Wait, what can you tell me about it?
There are rumors.
People go there and they never come back.
My daughter's there.
I gotta find her.
How long has she been there?
I don't know, a few days, a week.
Turn around, okay?
It's too late for her.
Even if you find her alive,
it won't be what you think.
What do you mean, what do you mean?
I mean, I, look, I'm not gonna hurt you.
I gotta find my daughter.
Trust me, you don't.
It'll be her, but it, but it won't.
She'll be dangerous.
I've said too much, okay?
No, just tell me what you know.
I need to find my daughter!
They're vampires, okay?
They'll suck the blood out of you.
Something happened to my cousin
and I haven't seen her again.
The policia, they do nothing.
It's a curse.
Vampires?
Ah, ah, uh!
Keep peeing blood.
When's it gonna be yellow again?
Seriously, no glass?
Do you know that there's no
mirrors in this entire place?
How are you feeling?
Better than Quinn, apparently.
Yeah, I heard he has blood in his urine.
I mean,
they said that after the
operation these would be swollen,
but this is ridiculous.
I could take an eye out with these things.
What do they feel like?
They feel full, but with
a little bit of pressure.
You said he wouldn't use implants,
but those look like implants.
I know.
He said it was something about
redirecting the blood flow.
What's that old joke?
If guys had boobs, they
wouldn't leave the house.
And I guess the same can be
said about girls with implants.
Yeah.
You know what?
Actually, if you could give me a minute,
that would be great.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll give you a
minute to self-reflect.
Ah, yeah, thank you.
I stopped the bleeding,
but he has lost a lot of blood.
He can't afford any more.
So you come and get me the
moment that he awakens.
I need to speak with him.
I will get very upset
if I see one bite mark anywhere on him!
You are a fighter.
I'll give you that.
Please, end this misery.
Oh, you're lonely.
I understand.
But don't worry, you'll have company soon.
Three more will be bled.
Why are you doing this?
Simple supply and demand.
Now I have a question for you.
Who do you call the day that you escaped?
Nobody, I, I couldn't get through.
I told you.
Then no one is looking for you?
I hear differently.
I could take you back to the
operation room right now.
Don't make me drain you dry.
Please, drain me.
I don't wanna live like this.
That's Madeline.
Someone that I knew a long time ago.
You could call her the one that got away.
Sorry, I, I was just looking around.
I don't mind.
And how are your friends doing?
Um, they're upstairs resting.
Sky's a little concerned
over the swelling.
But it's normal, you know,
a few days after the surgery.
And your friend Kurtland, how is he doing?
Peeing blood, I think.
How's that man with the hand injury?
Oh, he's recovering.
But don't you concern about him.
You just look just like her.
That photo looks like it
was taken a hundred years ago.
Who was she?
I'd rather talk about yourself.
Do you drink?
Only if someone's offering.
Oh, hey.
How'd your surgery go?
Better than mine, I hope.
I don't feel very well.
I thought walking might help.
Yeah, they told me to do some movement,
but it's not working.
I keep bleeding even when I'm not pissing.
Look.
Ugh.
Same with me, and the blood's
a different color, right?
Yeah.
What about Alana?
She's having issues, too.
It hurts her to walk.
Thanks.
What is it?
Oh, it's just a special cocktail.
Does it have a name?
I, I worked my way through
school as a bartender.
I know nearly every drink.
No, it's just my own private recipe.
Then let's call it
the Dr. Pavor special.
Let's drink too that.
Go on, go on.
It's gonna put some hair on your chest.
That's the last thing I need.
What do you need, Madeline?
Ma'am, I'm sorry, Madison,
tell me your hopes and your dreams.
Perhaps I can make them come true.
I doubt it.
I wanna open my own lesbian bar.
Are you and Miss Winslow a couple?
We're just good friends.
I like your nurse Anna, though.
I'd like to have her.
I'm sure she would like to have you.
Drink up.
Wow.
What's in this?
Remember, it's a secret recipe.
Yeah, my heart is racing.
Oh yeah, it really pumps your blood.
You know that offer?
The free removal of your tattoo?
Let me see yours.
He woke up, Dr. Pavor.
Stop her!
Don't let it go!
I really feel like Alana's the one.
Guys, where's Alana?
We need to get her and
get out of here right now.
Fangs out, losers.
What the fuck is that?
They're vampires.
I heard you like me.
Please move.
I don't wanna hurt you.
Oh yeah, so you just leave
your friends behind like that?
So what if I like you?
How could it work?
Well, I could give you a taste
or you could give me a little taste, huh?
I'll give you a taste.
Ah, no!
Ah!
I'm not a vampire.
Okay.
Am I gonna live?
Not forever.
Now, who is coming?
It's the father of
that girl that escaped.
I think she called him.
Oh, I knew it.
Did he do that to you?
Yeah, and he killed Tony, too.
Oh, he shows up here,
he's gonna be dealt with.
Wait, can't you get me that stuff?
Look, I need it to fix my arm.
You promised me.
You promised me the stuff.
I'm the liaison for the cartel.
You promised me to give me
this stuff to make me better.
Give me it, please.
That's all I'm asking.
Dr. Pavor, Madison killed Anna.
Yeah, I felt her loss.
Where's Madison?
I took her to the operating room.
Everyone is ready for you.
You will be rewarded,
and then you help me avenge Anna's death.
Are you gonna turn me?
Drink.
It won't take long, my friend.
Now I'm a vampire.
You suck.
What the fuck is this?
Get this thing off me.
What's going on?
Would you like your questions answered?
Perhaps I owe you that much.
Yes.
Why are you doing this to us?
When Madeline turned me into
vampire dust many years ago,
I made use of my skills as a doctor,
and we look into a safe
way to secure blood.
Just like humans raise their
crops and vital liquids.
Why couldn't we do the same to humans?
What's gonna happen to us?
Your breasts are overflowing now.
Same goes to your genitals.
You must be bled once or twice a day,
or you will die due to the
building pressure in your body.
How many others have you done this to?
Faye here, she came for a
nose job and other body works.
It didn't go as she planned.
By the way, you tasted her earlier.
That cocktail that you drunk.
You're sick.
Oh, it's addictive.
That's why I have clients
in powerful positions
helping me finance my work.
You're selling this blood to humans?
It's better than any
other drug on the market.
You remember that man that lost his hand?
He was nearly dead hours ago.
Smite.
Come in here.
I gave him a dose and look at him now.
How do you feel?
Excellent.
Oh, I see we've got new cattle.
Oh, good.
Very, very, good.
You can tell the cartel
that our next shipment
will be going out tomorrow as planned.
What is that?
There's a security breach upstairs.
It's in the back door.
It's him, I know it's him.
You know what?
I'll handle it myself.
This time, it's personal.
Dad.
That's right, my dear.
He was foolish to try to to save you,
and now he's going to die.
So we meet again.
What the?
Where's my daughter?
Oh, in hell.
And you're gonna follow her.
Stay where you are.
Tell me where she is, I'll let you live.
I've changed.
You can't hurt me now.
I'm invincible!
And I'm Superman.
Where's my daughter?
Dad!
Oh you are responsible
for his fate, Faye.
I hope that you are aware of that.
No!
That's it!
Now I'm going to drain you completely dry
now that I have others to take your place!
Invincible?
You're not invincible.
I'm coming, Faye.
Daddy's coming.
Check on Smites.
What to do about you?
I had such plans.
You were going to be my
third bride, Madison.
I was gonna make you part of my family.
We were going to be connected forever.
No thanks.
You had to disfigure yourself.
I cannot be close enough
to you to save you.
First time in my life
I'm grateful I went to an
all girls Catholic school.
They made you burn that into your flesh.
No, the nuns hated it.
That's why I did it.
What a waste.
That abomination tainted your blood.
You're useless to me now.
You will be empty soon and finally free.
I heal quickly now.
I'm going to kill you so slowly
and you'll never see your baby girl again.
You will die knowing that
you couldn't save her.
Maria Angela, she's hurt.
I'll kill him myself.
I'll see Faye again, but you won't.
Madison.
What?
See the cord on the floor by your feet?
See if you can kick it loose.
Unplug it and then we'll
stop the blood pumps.
Okay.
Thank you.
Now go, help my dad.
What about my friends?
I'll free them, I know how.
I have enough strength.
Now go, please.
My dad is in trouble.
I was warned about vampires.
I never really believed they existed,
but I guess they're real.
What are you some doctor surgeon vampire?
Most people needs to see
it with their own eyes.
You have been bitten.
It's just a scratch.
What if you're done with my daughter?
You should be more
concerned with yourself.
You can turn soon, if you don't die first.
Is it Dr. Pavor, is it?
What is that, some weird vampire name?
Hey, how about you just gimme my daughter
and we'll get outta here.
You're a fool, you know that?
You came out this way for nothing.
Look, asshole, I'm gonna
give you one more chance.
You tell me where my daughter
is, I'll let you live.
Otherwise I'm gonna kill you
just like I did your nurse friend here.
Vampire or no vampire.
You know that your threats
are not amusing, right?
What kind of death are you to serve, huh?
Slow, quick, or eternal?
Oh, do you expect to kill me with that?
No, I'm the weapon.
I must have been blessed
over a hundred times
by the nuns in school.
You said my blood was tainted.
I bet holy blood is even more
powerful than holy water.
Detective, grab him.
You thirsty?
Try my special cocktail.
Oh my, ah!
What the fuck?
Do you know her Faye is?
Is she still alive?
Yeah, follow me.
Faye's in here.
♪ Na na na na na na na ♪
No, what did you do?
- Faye.
- Dad.
Faye, oh my God, oh my God.
What did he do to you?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Oh, I'm okay.
Oh, but you're hurt.
Oh no.
It's just a scratch, I'm fine.
We gotta get outta here.
What were you thinking?
Coming down to Mexico for
surgery without telling anyone?
I know things,
I know things haven't been
great since the divorce,
and I haven't been
paying attention to you,
but this is, this is like really bad.
And I'm really sorry I messed up,
but when we get back, we'll
work it out, all right?
I know I should have
said something to you,
but I really wanted the surgery
and, and you and mom were...
It means the world that you came for me.
Great, but, but we gotta get outta here.
I had to.
I couldn't let them live like human cows.
Don't worry about it.
I'm gonna fix this.
I'm gonna tell, tell 'em Pavor
butcher them all then fled.
Then we can go back and
we can be a family again.
- Yeah.
I'd like to live like a family again.
But, you've been bitten
and I've been damaged.
No.
Whatever that maniac did to you,
we'll fix it, we'll fix it.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna make
everything go right again.
All right?
If you just for, just for, forgive me.
I forgive you.
Can you forgive me?
Forgive you?
You're, you're my daughter.
Forgive you-
I couldn't let you
become one of them, Dad.
And I can't live with this.
- Stop her, stop her!
- No, no!
Please take her home to her
mother so she can get help.
She killed my friends!
Please, promise me you'll take her home.
Please.
Why should I let you live?
You shouldn't.
I deserve to die.
Come on, let's get you home.