Oh!
Sorry. Okay.
- After you, Sandy.
- Oh, my God. You get it?
Yes.
Is there anything you wanted?
You guys...
Welcome.
You look so good!
- Yeah, I love the costume.
- And you got the news?
- Yeah, we all did.
- Hey, how's it going?
Uh, a little treat, I think.
Yeah, I'll grab a black coffee?
And we'll grab Sandy's coffee.
- Oh, thanks.
- Yeah, you're welcome.
- The usual, "Sandy"?
- Yes.
- I'm Zoey.
- I'm Enzo.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Paolo. Nice to meet you.
So, where are you guys from?
Well, I'm from Australia,
but I flew in from Milan.
Oh, good.
So you missed the whole...
Yeah, just made it. So lucky.
If anything closed...
I think we were, like,
one of the last flights.
- Super lucky. We're really like...
- Yeah.
In Red Hook, it's crazy right now.
The trees are down.
I mean, I thought Hurricane
Sandy was gonna be like Irene.
Why does everybody underestimate
the female hurricanes?
I think this one's gonna be bad.
So you guys friends, or...
- We're actually brothers.
- Yeah.
From different mothers.
Literally. That's not a joke.
- Yeah, well, long story.
- Long story.
A story for another time.
Well, if you guys
are around later,
my roommates and I,
um, we live upstairs,
but, um, we're
having people over.
What's the theme?
Did you figure it out?
There's a lot of tension between
it's either vintage Halloween
- or fall for Sandy.
- "Fall for Sandy"?
It's like, we fell
for Hurricane Irene,
- Fall for Sandy...
- Oh!
But also, autumn.
I like that, I like a good autumn.
I don't like a good autumn.
- Double entendre.
- Yes.
We have dinner plans tonight,
but maybe we'll come back later.
- Yeah, I mean...
- We don't know if those are good, anyway.
- That's true, yeah.
- Yeah.
It's just the second floor
facing the window.
- Okay.
- 2B.
Okay, well, or not to be.
Well, I hope it's to be.
Yeah, so do I.
Ignore that. That was silly.
That was really silly.
Thanks for the cup.
Yeah. Thanks for the coffee.
It was great.
Great, thanks.
- See you.
- Bye.
Well...
Inviting strangers.
- Just felt right.
Hey, Mom. ZOEY'S MOM: [ON
PHONE] Hey, honey, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm just... I'm tired.
ZOEY'S MOM: Did you hear
about the apartment?
Yeah, we just got the notice.
I want you to come home
and live with me.
I love you,
but I'm not gonna move home.
Why not?
So, do you have a plan
- of where you're gonna go?
- Yeah. Uh-huh.
Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Are you okay?
No, I'm just... I'm... I'm...
- All right.
- Just tired.
I just want you to be okay,
all right?
So, are you guys
prepared for the storm?
Yeah, we're prepared.
Do you have everything you need?
Definitely. Yeah.
We're very prepared.
God bless you. You take
good care of yourself.
Uh-huh.
Bye, say hi to the girls.
Isn't that cute?
- They're so nice.
- I know, I love them.
Hold on, hold on a sec.
ZOEY'S MOM: It's getting
so quiet.
"Dear Zoey, Liza and Jen,
please be informed
"that an inspector will be
entering your apartment
"within the next 48 hours
"to prepare your move out
"scheduled to take place
by the end of November."
- I'm sorry.
- I know.
Zoey. Zoey?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Last one to shower
fills the tub.
Okay.
Hi, did you eat?
Yeah.
Jen is going crazy.
Yeah, I know.
Oh. Do you want to trade me
the petty glitter?
Sure.
Got some new colors.
Ah, what does it... I can't...
"Storm ready"?
Yeah.
I feel like
the big nail polish industry
is just capitalizing
on this storm,
just trying to sell
more nail polish.
Oh, my God.
Don't let Jen hear you.
She'll be so upset
that all of her hurricane aid
was for naught.
Tease me all you want,
but you'll thank me later.
Remember to... Fill the tub!
We know.
Oh, my God.
So can I just leave it like
this, or do I need to drain it?
You're disgusting.
- Liza! Door. Thanks.
- Sorry.
Sorry, I know
it's your time to read,
but I need
to tell you something.
We had a dog and didn't go on
to Hannah's. It was stupid.
That's what you get.
Why are you telling me that?
Just wanted to... Zip it.
The time my brother wanted to do math!
No, no, no.
What?
Are we gonna do this?
Storm ready?
It's too much.
I know.
It's so much. I love it.
No, there's too many themes.
No, it's just cute.
- This looks amazing.
- You look amazing.
You look so good!
Oh, my God.
- So pretty.
- Oh, pretty.
That's where that was,
I was looking for that.
- Didn't I ask for it?
- No.
- Ow!
- Give her 200 bucks!
You are out of control.
Did you fill up the tub?
Yes, I'll just go triple check.
I filled the tub.
- Called it.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
- You smell so good.
- Thanks.
Julian's gonna love this.
No, he's not coming.
- Why not?
- I didn't invite him.
You spent the night at his
house, you didn't invite him?
He didn't understand
my Sandy costume.
He thought
I was a deranged clown.
Did anyone understand
your costume?
Yes, actually.
I met a man who did understand
and I invited him.
What?
And his brother.
Two strange mystery men?
Two strange, tall mystery men.
Okay, you're freaking her out.
You need to relax.
This is for you.
- Fall for Sandy!
- Thank you.
A vintage Halloween soiree.
You all...
Oh, my God.
- Hello.
- How are you doing?
You walked here?
You're drenched.
Yes, a crane dropped on the way.
Aw!
Hi.
Oh!
Some pastry.
Hey, mama, how are you?
Good, thank you.
We walked in...
This is embarrassing.
You have to put
your finger in that thing.
You gotta put your hand in here.
This is Bianca.
First day jitters!
- This is her first day?
- Well, it's a hangout.
It's a hangout.
- It's a chill sesh.
It looks like a crane collapsed
on 57th street.
Okay, this is saying winds
are 95 miles an hour.
Ninety-five?
A crane,
like a construction crane.
Don't worry, I put together
a bunch of stuff just in case
anything happens.
I'm aware
that it's better to be prepared.
A kit for us, okay?
Oh.
So, we've got a first aid kit.
Trash bags, candles.
And a bunch of water.
We also filled up the tub
to make sure
that we have extra reserves.
And also an AM/FM radio, okay?
So...
There's a lot of really good
alternative music stations on there.
Jen, I think
that's really thoughtful.
This is great.
All right, you don't know
what's gonna happen, you guys.
All the talk about it has been
that it's gonna be pretty serious.
So I just thought
that I would prepare the party.
Well, you did a good job.
You did a good job.
- Thanks, Mom.
- Thank you.
And if anything happens, you guys
know where the fire exit is, right?
Okay, so it's out the hallway, and
then we go out that big back hall.
And there's a...
You didn't know where it was?
- Well, now I do.
- Exactly!
So it's out the hallway, and out
that big back hall. You guys.
I think we should have a drink, just,
like, chill out. We're gonna be fine.
Yeah, let's have
a drink or something.
Oh, man.
My cousin, Julia,
and her husband aren't coming.
Aw!
They can't get a cab
from the upper west side.
Guess they'll have to take
a rain check, badam pum tss.
Pretty good.
- What is that?
- Yeah, it's like a...
A flood alert or something?
Yeah, it's on here.
Wait, everyone's getting it?
I'm not getting it.
Yeah, flood alert.
That's so crazy.
- Did you get it?
- Yeah, I got it.
It's saying... Yeah.
Bloomberg just posted,
"This is the storm
of the century."
You guys, turn on the TV.
The high winds
from Hurricane Sandy
are suspected of causing the
facade of an apartment building
to collapse
in Lower Manhattan, today.
Apparently,
apartment buildings around...
- Wait...
- I'm gonna... I'm gonna check outside.
- Maybe the breaker or something?
- Liam, be careful.
- I didn't tape the window.
- It was gonna open anyway.
- Guys, there's no power on the whole block.
- Oh, my God.
- Are you kidding?
- There's no power.
Okay, let's go to the roof,
we can see how far it goes.
Seriously?
- Roof!
- Okay, okay.
This is a bad idea.
Zoey, this is too dangerous,
you guys.
Man, I kinda wanna see.
I got it. I got it.
Here, put these trash bags on.
- Put it on.
- Watch your step, you guys.
Zoey, don't run so fast.
Zoey!
You guys hear that?
There's someone out there.
You guys, I think the brothers
are here.
I'm gonna go let them in, okay?
- What? What are you saying?
- The brothers.
From Tim and Joe's.
I'm gonna go get them.
- No, do not.
- You're not going anywhere.
I'll go get them.
Yeah, I'll go with you.
You want?
Yes, please.
- Hey. How are you doing?
- Hey.
This is Enzo, I'm Paolo.
- Hey, nice to meet you.
- Paolo.
Nice to meet you, Enzo.
Hey.
We'll keep warm.
- Hi. Paolo.
- Hi.
Hi, I'm Bianca.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hey, you okay?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry, I went with Jen.
That's okay.
- You good?
- Yeah, I'm good.
Let's. Okay.
- You guys want some wine?
- Oh, thanks.
Cheers.
So you guys were saying
there's a long story.
- The two mothers.
- Oh, Yes. Yes.
- Well, we have all this time, so...
- We have time.
Yeah, well,
we have the same dad.
Paolo, who's my older brother...
Um, Dad
met my mum when
he was travelling to Australia.
She's from Indonesia originally.
And they fell in love.
And he was still married
to Paolo's mum.
So, that kind of happened.
And then, probably
about a year later, I was born.
In Italy.
So you guys have been
in relationship with each other?
Yeah, we grew up together.
Summers.
Well, we're kinda catching up.
Gonna hang out for a week
and then I'm gonna
hit the road
and go on a road trip by myself.
To see the sights?
I'm drinking here, so...
Does anyone have a phone
that's getting through?
I just wanna text my girlfriend
to tell her that...
No, my...
Mine's dead.
Oh, you know what,
I'm so fucking stupid.
I can't text her anyway because
I don't know her number.
Does that make me bad
for not knowing her number?
I only know one number, it's
my buddy, Chad's mom's number.
Because I call her.
We grew up together
and I would call Chad but
I call her every year
on Mother's Day.
- It's a landline.
- Yeah it's a landline.
- That's so cute.
- 5-3-9-0-3-9-1.
- Aw.
Whose phone is not dead
at this point?
- Mine's working.
- Yours is working?
Mmm-hmm, I don't have
any internet, but it's working.
Do you have any service?
- Yeah, kinda.
- I have a little bit left.
I'm just, like, hogging it and holding
it for the last... I don't know how long.
Me, too, and I keep pressing it.
Just, like, maybe.
It's like a kneejerk...
You know what, you guys...
- It's my favorite phone.
- I know, just in case
it comes back on.
- Let me try it one more time, see if I can get it.
- I can call my mom.
We are gathered here today
to bid adieu to our sweet,
sweet telephones.
- Oh, no.
- No!
Boo!
Dearest phone, you are
a constant source of comfort
and distraction.
Both good and bad.
You allow me to connect to the
people I love most in this world.
And you allow me
to completely disengage
from the people
who I love most in this world.
Good night, sweet prince.
That was good.
Words can be a lot...
Hoping we would be able
to get in touch with them,
'cause I haven't heard from her.
Okay, don't make me
feel bad about this.
It's kind of like
a thing that I'm doing.
- All right, um...
- Switch them off.
Em, I hope you're safe.
If you're on your way,
I hope you scream loud
so we can come get you.
How dare you?
You're making it very real.
You're making this too real.
I love you so much.
It will be okay.
Oh, my God.
- Are you crying?
- I just can't...
In the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Phone.
Yeah!
- Amen!
- Bye.
- Wow.
- Rest in peace.
- Good riddance.
I feel very free.
- I feel good.
- I do, too.
- Funny.
- I'm kind of upset
that you guys are gonna
lose this place soon.
Yeah, that's one word for it.
It sucks.
Can we have that when you leave?
Oh, you wanna inherit that?
- This thing? No!
- Yeah. For the coffee shop.
Yeah, you can have it.
What do you mean, "You can..." You
can't give that away, that's mine.
- No, it's not.
- Yes, it is!
We split it, remember?
Well, you were with me
when I bought it.
- And I paid you. Yes.
- Did she pay?
So you just cut it down
in the middle.
I mean, it is, honestly,
best that it goes with them
because we don't have places
to put it in 30 days.
- None of us.
- That's true.
Nobody has a home
for this thing.
So you can have it.
Thank you.
I'm sensing a little bit of, um,
I don't know, some tension...
- Yeah, that's very perceptive.
- between you.
Just bear with me. One sec.
Okay?
Everyone's full
of ideas tonight.
Yeah, everybody has a lot of...
Do you smell cookies?
Wait, hold up.
Are y'all making cookies
or some shit?
Are y'all making butter walnut
cookies or what?
Uh, I wish.
- Don't you smell that, though?
- Yeah, it's nice.
It must be next door.
Thank you for waiting,
my name is Doctor Liam.
Oh, he's a therapist.
- Oh! Therapist.
- I'm here, today,
to explore the emotional journey
you three are
about to embark upon.
Now, I've found it to be helpful
with previous clients
to partake in some roleplay
in order to empathize
and really understand
the experience
of your fellow roommates.
You, my dear,
will be playing Liza.
- Okay.
- What a lucky girl.
Jen will be taking
the role of Zoey.
Oh.
And Jen.
Oh, great. Great.
This is a safe space,
remember that.
Let's talk about how you're
feeling about the impending move.
Okay.
Well, I'm feeling very analytical
and very objective about it.
It's not ideal, the one thing
I can say is it's not ideal.
Not ideal.
But, you know, I've got
a lot of bigger fish to fry,
I've got a lot on my plate,
I'm doing my residency.
And I'm thinking about a lot of
just, like, big time doctor things.
I'm feeling the exact opposite
of that, actually,
I'm feeling
all sorts of emotions,
I'm seeing colors,
I'm painting it out,
I'm doing a lot
of free associating.
- Very visual experience.
- Visual dreamwork.
And I'm doing a lot
of late night snacking
of frozen pizzas at midnight.
Well, what I'm doing is,
I'm actually not
thinking about it at all.
I'm just really present
and living in the moment.
And kind of just,
like, going with the flow,
whoever's around me and whatever
I'm doing, right then and there.
This seem like an appropriate
impression of each other?
Listen, you guys, I think you're being
too childish about this right now, okay?
It's a serious thing.
- It's a serious thing.
- I'm not being too childish about it.
I'm just eating fruit roll-ups
all the time
and watching re-runs
of Full House
and it's really comforting to me
and going to my acting class and
then doing my acting exercises
in the room, super loud,
even though
other people have stuff to do.
You know
what I think would help?
Is if we just like,
have a big party,
and invite a bunch
of random dudes over,
um, that we just met
this morning,
and like, shake things up,
you know what I mean?
Like, who cares if there's
a hurricane on the way.
Let's just go with our hearts
and, like, have a good time.
Well, I care very, very much. I care
very much that there's a hurricane
on the way, and that's why I have
prepared so meticulously for it.
And I've done nothing for it.
I forgot to fill the tub.
And I interrupted Zoey
when she was having a bath
and having one moment
to herself.
And then left the door open, which
I always do because I just forget.
And I'm in my own world and don't
really think about other people.
You know what?
I think we can all take a breath
and remind ourselves
that this is a safe space...
No, I think
we're gonna keep on going.
It's so funny that you don't
think about other people.
- Oh, that's funny? That's funny to you?
- Yeah, that's funny.
- Yeah.
- Why is that funny to you?
I don't know, maybe because, um,
it's what you do?
Let's drop this, that's what
you do, Zoe, that's what you do.
You don't think
about other people.
What are you talking about?
We're moving out because of you.
I needed to do
what was best for me,
and what was best for me
was to move out.
And then it was up to you guys
to find another roommate.
I didn't know that we weren't
gonna be able to keep the place
because my name
wasn't on the lease.
That's not my fault.
You don't even know where you're going.
That's what's crazy about it.
Okay, so, what,
I'm gonna stay here forever?
You could have chosen
a better time.
That's what I mean,
it's not fair.
I know that
we're not 22 anymore.
- Do you?
- Yes, I do.
It's like, what do
you want me to do?
I can't even afford
to live somewhere else.
That's not my fault.
You are the one causing
all of this!
You are the hurricane!
Sorry, you guys.
- Everyone okay?
- Yeah.
Okay, yeah.
That was such a stupid
idea, I'm so sorry.
- That's okay.
- So, would this be a bad time
to offer a business opportunity?
Yes, this would be
the worst time.
I think I need a drink.
Thank you.
Yeah, I'll have some wine.
People might be dying tonight.
If we die tonight,
what would you wish
you'd gotten off your chest.
That's what's going through
my mind right now.
It's so funny that you would
say that.
Um...
Okay.
So, I got a message.
I don't even really know
when I got it
'cause it was just sitting there
in my inbox.
Okay, so...
backstory.
My sophomore year of high school,
I had Miss Keane for math.
She was really cute,
like she was super smiley
and happy and
I wanted to impress her.
So, I studied really hard
and I got pretty good at math.
And then I found out that
she was the assistant coach
for the basketball team,
so then I got pretty good
at basketball.
I'd say, "God,
"if this shot goes in,
"the next time
we have a math test,
"Miss Keane is gonna look up and I'm
gonna look up when it's all quiet
"in the classroom.
"We're just gonna look
at each other."
Whoosh. Swish.
She used to drive me home
after practice.
And I would just sit there
in the car...
She kissed me
for the first time in the car.
I know that we were together,
but I don't remember it like...
going to get ice cream or going to dinner.
I don't remember anything.
I just remember breaking up
and her moving schools and
not knowing where she was
and just never...
seeing her again.
But she wrote me this message.
She's uh...
She's married. So...
She's not Ms. Keane anymore.
And...
I am so glad that
I'm not 15 anymore.
May I have some of that?
See if you're next.
Thanks.
Okay.
Um, I guess not many
people know this, and...
Of course, none of you guys would know
this, but when I was in my early 20s,
I was going to get married.
And a week before
I was meant to get married,
I walked away.
Um,
I felt like I hadn't. I hadn't adventured.
I hadn't seen the world.
I hadn't made mistakes...
and my fiancee,
Elizabeth,
who was a childhood friend,
a childhood sweetheart, I guess,
she didn't deserve
that uncertainty.
And I just wish... I wish
I had been better for her
and that I had the courage,
I had had the balls...
to, to...
to not put her through that.
But then the stupid thing was was that
I just ended up working for my dad,
going into the family business,
and I didn't even
fulfill my promise.
I mean, I'm trying to,
I'm trying to now. I'm trying.
Had I known I was gonna to be
in this situation earlier,
I was kinda lost as a kid,
you know, um...
My biological father was gone, so my
mom remarried, and she had these...
I was... these two sisters,
kind of insta sisters, stepsisters.
And...
for about...
that was about two years...
when they were out of the house,
I would dress up in
their clothes by myself.
I created this...
I guess it was some kind of alter ego,
or I don't know if it was like this
grandmother that I never had,
who was sort of a father figure
who made me feel
like I belonged to something.
Her name was Sophia
and I would dress up,
and... and become Sophia.
I never told you this because
you'd probably think I was crazy,
but Sophia just kept me
grounded for a while when
I didn't know who I was.
Feels good to say that.
Congratulations.
I feel like you need
to wear the bella.
Can you please give me the bella?
I was waiting for that.
There you go. It's a start.
Yeah.
Uh...
Um...
I don't know any of you guys.
You're all strangers.
I guess that's appropriate.
I moved here
to go to business school,
and I got a scholarship that
first year, and it was great.
And I was like killing it.
It was awesome.
And I met a lot
of interesting people
and, uh, started getting to know,
like, the business world out here,
and I got a great internship
at a great financial firm.
That's what I do.
Um, but...
then I kind of got swept
in a different direction.
Um, I went on a trip with a bunch
of people that I was interning with.
This girl, and these
older trader guys,
and they're like, "We're gonna
go away for the weekend."
Um, I mean, just ended up like
this island, um, in the Bahamas.
And I was like, "What? This is
crazy, you know?" And then...
At the end of the trip,
um, they paid me and the girl,
and I was like, "You don't have to do that.
We were just, like, on a trip."
And they're like, "No it's... We know
you're like, struggling in school."
So it's been going on for a few years,
and it's how I've made a living.
I realize, like all these people
that I'm meeting and doing this
with "providing"
who are just people
who want to, like, connect
and like, not be alone
in the world,
and I find that
I'm just alone, um,
when I get home because
I've kind of chosen this life
that's like, an easy way to
make a buck. And I kind of feel like I
have to be pretty closed off to not, like,
fall for anybody or whatever. I guess
I'm sharing all this with you because
I think I am ready to end that chapter
of my life and start a new chapter
where I am truly, like, connecting
and finding someone that
I wanna be with.
And start a family, so...
I know we're here
for our first date.
I know you didn't know
any of this.
Uh, there's that.
That's a lot.
Can I borrow
some of your clothes?
Yeah. I know
I have great clothes.
It's crazy.
I'm gonna miss that part.
Okay. Do I have to go?
Halloween and, like, this
time of year is always
feels a little weird for me.
So when I was in college,
I had, um, a boyfriend
who I really thought
I was going to marry.
Um and we... We wrote music
together and played guitar,
and our songs were really stupid,
but they were also kind of good,
and people would like them and
we'd have these little concerts.
Um, one night we were
at our friend's Halloween party
and we came back home
and we were both really drunk.
We were, like, in our bedroom. And,
um, things just started to happen,
and I just felt
a little too drunk.
But he just kept going,
and I was saying no and,
but then it just kind of happened.
And, um, the next morning,
you know, we both
laughed about it.
He apologized for what happened,
but, um,
it happened again
and happened a lot of times.
I just kept justifying it
to myself, and
he'd apologize.
And I just keep
making excuses for him
because I loved him so much.
But every time that it happened,
I felt like a little part of me,
like, my power wasn't...
It was diminishing, And I...
I didn't call the police
or I didn't do anything.
And then, um,
about a year later, I found that
he was texting this other girl
and he moved out.
It took me a lot of years
and therapy to realize
that what was happening to me
wasn't okay.
I found out, um,
that that next girlfriend
that he had, um,
the same thing happened to her.
And I just wish that I had
said something.
Oh, sorry.
A plus...
It feels good to laugh.
Your turn.
Oh, wow. Okay.
So some of you guys know I
moved here about three years ago
and it was really scary.
I didn't know anyone.
Um, and,
it was kind of an intimidating
place to feel alone. Uh...
But I met some amazing people
who took me in.
Suddenly, it kind of went from
being this unfamiliar,
scary place to...
To home.
And, that realization was
pretty amazing for me.
But there was one person I met
who I knew pretty quickly that
I didn't just wanna be friends
with them. Um...
I felt something more. Um...
But I was terrified
to say anything. Um...
But there's something that I
admire so much in this person.
This comfort in being themselves
kind of inspires me and,
I guess this is the night
with an unpredictable end. Um...
And I feel like
maybe now
would be the time that I...
That I let them know how I feel.
I...
Is it Ryan? Yeah.
You wish.
Yeah, sorry.
It's just like that,
it's so nice.
I don't really feel like,
honestly, I'm listening to that.
And it's like
I'm listening to it.
I'm like, he's talking about me?
I'm like...
Hoping, you know, that you were.
There's still
just a part of me that's like,
"Couldn't be, couldn't be you."
I just feel really unworthy.
Already nervous,
but was great
going around the circle.
Like, what are you going to say? Like all of
these things are so important, so big and...
like, what do you
have to contribute to share?
I just felt like anything that I
have to say would be inadequate.
And I spent, um,
I spent a lot of time
feeling inadequate,
just so dumb because
I'm pursuing this thing
where it's like you need to
believe that you
are enough,
are more than enough.
And I'm supposed to be,
like, so confident.
I know I come off that way but it's like
a lot of times when I feel insecure,
I just get louder.
Um,
my friends from high school be
like, "Oh my God, you're so brave.
"You're so brave for going after
what you really want."
And it's like,
I feel like I'm just going
through the motions of, you know,
taking odd jobs,
like making ends meet,
like going on auditions
and all that stuff. That's like,
it's like, that's the easy part.
And what is much harder is
actually thinking
that you deserve it.
And I just don't feel that way.
I just don't feel that way.
Maybe you guys
are gonna kiss or what?
It's the last time
I hang out with you guys.
Fucking storm, now this.
I'm perfect. So...
I'm not perfect.
I had a friend in college and
we were friends for a long time.
We ended up hooking up and
she got pregnant, and um...
I didn't show up for her.
I sent money.
I feel like
my absence that day
was really violent.
I always ask
why I'm not with anyone.
I think I kind of blew it.
I fuck up and that's it. That's...
That's the move that you made.
You can't get it back.
Tim.
Um, okay.
This is something that I've been
keeping from everybody,
but, um, mostly from Joe.
A couple weeks ago,
I started looking at rings.
And this is not a proposal, because
I don't have a ring right now.
All right. All right.
I just... I just wanted to let you
know the reason I don't have a ring yet
is because I wanted to use
my grandfather's ring.
And when I asked my grandma
if I could use it,
she wouldn't give it to me.
Shit. She said no.
I love her
and I know she loves me.
And sometimes,
you told me this, actually,
sometimes when you love someone,
you have to let them go.
I don't think we need a ring.
- I know you would like a ring.
- I would love a ring.
It'd look great. You would look
great with the ring.
So I'm glad that
we can start talking about
our future together.
- I love you.
- I love you. Plenty of time.
I'm gonna be such a bridezilla, but,
like, nice, I'll be a nice bridezilla.
So you guys, most of you know that I
come from a pretty well-to-do family.
I'm Joseph the third.
My mom's a doctor.
Dad's a lawyer, so...
but they were also very, pretty liberal.
Like I never had to come out.
Like my mom's brother's gay, My
dad's best friend's a lesbian.
So it was never a thing like...
When I was eight, my mom
took me to a Cher concert.
She was like,
" I knew you'd like it."
Um, so I was always, like, you know,
it was a good house to grow up in.
I think the trap, if anything,
for me and my sister was
that we had successful parents,
uh, we had black, successful parents,
like an Upper East Side family
of color.
Like that's a lot of pressure,
like, you do not come home
with anything less than an A.
So I think that weighed on Natasha and I.
We just became best friends
because we had that in common.
But that success thing
was really an issue.
I mean we were in college. I was
a sophomore. She was a senior.
She started taking Adderall,
um, and then pain meds,
and then cocaine and
barely graduated college like in
and out of rehab all of a sudden and
overdosed like four times and...
It was a lot, and, you know, my
big sister just kind of changed.
She shifted. One minute, it's like,
"I'm sorry. I want to be better.
"I'm gonna do better. I'm just..."
and then the next minute it's...
She's lying and she...
She's breaking into Mom and Dad's.
She's breaking into my place.
She's stealing. And the 17th
time she went into rehab,
my mother was like,
"Listen, this is it.
"Like it either sticks or we're done. We
can't... We can't do this with you anymore."
And then she disappeared.
At this point, I'm in grad school.
We moved in with each other.
Had a job. We're talking about starting
our business and she shows up at my door.
Ninety pounds, unrecognizable, talking
about she's hungry, needs money for food.
And I'm... It's like we grew up in the same
house, you know, like we had the same parents,
the same opportunities.
Like what? What?
So you know, I did what
you're not supposed to do.
I gave her money, just like
get out of my face.
And a week later, she overdosed
for the fifth time,
and she didn't survive,
and I felt happy
it was over, you know, like,
she was out of pain,
sure, but my mom...
Oh, sorry.
Oh, God. Now everyone's looking at me.
I'm last.
Hold on... liquid courage.
I don't have like
a big confession.
So much is like no one ever
asks me how I'm doing.
I don't know.
This is a stupid story.
Um, when I was younger.
- Hello?
- Come in.
Hey. Hello.
Come in, come in.
This is our neighbor.
- I'm sorry. She's so ruffled.
- She's so scared.
I've been baking all day.
I heard you guys have people here.
I just wanted to try this.
Yeah, we heard that it's kind
of like a meeting here. A party.
- Yeah.
- And we thought we can join you guys.
Please come in.
Okay, do you wanna come
in my room where you can settle?
A cute story.
- Thank you for being this...
- I'm Josh.
- Hi, Josh. I'm Alex. Nice to meet you.
- Hey, you too.
- Are those butter walnut cookies?
- Yes.
- Oh, look at these.
- I thought I smelled those. Oh, my God.
- Oh, yeah.
- You made these?
Alex is a chef. He's like,
got his finger on them.
Are you guys hungry?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
All right. I've been trying stuff
out all day, it's for the new menu.
- You want food?
- Yeah!
- Are you serious?
- Yeah. I'll be right back.
All right, guys.
This is
a garlic roasted chicken.
Some Artisan flatbread.
And this one's honey
and some ice.
You hear that, right?
Oh, my gosh.
It's our neighbors.
- Downstairs, yeah.
- Downstairs.
She was an opera singer
or something.
Oh. Does she go to church?
- Let's see if they're all right.
- I'll go check on them.
Oh, we're good. We just heard
you singing through the floor.
- Oh, no. Were we too loud?
- No. No.
- Please do.
- Oh, we have plenty of food and water
- and warmth and candles upstairs.
- We're not starving but,
I'm really packed full.
You guys should come up.
- Really?
- Yes.
I could go recruit some people.
We could get you up there,
if you want.
Yes, yeah.
We could absolutely...
We have some
strapping young men.
May I present
Mrs. Barbara Hirsch?
- Hi!
- Nice looking group.
I think so. I think so.
- Oh, guys, this is...
- Mr. Hirsch.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- My goodness.
Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Damien, this is
my daughter, Olivia.
We heard the
Hirsch's moving around,
and then we just followed
the sound of fun.
I think they called it
The Great Northeast Blackout
- in 1965.
- Yeah, in '65.
I was working with...
Yeah, but you know,
it wasn't really that scary.
I think they called it
"The Season of Love."
Flower power children. It was...
Wild, young woman,
before I knew her.
Well, I wasn't indulgent.
And then, I think
the next one...
- '77.
- 1977. Wow.
She was in...
- Bubbling Brown Sugar.
- Bubbling Brown Sugar, and uh...
This is
going to be my first night
on as the lead...
and the lights went out.
So, we just had to be there.
About second act,
it went black at 9:30.
We had to walk home, you know,
all the way from 52nd Street.
Kind of romantic.
It was romantic.
- We're just so happy to be here.
- Yeah.
Thank you for inviting us.
I've never been to a party
in a long time.
Take this piece...
Look...
Can you see them?
You see all of them?
It was in '80s,
and I was on my way home,
walking through
Washington Square Park
and a young man approached me,
and he was asking for money
to buy food, and...
I said, "No, I'm not
giving you any money."
Come home with me.
I'll fix you a hot meal.
And he sat at the kitchen table,
and he started sketching.
It was so beautiful. It was...
It took my breath away.
And I bet you can't guess
who that young artist was.
- When was it?
- '80s.
Basquiat?
He was in this building.
- No, really?
- Yes.
And we have one of his
works of art.
- In your apartment right now?
- Right now...
- in my apartment.
- In your empty apartment?
Yeah, but the door is locked.
I love that.
It's pretty cool, huh?
- It's been fun.
- Yeah, it's been fun.
I'm glad you came.
And I think we're gonna be
really good friends.
- Oh, no!
- I know, but...
- Here we go.
- Hey, listen.
Okay. I'm pretty aware
of my surroundings.
Tonight would be the night.
It's like, take your chance.
- You know what I mean?
- I think...
You guys would be cute together.
Okay.
- You guys get any sleep?
- I'm not.
Sometimes, I'm come
like sleeping
and always watching with
my other eye, you know,
like this is close, and this is,
like, almost open.
It gets a little easier.
I mean, she sleeps
through the night.
Now, I can't get her up
in the morning.
- It goes by quick.
- Oh, my God. Yeah.
I still remember.
And now...
she's a young lady.
- You divorced or...
- No, no.
You're wiping your face
with the boat?
Olivia's mom, Sarah,
she passed away when, uh...
Olivia was about Siena's age.
- I'm so sorry about it.
- Thanks.
If you ever need something,
you just knock the door,
and we will be there, okay?
You come with us.
Yeah, and she's getting
old enough to baby sit.
So, if you guys
need to baby sit...
- Please.
- Okay, that'll be great for us.
- Yeah.
- It would be good.
Four cheers.
It's nice to meet new friends.
Yeah.
Cheers to you.
I'm in drink number 10.
- Okay.
- And you?
Go have a drink.
You won't remember
this conversation?
- No.
- Cool.
- Okay.
- All right, thanks.
Give you a hand?
Sure.
Cool.
I've never actually
done dishes before.
It's mostly the drying portion.
Uh... perfect timing.
Hang on.
Classic.
I'm sorry,
I didn't get to hear
the rest of your story earlier.
Do you really wanna know?
Yeah.
I do.
- Hey.
- Hi, how're you doing?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
- They're so cute.
- Yeah.
What was it like, having a baby?
For me, it was amazing.
It was the best experience
I had in my life.
I had a natural birth.
- You got a natural birth?
- Naturally, at home.
No medication.
Was it painful?
Yeah, but it's not...
pain. It's kind of strength.
You have a lot of strength
inside of you.
You can probably
pass that strength
right under her.
I hope so.
This is a little tight.
Thank you very much.
All right.
Somebody's jealous.
I think it ties it together.
It's perfect, especially with
the feather in your hair.
- I know.
- Yeah.
♪ Sandy, you're a bitch
♪ No one is gonna
Want you, Sandy
♪ After what you did
♪ No one is gonna
Want you, Sandy
♪ After what you did
I think so.
♪ Nobody likes you, Sandy
♪ Sandy, you're a bitch
♪ No one is gonna
Want you, Sandy
♪ After what you did
♪ I hope you're real
Proud of yourself
♪ I hope you're real proud of
What you did
♪ Nobody likes you, Sandy
♪ Sandy, you're a bitch
♪ I said nobody's
Gonna want you, Sandy
♪ Nobody's gonna
Want you, Sandy
♪ After what you did
♪ I hope you're real proud of
What you did
♪ Sandy
♪ You've been a bad girl
You've been real bad, Sandy.
And I'm about to tell you...
Tell me. Tell me.
That you're not gonna
come around here no more.
♪ I hope you're real proud of
What you did ♪
Yeah!
It looks like a spaceship.
It's a wedding gift,
but I've never played it.
- Oh!
- Let me see.
It looks like a spaceship.
You play with the ring.
You don't have to ring them.
- Wow!
- Whoa!
The virgin.
That sounds cool.
Mmm.
I think we're gonna
take that queue as well, and...
- Head back home. You ready?
- I'm ready, yeah.
You guys wanna take this?
No, hang on to it for the night.
- Yeah?
- Okay.
We'll do another duet.
Absolutely.
Hello? Who's that?
Come in. Are you all right?
Amelia's water... My...
my wife, her water broke.
We're having a baby.
- Oh, my God.
- Are you kidding?
Her water broke hours ago.
I don't know what to do.
Okay, Someone...
Okay, you need Jen.
You guys calm down.
It's okay. Tony...
I tried to call 911
and there's no cabs outside,
- and I need help.
- Okay.
- I don't know what to do.
- I'm on my head.
- First labor takes a while.
- It's not her first labor.
- What?
- Wait, who else is with her?
- It's just me.
- Okay. Okay, Tony. Okay.
- I can help. I can help.
- Thank you.
- Okay. I'm gonna get Jen ready,
- and then we'll come down, okay?
- Okay.
Barbara had a home birth.
She would know what to do.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, good idea.
Yeah, go for it.
- Are you okay?
- I'm too drunk to do this.
You're not too drunk.
We'll get you some coffee.
We can go downstairs and get
like, the pour-over.
Okay, okay. Go get your stuff.
I don't really know what to do.
Towels, clean towels,
as many as possible.
- Look for a few towels.
- They're in the back.
And also, we will need some,
like, piece of plastic bag
- for the floor.
- Trash bags.
Yeah, or you know,
I saw in the bathroom
that you have this curtain.
- The shower curtain?
- Yeah.
We also... We'll...
maybe a bowl...
Like this?
I think that, that's the basics.
As clean as possible.
Do you need, um, like...
scissors or knife or...
Jen. Jen, what are you doing?
My stethoscope.
I can't find my stethoscope.
Okay. We're gonna find it.
We're gonna find it, okay?
She always take my stuff
for her acting class.
I don't have them.
I don't have my things.
She needs to go to the hospital.
We don't have
that option right now.
I don't know how to do this.
I have never
practically done this.
My rotations have never been...
I've never delivered
a real life baby.
- It's just books.
- Okay, I know, I know.
That's what it feels like,
but you know what to do. Right?
I cheated. I...
I cheated on a couple of exams.
That's what this is about...
Remember when I had
the panic attack
in the bathroom,
and you stayed with me
for three hours,
even once I got my breath back.
That's just common sense.
- Everybody would do that.
- No, they wouldn't.
You didn't learn that
in a book or anything.
That's just you.
That's who you are.
It doesn't matter
if you studied it or not.
You know what to do.
You always know what to do.
My gym bag.
- What?
- My gym bag. It's in my gym bag.
No, I don't think
you have any here.
- Okay.
- You guys will be okay.
Oh, yes. Of course.
Thank you.
- Want one?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna listen to
your little baby now, okay?
That's good. That's good.
You're doing good.
We're really close.
She's coming to meet you.
She's possibly doing great.
That's good. That's good.
Awesome girl. Good girl,
good girl. Bear down.
- You are a great pusher.
- Yeah.
- You're great at this.
Bear down. Good girl,
good girl. Bear down.
You got this. You got this.
Nice push.
Nice push, Mom. Nice push.
Push.
On this next one,
I need you to do a double push.
You're gonna push,
take a little inhale
and double push, okay?
- Okay.
- Very good.
Very good.
Push.
Good Mama, push, push,
push, push.
Good Mama, push!
There she is.
How did it go?
Good.
Everything's good.
Everyone's good. Mom's good.
Baby's good.
They named her Ava.
You did?
Yeah, we delivered a baby.
She delivered a baby.
I'm going to bed.
Get some sleep.
- Good night.
♪ Gotta burn to emerge
They say
♪ But I've burned and burned
♪ And my ashes
Turned into nothing
♪ For so long
♪ Long is the road less traveled
♪ I heard when will I love
♪ That I can feel it
Turning around
♪ Like a Phoenix
From the ground
♪ We shake when we burn
♪ The things we
Don't wanna return
♪ And I've spent too long
♪ Choosing not to be strong
♪ Like a Phoenix from the ash
♪ I can feel my heart
Growing back
♪ Tryin' to stay open
♪ Even without closure
♪ Trying to getting on
Not knowing
♪ Which road to take on
♪ Like a Phoenix from the ash
♪ I can feel my heart
Growing back
♪ Mmm
♪ We shake when we burn
♪ Don't forget to take
♪ The love you've earned
♪ Look for the
Embers in the end
♪ They're the ones who keep you
♪ Ooo
♪ Keep you
♪ I'll keep you...
♪ Ooo
♪ Like the Phoenix
♪ In your heart
♪ I'm immune to the waves
And the seasons
♪ I'm immune to the waves Constitution
♪ I'm amazed at man
♪ Still I stand
♪ Don't hold me back
Don't hold me back
♪ I got so much in me
♪ I got so much to give
♪ I'm underground
I'm in the sky
♪ I'm on the ceiling
♪ I make it rain
I'll take the blame
♪ I fake the feelings
♪ I'm New York City
♪ One day
♪ If I take you somewhere
♪ Will we gather by the fire?
♪ That she holds in the sky
And meet me there
♪ I'll always keep more
♪ New York City
♪ Can you hear me?
♪ I am New York City