(WAVES BREAKING)
OFFICER 1: You two,
cover the front.
Barnes and Williams,
you got the rear.
OFFICER 2: Right.
(DOG BARKING)
(SIGHS) What? What...
(BANGING ON DOOR)
OFFICER 1: Open your door!
Police Department!
(SIGHS)
If there's no answer,
knock it down.
Open the door! Police!
Open your door!
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Police Department!
Kick it!
Come on. What the...
OFFICER 1: Freeze!
(OFFICERS SHOUTING)
Hands up over
your head! Now!
ROCKFORD: Oh, what... What...
Against the wall.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go. Spread 'em.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Put your hands together here,
now. Spread 'em a little further.
Anything you say or do will be
used against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an
attorney. If you cannot afford one,
one will be
provided for you...
Hold your hands
still, now.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Ah, you guys
never learn, do you?
How many multi-million
dollar settlements
do you think this
town's gonna go for?
What's that
supposed to mean?
Well, you ought to be
able to figure that one out.
I'm suing your butts off,
collectively and individually.
On what grounds?
Well, how about false arrest? These
stormtroopers had to be your idea, Chapman.
Oh, Diehl,
has this guy gone completely over the edge?
I mean, when did I qualify
for the Ten Most Wanted?
My office.
(SIGHS)
False arrest,
huh? You know something? You're full of it.
You never commit any crimes,
but you always wind up at the booking desk.
What is that,
coincidence or what?
More like sloppy
police work.
You know something? You're 90% mouth,
aren't you?
Look, let's just do this
and get the hell out of here.
When I get rousted out of
bed in the middle of the night,
it tends to put me
in a really lousy mood.
(LAUGHS) Well, you can
imagine the mood I am in.
I not only got rousted,
I got patted down.
Try that
at 3:00 in morning.
You know the drill,
Rockford. You've been busted often enough.
You could have been
carrying a concealed weapon.
Yeah? Where?
Any other complaints?
Well, how about malicious
destruction of property? Hmm?
I really ought to... You know,
I don't expect the department
to turn out
charm school graduates,
but the primates Chapman
sent out there,
they not only busted the door locks,
they busted the doors.
You can teach 'em the
entire California Penal Code,
you can't teach 'em
a little patience?
Is that it?
Not even close.
You'll get all
the particulars
when my attorney files
all the appropriate papers.
McENROE: Attorney? CHAPMAN:
You can't threaten us, Rockford.
DIEHL: Sure, he can.
What's he got to lose?
Did I mention that I have a
breakfast meeting with the Chief?
Is it my turn now?
Well, these cuffs
are put on,
so I don't have any feeling
in my left hand.
I think it was deliberate.
(EXCLAIMS) Who would
want to hurt you?
Take 'em off.
Sir. Sir, we ought to keep the
cuffs on him till we put him in a cell.
What's he gonna do,
make a break for it?
If he does, Officer,
you shoot him.
(STUTTERING) That
breakfast with the Chief,
there was some talk
about a lawsuit,
I mean,
a slide presentation.
I really ought to
look into it.
Is it okay if
I get a cup of coffee?
(SNICKERS)
It'll just give you something
else to complain about.
Sure, go ahead,
help yourself.
(PHONE RINGING)
Commander Diehl. Yes.
Uh-huh, I see. ... Well...
(MOUTHING) He's right behind...
Yeah, write it up.
I gotcha.
Chapman,
that was forensics, and...
Hey,
you. What do you think you're doing?
Sir?
What the hell are you wearing?
You working under cover?
Oh, no,
I'm not on duty, sir.
I just came by the station
because, uh, well, I heard.
DIEHL: You heard we ran in your friend,
Rockford, right?
He is a friend of yours,
isn't he?
BECKER: Well,
that's a loosely used word, sir.
I mean,
we run into people all the time.
That doesn't mean that
they're your friends.
You are in his
"Known associates" file.
Oh.
Maybe we can use you in there.
He might relax with you,
maybe open up faster.
You comfortable with that?
Fine.
Sir, what is he doing here?
They're friends, you know.
What the hell did you
do this time?
You got Chapman
and Diehl on your case.
Well, I didn't do anything.
Not that it seems to matter.
What the hell
are you doing here?
What kind of a dumb
question is that? I work here.
Well, not at this time
of the morning,
and not dressed like that,
you don't.
The sergeant at the booking
desk knows we're friends.
Everybody in this department
knows we're friends. Chapman, Diehl...
I'm a "Known associate”.
Officially, I'm in the computer. Once in,
it stays in.
There's no getting it out!
I can feel my career hitting
that "Do not resuscitate" wall.
Is there an answer to my
dumb question in all that?
The sergeant at the desk
called me at home.
He woke me up.
Oh, what a shame.
I slept in till 3:00.
Okay, Rockford,
we're all tired.
Maybe we can try
and wrap this up.
Wrap what up?
Nobody's told me
what you dragged me
down here for.
Well, maybe somebody would
if you'd shut up for five minutes.
You been Mirandized?
I know what my rights are.
Nothing is easy
with you, is it?
I've been Mirandized.
Fine. So, we'll start
with something simple.
The bad blood between you and Bud Monckton,
when did that start?
Is that who's behind this?
I should have guessed. It
has his paw prints all over it.
There's no bad blood.
CHAPMAN: You attacked him at the
Goodhew Awards a couple of months ago.
He attacked me.
That's not what I heard.
Well, you heard it wrong,
Chapman. You always do.
I would say it's your big failing,
but you have so many.
What about the altercation
that took place last Thursday?
That Monckton's fault, too?
Yes. Every time I run into the guy,
he's all over me.
He keeps accusing me
of trying to steal his clients.
That's what happened
last Thursday.
I show up on what he considers his turf,
and he went ballistic.
Were you trying
to steal his client?
Forget he said that.
He's sorry.
I'm what?
Sorry.
Right, we covered that.
So, you showed up at
Monckton's workplace because...
Well, about 10 days ago,
I took a job that had nothing
to do with Bud Monckton.
Yeah, I hate paperwork.
But every once in a while,
well, I was playing Catch Up.
ROCKFORD: Oh, Bobby.
(LAUGHING) Bobby. Hey. Hey,
no, I'm not ducking you.
No. Hey, hey, yeah. Bobby,
yeah, I know what I said. Yeah.
Yeah. Hey, look, Bobby, I can't give
you what I don't have. I'm tapped out.
(CAR DOOR CLOSING)
Well, yes,
I know it's been three and a half weeks.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR) Listen,
if it makes you feel any better,
I got at least a half
a dozen other people
who've been waiting for
payment for over two months.
Yeah. Bobby? Bobby?
Oh, damn it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Hey...
Your door is locked. I
thought it was just stuck,
but I couldn't budge it,
and I'm a lot stronger than I look.
I do weight training. Not to
bulk up. Hector would hate that.
Actually, I'd hate that, too. I don't
think it's attractive on a woman,
all those muscles.
Oh, I'm talking too much,
aren't 1?
(STAMMERING) It's
because I'm so nervous.
I've never done this
sort of thing before.
You probably don't think so
because you do it all the time,
but from my side,
it's very scary.
Oh, it's a good idea
having a kitchen.
That way, you don't have to go
out to lunch, maybe miss a client.
You could offer someone
a cup of coffee.
Oh, would you care... Oh,
not for me, thank you.
I try to limit my caffeine.
Probably a good idea.
But... But I keep it at home.
I offer it to my friends.
I'm no fanatic.
You know, this is...
This is really nice. It's very warm,
very comfortable.
It's not like an office at all. It
feels more like somebody's home.
It is somebody's home.
Mine.
Oh, my God.
You're not James Rockford?
Oh, I wrote down the wrong
address. I'm really sorry.
I don't know what to say,
I... Wait. No, no, no, no, no.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's the right address.
I'm Jim Rockford,
and this is my office and my home.
Oh. Now,
why don't you come right over here?
(CHUCKLES) You sit down.
Make yourself comfortable.
Tell me what
I can do for you.
Randy said you were
easy to talk to.
He said he felt like
he'd known you for years.
Randy?
Randolph Silvero.
Silvero Micro-CompuMeg.
He's a family friend. He
told us what you did for him.
He said you were
very discreet.
That's the most important thing for me,
discretion.
Of course, with me,
it's not like it was with Randy.
It's not industrial espionage. But
you take other cases, don't you?
Not unless I know
the client's name.
Oh, I... I'm...
I'm really sorry.
(STUTTERING) I'm not
always like this.
It's just that lately,
I've been...
I'm Linda. Linda Gustavo.
How do you do?
Mrs. Hector Gustavo.
Randy told us
what you charge,
so we don't have
to talk about that.
I'll pay you for a week in advance,
not including expenses,
since we don't know
what they are.
If it takes more than a week,
I'll be happy to pay you more.
Is that all right?
Oh, sounds fine.
(STUTTERING) I just have to
know what you want me to do.
(LAUGHING) You know,
is it some sort of investigation?
Investigation.
Yes. Yes.
(STUTTERING)
This is very difficult.
(SIGHING)
(STAMMERING) I...
I'm just going to say it.
I'm going to put it out there
and I'm going to deal with it.
I am not going to cry.
Thank you.
I think my husband is
sleeping with another woman.
No, I don't think,
I know he's sleeping with her.
Mrs. Gustavo...
He comes home, he smells from her perfume,
his clothes, his hair.
(SOBBING)
Do you know how long it's
been since we made love?
Before, he couldn't
take his hands off me.
I even know who it is.
All I need is proof.
Mrs. Gustavo...
(SIGHS)
...you don't know how
difficult this is for me, but,
much as I'd like to help you,
I don't handle domestic cases.
It isn't a question of money.
I know. You think if you give me proof,
I'm gonna go crazy,
and I'm gonna kill my
husband. I 'am not...
Well, no, I... ...going to kill my husband,
Mr. Rockford.
I am not even going to kill
that tramp from the office.
He's going to fire her
and never see her again.
I have been married
for 12 years.
Do you think I am going to let Eleanor
Hooperman just walk off with Hector?
Mrs. Gustavo,
when I went into this business years ago,
I made just one promise
to myself.
No domestic cases.
Now, I've never broken that promise,
and I don't intend to now.
No matter how much
I'd like to help you...
No, no. Don't do that.
Now, don't do that.
That's way too much. There are
some very good people out there.
They're easy to
talk to, discreet.
I'd be happy to refer someone.
Why don't I
just kill myself?
I'd rather be dead
than run all over town,
telling total strangers
about my sex life.
I'm a total stranger.
No, you're not.
You know Randy.
Now, you said
you weren't going to cry.
(CRYING) I can't help it.
You took Randy's money.
Why won't you take mine?
You don't know how difficult
you're making this for me.
(STUTTERING) I mean,
as much as I'd like to help you,
this just isn't my kind
of case. Not at all.
(PHONE RINGING)
That's not your
kind of case?
Sure, it is.
What'd you do for
the lady, Rockford?
Break into some
cheesy hotel room
with a photographer,
catching Gustavo in flagrante delicto?
Yeah, me and Lyle Talbot,
we work as a team.
Does he have to be here?
Yes.
Can we get some
decent coffee in here?
Good idea.
So, you got hired
by Linda Gustavo
to get the goods
on her old man.
And you did this
by following him?
Well, I followed him, yeah.
I also got a job at his record company,
Felicidad Records.
Which is where you had the
confrontation with Bud Monckton.
No, which is where he had
his confrontation with me.
The guy's paranoid. I...
He runs security for them.
He thought I was trying
to steal the account.
I was just trying to check up
on Gustavo from the inside.
So, I wrote a few glossy
letters of recommendation.
I got exactly the job
I was shooting for.
It gave me unquestioned access
to the whole complex,
and at the same time
it rendered me invisible.
RECEPTIONIST: Felicidad Records. I'm sorry,
she's not in...
So, did you finish the copy? He's
going to be asking for it, you know.
It's on his desk.
He'll probably want me to
rewrite it before lunch. Again.
ELEANOR:
He's a perfectionist.
STRINGER:
He's a control freak.
Yeah. That, too.
I'm going to say no.
Hey, I'm the writer. I'm not
going to let him ruin my work.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Come in, come in.
Sit down.
I've been going over your copy,
Sam. It's just not there.
You know,
there's no juice in it. No excitement.
What you hear in the music,
that's what I want in the words.
I don't know how you can
listen to this and give me that.
I'll have a rewrite for you
when you get back from lunch.
(LAUGHING)
Did I ask for a rewrite? Hmm?
I think that's your
problem right there.
You rewrote the life
out of it. Put it away.
Go back to it in a couple
of days. See what happens.
Look, I know it seems like I've
been beating up on you a lot lately.
Hell, I've been beating up
on everyone.
It's because we've finally
got a shot with this one.
It's gonna take off,
I know it.
You're that sure?
Have I ever said anything like that before,
in all these years?
I think the whole Latin thing
is going to explode.
Go mainstream,
like it did in the '40s.
Carmen Miranda, a major star.
Cugat, he was making movies,
playing clubs,
selling records,
selling chihuahuas.
In the '40s, if it was Latin,
it was happening.
My God, listen to this.
(VOLUME INCREASES)
You got a bunch of monks
all over the charts!
You think that's not
going to go platinum?
(MUSIC STOPS)
(REMOTE CLATTERS)
Come on, let's eat.
Can we go someplace
besides Rex's?
(LAUGHING) People fight
to get into that place,
and you got a problem with it.
You know, executives
all over the world
take courses on how
to avoid trouble.
They vary their
work schedules,
vary the routes
they travel.
So? I do that.
You also have lunch at the same time,
at the same restaurant,
and at the same table
every single day.
If anyone, anyone,
wanted to get you,
they wouldn't have to set
up some elaborate ambush.
They could just wait
for you at Rex's.
Nobody wants to get me.
Unless it's someone who
bought one of our earlier releases.
(SIGHS) My God,
20 years of nose flutes and clam shells,
and Amazonian
goatherd choirs.
Get the baseboards, okay?
Last guy did a lousy job.
And be out of here
by the time we get back.
(DOOR CLOSING)
Rockford. What the hell
are you doing here?
(EXHALES)
A remedial reading course would
open up whole new worlds for you, Bud.
Oh, sure, you're building
maintenance, right?
What am I, stupid?
I never swing
at the easy ones.
You can tell me,
or you can tell the cops.
I'm gonna call 'em.
Well, good idea.
I'll tell 'em what I'm doing here,
you tell 'em what you're doing.
What I'm doing is security.
Oh, you're going to have a
hard time making that one fly.
Security doesn't hang
bugs on the boss.
Why'd you say that?
Did you find something?
I don't have to find a bug to know
that you've hung 'em all over the place.
It's your M.O., Bud.
Anybody that knows you
knows that.
You know, being stupid and predictable
isn't all it's cracked up to be.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ROCKFORD SHOUTING)
How about we go back
to that bad blood
that didn't exist
between the two of you?
You never liked Monckton,
did you, Rockford?
What's to like?
He's a tree with lips.
He's also dead.
You entered his house
at 9:45 p.m.
A disturbance was heard
at 10:30 p.m.
The coroner confirms that
as the probable time of death.
The security camera
never clocked you out.
Look, Monckton called me and
asked me to meet him at his place.
He said he had
some information.
He wanted to make
a deal with me.
When I got there,
the place was empty, so I left.
You expect us to believe that?
Of course not. It's the
truth. I want my attorney.
Sure, fine. Becker can make
the call for you, if you like.
Would you do that, Dennis?
Would you tell her to
get over here, right away?
Who? Kit?
My ex-wife? What the
hell's the matter with you?
Why would I want to
drag her into this?
Beth. Call Beth.
Beth?
Yeah. Call her.
Here, use mine.
You mind telling me
the cause of death?
Like he doesn't know.
He was shot.
BECKER: This is
Lieutenant Becker.
I'd like to have the phone number
for Elizabeth, or Beth Van Sant.
Maiden name, Davenport.
Oh, the listing might be under
her husband's name. Uh...
Roger.
Roger Van Sant.
Yeah, you can try Beverly Hills,
Brent wood, Bel Air,
Holmby...
Pasadena.
Pasadena, even.
Yeah, I'll hold.
What caliber weapon
do you own, Rockford?
.38.
Where is this weapon kept?
(SIGHS)
Lieutenant?
In the cookie jar.
(SCOFFS)
What?
In the cookie jar, sir.
(LAUGHS)
We got motive.
We got opportunity.
And once we pick up the murder weapon,
we got you.
Right to the wall
with me, huh, Dennis?
Don't start. Beth's
waiting in the squad room.
Thanks. No, thanks a lot,
since my right to consult with an attorney
is recognized under
the law, but thanks.
Knock it off, okay? There's
nothing for me to feel guilty about,
so don't even try.
You told them
I carry a .38.
Like that information's
not in the computer?
My cookie jar
isn't in the computer.
At least, it wasn't.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Hi.
We can go to my office,
but I thought you could
use some coffee first.
Thanks, Dennis. Do you believe that moron,
Chapman's
trying to hang
a murder rap on me?
Punching people out all the
time? What the hell you expect?
Oh, when did I become
the town bully?
Monckton's the guy that has
a problem in that area, not me.
Had a problem.
What'd you do to your hair?
Nothing. I just
let it go natural.
Well, you don't have curly hair,
you have straight hair.
You've always
had straight hair.
I used to have it straightened,
Jim. I don't any more.
I liked it straight.
I didn't.
You used to wear suits.
Oh, you don't like
what I have on?
I didn't say that. No, no,
what you have on is fine.
(CHUCKLING) Well,
it's a little casual,
considering the
circumstances, but...
You wake me up in
the middle of the night...
ROCKFORD: Oh, come on,
it's hardly the middle of the night, Beth.
It is for those of us who
didn't get to bed until 2:30.
We ought to take this
into the office.
After four years of not
hearing one word from you,
I get a call from Dennis saying
big surprise, you're in trouble.
For privacy.
I drag myself down here,
don't ask me why,
old habits die hard, I guess.
And what do I get?
"Thanks? Nice to see you?"
No, I get a critique on my hair
style and a dress code alert.
Guys, we're starting
to draw a crowd.
CHAPMAN: Becker...
Beth... No, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Now, I know it's been a while,
but it hasn't been any four years.
Four years,
practically to the day.
How do I know that?
Because I took you out to lunch.
A very nice lunch to celebrate
the publication of my first book.
We had champagne,
which neither of us like, particularly,
but it seemed appropriate. I gave
you an autographed copy of the book,
and that, as they say,
was that.
(SIGHS) That was
four years ago?
When it actually made the
New York Times Best-Seller List,
I thought,
"Oh, he's gotta call now."
It was on the list
for over a year.
Nineteen months,
for the sake of accuracy.
My second book
did even better.
(STUTTERING) I don't...
I don't know what to say.
You've got a right
to be sore.
Hey, it's history.
Well, Beth,
where are you going?
Home. I don't practice law any
more. I haven't practiced it in years.
Well, isn't it kind of
like riding a bicycle?
You can't leave me now.
You're good.
I need good. I need your knowledge,
your expertise.
And?
Your ability to carry me
for a couple of months.
Four, tops. You know,
I gotta put my trailer back together.
That's gonna take
what little I have.
I want you to file a separate
suit against this department
for malicious destruction
of property. Major damages.
Flattered as I am, let me put
this so you'll understand it, Jim.
If I were practicing law,
which I am not,
it would be
a polar day in hell
before I'd ever
represent you again.
And I don't like
your hair either.
Where's she going?
Well, it doesn't matter.
We don't need her anyway,
right now.
Why don't we need her?
Not that we have her.
Your .38 wasn't there,
so they decided not to charge you.
At least, not yet. Too
circumstantial without the weapon.
What do you mean
it wasn't there?
They looked in the cookie
jar. They found Oreos.
Did they look
under the Oreos?
These are trained police officers. Of
course, they looked under the Oreos.
It wasn't there. Go home.
You know, this would go a lot
faster if you'd stop trying to help me.
Well, tell me what to do.
The temptation is strong.
Look, I do this all the time.
You leave me alone for a
few minutes and I'll have it up.
Look good as new.
It is new.
(GRUNTS) Well,
the cops busted it.
If you ask me,
they ought to pay for it.
These things are expensive.
I noticed.
What makes them special?
Anybody ever tell 'em,
"You bust it, you buy it?"
Probably not.
Want some coffee, George?
Nah.
JESS: May I have a cup?
Jess Wilding. I don't know
if you remember me or not.
Nobody forgets
the IRS, Miss Wilding.
Come on in. Take inventory.
Slap a lien on something.
You've made a few changes.
Not all of them
were my idea.
(SIGHS)
Is that going to be it
for the small talk?
I'm not here on business.
What else is there?
There's personal.
It's so amazing.
You could charge
for this view.
I don't.
Why are you so hostile?
(LAUGHS)
You're the IRS,
you tell me.
It can't be the first time
you've had this reaction.
Oh, you still can't be sore
about that audit I gave you.
I was more than fair with you.
Fair? You disallowed deductions that
are key to the operation of my business.
What? Dinner and the Lakers
with Dennis Becker?
Lieutenant Becker.
He's a cop.
He's a friend.
Can't wait to tell him that's now
common knowledge on a federal level.
You're not at all like
your father, you know.
After I did your audit,
he took me to dinner.
He said that I'd worked hard
and I earned a good supper.
Yeah, sounds like Rocky.
I was in Switzerland
when he...
I---
I didn't hear about his
death until I came back home.
I bought him a cuckoo clock.
You know, a little one.
I really think he would've
gotten a kick out of that.
You two stayed in touch?
I didn't know that.
Rocky never mentioned it.
I'd like to visit his grave,
if you don't mind.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Of course.
I'll write the directions
out for you.
No, I don't mean that.
I'd like you to
go there with me.
I think Rocky would want that.
God, I'm going to miss him.
Are you all right?
(SNIFFS) Yeah. Sorry.
I swore I wouldn't do this.
Well, you and Rocky must've
spent quite a lot of time together.
I'm surprised I never
ran into you at the ranch.
Well,
you always used to call before you came up,
so when I'd get a call from Rocky saying,
"Can we make it next weekend?"
I knew it was because
you were there.
I don't think he wanted
to share you.
Or you.
I got a few of those
phone calls, too.
You're having trouble
with that, aren't you?
with the idea that Rocky
could have a relationship
with somebody,
and you wouldn't know
anything about it.
Hey, it's none
of my business.
You know, Rocky didn't
just exist in a vacuum.
You know, he was more
than just your father.
Isn't it great you turned
up to point that out?
I might never have figured
that out on my own.
Rocky was not
a secretive man.
He was an open book.
Well,
looks like you missed a couple of chapters.
Yeah, well keeping me out of the
loop wouldn't have been his idea.
"Keeping you
out of the loop"?
Oh, forget it. I don't even know
why I'm trying to talk to you.
You're certainly not
anything like your father.
Yeah. Well, neither are you.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
Fresh start?
I'd like that.
There's a car following us.
Been with us since
the top of the hill.
Well, he doesn't have much
choice. There's only one road out.
That's what I thought. But when I stopped,
he stopped, too.
So what are you going to do?
Lose him.
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
He's driving like a crazy person!
He came that close to hitting me!
He's going south
on Sepulveda.
You better get the cops out
here before he kills somebody!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(CARS HONKING)
(SCREAMS)
Hang on.
(CAR BRAKES SQUEALING)
(LAUGHING)
You're good.
MAN: Hey, watch it!
Damn!
What the hell do you think you're
doing? You trying to kill somebody?
What, you think I don't
know what you've been doing?
You think I wasn't
gonna find out?
Don't do that.
Mr. Gustavo, if you'll just...
Who put you up to this?
Get back in the car, Jess.
What should I do? What should
I do? I said don't shove me.
Now, I want names, damn it!
Don't shove me, damn it!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SIREN WAILING)
Hit him, Jim!
Just hit him!
Get back in the car, Jess.
Hit him!
Get back in the car!
LEWIS ON PA: You two,
break it up. Step away from the vehicle.
Okay, everybody settle down.
You all right, sir?
Why don't you ask me
if I'm all right?
You all right?
Yeah.
I'm gonna file assault
charges against this man.
You want to file charges? You're
the reason for this whole mess.
Officer, he was following us.
His car's in front of yours.
He's been following me
for over a week.
You ask him
if that's not true.
You ask him if he hasn't been questioned
in the death of one of my employees,
if he isn't the
number one suspect.
It's a long story.
Maybe I struck first.
You bet you struck first.
I'm a witness, Officer.
Well, if I did,
it was in self-defense.
I was afraid
he was carrying a gun.
Check the car.
Allow me.
I mean, for all I know,
I may be next on his list.
The police officer
I spoke with,
a Captain Chapman,
he said they've been trying
to put him away for years.
Look what I found.
(SIGHS)
MARTINEZ: You have the
right to remain silent.
Anything you say, can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
You have the right
to an attorney.
If you cannot afford one,
one will be provided for you...
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Excuse me, I wonder
if you could help me.
I'm looking for
Lieutenant Becker.
He's not in his office.
Becker? No,
ma'am. He's in Commander Diehl's office.
(CHUCKLES) Been there a
lot lately. I think he's in trouble.
(LAUGHING)
They seem quite busy today.
Mmm.
Are you here to confess?
Excuse me?
Well, I don't
mean to pry, but,
I have been here for 45 minutes,
and you just came in.
I'm an attorney.
Oh, I don't need one.
I did it.
Oh.
(CHUCKLES)
(SNICKERS)
(STAMMERING) I'm just...
I'm just going...
(MAN SHOUTING)
Bye.
Hi, Sally. SALLY: Good morning,
Commander.
I may have to get myself
a larger office.
Did you get
everybody's statement?
No, sir, I was
waiting for you.
Thank you.
Oh, you've been spending so much time here,
you're practically family.
So, where do we start?
Well, could we start with a
couple of industrial strength aspirin?
I have the worst headache.
You're a real chronic complainer,
aren't you, Rockford?
You always gotta find
something to bellyache about.
Do you have an aspirin?
I don't get headaches.
Yeah? Well, you give 'em.
Jess?
Sorry.
Dennis?
Becker doesn't have any aspirin,
Rockford. Nobody here has any aspirin.
Could we please
just get on with this?
I can lay it out for you in very
simple terms, Commander.
He was following me.
Right away, that's a lie!
He followed us.
I was following them
because he was following me.
You know, believe it or not,
that actually makes sense.
HECTOR: After what happened
to Bud Monckton
and Mr. Rockford's
involvement in that...
I had no involvement in that.
I wanted to know why
I was being followed.
I demanded to know
who hired him.
Your wife hired him.
What?
Damn it, Chapman,
that's inexcusable.
But... That's
privileged information.
You can't just blat out something
that was told to you in confidence.
My wife?
Yeah. Yeah, Linda.
Uh, 52", 5'3",
exotic looking.
I'm not married.
I've never been married.
Your friend, Randy Silvero,
recommended me.
I don't know any
Randy Silvero.
Randy Silvero's not a
figment of my imagination.
He's the CEO of a Fortune
500 company. Check it out.
Mmm.
You say you don't know
who Linda Gustavo is?
Well, neither do I. But
she claims to be your wife.
She even overpaid me
to work for her.
I've never done
a domestic case before.
Looks like
you still haven't.
I would like to know why I
get stuck babysitting you.
It's getting out of hand.
They see you, they think me.
It's like we're joined
at the hip or something.
They could've kept you
in a holding cell.
Are you listening to what's
coming out of your mouth?
Put me in a holding cell?
Well, they could
teach you something.
At least, you'd realize that you
could stay out of trouble for 24 hours.
Dennis, I am trapped in
a Kafkaesque nightmare.
Don't rap me across the
knuckles. Get me some aspirin.
What is this,
a Christian Science Reading Room?
I'd think twice about ticking off the
one friend you have in the department.
Your timing is
not real good.
Hi, Sally.
Hi, Lieutenant.
Oh! Hey, Becker.
How's it going?
Never better.
Oh. That's not what I heard.
(LAUGHING)
What he heard?
Oh, he doesn't
know anything, Dennis.
Don't bet on it. He's always
sucking up to the brass.
Hey, Pete, get Sally
a cup of coffee
and tell her
I'll be a little while.
Sure.
Two sugars.
She's a regular.
Well, so am.
You couldn't have had Pete pick up
a couple of aspirin while he was at it?
Would you knock it off? You're
getting to sound like a real junkie.
Do you know that bees
can die of loneliness?
Well, they can.
Do you have any idea how
long I've been waiting for you?
What are you doing here?
I thought I was
your attorney.
I thought you weren't.
Well, I could hardly
leave you unrepresented.
Not with the regularity
you're getting hauled in here.
Don't touch those. Those
are the revisions on my book.
I feel like I need
a program to keep up.
It wouldn't help.
So, what happened
this time?
Well, this time,
it seems to be Gaslight,
and I seem to be playing
the Ingrid Bergman role.
Do you have any aspirin?
I don't think so. Were you
in Diehl's office with Becker?
With the gruff
but lovable Chapman.
(STAMMERS) You didn't
make a statement?
Of course, I made a statement. If I didn't
make a statement, I wouldn't be out here.
You didn't sign anything?
I signed the statement.
Without counsel present?
I didn't know I had counsel.
Are you sure you don't
have any aspirin?
I'm going to talk to Diehl.
That really ticks me off.
She made herself right
at home. Did you see that?
It may not be
the corner office,
but it's my office
and my desk.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
I have a theory, Dennis.
My theory is that you,
Beth, everybody has aspirin,
but for some inexplicable reason,
nobody'll cop to it.
Like it has some
sort of stigma attached.
Well, nobody ever
collaborated with the Nazis,
nobody ever spoke,
and now nobody has aspirin.
(EXCLAIMS)
Now, what does
that look like?
|I don't know,
and neither do you.
Yeah, well I say
it's aspirin. Any water?
Hey, I'm not gonna let
you take that... Now, now...
Hey, give me that thing!
Give me that!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
God!
(MUMBLING)
I don't believe you did
something so damn stupid.
(SIGHING)
Shut up, Dennis.
All I want to do
is sit here
and be real quiet
till this stuff kicks in.
What stuff? You don't
even know what you took.
All right,
I talked to Diehl.
He said that Hector Gustavo
will not file assault charges
if you will agree
to psychiatric help.
Go for it.
What happened?
Oh, I'm sorry, Beth.
I guess I should've waited,
but I really had to get
something for this headache.
I told you I didn't
have any aspirin.
Oh, you said you thought
you didn't. I found some.
I took two. You think that's
enough to knock this headache?
I don't know, but you won't have
to worry about water retention.
These are for PMS.
(EXHALES)
That's just great.
Hey, where the hell do
you think you're going?
Hey, come back
here! Hey!
Chapman!
Chapman, I've decided
not to hang around
for the rest of
the inquisition.
I know you're having a hell of a good time,
but I'm not.
I've got a killer headache,
I'm tired,
and I don't enjoy seeing
even a lousy cop like you
make this big
an ass of himself.
(BECKER SCOFFING)
Jim, I really think...
You've got bupkis for a case against me,
and you know it.
So, cut me loose now
or book me.
Okay. I'll book you.
On circumstantial evidence?
Finding my gun
doesn't change anything.
Your own men can testify
it wasn't on my premises
the night of the murder.
They tore my
whole place apart.
And then, all of a sudden,
somebody dials 911,
I get rousted, and where's
the missing weapon?
In the trunk of a car that's
already been searched. It's a setup.
That's what you'd like us to believe,
but we're not buying.
I just got the lab report
on your .38.
It's the murder weapon.
You're right
about one thing.
I am having a hell
of a good time.
(SIGHS)
Bad is never good enough
for you, is it?
You have to make it worse.
You have to alienate people.
You forced him
to lock you up.
Oh, I didn't have to
force him very hard.
Dennis, uh,
I need a favor.
Yeah? So why are
you coming at me?
You're my friend.
You're not going to stop until
they cancel my pension, are you?
Oh, Chapman knows
you're my friend.
You're even officially
recognized by the IRS.
IRS? Yeah. Would you see
that Jess gets back to my place?
She left her car there.
Who's Jess?
Oh, well, she's...
She's a friend of Rocky's.
Rocky? I thought that
you and she were...
I mean, she's a very
attractive woman.
Well, not all of dad's friends
were hideous, Dennis.
Some of them were
quite attractive.
Well, not many, of course.
He was a modest man.
You know what
I'm talking about.
I mean, it's very nice.
I think it's terrific.
A guy gets at
a certain age and, uh,
a lot of people think
it's a 10-4 in his sex life.
Who said anything about sex?
I said she was his friend.
Which is a euphemism, right?
Wrong.
What's the matter with you?
There's nothing the
matter with me, okay?
Rocky was your father.
Nobody likes to think of their parents as,
you know.
I mean, just take a look
at the lady, Jimbo.
All I'm trying to say is that no man,
no matter how old,
is gonna have a woman that
looks like that just as a friend.
I just have to sign
my statement.
They told me I can leave. Do
you want me to wait for you?
(CHUCKLES) Jim.
Do you want me to wait?
You better not.
You could be looking
at 20, 30 years.
They're going to book you?
They can't do that.
He insisted.
I'm looking for
a Captain Chapman.
I'm Chapman.
What can I do for you?
Do you have in your
custody a James Rockford?
I'm Rockford.
Nobody's talking to you.
He's Rockford. I was just
gonna take him to book him.
I'm afraid not.
He's ours now.
What the hell are you talking
about? This man is my prisoner.
No, he was your prisoner.
Millard Weeks, FBI?
Beth!
He's now a prisoner of the
federal government. Let's go.
Beth. Beth.
Okay, Mr. Rockford.
Now, you know the drill.
I have some questions
that I'm going to ask.
I have a few
of those myself.
I'm sure you do.
Are we about ready here?
Couple of more adjustments.
Okay, are you comfortable?
No, but I'm far beyond
worrying about comfort.
Am I looking at
a federal rap here?
If so, what the hell
am I supposed to have done?
Mr. Rockford, why don't
you just cooperate?
And if I don't?
You gonna throw me in jail?
You gotta stand
in line for that.
Well, if you just
tell us the truth,
you have nothing
to worry about.
(LAUGHING)
You had a hard time
saying that with a straight face,
didn't you?
I'm sorry,
but you're gonna have to unhook me.
No, wait, wait,
just a damn minute.
I can't.
|I don't know, maybe it's stress,
sleep deprivation.
Hell, it could be PMS.
The pills worked.
I don't have
a headache any more,
but I'm gonna have
to use the john again.
No. You're just gonna
have to hold it this time.
(SIGHS)
Now, did you know a private
investigator named Bud Monckton?
Monckton? What do the
Feds have to do with him?
Mr. Rockford, this is not
your first polygraph.
You know how this works. I ask a question,
you answer, yes or no,
because that's the
only thing that registers.
Now, did you know a private
investigator named Bud Monckton?
Yes.
Did Mr. Monckton telephone you
on the night of the murder?
You had a bug
on Monckton's phone?
(LAUGHS) You did, you did.
You were wiretapping him.
Mr. Rockford...
Legal or illegal?
(BANGS TABLE)
All right, all right,
all right. Sorry.
Ask again.
Did Mr. Monckton telephone you
on the night of the murder?
Yes.
Did he tell you he had some
information that he wished to sell?
Yes.
Did you go to his residence
per those instructions?
Yes.
And did you purchase
that information?
No.
No?
No. He wasn't home.
You didn't see Bud Monckton?
No.
He's telling the truth.
He didn't sell you anything?
He didn't sell me anything,
he didn't tell me anything.
He wasn't there.
Damn.
Can I go now?
Yeah.
Back to jail.
(EXCLAIMS)
You ever wonder why they
call it the justice system?
I wonder that all the time.
You know, I've never known
anybody named Millard before.
You don't know me.
That's true.
But if I did,
I bet we'd be best friends.
You know, I'm starting to understand
why Chapman wants to put you away.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(YELLING IN SPANISH)
Out, out, out, out!
Vamonos, Vamonos!
(GROANING)
JOSELITO: Now, now, vamanos!
Come on, come on,
come on! Now!
(YELLING IN SPANISH)
Which one of you
is Rockford?
Well, looks like we're gonna
go international. I'm Rockford.
You come with us.
No, he's not going anywhere.
This man is my prisoner.
He's in the custody
of the FBI.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Lose the cuffs.
Nuh-uh.
You want me to do it?
You're liable to get hurt.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(LAUGHING)
Okay, listen up.
This how it goes.
You two are going to
walk over to the bus stop.
When you get there,
you wait.
You take the first bus
that comes along.
That way, you get to live
and you have a real
nice story to tell your kids.
(MEN LAUGHING)
And this is not gonna happen.
I represent the
federal government...
Or I pop you, right here.
Your choice.
You better start
walking, Millard.
I'd go with you, if I could.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Nice suit, gringo.
(ARGUING IN SPANISH)
(SHOUTING)
(SCREAMS)
Do you have a problem with
the concept of private property?
No.
Good choice.
Well, you care for a taquito?
(LAUGHING) A taquito?
Yeah. I haven't eaten
in two days, Jess.
All I've had is about 10
gallons of genuinely bad coffee
that's now starting to
dissolve my stomach lining.
Need something in there
to soak up the acid.
Well, a taquito
should certainly do that.
ROCKFORD: Two taquitos.
So,
on the phone you said you were in trouble.
Yeah, that's me,
master of understatement.
Are you talking new
trouble? More trouble? What?
It doesn't seem possible,
does it?
Thank you.
Jim, the last time
I saw you,
the FBI had you
in handcuffs.
Yeah?
Well, they still do.
What happened?
Well, it's a
little complicated,
but Chapman can now add grand
theft auto to his list of charges.
You didn't steal a car
from the FBI.
It was either that
or be kidnapped.
(LAUGHS)
You know,
Rocky never understood
why you wanted to
be a private investigator.
I have to admit,
I don't either.
I don't know how you go
through that all the time.
You think this is
my average work day?
If it were,
I'd be dead in a week.
Where's the rental?
Around the corner,
end of the block.
It's not a rental.
I'm driving my own car.
That's no good.
I told you to rent one.
I can't leave you
without a car.
Well, I don't intend
to be left.
Then I don't intend
to take you with me.
Damn it, Jess,
I'm running from the cops,
the FBI,
and a cast of thousands.
I... I'm wanted for murder.
You could be charged
with aiding and abetting.
You could be looking
at serious time.
You don't like my terms,
you better call somebody else.
Oh, why don't you call
your friend Becker?
No, no, no, he's a cop.
He'd have to turn
you in, right? Yeah.
Oh. What about
your attorney, Beth?
(SMACKING LIPS) Wouldn't work,
either, would it?
Because as an attorney
she's an officer of the court,
and she'd have to
turn you in, too.
My, my, my, my,
we have a real predicament here, don't we?
I'll drive.
Okay.
JESS: Jim, I really think
this is a mistake.
I mean, the Highway Patrol
is always all over the place.
ROCKFORD: I'm not going
anywhere near the cove.
According to what, I hope,
is reliable information,
Angel should be
right along here.
Here, here it is.
This is a step up
for him.
His last place
had cardboard walls.
You sure he'll take you in?
I'm sure.
(DOORBELL CHIMING)
So, he must be
a really good friend.
Angel? He'd sell me by
the pound if he had a buyer.
He owes me.
Jimmy, what are
you doing here?
Who told you
how to find me?
It was Pastorelli,
wasn't it?
That guy doesn't know the
meaning of keeping his mouth shut.
This is my punishment for
even talking to that creep.
Did anybody see you
come in here?
Nobody saw us.
Okay. Well, just don't
stand around out here
waiting for some gardener
to make a positive I.D.
Get in, get in!
Angel, this is
Jess Wilding.
Who cares? It's not
like you're gonna stay.
ROCKFORD: Angel?
I can't hear you, Jimmy.
Can't, can't hear a word
you're saying.
Don't try to talk me
into nothing.
Every time I get something good going,
you show up.
You're like some giant cat
who's all the time leaving
dead rats on my doorstep.
What am I supposed to say,
thank you?
What do you think, I can't come up
with enough dead rats on my own?
What the hell
are you talking about?
You're hot, man.
You got that wanted smell.
You're all over the tube.
They got an APB out on you.
What, you didn't know that?
Well, that's one dead rat
I ain't getting nowheres near.
Just keeps getting better,
doesn't it?
Where's the TV?
Where is it, Angel?
I won't tell you.
You think I'm gonna let you
squat here watching television
while they're putting your
picture up in the post office?
You're making me an
accessory after the fact.
Well, look on it
as a refreshing change.
You're usually an
accessory before the fact.
Don't make me
call the cops, Jim.
I don't want to do that. It's
not like there's a reward out.
Why don't we
get out of here?
You heard what he said.
If there was a reward
out on you,
he'd turn you in
just like that.
Like you wouldn't. I love
these holier-than-thou types.
Where's the TV?
Is this the channel where
you heard about the APB?
Yeah, they keep cutting in
with these bulletins.
Like, who cares about some
guy nobody ever heard of
killing some other guy
nobody ever heard of?
Where's the remote?
I'll make
a deal with you.
Just hand it over, okay?
You stay here
until the next update,
and then when you're brought up to speed,
you're out of here.
I'll make a deal with you.
You hand me the remote
and I won't break your arm.
You're not making
any friends here today.
You know,
the next time you need me,
I just might not
be there for you.
You're not there
for me now, Angel.
It's on. It's a bulletin.
Turn on the sound.
FEMALE REPORTER ON TV:
...where the vehicle had been abandoned
at Sixth and Alameda.
The discovery was made by a
police officer on routine traffic control.
To recap this
late-breaking story,
private investigator,
James Rockford,
charged with the murder of
fellow investigator, Bud Monckton,
is being sought tonight by both
the Los Angeles Police Department
and the FBI.
At a news conference
held earlier today,
Captain Chapman
had this to say.
The murder apparently
resulted from
a longstanding
and bitter business rivalry.
Both Bud Monckton
and James Rockford
specialized in
low-end divorce work.
There was a history of
violence... How can he say that?
...between the men that ended
tragically... I don't take domestic cases.
...with the death of
Mr. Monckton.
I would ask any citizen
who sees this man
to report the sighting
to the police.
Under no circumstances should
anyone attempt to approach Mr. Rockford.
He may be armed,
and should be considered dangerous.
(REPORTERS CLAMORING ON TV)
That's a terrible picture.
Tell me.
Again, an all points bulletin has
been issued for James Rockford,
primary suspect in
the murder of Bud Monckton.
Now back to our regularly
scheduled programming.
What are we going to do now?
Damned if I know.
(SIGHING)
You all right?
Mmm-hmm.
Just decided to shut up
and be supportive.
You better go home, Jess.
What, and leave you here
all alone to have all this fun?
You know, I'm usually pretty
good at this sort of thing.
I mean, I make
my living at it.
But I don't know what
the hell's going on here.
Every time I think
I'm getting a fix on it,
it morphs into something
completely different.
What are you doing?
Did I say sit down?
Did I say,
make yourself comfortable?
You guys gotta
get out of here.
The welcome mat is not out.
Before you burn
this particular bridge,
you better make damn sure
you're not gonna
need it again,
because when it's gone, Angel,
it's gone for good.
Now, he threatens me.
This from a man who knows that
I'd give him the shirt off my back.
Why not? It doesn't belong to you,
and neither does this house.
All I'm asking for is a few
square feet out of a possible 5,000.
I can't do it, Jimmy.
I mean, it kills me
to say this,
but you guys gotta move it.
The caterer's here.
The caterer?
Nothing fancy. Pigs in the blanket,
a couple of dips.
But they want to
set up out here,
and now that you're among
America's most wanted,
well, they just
ain't gonna get it.
Angel, I wouldn't last
10 minutes out on the street.
Put me in the maid's room,
the garage.
Just till dark.
I'll take my chances then.
Oh, Jimmy!
Hey...
I'll owe you, Angel.
Wouldn't that make
a nice change?
Why me?
Because, deep down,
you're a really nice person.
I know that.
All right. Come on.
Now, when the party
gets rolling,
you got these types
that like to look around,
so I'm gonna
put you in the back
where there shouldn't be
too much foot traffic.
I know it's none of
my business, Angel,
but what are
you doing here?
You're living
like Donald Trump,
you're throwing
catered parties.
You can't afford
to give a party.
I can't afford
not to give one.
Invite the right people.
That's how deals are made.
That's how
careers are born.
Now, when it comes
to the caterer,
well, that's bare bones stuff,
like I said.
What costs is the hard stuff,
but I'm not serving that.
It's just wine and
name brand mineral water,
and Mr. Brophy's never
gonna know it's gone.
Mr. Brophy is
the owner here?
ANGEL: It's one of those
Mr. and Mrs.
You-Can-Go-To-Hell
divorce cases.
You see, Mr. Go-To-Hell said
that I should stay here on the pad
while he's in London
doing business.
He's afraid that Mrs.
You-Can-Go-To-Hell is gonna slip in
and slide off
with the family silver,
and he wouldn't
give her a pickle fork.
Is this where you're putting us,
huh? In this wine cellar?
Yeah, until dark.
That's our agreement.
How are we going to know
when it's dark?
There aren't any
windows in here.
Yeah, and no one'll
see you,
and no one's gonna
blow the whistle.
You want to lay low?
Don't get much lower
than this.
Here, chill.
Have some vino.
Mouton Rothschild?
1961. You're not serving this,
are you?
What's wrong with it?
Well, nothing.
It just goes for seven,
$800 a bottle.
What's the white
he's got?
Conti Montrachet, 1987.
Oh, hey, that only goes
for $800 a bottle on up.
That should go very nicely
with the pigs in a blanket.
Seems to me you've got
enough to worry about
besides what I choose
to serve at my party.
I just worry that
you're serving it
from somebody else's
wine cellar.
You pop just one of those corks,
Angel, it's grand theft.
You just run on down
to the police station,
and then you can
turn me in.
(CHUCKLES) Hey, maybe we can
do time together. Be like old times.
That is, until they drop
a pellet on you.
Chin-chin.
Regular Hallmark card,
isn't it?
Yeah, I'm almost tempted
to open one of these
if I didn't feel so sorry
for Mr. You-Can-Go-To-Hell.
You have no idea the damage
Angel can do without even trying.
Jim, I've been thinking
about this.
The police don't have
an APB out on me.
I'm not on any wanted list.
Why don't you tell me
what you would do
if you could do it,
and let me do it instead?
Oh, no, that's very nice,
I appreciate that, but nothing...
I'm a very capable person.
Capable has nothing
to do with it.
You don't know what
you'd be dealing with here.
Neither do I.
I know it got one man killed
and put me in a frame
I can't seem to break out of.
What are you suggesting?
That we just give up?
No. Well, hey, I don't know.
Damned thing
doesn't make any sense.
Everything makes sense if
you put the pieces together right.
Okay?
What's the first piece here?
Linda Gustavo,
she hires you.
Only it turns out
there is no Linda Gustavo.
You know, I've been
thinking about that.
I mean, she really put on
a convincing performance.
She conned me into taking a
job I swore I'd never go near.
An actress.
Well, enough of those running
around this town that could use a gig.
She could be the one
that dialed 911
and told the cops to look
in the trunk of my car
for the gun
they planted there.
But who hired her, and why?
I don't know.
But my gut feeling tells me it has
something to do with Felicidad Records.
I mean,
there's something weird about that company.
Mmm. Music-business word
is not uncommon.
No, no,
it goes beyond that.
Why is there
a huge framed photograph
of President Reagan
hanging in the executive john?
They're Republicans?
Clandestine Republicans?
Why wouldn't they hang it
in a place of honor?
Why do they have these
satellite photographs
of the rain forest or some damn
thing? And surveillance photos?
I don't know. Really confusing,
isn't it?
I'll tell you something else. There's
enough Latins running around in all this
to do a remake of one
of those old Fox musicals.
Whoever Linda Gustavo is,
she pointed me directly at Hector Gustavo.
Or Felicidad Records. Or...
Bud Monckton.
Yeah, you see? You see,
this whole Bud Monckton thing,
that's a real sour note
in all this.
I mean, the FBI should've never
even heard of a slimeball like Monckton.
They not only knew about him,
he had some information they wanted.
You sure you don't
have any aspirin?
I'm getting my headache
back again.
Forget your headache for now.
We're on to something here.
You want to tell me
what it is?
Bud Monckton.
You didn't know
Hector Gustavo,
you didn't know
Felicidad Records,
but you had a history
with Bud Monckton.
A violent history,
as Chapman would say.
Somebody wanted to off ol' Bud,
for reasons yet to be determined.
Put me in the picture,
you've got the perfect patsy.
That's not bad
for the IRS.
Thank you.
(EXHALES DEEPLY) I've had so
much coming at me from all directions,
I guess I went into
overload and shorted out.
I don't have any answers yet
but I know where to find 'em.
Six for the road. Service
door at the end of the corridor.
Turn out the lights. Adios.
Pigs in a blanket.
(LAUGHING)
Jim, who do you think
would want to kill Monckton?
Anybody that ever met him.
(CHUCKLES) No, you gotta
narrow it down a little bit for me.
Now, whoever
killed Monckton
is the person
who's framing you.
Well, it's beautifully
cold blooded, you know.
I mean, steal my gun,
use it on Monckton,
and plant it back on me.
Nothing personal.
I'm just in it
to take the fall.
That sounded
a lot like admiration.
Well, hey,
you'd almost have to admire anything
that's put together with that
much thought and precision.
It's put together
like a Swiss watch.
There's the murder weapon,
there's videotape
of the two of us wailing away
at each other in the hall,
more video tape from a security
camera at Monckton's house
clocking me in at 9:45, the night of
the murder, and never clocking me out.
Why not?
'Cause I left
by the back door.
Now, either he didn't have a
security camera on that door,
or it wasn't working. But anyway,
gunshots were heard at 10:30.
Now, I have nothing
to prove I was anywhere
but right there
pulling the trigger.
If I make it, I'll call you.
No, no, no, wait.
I want to go with you.
No, no. No, Jess. No,
Jess. Yes, I...
You can't afford to say no.
You don't have a car.
I will, just as soon as I hot
wire whatever's in the garage.
Hey, when you're in
as much trouble as I am,
it's really
kind of liberating.
(SIREN WAILING)
Damn.
CHAPMAN: You know
how lucky you are?
Well, no, Chapman.
Just how lucky am I?
Flight to avoid arrest when
you're wanted for a capital crime?
You could have been shot.
Well, you're handling your
disappointment well, I'll give you that.
You think of yourself as some
kind of great comic, don't you?
Well, you're not funny.
You've never been funny.
Oh, sure I have. You've just
never heard my best material.
I save it for
the dinner crowd.
Come on, let's get this over
with. It's been a long day.
And a busy one.
Two GTAs in six hours,
and the last one has
an interesting history.
It was reported stolen two weeks
ago by a Mrs. Lenore Brophy.
Her husband stole it,
not me.
And I have it
on very good authority,
he wouldn't
give her a pickle fork.
Jim...
We don't need you here,
Lieutenant.
Yes, I was just escorting
Mr. Rockford's counsel...
She knows the way. And when
did it become Mr. Rockford?
What happened to Jimbo?
You're here to see
if you can do anything
for your old buddy,
aren't you?
No, sir. I'm just
escorting Miss Davenport...
Van Sant.
Well, you can't do anything for him,
Becker, so don't even try.
Not if you give a damn about
your career in law enforcement.
Now, take a look. There's
a lesson to be learned here.
You know what
that lesson is?
Try "Crime doesn't pay.”
Hey, uh, thanks for
being here, I...
Nice dress. Maybe
not for this occasion.
Are you going to start
with me again?
I was at a dinner party.
Actually,
I was the hostess.
I had to walk out on my
husband and all my guests.
I used to eat dinner.
All the time.
What'd you serve?
Give me the menu.
Start with the
hors d'oeuvres.
Jim, you getting hysterical or
something? How do you feel?
Like Job
without the boils.
They ought to be popping
out any minute now.
That's 5, 10, 11
12, 25, 35, 36, 37.
That's $12.37.
Make you nervous walking
around with all that cash?
I want you to make a list of everything
that goes into that property envelope,
and ask the sergeant
to sign off on it.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
Listen,
if I could just...
It means, the last time I was
a guest of this establishment,
a silver money clip went into
the envelope and never came out.
That's a lie.
That's not a lie, Chapman.
My complaint's on file.
Excuse me...
Shut up, Becker.
You accusing the police of
stealing your lousy money clip?
You're not listening, Chapman.
I didn't say that.
I said it disappeared,
that's all.
I'm just asking for a little backup
paperwork this time around.
Jim...
That's, uh, that's...
That's what?
You looking for
some more charges?
You've got too many
to deal with as it is.
Will you stop
antagonizing him?
What's the matter with you?
All right,
cut him loose, Chapman.
What?
I said cut him loose.
He's got a witness,
puts him at home at the time of the murder.
What witness?
A credible one, Captain.
Miss Wilding of the IRS.
I'm sorry. I would have
come forward sooner.
I just assumed that
you had all the facts
as a result of
your investigation.
Chapman never lets facts
clutter up a case he's on.
I'm sure there are
any number of people
that can corroborate me
on this.
The Sand Castle was open. There
were all kinds of cars in the parking lot.
And you say he got home when?
10:45. You see,
I was waiting for him,
so when he drove in,
I looked at my watch.
I decided it was a little
too late to barge in on him,
and I decided I'd come
back another time.
There's no way that Rockford could
have shot Monckton downtown at 10:30,
and get out to Paradise Cove
by 10:45.
Not even the way he drives.
Let's start by
losing the jewelry.
Why? You're not
going anywhere.
The hell I'm not.
The hell you are.
Chapman, can I see you
in here for a minute?
Let him go, Chapman.
But, sir, we have
the murder weapon.
His .38.
His prints all over it.
And he has an alibi
for the time of the murder.
Now, he could have
been set up, Chapman.
You cannot overlook
that possibility.
All right, all right,
maybe I can't make the murder charge stick,
but I've got
a laundry list that will.
Two GTAs,
flight to avoid arrest.
And the threat of
legal action.
You don't lighten up,
he's gonna go ahead with that suit.
You really want to take
that into open court?
It's gonna play like
a police vendetta,
and the department doesn't
need that kind of trouble.
Now, drop it, okay?
Just drop it.
Counselor, we will not be
pressing charges against your client.
Not this time. Becker,
get your friend out of the irons
and get him the
hell out of here.
Yes, sir.
(LAUGHS)
Do you mind
waiting for me?
I'd like to walk Beth
to her car.
Sure. I parked
in the police lot.
Bye, Beth.
Bye-bye.
I want to thank you for being there for me,
Beth.
Yeah.
I want you to bill me.
(LAUGHS) I will.
There were a lot of
people there for you tonight.
Becker and Jess.
She's a nice lady.
I thought that was one of
those politically incorrect words.
Yeah, well, it is. But I can
use it because I'm a woman.
Is she going to be
somebody serious?
Jess? She was Dad's friend.
She's your type.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Let me ask you something.
If you were describing a
friendship you had with somebody,
would you refer to it
as a relationship?
You know,
using the word relationship
instead of friendship,
but mean friendship?
Why don't you just
ask her, Jim?
Forget it.
I'll call you tomorrow.
What's that mean?
Another four years,
or just until you need
an attorney again?
The town's full
of attorneys, Beth.
It was just an excuse
to call you.
I've been looking for one.
I wanted you back in
my life. I've missed you.
I missed you, too.
You know what
really threw me, Jim?
You were the one
who encouraged me
to write the damn book
in the first place.
And then to not
even read it...
I read it, Beth.
Oh, don't make it worse
by lying about it, Jim.
I'm not lying, Beth.
I read it.
Then why didn't you call me?
I didn't like it.
Well... I'm sorry, Beth.
I... I didn't know
how to tell you.
I... I didn't want
to hurt your feelings.
Well, say something.
That's so sweet.
(CHUCKLES) It's stupid,
but it's sweet.
If you don't call me tomorrow,
I'm gonna call you.
Well, you saved my life
in there, Jess.
Thank you doesn't
quite cover it.
God, I'm glad
that's over with.
It isn't over. Not yet.
We still don't know
who killed Bud Monckton.
I don't care who killed him.
That may sound
a little cold...
Sounds very cold.
I never liked the man.
I didn't like him
when I met him.
I spent 20 years not liking
him. He was pond scum.
May sound a little harsh,
but that's the way I feel.
Jim, what would happen if
the police arrested you again?
They won't. Yeah,
but what if they did?
And what if it ends up
in court?
You testify, and...
But that's just it, Jim,
I can't.
I can't testify under oath
that you were home by 10:45.
I didn't check my watch.
I wasn't waiting for you.
I wasn't anywhere
near Paradise Cove.
You...
Lied.
Want to check out
Bud Monckton's?
Well, there's gonna be some lock picking
involved. You may want to wait here.
(SIREN WAILING)
Now, don't get
your hopes up.
Monckton's isn't one of those
lofts that made Architectural Digest.
(EXHALES)
It's pretty bare bones.
Will the police still
have it sealed off?
I'm in so much trouble,
I don't really give a damn.
You sure you don't want
to wait in the car?
So far,
you're real clean on all this.
Are you trying to
make me nervous?
How are we going to
get into this place?
This way.
What about
the security camera?
I doubt if anyone's checking
them now that Monckton's gone.
But just in case,
I'll take care of them on the way out.
Watch your step.
His office is over here,
if that's what you want to call it.
If we're gonna find anything,
we'll find it here.
Don't you touch
anything, huh?
If you do,
be sure and tell me
so I can wipe your
prints off. Can you see?
I'm fine. Let's go.
You wait here.
(GASPS)
Oh, I'm sorry.
I guess I should
have warned you.
It kind of threw me
when I first saw it, too.
I thought his obsession was
reserved for electronic bugs.
Oh, God.
You don't think there's any around
here that aren't in cases, do you?
Not in his
appointment book.
Is that what
we're looking for?
Well, we're looking
for anything
that'll tell us who and
what he was mixed up with.
Felicidad Records,
for example.
You know,
record companies make big bucks.
Big bucks could mean
a mob connection.
They'd have the talent
to take him out
and fashion a very
nice frame for me.
Well, what can I do?
Want me to
check the computer?
You know how?
Where the hell's
his appointment book?
Everybody has to have some
kind of calendar to work from.
Well, it's probably
in here.
You said the guy
was into electronics.
Oh, yes.
He's got everything in here,
including his grocery list.
It's blank.
JESS: Well,
this is where it was.
It was erased, I guess.
Ah, that's just great.
Don't worry about it, Jim.
I'll get it back for you.
You said it was erased.
It is, but it's still
in there someplace.
I just have to find it.
(CHUCKLES) I'm IRS,
I do this all the time.
What'd I tell you?
(EXCLAIMING)
Scrolled ahead too far.
Can you scroll it back
till you come to an entry?
Got it! It's for tomorrow.
What does it say?
If you thought the FBI
connection was strange,
I don't know what you're
going to make out of this.
What does it say, Jess?
Jim, Monckton has
a luncheon meeting
scheduled for tomorrow
with Senator Phillip Aspall.
Oh, I think I better
keep that meeting.
ROCKFORD: Senator,
would you mind telling us
about your association
with Bud Monckton?
Well, I wouldn't call it
an association exactly.
I hired him to do
a job for me.
And the last time
I talked to him,
he told me he had
the information I needed,
but before
he could deliver it,
this terrible thing happened.
I take it
you're close friends?
Oh, not really close.
(LAUGHING)
Not really friends,
actually.
Well, both Mr. Monckton and
Mr. Rockford were private investigators,
so that just naturally gave
them a commonality of interest.
Well, I can certainly understand
how Mr. Rockford fits into the picture,
but Miss Wilding,
I hope you'll forgive me,
your place in it
somewhat eludes me.
If the CIA budget is out of
balance with the Congress,
I don't quite see how
the IRS gets into it.
CIA?
(CHUCKLES) Not that
we wouldn't welcome
all the help we can get,
you understand.
Excuse me.
You said the CIA.
Well, a proprietary
for the CIA.
Felicidad Records
is a front.
A prime example,
as far as I'm concerned,
of unnecessary
government expenditure.
They set up these
front organizations,
and they never
pull the plug on them,
and you and I have to go on
paying for that with our tax dollars
for the rest of
our natural lives.
I was elected on a platform
of fiscal responsibility,
and I'm damned well
gonna follow through on that.
Bud Monckton was investigating
Felicidad Records on your
behalf to put them out of business?
That's right.
And I could have, too, with the
information he promised me in his report.
Names, dates...
All the figures we weren't
able to get a hold of ourselves.
All the information,
all the facts that we needed
that we couldn't get
our hands on before.
Incredible waste there.
Have you ever seen
their offices?
(LAUGHING) I'm a
United States Senator.
I don't have an office anywhere
close to what Hector Gustavo has.
You know,
I've been going crazy
trying to figure out what this
is all about, and it's so simple.
It's the American Dream.
JESS: How can you say
a thing like that?
The American Dream?
I mean, Bud Monckton
was killed,
you were charged
with murder.
You could have spent the
rest of your life in prison.
There is a potential for
corruption in anything, Jess.
Even when it's painted red,
white and blue.
Nothing sinister about
the dream or the good life.
It's what some people will do to
achieve it you have to worry about,
and how far they'll go
not to lose it.
I'm afraid I have
a problem with this.
They just can't get by
with what they've done.
You thinking along the lines
of yearly audits?
If that's the best I can do.
Oh, I think we can do
better than that.
Hey, what the hell is...
Hey! What...
How many times
you been shot
for making a dumb move
like that?
I'm sorry, Dennis,
I didn't mean to freak you out.
I just wanted to check with you
one more time before you go in there.
So you've checked.
Are you sure you know
what you're gonna do?
Not really. In situations
where I can lose
both pension and credibility,
I'm more into improv.
Okay, okay.
Lieutenant Becker,
we have all been the souls of cooperation,
as far as I'm concerned.
We've made our statements.
I don't know why you need
anything further from us.
I'm investigating the murder of
an employee of yours, Mr. Gustavo.
Surely, you want us
to find the killer.
But you have.
That private investigator,
James Rockford.
It's been on the news,
in the paper.
Yeah, but you haven't
read the latest edition.
We thought we had a case,
it fell apart on us.
So now, we're back
to square one,
so we're going to do things
a little bit differently this time.
Is everybody here?
'Cause I want everyone.
Receptionists, secretaries,
maintenance, security.
Anybody that works
for Felicidad, in here.
Why?
Because I'm running
an investigation.
And that's the way
I want to do it.
All right,
but we have to leave somebody on security.
Won't be necessary, sir.
My men will make sure
that nobody goes in
and out of those offices
till your people
are back in place.
Now, I'm on a very tight schedule,
Mr. Gustavo.
I'd like to get out of here
as soon as possible.
BECKER: Now, the questions
will be very, very simple...
(EXCLAIMS SOFTLY)
(CLATTERING)
(GRUNTS)
I want men at every
possible exit,
out of sight,
low key as possible.
We don't want to give them
any indigestion.
You got it? Let's do it. OFFICER: Right,
Lieutenant.
You, I want out of here.
Chapman doesn't believe in cops
taking their buddies along on busts.
Hey, I'm the one that handed you the bust,
Dennis.
And if he ever
finds that out...
He won't.
You got an anonymous tip,
you got a court order, you found the tapes.
Stellar police work.
All I want is five minutes.
Why?
Because they lost, Dennis.
I want to rub
their noses in it.
You're on the clock.
May I help you?
No, I see my party.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(LAUGHING)
Well, well.
Eleanor warned you, Hector,
but here you all are.
When you're running
a rogue CIA operation,
having a regular table for lunch,
even at Rex's, is a really bad idea.
Do you know how many people
want to put you out of business?
There's me, of course,
Senator Aspall,
the Ways and Means
Committee,
the FBI,
the local constabulary.
Even the CIA wants
to tie a can to you.
Yet, we all know
right where to find you.
You can leave voluntarily,
Mr. Rockford,
or I can have you removed.
That always looks so awkward.
You know what
your major mistake was?
You fell in love
with your front.
That's all the record company
was meant to be.
It gave you
a legitimate excuse
to run around Latin America,
doing whatever clandestine
dirty work you were hired to do.
But show business
is very seductive.
You liked playing record mogul
and the hype and the glitz
a lot more than
you were supposed to.
You were willing
to murder to protect it.
Hector...
Well, I'm here to
tell you it didn't work.
You killed Monckton
for nothing.
You thought if the Senator didn't get
his report, he couldn't close you down.
Well, he doesn't have to.
The cops are gonna do it.
We had nothing to do
with Mr. Monckton's death.
Sure, you did.
You're amoral thugs.
You decided to off Monckton
the minute you had found
one of the bugs
that he hung on you.
Me, you found
in the newspaper.
That vivid account
of the stupid brawl
that we had after
the Goodhew Awards.
Not as vivid
as your imagination.
Oh, and the car full of Latinos
that you launched at me.
(CHUCKLES) What'd you do?
Did you con them
into believing that
they were doing something brave
and wonderful for their adopted country?
You promise them
another Bay of Pigs?
Oh, and the elusive
Linda Gustavo.
She's Linda Almeida. She's
doing dinner theater in Santa Fe,
How To Succeed In Business.
(SIGHING) You know,
Bud Monckton,
he was certifiably stupid
in every area but one.
Bugs. That was his obsession.
And the rumor is you didn't
find everything he hung on you.
The rumor is the cops found
a secret stash of tapes
that have you plotting his murder,
plotting my frame.
And the big rumor is you're
going away for a long, long time.
Have a nice lunch.
ROCKFORD: Hey, Jess!
Hi!
(CHUCKLES) Hi.
I wasn't expecting you.
I know. I should have
called first. Sorry.
No, that's not
what I mean.
I was out fishing.
I could've missed you.
You catch anything?
Nothing I wanted to keep.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Well, this is for you.
What?
I mean, it's not exactly a present,
it's just...
Open it.
Okay.
Oh, a cuckoo clock.
You're right, you're right.
Rocky would have loved it.
Since he isn't with us,
I just thought,
|I don't know,
keep it in the family.
Well, thank you.
You're welcome.
(SIGHING)
You know,
you've never come out and said so,
but you want to know what
there was between Rocky and me.
No, no, I don't.
About six years ago, I...
I walked away from a fairly
disastrous relationship.
And unfortunately,
when I walked away,
I was left with this
very fragile ego,
and this inability to trust anyone,
and so much anger.
But, you know,
Rocky was so...
He was so warm, and funny,
and infinitely patient, and he healed me.
He was... He was the
grandfather that I never even knew.
He was my dad that I lost
when I was 12 years old.
He was my father confessor.
He was my best friend.
I'm going to miss him every day
of my life for the rest of my life.
He even taught me
how to fish.
(LAUGHS)
He taught me, too.
Hope you don't mind.
I mean, he let me think of
myself as part of his family.
But you...
You were the center
of his universe, Jim.
That never changed.
There was never a moment in
his life when you didn't come first.
I have a feeling that
you were a very close second.