[footsteps thudding]
[classical music playing]
[knock on door]
[man's voice] Go away!
[knocking on door]
The sign says don't knock
for crying out...
- [taser zaps]
- [screaming]
[screaming]
[thuds]
♪
♪ A birdie told a birdie
told me ♪
♪
♪ What was I supposed to say? ♪
♪ Words like a magical potion ♪
♪
♪ A little goes a long,
long way ♪
♪
♪ It's only just a rumor
while it's still in the dark ♪
♪ When the lights come on
we're gonna see what you are ♪
♪ It's only just a rumor
while it's still in the dark ♪
[cheerful music]
Oh, come on, man.
You can't come back to me
with that.
We've already been there.
Let's take this up a notch.
How's it going?
- I'm crushing it.
- I'm on it.
No.
No, no, no.
- Hey Tim.
- Birdie.
- Paula.
- How'd the Lancaster call go?
It actually got pushed
'til tomorrow.
You let me know if you need
any help with that.
We're all rooting for you.
I think I got it covered
but I'll let you know.
You got everything there, Paula?
Always do.
Just a heads up, the Lancaster
call got pushed 'til tomorrow.
Oh. They're stalling.
Which means you've got them
right where you want them.
I know.
I can taste it.
Birdie, bird.
I'm outta here.
Gotta get that step count up.
Oh, you're so good.
You ready for tomorrow?
Me? I was born ready.
I'll tell you what, tomorrow
I will get the coffee.
Yeah?
Deal.
- The ushe?
- The ushe.
You know me.
Of course I do.
[laughs]
♪
Hey babe!
[sighs]
[squeals]
Okay.
Deal me in, boys.
[camera shutter snaps]
Good evening.
I'm Trisha Murata and tonight
authorities believe
a 30-year-mystery has finally
come to an end.
Just hours ago at this
construction site behind me,
workers discovered the body
of famed Boston crime boss
Orleans “Lean” McGuiness.
McGuiness had been on the top
of the FBI's most wanted list
for over two decades.
Well dumping him
at a construction site
has mob written all over it.
Seems kinda cliché.
Don't you think?
This is real life.
Not an article in
The New Yorker.
Oh. So you can read?
[laughter]
Careful there, glasses.
Most of us swim in these waters
on a regular basis.
You haven't even gotten
your feet wet.
Alright.
Are we gonna finish class
or argue about the news?
Don't worry about him.
The ability to use various
equipment and technologies
and a thorough knowledge
of the law
are some of the key skills
a private investigator needs.
Now, who can tell me what
sub rosa means?
Yes.
[clears throat]
Um, it's Latin for...
[slurping drink]
It's Latin for...
For under the rose.
It's a...
[slurping drink]
It's a term that
investigators use
when they wanna do something
in secret.
Alright.
[burps]
This week's assignment,
it's gonna be a little more fun.
Surveillance.
Yeah.
I need all of you to surveil
someone from your life.
A few rules.
Don't get caught.
Don't follow your wife.
Don't follow your boss.
And definitely don't follow
your ex-wife.
I take it you haven't
told her yet.
I'm working on it.
So that's a no.
Yeah, well...
with Birdie, it's all about
finding the right time.
What are you afraid of?
Inflation. Carcinogens.
Murder hornets.
Teenagers on skateboards.
Pretty much everything.
But the thing that I'm afraid of
the most...
is that look of disappointment
on my wife's face.
You could be an incredible
private investigator.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
And I'd hate to see all that
potential go to the wayside
because you were afraid of
disappointing your wife.
I know.
You have to tell her.
I will.
Soon.
Soon is upon us.
Huh?
Soon.
See ya.
[optimistic music]
[sighs]
Oh. Oh, so that's how
it's gonna be.
I don't think you got it
Lizard King 784.
You're bluffing.
[car pulls up into driveway]
[door opens and shuts]
Hey.
Hey babe.
How was class?
Oh, you know, fascinating.
We're learning all
about bankruptcy.
Oh. So you're on chapter
11 then.
Uh, no. Actually, we're
on chapter 4 but...
I see what you did there.
Mmhmm. Mmhmm.
Yes! Eat it.
Eat what now?
Oh. I, um... got you
some new granola.
- Nice!
- Yeah.
The one I like
with the pistachios?
Yeah. Uh huh.
Did you get up
to anything fun tonight?
Oh, you know.
Just, um... a couple of briefs
and, uh, getting my Sudoku on.
Uh huh.
Yeah. Just a wild
and crazy night.
Actually, um...
you know there's something
I kinda wanted to talk
to you about.
Oh. Okay.
What is it?
I...
Uh... read that, um...
the article that you sent me.
And you know what?
I think you're right.
I think I should be taking
a daily probiotic.
You read the article I sent you?
Thank you.
I know it's not everyone's
favorite topic.
Well...
But if we're gonna grow
old together
we cannot ignore our gut health.
I mean, the balance of good
and bad bacteria are crucial.
It's crucial.
[laughs]
Crucial.
Yeah.
This initial offer is
unacceptable, is just unacceptable.
- Morning.
- Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Oh.
I made you a little breakfast.
Your favorite.
Um, I was hoping we could
have a chat.
This is so amazing
but I actually have the
Lancaster call this morning.
Can I take a rain check?
A rain check.
Uh... sure.
Great.
Uh, well. But how about...
a latte?
I love this little heart.
It's a little heart.
Oh, you know what?
Kyle... Kyle was grabbing
coffees on his way in.
But I feel so bad that you
went through all this trouble.
I mean, I...
I'm gonna take a little sip.
[phone ringing]
That's okay.
- I'm totally fine with that.
- Wait, I have to take this.
Kyle! I was just talking
about you.
You ready to crush it?
I'll see you tonight.
Hey...
[Birdie] You literally
finished my sentence,
that is exactly what
I was thinking.
We are so on the same page.
Just make something up 'cause
I don't wanna talk to him now.
Yo! Yo, the bird looking sharp.
You ready for this?
[in unison] Breaking necks
and cashing checks.
Thank you very much.
Mmm! Cinnamon.
Living on the edge.
[in unison] Game time.
[humming]
[reporter on radio] The case
of famed Boston crime boss
Orleans McGuiness continues
to unfold.
Police are now reporting
that this is an active
homicide investigation.
And that's the news
for this hour.
Coming up, a rare B-side from
the late Danny “Teardrops” Page.
Paid in full.
Okay, Gambot 200.
It is time for you to go
to your forever home.
You know, I think you're gonna
like Cincinnati.
Terrible chili but the people
are great.
Godspeed old friend.
Oh Kyle, your coffee's so great.
Is that cardamom in there?
Does everything you touch
smell like unicorns?
[keyboard tapping]
[garage door opens]
[speakerphone] Our position
from the beginning
was to have this resolved
in a reasonable fashion.
We understand that.
We believe 3.5 is
more than reasonable.
[speakerphone] You know three
million was our ceiling.
No. Up, up.
Now you have a new ceiling.
[speakerphone] Our client does not
think anything over three million
is in their best interest.
That's fine.
We can always see
what a jury thinks.
[speakerphone] Fine.
We'll make 3.5 work.
Great. We'll send over
the paperwork this afternoon.
Dream team strikes again.
Huh, huh?
[grunting in unison]
Yes!
Where'd we land?
3.5.
And on the first round.
Yes.
[laughing]
But didn't they start at three?
Paula, can you get the
champagne from my fridge?
This calls for a celebration.
Thank you so much, Tim.
These paralegals.
They file two forms, they think
they're Erin Brockovich.
[laughing]
Ms. Case?
Ms. Perez would like to see you
in her office in five minutes.
Well, I guess, good news
travels fast.
As it should.
She's gonna love this.
This is how you make partner.
I'm grabbing
the expensive stuff.
Uh huh.
[laughs]
- Well done.
- Thank you, Tim.
That's how you do it.
Thank you Leslie.
Teamwork, right?
Teamwork makes the dream work.
We did it.
Shut the door.
What was that?
This is not how
you make partner.
We got them half a million
dollars over their ceiling.
$3.5 million is a disgrace.
3.5 is fair.
We are not in the business
of fair.
We are in the business
of extracting
everything we can
until there is nothing left.
Kyle and I thought that this...
Listen...
I like Kyle.
He's a good worker bee.
But making partner
isn't in his future.
It is in yours so long
as you pull it together
and start acting like a killer.
But Mom...
I am not your mom
when we're at work.
I am your boss.
And I need you to step up.
Understood?
Understood.
Krshnit?
Oh... crushing it.
[blows raspberry]
11:27 AM.
Target said vehicle identified.
Brotastic.
[sighs]
[phone ringing]
[Birdie] Hey babe.
Hey.
How did the, uh...
how did the call go?
[Birdie] Fine.
[Alden] Was your mom pleased?
My boss wasn't exactly
thrilled, no.
What's new?
[chuckles]
Um... hey, uh... so, uh...
I'm thinking about, you know,
going with some of the guys
to happy hour tonight.
Um...
Hey. I'm out.
I'll see you tomorrow.
[Birdie] Okay.
Okay. Those are gross.
Uh, no. I'm good.
Okay. Well, don't wait up.
You know how hard CPAs
like to party.
[Birdie] Mmhmm.
Okay. Bye.
[mysterious music]
[camera shutter snaps]
[car engine starts]
[tires squeal]
[slurping]
Dry cleaning. 5:10 PM.
[ominous music]
I'm Kyle.
I like to do five K's
just for fun.
[camera shutter snaps]
[ominous music]
[knocking]
Goodnight, Tim.
Oh, Birdie. Good night.
I didn't think anybody
was still here.
You're taking off soon?
Tonight feels like one of
those nights
I'm never gonna leave.
Ugh, I hear you.
[chuckles]
- Okay. Good night.
- Good night.
Hey. Today was still a win.
I know Eleonore can be tough
but you did right
by your client today.
That's the best we can do.
I don't know. Sometimes
I just question it all.
We all do.
You just gotta live
to fight another day.
Thanks Tim, that means a lot.
Get outta here. Good night.
[phone ringing]
This is Tim speaking.
A new suit.
Fancy boy.
My name's Kyle.
I don't need to wear
a seat belt.
[engine starts]
[car door slams]
I'm Kyle.
I work 18 hours a day.
[ominous music]
Three... Five... ugh.
[car engines start]
[tires squealing]
What the?
Come on.
Ugh!
[car shuts off]
[sighs]
Ilm Kyle, I run out of
buildings at full speed.
Guess I'm going in.
[suspenseful music]
Hello?
Barf.
What's that all about?
Divorce?
[phone chiming]
Hello?
Somebody here?
[phone continues chiming]
Tim?
[dramatic music heightens]
Oh no! Oh no!!
Freeze!
[screams]
Let me see your hands.
It's not what you think.
How do you know what I think?
[gags]
Yeah.
[vomits]
Eww.
[sirens wailing]
Ah.
Your blood pressure's
a little high.
You been under
any stress lately?
Slightly more than usual, yeah.
[mysterious music]
Mr. Case... let me
get this straight.
You followed a Mr. Henicker, Kyle,
back to the office because
you were "doing homework"
for your "private
investigation class"
'cause he bought
your wife "coffee".
Did I miss anything?
I don't appreciate your liberal
use of air quotes
but aside from that,
it's correct, yeah.
[Birdie] Alden?
[Alden] Oh.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Is that Tim?
Wait, what are you doing here?
Err... I...
[sighs]
Say something.
A few hours ago Tim was giving
me some really kind advice
and then I got in my car
and I drove home
thinking that my husband
was out networking
with other aspiring accountants
because that's what
he told me he was doing.
Yeah.
And now Tim is dead
and my husband has been lying
to me for four months.
Four months about where
he spends his nights.
I... I don't... I don't know
what I'm supposed to say.
I'm so sorry that you had
to find out this way.
I... I was... I was trying
to tell you this morning
and then you...
you rushed out.
To work, Alden!
I had to get to work.
That's not fair.
You're right.
I thought we agreed.
I thought we agreed that
accounting was stable
and consistent which is
what we need for you
after your whole crypto
currency debacle.
You promised that
you would play it safe.
Okay. All of the blogs said
that crypto mining
was a solid investment.
But we are still paying it off, Alden.
You promised!
I know.
That you would find
something reliable.
I know.
And... and I tried accounting.
I just couldn't do it.
And then across the hall
they had this Intro to
Private Investigation.
So I went over and, I don't
know, something clicked.
Accounting is just not my thing.
It's just not your thing?
Alden, this isn't a college
job fair.
Okay.
I really don't wanna be the wife
that nags you all the time.
I don't.
I love you but I just...
you keep making promises
and then you break them.
Okay. Uh...
Going good.
There we go.
Oh. Okay.
No. No, no, no.
No. No.
Off. Off. Off.
Oh boy.
Okay. Come on, come on.
Off. Off. Okay. Okay.
- Hey. Hey.
- I got it, I got it, I got it.
No, no, no. I know, I know.
I know, I got it.
You're gonna burn yourself.
I had it.
[sighs]
Sorry.
I know how well you knew Tim.
I'm not sure I know anyone
well these days.
Any, uh... any more updates?
Apparently suicide.
Hmm.
So tragic.
It really is.
It's just...
well, I mean, it doesn't explain
why Kyle ran away
before the cops came.
You know?
Innocent people don't run.
How are you doing?
Still processing.
I know this is tough
but we need to think about
the big picture here.
We need to assure our clients,
our future clients
and our employees that
everything is under control.
Yeah, that makes sense.
But we're not expected to do
anything today, right?
Well, people will be
looking for us
to guide them through this.
Tim wasn't just a partner,
he was a real leader,
and now someone's gotta
fill that void.
I need it to be you.
Okay. I can do that.
Good. Now...
as your mother asking...
how are you and Alden?
I don't know, Mom.
I mean, the jealousy
with Kyle was one thing.
But this lying about taking
a PI class
has just taken things
to a whole other level.
It's... I don't even know
who my own husband is anymore.
I thought you'd be relieved.
Usually when a husband lies
about where he is
it's because he's with another
woman or man.
For better or worse,
your husband lied
about night school.
So what, he's just gonna become
a private investigator now?
Let me ask you this,
has he seemed happier lately?
I don't know.
Have you asked?
[knock on door]
A couple of us were thinking
about going out
for drinks tonight
in honor of Tim.
Would it be okay if I sent out
a companywide email?
Of course.
Thanks Paula.
Anything more from the police?
Suicide, open and shut.
Why?
I mean, did Tim seem depressed
to you?
Nuh uh.
Was he having money problems?
Oh no.
[chuckles]
Tim was very wealthy.
His position here was more
for status than for a paycheck.
It just doesn't make any sense.
Well I've learned that people
often only show us
what they want us to see.
I know this is tough.
Chin up.
Everyone's watching.
[sighs]
Our win seems like a million
years ago, doesn't it?
[clears throat]
Yeah.
This is really hitting home, huh?
Yeah. I mean, it's just...
it's such a shock.
You know, I came in today
thinking it was just another
work day and then...
Paula, she told me what happened
and I just... I can't
believe it.
Paula told you?
Yeah, this morning. Why?
No, you're right.
That is unbelievable.
Well... hang in there.
[sighs]
I'm gonna miss you too but
you've got a new family now.
[phone chimes]
Hey.
Are you sure you saw Kyle
running out
of the building last night?
Positive.
It's in my log book.
You have a log book?
[Alden] Yes, I have a log book.
At 7:43 PM Kyle left the Ironman
Gym on Roosevelt Ave.
In a different suit
than he entered with.
At 7:56 PM he arrived
at the office parking lot.
He walked into the building
at 7:58
and minutes later he ran
to the car and drove away.
[scoffs]
I just talked to Kyle and
something isn't making sense.
He said that he found out
about Tim this morning.
That's impossible.
He was running away
from the building
like he'd committed
a crime last night.
[Alden] There is something off
about Tim's death.
I feel it and I know you do too.
Slow down there, Columbo.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
[Alden] Or maybe...
or maybe I need to follow him
again tonight.
Except he's going to this
company drinks tonight
we're having for Tim.
[Alden] Great!
I'll come to that.
And then... and then maybe
before, you know,
you and I could, uh, get pizza.
No! No pizza.
I'm still mad at you.
Of course.
We can do Chinese.
Deal.
Done.
[call ringing]
Hey. Uh... I need a small
quick favor.
I've never done this
for a student before
and I'm only doing so now
because I believe
in your potential.
Understood?
Understood.
It's no suicide note.
None found.
By the way, this wasn't free.
You owe me 7.50.
I mean, like...
like a bribe?
No. Copies.
- Here's the receipt.
- Right.
Who takes a $7 bribe?
[country music playing]
♪
Suicide awareness for charity
in honor of Tim.
That is just so thoughtful.
How are you holding up?
I'm hanging in there.
Tim looked out for everyone.
But who was looking out for him?
Thank you.
I told you I should've brought
my cowboy hat.
[country song playing]
[sighs]
[slow country music playing]
♪
[sniffling]
Alden.
Birdie's hus... husband.
Yeah. We met at the, uh,
holiday gala last year.
I'm sorry about Tim.
Oh, you... you two were close.
[sobbing]
Oh. You were very close.
I loved him.
Oh.
It must be hard.
Keeping all that a secret.
We were going on a cruise
next month.
You know, he told his wife
about me.
His wife knew that you guys
were in a relationship?
Yeah, that's what Tim said.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What's the deal with
your license plate?
KRSHNIT?
[chuckles]
Yeah. Um...
Tim encouraged me to get
that actually.
Uh... it just, it reminds me
every day
to go after what I want,
you know?
I can get on board with that.
I am so glad that you two
are getting along.
But I think it's time
to hit the trail.
Alright.
Catch you at the next rodeo?
Partner.
Yeah.
One day at a time, buddy.
Kyle and Tim together?
I know.
I did not see that one coming.
And Penelope knew about it?
If Tim was gonna leave
his wife for Kyle,
he would take all of his money
with him.
I call that motive.
Or... the plot of a Murder
She Wrote episode.
Where's your evidence?
Oh, I'll find some.
Mmhmm.
[both sigh]
Okay. How about this?
We go to Tim's funeral,
we strike up a friendly
conversation with the widow,
and then when
she's distracted...
Alden, go to sleep.
I'm tired.
Babe! You know I do my best
brainstorming in bed.
[sighs]
Okay. How about this?
Tomorrow we drop off some of
Tim's things from his office
and size up the wife.
The widow.
She sounds way more guilty
when you say it like that.
Fine. The widow.
Marrying you was the best thing
I've ever done.
I thought Tim was loaded.
Well this isn't his place,
this is Paula's.
Can you believe Eleonore had
Paula clean out Tim's office?
Good morning.
- Hi.
- Come on in.
- Thanks so much.
- Yeah.
I've just got Tim's stuff
over here
so give me a second and
make yourselves at home.
Okay.
Wow. I didn't know she was
so into horses.
Oh, you noticed that too?
You know, it's kind of charming
when it's in a bar
but when it's in your house
it's a cry for help.
Says the guy who has no less
than 20 robots in his garage.
Help.
Here we go.
Oh. Thanks so much, Paula.
Thank you.
Is this, um, is that you?
Yeah. That... that's me
and my sister, Caroline.
Now she's my angel in heaven
shining down on me.
I'm so sorry.
So sorry.
Well... thank you so much
for keeping these safe, Paula.
Anything for Tim.
And if there's something else
that you need,
please just ask me.
We will.
Take care.
Thanks again, Paula.
Bye.
[door lock clicks]
[Alden chuckles]
Okay.
Now we're talking.
[posh accent] Hello Governor.
That's a house.
On behalf of the firm, I wanted
to offer our services
in case you wanted any help
at all with Tim's estate.
Oh, Timmy had many things.
An estate was not one of them.
So all this...
Oh dear, all of this
is in my name.
From my father's side
of the family.
Not even... life insurance?
He had a meager $100,000 policy
that didn't pay out to suicides.
Did you see any signs at all
that Tim might've
been depressed?
Hardly.
He was excited about going on
that cruise next month
with that boy from the office.
So you did know about that?
That Tim was gay?
Yes, I knew.
We didn't keep secrets
from each other.
It might've been unconventional
but in marriage you're
either growing together
or you're growing apart.
But you didn't come here
for marriage advice.
So why don't you ask me
what you're really thinking?
Do you really think Tim
could've killed himself?
I'm convinced he didn't.
And what... what makes you
so sure?
Tim struggled for years
with who he was.
He finally was comfortable
in his own skin.
Was he having trouble
with anybody or...?
There's one thing that comes
to mind.
There was an incident at the
apartments he was representing
for the new owners.
The Cecil Bay Apartments?
That sounds right.
He said it was sadly something
to do with redevelopment
or some such and that when they
handed out the eviction notices
he was threatened by one
of the tenants there.
He didn't go into much detail
but something gave him
quite a fright.
Hmm.
I take it by this line
of questioning
you're investigating this.
- Yes.
- No.
Well, not in any
official capacity.
Well, not... not in any
If you have any other comments
or anything else occurs to you,
please feel free to contact us.
And again, if the firm...
if the firm can help you
in any way,
please don't hesitate to ask us.
Sure.
I think your husband
is doing quite enough.
Yes, he has.
Marcia will see you out.
Thank you so much
for your hospitality.
One more thing...
Alden, we have to go.
Let's be honest.
You see everything
that goes on around here.
You notice anything strange
about Tim's behavior lately?
Bill Coulter from
the yacht club.
I know they were involved
in some sort of lawsuit
with each other
but last week Bill and Tim had
an argument in the driveway.
What happened?
Did he get violent? Physical?
Bill didn't get out of the car.
But there was a lot of yelling.
What was the lawsuit about?
I don't know.
But they were both very angry.
That's my business card.
Feel free to contact me,
day or night, preferably day.
Good day.
Business cards, really?
- I printed up a few.
- [phone chimes]
I'm trying out a couple
different fonts.
Ugh. I gotta get back to work,
I'll drop you off at home. Okay?
I thought we were going
to the yacht club.
Well as much as I do love their
Cobb salad, I just can't.
I don't have time.
Since when have you been
to the yacht club?
Lots of times.
They're our clients.
Well let's go then.
I can't. Eleonore's breathing
down my neck.
Actually... that's perfect.
Then you can get the files
on that case that Penelope
was talking about.
The Cecil...
- The Cecil Bay Apartments.
- The Cecil Bay Apartments, yeah.
The Cecil Bay Apartments
have new owners
and they wanna turn them
into high-end condos.
Tim was dealing with
the current tenants,
trying to get them out nicely.
Well, that sounds like a recipe
for bad blood.
We definitely need
to get those files.
No. No, no, no.
No one's going over any files.
That's privileged information.
Ah. Got it.
Playing by the book.
No, I'm not playing anything
any way.
No, I gotcha.
Alden, there's no...
nothing to follow. Okay?
[phone chimes]
No. You know what, I have
to get to work, okay?
And I would love to do this all
day but I actually have a job
that I have to get
to the office for.
It's fine. I can go by myself.
[car engine starts]
[fire roaring]
Mister... Coulter.
You can take the salad
but leave the drink.
Actually... I was hoping
you and I
could have a friendly
little chat.
Depends. Are you working
for my ex-wife?
No.
Then sure.
Interesting book.
Knots For Sailors.
It's driving me crazy.
I wanna talk to you about...
Tim Grant.
I thought you said this
was gonna be a friendly chat.
Oh. So I see you've heard
the news?
I heard he checked out early.
That's one theory.
But you have another.
Rumor has it you and he had
a pretty heated argument.
Oh yeah, I wanted to murder him.
[laughs]
Did you?
Son, if I killed every person
that sued me,
I'd be a serial killer.
What was the lawsuit about?
Yacht stuff.
Rich old guy drama.
I'm honored that you think
I'm capable of murdering Tim
but I just don't see
that happening.
Oh yeah? Why is that?
[chuckles]
Hip replacement a month ago,
lost a fight with a sidewalk.
I don't think I'd stand much
of a chance with Tim.
[sighs] Oh!
That's why you waited
in the car.
You're a very bright young man.
Thanks for lunch.
What?
Five missed calls this morning, Birdie.
I'm sorry.
That's five times I needed you
and you weren't there.
Alden and I took a few of
Tim's things out to his wife.
Oh. That's very sweet of you
but that is not your job.
You're right. You're right.
But I'm here now. Okay?
My head's in the game.
There are a dozen people
clawing their way
to the top here
and right now you aren't
one of them.
The door's open, Birdie,
but I can only hold it open
for you so long.
I'm doing the best that I can.
Well, it pains me to say this,
but it needs to be better.
Hey girl. Figured you could use
a midday pick me up.
Oh, wow.
I can't remember the last time
someone brought me a coffee.
Oh, it's nothing.
Uh... hey. While I have you,
a quick favor to ask you.
Have you seen the files on
the Cecil Bay Apartments?
Oh, are you taking over
that case from Tim?
I'm just trying to fill in
some of the gaps
that Tim left behind.
That's great.
Uh... Yeah.
Here you go.
That should be everything
you need.
Great. Thank you so much.
Oh... and hey,
one more thing.
When Tim gave notice
to the tenants,
did he mention seeing anything
strange or...?
Strange?
Oh, you mean like that old lady
with the gun in her nightgown?
[whispers] I would classify that
as strange.
I'm sure it was.
No. But she did really
spook him.
Huh.
Thanks.
Natbot 8,000.
Can you solve Tim's murder?
Don't look at me like that.
That's what you're here for.
- Hey.
How's the office?
Definitely not as fun as
what we were doing before.
Any luck at the yacht club?
Nope. Swing and a miss.
Hmm.
Well, I thought these
might help.
The Cecil Bay Apartment files?
Mmhmm.
What changed your mind?
You know, I just thought
playing it by the book... overrated.
[upbeat music]
♪
Okay. Let's get all the tenants
up on the board,
shake the tree,
see what comes out.
♪
There are 15 tenants in
the Cecil Bay building.
So Tim, acting on behalf
of the new owners,
was in the process of evicting
the tenants
so they could turn the building
into luxury condos.
Right. On that fact alone,
everybody had a motive
to want Tim gone.
And our working theory
is that same person
went to Tim's office three days
later, killed him,
making it look like a suicide.
Exactly.
We've been able to definitively
rule out 12 out of 15 tenants
for various reasons.
Either lack of means
or opportunity or both.
Which leaves us three
potential suspects.
Right.
Number one.
Francis Taylor.
[camera shutter snaps]
Apartment 201.
Now this guy was convicted
of manslaughter in 1982,
he served 12 years,
he's been living in
the building ever since.
He's been employed
as a counsellor
for newly released inmates,
helping them get adjusted
to their new lives.
It's possible he did it.
I don't see it.
I don't either.
And then we have the old lady
with a gun in her nightgown.
[camera shutter snaps]
Eugenia Carmopolis,
apartment 112.
She does have a concealed carry
permit so she has the means.
Only problem is
she's legally blind.
Which leaves us...
Frederick Gasko.
[camera shutter snaps]
Apartment 101.
Now Mr. Gasko is the only tenant
in the building
who pays his rent in cash
and the only picture on file
is from a driver's license
from 1989.
Which I think we both agree
is totally fake.
For sure.
I can't believe they spelled
Massachusetts wrong.
I mean, how do you get away
with that?
No, I think that's actually
the real crime here.
But the question is...
why does Mr. Gasko
need a fake ID?
Perhaps it's because Frederick
Gasko and Lean McGuiness
are the same person.
It does look like him.
Because it is him.
One of America's most dangerous
mobsters, on the run, 30 years,
hiding in plain sight.
Lean McGuiness killed Tim
because he was about
to blow his cover and kick him
out of his hiding spot.
Mic drop.
That's the game.
Happy birthday!
Hold up.
I'm bumping on one thing.
What?
Lean McGuiness' body was
discovered before Tim died.
How does a dead man kill Tim?
[groans]
Okay, that's actually
a really good point.
I'm not sure but there has to be
a connection.
Come on!
There's no way
it's a coincidence
that Tim very likely
discovered Lean
and then both Tim and Lean were
found dead within the same week.
It does seem unlikely.
Come on.
Just acknowledge
we're onto something here.
Alden Case, you are becoming
quite the investigator.
[machine frothing]
You're up early.
Did you get any sleep?
Actually, I woke up in
the middle of the night
with an idea.
I know... what we need to do.
- Veggie omelets?
- Mmhmm.
- Kiwis.
- Yes.
- Strawberries and pancakes?
- Correct.
What are you
buttering me up for?
Hear me out.
I think we need to visit
the Cecil Bay Apartments
and see if Frederick Gasko
is there.
Whoa! That's a big step,
don't you think?
You saw the pictures.
Frederick Gasko is Lean McGuiness.
It's the same person.
Yes, they do look alike. Okay.
But I think the safest thing
to do would be to call the FBI
and tell them what we think.
Argh!
They are still investigating
what happened to Lean McGuiness.
We don't wanna get
in the middle of that.
Okay.
Before we do that,
how about this?
We go to the apartments,
we knock on the door,
if Frederick Gasko answers,
that's it I quit, game over.
And if he doesn't answer?
If Gasko's not there,
we call the FBI,
we tell them what we know.
And you will stand down?
I will hand the information
over to the fancy people
with their badges. Promise.
Let me think about it.
I have this meeting
at 10:00 AM
that I am not looking
forward to.
Oh yeah, I bet.
I bet you do.
Meetings are tough.
You just think about it. Okay?
Mmhmm.
Just think about it.
That's... that's excellent.
You got a lot of knots
back here, what's going on?
I know. Oh God.
Yes, I know.
100 percent, Mr. Keller.
I mean, we're very excited,
you know.
We can't wait
for the next steps.
Thanks Ben, chat soon.
[phone beeps]
Wait, was that the Keller call?
I thought it was at 10:00.
It got moved to 9:00.
I thought you knew that.
Kyle, great work.
Start putting together
your proposal.
I'm on it.
Doesn't feel good, does it?
You did this on purpose.
Kyle isn't half the lawyer
you are.
But he's hungry.
Hey. Let's do this.
Pick me up at 6:00
This is it.
I can't decide if I want Gasko
to be home or not.
Okay. So we are just knocking
on the door, Alden.
And if he doesn't answer...
I will stand down.
Okay, let's do this.
One sec.
Fake mustache.
Why would you need
a fake mustache?
So no one knows who we are.
No one knows who we are anyway!
Exactly.
Alden.
Hmm?
[chuckles]
Wait, wait, wait.
What's with the hat?
Come on, rookie.
Oy vey.
I can't believe
we're doing this.
In and out, okay?
We're just knocking on the door.
Just follow my lead.
This is what I've been
training for.
Okay. 102, Ms. Berman.
She's a kindergarten teacher.
[buzzer rings]
[Ms. Berman] Hello?
Yeah. This is, uh,
Mario's pizza.
What accent is that?
We got a couple of pies here,
they're for 103,
that we can't deliver.
[Ms. Berman] Well that's not
my problem.
Okay. New plan.
Yeah.
We wait until someone comes out.
Or we just use the keys.
Where did you get those?
They were in the file.
Come on.
Rookie.
Oh.
Charming little spot.
Was it you?
I'm sorry?
Huh?
Was it you who took
my wheelchair?
'Cause I left it right here and
the next thing I know it's gone.
We... no, no, no.
We haven't seen it.
Are you alright?
Do you need us to take you...
[gun cocks]
I'll be fine.
Well that checks out.
I think she likes you.
It's the mustache.
Oh... are you jealous?
Maybe.
Yikes.
Okay.
This is it. 101.
This is it, this is it.
Uh... I'm having
second thoughts.
I'm just gonna knock.
It literally says don't knock.
It also says leave packages.
I don't plan to do that either.
Uh...
[knocks on door]
[door creaks open]
[mysterious music]
Mr. Gasko?
[door creaks open]
Alden!
- Mr. Gasko?
- Alden, let's go.
Birdie, you need to get in here.
Uh.
[electricity zapping]
[whistles]
This guy needs a housekeeper.
We should really get outta here.
Yeah, we should.
Oh, my gosh.
What is it?
Look at all this mustard!
This guy must be a real
sandwich nut.
Alden, let's go!
Come on.
Will you relax?
It's not like we're...
What?
Birdie. Check this out.
Alden!
Right.
Yeah. Now might be a good time
to call the FBI.
Let's call them from the car.
I knew we shouldn't
have come here.
This was a mistake.
Ella, call FBI.
FBI! Put your hands up.
[voice on phone] Calling
Federal Bureau of Investigation.
[operator] FBI.
What's the emergency?
[police siren wails]
I could get disbarred for this, Alden.
I told you we should've gotten
out of there.
Birdie, we are this close
to blowing this whole thing
wide open.
What planet are you living on?
In the real world, if the FBI
has you handcuffed
in the back of a car,
that means you have to make
some serious life changes.
Okay. Here's what
I think we do.
No. You know what?
I can't partake in your
detective fantasy anymore.
Okay? I'm done.
I'm done.
[distant conversations]
[woman's voice]
Yeah, I'm on it.
Unbelievable.
Here he comes.
Alright. Come on now.
You're lucky my mom
is who she is.
Yeah.
Thank you.
[Birdie sighs]
[Agent Digbee]
Your story checks out.
Of course it does.
But listen up.
Amateur hour is over.
You understand?
You're free to go.
I am not an amateur.
I've almost got
my certificate...
Uh... thank you so much
Special Agent Digbee.
So sorry for the trouble.
Okay. Well what about
the Tim Lean connection?
[groans]
'Cause I'm starting to think
that there is a real mob element
at play here.
In fact my new theory...
Mr. Case, some free advice.
Stay in your lane.
Perhaps Reddit would be a more
appropriate arena for you.
Plus...
I got an unmarked blue sedan
that's been trailing me around,
which means we are definitely
close to something.
- Wait. You're being trailed?
- Yes.
- By a blue sedan?
- You're sure?
- Yes!
- Well this changes everything.
- It does?
Absolutely...
Not.
Oh.
Counselor.
Alright, I'm going
to talk to them.
No, no, Alden.
You promised.
You promised that you would let
the people with the badges
solve this.
I am not quitting.
Oh, there it is.
That look of disappointment.
Please. Please. It is time
to walk away.
From what, Birdie?
From the case or...
or from our marriage?
Maybe... maybe we should
just quit and get divorced.
Huh Birdie?
You saw the papers.
I drew those up after
the cryptocurrency thing.
I was angry. Okay?
You weren't supposed to see.
How did you get those anyway?
They looked pretty official
to me.
I might've lied about accounting
but you kept a divorce
secret from me.
I don't know whether to be
hurt or impressed.
Well, if you saw them
why didn't you say anything?
Because maybe... maybe
saying it out loud made it true.
So... so what is it?
Are we... are we...
are we done?
It's like Penelope said,
we're either growing together
or we're growing apart.
And for a while now...
we've been growing apart.
When we got married,
is this what you pictured
our life being like?
No. Not exactly.
I thought we'd, you know,
have a boat and...
and a kid or two.
But as long as I'm with you,
none of that matters.
What did you think it was
gonna be like?
Not this.
I'm not quitting on us.
What are you doing?
I'm walking home.
Here's the keys.
It's the other way, Alden.
Thank you.
Good evening.
I'm Trisha Murata reporting live
from the Cecil Bay Apartments
on Third Street.
More pieces of the puzzle
are emerging as investigators
confirm the location
where notorious mob boss...
[sombre music]
[crying]
Bird! Bird. Hey, hey.
[sighs]
So what happened last night?
Is it true?
Did you get busted by the FBI?
No.
Well... not exactly.
How did you hear?
- Paula.
Yeah. Yeah
The Cecil Bay developers
called first thing this morning.
How bad is it?
Oh. No, no, no.
They're ecstatic.
They are?
It's now the hottest property
in town.
Nothing gets rich yuppies
putting down deposits
more than a condo building
that was once a mob hideout.
That's great.
Well, great. I'm glad to hear
you say that.
So no hard feelings?
What do you mean?
Well, I assume Eleonore
told you.
I'm the lead on Cecil Bay.
Oh! Yeah, no...
she told me.
I am so happy for you.
- Dream team, yeah?
- Mmhmm.
Yeah.
[grunting together]
[sighs]
Okay.
Kyle was having
an affair with Tim.
Which Tim's wife was oddly
cool about it.
Simultaneously, Tim was trying
to evict Lean McGuiness
from his hiding spot
of 30 years.
Which might've caused Lean
to call his old mob connections
to get rid of Tim.
We also know Lean had
a neighbor,
one Mrs. Eugenia T. Carmopolis,
who was in possession of a gun.
Now... could this have been
a neighbor dispute?
Did Lean like to watch
his TV too loud?
We just don't know.
So apparently the Cecil Bay
Apartments completely sold out.
Everyone wants to live where
Lean McGuiness was hiding out.
Hmm.
Babe.
That's a big deal.
We connected the dots to
Lean McGuiness' hiding spot.
A week after the FBI did.
Well, they got resources.
[loud crash outside]
No, no, no.
Let me go first.
What was it?
What?
Wait, Alden.
Be careful, be careful.
It's just a brick.
Perfect.
A baseball glove?
I don't know.
Will you just... be careful.
Okay? Don't cut yourself.
What's it say?
[in unison]
Let sleeping dogs lie.
Okay.
So... because you are
"hot on the trail"
with something involving
"Lean McGuiness",
you think that the brick
that went through your window
was somehow "mob related".
That's correct,
officer air quotes.
It's officer Newton.
It's not officer air quotes.
Sorry, officer "Newton".
You know what?
Officer... are we in danger?
It's probably just some kids
playing a prank.
I'll write a report, let you
know if anything comes up.
Thank you.
Should I be concerned
about that?
Oh, that's just
an "art project".
Don't do things that I do.
Have a nice night.
Not you.
Well, why throw a brick
through the window?
Why not just leave
a note in the mailbox
or tape it to the front door.
It's to send a message, Alden.
Leaving a letter in the mailbox,
not exactly threatening.
Mmhmm. Well it'd be
the decent thing to do.
You know what I think
the decent thing to do is?
I think the decent thing to do
is just to take a step back
and let things cool down a bit.
I can't do that.
Alden... whoever threw
that brick
knows where we live.
What if next time
they don't stay outside?
Waiter.
Watchmaker's apprentice.
Cheesemonger.
Notary.
T-shirt screen printer.
Museum docent.
Barista.
Crypto currency miner.
What are you getting at?
These are all the careers
that I have started and quit.
And some of them were too easy,
some of them were too hard,
some of them were
just terrible ideas.
Yeah, but all those things
make you you.
I don't wanna be known as the
guy who quits things anymore.
This case, I have to solve it.
And that brick...
that means we're making somebody
very nervous.
Yeah. And I'm a little scared.
Me too.
And I don't know exactly
how this whole thing's
gonna play out.
Kinda like me and you.
But I'm not quitting.
Because I know in my heart
they're both worth fighting for.
[mysterious music]
Wow.
It was Kyle all along.
Ado Construction is the company
that was developing the site
where Lean McGuiness was found.
It's on Kyle's shirt
in this picture
because the owner of the company
is Kyle's uncle!
How much coffee have you had?
Birdie, this is the connection
that we've been looking for.
I think Kyle killed
Lean McGuiness and then Tim.
What? No. I...
I really don't see Kyle
being capable of one murder,
let alone two.
Do you have any proof?
Not yet.
I'm working late.
I have to get my steps in.
I think it's called running.
No. It's called getting
your steps in when the office
has a competition of who
can get the most steps in.
And Kyle is killing it.
See what I did there?
That was pretty good.
Look... do your thing
but just please be careful.
Okay.
[sighs]
I'm Kyle, I get all my steps in.
Kyle gets all his steps in.
[knocks on door]
Hey Paula.
Hey Alden.
Birdie's in her office
if you're looking for her.
Uh, actually,
I'm looking for you.
Oh.
You know how when Tim died
you said to let you know
if there was anything
you could do to help?
Well, I need your help.
Um... you know how everybody's
been tracking their steps
for that infernal
wellness challenge?
I have almost hit
my goal this week.
Good for you!
Do you have, uh, login info for
the company tracking profile?
I do.
And you could pull all the GPS
data for the last... two weeks?
I've got some work to do now
but I could do it later.
Should I just give it to Birdie?
Oh. No, no, no.
Birdie's slammed.
She's probably gonna
be here all night.
Um... I could come back
in a couple of hours.
You know what?
I have errands to do
in your neighborhood.
Why don't I just pop
it by tonight?
That sounds perfect.
- Great.
- I'll see you then.
- Okay.
[chuckles]
Okay.
[mumbling]
I need coffee. Coffee.
Yes, coffee.
[lights click off]
[ominous music]
[door opens]
Mom?
[screams]
Kyle!
You scared me.
I see you're part
of the night crew.
I'm ordering Thai.
You want in?
Sure. Is anyone else
still here?
No. Just you and me.
[doorbell rings]
Hey Paula, come on in.
Hi.
[ominous music]
[chuckles]
Of course.
Something funny?
Ah... no.
I mean, yes.
But no.
I just realized something.
Anyway, thanks for coming.
Did you bring the step data?
I sure did. Why do you want it?
I think I might've figured out
a way to prove
there was foul play
in Tim's death.
Oh! Good.
Uh... here.
Would you like something
to drink?
Got any bourbon?
Coming right up.
[chuckles]
[ominous music]
I'm sorry to do this to you, Bird.
[sighs]
[ominous music heightens]
They forgot your chicken satay.
Oh. That is totally fine.
I will survive.
You sure?
Yup. Yup.
Okay, if you say so.
[chuckles]
Phew.
How many steps you get in today?
Uh... 5,000, and that's
with a morning run.
How about you?
Uh... let's see.
[clears throat]
22,477.
How is that possible?
I'll show you. Okay?
Check this out.
Okay. So you can manually enter
your steps on their back end.
Wait. Are you serious?
Yeah. Yeah.
I read their terms of service,
it's actually kind of scary.
They store the GPS history
of every user.
Like, you wanna see where
everyone is right now?
That's a complete invasion
of privacy.
Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
But I guess since
you're already logged in...
we can sneak a peek. Right?
Yeah.
The trick is, the step counter
tracks data using GPS.
Which means I should be able
to prove unequivocally
that Tim was actually murdered.
Wow. Alden!
[glasses clink]
You are quite the sleuth.
[chuckles] Well...
Have you told
anyone else about this?
No. No, you're the first.
Mmm. That's good.
I really wish you had let
sleeping dogs lie.
Hey, that's what the brick said.
[taser zaps]
Paula?
[thud]
[grunting]
Paula?
This is very impressive.
I just wish someone
had spent this much time
trying to find justice
for my sister, Caroline.
Justice? Why, what happened?
What happened?
[chuckles]
You are a funny little monkey,
aren't you, Alden?
Look, Paula. Whatever happened
to your sister Caroline,
I would've helped, I swear.
No you wouldn't have!
You would've been too scared of
Lean McGuiness and his thugs.
You would've kept your mouth
shut just like everyone else.
Everyone knew who killed her
but they didn't do anything
about it.
She deserves justice.
Huh?
You've been on my tail
this whole time.
I have?
Oh... I have.
Because Kyle didn't kill
Lean McGuiness.
You did.
And the GPS
would've proven that.
So, look at this.
Okay? So that's you and me.
Okay.
Uh... that's your mom.
And... Paula is...
At my house.
That's weird.
Yeah.
Wait. You said they store
people's GPS history, right?
Mmhmm.
So can you see where everyone
was the night Tim died?
Yeah. Yeah, I can.
Wow. I... I can't believe I
never thought of this before.
Let's see here.
That's me finding Tim.
[ominous music]
Wait a second.
Paula was there too.
And she's leaving through
the back door.
Does that mean...
Paula killed Tim?
Yeah.
I think it does.
Alden.
Oh my gosh! Alden!
[phone chiming]
That's my mom, don't answer.
She is a talker.
Oh. Let's let that go
to voicemail.
[voicemail] This is Alden.
I can't come to
the phone right now.
Leave a message.
Alden! Alden! It was Paula
all along.
Call me.
Now...
What to do with you?
Look, what do you say
you cut me loose,
we mosey on down
to the Side Saddle,
we go halfsies on a basket
of jalapeño poppers
and we just put this whole
thing behind us. Huh?
I'm afraid it's not that easy.
It is!
That monster killed my sweet
sister 33 years ago.
She was just walking
home one day,
took a shortcut down an alley
and saw something
she shouldn't have.
And she was gone.
They found her body
two weeks later.
Two weeks later!
I'm really sorry
about your sister
but you don't have to hurt me.
I didn't do anything.
But you did!
You got in the way!
I did everyone a favor
by killing Lean.
And now... I have to do
something with you.
No you don't.
No you don't!
Does Birdie have any bleach?
Bleach?
What's this?
No, no, no.
Really? Now you're fixing
the street?
[tires screech]
This is not happening, this is
not happening. Okay. Just...
Hey!
Hang in there, baby.
Birdie's coming.
[tires squeal]
Now that I think about it,
we don't have any bleach.
We only use Earth friendly
non-toxic cleaning products
in this house.
We're on sort of a...
a new green...
[Paula] Never mind.
I found drain cleaner, floor
polish and some laundry pods.
Uh... you know me,
Mr. Curious.
Why did you have
to kill Tim too?
[Paula] I went to the office
to scare Tim
but he was gonna turn me in.
So Tim had to be put out
to pasture
because he figured things out
and wouldn't let it just be.
You all assumed that Tim went
to the apartments by himself.
Ha!
I'm always with Tim.
But nobody ever sees Paula.
I was with Tim,
like I always was,
when he went door to door
at the Cecil Bay Apartments.
And when we went
to apartment 101
and Mr. Frederick Gasko
came to the door,
I knew instantly who he was.
This old block of wood
doesn't forget a face.
So I went back.
[chuckles]
[taser zaps]
[Gasko yells]
To Mr. Gasko with
my trusty zapper
and I gave him a send-off
that he deserved.
[chuckles]
I would've said shock
of his life, but...
no time for humor.
What are you gonna do with that?
What are you doing?
No, no, no.
No, no.
No. No.
Take a sip.
You'll go right to sleep.
Nuh uh.
Oh, that smells terrible.
You know, we could do this
the easy way or the hard way.
Look at me.
Look around you.
I'm a 38-year-old private
investigator in training.
I don't do anything
the easy way.
Have it your way.
What does that mean?
Paula, what does that mean?!
Uh... So... so... so,
you drove to Rhode Island
with Lean's body in your car
and you dumped it at
the construction site
to make it look like a mob hit.
But why was Kyle wearing
the T-shirt?
[Paula] Kyle's uncle owns
Ado Construction.
Yeah.
[Paula] You'd be hard-pressed
to find a construction site
in Rhode Island that wasn't done
by them.
It was a happy accident.
Oh... Uh huh.
And, uh... how did Tim
figure it out?
[Paula] Tim knew my sister
was killed by Lean McGuiness
and when they found his body
he put two and two together.
We were the only people
who knew Lean's hiding place.
Help me out here.
Any ideas?
What?
Man, you're good.
[Paula] Tim was gonna go
to the FBI about me,
and they would've found me,
so he had to be silenced.
[grunting]
[robot whirs]
No.
Yes!
[chuckles]
[garage door creaks open]
Help me! Help!
Help!
No one is coming
to save you, Alden.
No, no, no, no, no.
Help!
No, no, no. Paula. Paula.
[stuttering]
P... P... P...
What about Birdie?
Think about...
think about Birdie.
Sweet little...
sweet little Birdie.
I know, poor Birdie.
Right?
Don't worry, I am gonna be there
to help her through this.
That's not really
what I had in mind.
And now...
it's time for heaven
to get another angel.
Nuh uh.
- Open up.
- Mm.
- Open up! Open!
- Open up.
- Mm.
- Open up!
Mm. Mm. Mm...
- Open up, Alden!
- Mm.
[Rick] Alden?
In here!
Freeze!
Who are you?
That's Rick.
Drop the... turkey baster.
[garage door creaks open]
Get her! Get her! Get her!
- [taser zaps]
- [groaning]
[Alden] Get her!
Natbot!
[robot whirs]
[Alden] Get her, Rick!
[Rick] Got you.
[Alden] Get her!
[Paula] Let me go!
[Rick] Come on, get up.
- Get her, Rick.
- Get off of me!
[Alden] Show her who's boss.
Get her!
There you go.
You got her.
[laughing]
We did it!
I knew it was you in the blue
sedan the whole time.
Alden!
[knocking on door]
Alden! Are you okay?
Birdie! Natbot.
[garage door creaks open]
- Alden?
- Birdie!
Alden?
Hi honey.
[sirens wail]
Tonight, a bizarre ending
to the mystery
surrounding the fate
of Lean McGuiness.
We're hearing that
Paula Saint Gervais,
who's sister,
Caroline Saint Gervais,
was killed by Lean McGuiness
in 1987...
Well, I told them all about
the GPS.
That should seal things up.
Thanks, man.
Hey, I'm really glad it was me
you chose to follow.
Well, yeah.
You did good, glasses.
[chuckles]
Looks like you finally got
your feet wet.
Thanks Detective.
- Don't.
- Yeah, it's...
Yeah. Yeah.
Did you just make a new friend?
I don't know if I'd go that far.
Before they take her away,
there's something
that's been bothering me.
Wait. What do you mean?
Officer! Wait, one sec.
I need to Columbo her.
Hey Paula, how did
you get Lean's body
into the car that night?
I didn't have a plan for that.
[Paula] When I got to
the apartment building
there was a wheelchair
sitting there.
Of course! Mrs. Carmopolis'
wheelchair.
Yes!
Well, I think we're done here.
Take 'er away, boys.
I've always wanted to do that.
You were made for this.
[sighs]
I'm so happy to see you.
I know.
Authorities aren't releasing
any more details at this time.
But my sources tell me
the case was solved
by a local husband and wife
private investigation team.
So... how does it feel?
Ah, it's a little sore.
No. How does it feel
to solve the case?
Oh... [chuckles]
I... I can't believe
we solved it.
- We did it!
- I know.
[both slurping]
Mmm.
That hits the spot.
- It's pretty good.
- Mmhmm.
So tell me...
When we got married,
is this what you imagined
your life would be like?
Oh, not at all.
This?
Way better.
Hmm.
'Cause I get to do it with you.
What's this?
It was our divorce papers.
[chuckles]
[laughing]
- No more secrets.
I love you, baby bird.
I love you, big bird.
Babe. Come on.
We can't be late for my mom.
Well, the door's not
gonna lock itself.
I know, but you know how
punctual she is.
Okay? I just...
I know. I mean,
safety first.
Are you the Case's?
Who... who's asking?
I'm Johnny D'Rossi.
My family owns the wine
and cheese store on Fifth.
Mmhmm.
Oh. You guys have
great pickles.
Thank you.
This is for you.
It's a ham.
[sighs]
Oh.
Bone in.
I spent a lot of years
with Lean McGuiness.
Too many.
But his murder had a lot of
people worked up
and what you did
prevented more bloodshed.
You ever need a favor,
you come by the store.
Your husband, he did
a great service.
Actually, uh...
we're partners.
Hmm? Oh...
Well then, you're lucky you
two have found each other.
Yeah. We are.
[chuckles]
So... was that really Johnny
"Palm Trees" D'Rossi?
Yup.
[Birdie] Of the D'Rossi
crime family?
[Alden] Mmhmm.
And the giver of fine hams.
Oh, this ham's really heavy.
Hi.
Birdie. Alden.
Mrs. Grant reached out and
wanted to speak to you both.
What are you holding?
Mobster ham!
[thuds]
Oh, Mrs. Grant.
It's nice to see you again.
I wanted to formally express
my gratitude to you both.
Tim has considered this firm to
be part of his extended family
and I am so grateful for your
diligent work to find the truth.
Well, it's the least
we could do for Tim.
Because Tim's death has been
reclassified as a homicide,
his life insurance policy
is no longer void.
And I think that Timmy
would want you...
to have this.
A million dollars?
It's a $100,000.
$100,000?!
[laughing]
This is... I... I don't even...
Thank you.
Maybe that will help you get
your investigation business
off the ground.
That is so generous.
Thank you very much.
And I'll be in charge
of the accounting.
Absolutely.
Detective.
[laughing]
Good work you two.
You know, Penelope was right.
You keep this going,
I might have a few clients
to send your way myself.
Eleonore? Is that actual
approval I'm hearing?
Something like that.
Hmm.
So I'll see you tonight?
Tonight.
Mmm.
Can't wait.
Birdie. One second.
Penelope was very impressed
with what you and Alden did.
You two seem... better.
We are.
Hey, Mom. I mean... Eleonore.
I'm sorry that I was so
distracted around here.
No.
I'm the one that should
be apologizing.
I can admit that I pushed
you too hard,
and what I don't wanna do
is push you away.
I think this is where we hug.
Not in the office, dear.
Missing persons investigations.
Who...
[knocks on door]
I'm so sorry I'm late.
[Thumbs] Oh, hi. Come on in.
Thanks.
[Thumbs] Mrs. Case,
glad you could make it.
Hi.
- [Thumbs] Okay...
- Thank you.
Missing persons investigations.
Who knows where to start
with something like this?
[Alden] I mean, everyone is
saying that Rick is the hero,
but when you think about it,
he was just sitting in his car
the whole time.
Well, I mean, he did kinda...
you know...
save your life.
Well...
[Birdie] Are you
expecting somebody?
No.
Hello?
Mr. And Mrs. Case.
I got your name
from Penelope Grant.
I need your help.
- Of course. Come on in.
- Thanks.
[Birdie] So... how can we help?
[Woman] I don't even know
where to start.