[drums]
Let's do things differently this time.
So differently.
His name is Miles Morales.
He was bitten by a radioactive spider,
and he's not the only one.
He hasn't always had it easy.
And he's not the only one.
And now he's on his own.
You think you know the rest.
You don't.
I thought I knew the rest, but...
I didn't.
I didn't wanna hurt him.
But I did.
And he's not the only one.
-Hey!
Stealth Leopard!
-Gwen!
Is the song over?
[Gwen] Seems over.
-Are you okay?
-Dude, you don't hang out,
-and you don't wanna talk...
-I didn't join a band so I could talk about my feelings!
-Well, I did.
-I joined it so I could hit my feelings with sticks!
-Yo, if you don't tell someone what's going on...
-you're gonna snap.
-I'm fine.
-That's not how someone who's "fine" would say that.
-You say,
"I'm great, thanks!
-How are you?"
-[sarcastically] I'm great!
-Thanks!
-Whoa.
How are you?
Fine...?
Gwen, come on.
I don't get you, man.
You're right!
I play drums.
[Gwen] I always wanted to be in a band.
Guess I just never found the right one.
In this line of work,
You always find out the solo act.
But before Miles,
-[past Gwen] What-? How many of these did you take?
-[present Gwen] ...there was Peter.
I think they look great, I dunno.
Is this...that...dangerous mask?
I don't know, I...she seems like a good guy.
Why wear a mask if you've got nothing to hide?
Alright, no politics at the dinner table.
Thank you, May.
But they didn't really know me.
And I didn't really know him, either.
Touch him again, Ned.
[Peter] Gwen, it's okay.
...Until it was too late.
[grunts]
-Hey, Gwen!
-Hey!
Peter?
[screaming]
What?
No...!
-No, no! No, no, no, no...what did you do?
I just...wanted to be special.
-Like you...
Gwen.
Gwen...?
-Don't worry.
Who's Gwen?
Everything's gonna be okay.
-Don't...don't go!
-Everything's gonna be okay...
Oh, Peter...
Hey, hey!
Hey!
Peter...?
I never really made another friend, after that.
Except one.
But he's not here.
And there's no way to get there.
[Jameson] Hush your mouths as captain George Stacy
leads the manhunt for Spiderwoman! Who is she?
And why won't she show her face?!
-Peter Parker, an innocent young man...[fading]
-I've known May and Ben Parker for twelve years.
Peter Parker ate at my table.
He was my daughter's best friend.
And I will not rest until I find this Spiderwoman.
[George] Oh! Hey, hey, hey, hey.
How's the band?
[stilted] Uhh...uh, yeah, great. Uh, I quit, so...you know.
Thumbs up.
We, uh...we caught a break in the Spiderwoman case.
Oh.
That's...good.
We're close.
I'm telling ya, I can feel it.
[Gwen clears throat]
...Me, too.
It'll be good for us.
Don't be so sure.
She killed your friend.
You don't know that.
What do you mean I don't know that? I do know that.
Y'know--I was there.
-She ran from the scene...
-Maybe she didn't have a choice.
I've got a job to do, Gwen.
It won't bring him back!
Uh...I don't wanna argue about this.
Okay?
Yeah. I can tell.
Say, uh...
Too punk rock to give your old man a hug-
-[radio] All units, possible superhuman event.
-Guggenheim Musem, suspect is Adrian Toomes...
-Oh, hey. This could be it.
-...also known as the Vulture.
-So...I, uh...
I'll see you later?
[exhales] Cool.
Um, I'll--I'll call.
-Local.
49 currently on scene. It's a real mess down here.
We're gonna need all the help we can get.
-This is Captain Stacy. I'm 5 out.
I need you to look alive, there's a good chance our girl shows up.
Tonight's the night we catch Spiderwoman.
[click]
Oh, great.
[crowd chattering] [Vulture laughing]
Fury.
Explain to me how a guy with a 40 foot wingspan
just waltzed into the Guggenheim unnoticed?
Hey, it's New York. Everyone's got their thing.
-[Vulture speaking Italian]
-You know what he wants?
-Do you speak Italian?
-Uhhh...
I'm an Irish cop.
Maybe you love pasta or something.
Everybody, on my signal!
Look out for signs of Spiderwoman!
[grunts]
Hey-mmph!
We found her.
-[deep voice] How's the manhunt for me going?
-[George grunting]
[shouting]
Good to know!
[echoing] Vulture!
Well, screaming their name usually works.
[Vulture roaring]
[Gwen grunts]
I guess that worked...
I am the Vulture, the pinnacle of man's genius!
You're not my Vulture. What are you, made of parchment?
What cursed world have you brought me to?
[grunting]
You're glitching, huh? Been there.
Uh, where you from, bud?
I am an artist! An engineer!
Oh, great. A renaissance man.
-Yes!
Cool, let me guess.
You were having an espresso in some old-timey Leonardo DaVinci dimension,
-and suddenly a portal opens up, and you wind up here,
-[Vulture screams]
[screams]
Am I warm?
Yes, that's pretty much it.
Sidebar? Uh,
maybe you could stop making a mess of the art museum for no reason?
You call this art?
We're talking about it, aren't we?
Oh, that's cool.
[Vulture roaring]
I mean, it's more of a meta-commentary on what we call art,
-but it's--it...
-[Vulture grunts]
...it's also...art?
Oh, look! It's your cousin.
[Screaming]
I wouldn't play with fire, dude, you're kind of made of paper!
Ohh, no.
[Shouting]
[Miguel speaks Spanish]
I'm sorry, who exactly are you supposed to be?
That's classified.
You're...the Blue Panther.
No.
The Caped "Blue-cader"?
No, I'm...
Dark Garfield?
No. Stop.
Macho Libre?
I'm from another dimension.
[sarcastically] You are?
Wooow...
Actually, I'm not confused.
My name...is Miguel O'Hara.
[Heroic music]
I lead an elite strike force dedicated to the security of the multiverse...
Actually, forget it.
[Music winds down]
Can you go to any dimension you want with that watch...
-...thing?
-It's...
-much cooler than a watch.
Okay! Sensitive.
Look, there is a big flying turkey from the renaissance
I have to bring to justice, so if you don't mind.
It's alright, kid.
[Gwen] Wow.
[Miguel] I'll take it from here.
Okay. Knock yourself out.
Well...why are you saying it like that?
[Miguel grunts]
-[Miguel] You're not funny!
Oh, I don't know...[laughs]
It's really fun cleaning up your shocking mess, by the way.
What mess?
Kingpin's collider!
What are you guys talking about?
[Gwen] None of your business!
[Miguel] You shut up!
-[Vulture] Hey!
Nosy.
-[Vulture roars]
-[Gwen] We saved the multiverse!
[Miguel] You left a hole wide enough for guys like him
-to randomly get shot into the wrong dimension!
Now I'm stuck putting everybody back where they belong
before all of time and space collapses!
Now, don't even get me started on Dr. Strange, the little nerd back on Earth 1999999!
Who's Doctor Strange?
Sounds like he maybe shouldn't practice medicine.
-[George grunts]
-[Gwen in deep voice] Sorry Captain,
-can't talk right now! I'll be back!
-Wait! Hey!
[laughing]
[Gwen] So, you want me to handle this one, or...?
Huh. Okay.
Ay, por Dios, he's got Hammerspace!
[Laughs]
Lyla? Can you please...
y'know...
Nah, you gotta say it, first.
[sighs]
[quickly] Call for backup.
What?
Call for backup.
C'mooon.
Please, just call for--
Yeah I already called her.
[groans]
But I enjoyed thaaat~!
Spiderwoman.
Me, too.
Uh--are you, uhh...
Oh, this?
We don't know the sex yet,
my husband wants it to be a surprise. [laughs]
He's really corny. [laughs] But so hot!
Will you adopt me?
What...?
What? What??
-[crash]
-[Miguel] Guys!
-Can we focus on the big fire-breathing threat to time and space, please?!
Yep! Yep, yep, yep, yep.
[screams]
[slowed-down grunt]
What about her?
No.
We could use the help--
Is it 'cuz she called you Dark Garfield?
No!
Do you say anything but no-?
No.
Yes!
Why not?
You know why.
Enough of this.
-Take a good look at my great fire from my backpack!
-[Miguel grunting]
[screams]
[Miguel] Don't let him out!
He'll disrupt the canon!
[Vulture speaking Italian]
[Vulture screams]
-[police] Go to the ground!
-[Miguel] Will you get out of here?!
We have you surrounded!
[Miguel] I'm a good guy!
You don't look like a good guy!
You're just gonna have to shut up and trust-
No!
-[Vulture laughing]
-Mayday! Mayday!
[screams]
[grunts]
[crowd screaming]
[music slows]
[screaming]
[straining]
[crowd screams]
-[metal groaning]
-[crowd] Whoa!
Yeah, I think it's a Banksy.
[Miguel] That's what I was gonna do.
[panting]
[grunts]
Whew.
[sighs]
[clicking] Ugh!
Hands in the air!
Captain, come on.
Suspect is armed.
With what? I'm--I'm out of webs!
Get down on the ground!
Which is it? Hands in the air, or get down on the ground?
You're under arrest.
I just saved a bunch of people!
For the murder of Peter Parker.
-Captain, come on. I-
-You have the right to remain silent.
-You don't understand!
-Anything you say...
You don't understand.
Dad...
I...I've thought about...telling you.
But you can see why I didn't want to.
You can see why I didn't wanna tell you.
I didn't murder Peter.
-I didn't--I...
-I didn't know it was him!
-I didn't have a choice!
-How long...
have you been lying to me?
Can you just--
can you just not be a cop for a second, and be my dad here,
and listen to me?
Do you really think...
I'm a murderer?
You're in this to help people, right?
Right?
-So am I!
And the way to help right now is to listen to me!
-Please, Dad.
You're all I have left.
[shakily] You have a right to remain silent.
-Uhh, what?
-Anything you say can and will be used
-Dad, are you really this afraid of me?!
-against you in a court of law. You have a right to an attorney...
No! Stop!
Don't get any closer!
-Dad!
-[gently] Hey, hey, hey. C'mon.
Just breathe.
We got you.
Right, Miguel?
[sighs]
[Miguel] Lyla.
Scan this mess.
No further anomalies.
[Lyla] Canon remains intact.
-[Jess] We can't just leave her here.
She's doing this on her own.
[crying]
I don't know how to fix this.
Yeah.
Well...
Join the club.
-[Rio] I know he's just a sophomore,
but we wanna get a jump on the college conversation, so...
I'm sure he's gonna be...
here. Any minute.
[laughing] He's very serious about his future.
Uhh...
-[Spot] 'Scuse me, do you have, uhh...
-[cashier yawning]
...an ATM machine?
Yeah, right around here, in the back.
-Preferrably not chained to the wall?
-What?
-[Spot] Uh, nothing!
This should be simple enough.
Just make a hole...
grab the money.
Oh! That's not right.
Just get the-...ugh...
[grunts]
[awkwardly] Give me your money.
Where are you, money? Where are you?
[exclaims]
Oh...
[groaning]
[muffled whistling]
Whoa!
-Hey, who left this ATM on the sidewalk?!
-[Spot] Augh!
[grunting]
Yo, what you doing back there, man?
-Nothing!
Nothing, everything is--everything's cool, man!
All good!
-Just forgot my pin number!
-Get your butt out of here!
-Ahh! No!
Sir, please! Just let me rob you!
-[cashier] I'm going to rob your [unintelligible] face!
-[Spot] There's no reason to bring wood into this!
I've never robbed anybody in my life,
[microwave beeping]
please don't make this a bad experience for me!
-[cashier] Bad experience?
-[microwave humming]
-I'm trying to run a business, here!
[Spot] I have this whole-[whoosh]
Oh, wow. Is this curry powder?
We'll say I'm a scientist.
I was. I am!
-[Spot] I...anyway.
-[cashier shouting]
-[Spot] You heard of Alchemax? I used to-
-[microwave beeps]
[casually] I used to work there.
-[Spot] I was actually considered handsome, by scientist standards.
-[cashier grunting]
But I had a little accident...!
[Spot grunting]
[grunts]
Hey!
Oof!
-[Spot] I'm so sorry!
First of all, I'm not even robbing you,
I mean, this ATM machine doesn't even belong to you, right?
This belongs to the bank!
-[Spot] They're the real criminals!
-[cashier] You're the real criminal! You're robbing me!
Y'know, I can't really get a job anywhere anymore,
being like this, so I've turned to a life of crime,
-[Spot] ...I'm having trouble finding...ah!
-[Miles] Why do people say "ATM machine"?
Who said that?
The M stands for "machines".
Spider--aahh!
[groaning]
-Hey, Lenny. How much do I owe you for this beef patty, man?
-[Spot groaning indistinctly]
Spider, if you catch him, it's on the house, brother.
Oww!
Oh! Spiderman. Wow.
[crash] Ahh!
This is real!
So, are you like, a cow, or a dalmation?
I am...
[music swells dramatically]
The Spot.
[laughing]
We meet again, Spiderman.
[Miles laughing]
-Oh, that's funny to you?
-Of course not.
No.
So, is that a costume?
Unfortunately for both of us, this is skin.
Oh, dang.
You see...
[music swells dramatically]
I'm from your past.
One year ago...
[phone notification]
Hold up.
Oh, come on!
[Miles] Uh oh.
-Well, this has been fun, um...
-Who are you talking to?
-But I really gotta wrap this up.
-[politely] No, no, no! No, go ahead, take your call.
[screams]
[muffled] This job is so dumb sometimes!
[muffled groaning]
Maybe just pay me now.
[Miles] Okay, let's do this one last time.
My name is Miles Morales.
I was bitten by a radioactive spider,
and for the last year and four months,
I've been Brooklyn's one and only Spiderman.
And things are going great.
-[Miles] Hey, hey, hey, hey!
-[screaming, crashing]
-Whoo!
-You could hurt somebody!
[Miles] Catching all sorts of bad guys,
[Miles grunts]
Can't you just act like a regular supervillain so I can catch you?
[screaming uncomfortably]
I designed my new suit,
with some fly ambience down the side.
Aunt May moved to Florida,
[Miles] Done.
I guest hosted Jeopardy.
Endorsed baby powder,
apologized for endorsing baby powder,
my mustache came in,
[deep voice] Mustache.
-[bystanders laughing]
-[Miles] ...and out.
Been developing a new twist on my venom thing.
Zap!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
-[Miles] Sorry!
-How much longer can I keep lying about who really I am?
-[Jameson talking indistinctly about Spiderman]
I hear that new Spiderman is Puerto Rican.
[awkward laughing] Nahh, he...
he seems more Dominican to me.
-I mean, would they get it if I told them?
[both] We love you and accept you,
even though you have been lying to us for a year!
Maybe in some other universe.
Sometimes I just...
wish I wasn't the only one.
I don't dwell on it.
I miss my uncle, sometimes.
Miles, I see exactly what you're doing here.
Even though he...turned out to be the Prowler.
I try to do what he told me.
Just keep going.
-[Spot] You're looking at your texts?
-You understand this is the fight of our lives, right?
-Sorry, sorry.
-Just--just a second.
-Oh, okay.
No, no, no. No, go ahead. Take one call.
-You turn off your phone at a movie theater, but you don't turn it off when you're fighting me?
-One sec.
-[Jeff] Ah! "In a minute".
Ahh, he wrote it all as one word.
That's cute, right? Youth.
Ohhh, my nose!
-Sorry, I just-
-[Spot crying]
I really gotta be somewhere-
-Sike.
-[Miles screams]
[Screaming]
[tapping]
[Jeff] Heh. There's bubbles now. Hold on.
Whoa!
[Spot shouting] ...I think this is going great!
[Miles screams]
-[Miles and Spot screaming]
-...Still bubbles on here.
You know, I think it's probably okay.
[squawk]
[Spot] We're figuring it out! We're finding our rhythm!
I've been waiting for this moment for a really long time, so...
[swan squawking]
-[Spot] Hey, where'd the goose come from?
-Whoa!
I don't think I want this costume anymore.
-Almost there, Mami...smiley face...
-[Spot grunting]
Great. Is this your goose?
Get it off me, get it off me, get it--[grunts]
Ow!
-[Miles] At the end of the day,
[Spot] I got you right where I-
ow!
[Spot grunting]
-I'm Spiderman.
-No one can take that away from me.
-Unbelievable.
Come back here, nemesis!
Don't escape!
Your costume's too tight in the back, by the way!
Yo, what's up, man?
Umm, writing an essay.
There's a bad guy on the roof of the Peterson building. Can you call the police?
-Tell them to pick him up?
-I dunno. Sounds like a slippery slope.
Just this one time?
It starts with one call, then it's walkie talkies and synchronized watches...
in a month, it'll be a spider signal...
[muffled] I'm not your guy in the chair.
Are those my Jordans?
I can't help it if we're the same size.
[bell ringing]
-[counselor] You see, every person is a universe.
And my job is to capture your person's universe
on this piece of paper.
That's blank.
-[counselor] Exactly.
I have no idea who this kid is.
I don't know if he knows.
And he's gotta decide if he's gonna commit himself to his future,
[bell ringing]
-[muffled] ...or whatever he's doing instead of being here.
Can't have your cake and eat it, too.
Unless you bake two cakes!
Rio: Miles?
Jeff: Miles!
[flatly] Interest in comedy.
How's this going?
-Now, son, what have we always said?
-College! Woo-woo!
[all] On time means five minutes early.
I know! I know, I know, I know. Look.
I gotta get back to being a great student, so can we make this quick?
-[counselor] Okay.
Miles' grades are pretty good.
A in AP physics,
That's my little man!
and AP studio art,
[chuckles] He takes after his uncle.
-A- in English,
He's a tough grader.
And a B in Spanish.
-What?!
-Whoo, okay.
-Miles. [Speaking Spanish]
-Are you trying to kill your mother?!
Calmate, Mami.
Eso no es my fault!
[speaking Spanish] ..."my fault"?
[speaking Spanish] ...Spanglish!
Mom, I just missed a few classes!
Oh, just a few classes. Well, what's "a few"?
-[casually] I mean, you know, like...
...five?
Five?!
[counselor] Actually, six.
You're dead.
-Mom.
-[Jeff mutters]
-[sighs] He takes after his uncle.
-Wait, wait, wait. But...
But I...
-I just have a lot going on.
-Alright.
We can still salvage this.
I'm sorry, "salvage"?
Miles has a great story to tell.
Having a story at all seems gross.
Your name is Miles Morales.
Correct.
You grew up in a struggling immigrant family.
I'm from Puerto Rico. Puerto Rico's part of America...
We own a fort in Brooklyn. I-I don't know about struggling...
-[Jeff muttering]
-It doesn't matter. You're all struggling.
[quietly] I'll be captain next week.
And now, his dream is to attend the top physics program in the nation!
Whatever it takes, we'll do it!
At Princeton University.
In New Jersey?!
No, no, no no no no! That's too far!
New Jersey's too far from New York?!
There's great schools in Brooklyn!
Princeton has the best quantum researchers in the country!
-[muttering] ...Quantum research...mm-hmm.
-They're moving electrons across dimensional thresholds!
...Electrons, uh-huh.
I mean, they're studying dark matter!
Yeah, I don't know what any of that means.
I could help figure out how to travel to other dimensions.
[laughing skeptically] Yeah, okay.
Oh, yeah. That sounds like a really good fake job.
Dad. When you were my age,
you followed your dream, and went out on your own,
to start a business with Uncle Aaron.
-Right?
-That's...different.
We used to...see, when you were born,
[laughs] plus your mom used to...
[firmly] Look, life is a journey.
You all got me into this school 'cuz you thought I could do something special.
And now, I think so, too.
And the special thing I wanna do is this.
There are people out there who can literally teach me the things I wanna learn.
But they aren't all in Brooklyn.
[thud]
That's your story!
-[counselor] Now, just stick to the script.
-[ringing]
-[Jeff muffled] Miles, you okay?
-[indistinct]
-Ooh, I gotta go.
-You...
You guys just keep talking!
-This is all great stuff!
-Miles, wait!
Did you order the cake for tonight?
Yeah, totally! I'm--you know, call me! Uhh-
I gotta go. Alright? Uhh--bye!
This kid.
I swear. What are we gonna do with him?
[radio clicks] All units,
-supervillain event over on...
-I-I gotta go.
What?!
You're gonna leave, too-?
You leave--everybody leaves.
[stammering] Why am I here?
-Why am I here? Why am I still here?
-I know. I'm so sorry.
-But we'll figure it out.
Together.
Wow.
Excuse me. I-I'm so sorry.
-He's lying to you.
Jeff?
-Your son.
He's lying. And I think you know it.
How's your essay?
Marinating.
This is part of my process.
Oh. Oh, really?
[laughs] I think your guy got away.
Thanks. I'm on it.
-Yeah, you seem really stressed.
I agree!
-You're stretched too thin. I've been worried-
-Yeah, alright. Thanks for the tip!
-[Spot] C'mere!
-[Miles screams]
-That was bad.
-[Jeff] I know.
What is really going on with this kid?
I don't know!
[crash]
Hey!
-Spiderman!
-Officer Morales!
I mean, umm...
[deep voice] Officer Morales.
[Spot] This is not what it looks like.
Hey! Hey!
-Officer...! [grunts]
-My kid goes here, man!
Yo!
I'm on the PTA!
You know how many lemon bars I gotta bake for that?
[Spot] Who laughs in the middle of a fight?
I did not!
-[Miles] It was...
-[Jeff] Are you serious?!
-[Spot] It was inconsiderate and super rude!
...And a little cocky--oof!
[Jeff] Yeah, you got me agreeing with the bad guy right now.
Bad guy? He's barely a villain of the week!
What'd you call me?
-You realize I'm right here.
-C'mon, man!
-Everything-
[Jeff screams]
[Miles] ...is under control!
Of course we'd end up back here.
-[Jeff] Well, you know what? You are just like my son!
-I am? I--[laughs] That's so silly! I--what?
-Imagine that.
-Back...where it all...
-started!
-Watch out!
-[Spot] The crucible of our connection!
-[Miles] Hey, don't try to wow me with big words.
-I do the crossword every day.
[exhales]
[tense music]
[music stops]
[music resumes]
-[Spot] Is it all coming back to you?
-What are you talking about?
The creation event!
What?
[phone ringing]
Ah!
Yeah?
Hey, baby. We got cut off.
-[Rio talking indistinctly]
-[Jeff screams]
-[Rio] Nothing is more important than management.
[Screams]
Yeah, I'm kinda in the middle of something.
[Spot grunts]
Destiny brought us here!
You see now, don't you?
[deep voice] I-I really don't.
I am your nemesis.
You're not my nemesis.
[sing-song] You missed!
-Can't contain the Spot--augh!
You really don't remember what you did to me?
-What I did for you?
Uhhh...
No.
I worked at Alchemax.
I ran a test on this collider
that brought a spider here from another dimension.
-[Octavius] 42.
-[Spot] Its home dimension...
It escaped.
And it bit you.
My spider made you Spiderman!
What?
You ran through the cafeteria.
He took a bagel!
You hit me with a bagel!
[screaming in pain]
I've hit a lot of different villains with a lot of different food!
You make your flippy, little sassy jokes,
and everyone loves them.
-But no one knows what it feels like...
to be on the other side of them.
I'm just trying to lighten the mood, y'know...?
I created you!
And you created me.
Spiderman, why did you create that guy?
I-I didn't!
He's talking crazy!
I was in this collider room when you blew it up!
[screaming]
-Because of you,
I lost my job,
my life...
my face!
-[crowd laughing]
-My family won't even look at me!
I made you into a hero!
You made me into this!
[distorted] Look at me!
You did this to me!
Look at me!
I'll make you respect me!
Yaah! Ahh! Ow!
[grunting]
[screaming] I am your...
[fading] nemesis...!
[Miles panting]
Well, what...
where'd he go?
He...kicked his own butt.
You know we're supposed to catch 'em, the bad guys. Right?
I always do!
...Usually.
Gutierrez, get the crane, man!
-Yes, sir!
-[groaning] Ohh, this here is why nobody likes us, man.
Us...?
I am trying to do right out here.
I mean...I'm trying, too-!
-And you need to be a better role model.
-I'm a great role model!
[siren] [crashing]
Hey, Gutierrez.
You can cancel the crane.
I swear...[muttering]
Uhhh...
Do you wanna talk about it...?
Are you crazy?!
Well, men of your generation ignore their mental health too much.
-[Jeff laughing]
[shakily] What am I--what am I even doing?
'Cuz no matter what I do, someone always thinks I'm blowing it.
I know the feeling.
So...your son!
How's he doing?
-You think he's gonna figure it all out?
-[Jeff sighs]
Honestly?
[hesitantly] ...Yeah...
He's a good kid...
[excitedly] Yeah?
Y'know, it's scary. He says these things that are so smart,
-Cool! Well, I should probably-
...and he does these things that are so stupid.
[sighs] I just don't want him to mess it up.
[muttering] Maybe get off the kid's ass.
I'm sorry, what?
What? What--I...I don't know!
And I hate that he's not being honest with me!
Maybe he's scared to talk to you.
[loudly] Why would anyone be scared to talk to me?!
[stammering] Uhh...I don't--I don't know.
It's just...
you're getting pretty good at being a parent, you think...
you got it lit.
And then they go and grow up.
I just don't wanna lose him. Y'know?
Well...
as an objective observer with no skin in the game,
I say...
you gotta let him spread his wings, man.
Like this.
...Yeah.
[Jeff laughs] I don't know.
If this isn't nice...what is?
I should go.
Yeah, and--and catch that holes guy.
Don't worry.
I don't think that guy's gonna show his face again.
What?
Okay...
I think I kicked myself...
...into myself.
Well, this is new.
Helloooo...!
Hello! Echo, echo, echo--no echo.
Hypothesis:
I'm going to put my head in that hole.
[screams]
[Spot grunting]
Ow! Ow, ow, ow! Stop it, stop it, stop it!
[sighs]
That was...
cool!
My holes can take me anywhere.
[lego people screaming] [legos crashing]
[Spot chuckling]
'Scuse me!
-Hi.
Sorry to bug you, I know you're busy, sorry.
-What do you want?
-I know it's weird, I just came out of nowhere,
but I think I'm becoming a trans-dimensional superbeing.
So?
-So?
I'm literally splitting the fabric of space and time!
For you, it's just a Tuesday night.
You're acting like weird stuff like this happens to you all the time.
Can I have some gum?
Ahhh, whoa!
Wow.
The power of the multiverse in the palm of my hand.
My holes aren't a curse!
They're the answer!
-Can you stop talking about your holes?
You're making everyone uncomfortable over here.
-No, no, no! You're gonna love this. Look, look, look.
[straining]
[groans]
I'm outta spots. Wouldn't ya know it?
Uhh...
-As you were, gentlemen.
I'm coming for you, Spiderman!
Oh no.
-[Jameson] Tomorrow morning, Spiderman.
-Page one with a decent picture this time!
-Uh-huh. Yeah, absolutely right, boss. I'm--
Shut up.
Uh-huh.
-Get outta here!
-You got it, boss.
I'm on it!
God, I need a raise.
Beep, beep!
Miguel, it's Peter.
We got an anomaly.
Thank you, Peter. You're one of our best.
Jess? Who's on this?
Beep, beep.
Have you seen Miles?
Nope.
Hey!
What about Miles?
Nope.
Have you seen Miles?
-[speaking Spanish]
-What are you doing?
-Well?
-Speech! Okay, everybody!
-What? No!
Todos! [speaking Spanish]
-[whispering] Oh, dear God, no.
-It's time for the speech!
Rio, come on.
[quietly] Ummm...
[into the mic] Hi.
-[Miles] "And I want you to know, no matter what,
even though we've had our ups and downs,
I am so proud of you today!
-And every day!" Parenthesis, "mostly.
-Hey. Umm, hey.
-"LOL". Heh. "PS--"
-Hey, Mr. Spiderman.
It won't fit on one cake.
Can't you write smaller?
Can't you write shorter?
-[baker] Come again!
-[Rio] Uhhh, what else can I say about Jeff?
That he was almost ten pounds as a baby!
I know, I know! You're gonna be embarrassed. You're gonna be...
[muttering]...he almost killed his mother. Look at those shoulders.
-Oh, no. Okay, okay, okay, that's it, okay.
-He was a big baby.
-Oh my God! [laughing]
-Okay. [laughing awkwardly]
-Oh, he's so funny!
-Ohh, I'll take the mic. No more mics for you.
-Thank you Rio, for that.
-[through her teeth] Where is that kid?
-[Jeff] You know, I didn't always know what I wanted to do in life.
-I was pulled in a lot of different directions when I was young.
-You know, me and my brother came up in this neighborhood,
-just a couple of knuckleheads running the streets.
[villain exclaiming]
[villain grunts]
[chuckling] You guys used to...
-chase us outta your stores, and now,
-Hey! Taxi!
-if you can believe it, it's my job to look out for you.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-And then, I had a kid,
-Be right back!
-and everything changed.
-For the better.
-I mean, I don't even know about giving a toast, 'cuz I...
-Hey! Hey! Wait!
-I should be toasting you all.
So, to my brother,
who we miss every single day.
[laughing] He's definitely up there laughing at me, right now.
They're making me captain, bro!
To my wife, mi amor,
I can't even start, 'cuz I'll never stop.
You'll have to take the mic from me! [laughing]
And to my son...
[clears throat]
The reason that I do any of this in the first place.
Well, I love you, Miles.
And I will always, always be here for you.
Vinny, man, come on! Drop the beat!
[Rio groaning] I'm gonna kill that kid.
-Hey, congrats, Jeff!
-Hey, hey! Hey! [laughing]
Thank you for coming!
Hey, Miles!
What's up, man?
There you are. You keeping your head up with that school?
Oh, yeah. You bet.
¡Hola!
Hey! Your parents have been looking for you.
I don't know why, I've just been here the whole time.
-¡Oye!
-Aaah!
-Hi!
-You were supposed to be here at 5.
-I know, I know, I know, but-
-You're disrespecting your dad!
-Yep. Mm-hmm.
-Missed his beautiful toast,
Come on, did you even see the cakes?
There's some heartfelt messages on them!
That's...not what I meant.
Your dad studied for 8 months.
9!
It was like giving birth!
[flatly] No it wasn't.
Of course not.
You made us sit in that office to talk to that lady without you!
Gah, it was an emergency!
What, a graffiti emergency?
A party with some friends I've never met emergency?!
Explain yourself.
[muttering] Sounds like you're explaining it pretty well.
Ha. That's funny.
Jeff, we have a funny son.
I'm not laughing.
-¡Hola! [speaking Spanish]
-Hey! [speaking Spanish]
[speaking Spanish]
-I don't feel grown up.
-Wow, this is a cool shirt!
-Okay! Okay, okay.
-It's like a...[unintelligible]
You know, have you checked out the [unintelligible] ?
¡Oye!
Aahh!
Who are you running around with, anyway?
-Just...
-Is it Genki?
I never liked him.
Yes, you did!
He calls me by my first name.
Ugh. We hate that.
I have more friends than just Genki.
Like who?
Well, there's...there's...
Peter.
Y'know? Uhh...
But he left town, umm...there's...
There's Gwanda!
Y'know? She--she also...left town...
Miles, por favor, dame un break.
Is that Spanglish?
Has it ever occurred to you that maybe, I'm just doing...
benign, private, unremarkable things when I'm not with you guys?
-Nope.
-Never.
I am 15 years old!
-I am basically an adult!
-[sarcastically] Oh, right! Right.
-You don't even have a driver's license!
-Neither does Mom!
Because we live in New York, and never plan to leave.
-It's my life!
-It's not your life!
It's mine. And your father's, and your abuelos y abuelas,
who put you in this spot I'd give anything to be in.
Alright, alright. Whatever. Whatever.
Whatever?
-Woooow.
-Whatever?!
[laughing] Do I get to say it?
-Please tell me that I can say it.
-Say it.
You're grounded!
What?
Oh, yeah!
For how long?
-A month!
-Dad!
Mom, are you--
Seriously?
Yeah! Dead serious!
You don't understand!
You're right! You are right!
I have no idea what's going on with you!
-[music gets louder]
-[Jeff] So, why don't you tell me?
-[Miles] Just listen to me!
Okay, champ! You got it!
Go for it. Say whatever you wanna say.
What do you got to tell me so bad?!
[sighing]
You know what?
Never mind.
[Jeff] Alright, great. Walk away.
Because now you got two months!
That was good, right?
[sighs]
Two months.
I'm Spiderman.
I'm not grounded.
-[Gwen, muffled] Miles!
-Miles!
Got a minute?
Whoa! What...
[stammering] H-how did you get...
How did you get-
How have you been?
Uhh--I've been...good.
I've been...yeah, just great.
Look at you!
You, uhh...you grew, huh?
-Had a little growth spurt?
-Uhh, yeah.
Your hair has gotten...
pinker.
Is this the room you grew up in?
It is.
Umm...but...
My dorm room is--is...[deeper voice] very adult.
Cool, yeah, no, I used to play with these when I was younger, too.
[nervously] Uhh, that's...
-that's a...that's a collectible.
-Wow!
-I used to have this one!
-Actually, that's an
-extremely rare...highly sought-after...
-Why is it still in the package?
[groans in pain]
Um...
[uncomfortable laughing]
[tense] That's fine.
-Hey!
-Are these your drawings?
-What? No.
-Wow, they're good!
Wow, there's...
so...many...
Missed you, too.
So...
what are you doing here?
I-I mean, I...thought I'd...
never see you again.
Wanna get outta here?
I'm...grounded.
Bummer.
Is Spiderman grounded?
Uhhh...
I mean, I-
[chuckling]
[Rio] Miles?
Your dad's ready to listen now.
That's three months!
[Miles] Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
There's an elite society with all the best Spiderpeople in it?
Okay, so there's this lady.
-Jess Drew. She rides a motorcycle,
-Uh-huh?
-A motorcycle?
-Oh my gosh, I'm learning so much from her!
Oh, yeah, I've...I've learned a lot of stuff, too.
I've leveled up my whole thing!
See?
-Eh?
-Oh, yeah? Let's see it, then.
[Miles] Let's go!
Thread the needle!
Whoa!
[screaming]
Easy!
-[Miles laughing]
-And Miguel.
[echoing] The whole thing was his idea.
And...who's Miguel?
Oh, he's like a...ninja, vampire Spiderman, but a good guy?
A vampire good guy!
I'd pay good money to see that.
So, how long ago did they invite you?
Uh, only, like...a few months ago.
"Months" is kind of a long time, isn't it?
Okay, this one counts as two.
Whooo!
[laughing]
Look at you.
Look at me!
-[Miles] Keep the change!
[Miles] So, this club...
Look at that dumb-dumb.
...What kind of stuff do you do?
Guy in the stripes. Ten points.
-We're trying to keep the multiverse from collapsing.
I thought we did that already.
Like, last week we had this mission to some Shakespeare dimension,
What?
-And Hobie and I just, like...
-Wait, wait, wait.
-Who--who's Hobie?
-Oh my gosh,
you would love him!
He lets me crash in his dimension sometimes.
Hey, what does that mean? You stay overnight, or...?
Anyway, listen, they're--they're pretty strict about where I go, or I...
I really would've come to see you sooner.
Right...
so, uhh...
so...so why'd you come now?
[smearing]
Don't--don't do that.
Ah!
Hey, Gw-...
uhh...Gwen?
Where'd you go?
Where'd she go...?
Ah!
Oh, hey. There you are.
What are you doing?
Waitin' for you.
[Miles and Gwen laughing]
[Gwen] This is a cool thinking spot.
Right?
I mean, who needs a treadmill when you have the Williamsburg Bank building?
So, uhh...you and your dad.
You still haven't talked?
What exactly would we talk about? [laughs]
"Hey, Dad. How's the last few months been?"
[quietly] "You still think I murdered my best friend?"
Oh.
I mean, my parents...
I mean, maybe if I told them-
Don't.
Trust me on that.
Well...
Maybe, some things are supposed to be just for us.
[Gwen] Hmm.
That's a nice way to think about it.
I'm just...a really emotionally intelligent guy.
Beyond my years.
[chuckles]
You know, it really is always so great to talk to you.
Yeah?
Yeah.
[Miles chuckles]
I mean...how many people can you talk to about this stuff?
You don't even know.
[Gwen sighs]
[chuckling] What?
You're the only friend I've ever really made, after Peter died.
...Other than Hobie. Right?
That's different.
Yeah? How's that?
I don't know. You...
and me...it's...
We're...the same.
In the important ways.
Y'know?
[Laughs]
In every other universe, Gwen Stacy falls for Spiderman.
And in every other universe...
it doesn't end well.
Well...
there's a first time for everything, right?
[chuckles]
-[Gwen] Mmm!
[chewing] Oh, wow.
Feelings make me hungry.
Oh, yeah.
These plátanos are just deep fried filling.
She looks old enough to vote.
I bet she doesn't even speak Spanish.
[speaks Spanish]
This keeps you from glitching in other dimensions?
-Yeah. It's pretty cool.
What's it gonna take for Miguel O'Hara to notice Miles Morales?
[chuckles] I'll put in a good word.
I'm just saying. If I had a watch, I could come with you.
Miles...
-Look...
-I did save the multiverse!
It's a...really small, elite strike force...
-I can turn invisible, I have like, electric powers...
-There's just-
-There aren't a lot of slots.
-Think about it!
Uh-huh. Right.
-Look, if it was up to me, you-
-Oh, I know. I know.
Oh, no! No, no, no! Don't do that! Miles!
[scoffs]
-Alright. Jeez.
-It's, uhh...it's really delicate.
[sighs]
Sorry. Didn't mean to, um...snap.
Okay. Alright. I'm sorry.
Helloooo!
[both exclaim]
-Hi. [laughs] I'm Miles' mom.
-Oh, boy.
Rio! Hi!
I've heard so much about you!
Huh. You're using my first name. Okay!
This is nice. We found it in Miles' room, so...
I guess you must've been there. Huh?
And you must be Jeff.
[chuckling quietly] She called me Jeff. Heh, seriously. Jeff.
[firmly] You must mean Lieutenant Morales.
Soon to be Captain Morales.
Ah! Captain. [laughs]
Gwanda and I are friends from school.
Yeah, yeah. We were just catching up.
Ohhh.
Don't take him from me!
-[laughing]
-Mom!
I'm just kidding. He's grounded, so you can't.
-Don't break his heart.
-Mom!
[ringing] Shoot!
-Shoot, I have to go.
-[muffled speech from watch]
Really?
Yeah, I, uh...forgot to get my steps in! [awkward laugh]
Uhh, really...really wish I could stay longer.
I, uh...[whispers] I'm sorry.
Goodbye.
...Yeah. Bye.
I can hear you being quiet, Mom.
I, um...
hope I didn't ice your game, man.
No one my age says those words in that order, Mom.
It's just...
hard, to see my little man not be my little boy all the time.
Yeah.
I hope you know you can tell me anything.
[speaks Spanish]
Well...
I'm...
[sighs]
I'm sorry I was late.
Go.
She seems like a...nice girl.
Is this a trick?
It's not a trick.
Jeez.
What're you...
Lemme fix you, just...[sighs]
well, for years, I've been taking care of this little boy, right?
Making sure he's loved,
that he feels like he belongs wherever he wants to be,
he wants to go out into the world and do great big things...
and what I worry about most
is...they won't look out for you, like us.
They won't root for you, like us.
So.
Here's the deal.
Wherever you go from here
you have to promise to take care of that little boy for me.
Make sure he never forgets where he came from.
And...
he never doubts that he is loved.
And he never lets anyone
at those big fancy places he's gonna be in...
tell him that he doesn't belong there.
And when he comes home--and he'd better come home!
You're gonna be early,
and you're gonna be holding a normal, nice cake.
[laughing] Yeah, okay.
You gotta promise, Miles.
I promise.
Just...
don't get lost.
Mm-hmm. Yep.
¿Me oyes?
Alright!
Cool.
[speaks Spanish]
[laughs]
Now, get--go. Get outta here.
But when you come back, you're still grounded.
[laughs]
[laughs] Yeah, I'm smiling like it's a joke, but it's true.
Yeah, I-I figured.
See you later.
With a cake.
[grunts]
[phone camera shutters]
Shoot.
Whoa, hey, hey, hey! The car!
[Gwen] Aw, shoot.
Oh, shoot, shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot...
Show me what happened.
[watch] Replay commencing.
-[Spot] ...spots! That's the thing.
[crashing] I need more spots!
[laughs] Oh, my God! It was right under where my...
my nose would've been! I just...
need a little bit more dimensional juice, or whatever.
-[Gwen] Shoot!
-Never did come up with a cool name for that...
Branding was never my strong suit.
[fast forwarding] ...powerline to my micro-collider...prototype,
could generate a little more concentrated dark energy...
[Spot whistling]
-[laughing] This is what I love about heists!
-Shoot, shoot!
I just need enough to get me somewhere with a full-sized collider.
And Spiderman...
I'll make you pay...
for everything you took away from me.
This should work!
Or vaporize me and everything in this building.
Oh, what the heck?
[both] Shoot.
Oh!
I did it!
[exclaiming]
Ow!
Oof...
[straining]
[screaming]
[both] Shoot.
[watch] Replay complete.
No! Why, why, why, why, why?!
[shouts angrily]
Gwen, Gwen, Gwen, Gwen-
Jess: Gwen!
Hi!
-What'cha doing?
Nothing!
Uhh...good! All good.
Yeah, everything's good. Um...
Bye!
Where's the...the bad guy you were supposed to monitor?
Oh, he just stepped out for a moment.
Dude!
Look, he's just some villain of the week!
Lyla?
Oh, we don't need-
Tracking...
Oh, hey, look! I got him!
Nope, never mind.
Hold on--oh!
Slippery guy.
Did you go see your little friend?
What? No! Miles?
I mean...
-Are you kidding me right now?
-Only briefly!
From afar.
How far?
Like...
[muttering] you know...about this...
-About...this far apart...
-Oh, that's way too close.
Girl!
-[Gwen] I just--look, I had to know how he was!
[laughs]
-I can't--I honestly can't with you.
-Look, I know I messed up, okay?!
-[Jess] He can't be part of this.
-[Gwen] I...
-I know.
I'll never see him again.
-Alright?
-No kidding!
Hey, guys? Guys?
He's making his own portals.
What?
-[Lyla] He can jump wherever he wants.
-He could be a total canon-killer.
You said he was a villain of the week!
Do you know how bad this is for you?
Every dimension he stops at has an Alchemax.
What's he up to, Gwen?
-[Gwen] I don't know.
-[Jess sarcastically] No, no! Amazing!
My star pupil, everyone.
I'll get him. Okay?
I can get backup.
If Miguel finds out I let you go-
Don't tell Miguel.
He'll kick me out, and...
what if he sends me home?
I got him!
Earth-50101.
Whaddya wanna do?
You never made a mistake?
Never got too close to someone?
I did.
But I got over it.
Alert the local Spider,
-tell him Gwen will meet him there.
-[Lyla] I'm on it.
-Oh, thank you. Thank you so much,
-Yeah. Okay.
-I promise I will not let you down again.
-You're welcome. Shut up.
You got an hour to fix this,
or I can't help you.
Goodbye, Miles.
[screaming]
[screams]
Ah! Sorry! Sorry!
Whoa!
Oof!
[screaming]
-[Spot echoing] You see that? This is incredible!
-[fading in and out] I'm like a whole new person!
-[Gwen] Where did you go?
-[Spot] If I were to look in the mirror right now,
-Stay still!
-I wouldn't recognize myself,
-but I would envy that person that was on the end!
-Slow down!
-I have eyes on the anomaly.
-[Jess] Try getting hands on.
Stop hovering. You're literally hovering.
Hello! Pardon me, locals!
Wow. Four on there, wow. That's very dangerous.
That looks good!
-Which way to Alchemax--oh!
-[customers screaming]
Hahh! [coughs]
-It's a place with a big collider--[grunts]
-[exclaiming]
Hey, cow spots!
Mooooove over!
That's the best you can do?
-[Miles] Gwen! I'm here to help!
Miles?!
[grunts]
-[Spot] Foot in your face!
-You weren't expecting that, were you?
[crash] [grunts]
Oh, no!
Neither was I! I'm in the zone!
Whoo!
I got you!
-Did you follow me?!
-No!
I just saw where you went, and...
went there without you knowing.
You're not supposed to be here!
What are you talking about? I'm helping-
No!
No, no, no no no no no no! No!
-[grunts]
Whoa!
[Miles grunts]
I shouldn't have ever come to see you.
Dang.
Hyah!
Ahh!
Hey, who's the new guy?
[Gwen] Hey, Pav.
He's Miles, and he wasn't invited.
[laughing] Oooh, you weren't invited, and you came anyway?
Right?
Hey, new guy must be in love with you.
-[Miles] No...!
-[Gwen] Okay, whoa.
I'm not.
-Oh, I'm very good at reading people.
-No, he's not.
Who are you?
I'm glad you asked, new guy!
-I'm not a new guy.
My name is Pravitr Prabhakar.
And, for the past 6 months,
Six?
And even he got a watch?
Yeah, uhh...
Being Spiderman is so easy!
-I wake up, skip the workout, because I'm naturally buff,
and I don't wanna get too big, you know?
Do almost nothing with my amazing hair,
You don't use any product at all?
Just coconut oil, prayer, some genetics...
Then I swing by school, don't really have to try, but I do anyway,
fight a few bad guys,
feed a few street dogs,
quick break for a cup of chai with my Maya auntie,
I love chai tea!
What did you just say...?
"Chai tea"?
-"Chai" means tea, bro!
-Oh.
-You're saying "tea tea!"
-Oh, umm...uh...
Would I ask you for a "coffee coffee"?
-Hmm? Or "cream cream"?
-I'm sorry...I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry.
-Then, I hang out with my girlfriend, Gayatri.
-She's an extremely classy teenager.
Hey, girl. Tonight, I was thinking...
Ah, hello, police inspector Singh!
-This is your daughter, I do not know her.
-And to top it off,
I live in the best possible Spiderman city,
Mumbattan.
Quick tour.
This is where the traffic is,
this is where the traffic is,
this is also where the traffic is,
there's traffic here, too!
And this is where the British stole all of our stuff!
-[Spot] Ahh.
Hello, Spiderman.
-Hi.
-Hey.
Not you.
-[Gwen] Are you talking to him, or me? Or...him?
-[Pavitr] Well, what's that...that's me.
I think he means me.
Yeah. Him.
I got this, guys!
Huh?
Wow! How are you?
Since I leveled up my game,
I'm on a journey of self-improvement!
And you came to India.
That's a Western culture cliche!
[unintelligible]
No, no, no! I did not mean it like that!
Now, let me guess.
You wanna ask me about saffron and cardamom and naan bread,
which is the same as saying "bread bread", which is the same as saying "chai tea"!
Oh, I love chai tea!
No!
[Pavitr screaming] [Gwen grunts]
C'mon, man!
I think maybe we got off on the wrong foot.
Let's talk about this!
Fine.
You made me feel empty, like I had a hole inside of me!
We all have holes.
But now, I found out what to fill that hole up with!
More holes!
That doesn't make any sense!
-It will!
Okay. I'm good.
-Don't worry.
-[Gwen] We won't.
This romantic tension is so palpable!
-Will they, won't they...?
If Spot gets more holes, he'll be unstoppable!
We can't let him get to-
[Gwen] Alchemax?
How can you guys even concentrate?
[scientists scream]
[Pavitr] Hey, does he know about Hobie?
What should I know about Hobie?
Oh, looks like he did not know.
Boop.
Go away. Go away.
See you later. Take some holes.
Hey, you! Could you please deactivate this wonderfully strong barrier?
[scientist] It can't be turned off until the collider sequence is complete!
Collider sequence?
-[Miles] Wait! You don't know what you're doing, man!
-[Gwen] Spot, you need to stop!
I'm about to be so much more than a villain of the week.
-[Miles] I'm sorry I called you that, okay? You're a great villain.
Oh, not yet, I'm not.
[computer] Initializing collider.
No!
[grunting]
How's it going now?
Great!
Anyone got any ideas?
[Pavitr laughing] I have somebody in mind for this!
Stand back.
I've been working on something new.
[Pavitr] I'm not following what's happening right now.
[Miles straining] Just give me a second.
[Gwen] Do--do you want us to do something, or do we just stand here?
Are you like, charging it...?
No, I'm absorbing it so I can send it back!
-[Gwen] It looks like you're just...
-[Pavitr] Does his power have a name?
-[Miles] Please, hold your questions until I'm done breaking this thing!
-[Gwen and Pavitr overlapping]
Just let me do this!
[Hobie] Oi!
Hobie!
[Pavitr] Hobie, my guy!
[Miles] Hobie?
Look at that. Another one.
I love how many different variations of you guys there are. I mean...
My left palm, big step up!
You got me?
What's this dude saying?
[Pavitr] It's English for "we get along great and we're close friends"!
Is this the other one, from 1610?
-Do you understand this guy?
-Huh.
Hey, Hobie! Thanks for breaking the shield!
I loosened it.
Bit of advice:
Use the palm, not just your fingers.
Also, your suit.
Is he bleeding from his armpits?
[quickly] Miles, Hobie. Hobie, Miles.
Hi. I've never heard of you, because Gwen barely ever mentioned you.
Hi, my name's Hobie. Hobie Brown.
I was bitten by a...wouldn't you like to know?
Yeah, I'm here.
And for the last three years, I've been the one and only--wait, wait.
Hang on, wait, wait.
Think I'm gonna show you my secret identity?
Come out of it!
That is, when I'm not playing shows, antagonizing fascists,
staging unpermitted political action-slash-performance art pieces,
Or,
having a laugh at a pub in [unintelligible]
I'm not a role model.
I was briefly a runway model.
I hate the AM, I hate the PM,
I hate labels,
I'm not a hero,
'cuz calling yourself a "hero" makes you a self-mythologizing,
narcissistic autocrat.
Oh, I thought you hated labels.
Gwendy, you left your jumper around my place.
What's a jumper?
It's a sweater.
How many sweaters do you have?
Uh--that's...that's not my nature.
And your toothbrush.
Wait, what?
[Pavitr screams]
Are those my chucks?
[Gwen laughs nervously]
[Gwen grunts]
Y'all make a heck of a team.
[Hobie] I don't believe in teams.
[Miles] Aren't you in a band?
I don't believe in consistency.
This guy is killing me.
Ahh!
[grunts]
This is gonna be good for us, Spiderman.
You and me are finally gonna live up to our potential.
You'll finally have a villain worth fighting,
and I won't be just a joke to you!
[Spot grunts]
You're not a joke! Right, gang?
-[Gwen] Absolutely!
-[Pavitr] Completely unamusing!
-[Hobie] I don't believe in comedy!
[Hobie] Just kidding!
[Miles] See?
No one here thinks you're a joke!
They won't after this.
[Miles] No!
-[Pavitr] Well, that was another easy adventure
-for Spiderman!
-[all] No, no, no!!
[all screaming]
[distorted] I'm coming!
Huh...
What was that?
[distorted] Our future.
I'm gonna take everything from you.
Like you took everything from me.
[whispers] What?
-See you back home...
Spiderman.
[muffled] Miles? Miles!
[muffled overlapped speech]
[Pavitr] Everyone, [speaking Hindi]
[crowd screaming]
We'll clear the path,
you slow down that building!
I'll do it, but not because you told me to.
[straining]
Everybody, run!
[crowd screaming]
[screaming]
No!
[straining]
[Lyla] Gwen, heads up.
Markers are predicting an incoming canon event,
so tread carefully.
-[man exclaims]
-I'm on it.
Somebody help!
-Hurry, everyone! This way, quickly!
-Help!
Inspector Singh!
[straining]
[screaming]
[straining] I can do both...!
Where's your [speaks Hindi]
I got him, I got him!
-Miles!
Don't worry. Thread the needle, ring the bell, right?
It's too dangerous.
I'll be okay, I--I promise.
Miles! No!
-[Pavitr straining]
-Miles!
No!
No, no, no, no...oh...
Please, no!
Miles?
Come on!
[gasps]
You're alright!
I promised.
Oh!
Are you okay? I was so worried!
[clears throat] I mean...
You seem like a nice young woman that I do not know!
[laughs]
Papa!
Gayatri!
Papa?
Not bad, right?
Right.
I have never seen him so emotional!
Excellent job.
Done, done!
Miles, my guy!
[crowd clapping]
[cheering]
So?
Whaddya think?
What I always think.
You're amazing.
We...make a good team.
Yeah?
Yeah.
[rumbling]
[Pavitr] Guys, what's that?
It's a metaphor for capitalism.
It's a lot worse than that.
-[Jess] Okay, guys. Secure the area, clear all civilians,
and let's contain this quantum hole.
Hey, I'm Miles. Uh...
We actually met before. When I was invisible.
I know who you are.
Is everything going to be okay?
[Gwen] Okay...
-let me--let me explain.
-Miguel wants you back at HQ.
Miles was just about to head out, for...
All of you.
I don't follow orders. Neither does he.
I'm invited to HQ?
Whoo!
How are you even cooler under your mask?
I was just cool the whole time.
Dang.
Hey.
Over here.
Yo!
This place is wild!
-[Jess] Any sign of Spot?
Let me ask.
Hey, anybody spot Spot?
Oh, so funny. Anybody else got jokes?
-Now that you mention it...
-[spiderpeople chattering]
This is unbelievable!
This is the lobby.
Oh.
Welcome to Spider society!
Bit much, innit?
What happened to that small elite strike team?
A lot of these are part-time.
Gwendy, how much have you told him?
Hmm? About his place in all this.
A little.
[Miles glitching]
Ahh. [pants]
[Hobie] Maybe not enough.
Here.
Oh! My own watch!
-It's a day pass.
-Oh.
-This just keeps you from-
[glitching]
...doing that.
Hup, hup, hup!
-Hey, Gwen!
-Hey, Peter.
-Hey, I'm Miles.
-Hey, Gwen.
-Hi, Gwen.
Hey, Peters.
I'm, uh...I'm a new recruit.
Peter, take a team to the transport deck to help deal with this Spot mess.
[beep beep]
I wouldn't call it a mess.
More like a...success in progress.
Ben, I need-
Sorry. I can't talk right now.
-Thinking about my past.
-Actually, we need you here, for some reason.
[wailing in anguish]
That was a particularly...harrowing memory.
Is...is he okay?
Ahh!
Hey. The name's Web-Slinger.
Why does the horse need a mask?
To conceal her face.
Giddy...up!
[roaring]
Who is in these laser cages?
Anomalies. Folks who wound up in the wrong dimension.
-[Jess] We kick their butts, and send 'em home!
They're not very interesting.
What?
-We got a bunch'a Doc Ocs.
-Well, that's interesting!
-A Mysterio,
-Ooh.
a Missterio.
-Wow!
-Video game guy,
-I love video games!
another video game guy...
Are you talking to me?
Typeface.
Go to Helvetica, Spiderman!
Bold.
An interesting Kraven,
a boring rhino,
a Prowler,
Prowler?
-[Gwen] Not your Prowler.
Hey.
It's rude to stare.
-Caught that one myself.
-[Prowler] I slipped.
-[Gwen] You? Okay, I did all the work.
-You...
-How many missions have you been on together?
-[Gwen] Oh, not that many.
-[Hobie] Couple dozen.
[sarcastically] That's cool.
-[Margo grunts]
-Sorry.
I'm Spiderman.
Wow, no way!
All of us are.
Can we just keep moving?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you?
I'm an avatar!
My body is back in my parents' dimension, chilling in my game chair, and eating Fritos.
-[someone distant] Surprising! You don't listen!
Here is...better.
Hear that.
What does that do?
Apart from having a great name?
Go Home Machine.
What'd I say, eh?
I voted against it.
-[Margo] It detects whatever dimension your DNA is from,
and sends you there.
Super humane, and not creepy.
[screaming]
-See you, guy! Don't come back!
We should go. We don't wanna keep Miguel...
I'll...s-see you around?
Let's go!
-Hey, good luck out there, man.
-Whoa! Whoa.
Okay, bye!
-[Lyla] Miguel sounds hangry.
-[Jess] He likes those empanadas from the cafeteria.
My name is Miguel O'Hara.
I'm this dimension's one and only Spiderman.
Or, at least I was.
But I'm not like the others.
I don't always like what I have to do.
But I know I have to be the one to do it.
I've given up too much to stop now.
[whispering] Hoo, yo!
Bet this doesn't even do anything.
Maybe it did, before you ripped it out of a wall!
Propaganda, bro.
It'll distract you from the truth.
[sighs] And what's that?
I ain't got a Scooby Doo, mate.
'Cuz that's what they want.
-[Hobie] Why do you wanna be a part of this stuff?
-[Miles] To get a watch.
Make your own watch.
Pshh.
Bet you--bet you got a nice setup, huh? Nice parents?
They're fine.
I mean, we got in a fight, but...
they just want what's best for me. So...
That's a bloody shame.
Why?
'Cuz you're not ready for everybody else.
[recording] Get down.
-[Hobie] Listen to me, bruv.
-The whole point of being Spiderman is your independence.
Being your own boss, you don't need all this!
Then why are you here?
Looking out for my drummer, is all.
I want to be in a band.
I...I wanna see my friends, and...
I need a watch to do that.
Guys, come on.
Alright. Squashed.
Just don't enlist until you know about who you're fighting.
[whispering] Yeah, I know. It's slow.
But...it's his thing.
Miguel O'Hara?
-Meet Miles Morales.
-[laughs]
Hey! ¿Qué tal, tío?
I speak Spanish.
Te traje una empanada-
Qué maravilla.
-That's not--I'm really excited to get going. I got some...
-Oh? Great.
fresh new ideas on how to catch the Spot.
-He just wants to be taken seriously.
-Oh, wow! Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Whoa!
He's worried about Spot.
I'll worry about Spot!
What did I do?
Miguel! It's not his fault!
Fault? Hold up.
You blew another hole in the multiverse!
He doesn't know any better!
I do know--what...uhh, not know...
But you did, Gwen.
And you...
I was gonna try and ignore you.
-I just can't, with you.
-I'm not even here.
Not really.
What's happening?
-[Peter] Hey, Miguel!
Come on, go easy on the kid.
He had a terrible teacher!
[laughing] He had no chance!
-Peter!
-Peter?
-[sarcastically] Oh boy!
Humbling reality Spiderman has arrived.
-Miles!
-Dude!
Don't be afraid of my friend Miguel,
he just looks scary. He's got no bite.
[quiet groan] Peter.
-You're growing up on me! You look great!
Ehh...
-You look solid. Y'know? You look good. [laughs]
-Define solid.
What happened? You bleeding from the armpits?
-Peter, you-
-Don't worry about the suit. We'll get you a new suit.
Peter, you gotta tell him...
Wait...
-What is that?
-[squealing]
-[Peter] Mayday!
-You have a baby! This is crazy!
-I have a baby.
-[babbling]
-Don't forget to keep your little day pass on, honey!
Oh, you have one, too.
I didn't know they made those for adults.
-Gimme a second. Mayday!
-[Mayday laughing]
Kid's an anarchist.
-[squealing]
-[baby talk] I'm coming up to get you! Here I come!
[muttering in Spanish]
[Peter] Ha! I knew I was gonna regret making her that web shooter.
I shouldn't have done it. That's an actual mistake.
[Mayday squeals]
Wanna see pictures?
-I mean, she's right there, so...
-Look at this pic!
-Oh! You've got...okay, uh, wow.
-Look at this special kid! [laughs] Oh, she's incredible!
-Mm-hmm.
-Yup.
-This is her funny face.
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, that's her mad face.
This one is the studious one.
Watch out, the next one, you're gonna crack up! You're gonna crack up.
Oh, Miguel's gonna die. [laughing]
Miguel! Miguel, look at this one.
I'm trying to hold a serious adult conversation, here.
You know, you're the only Spiderman who isn't funny.
We're supposed to be funny!
The fate of the multiverse...
You always lose me with that!
You say, [gruffly] "the fate of the multiverse",
-and my brain dies!
-[Mayday cooing]
We are--[sniffing]
You guys smell that? Mayday took a crap.
-[Mayday babbling]
-Yup! She's a Parker.
-That's what happens when a Parker eats an avocado.
-[Miguel] Miles.
You disrupted a canon event.
Canon event?
The kid wasn't thinking!
That's not how he works!
That's insulting.
Taking a crap on the establishment. I salute you.
Wait, what are you upset about?
I saved those people.
And that's the problem.
Lyla? Do the thing.
Huh? What thing?
What--what do you mean, "what thing"?
The information explaining thing!
...Okay.
What's this?
This...is everything.
Can you be more specific?
Can you not talk for a second?
Yeah, yeah.
This, here...
This is all of us.
All of our lives woven together,
in a beautiful web of life and destiny.
The Spiderverse.
The Spiderverse?
Huh, that's...
stupid.
It's called the Arachno-Humanoid Poly-Multiverse.
Which sounds...
stupid too, I guess.
And these nodes, where the minds converge?
-They are the canon.
-Chapters that are a part of every Spider's story, every time.
Some good...
some bad...
some very bad.
Just keep going.
Uncle Aaron...
This one, event ASM-90,
a police captain close to Spiderman dies
saving a kid from falling rubble during a battle with an arch-nemesis.
Captain Stacy...
I'm so sorry.
That happened to you?
And me.
Eh? What of it?
-[Miguel] That's how the story's supposed to go.
The canon events are the connections
that bind our lives together.
And those connections can be broken.
That's why anomalies...
are so dangerous.
Inspector Singh's death was a canon event.
You weren't supposed to be there,
and you weren't supposed to save him.
That's why Gwen tried to stop you.
-Miles!
I thought you were trying to save me.
I was. I...
I was doing both.
-[Miguel] And now, Miles,
because you changed the story,
Pavitr's dimension is unraveling.
If we're lucky...we can stop it.
We haven't always been lucky.
That--that wasn't me.
That was the Spot!
It's what happens when you break the canon.
How do you know?
Because I broke it once myself.
I found another world where I had a family.
Where I was happy.
At least, a version of me was.
And that version of myself was killed.
So I replaced him.
I thought it was harmless.
But I was wrong.
Dad! Dad, help!
-Isn't that right, Peter?
Yeah.
You break enough canon, you save enough captains,
and we could lose everything.
My dad is about to be captain.
No...
[Spot] I'm going to take everything from you,
-[child] Help!
-like you took everything from me.
I'm coming!
[panting]
Spot does it.
He kills him.
When does it happen?
In two days.
When he's sworn in.
That's...what the model says.
-I'm sorry, Miles.
Send me home!
I can't do that.
-Not now.
What am I supposed to do? Just let him die?!
What about your dad?
He's a captain. Right?
Yeah.
And that's it?
You just aren't gonna do anything about it?
Okay, what about Uncle Ben?
That'd've been okay, if you knew,
and you just...let it play out?!
If not for Uncle Ben,
most of us wouldn't be here, Miles.
And all the good we did, it...
it wouldn't have been done.
So we're just supposed to let people die,
-because some algorithm,
-Oh! Whoa!
says that that's supposed to happen?
You realize how messed up that sounds, right?
You have a choice between saving one person
and saving an entire world.
Every world!
I can do both!
-Spiderman always-
-[Peter] Not always.
Miles.
-We all want to live the life we wish we had.
Believe me, I have tried.
And the harder I tried,
the more damage I did.
You can't have it all, kid.
Being Spiderman is a sacrifice.
That's the job.
That's what you signed up for.
-[Peni] Miles...
-[Miles] Peni?
What is this?
Is this an intervention or something?
We know it's hard.
But it's the truth, Miles.
Is that why you're here?
To let me down easy?
-Worked last time, why not run it back, huh?
-Hey, hold on, hold on!
-You were right, Gwen.
-You should've never come to see me.
-Kid, look at me.
-Stop calling me that.
Here we go.
Hobie, you're not helping.
Good.
Miles, please understand...
You can't ask me not to save my father.
I'm not asking.
-[Peter] I got this, just--give him a second, please.
-[Hobie sarcastically] That's a great look.
-[Gwen] Don't!
-[Peter and Miguel arguing]
Stop it!
You let him leave, he'll only do more damage.
-You both know that.
-[others arguing]
-[Miguel] Just need to hold you a few days.
-[Hobie silent]
Sorry it had to end like this, kid.
I said...
not to call me that!
Miles!
Alright. I'm sorry for doing this.
This is bad parenting!
This is where I reckon I quit.
-[Miguel] All stations, drop what you're doing
and stop Spiderman!
[all] You?
[all confused]
Por Dios! Miles! Miles Morales!
He's entering Sector 4!
[whispering] Is that him? Right?
Do I, uhh...have web on my face? What's the deal?
-[Miguel] Miles! Lord--he's right there! He's right--
Turn around!
I don't see anything, boss.
[laughs nervously]
Whoa!
-[yowling]
-[screaming]
[retches]
[groans]
Could this day get any damn weirder?!
[roars]
Whoa!
I guess it can!
-Whoa!
Sorry!
[Spidermonkey screeching]
[screaming]
-[sobbing] And then I looked at my uncle, and...
Uhh, let me guess.
He died?
[slow-motion screaming]
Whoa!
On the count of three, draw.
-One...
[grunts] You didn't wait for three!
Hey, Miguel!
Would you take a photo of this? It's our first chase.
[phone camera clicks]
-Yippi-ki-yay! Whoo!
-[spiderpeople shouting]
[all] Booooo!
[yelps]
Miles.
-Hi.
I'm a huge fan of your work.
-Thanks!
Do you think Spiderpeople too often use comedy as a crutch?
Uhhh...
Get it? Crutch?
Oof!
I can do anything you can!
Ohhh, dang! I pulled something!
[Doc Oc] Hello, Peter.
Whoa!
[yowling]
[all screaming]
'Sup? There's nowhere to run.
[screaming]
My bad, everybody. There was somewhere to run.
Stop running!
Then stop chasing me!
You're so frustrating!
I know he's your friend,
but it's the only way!
But my gut says-
Then use your head!
Oof!
[grunts]
-This is called the sleeper hold!
-[Miles grunting]
I'm using my bicep to constrict your-
[screaming]
Ah!
[grunts]
[whispering] Miles!
-No, no, no. Let me go!
-It is crazy to run!
Running is the least crazy thing going on!
I feel bad!
Good!
But this is just how stuff works!
You're not gonna win, here!
-No. No.
-Wait, don't move! Stop moving so fast!
No!
Do you wanna hold my baby?
What?
Would you just give the baby one squeeze, and then we'll talk?
-Cuz I think it's gonna change our vibe.
-No!
It's very rejuvenating!
I'm plenty juvenated!
You'll get moreso
when you go chest to chest with this magical child!
You don't get to have a heartfelt
-conversation with me right now!
-Just hold the baby, we'll see what happens!
[screams]
[Mayday coos]
You're the reason I had her, okay?!
I thought...
that if I did a decent job raising her,
there was a chance she was gonna turn out like you.
And that got me excited, because you are a wonderful person!
And I like being around you!
Then why didn't you come see me?
Be-...
I couldn't.
I wanted to be with you guys so badly.
But this thing isn't what I thought it was.
Look...[sighs]
bad things are gonna happen.
It makes us who we are.
But good things happen too, you know?
Like you happened.
And she happened.
[giggles]
-Hey! I don't...listen...
-[Mayday cooing]
You are so bad at holding a baby!
[Lyla] We got your location, Peter.
-Inside the core.
-Wait! Wait, wait, wait, no! No, no!
You do not have my location! Over!
Send everyone.
-No, no, no! Look--Miles!
I didn't know! I promise you!
Please, man, let's talk about this.
We did.
[Mayday squeals] [Peter grunts]
[sarcastically] Good talk.
[straining]
[distantly] Get him!
Ahh!
-[Gwen] Miles!
-[Gwen] Where does he think he's going?
-[Peter] I don't think he planned this out.
If I hadn't said it before, by the way,
you're a terrible mentor.
[grunts]
-[Peter] He did just beat you!
So I'm not a terrible mentor!
You're both equally terrible. Does that settle it?
[grunts]
Stop pretending you know what you're doing!
Oh, I have a plan.
I just...haven't told you yet!
Whoa!
[grunts]
[straining]
[computer] Departing for the Web.
That's not good.
[shouts]
What are those, claws?
Dude, are you sure you're even Spiderman?
Are you? Who do you think you are? Really?
My name...
is Miles Morales.
I was bitten by a radioactive spider!
And I'm pretty sure you know the rest, sir!
'Sup, man?
[grunts]
I don't get it!
You're an anomaly!
Not if you let me go home!
Snitch!
Everywhere you go, you're an anomaly!
You're the original anomaly!
Miguel!
The spider that gave you your powers
wasn't from your dimension!
It was never supposed to bite you!
Miguel, don't!
-There's a world out there with no Spiderman to protect them,
-because it bit you instead!
-You're not supposed to be Spiderman!
No!
You're lying! I'm Spiderman!
You're a mistake!
If you hadn't been bit,
your Peter Parker would've lived!
Instead, he died, saving you.
-If you would've stopped the collider before it ever went off,
Spot wouldn't exist,
and none of this would've happened.
Aahh!
And all this time,
-I have been the only one holding it all together!
-Get off of me!
[Peter] Miguel, go easy on him!
You don't belong here.
-You never did.
-[Miles straining]
Let me go!
[Gwen] Miguel, that's enough!
This isn't what we talked about!
You talked about this?
You knew?
-You...you all knew?
I...I didn't know...
how to tell you.
That's why you never came to see me.
Miles, it's for your own good!
Who decides that?!
I'm not a kid, Gwen!
Ah!
That's exactly what you are!
You're just a kid!
Who has no idea
what he's doing!
[grunts]
Yeah, well...
I did lure hundreds of Spiderpeople away from your little clubhouse.
Huh?
[spiderpeople shouting]
I guess he did plan this out!
And...
I'm about to do this.
[Miguel panicking]
Everyone keeps telling me how my story is supposed to go.
Nah.
Imma do my own thing.
Sorry, man.
I'm going home.
[screaming]
Goodbye, Gwen.
Miles!
I taught him how to do that, so...
I gotta be a pretty good mentor, to pull that off!
Nope.
No.
Uh-uh.
That's kinda cute.
Oh, no. No...
[hissing] Ah!
Huh?
Hmm...
[beeping]
Wha...?
[Computer] Initializing Go Home Machine.
Retinal signature identified.
Come on...!
[distorted] No!
No...no...no!
What's happening?
The machine activated on its own!
How's that possible?
It isn't!
[Lyla and Margo talking indistinctly]
How 'bout this?
-No, no, no, no! Ugh!
-Hey, how 'bout now?
You're getting in the way!
Stop him!
Now!
Man, what does it look like I'm trying to do?!
[grunts]
[roars]
[grunting]
Do something!
-Now!
-[Peter] Miguel!
-[Gwen] Stop!
[grunts]
[straining]
No!
[roars]
O--okay, enough! It's not the console's fault.
All he had to do was listen!
Why didn't he listen?
[sarcastically] Maybe, you weren't hard enough on him!
[Jess quietly] Gwen, don't do it.
You let him go.
-Me?
-You didn't catch him,
-Gwen.
-Okay, let's all just take a breath...
-Peter!
You wanna back me up?!
Well, okay. Miguel?
As a father of a daughter, and
the son of a mother...
Yeah, actually, stop talking.
Okay, duly noted.
Let me just talk to him.
We tried that.
He's my friend.
Yeah, and that's the problem.
Do you know for certain what happens if he breaks the canon?
You wanna find out?
I told you she was a liability!
You're wrong.
Jess?
Tell him he's wrong.
He's...not.
Are you serious right now?
I told you.
You let him get away,
I can't help you.
I'm not coming.
You're right.
What?
What the hell?!
Go home, Gwen.
We are supposed to be the good guys.
We are.
Jess. Ben.
Come with me.
Hell yeah!
[Miguel] Somebody catch Spot.
[Peter] Yeah, sorry. I, uhh...
I gotta get her down for a nap.
Not you.
I've had the right amount of you.
[blows a raspberry]
[laughs and squeals]
[screams]
[grunts]
[panting]
-How was work?
-[Peter sighs]
[muttering] I don't know.
Peter?
Did you bring our baby to another fight?
Did I bring our ba-? No. No--no.
'Cuz you asked me not to. So, I didn't. I wouldn't.
Mm-hmm.
[groans]
[grunts]
You think I'll be any good at this?
You're asking that now?
There's no playbook for raising someone like her.
-Or...
being someone like you.
You just gotta...make the right adjustments at halftime.
-That's a sports metaphor, by the way.
-I understand.
[laughs] Wow, sorry.
You were just such a nerd in high school, I figured...
I have watched sports!
-Ah! Okay, champ.
-Unbelievable.
Wanna go easy on the penguin?
[stammers] Just...
You won't even look at me?
What?
What--what is that?
I'm looking at you.
Like you asked.
[sighs]
You look skinny.
Where have you been?
Just been, uhh...
out murdering all my friends.
Oh. Oh, that's funny, uhh, okay. Yeah.
Okay.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
You're a good cop, Dad.
You know you put on that badge because you know if you don't,
someone who shouldn't will.
But...
you have to understand.
This mask is my badge.
And I'm trying to be good, too.
I was trying so hard
to wear this thing the way you would want!
And I didn't.
I didn't!
I can do all these things,
but I can't help the people I love the most.
And they can only know half of who I am!
So I'm...completely on my own!
And now, I don't...
[voice shaking] I don't even know what the right thing is, anymore.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do!
But I know...
[sighs]
I can't lose one more friend.
Gwen...
I always taught you to do it by the book.
Yeah, and how did that work out?
I took an oath.
Then arrest me, Dad!
-Get it over with.
-I...
I can't.
Why not?
Because I quit.
When?
About halfway through your big speech.
You're...
Wait a minute. You're not--you're not gonna be captain?
That means...
My job...being captain...
This whole...
thing doesn't matter anymore.
You're the best thing I've ever done.
It was a good speech, huh?
No wonder you got an A in English.
B. I got a B. Plus.
Missed a few classes.
I don't know what it is you gotta do,
But I...I think that this thing is supposed to help.
The guy who left it was a real piece of work.
I'll be right back.
Promise.
Parenting...
stuff is...
a big-ass mystery.
-[Miguel] You're a mistake!
-If you hadn't been bit,
-Peter Parker would've lived!
-And none of this would've happened!
-[Peter Porker] Miles...
-the hardest thing about this job is...
-you can't always save everybody.
-[Spot] I'll make you pay...
-for everything you took away from me.
-[Miguel] ...the choice between saving one person,
-and an entire world. Every world.
-[Miles] I can do both!
-[Miles] Spiderman always-
-[Peter] Not always.
-[Rio] Whatever you wanna do out there,
-don't get lost.
-[Peter] Things are gonna happen.
-[Gwen] I...I didn't know...
-...how to tell you.
-[Miguel] You're not supposed to be Spiderman!
-[Aaron] Keep going.
Ah!
[panting and groaning]
Did you check your locations?
Yes, Dad.
No sign of him.
Lyla, would you just send everyone out?
Anywhere. Anywhere he might be!
[laughing] Congrats, Captain.
Captain? You can't call me that 'till I'm sworn in.
You know that.
We're all proud of you!
Perfect pose.
-[glitching]
-Wha...?
Possible disturbance in the alley.
Better go check it out.
[grunts]
Now, I'm here in the alley.
There's something unusual happening.
Looking at the walls--those are normal.
But there's something in front of me-
Ah!
Ohhhh no!
[sighs]
I made it.
I'm home.
-[Rio] Miles?
-[gasps]
Is now a bad time...?
-Am I--am I too late?
-What'd you do to your hair?
Are you guys okay? Tell me you're okay!
I'm okay...!
You were right.
You were right about everything.
Of course I'm right. I'm always right.
What am I right about?
I saw...all these amazing places!
And met all these amazing people!
But...
¿Que te pasa, mijo?
[sighs]
But they didn't want me.
I...I kept thinking about what you said.
I let 'em have it, Mom.
I beat 'em all.
I know how strong I am, now.
I'm strong because of you!
-And Dad!
¿Que to?
And us!
Mom...
there's something coming for us.
Something...
something terrible.
Miles, you're talking crazy. What's going on?
-His name is Spot.
He's my nemesis.
And I'm gonna stop him.
I know you know I've been lying to you.
It's because I thought if you knew...
you wouldn't love me the same.
And then I went out there, and...
And now...
I'm not afraid of anything.
What do you wanna tell me?
You gotta promise nothing's gonna change.
Papa, I will always love you.
You gotta promise.
Always.
I don't care what you say.
¿Tú me entiendes?
[sighs]
Mom...
I'm...
I'm Spiderman.
Who's Spiderman?
...The superhero?
He got bit by a spider?
Gave him spider powers?
He's me?
Is this where...like, you dress up like your favorite character?
Or, like, what's it called?
Like Comics Con!
I don't know what that is.
You really had me going there, Spiderman.
[laughing] Imagínate.
Why don't you have 8 arms?
Um...
Do you push silk out of your culito?
I had a nightmare about that once. But no!
Are you sure you woke up?
Mom! Stop playing around!
This is serious!
Dad worked with Spiderman.
I mean, he didn't realize Spiderman was me at the time, but...
-[sighs] I wish Dad was here to explain this.
-[firmly] Miles, please.
I got you to take care of,
I got me to take care of.
-So help me out.
-Mom, hold on! Hold on!
I need to talk-
[grunting]
42.
-[computer] Dimensional signature identified.
[door unlocking]
Uncle Aaron?
Hey.
You okay?
Whoa!
I missed you so much.
[laughing] Okay.
Alright, then. Alright.
Whoa. You took your braids out?
Uhh...
-On purpose?
-Yeah.
Yeah, I'm still...
...getting used to it?
They gave me more hours at the hospital, so next month,
-I swear, I'll pay you back...
-Stop it, stop it.
We're family.
Thanks.
-[Rio] Hey, honey. How are you doing?
Hey. How'd it go with Miles?
-Well...
you know how you grounded him?
Mm-hmm...
I ungrounded him.
You...you what?
A little bit.
-[Rio] How much trouble could he get in tonight?
-A lot of trouble!
-I don't wanna think about it.
-[Rio] Oh, Miles. I have to work an overnight tonight.
Here's a grocery list.
I'll make sure he gets this done.
Alright. We gotta roll.
Security switches out at 6. That's the window, right?
...Right. Yep.
I'm...I'm following you in...
what you are...saying.
[grunting]
[panting]
You alright?
[weakly] I have a cold.
C'mon, man.
Make sure you got the plan.
Yeah, but...but...
maybe we should go over it one more time,
just to make sure there's no...
problems.
[distant sirens]
[whispering] There's no Spiderman here.
-Oh, no.
-Dad...
-[Jeff] I'm sorry, baby, but you did unilaterally unground him.
-[Rio] Jeff...
-I just--I just worry about him getting mixed up with the wrong people, okay?
-This is probably that girl.
-What is he even thinking, being with her?
I have some ideas.
Baby...you're really not helping.
-[Rio] You saw the way he lit up around her!
-...I just hope she doesn't get him hurt.
-[Jeff] I mean, am I responsible for this?
-[Rio] No, no!
Maybe it's all my fault!
Come on, papa, you're a great dad.
This is all...
It's just...it's hard. It's like...[sighs]
we got a whole new kid who just wants to grow up so fast.
And maybe, we gotta grow up, too.
A little bit.
Maybe we just gotta let him spread his wings, man.
"Man"?
-[Gwen] It's not your fault.
It's mine.
Oh, come on. What the heck are you doing here?
Oh, uhh, his window was open, so I came in.
Because that's...normal...to do.
I wanna talk to your parents.
Right. My, uhh...my dad's kinda hard to get on the horn.
Oh, really? What does he do?
Deal drugs?
He's a cop.
Statement withdrawn.
Yep, well, I'm gonna call the station.
I don't think he's there. Or...
anywhere around here.
Well, that's his jacket, emo!
Where's Miles?
I don't know.
-[Jeff stammering]
-You don't know?
What do you mean, you don't know?!
Yeah. Umm...I'll leave.
Where do you think you're going, young lady?
I'm going to find him.
I don't know where, exactly...
But I know where to start.
One thing I learned from Miles...
it's all possible.
He loves you more than you could ever imagine.
I've seen it.
If you do find him...
[firmly] tell him 5 months.
And tell him we love him.
You got it.
Uncle Aaron...
-[Miles] Wait, wait.
-I was...listen.
-Okay, um...
-You don't understand.
I'm not from here.
[grunting]
I'm from an entirely different dimension.
Wait, wait, wait. Please, please. Please!
Please!
-I got sent here by mistake!
-Uncle Aaron, wait, wait, wait, wait! Uncle Aaron!
Please.
Uncle Aaron?
Just...hear me out.
[music gets louder]
[sighs]
I was bit by a spider that gave me powers.
It wasn't supposed to bite me,
it was supposed to bite someone else.
Someone from here.
I don't belong here.
I need to go home.
Okay?
I have an Uncle Aaron, too. I-I had one.
-He was a bad guy...called the Prowler.
-He...he looked out for me.
-He did a lot of bad things, but...
I knew he wanted to be good.
He just...didn't know he had a choice,
but you do!
You can be a good guy!
[chuckling]
A good guy?
[sighing] Please, just trust me.
I know you don't wanna be the Prowler.
[panting]
I'm not.
[Jameson indistinct on TV]
[distorted] Your dad is still alive?
...What?
Your father.
You said he's still alive.
Yeah.
Huh.
Who are you?
I'm Miles Morales.
But you...
you can call me the Prowler.
If I don't get home...
our dad...is going to die.
Your dad.
Please.
You have to let me go.
Why would I do that?
[whispering] Don't tell Mom.
[Gwen] I never found the right band to join.
So, I started my own.
With a few old friends.
Want in?