[dramatic swell]
[suspenseful music playing]
[eerie whispers]
[indistinct whispers]
[dramatic music swells]
[dramatic swell]
[whooshing]
IN HIS SHADOW
[wind whooshing]
[indistinct chatter]
Damn it.
Done having your fun?
Yeah.
[sighs]
[marble rocking on board]
- [marbles clatter]
- [chuckles]
[continues chuckling]
[man 1] What is it?
What are you laughing at?
I won.
A glutton for punishment.
You don't mind conning a blind person?
Blind or not, it doesn't matter, bro.
I'm more disabled
than you are in this game.
Man, you memorize every move, right?
No.
I'm actually not blind.
But don't tell anyone,
or they'll cut my benefits.
[chuckles] Screw you.
I almost believed you!
[chuckles] Okay, I'm good.
I'm only gonna lose anyway.
You whoop me no matter what.
Stop it. Take it easy.
Don't lose any of my marbles.
[sucks teeth]
- Play your song and stop crying.
- [man 1] My track?
- Yeah.
- [man 1] Okay.
It's not finished yet. It's a rough cut.
You know I'll need you to work
your magic on it. There you go.
[chuckles] Here.
[upbeat music playing faintly]
Not half bad this time.
- [chuckles] Fuck you, man.
- [man 2 chuckles]
Really?
[man 2 sighs] It's pretty good.
Hmm.
[dog growls]
[motorcycle revving]
[dramatic sting]
[man 3, muffled] Enough of this disrespect
toward me, you hear me?
I've waited long enough.
Tell him to get me my money, or else I'm...
- What is it?
- They're coming this way.
- Who?
- Ibrahim.
- Okay, maybe see you tomorrow?
- [dog barks]
- [Ibrahim] Hold up, where you going?
Come by my place tonight.
We need to have a chat.
- [barks]
- What has he done?
You stay out of this.
Ain't none of your business.
[man 2] Every one of us has a monster.
My monster was him.
My older brother, Ibrahim.
He wasn't always like this.
And I wasn't always
the blind kid in the neighborhood.
["Zombie" by Fela Kuti playing]
THE '80S
MURETS PROJECTS
What motivated my father
to relocate to these projects was this.
[father] I need this.
FOR RENT
Baby, we can't spend the rest of our lives
working for a boss
who treats us like we're lower than dirt.
I hear that.
What are you gonna call the restaurant?
Restaurant Keïta.
[man 2] My Dad and Agna...
- I like it.
- ...then pregnant with Ibrahim,
came here to start a new life.
A better life.
In the luggage they carried,
they brought
their greatest hopes and dreams.
They'd stop at nothing
to make them come true.
Before, there was nothing to eat
for the people who lived here.
The restaurant was a gift.
A gift for the neighborhood.
A place for conversation and socializing.
Brimming with life.
So hurry up. [chuckles]
- My father was happy.
- We're out of bananas, okay?
He could provide
a decent life for his family.
- Can I go play soccer?
- Yeah, no problem.
And Ibrahim had found his place
in the neighborhood.
- [kid 1] Hey, bro!
- What's up?
- [kid 1] You good?
- Let's go play.
["Zombie" continues playing]
[children chattering, laughing]
[indistinct argument]
- [man 2] Everything was going well.
- [Agna] She's not welcome here.
Until my father returned
from a visit to the homeland
with a surprise in his luggage.
- [father] Make it work!
- [man 2] My mother.
- [Agna] She needs to pack and leave!
- [father] It's complicated, Agna.
[Agna] You can't force
a second wife on me.
This is Europe! You know that!
Am I not enough anymore?
- [father] It's not about that.
- [Agna] Why are you forcing this on me?
[father] This is my house.
I pay the bills.
It's my decision to make.
End of story. Period.
What do you mean?
I was the one who helped you
open the restaurant!
Have you lost your memory?
The wallpaper, everything in this house,
we did it together!
- She needs to pack her things and leave.
- [father] I've said the final word.
[Agna] You can't do this, Ousmane!
I won't stand for it.
Everything here, we did it together.
- She's going back home!
- [Ibrahim breathing heavily]
[man 2] That's when Ibrahim's
carefree nature slowly began to shift.
[baby crying]
And, especially a year
after my mother arrived.
Well, that's when I entered the picture.
[crying continues]
[gentle music playing]
From then on, things would forever
be different in the Keïta household.
Everyone was gonna have to
fit in together under one roof.
And it wasn't gonna be easy.
[crying continues]
[woman] What are you doing
with my son's hair?
What'd you say?
What are you doing with my son's hair?
What do you mean?
I'm cleaning. Is that not obvious?
What are you trying with that?
Will you visit the witch?
You're completely out of your mind.
You're absolutely right I am!
Throw it away!
Of course I'm going to throw it away!
- [woman in Wolof] I will beat you!
- [Agna] You home-wrecker!
[man 2 in English] My mom had always
been afraid of witches.
An old belief she kept from her homeland.
She was sure Agna was visiting
a witch in the projects.
Having heard about the witch
my whole childhood,
I used to try to look for her.
And one time I thought I found her.
[witch] Adama...
[Adama] Ibrahim found a way
to keep himself out of the house,
where he was suffocating.
- What's up? Chill? What's the word?
- You good, bro?
[Adama] But I didn't know
about any of that at the time.
All I cared about
was beating my Dad at oware.
[upbeat music playing]
- [chuckles]
- Is it me, or are you taking a thrashing?
This could be the first time
your father's ever lost this game.
Aïssata, go play somewhere else.
[Adama] The arrival
of my half-sister, Aïssata,
helped Agna win back some ground.
- Nice move.
- [man sighs]
- I didn't see that coming.
- [Ousmane chuckles]
I win!
[Ousmane chuckles]
You believed I was in
a position of weakness.
- Well, I took advantage of that.
- [chuckles]
Like my army commander used to tell me,
"Embrace your weakness."
"Don't fight it.
Look to make it your strength."
- Okay?
- Hmm. Play again?
With pleasure!
[man 1] Cops! Cops are here!
Run!
- Cops are here! Cops are here!
- Wait.
- Just one sec. Be right back.
- It's okay. Come here, sweetie.
- [young Ibrahim panting]
- [siren wailing]
[cop 1] Stop! Stop!
[police siren wailing]
- Don't move! Get over here!
- [car tires screech]
[cop 2] Stop!
- [cop 1] Hey, stop! Stop!
- [cop 3] Hey! What the hell are you doing?
What's this? What are you doing?
[man 1] The pigs are here!
The pigs are here!
Hey, heads up for cops!
- [cop 2] Stop!
- [cop 1] He's over there!
[grunts] You little shit!
Don't you ever step foot
in my house again!
- [cop 1] Sir! Sir! Sir! Sir, enough!
- I don't wanna see you again!
- [cop 1] Enough! We got it!
- Don't set foot again in my house!
You taint the family name!
You're a disgrace to the Keïtas!
- [Agna] Don't! Stop it! That's enough!
- Come here! Good riddance!
Enough! Stop it!
This is all your fault!
You're too weak with him.
[cop 1] Come on now.
That's right! You're no longer my son!
Get out of here!
[Adama] That was the first time
I'd ever seen my Dad like that.
I couldn't grasp everything...
[sighs]
...but I could see the Keïta home
was not a happy one.
["Baara (Mixed)"
by Amadou & Mariam playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[grill sizzles]
[children clamoring, screaming]
Hey, over here!
- Come on!
- Come, come!
[screaming continues]
Don't mess with him. He really hits.
- Yeah, right.
- [young Adama] I'm telling you.
[horn honks]
[Adama's mom] I was crossing.
You were driving crazy!
Hey, shut your dumbass!
You can't even drive! Don't touch me.
What're you gonna do?
- [horn blaring]
- [Adama gasps]
- [tires screech]
- [boy gasps]
[inaudible]
[Adama's mom] Somebody help, please!
Somebody help me, please!
[inaudible]
[indistinct whispers]
[music building, fades]
[machines beeping]
[Adama] My dad saw it
as a horrible accident,
while my mom was convinced Agna
had the witch do this to me.
She thought black magic
had put me in this condition.
Black magic had taken my eyesight from me.
[indistinct whispering]
Whatever the case, things would
have to change to accommodate me.
[young Ibrahim] How is Adama?
I can help you guys.
Mom shouldn't have
to move out like that, Pops.
Really? Tell me.
Can you help Adama get his sight back?
There's nothing we can do
about the apartment.
It's too small.
Too cluttered.
We need more space.
So the boy doesn't bump into things
while adapting.
We all must contribute,
including your mother.
- I got an apartment.
- [Ousmane sighs]
A big one, in Block B.
Plenty of rooms.
It can fit the entire family.
And how did you find
an apartment so quickly, huh?
- [sighs]
- Who did you extort?
Who did you pay?
You really think
I'm gonna live in an apartment
that you paid for
with your dirty money? Huh?
I have to take care of my family, not you.
You know what?
Come talk to me when you're an honest man.
A real man.
Until then...
I'm dead to you.
[children clamoring]
[loud thud]
[young Aïssata] My room is so big!
- Do I get it all to myself?
- All to yourself.
And what room is going to be Adama's?
Right next to yours.
From his room, you can see my tower.
When will he arrive?
Pretty soon.
Aïssata, why don't you go play
in your room, hmm?
I'm going to talk to your brother.
[exhales]
Ibé...
- I don't think this is a good idea.
- [Ibrahim] No, no, no. It's fine, Mom.
You've gone through a lot.
- We don't always have to surrender.
- [Agna] Hmm.
The old man has to come now.
Hmm. [chuckles]
[both sigh]
My gosh, you've grown up so fast.
[chuckles]
- [affectionate cooing]
- [chuckles]
- [Ibrahim chuckles]
- [speaks in Bambara]
- Hmm. So, this apartment is mine.
- All yours.
- Don't worry.
- [chuckles]
[Ibrahim chuckles] Okay, I'm off.
[in Bambara] Thank you.
[in English] Thank you.
[melancholy music playing]
[cane scraping]
[music continues]
Well done, my boy!
You don't need my help anymore. [chuckles]
[chuckles softly]
[Ousmane] Here, pass me your cane.
There we are.
Are you comfy?
Here, I got you something.
What is it?
Make a guess.
An oware set?
That I made especially for you.
Here.
"Embrace your..."
"Embrace your weakness and...
look to...
make it your strength."
"Embrace your weakness
and look to make it your strength."
Great job. Great job, my boy!
I'm so proud of you.
[young Adama] Embrace your weakness
and look to make it your strength.
Embrace your weakness
[adult Adama] Embrace your weakness
and look to make it your strength.
Stay out of this.
Ain't none of your business.
Hey, hey, hey,
you leave your brother alone!
- [Ibrahim] Half-brother.
- Brother!
There are no half-brothers here!
What do you get from picking
on someone weaker than you, huh?
I was talking to his friend.
He's a man, you know.
You need to stop protecting him.
I treat him like any person.
That's what he needs of you, Pa.
Any other person?
- So, I should beat him up?
- You did it to me, didn't you?
I was right to!
And I'd do it again if I had to!
[dog barks]
[Ibrahim] Tonight.
[continues barking]
- [Ousmane coughs]
- Here, come.
You all right, Papa?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine, my boy. I'm fine.
Will you go?
Don't have much of a choice, do I?
[sighs] Damn it.
I have a bad feeling. Don't go.
If I don't, he'll go to my house
where there's my mom, my sister...
No fuckin' way.
Hey, is it about Aïssata?
No, no, it can't be.
We're super careful. It's not about that.
Hey, nothing's gonna happen.
It's all good.
I'll sort your brother out, no problem.
[inhales] Okay, let's play again.
[siren wailing in the distance]
[dog panting]
[dog whimpers, barks]
It won't take long.
[dog barks]
Sit.
- You know I can't bring you inside.
- [dog whimpers]
[dog whimpers]
Shh.
[indistinct chatter]
[shoes squeak]
[chatter continues]
[Adama breathing shakily]
- [man] Hey, watch out. Over here.
- [footsteps descending]
Hey, how you doing? Good?
Yeah, not bad.
[doorbell buzzes]
[door opens]
Oh, I wasn't expecting you so soon.
- I had no time to get the papers ready.
- Excuse me. I need to use the bathroom.
- [door shuts]
- [Ibrahim] Shut the fuck up!
Who do you think you are
putting your hands on my sister?
She's a queen, and you're a bum!
That's right, I said it. A bum!
- [man] Ibra, I didn't touch your sister.
- [Ibrahim] Shut up! Don't lie to me!
I swear, I will end you!
Don't you ever go near her again!
Get him out of here before I pop him.
[loud thud]
[door opens]
- [woman] Sweet boy, what is happening?
- Shh.
- Sorry.
- [loud thud]
- [Ibrahim] You're fucking dead! Dead!
- [man grunts]
- Get up, get up!
- Go ahead. Kill him, kill him!
Do you understand the words
coming out of my mouth?
I have eyes and ears
all over these streets.
If you come anywhere near her,
I'll end you, you bitch! Huh?
Yeah, you bitch.
You understand what I'm saying?
You better.
On my mom's life, I'll kill you.
You little shit,
you like touching people's sisters?
Try to play with me!
[Adama gasps, breathes shakily]
[Ibrahim] Get up!
[loud thud]
He's left.
Malik. They released him.
[Adama breathes shakily]
I can't take this anymore. I...
They make things unlivable around here.
Look at how they constantly stop
the elevator to do their dealing.
[Adama] It'll be fine, Mrs. Diop.
It'll be fine.
[somber music playing]
[Mrs. Diop breathing shakily]
[indistinct chatter]
[upbeat music playing]
[melodic drums beating]
[Adama's mom] Adama.
[dog groans]
Hey.
- Someone's here for you.
- Who?
[chuckles]
Come on, time to tell him
that beat-up old t-shirt has to go.
Poor guy can't see it.
Hey, hey, easy. Lay off that T-shirt.
It used to be mine.
- Ah, I see.
- [chuckles]
My gosh, what a nice shirt.
- Really lovely.
- [all chuckle]
You damn suck-up!
You have no shame!
The t-shirt's just fine.
All right, kids,
I'm headed back to the restaurant.
- See you later.
- Okay, good luck.
- [Aïssata] Bye, Dad.
- [Ousmane] Bye.
- [Adama's mom] You're so pretty.
- Thank you.
- [Adama] How you doing?
- [Aïssata] Good, you? [exhales]
Just fine.
Getting some work done.
[Aïssata] Hmm.
[sucks teeth]
Do you know where he is?
[Adama] Who?
Who do you think?
Don't know.
[sighs]
I've been calling him the last two days.
It goes to voicemail.
Son of a bitch is ghosting me.
I tried everything. IG, SnapChat.
I just hope nothing happened to him.
Because if he's ghosting me
for some other bitch, she's gonna be hurt.
[chuckles]
Something funny?
Not a thing.
Not a thing, Aïssata.
I'd never dream of it.
You're the baddest thug on the block.
I don't mess.
[chuckles]
Whatever.
Let me hear the track.
- Okay. This one?
- Yeah.
Here he is.
Your man's right here.
- [upbeat music continues playing]
- [Ousmane panting]
[exhales]
[coughing]
[music continues]
[chuckles]
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
[wheezing]
You like it?
I love it!
[both chuckle]
Ah! Ay!
My man's got the magic, right?
[music stops]
If it weren't for my magic, not his BS,
you wouldn't say that.
Are you jealous?
Yeah, you bet I am.
Come on, don't even. You're the best.
[chuckles] There. That's more like it.
I'm being serious, though.
He's never done this.
We talk, like, ten times a day.
[sighs]
- You won't repeat this.
- Repeat what?
Swear!
- It's between us.
- Mm-hmm.
Let's hear it.
[exhales]
I was at Mrs. Diop's.
I heard Ibra and his guys beating him up.
And threatening to kill him
if he saw you again.
Damn it.
See now?
I've already told you,
do whatever you want,
but not in front of others.
Who cares about what other people think?
You can't just... blah, blah.
Where do you think we are?
[metallic noise echoing in the distance]
What is it?
You don't hear that?
- [dog whimpers]
- No.
- I heard a weird noise.
- [dog whimpers]
Come with me. Quick.
- [heart beating]
- [Ousmane gasping]
[Ousmane wheezing]
[loud clanks]
[clanks continue]
It's Dad!
[Aïssata] Papa!
We have to call someone!
Papa!
Help! Help! Papa!
- Papa, please! I'm begging you!
- What's wrong?
- What's wrong with him?
- We have to call someone! Help!
Somebody help!
- Please, call someone!
- Please help!
Papa, please stay with me, please!
Papa, please!
- Papa!
- [echoing] Help!
[somber music playing]
[somber music continues]
[imam praying in Arabic]
[all pray in Arabic]
[breathing shakily]
[woman 1 muffled] She's right.
This place should be yours.
You started it with your husband.
Your sweat and tears.
[woman 2] I can't believe he left
the restaurant to both of you.
[woman 1] I mean, seriously...
She hasn't done a thing.
Ousmane already got her that apartment.
Now she also inherits this?
What about Ibrahim?
What does he get?
Nothing?
Sorry, but that's not right.
Even if they weren't speaking,
you can't do that to a son.
Don't take this lying down.
Now he's no longer with us.
You have to keep a low profile, son.
Even more so than before.
[Aïssata] Malik, wait!
- What is that?
- Nothing.
- What do you mean "nothing"?
- It's nothing, relax. Not here.
I'm sick of not seeing you anymore.
I'm gonna talk to him. I don't care.
To who?
- To Ibrahim.
- No.
No, no, no. You won't talk to him at all.
Hey, this stays under wraps.
Wait till this blows over.
There's no other choice.
I swear, I saw it in his eyes.
He really wanted to kill me.
He wasn't always like this.
He doesn't know how else to do it.
It's how he protects us.
With time, he'll learn to accept you.
I can't.
I can't. You wouldn't get it.
For real?
[gentle music playing]
[music swells]
- [dramatic swell]
- Adama.
Only you can save us.
Come visit me when you're ready.
I can help you, Adama.
I can help you.
We're closing.
Hey, bro, are you blind or deaf?
What are you doing?
He won't listen to me.
Leave him alone.
We gotta talk about Eddy.
It's more urgent. Go ahead.
[mechanical whirring, squeaking]
- [somber music playing]
- [sighs]
[motorcycle engine revving]
- [robber 1] Don't move! Don't move!
- [tires screech]
[robber 2] On the ground! On the ground!
Keep your hands behind your head.
- [man] What're you doing? Give me that!
- [robber 1] Shut the fuck up!
- [man] Wait, no!
- [gun fires]
- [robber 1] Okay, I've got it all!
- [engine revving]
- [banging on door]
- [Ibrahim] Open up! Open up!
What's all this about?
What's wrong?
Put it all over there, to the left.
In the bedroom.
What's this all mean?
[bag thuds]
Ibrahim, what's going on?
[Ibrahim] I have to stash
some things here for now.
We're at war with Eddy
and the guys from his block.
- It's heating up the neighborhood.
- That's not my business.
- What did you say?
- I'm the one you're putting in danger!
- [Ibrahim] What was that?
- Why don't you take it to your place?
If the cops search mine, I'm through!
They won't mess with the old and blind.
Plus, this is my place too.
I don't care what his will says!
I want to stash shit here, so I will!
Whether Dad likes it or not,
this place is half mine. Period.
Got it?
[Adama breathing heavily]
I won't abandon you and your mom.
I'll take care of you now that he's gone,
but we'll do things my way.
[money thuds]
I put cash here like the old man used to.
[Adama breathing deeply]
[inhales]
[dramatic music playing]
[music building]
[music fades]
[dog panting]
[Adama breathing heavily]
- [breathing heavily]
- [dog whimpers]
[dramatic swell]
[loud bang]
[man whistles] Hey! Hey! Cops!
Cops! Cops! Cops! Cops!
Stop right there!
- [police siren wailing]
- Tom!
- [cop 2] Hold it! Don't move!
- [siren wailing]
- Stop! Stop!
- That way! Go that way!
- [cop 2] Stop right there!
- [cop 3] Hey!
[man] Cops! Cops!
[breathing heavily]
[grunts] You bitch!
- [indistinct yelling]
- [Tom grunts]
Hey!
Hey, you, back up!
[clamoring]
Stand back! Stand back, I said!
Stand back!
Nothing to see here!
Hey, what's the matter?
What's goin' on?
[man] Get fucked! Fuck off!
We're doing our job!
- What'd he do?
- [cop 1] We got a call.
People saw one of Eddy's guys get held up.
Tom, what's your side?
[Tom] I didn't do nothing.
It was the other son of a bitch.
[cop 1] Hey! Hey! Shut the fuck up.
You better show some respect.
Show some respect!
[exhales]
Why did your guy book it
as soon as he saw us?
Search him here.
It's not up to you to tell me
how to search somebody.
If he held someone up, he'll have a gun.
Search for it.
If you find something...
you have my word,
you can cart him off, no protest.
But cart him off without searching him,
without proof of your claims,
I'll start a riot here
like you've never seen before.
[sighs]
[sighs] That's all he's got?
[cop 2] Nothing else.
- Oh fuck.
- [Ibrahim] Get the fuck out of here.
Fuck off.
- [indistinct yells]
- [man 1] Better fuck off fast!
[man 2] Hey, hey, hey, hey, beat it!
[clamoring continues]
[kids yelling, laughing]
BIEVRE SHOPPING CENTER
BAKER
[sirens wailing in distance]
[upbeat music playing faintly]
[drums beat]
[lock rattling, unlocking]
[ominous music playing]
[eerie swell]
[upbeat music continues faintly]
[dog huffs]
[growling]
- [dramatic sting]
- [dog barking]
[robber grunts]
[dog yelps, whimpers]
[upbeat music continues faintly]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Ibrahim] I swear, she said,
"Send people your resume."
[laughs] She said that, bro.
That boy, your cousin,
he's out of his mind, I swear.
That girl said...
Hmm?
What do you want?
[man sighs]
The store owners are complaining.
I don't like what I'm hearing.
I'm protecting these projects.
Everyone has to contribute.
You protect your interests,
not these projects.
I'm not stupid, Ibrahim.
Hey, old head.
Don't come here and lecture me.
I'm not ten anymore.
Ibrahim, stop telling yourself
you grew up without love.
Your dad loved you.
Like crazy.
I know deep down you know that.
[man sighs]
That old dude's crazy.
Yeah.
[dramatic music playing]
[breathes deeply]
[friend] Ibrahim, what are you doing?
Ibra! Where you goin'?
[Ibrahim breathing heavily]
[groans]
[grunts]
[dramatic music continues]
- [Adama's mom sobbing]
- [Adama breathing shakily]
[inhales shakily]
[breathing shakily]
What happened?
[Adama's mom] They stole everything.
Ibrahim's whole stash. It's all gone.
[continues sobbing]
This will never end.
I'm sick of this.
[Adama breathes shakily]
I'm sick and tired of this.
[continues sobbing]
[somber music playing]
[cane scraping]
[witch echoing] Come in.
How far will this go?
Huh?
[breathes deeply]
I can't take this anymore.
I'm afraid for my mom.
[breathes deeply]
[sniffles]
I need to get rid of him.
You can make it happen.
[indistinct chants echoing]
You made me blind, after all.
[unsettling music playing]
[witch echoing] Is that what you think?
It's what my mom thinks.
[breathes shakily]
[indistinct incantations echoing]
[uneasy music playing]
[whooshing]
[incantations continue]
[humming]
[dramatic swell]
[uneasy music building]
[music intensifies]
[echoing] Adama.
[dramatic sting]
[moans]
[music accelerates]
[dramatic sting]
[music fades]
[exhales]
[breathes shakily]
[dramatic swell]
[dramatic music playing]
[percussive music playing]
[drums beating rapidly]
[drums halt abruptly]
BASTIONS PROJECTS
What do you want, pal?
Hmm?
This has gotten out of control.
You don't know what he's capable of.
No.
But I can do much worse.
Your war's wearing on everyone.
The old and the young suffer most.
Please give his stash back.
[laughs]
"Give the stash back"?
[Adama exhales]
[scoffs]
No, think about what you're saying.
Where do you think you are?
- [Adama sighs]
- Business is business.
I took back what belonged to me,
that's all.
I'm not giving anything back.
I can tell you're a good kid.
Head back home before things go wrong.
Take him home.
- [man] Let's go.
- Don't touch me.
Go home!
I don't need your help.
[Adama inhales]
[cane scraping]
[gentle music playing]
[indistinct, faint yelling]
[engine accelerating]
[tires screech]
- Hold him! Don't move!
- Hey!
- Stop!
- Get over here!
Ah!
- Stop! Let go of me!
- [thug 1] Move, dammit!
[Adama grunts] Stop! Ah, fuck!
[grunting]
[dramatic sting]
[Adama gasps]
[spits]
[groans]
What were you doing talking to Eddy?
Nothing! I wasn't doing anything!
[grunts, coughs]
Our stash is gone.
You were at Eddy's hood,
but you weren't doing anything?
Tomtom saw you leave.
What were you doing there?
[Adama gulps]
Trying to get the stash back.
To fix the situation.
I swear to God.
[Adama grunts]
- [Adama yells]
- Talk!
- Talk, motherfucker!
- [Adama grunts, coughs]
[groans in pain]
Don't feel like talking? Come here!
He needs to talk.
Or we're dead.
He needs to be able to talk, then.
Chill, I have another idea.
[Adama coughs, whimpers]
- We'll let you think things over.
- [Adama breathing heavily]
When we come back,
you better have something good to tell us.
[breathes deeply]
[Adama whimpers]
[Adama coughing]
[door slams shut]
[Adama continues breathing heavily]
[uneasy music playing]
[echoing] Adama...
[witch whispering incantations]
The enemy of your enemy
is your friend, Adama.
[dramatic swell]
[inhales]
[bicycle bell rings]
Couldn't this wait
till I finished classes?
It couldn't wait.
You heard what people are saying?
Your brother is holding Adama captive.
Ridiculous.
No, it's not ridiculous.
When I asked my boys about it,
they told me.
His mom called me looking for him.
- She's scared.
- Who said that?
- [horn honks]
- I can't tell you.
You don't trust me, is that it?
Yes, of course I trust you.
I just don't trust your brother.
If he can do that to Adama, imagine me.
Look, I don't know what your friend said,
but he's full of shit, okay?
Ibra is no saint,
but stop blaming him for everything.
He'd never do that to Adama.
Really?
Was he not close to killing me?
He was trying to protect me.
That's different.
[Malik scoffs]
Stop making excuses for him all the time.
Open your eyes, please.
For real.
Before you lose everything.
[siren wailing in the distance]
- [door opens]
- [Adama gasps, groans]
[Adama breathing shakily]
Your son is right here.
[Adama's mom] Oh no, my baby!
What have they done to you?
My God! [sobs]
[Adama groans]
What's the matter with you?
Why would you beat him up like that?
- Hey, calm down! Take it easy, damn it!
- [sobbing]
Take it easy. Calm down.
[Adama's mom] Let go of me! [whimpers]
[Adama's mom sobbing]
[dramatic music playing]
You're gonna be okay.
It's okay, baby.
Get him to say
what he was doing at Eddy's, got it?
Or I'll kill him.
[door slams shut, locks]
Let me clean you up.
I'll make it all better.
I'll... I'll take care of you.
[sobbing]
My baby.
[inhales deeply] I can see.
My vision's improved.
[tender music playing]
[Aïssata] Hmm.
Have you heard from Adama?
What do you mean?
I guess Maimouna's been looking for him.
Do you know where he is?
Why are you asking me?
[Aïssata] No reason.
It's just people have been saying things.
What things?
What are they saying? Spit it out.
What is it?
- You're holding Adama captive.
- What?
Hey!
Ibé, tell me you didn't do that.
Ibé! Tell me that's not true.
[exhales]
Ibé, tell me you didn't do that.
Ibé!
- He betrayed me.
- What?
He did it to himself.
Nothing to do with me.
You have to let him go, Ibra, please.
You need to let him go.
- I can't. Not now.
- Mom.
Listen to your sister!
You can't do that! He's your brother!
- He's not family anymore.
- [Agna] What do you mean?
Mind your own business.
Leave me alone to my own affairs.
No, we won't mind our business.
This is serious.
- Did you know he beat up Malik too?
- Ibé...
He almost killed him.
- Dad never would've let you do this.
- Shut the fuck up!
What's with you? Shut your fucking mouth!
Don't talk about him here, okay?
Say his name one more time!
Where was he when you had to pay
for your rich school?
And when you needed a computer?
When we had to pay for this place?
I'm out here grinding for you!
You can't imagine what it's like
having a million problems to deal with,
but I do it so you can have a good life!
Oh, I see! It's mom's and my fault?
- Be a thug with everyone else, but not us!
- What the hell do you think?
You think this all comes from thin air?
That, that, that, all this?
How does it all come to be here?
You don't think I want to do legit things
like all your rich Parisian friends?
That's right, play the victim.
[Ibrahim] Ain't no victims here!
Ain't no victims here!
Don't even start with me!
I made all my money on my own,
and I don't owe anybody a thing!
[Aïssata] You can have your dirty money!
What do you think?
[Ibrahim]
Stop pretending like you don't get it!
- [Aïssata] My conscience isn't for sale!
- [Ibrahim] This is just business!
You can't do what I do
without commanding respect, got that?
[Aïssata] If you want blood on your hands,
go ahead! But you're on your own.
[Ibrahim] You don't know
what you're talking about!
[Aïssata] You think I give a fuck
about your money?
- [Ibrahim] Stop getting on my nerves!
- [Aïssata] You first!
- [Ibrahim] To hell with you!
- [Aïssata] Be gone! Piece of shit!
- I hate you! I fucking hate you!
- [door slams]
[sobbing]
[pensive music playing]
[door creaking open in distance]
[door slams in distance]
[groans]
[Adama groaning]
[foreboding music playing]
[exhales, breathing shakily]
[breathing heavily]
[Adama inhales]
[door unlocks]
[grunts, breathes heavily]
[Adama breathing heavily]
[Agna grunts]
[Maimouna gasps]
[Adama breathing heavily]
[grunts softly]
- It's Agna.
- Huh?
[breathes shakily]
[Adama exhales]
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
[breathing shakily]
I killed her.
[Maimouna sobbing]
Let's go, let's go, let's go! [panting]
Come on, let's get out of here!
[somber music playing]
[Adama breathing heavily]
[Adama breathing shakily]
- [sniffles]
- [Adama inhales]
Bring them in.
Come on, this way.
You sure about this?
What's the risk?
She's an old lady. He's a blind kid.
And I figure...
if your enemy's family joins your side,
you have him in your hand.
If anything happens, they're out.
Who gives a damn?
[car door lock chirps]
[Ibrahim breathing shakily]
She was like this when I walked in.
I called an ambulance. They're coming.
[Ibrahim breathes deeply]
She said she came for you,
but I didn't see her come down here.
Shut the fuck up!
- I'll kill you! I will end you!
- [friend] Ibra!
Ibra! Stop!
- [Ibrahim] I'll kill you!
- Stop!
- [Ibrahim yells]
- [friend] Ibra! Stop!
- I'll kill you, you son of a bitch!
- Ibra! Ibra! Stop!
- You're dead! You're fucking dead!
- Ibra!
Ugh! Let go of me!
- Look!
- Easy! Come on.
Look!
I know.
[Ibrahim] Look at what they did!
Look at what they fucking did!
[Ibrahim sobbing]
[continues sobbing]
[Adama breathing deeply, slowly]
[gentle music playing]
[exhales]
[Maimouna] Adama.
[Adama] Hmm?
While we're here, no one can know
you've recovered your eyesight.
It's like a shield.
No one suspects a blind person.
[Maimouna sighs]
You can't be a murderer
if you're a blind person.
Come here, my boy.
[Adama exhales softly]
[exhales]
I really didn't see her, Mom.
[somber music playing]
[breathing heavily]
I thought she was one of them.
I know, my son.
I'm aware of that.
But just stay blind.
No one will be able to question you.
Remember what Dad used to say.
Make a strength of your weakness.
Let me see your eyes.
[gentle music playing]
[sighs]
[engine turns over]
[engine accelerates]
[gentle music continues]
[knocking on door]
[Adama exhales]
Thanks.
[door shuts]
- [woman] Salam.
- [Malik] Hey, Mom.
[mom in Arabic] How are you?
[in English] Aïssata's waiting for you
in your room.
[in Arabic] Ask Aïssata
if she's eating with us.
[Malik in English] Holy shit.
[items clatter]
Where were you?
I was at the grocery store.
Grocery store?
You store groceries there?
No, it's just because...
because the store was closed.
[mom in Arabic] Ask Aïssata
if she's eating with us.
[Malik in English] My mom wants to know
if you're eating with us.
- [Aïssata] Mmm.
- Are you staying?
Yeah.
[mom speaks Arabic]
[mom in English] Here you go.
[Aïssata] Can I help in any way?
[register dings]
[dramatic music playing]
[man gasps]
Do your worst.
But I'm done with this.
I won't give you another penny.
[man breathes heavily]
Thank Heavens Ousmane
is no longer here to see this.
[dramatic swell]
What're you thinking?
Drag this out of here.
[dramatic music continues]
[sniffles]
Your presence puts us
and you at grave risk.
You're already on thin ice.
I know, but I had to talk to you.
It's all going to hell.
Ibrahim's been losing it
since Agna got into a coma.
You can't believe
how mad Aïssata is at you.
She's looking for you!
There's nothing?
No sign she'll wake up?
- [Malik] No.
- [Adama sucks teeth]
And it gets worse.
Ever since Eddy busted in
and stole the stash, he's been in control.
[upbeat music playing]
[dramatic swell]
Ibrahim's getting threats
from dealers he owes money to.
[grunting]
Some of his guys have disappeared.
The two projects are at war.
- I need him to call ASAP!
- The walls are closing in on him.
Motherfucking cops piss me off!
He's resorted to extorting
the store owners.
You know Chérif, the barber?
You know how he is. He stood up to him.
Now Chérif's gone.
That's it. No more barbershop.
It's ashes now.
- Damn it.
- [Malik] Mrs. Diop's shut herself in.
Aïssata's miserable.
My fucking love life, man, the hood,
and the kids, everything's on fire.
It's all gone wrong.
I had to see you and talk to you
because of this.
We need to do something.
I'm moved by what you're saying,
but what can I do?
Huh?
I don't know.
[Malik breathes deeply]
Maybe...
[breathing shakily]
Maybe you should go to the cops.
What?
This has to end.
Go and tell them what happened.
Tell them what Ibrahim did.
I don't love the police either, bro.
We don't have a choice.
It's gone too far.
[Adama breathes deeply]
What do I say about Agna?
Well, tell them the truth.
Tell them you're blind, you can't see,
and you didn't know it was her.
You thought it was Ibrahim and his gang
were coming to kill your mother and you.
- Go with the truth.
- He'll never go to prison.
Never.
I have no proof of what he did.
Nothing. Not even a fucking stash.
Did he squeal?
- To the cops?
- Mm-hmm.
No.
Of course he didn't squeal to the cops.
He's not the type who'd go to the cops.
[Adama sighs]
Even Aïssata can't tell anybody.
- [Adama sighs]
- They want you specifically.
[gentle music playing]
[breathes deeply]
[doorbell rings]
Morning, Aïssata.
- [Aïssata] How you doing, sweetie?
- Good. Malik isn't home.
I know.
I just came to get something, and I'll go.
Is your mom not home either?
No, she's at work.
Okay. Can I come in?
[sighs]
- I can't fucking believe this!
- [both chuckle]
Stop it.
- Holy shit!
- [Adama chuckles]
I mean, this is fucking wonderful!
- Like, you see me?
- Mm-hmm.
[Malik] It's like a fucking miracle!
Holy shit.
[Adama sighs]
It can happen.
What?
The blind getting their sight back.
[Malik] What do you mean?
[sighs] In times of emotional duress, or...
after a blow to the head,
you can get your sight back.
But Agna was a real accident.
My vision was still blurry
when it happened.
I thought he was coming to kill us.
I believe you.
[Malik sighs]
I have to get out of here, bro.
I can't stay locked up like this
day and night with my mom.
I can't. Not anymore.
I need to move far away.
[Adama sniffles]
I need to run away.
That's the only way to solve this.
I've always been a burden
on everyone anyway.
Come on, stop it.
Thanks for this.
Thanks, bro.
[sobbing]
[sniffles]
[door unlocks]
[Aïssata sniffles]
- You all right?
- Mm-hmm.
- You don't look all right.
- No, I'm fine.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Come on, you can talk to me.
Is it about Mom?
What, did the hospital call?
What is it?
We can find him.
We can find Adama.
Look, I want that as much as you do.
But I need you to promise me
you won't hurt Malik.
What's up with him?
What does he have to do with this?
Promise.
[Ibrahim sucks teeth, sighs]
Go on.
[Adama groans softly]
[somber music playing]
[whooshing]
[whooshes]
- [indistinct whispering]
- [music building]
[Adama gasps]
Eddy wants to see you.
[Malik grunts]
[Eddy] There's a right hook and another.
- [Malik] Let go of me!
- [Eddy] Going to get something.
What are you doing? What's that?
- [Eddy] Shears. He grabbed shears.
- What're you doing with that?
No, no, no! Don't do that!
Stop, please! [exhales]
- [shears snip]
- [Malik yells] Fuck!
Oh, damn it! Oh!
- [Malik groaning]
- [breathing angrily]
There's that.
He left something for you.
[Adama exhales]
[breathes shakily]
I understand.
Don't worry. [sniffles]
He said your buddy is in your basement.
He wants you to join him.
If I hand you over,
in exchange, he'll let me use
a few trap houses for a couple months.
[sniffles] Which I accepted.
You don't blame me, do you?
[sniffles] It's all just business.
Take him away.
[man clicks tongue] Come on.
What if I could promise you
the whole projects?
[Maimouna sobbing]
All right, let's go.
[Maimouna sniffles]
[somber music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[dramatic swell]
[thug] I say we just wait
a little longer, Ibra.
We're cornered.
Those bastards must be waiting.
- And plus...
- [door opens]
You promised me.
You fucking promised me!
- Aïssata, come on. Get out.
- Oumar, let go of me, please.
Ibra, I'm begging you. Please let him go.
If you love me, let him go.
Please listen to me, Ibra.
Please! Mom's in a coma because of you!
You don't want to see it, but everything,
everything that's happening
is because of you! You! Damn it, let go!
Let go of me, damn it! Stop!
- You let me out! Open the door, damn it!
- [bangs on door]
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You've gone mad! Let me out!
- Let me out!
- [continues banging]
[gun cocks]
[clicks]
[lock clicks]
[metallic squeak in the distance]
[metallic clank in the distance]
[man] Who's there? Who's there?
- [loud thud]
- Hey! [groans]
[Malik grunts]
[Malik breathing heavily]
[door unlocking]
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
It's me, bro.
It's over.
Fucking hell.
- We need to move.
- Okay.
[Malik continues breathing heavily]
[intense music playing]
[indistinct yells]
[Adama breathes deeply]
[line ringing]
[man] Police, what's your emergency?
[hissing]
[echoed whooshes]
[whooshing]
[indistinct whispers]
[witch] Adama.
[dramatic music playing]
[men coughing]
- [man 1] Fuck!
- [men continue coughing]
[men grunt]
[man 1] Ah, damn it! [coughs]
- Come on, get up!
- [man 2 coughs]
[coughing continues]
[dramatic swell]
[Oumar and Adama grunting]
[loud thud]
[Adama breathing heavily]
[man] The power's out.
Something's not right.
I don't give a damn, man!
We got twenty-two pounds in the house.
Come pick it up.
Get a car, grab some gloves, and stash it.
It ain't my problem where.
Figure something out!
Just get your ass over here! Now!
[knocking on door]
Five minutes, hurry up.
You can come with Tony if you want.
Here, listen to me. Listen to me!
Ibrahim looked me right in the eyes...
What's going on?
What's all that noise?
Come.
Stay in here.
Lock yourself in.
Under no circumstances
will you open the door.
Wait till the cops arrive.
- [phone line ringing]
- [man] Police, what's your emergency?
[Adama] Hi, I'm calling from an apartment
in Block C of the Murets Projects.
A gang from
the Bastions Projects are here,
and they're attacking everyone in sight!
[man] Who's attacking you?
[Adama] A gang from the Bastions Project.
They're armed,
and they're attacking people!
[man] Armed with what?
[Adama] I don't know.
You have to stop them. Come quick!
[dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
[breathing shakily]
[Adama grunts]
[Adama grunts, panting]
What are you doing here?
[Adama grunting, yelling]
- [Adama coughs]
- Get up.
[Aïssata] Ibra, is everything okay?
Answer me, damn it!
- What's going on? Fuck! Tell me!
- [Adama grunts]
- Ibra, answer me, damn it!
- [door handle rattling]
[Adama grunts]
Ibra, answer me, please!
- [banging on door]
- What's going on?
[Adama grunting]
[Adama straining]
[choking]
[Aïssata] Open the door, Ibra!
What's going on? Come on! Answer me!
- Look what you've made me do.
- [Aïssata] What's happening?
[Ibrahim] Look what you've made me do!
[Ibrahim grunts]
- [Adama grunts]
- [Ibrahim groans]
- [Ibrahim thuds]
- [Adama breathing shakily]
[Adama gasping, coughing]
[Ibrahim breathing heavily]
[Ibrahim groans]
[door handle rattling]
[Aïssata] Ibra, just answer me, please!
What's happening out there?
[Ibrahim exhales]
[Adama breathing shakily]
[Aïssata] Damn it, Ibra, answer me!
Ibra, damn it, answer me!
What the fuck's going on?
- [door handle rattling]
- [banging on door]
Ibra! Shit!
Ibra, please, stay with me.
Ibra, everything will be fine. Look at me.
I promise, everything will be fine.
- [clamoring]
- [Adama panting]
Please stay with me. I'm here.
Please. I'm here.
Look at me. No, no, no, no! Don't go!
No, no, stay with me, please!
No, no, no, no! No! [sobs]
No, not you, Ibra! Please!
Ibra, please, don't go! Don't leave me!
[sobbing]
Ibra!
[sirens wailing in the distance]
[clamoring continues]
[intense music playing]
[inaudible]
[dramatic swell]
[clamoring]
[sirens continue wailing]
You! Come with me!
Hurry it up! Come on! Let's go, let's go!
Hey, hey! He's fine, he's fine, he's fine!
I know him. The kid's blind.
Can't you see he's blind?
Why would he be mixed up in all this?
Let him go. Come on, let's move.
We got bigger fish to fry. Come on.
- [cop] Come with me, you piece of shit!
- Let me go!
[intense music continues]
[whistle blows in the distance]
[music building]
[music halts abruptly]
[mysterious music playing]
[whooshing]
[young Adama] Embrace your weakness.
Look to make it your strength.
Embrace your weakness.
[adult Adama] Embrace your weakness.
Look to make it your strength.
Embrace your weakness.
["Le Roi des ombres" by Kaaris playing]
[song ends]
[instrumental music playing]
[music fades]