Being hungry all the time
is humanity's worst tragedy.
The first time I ate a mouse,
I thought,
I need to eat this to survive.
We had nothing to eat and
we certainly couldn't buy medicine.
So they laid me to one side,
waiting for me to die.
I was hung upside down
and beaten for 14 hours.
We never knew when we'd get beaten.
There was constant fear.
We never imagined anyone
could sell and buy people.
I'm filled with hatred of North Korea
that murdered my family.
My family has believed in God
for generations.
They were all arrested.
From my early years in the military,
what I remember most
is robbing people
in the villages when we got hungry.
I saw my friends
fighting for their breath,
and right in front of my eyes,
they'd die.
If the person who created
such a place isn't a criminal,
I don't know who is.
North Korea is the most isolated
country in the world.
Famine and food shortages
have killed millions since 1994.
Repression is total.
The government operates a
system of concentration camps.
Prison Camp Locations
Escape is punishable by death.
I escaped on February 1st, 2001.
I went through China, Vietnam,
Cambodia and Thailand.
You had to bribe the police for
a pass to travel toward the border.
I sold everything I owned. I bought
the travel pass with the money.
I crossed the border at night.
If you didn't bribe,
you would get caught.
If you got caught,
you were shot to death.
These are the stories of
people who fled North Korea
between 1992 and 2006.
Such events
are still happening today.
MRS. KIM
She was a dancer in North Korea.
Her best friend became
Kim Jong-Il's lover.
The friendship cost her everything.
You could say I was sent to prison
for knowing the private lives
of powerful men.
One guy was imprisoned
for saying
Kim Il-Sung had a lump in his neck.
One had spread a newspaper with
Kim Il-Sung's picture on the floor.
One was in for listening
to South Korean radio.
We were all deported,
my parents and my four kids,
2 years old, 4 years old,
7 years old, and 9 years old.
I was released from Yodok prison camp
after 8 and 1/2 years.
One of my sons had died,
and I gave up my daughter
for adoption after leaving the camp.
Otherwise, she would have been
stigmatized and unable to marry.
I don't know what happened
to my husband.
For the last 35 years,
I've wondered if he's still alive.
I don't even know what his crime was.
One of my sons tried to escape in '89
but was caught
at the border and shot.
I had such mental trauma.
My mother and father
died of starvation
in Yodok prison camp.
My first son drowned in a river,
on the way back from camp school.
I'm so filled with hatred and anger.
My last son was captured twice
and tortured so much
his lungs filled with blood.
He was released
because he was nothing but a shell.
He's still hospitalized,
handicap level-2.
He can't breathe.
How can anyone praise Kim Jong-il?
I'm filled with hatred
for North Korea.
They murdered my family.
I can't live without tears.
My heart aches.
He left me alone in the world.
Cursed Kim Jong-il.
The Kim dynasty has ruled
North Korea for 60 years.
The Great Leader Kim Il Sung
President for Life
They had us all worship him as a god.
Christians say grace
before their meals.
We said grace to Kim Il Sung.
He was like a supreme being
so we thought he didn't even pee.
He was our father's father
and our mother's father.
The most revered one.
On April 15th, 1912,
Kim Il-Sung was born.
The Almighty Sun hath risen.
We were so lucky to worship
the 21st Century's Sun.
In one generation, he defeated
two great imperial powers.
In our 5000 year history,
he was the first to do that.
He's our nation's hero.
That's what we were taught.
He can travel miles
while sitting down.
Kim Il-Sung has superhuman powers.
He'd appear simultaneously
in the east and the west.
Kim Il-Sung can fly north,
south, east and west.
He appeared like a star
and we worship him like the Sun.
So April 15th
became the Day of the Sun.
In 1994, Kim Il Sung died.
His son Kim Jong Il took power.
I thought the world was ending.
What would we do?
Without him, nothing could be right.
I absolutely thought he was divine.
Just replace Kim Il-Sung with God.
That's our religion.
We were totally brainwashed.
If I were still there,
I would still worship him.
I'd also worship his son,
Kim Jong-il.
The Dear Leader Kim Jong-Il
The General
I thought of the Great Leader
as a father,
so how could he let his people
live like this?
I jumped off the train.
I had boarded the train to Hae-San.
It was winter.
The train was going uphill,
so it was slow.
There was a lot of snow
on the ground,
so we didn't get hurt.
I didn't know where we were,
but everyone was jumping off,
so I jumped with the others.
My childhood was happy.
I had five or six aquariums
with all kinds of fish.
We kids all competed to see
who had the best fish.
One fish had bulging eyes.
That was the most prized,
and I looked all over for it.
KANG CHOL-HWAN
His grandfather was arrested
for an unnamed crime.
North Korean practice
is to purge three generations.
Kang, his grandmother,
father, uncle,
and little sister
were taken to Yodok prison camp.
The soldiers' tone was so harsh.
I was getting frightened.
Kang screamed so much,
the soldiers let him take one
of his beloved aquariums.
He was 9 years old.
The iron gates opened.
The soldiers were armed.
I began to feel real fear.
Everyone was so skinny.
The children were so weak
and fragile.
They were in rags.
At first, I dried bugs for my fish.
That's how I fed them.
But when I started forced labour,
I didn't have time for them.
I had no time to cry.
Every day was so tiring.
We worked so hard.
I was so cold.
You don't care about your pet fish
when you're dying.
I was bitter.
Everything I treasured was gone.
The worst job was mining.
In my ten years in the gulag,
the best job I ever had
was taking care
of the beehives
for the high officials.
The only bad part
was that we were isolated.
At night we were lonely,
but we found some books.
There were smuggled books
circulating in the camp.
"The Count of Monte Cristo".
"Anna Karenina", "Resurrection".
I think "The Count of Monte Cristo"
touched me the most.
- He looks dead.
- He is dead.
We'll get the undertakers.
Reading "Monte Cristo"
gave me the idea
to escape North Korea.
If I ever got out,
I'd take revenge like him.
Holding to his duty
to be loyal to the leader,
Kim Jong-Il said,
"Nobody in the world
has ever dedicated all his life
to the people's cause
for so many years
and undergone so many hardships
as our leader has done.
Whenever I think of the leader
working restlessly
for the People's happiness,
I feel my eyes moisten.
I wrack my brains to take the load
from his mind and make him happy.
SHIN DONG-HYUK
He was born
in Total Control Prison Camp 14.
He never knew
why his parents were there.
They had fenced off a large area
with barbed wire
and built housing and factories.
You don't live behind bars in cells.
Within a confined area,
you'd do the work you were assigned.
There were coal mines and farmlands,
and jobs where you cut down trees.
Or we were assigned
to sweat shops and other factories.
Camp school was simple.
They taught us how to dig for coal
and how to transport it.
During Korean class,
we learned how to read and write.
In math,
we only learned to add and subtract.
After roll call,
you'd recite the rules of the sector.
RULES OF THE SECTOR
Any prisoner who does not do his best
to complete the assigned work,
will be presumed
to have an attitude...
and will be executed
by firing squad immediately.
Any prisoner who steals
or hides food will be executed
by firing squad immediately.
Any prisoner who disobeys...
or does not obey diligently...
will be executed
by firing squad immediately.
Any prisoner who tries to run away,
or fails to report someone
else's attempted escape...
will be executed immediately.
On November 29th, 1996,
after my mother and brother died,
only me and my father were left.
SHIN was forced to watch
his mother and brother
publicly executed.
Older people or intellectuals
committed suicide.
But almost none of the kids did.
We never knew when we'd get beaten.
There was constant fear.
If you didn't work hard enough,
you got punished by the guards.
They cut your food ration.
Sometimes they'd cut it in half.
Sometimes they'd make you
completely starve.
North Korean Film
North Korea's economy depends
partly on forced labor.
Some products made in prison camps:
army uniforms
bricks
leather shoes
snake liquor.
Some forced-labor products
have been exported:
doilies to Poland
paper flowers to France
bras to Russia.
A guy from Pyongyang
came to the camp.
Usually, we didn't talk to outsiders.
He was afraid too.
But we worked together.
We started trusting each other.
He told me
what his life had been like.
His life in Pyongyang.
The best stories were about eating.
After I heard his stories,
the camp became totally unbearable.
I asked him to tell me the stories
over and over.
I came up with the idea of escaping.
"Let's try to escape."
So we planned it together.
On January 2nd, 2005,
we said we were going
to collect firewood.
I knew we could get shot
or electrocuted,
but right then,
I was full of confidence.
When January 2nd came,
we climbed the mountains.
I saw the guards
and the barbed wire gates.
All of a sudden I was afraid.
I was shaking, losing my nerve.
And then my friend said,
"I don't think we can do it.
You're scared and I'm scared."
But I couldn't give up.
I had to escape.
We were about 20 meters
from the gates.
It had been 15 minutes
since the guard passed.
We had to run.
I practically dragged him.
I was one step ahead of him
as we approached the gates.
He was following,
and then I slipped in the snow,
so he ran ahead of me.
When I saw the wired gates,
I figured he was squeezing
through the electric wires.
So I followed his lead
and squeezed through too.
When I got up and looked behind me,
I realized
I was on the other side of the gates.
Then I saw my friend was stuck
and didn't move.
He was still stuck in the wires.
Right then,
all I could think was I had to run.
Run down the mountain away
from the gates.
I was all the way down
when I realized
maybe he was electrocuted.
If I hadn't fallen,
I would have been the first
to squeeze through the electric wire.
I would have been
the one electrocuted.
SHIN DONG-HYUK
Born in Total Control Camp 14
Escaped in 2005 at age 24
The whole nation
is run by Kim Jong-il
and his gang.
The camps,
the starvation, everything.
And the North Korean people
continue to suffer.
There will be more and more victims
until you change the system.
KANG CHOL-HWAN
10 years in Yodok,
released in 1987
fled North Korea in 1992
first to expose
the existence of camps
Japan colonized Korea
Kim Il Sung is born
to a Christian Family.
His grandfather
is a Protestant minister.
1919-1940
Korean freedom fighters,
aided by the Church,
resist the Japanese.
Kim Il Sung joins the resistance
and adopts communism.
The Japanese put a price
on Kim Il Sung's head.
He flees to the Soviet Union.
The Allies defeat Japan
in World War II.
The Soviets and Allies
divide Korea along the 38th parallel.
Kim Il Sung founds the Democratic
People's Republic of Korea
as a Marxist state.
North Korea attacks South Korea.
1950-1953
The Korean War brings
widespread destruction and death.
Kim Il Sung blames Americans.
Demilitarized Zone (DMZ)
established along the 38th parallel.
No peace treaty is signed.
1950's-1970's
Kim Il Sung and the Korean
Workers Party rebuild
North Korea and establish
a Worker's Paradise.
Free from Oppression and Hunger.
In North Korea, an artist
is an instrument of the Party.
He's a mouthpiece for the system.
KIM CHEOL-WOONG
CONCERT PIANIST
If your head's not Red,
you can't proclaim the Red.
The children of the upper class,
those loyal to Kim Jong-il
are the only ones admitted
to the music conservatory.
Your family background is everything.
As a kid, I didn't know
my class background was bad.
If there's a political prisoner
in your family
and you make even a tiny mistake,
it gets blown way out of proportion.
LEE SHIN
SINGER
In North Korea,
no matter how talented you are,
if your class background is bad,
you're stuck.
They said my voice
was like a South Korean pop singer's.
My voice was unacceptable
in North Korea,
because it sounded capitalist.
We thought ours was the only kind
of music in the world.
When I was sent to Russia to study,
I was stunned to find out
how restricted we were.
Everything I thought
I knew was a lie.
It was a rude awakening.
Our country knowingly taught us lies.
The turning point was when I played
a piece by Richard Clayderman.
Someone heard and reported me.
Even if you just listened to music
from capitalist countries,
you'd get arrested.
My whole life
was dedicated to the piano,
but I couldn't play what I wanted.
I decided to escape.
I was starving
and tightening my belt
around my belly.
We pretended we were pretty
and our stomachs were full.
We sang, "How shall we spread
this bountiful rice?"
We sang a lot of songs like that,
with a smile.
I don't understand even now.
Early on, the government
dictated agricultural policies.
Food shortages began
in the 1980's.
1989: demise of the Soviet Union
1994: famine declared
1995: devastating floods
By the mid-90's,
starvation was widespread.
Nevertheless, the Party
ordered farmers to grow opium.
Because of The Great Famine in 1994,
we were having a very hard time.
We'd go to the mountains
to pick roots.
We ate grass from the fields
and bark from the trees.
BYEON OK-SUN
She lived with her parents,
3 brothers,
and sister in a northern town.
The only source of food was
the state-run distribution system.
By the time she was 17,
that system had collapsed.
One day, I was with
my father in the mountains.
I got soaked with rain
while we were foraging.
After we finished, I went home.
My body started
to burn and I fainted.
We had nothing to eat
and we certainly
couldn't buy medicine.
So they laid me to one side,
waiting for me to die.
I had typhoid fever
and was in a coma.
When the food rations stopped
in the late 1980's,
people's lives completely changed.
People started selling
household items,
like TVs, electronics, and furniture.
People would sell
anything to buy food.
When everything was gone,
they'd sell their homes.
They didn't think of stealing.
There was nothing to steal.
They were the first to die.
They say man is selfish by nature.
Do you think so, too, Si Nae?
No, that's a lie. Babies are not.
My brother-in-law's
written from abroad
about the sad state there.
How ugly things are turning there!
What would the revolutionary martyrs
say if they were alive?
NORTH KOREAN FILM
GIRLS IN MY HOMETOWN
My home is in Anbyon,
Kangwon Province.
A nice place to live in
with its abundant fruit.
Rich crops sway in breeze.
Persimmon trees bear
plentiful fruits in every house.
Come to see our village.
You can meet pretty girls here.
1991: "Let's Eat Two Meals a Day"
campaign
1995: North Korea
asks for international aid
$2.5 billion sent -
North Korea demands control
30% to 70% diverted to the elite
Humanitarian organizations
withdraw in frustration
Estimated number of dead:
600,000 to 3,500,000
Taking care of corpses
was the biggest problem
towards the end of '95.
This problem was even reported
to Kim Jong-il,
so he stationed military units
in each town.
They weren't armed.
The soldiers loaded corpses
into their military trucks
around the clock.
The bodies were rotting.
We didn't escape
because we wanted to.
We had to.
I crossed over
to get medical treatment.
My brother carried me on his back.
I'd been in China for a month
when I came out of the coma.
I woke up in an empty room,
alone except for an old woman.
I was scared.
She said, "You're in China."
"How did I get here?"
She told me my brothers
carried me on their backs.
My brothers had gone to find work
to pay for the treatment.
They left me with her.
Most Chinese were afraid. Very few
were willing to hide defectors.
The woman said she'd protect
the weakest of us four,
so I stayed.
My older sister and 2 brothers
scattered to make their own ways.
It was my oldest brother's duty
to take care
of his parents and siblings.
His sense of duty toward our parents
was very strong.
No matter where he was,
in North Korea or China,
he felt that responsibility.
He took me on his back to save me.
After he saved me in China,
with our parents back in North Korea,
he felt very tortured.
He'd get food
and take it back to our parents.
He was constantly
sneaking back and forth.
Then somehow,
the National Intelligence Service,
caught him making trips to China.
When he realized they were on to him,
he decided to give himself up.
If you give yourself up,
you expect to receive
a lighter sentence.
That's what he thought.
Instead, he was taken
and publicly executed.
The fact that they killed a person
like him, it's hard to deal with.
Even now. He's my brother...
I feel so guilty.
My big brother's death was...
I feel he died because of me.
I live with a guilty conscience
all the time.
They kill people without mercy.
They don't even feel any guilt.
I know it's the country of my birth,
but I really hate it.
I don't want
to live there ever again.
Those feelings are strong.
The kimjongilia,
or flower of Kim Jong Il,
was created for the Dear Leader's
46th birthday.
They say it represents love,
peace, wisdom, and justice.
LOVE PEACE
WISDOM JUSTICE
The military suffered too.
The state only supplied us
with rice and salt.
We had to get
everything else ourselves.
We started to grow beans
on our basketball courts
and soccer fields.
The soldiers learned to
survive without eating fat.
On Kim Jong-il's birthday,
they'd give the ghastly-looking
skinny soldiers a piece of pork.
They'd eat it and get diarrhea.
They said soldiers died
of uncontrollable diarrhoea.
That's nonsense. It was malnutrition.
When I was serving in the military,
the malnourished soldiers
were admitted to the infirmaries.
The infirmaries
held 200 to 300 patients.
They'd shave everyone's heads
with razors.
You couldn't distinguish men
from women.
Women's periods stopped
due to malnutrition.
These days, many officers desert.
Even if you want to work,
there are always supplies missing.
Making it impossible to do the job.
But commanders go on
issuing orders every day.
You have to steal
the supplies you need.
This is the current situation
in North Korea.
If you care at all, it is impossible
not to express your frustration.
Consequently, many are arrested.
PARK MYUNG-HO
He was a captain
in the Korean People's Army.
He served for 20 years.
His father was a soldier too.
Ever since I became an officer,
I have felt this so-called "country"
has been made so tragic and horrific.
I held so much resentment
toward the government.
Really.
For about 10 years, I brooded.
That's what drove me to escape.
If we went through China,
the whole family
would have had to separate,
so we decided to cross
the 38th parallel by boat.
On the evening of May 23rd, 2006,
I saw a thick fog rolling in.
I could tell it would last
two or three days.
At around 10 that night,
we sailed for the 38th parallel.
We evaded Navy ships twice.
Because our boat was small
and theirs were big,
we could see them first
and get away.
Actually, the North Korean ships
had no fuel.
They couldn't start their engines
and were under sail.
I covered all the metal on our boat
with blankets to block their radar.
We landed in Incheon City,
Ong-jin province.
When I saw all the trees
on the mountains,
I knew we were in South Korea.
PARK MYUNG-HO
TOOK HIS FAMILY OVER 200 MILES
THROUGH DANGEROUS WATERS
REACHED SOUTH KOREA IN 2006
Tumen River border between
North Korea and China
300,000 people have fled
North Korea in the last 10 years.
Because the DMZ is impassable,
most go to China.
There are approximately 2,000,000
ethnic Koreans living in China.
I heard rumours
that people escaped to China.
I went with money
I brought from home.
I had about $2000 that I...
I guess you'd have to say I stole it.
I stole it and took off.
I used the money
to bribe the National Border Control.
They guided me
across the river to China.
I just recklessly went
to the first ethnic Korean village
across the border.
I proudly announced I was
a concert pianist from Pyongyang.
They didn't care
about my piano playing,
they wanted my physical strength.
From that day on,
I became their servant.
I went to find my older sister.
She had escaped to China,
so it was too dangerous for me
to continue appearing on stage.
We found out
she had been sold to traffickers.
So we went to find her
but couldn't,
and wound up stuck there.
We had a "guide"
who claimed
he was looking for her.
In fact, he was selling us
to traffickers too.
We didn't know
we were being sold.
They said the police were after
us and we had to flee.
But it was a lie to trap us.
They were going to sell us.
In the taxi, I cried and pleaded,
but no one saved us.
In China, I gave up being human.
Because we were North Koreans,
we were defenceless.
All kinds of women
from 16 to 40 years old
were sold.
We were beaten for no reason
and couldn't defend ourselves.
The men would get drunk
and violent.
The girls
would try to escape
and get caught.
I was desperate.
I decided to risk crashing
the South Korean Embassy in Beijing.
I faced down the police.
My mom, my sisters and I
made it inside safely.
I don't know
where I got the strength.
LEE SHIN
5 YEARS IN SEXUAL SLAVERY
REACHED SOUTH KOREA IN 2003
We were constantly
in danger in China.
You can't walk around openly.
If you're caught, you're sent back.
I slept in a storage room
like this one.
The police even patrolled there.
They were uniformly brutal,
demanding ID or family papers.
Ethnic Koreans who protected us
were fined
if they were caught by the police.
There's a detention centre in China
for defectors.
I was held there
for about four months.
They torture you until you admit
you're a defector.
I was hung upside down
and beaten for 14 hours.
I was so worried about my hands
I tucked them tightly in my armpits.
I thought, I can't ruin my hands.
Small groups
of South Korean Christian activists
attempt to spirit defectors
out of China.
Shenyang, China
500 miles from North Korean border
an actual mission
rescue mission office -
February, 2008
going to meet NK defectors
Back. Back
Over there.
Defector pick-up point
Can you see us? We're here.
Look at that guy over there.
Suspected Chinese agent
Not there. Turn around.
Turn around.
They were supposed to be
at the glass door.
Get out of there.
Mission aborted
CHOI YOUNG-HUN
A SOUTH KOREAN ACTIVIST WHO
TRIED TO RESCUE NORTH KOREANS,
HE SPENT FOUR YEARS
JAILED IN CHINA
Come here quick.
I need to hold your hands.
I'm shaking.
You were more distressed.
She's the hero.
It's my wife who's the hero.
Chinese prison is simply hell.
10 days after his release
Chinese prisoners
work 18 hours a day.
You know
the Korean wedding bouquets?
You make the flowers
out of paper,
tie them with wires.
You make
the flower shapes like this,
then cover them with asbestos powder,
which causes lung disease.
Asbestos,
it's very irritating.
So we make these artificial flowers,
and the irony is that they
are exported
to South Korea.
I thought everything
would be back to normal
once he came back.
But he is broken,
mentally unstable.
I don't know what
the future holds for our family.
It's nerve-wracking.
In North Korea
they say there is no God,
but my family has been religious
for generations.
They were all arrested.
I just thought, that's how life is.
I had to hide my faith.
There was a Korean-Chinese pastor
who urged us
to come to China.
I stayed with a missionary for a year
who taught me the Bible.
Then he wanted me
to go back to North Korea
and spread the gospel.
I said no.
I left because life there
was too hard.
I was determined
to go to South Korea.
With the missionary's help,
I made it there safely.
In China, a fellow defector told me
there was a piano in the church.
So I went to the church
at the foot of the mountain.
And that's how
I got to play the piano.
They liked my playing.
They asked me to stay
and play the piano.
From then on, I lived in the church.
Through them,
I met South Korean missionaries
who helped me get to South Korea.
Unlike China, Mongolia does not
repatriate North Korean refugees.
So for North Koreans,
it is one of the few routes
out of China, to freedom.
The guide was leading
a group of defectors.
My sister and I had to meet them
at the border of China and Mongolia.
Someone suddenly appeared in front
on us. Everyone scattered.
It all happened so suddenly
Our guide ran away.
I didn't know what to do.
I wanted to go back
but I couldn't speak Chinese.
I couldn't think at all.
And the future seemed pitch black.
Only me and a teenage boy
made it into Mongolia.
Everyone else was arrested.
They've all been released.
Except my sister. I have no news.
I think I won't see her again
in this life.
Don't worry about us, sister.
Our father is still with us.
We open our hearts.
Without reserve full of hope.
We live relying on General
as our god.
Only on our General forever.
The future?
Well, I don't know.
Kim Jong-il
only talks about reunification.
It won't happen while he's alive.
For over 20 years,
the entire North Korean population
has stopped working.
If that turns into 30 years,
I think it will be over.
We refugees don't actively
go out and fight
because of the danger to ourselves
and our families still in the North.
We still fear North Korea.
If outside countries
stop helping Kim Jong-il,
North Koreans will end this tyranny
with their bare hands.
I am certain.
If they fight for democracy,
no matter how many laws there are
against "political" crimes,
there won't be enough prisons
for a million political prisoners.
They can't execute a million people.
We know when Kim Jong-il dies,
there will be chaos.
But whatever chaos comes
couldn't be worse
than the chaos under Kim Jong-il.
When the leader changes
and I can go back,
I want to do all I can to change it
as fast as possible.
I want to make that land prosperous.
In North Korea,
it's the dictatorship that's evil.
If you look at the individual,
many are so good
and innocent and kind.
If Kim Jong-il's dictatorship
collapsed now,
I'd be in North Korea tomorrow.
Camps existed in the past,
like in the Hitler,
Mao and Stalin eras,
but I think it's a disgrace
to the human race
that such camps exist today.
I want Kim Jong-il to fear.
I want to make him stand
in the International Court.
He killed and imprisoned
tens of thousands of people.
He forces young children
to watch public executions
and terrorizes the population.
That in itself is a crime.
We have no freedom of speech.
We have no freedom of movement.
If the person
who created such a place
isn't a criminal,
I don't know who is.
I'm grateful for South Korea
and the world
and peace.
I love the people
who love peace and liberty.
Since I've tasted freedom,
I need to share it with my people.
We have to free the North Koreans.
I wonder if anyone's listening
to our pleas.
North Koreans can't speak,
can't see, can't listen,
can't eat, can't smell, can't speak.
They're bound by wires, like plants.
I feel such compassion for them.
The world has to save North Korea.
We have to speak of it.
We wish to thank all of the people
who participated in this film.
We hope their courageous testimony
will help save the millions of people
still at risk in North Korea.