(upbeat music)
(instrumental music)
- Once it's loaded, we're out of here.
- Radio Evan. We're after the center container.
(upbeat music)
- Damn, tell Evan there's some guy down there.
He just took off running.
(upbeat music)
(phone rings)
- This is Chance Wayne.
I'm not home right now.
Leave your name and number and I'll get back to you.
- Chance, this is Hector Hernandez.
I found the murderer of my daughter, Sharon.
Five years we've been looking and we were right.
It's Evan Long.
I'll call you every hour.
Adios, my friend.
(instrumental music)
(upbeat music)
- I'm getting real tired of you, hermano,
I think it's time for you to join the choir, muchacho.
(whistles)
Okay, I'm personally gonna take care of this one.
Chilly, I want you to drive.
- Right.
- The rest of you, get in the van and follow us.
- You got it, Evan.
(train whistle)
(train rumbles)
(helicopter hums)
(upbeat music)
(gun shots)
- Let's go, Evan.
We're hooked up.
(gun shots)
(upbeat music)
- I'm gonna have to jet us from the load.
Mark the spot, we're gonna have to come back.
(helicopter buzzes)
(instrumental music)
- Neck wounds, both carotid arteries and jugular veins slit.
Pharynx and esophagus eviscerated,
probably post-mortem mutilation.
Apparent petechial hemorrhaging.
I'm sorry Hector, I really screwed up.
I'll find out who did this and that's a promise.
- Hey, pop.
What do you think you're doing?
- Watch out, sink hole.
- You'll have a stain.
- Something I can do for you, pop?
- Sheriff's Department retired.
- Well, if you're retired, go peel an apple or something.
This is federal land.
It's my crime scene.
So
move out of it.
- I hear you talking.
- Go on, get out of here.
- What is your name, sir?
- He's Cam Cavanaugh, federal investigator.
I'm JoJo Golina, assistant US Attorney.
- Well, I need to establish a time of death
but this looks pretty fresh to me.
Maybe an hour or two.
- 12 hours, would be my guess
- Either get out of my crime scene or go to jail.
- Boy, you sure are using up a lot of oxygen, Mr. Cavanaugh.
You gotta simmer down.
This is not a crime scenes, it's a dump site.
From them little fish bites,
I'd say somebody dumped him out in the bay
and then he floated in.
Now the maggot larvae, that's at least two generations.
And since it breeds every six hours,
it's been at least 12 hours since he was washed up here.
Now the next thing that you got wrong is the knife
and that is post-mortem.
He was strangled then knifed.
- Says who, pop?
- Them particular hemorrhages on the eyeballs.
You see them little blood vessels, they burst on the cornea.
The only way that happens is with strangulation.
Now, the third thing that you got wrong is
I'm not your pop.
Although I might enjoy that as it would give me
some jurisdiction over that huge hole in your head
that you keep bellowing out of.
Ma'am.
- Sheriff.
(instrumental music)
- What a joke.
(upbeat music)
- She was so beautiful, Sharon.
Oh God, forgive me.
Maybe he's better off where he is now.
Maybe he is with her.
Maybe they both have found some peace now.
- Peace without justice,
there's no such thing.
- You have lost so much yourself.
You lost your wife to a disease,
your son in Vietnam.
You are the only one left who cares.
- And I'm so sorry, Helena.
But the next time that I come,
I'm gonna bring some justice.
I'm gonna find out who killed Hector
and you can count on it.
- You're not gonna believe this.
I just checked Hector Hernandez's phone machine
using retrieval code,
there's a message on it from Chance Wayne.
So now I say we close the account in full.
- The parameters of this case are fairly simple.
The plaintiff, Buck, contends that his valuable stamp
was lying in an ashtray and was used by his brother, Billy
to send a postcard to his brother, Bobby.
The defendant, Billy, claims that the stamp valued at $100
should not have been lying in that ashtray.
And Bobby says that he is now the owner
because it was affixed to a postcard
addressed to him.
However, the plaintiff did own the stamp,
So the court finds that the stamp still belongs to Buck
and granddad will take everybody
to the park on Sunday and supply lunch.
No hugging the judge until the court is dismissed.
- You used to run a much tougher court, Bob.
- Well, I've mellowed since I retired, Chance.
- Uncle Chance. - Hey, uncle Chance.
- Hey, you guys getting big.
- I'll be right back,
I gotta supervise the verdict.
Come on guys.
- Catch you later. - Alrighty.
- I'm glad you came by.
I'm worried about him.
He's been getting phone calls, threats on his life.
And the doctor says his blood pressure is high.
So he's gotta reduce stress.
And I thought that maybe you could rein him in
because he's always listened to you.
- Yeah, he'd listen to me
and then he did whatever he wanted to do.
But I'll give it a shot.
Thanks.
- Justice is swift.
They're outside playing.
Case closed.
- Well, you guys, make yourselves at home.
- Thank you.
- Well, I understand that
somebody's been threatening your life.
- A little threatening every now and then
is good for a guardian of justice.
If I wasn't getting threatened,
I'd be worried I wasn't doing a good job.
I'm not worried.
- Is that why you're wearing that round wheel on your ankle?
- At least if I go, I won't be hiding behind the curtains.
- Well, Anne also said that your blood pressure is up.
- I sure hope you ain't gonna charge me for this visit.
- I just don't want you to pitch forward
and to play the pastor.
- So a book says I'm below 180 over 90.
- Bob, when I start taking bets on your blood pressure,
you got my permission to hook me up to my car exhaust.
It's probably just the thrill and excitement
of seeing me that's all.
So who's threatening your life?
Maybe I can give you a hand there
- You remember John Paper Collar Dolan aka tidewater Dolan,
fit throwing Dolan, half a dozen other scum bowl aliases.
- It's hard to forget the best bunco player in third state
till you matched him up.
- Well, he's rejoining society today at noon.
There's a wine and cheese reception outside the prison gate.
You wanna go?
- Well, he's a gas but he's not a killer.
- Prison changes people.
Anyway, I figured we go over to the prison,
give him a little backseat attitude check,
like we did in the old days when we were cops together.
- Why not?
- No, no, the doctor said I had to quit.
I just like to roll them.
Kinda stupid, isn't it?
(instrumental music)
- I hear some guy named Hernandez got himself killed
and that you've been out flapping your wings over the body.
That wouldn't be Sharon's father, would it?
- Yeah, it's five years since she was murdered
and I still haven't solved it.
Hector and I was working on it.
Now somebody's killed him.
See, I think Hector found something and it got him killed.
We both been trying to find Evan Long,
now, he picked up Evan's trail.
- Good, it's done.
- Better be, here comes your boy.
(upbeat music)
- Stay cool, Little.
Well, well, well,
What have we got here?
The Poligrip twin.
What do I owe this pleasure?
- Well, we just wanted
to welcome you to the free world, John,
make sure you didn't stumble on your first day out.
- I'm totally rehabilitated.
My self awareness is in the green.
I'm a self actualized vanilla sundae
with a whole bunch of new skills.
- What kind of new skills?
- I can shower with my back against the wall
and pick up wet soap with my toes.
- Hopefully, out here you won't need those skills.
- Bob says that his life has been threatened.
You know anything about that?
- Bob, I bear you no ill will, even though you maxed me out.
I think the years I spent in this prison
has forged my personality,
made a whole new person out of me.
And that person respects the law
and yearns to contribute to society.
- Well, that certainly makes all the years I spent
on the bench seem worthwhile.
- And they were worthwhile, Bobby,
They were years spent allocating justice.
I respect that.
I respect that with my entire being.
(Bob laughs)
Well, hey, I have a business appointment downtown.
And if you guys would be kind enough to give me a lift and--
- A business appointment, in that suit?
- Hell, why not?
I wouldn't let him sit behind me, Bobby.
- Jeez, out only a few minutes ago
and already gainfully employed.
- I hope that makes you feel proud, doesn't it, Bobby?
- Beyond proud, I'm orgasmic.
(instrumental music)
- Pink, huh?
- Thank you, gentlemen.
It's been grand.
Seems like ages, doesn't it?
- But then again, it was a long sentence, Bob.
- But you've weathered it with great style, Johnny.
I'm proud of you.
- And I'm proud of both of you.
I mean, still smiling after being kicked out of your job
by an ungrateful system just because you're over 60.
- That's one of the nice benefits of a life of crime,
no forced retirement.
- Well, I've got to go, Chance, Bob.
It's been a groove in the gas
- Another minute and I was gonna need an insulin shot.
- What a yellow piece of phlegm. (laughter)
Come on, I wanna go check out
this so called business meeting.
- I was going to take you to lunch, Bob.
- Chance, this grunge has pushed my numbers up 40 points.
- It's your blood pressure.
- A job?
A job, Chance.
What kind of job do you think this hair bags got?
He's probably selling robots to veterans.
(laughter)
So you didn't notice him, huh?
- As I recall, John always named his bogus companies
with letters, like his real estate company was LMA,
Land Management Associates, right?
- Yeah, the swamp land deal.
- Here's PBL Inc, that sounds like John, doesn't it?
- That's probably him, let's go.
- Bob, do you mind if I take him first?
I don't wanna get stuck getting you CPR.
- I wasn't ready to take the elevator.
- Calm down, Don, calm down.
- He's in there.
- Don, the check is in the mail.
- Hey, I am not a nonprofit comedian.
I work for cash, Bucky, you understand.
Now, you pay me or I don't do the gig in Naples.
I mean it.
- Gentlemen.
- Satisfied employee?
- No, just a little screw up.
Johnny, you got quite a layout here.
Yes, sir, quite a layout.
Of course, I don't know about that,
turquoise and black outfit, sort of makes you
look like a molting peacock.
- Kind of a funky chic look, huh?
- What do we have here?
- Welcome to PBL Inc.
- Let me guess, psycho babble limit.
Police Benefit League.
Yes, we've been running the business now,
for what, two years?
- From inside prison?
- Well, it's been part of my rehabilitation.
- Who, I hesitate to ask,
does a police benefit league benefit?
- It benefits the police, I would imagine, don't you, Bob?
- Well, even more than that, it benefits the widows
and orphans of slain police officer.
As we give benefits with celebrity performers.
- Like who for instance?
- Listen, I hate like hell to have to ask you to varnish
but Florence and I have to go over a lot of things.
After all, it has been seven years, men.
- Oh, well, again, my ears are red with embarrassment.
- Bob, I think we should just let John here
get back to his charitable work.
(instrumental music)
- Trouble.
- Widows, orphans, what's next?
A blind man and a tin cup?
I'm gonna nominate this guy for prison home coming queen.
- Bob, Bob, now just calm down.
Just calm down.
Mow take a deep breath, and go,
ooh.
Just feel into it,
- This guy doesn't drive you nuts?
- Of course, he does, Bob.
But I'm not gonna get a coronary over it.
Ooh,
come on.
- Ooh.
- Oh, come on.
- Bob, there is a way to slow him down.
- How's that?
- Hello.
Hello.
- How's that?
- Well, you're still an officer of the court, right?
- Yeah, I'm on the roster as a rent a judge.
- Rent a judge?
- That means that I can rent myself as a judge
to whoever wants to shorten their time
on the court calendar.
- Well, why don't you contact his parole board
and get John Dolan assigned to you?
You be his parole agent, that way, you can hold his leash.
- Hey, that's pretty straight thinking on your part.
- I can't help you with that.
- Come on, I know that.
(instrumental music)
(car screeches)
(upbeat music)
(gun shots)
- That couldn't have been Dolan, could it?
I don't know if I'm gonna press charges
for this drive by shooting, Mr. Dolan
But you got a lot of monikers, Paper Collar John,
What's that mean?
- Well, in the late 30s, early 40s
when I first started grifting, I was 13.
the men wore clip on paper collars.
And it was said that I could change personalities
quicker than a paper collar, a supreme compliment.
Of course, I've been totally rehabilitated since then,
due to the psychiatric benefits of our prison system,
- Well, this is some record.
- To deceive is to enchant, Ms Henry.
- What a charming insight.
- Is there anything else, Ms. Henry?
- Can you believe this?
Now he's quoting Plato.
Next thing you know, she'll be taking him out
for a poetry reading.
He's laughing at us.
He knows we're back here.
- Will you just take another pill?
You got me worried.
I don't know, why don't we just put an end
into this legal exercise?
He's got an alibi.
We both know he's not a shooter.
- Yeah, are these ADA's getting younger?
This girl looks like she should be conducting
the interview with pom poms.
- Well, it's the new America.
You gotta get used to it, Bob.
Everybody looks like they're under 30. (laughter)
Excuse me, miss.
We've decided that it's not him.
So John, why don't you just pick up your stuff at the desk?
We'll give you a lift home.
We'll meet you outside.
- Gentlemen, you show wisdom almost beyond your years.
And Miss Henry, you've made a difficult situation
into a delightful interlude.
- I'll show you out.
- Well, maybe we gotta look at another possibility.
If that wasn't John, after you,
then maybe those shots were meant for me.
Now, Hector called me, left a message.
He said that he'd found Evan Long.
And somebody took Hector down, took him down hard.
Probably Evan, maybe he's got me linked in somehow.
- My doctor says I should avoid stress.
I bet this qualifies as stress.
- The Hernandez family, I owe them.
There're two of them dead.
I just, I feel responsible.
I don't know.
I just don't trust myself the way I used to.
I'm loosing top skill, I can't remember things.
I make lists and then forget where I put them.
- How's your blood pressure?
- Well, it's good.
- You sure?
- Yeah,
I can't eat sauces and strawberries
because of my diverticulitis.
Every time it flares up,
the doctor says I gotta go to the Gerber's.
I'm spooning down cream cone and applesauce.
Now, how's a guy on baby food,
gonna find a bastard like Evan Long?
Bob, I need your help, but I'm worried about you.
- Yeah, well, we're a couple of sad old ducks, ain't we?
- Is it just me?
Are you two guys trying to ruin my first day out?
- It's gonna get better, Johnny.
I made a call about an hour ago.
And guess what?
- You finally won the lottery.
- Better.
Your parole office wants you to have a new parole agent.
Wanna guess who got the button?
- Why do I get the feeling it's you, Bobby?
- 'Cause it is, Johnny.
I figured that you could start
by explaining this widows and orphans thing to me.
- Come on, fellas, it's been a long day.
John, why don't Bob and I take you
to the dog track over at TJ?
We go every Saturday and since Bob is your parole agent,
he can approve it.
Give everybody a chance to cool down there.
- Dog racing?
You guys go dog racing.
- Yeah.
- Below normal.
- What is that?
- This is a thing that measures your blood pressure.
- Let me have that.
I think mine's gone up a bit.
- Mr. Glass, JoJo Golina, assistant US Attorney.
It's nice to meet you.
How was your trip from Washington?
- This is one screwed to hell scenario you've got here.
I understand you even had a tip and booted it.
Who fumbled it?
- Well sir, it was on my watch so I guess I did.
- What was your name again?
Somebody write this down.
- Am I getting demerits?
- Just give me the name, lady.
Save the flip remarks for the yo-yos and happy hour.
- Okay, am I right or what?
- I'm Angus Glass, senior investigator with Justice GS 13.
And I'm here to kick butt.
You people have leprosy, I'm the leprosy doctor.
The only way you're gonna leave this leper colony
is by producing.
Are we straight so far, people?
Any questions?
- Sir, we're assuming this robbery
was not to steal milk products.
What was actually in that container?
Was it federal payroll?
- Any other questions or comments?
This case is a career wrecker.
If it gets booted there'll be massive collateral damage.
I will not be affected by its failure
because in failure, I will waste all of you.
- Aktung! Aktung!
We will now work on getting rid of our aggressions.
I want you to take your nerf balls and throw them
as hard as you can at the cut out of the evil Professor
On three.
And remember, no throwing the blocks.
(in foreign language) three.
That was great.
That's terrific, dud.
See, that's why we're all here to share our feelings.
Now since it's almost lunchtime,
I want us to take out our lunches.
We'll sit back in our seats
and then we're gonna play famous Americans.
Everybody think of some famous American that they admire.
- Hannibal Lecter.
- Let's think of famous non-cannibals.
Okay, give me some more names now
and I'll put them up on the board.
(guitar beat music)
- I didn't do it, he did.
- Hey Chancey, how you been?
- Fairer than ever.
You getting combat pay, no?
- Look, class will be over in a few.
You stay right here, I'll catch up.
Deviled ham, I'd have probably thrown it out too.
(instrumental music)
- Career day, that's interesting.
What is it?
- Well, for instance, this kid wants to be a hangman.
Mr. Career advice, at 100 year.
But maybe with a little bit of counseling,
we could convince him to be a dental surgeon.
- I can't believe the best criminal profiler in the US
and you're ducking deviled ham sandwiches.
- These kids have such low self images,
someone's gotta try and help them.
- Moch, I could use little help myself.
There's an autopsy tonight at six o'clock.
I'd like to get in and witness it.
And also, I need you to start a criminal profile for me.
- Criminal profile.
Wow, I sure miss that field.
One of those 15 open cases maybe?
- Yeah, it's Hector Hernandez, Sharon's dad.
And if you come up dry, I won't throw a sandwich at you.
- And I want you to meet someone.
Hi, honey.
- Hi.
- Honey, This is Chance Wayne, longtime good friend.
My assistant Heather Loquat.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Ma'am.
- Come, come, let's go, let's go.
- What exactly did she assist you in, Moch?
Everything you can think of.
- Stop bragging.
Autopsy is at six,
at the morgue.
I'm missing a beat somewhere.
- I will pay you half of what you're asking.
Your initial figure was ridiculous.
- Well, I'm afraid that my deal is non negotiable.
The package gets into Somalia with the food in two days.
There's no end user problems.
You got total flexibility.
It's too good a deal to pass up there, Dieter.
I'm taking all the risk
and the theft to make down the delivery.
One more thing,
I didn't come here to haggle with you.
You know what I mean?
- Okay,
deal.
- Good.
I'll call you two hours before we leave.
I want you to get some expendable labor.
You gotta get the package out of the valley.
I'm gonna start sealing up some of the loose ends.
That's too bad that we missed Chance Wayne the other night.
We're not gonna get a better chance.
Get that nasty little thread still hanging over at DWP.
We're gonna have to use him up.
- You got it, chief.
(instrumental music)
- Hey, where are you going?
(upbeat music)
Go run a big Power Plant in the sky.
Let's go.
(upbeat music)
(car screeches)
- So how long has the coronary lab on four?
I've been wandering around on two for 20 minutes.
- It's always been on four.
- Don't tarnish your legend, Chance.
Ed Hagman.
- Thanks for letting us ride the jumpsuit.
- Hey, no problem, Mr. Wayne.
What is it you're looking for?
- Won't know until we see.
- Chance, I wanna start with victimology.
- Borrow your glasses, I left mine at the motel.
Thanks.
Whoa, what are these?
- Fours.
- I use threes.
We're gonna study the victims habits.
Maybe we'll find out something about the killer.
Example, what did he do for a living?
- Commercial fisherman.
- Smell this, what do you think?
- Has chemicals of some kind.
Pretty strong, seawater didn't wash it out.
- Ed, you run me a lab analysis on this shirt, please.
Find out all you can.
- Yeah, sure.
- Now people make thousands of choices every day.
Why did Hector choose these clothes?
Everything's tan.
Tan shirt, tan jacket, tan pants.
- So, maybe he didn't wanna be seen.
Maybe he was in a field, something, trying to blend in.
- You have a swear knack for this courvoisier
You come here often?
- Too long.
Now the smell in his clothes could be photography fixer.
- Well, you were right about petechial hemorrhaging, Chance.
Definitely a post-mortem knife wound.
Looks like he got him from behind,
incision, lower right upper left.
- Left-handed cut.
- Let's work on a left-handed profile.
- Why would he strangle him and then cut his throat?
- Cut him to bleed him out.
- Well, maybe he wanted to move him.
And if that was his reason, could be a pro.
- Hagman, hi.
- I told you to get the hell off this case.
What are you doing here?
- Ignoring the advice.
It's not advice, it's an order.
Find a bench someplace and watch pigeons.
- I got a life improvement tip for you, Mr. Cavanaugh.
You're gonna see a whole lot better
if you remove them shades inside at night.
- Well, let me give you a little tip, all right--
- Hey, Cam, Cam, shut up.
We came here to get the results of the autopsy.
- It's getting crowded in here, Moch.
Let's mosey.
- Hagman, what do you know about that guy?
- Well, the cowboy's only about the best law man
this county ever had.
Name's Chance Wayne
- I'm impressed.
- Well, only 15 cases got by him.
And rumor has it, that he's got permission from the sheriff
to work them in his retirement, never forgot a fact.
- Wow.
Well, what about the other guy?
- Dr. Akira Mochizuki.
Did all the criminal profiling
till he hit 65 and had to retire.
I'll tell you what, between those two guys
and judge Maximum Bob Smith,
they're about the best this county ever had.
- Big deal.
- Thanks.
- Cam, get the results and call me in the morning.
(instrumental music)
- Mr. Wayne.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Hi, I just found out who you are.
Mr Hagman says that you never forgot a fact
What's wrong?
- Well, I can't remember where I parked my car.
I thought I parked it over there by the service road
but it's not there.
- The pink caddy that I saw you in yesterday morning?
- Yeah.
- Is that it over there right across the street?
- I don't know where...
- It's all right.
That happens to everyone.
- Well, it never used to happen to me.
It's very nice seeing you again, Miss...
Golina.
- Golina, yeah, that's it.
I knew it started with a G.
- You're on the list.
I won't forget it now.
Unless I lose my list.
Ma'am.
(instrumental music)
Arnold, thanks for including me in the squeal.
- You bet, Chance.
Sharon Hernandez is still on the board
with your name under it.
- Yeah.
- This is her dad's car.
Homicide have been notified.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Moch forgot to give me back my new glasses.
Let's make these do.
- Search path right over here, Chance.
Nobody used this door, lock's down
- Pretty soon you're gonna start showing up
on my nightmares, pop.
- Agent Cavanaugh, we had a crime path around the back there
so that nobody would go contaminating the crime scene.
Now, I hate to complain,
but you're putting your fingerprints
all over the steering wheel.
- What crime scene?
I don't see a body.
- We're pretty sure that this red goop
you're standing in, ain't taco sauce.
- Who's this, Doctor Watson?
- That's Judge Smith.
He's about to take your shoes.
- You wish.
- Agent Cavanaugh, we got a train of evidence problem here.
Now, you stood in the blood.
In court, we gotta prove that that's your footprint
and not the killer's.
I'm afraid we're gonna have to log
them loafers in as evidence.
Hope they didn't cost too much.
Arnie, help agent Cavanaugh with his loafers, please.
- Don't try it, smokey.
- Hey, Bob, look here.
- I'll take that.
This is still a federal case.
- Judge, I think you better give this boy
another curbside ruling.
- This appears to be the original site
of the Hernandez killing.
This car is parked in county territory,
giving the sheriff's department
jurisdiction in the entire case.
- Now that we have established our jurisdiction,
I'm not going to say this twice, Mr. Cavanaugh,
give me your shoes and that camera and then just step back
because now you're in my crime scene.
- This is a federal case, okay?
It's tied into a federal train robbery.
- What train robbery?
- Shut up, Bruno.
- Nothing.
- In that case, Arnold get the camera,
and investigator Cavanaugh's shoes
and then show these boys the gate.
(instrumental music)
- Stinks.
- Predictable as flies on garbage.
These boys couldn't catch a cold in December.
- I'm gonna get a federal restraining order on you two.
Now, give us that camera.
- Bob, I think you better quote this twit some more scripts.
- Can't keep us out, got legal precedent.
Jonathan Lewis versus the US government, 1984.
In this case, Jonathan Lewis, a milkman was arrested
for passing into a federal stakeout and held for 18 hours
in a federal office building without being charged.
The US District Court of Maryland found that this
was an irrational act, and that the US government
was guilty of overstepping the boundaries
of its authority over its citizens.
- Big deal.
(laughter)
- I never heard of that case.
- Made it up.
Had trouble getting the camera open.
- You did get the film?
(instrumental music)
- It's a good thing or I'd had your butt.
(upbeat music)
(knock on door)
Coming.
Yeah.
- We need to talk
- Well, come in, miss...
Come in, come in.
It's pretty damn breathtaking, ain't it?
You want my decorators name?
- It'd be better if you straightened up a little.
- I have enough trouble remembering
where I put things as it is.
- What do you shoot with that?
- When I was a boy,
my dad taught me shooting with that rifle.
He said he could pick a flower off buffaloes nose
at a that thousand yards.
I guess maybe he could.
Well,
Ms. Golina, what can I do for you?
- I want the film.
- I think maybe you better sit.
Your investigators Cavanaugh and Bruno,
they took the camera.
- Well,
when they got to the office, that camera was empty.
- Lot of disappointment in law enforcement.
- That's rich.
- Water?
- Mr. Wayne,
I'm in some career trouble.
I don't wanna bore you with the particulars,
but we got a federal gunslinger in from Washington,
a GS 13 named Angus Glass.
And
basically, he's about to ice my career.
- Are we talking about Hector Hernandez murder?
Or are we talking about federal train robbery?
- What do you mean. there isn't any federal train robbery?
- I may not be able to digest fried food,
but I could still digest facts.
- Such as?
- Such as, they don't send GS 13s down from DC
to supervise the murder of a Mexican fisherman.
And such as I haven't had an 8 a.m house call
from an assistant US Attorney
in 45 years of law enforcement.
And such as Cavanaugh and Bruno wouldn't be running around
like a couple of castrated hamsters,
just because Hernandez got murdered.
And for your information, your boy Bruno
spilled the beans about that federal train robbery.
Excuse me.
- I lost it.
- Now, I looked up Hernandez in the state police records.
His daughter Sharon was killed seven years ago
while attending Pacific Southwest University.
You got the case, you made the arrest
of a grad student named Evan Long.
But the file says, he was immediately turned over
to the federal government because of national security.
- And the feds waltzed him right out of my jail.
There was nothing I could do.
- You interest me, you and Judge Smith and Mochizuki.
You guys are law enforcement legends.
- Is there something specific that you want, Ms. Golina?
- The short tell is
I would rather work with you guys
than with Bruno and Cavanaugh.
They don't know what the hell's going on.
These GS 6's rotated out every 18 months.
They have no street sources.
They don't even know how to find
the address of a crime scene.
- We're going to take John Dolan
to the dog races across the border.
It's a combination apology and parole meeting.
Why don't you come along?
You can see this bunch of law enforcement legends firsthand.
- [Announcer] Here comes the rabbit.
And they're off.
Out of the box of down the front stretch, it's number eight.
Jungle Jim with number three.
- Johnny, I don't wanna spoil your appetite,
but I got a list of PBL benefits thrown last year.
You guys threw one in Del.
The only thing is I can't find a license for you
to do business in North Carolina.
- Well, at least you'll have something to go to bed with.
- You bet.
- Thank you.
- What are you eating, french fries now?
- No, these are for JoJo.
You know I don't eat anything fried and all.
- The wheel chair competition begin.
Listen, Bob, since we're talking
about the finer points in PBL, I've been in contact
with Sheriff Elmer Whitaker about having a do
right here in San Diego.
- So what are you telling me for?
- He said that since you're my parole officer,
if you said yes, he'd sign off on it.
- I figure I'll say yes, about at the same time
Palm Beach gets a black mayor.
- You are a cynical man.
Now, see, the idea is, I wanna present Chance
with the Eliot Ness law enforcement merits award
right there at the banquet, brass plaque,
newspaper reporters, the whole thing.
- How do you think of all this stuff?
- I wanna honor Chance for a lifetime
of busting felons, man.
- Well, you're a felon, why don't you to a testimonial?
- He won't have to
'cause I don't wanna be a part of his scam.
- Oh, gee, that's too bad, Chance.
Because there's a cash and dime
that goes with the Ness award.
(laughter)
- $10,000.
(instrumental music)
- All right, no matter.
Just remember you were my first choice.
Number five, number five,
yes!
Woo hoo, big bad John wins again. (laughs)
- No five.
No five.
- You didn't get our bet down, did you?
- Yep, just before they closed.
- Thanks a lot.
- We're gonna stick to lotto, boys.
- What, losers again?
How many nacho, Bob?
- Get outta there, Johnny.
- Chance, you got three tacos.
- They got plenty of them out there, John.
- John, you can share my french fries.
- You are a darling.
- Don't feed the animals, JoJo.
- You know I really could help you guys.
That fives, five now that's the trip.
- You're hunch better.
I thought you were slicker than that.
- I'm cashing my tickets in and you turn yours up.
- Hey, Bobby, what you taking there?
- Well, these are Vasotec, that's Lenoltec,
high blood pressure.
And this little red doohickey here,
I got from the health food store and that helps me poop.
- Really? - Really.
- Can I try some of those?
- Sure, take a few for the weekend.
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah. What is that, Chance?
- Well, this white one is for my diverticulitis
and these two little blue ones is for my arthritic knee.
You remember that brawl back in '56, John?
The first time that I busted you for running a boiler room
and I blew my knee out chasing you.
- It wasn't one of my finer operations.
- Why don't you give me one of them blue ones?
My elbows been killing me.
- Oh, yeah. won't hurt anything.
They're not prescription.
- What is that, Moch?
- These are synthetic rejuvenators
that I'm testing for the FDA.
Is that what cocks the hammer in your pistol?
- Let me try one of those. - How quick do they work?
- Fellows, strictly for experimental use right now, sorry.
- You guys are really a laugh.
Here you are exchanging medicine like a bunch of old ladies,
afraid to eat fried foods,
you've got to learn to live a little, come on.
- You keep eating those french fries,
you're gonna need a bypass.
- Amen.
- And now, I'm gonna go cash in.
- [Announcer] And they're coming around the final turn.
It's number five in the lead, number three is second,
with number one going ahead at the finish.
Number five is the winner.
- Can you believe that I'm having?
Forget about that puppy.
50 bucks on the nose.
Well, how are you doing, Bob?
- You bet fine.
- You keep it up, John.
Your parole evaluation hearing
is gonna come up between races
- [Announcer] and number three take 380 to show.
Get your bets down--
- Cash in, again.
- Trust, right?
Go ahead.
- I wanna know about that train robbery.
- It was federal payroll.
They were shipping in a dairy container
and it was lifted off by a helicopter.
- There are your train robbers, gang.
- I know this guy.
- You do?
- Yeah, Hollis.
Hollis something, I don't know.
He was in with me, a short timer.
Hard case, get down robber
You know anybody that knows him so we can get a line on him?
Yeah, I'll have a look around
if you reconsider the PBL awards banquet.
- Here we go again, guys.
- Okay, I'll reconsider, I'll think about it.
But you work both sides of the street,
and you'll drop an envelope.
- I'm thrilled, Chance.
I am really thrilled.
- I'm fibrillating.
- Fives, Bob.
$5,000. (laughs)
(instrumental music)
(upbeat music)
- Look at these idiots.
They're gonna end up glowing in the dark.
(upbeat music)
- (in foreign language)
- Thank you, Rich.
Michelle.
- Yes.
- Listen, when I ask for change,
would you be so kind as to bring me this bill?
- Okay.
- I'll be sitting right over there with three other guys.
- All right, great.
- Thank you, Michelle.
- You're welcome.
- He said he found the guy?
- That's what he said.
(guitar beat music)
- You guys remind me of a bowling team.
Don't you ever go around with women?
- You said he was here, where is he?
- He's just going over to the bar now.
Guy in the leather jacket.
His name is Hollis Davis according to the bartender.
I walked by him three times, he didn't recognize me.
- Well, I say we sit on him see where he goes.
- Oh, by the way, Bob, they sell
lottery tickets over at the bar.
And since you go for those sucker bets,
I thought maybe you'd like to buy one.
Just remember to ask for lots of fives.
- Why buy fives?
- Don't humor him, Bob, he's screwing with us.
- You mean, why is five a better number?
Is that the question? (laughs)
That's unbelievable.
- Why, pray tell, is a five a better number
than anything else?
- Bob, just let it be, okay.
- Because Bobby, the number five appears
most frequently in any random selection of numbers.
It has been scientifically proven.
Everybody in the planet knows it, except I guess you guys.
- You wanna bet?
- Oh, come on, man.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
You think I'm born under a mushroom somewhere, I see.
Let's go.
I bet $50.
- Okay.
- How can you prove it?
- We'll use the serial numbers on this bill.
- Oh, no, no.
- Oh get real, doofus, we're not using your bill.
- Miss, would you bring me a change for a 10, please?
Five and some ones.
Okay, does that make you feel better now?
- It certainly does.
- All right. Now, I say there's more fives
on this bill than any other number.
- We're talking only serial number.
- Only serial number.
- I got in.
- I got in the little bet myself.
- I'll cover you.
Read them and weep.
(game show music)
(guitar beat)
- What? - What?
- There are four fives on this bill.
- Get out of here.
How did you do that?
- Simple mathematics
and the random choice probability groove.
(instrumental music)
I think your boy is leaving now.
Good luck.
- Oh, come on, you're going with me.
- Why do I have to go with you guys?
- I'm your parole officer, sir.
And you, my dear man,
are in flagrant violation of your parole.
- For what?
- Gambling in an establishment that serves liquor.
And besides, you're loaded with the evidence.
This is a bust.
- Bad Bob Smith.
(instrumental music)
- Moch, give me the pictures.
- Right
- This keeps getting better.
Let's go
- I'm on point, let me go first.
You cover me.
I'll keep John with me.
- Fine.
- How are you gonna protect me with that?
I'm going to get hooker real quick.
- Bob, you better use this.
- I don't think I should be here.
(upbeat music)
- That's Hector's boat.
He took me out on it once.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
(instrumental music)
(gun shots)
(upbeat music)
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, how can you ask me that?
I'm leaking like a bag of sand.
(gun shots)
- Hey Chance, give me one of them guns, man.
Come on, Chancey, they're getting away.
- Yeah, Chance, do it.
- Well, you are his parole officer.
Let's go.
(gun shots)
- This gun is a labyrinth shell.
- You're pulling right.
You gotta aim low and fire slow.
- Listen, I didn't see you hit anything out there, Chance.
Maybe you should have worn your glasses.
- Is he all right?
- He'll be all right.
It went clean through.
- You used to shoot the 900.
Didn't get a shot off.
- Hey, you were always the first one through the door, punk.
You're the best.
- Are you two guys bonding?
You are bonding, aren't you?
That's beautiful.
That's real beautiful.
- My
blood pressure is
going down.
Does that mean anything?
- Get him to the hospital, Moch.
I wanna see what they were after on the boat.
- All right, now.
(instrumental music)
- Thanks for the backup, John.
- I didn't hit anything.
I never could shoot straight.
- Nobody would expect you to, you're a conman.
It's the thought that counts. (laughter)
(instrumental music)
Here's where he developed the pictures.
Maybe there's some negatives or prints around.
- You know all of those pistolocos in the prison
used to hide their valuables behind a picture of Jesus.
You got here.
- Evan Long.
Hector did find him.
That's why he called me, I knew it
- That looks like the nuclear power plant at San Onofre.
- Yeah, nuclear power plant.
Somebody's estate.
What the hell's going on?
Let's get out of here.
- You bet it, let's go.
- Well, Mr. Cavanaugh, we seem to be on the same schedule.
- Well, that's gonna change.
- Ms. Golina, you're relieved of your duties
and on suspension.
- Under what section and clause?
- I'll think of something,
start with disobeying a direct order.
Agent Cavanaugh, put Ms. Golina under arrest.
- Cam, you lay a hand on me,
and I'll file false arrest charges against you.
- Let's lighten up, fellows.
Moch.
You see we have a protective feeling for this lady.
- Arrest her Agent Cavanaugh, that's an order.
- Wait right here, just a second
- Elmer, we've got a problem.
- I'm Elmer Whitaker, sheriff of San Diego County,
something we can do for you, sir?
- I'm Angus Glass GS 13.
- We've got a problem
with the federal government here, Mr. Glass?
- It's way over your head.
This cadaver is part of a federal investigation.
- Well, then you got a federal case number.
It's a C number, classified.
- Unless you can give me a case number
or a damn good reason why I should think otherwise,
I'll have to ask you and your investigator
to vacate these premises while my coroner
completes his examination, Mr. Glass.
- Have an apple, Mr. Glass
- Right-handed, too bad.
- I better go deal with this.
Can you give me a lift?
- You bet.
- Chance, this guy can't be Chilly Delgado,
even though his prints and his dental say he is.
- How's that?
- Well, his background file says Chilly Delgado
was in an institution for alcoholism '85 to '87.
During that time his kidneys shut down
and they had to remove one.
Someone's been screwing with the NCI computer
because this guy has still got both of his.
- Hey, Chance, you got a minute?
- This fella John Dolan called me like you suggested.
- Like I suggested?
- Yeah, he threw a shindigs at the college auditorium.
He sells seats for 10 bucks, raises money
for widows and orphans of dead police, sheriffs, deputies.
He wants to give Bob,
Thurgood Marshall Jurist of the Year Award.
Pretty great honor, don't you think?
- Yeah.
- With $10,000 cash prize.
- Let me ask you this.
Ms. Golina, how many seats do you figure's
in that college auditorium?
- Well, without counting I'd say about 600.
- 600 to $10 a ticket, that's $6,000.
- Yes. And we get half of that
for the widows and orphans by contract.
- Okay, 3,000.
Now of the $3,000 that's left, Bob gets 10?
I don't know much about throwing benefits,
but something stinks here, I can tell you that.
- I never thought of that.
You're right, I'll tell him No.
- You don't like John very much do you?
- Well, honey, I've been trying for 15 years
not to like him, but I just can't help myself.
John Dolan's not an easy man to dislike,
maybe that's why he's such a good
hustler.
(upbeat music)
(instrumental music)
- You got the job done?
- The nuclear power rods are at the bottom of the pool.
- Yeah, borrowed CIA duty station.
This place sure brings back some memories.
Man, we sure had some good times back then, didn't we?
It sure was a good life
til you decided to hit the chicken switch.
- You dated innocent co-eds
and killed them for kicks, like Sharon Hernandez.
You were hitting a lot of soft targets back then, Evan.
- I don't need a high culatta,
not from a guy who's selling out his country
to a bunch of terrorists
'Cause the agency is cutting back and he's out.
- We need to get the merchandise
out of San Diego by this time tomorrow.
Take care of these people before you go.
- I'll do this first guy, Chance Wayne, just for fun.
He's on my unfinished business list.
But these other two, I don't know, why them?
- They're retired cops.
But they're a lot sharper than the guys I've got.
If we leave them on the board, they'll figure it out.
- There's always a need for covert ops.
Sometimes I think the reason I was put on this earth
was to float the guys that figured out what you were up to.
(instrumental music)
- I'm sorry, Ann, I didn't mean to get him hurt.
- You two, you're like old greyhounds at the dog track.
Here comes the rabbit, you've gotta run.
It's in your blood.
(door bell rings)
Hi, Moch.
- Hi Annie.
Meet JoJo Golina, assistant US Attorney.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
- Is Bob away?
- He's in the living room taking his blood pressure,
what's left to measure.
Come on in. - After you.
- Judge, how are you feeling?
- I don't know whether to root for this to go up or down.
Have a seat, Ms. Golina.
- Bob, we've got a big hit off the Federal computer guys.
The blade to take down Hector was a linoleum knife.
Now, there were killings in five other places
where the victim was taken down from behind
with a linoleum knife.
- You check on those towns military bases?
- Yeah, CIA has duty stations at each of those towns.
I'm beginning to think our killer
is some government nutcase.
- The duty station in San Diego, where is it?
- It used to be on the Pacific Southwest University campus,
but they closed now for a couple of years.
- Use your phone, Bob?
- Yeah, go ahead. - Thank you.
- How about this guy, Jim Cross?
They found him dead this morning.
You showed me a picture of him with Evan Long.
Now he's got to fit in somewhere.
- Yeah. And here's another unanswered question.
What was really in that dairy container?
- I'm certain It was a federal payroll.
They ship federal receipts by rail all the time.
- I don't think so, my gut says that's wrong.
This doesn't make any sense.
I just wish the hell, we knew where this house was.
Maybe we can rent a helicopter and look for it from the air.
- I gotta run to the county jail, guys
where they're holding this serial rapist
for me to interview.
See I've been working on this paper
and they're gonna transfer him in the morning.
So somebody give me ride.
- We're on our way.
Hope you feel better, Bobby.
- Here comes a rabbit.
(instrumental music)
Sweetheart, I... they...
I'll be all right.
- Greyhounds.
- Hi. - Hello, there.
- I'm Dr. Mochizuki.
I'm here to interview,
prisoner 36892.
- We have a problem in the holding cell.
I called one of ours but I'm afraid it maybe too late.
I'm a psychiatrist.
We do have to go through medical school.
Maybe I could just look at him for you.
- That'd be great.
I don't know what I would do if you hadn't come.
- Do you always wear high heels?
- You're cute.
- I know.
- At first, I just thought he was drunk.
He was running a fever.
Excuse me, fellas.
His name is Jesus.
- Ola, Jesus.
- What do you think it is?
- You get this man an ambulance,
radiation therapy right to the hospital
and you alert the hospital that he's coming.
Where did you get these burns?
(instrumental music)
Whatever was in there is radioactive.
- Let's put this together radioactive material,
Jim Cross, from water and power, Evan Long and Hector.
- Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
A nuclear power plant at San Onofre has a breeder reactor.
- Right, and Evan Long is a spy.
Now ,he could be selling it to a terrorist or to any country
that was trying to develop a nuclear weapons program.
Did Jesus say where the house was
where they dropped the canister?
- Rancho la Loma, house at the top of the hill.
- Let's go.
- That's it.
So what you got?
- I love it, I love it.
I'm on parole, you asked me to commit a felony trespass?
No, thank you, no, way to go, John.
Just
what you got?
- If you want an award just give yourself one.
Are we gonna get in or not?
- Hey, hey, hey,
that's another bone I gotta pick with you guys.
Elmer says he's not gonna let me have that benefit
unless you guys have a change of heart.
What's that?
Have you ever looked an orphan in the eye, Chance
and had to say, no?
- Man, you are really tough ride?
Just tell me, can we get in without setting off alarms?
- Not unless you got wings, brother.
Security is really tight.
I couldn't get close to the pool.
The heater to the pool was turned off though.
Laser trap set everywhere, ardent resonant cameras.
It's definitely a go next door as.
- John, you're talking real current stuff there.
- The past year my cellmate was
a very hip jewel thief.
And we did have a lot of time to talk.
- Bob, too much, Moch was right.
You and JoJo better go so on move fast.
They shut off the heater to the pool
and that's probably where it's at.
And bring Sheriff Elmer Whitaker with you, thanks.
- What's in the pool?
And what's going on here, Chance?
Hey, I wanna go home, man.
- Eat a sandwich.
- Cucumber on whole wheat.
Man, you really don't want to live, don't you?
- We're talking seven grain, John.
- All right.
- I think I'll stay here.
My hand shakes when I see people get arrested.
Nobody invited you.
What is he doing?
- Had him case the place.
- Chance, your memory is worse than I thought.
Have you forgotten this guy steals?
- We got company, front gate.
What is it?
- Sheriff's office, we'd like to come in.
You mind opening this gate?
- Sorry.
- We got us a warrant, now open the gate.
- Gentlemen.
Ma'am.
- Nice to see you again, Mr. Long.
- I don't think I know you.
- Is that Evan Long?
- Sure is.
- Mr. Long, you're under arrest.
That's a federal warrant.
- Mi casa su casa.
Open the gate.
Come on in folks.
- I'll take that.
- Hands behind your back.
- Let's check the pool.
- Move.
- This is a case of mistaken identity.
My name is not Evan Long,
it's Charles Watkins.
- We'll deal with that downtown once we check your prints.
- What is it you think you're gonna find back here?
- Canisters with used power rod center
from the water and power company.
That's what stole you stole-- (Evan laughs)
- That's one vivid imagination you got there, sir.
- That canister's gotta be cracked,
this whole area's hot.
There it is.
Guys, this stuff is nuclear grade plutonium.
You could make a nuclear weapon out of it.
- Hold it right there, put your hands up.
Throw your weapons into the pool.
(gun shot)
- Come on, get my cuffs off.
- It's not a suggestion drop them.
- Guess we know why you came down from Washington
now, don't we, Mr. Glass?
- Take Ms. Golina put her out in the van
with the rest of them.
- Get up, come on, get up!
Get going, come on, move.
- I hate to think my life's come down
to whether John Dolan's paying attention.
(instrumental music)
- Damn.
- I hate this.
Way out of character, John.
(instrumental music)
- You guys are the insurance policy,
anything goes wrong in a light you up.
- Well, this is not working out the way I planned.
- Well, it's been an hour.
We're in deep soup here.
I'm sorry, fellows.
Maybe the boy was right, maybe we should have
just found the bench somewhere.
- We really went down hard.
The old days we would have done a whole lot better.
- Who are you kidding?
In the old days, you would never that good.
I can get you out.
But first, you gotta tell Elmer down there,
it's okay for me to have my benefit
- Benefit?
You mean you're gonna sit there
and try to cut a deal with us.
- I'm trying to help out the widows and the orphans
and I'm being scrutinized for this by you two old fools
as if I was trying to sell Florida swamp land
or something, come on.
- Jonathan.
- Yes, Chancey.
- You get us out of here and I will not only see to it,
that you get your benefit,
but I'll agree to be the guest of honor.
I'm sorry, Chance but it's a little late for that now.
I already printed up the program.
Now we gotta get Bob to accept the Thurgood Marshall
distinguished jurist award.
- Bob accepts.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, I don't wanna be a part of that.
- Bob, you accept, let's go.
- Bob?
Now we're talking.
Here, Chance take this, don't ask me where I got it.
- Where'd you get it?
This was in my apartment.
- Let's not quibble over details.
Now, take this rope, tie it to that door over there,
with a knot that won't slip and get out of the way.
(instrumental music)
(upbeat music)
- Okay,
let's see what you got, baby.
(upbeat music)
(car screeches)
- Good afternoon, I'll take the piece
- Where they taking that canister?
- Answer.
- To the private airfield at the Naval Station.
It's a big press event, food drive for Somalia.
- Give me that piece, Chance.
I'll keep him covered.
- Thanks, John.
Those were under my bed.
- There's no commentary into your sex life
- You broke into my house.
- I'm pleading fifth on that.
Look at that, just like a John Ford movie.
- Excuse me, where's Mr. And Mrs. Burke?
I wanna interview them about the food drive.
- They're not here, Mr. Burke fell ill.
- What?
- Can you tell us more about it?
- Look, there's hungry children
who need this food, excuse me.
- Is that all you could--
Come on, let's keep it rolling.
They're loading, maybe get it of the plane taking off
- [Male Speaker] Tower, this is November four, six, one
Charlie Alpha, flight three for Somalia,
requesting clearance for immediate takeoff.
- [Male Speaker] One Charlie Alpha,
you're cleared via taxiway seven, two, runway one, five.
roger taxiing the runway one, five.
(plane roars)
- They must be using the food drive to smuggle
the nuclear power rods out of the country.
That's gotta be it.
(upbeat music)
- [Male Speaker] Tower one Charlie Alpha
request straight off departure from runway one, five.
- [Male Speaker] One Charlie Alpha standby.
(upbeat music)
- You're cleared for takeoff.
- [Male Speaker] One Charlie Alpha, roger.
- If it gets airborne, knock it down.
Aim for the engine.
- If we knock it down, we're gonna have
high grade plutonium all over the field.
- Yeah, this whole area is gonna be hot for 200 years.
(upbeat music)
- Moch, you got my glasses, these old ones seem like a hoot.
- Yeah.
(upbeat music)
(gun shot)
(tires screech)
(gun shots)
(upbeat music)
- Drop the gun.
You're under arrest for the murder
of Sharon and Hector Hernandez.
- What if I don't wanna be arrested old man?
- Then I'm gonna put you in another category.
(gun shots)
- Hold it.
Get your hands behind your back, get them back here.
- Chance.
Damn,
look at that.
- You okay?
- It hurts worse that I remember it.
(laughter)
(instrumental music)
- Think, that's the secret, think.
Use your head.
I wondered why the Siamese twins moved to London
till I realized probably that the other one
wanted to drive for a while.
Think, why would a Japanese kamikaze pilot
even bother to put on his helmet?
Think, you would never say to an older man,
no hard feelings.
You wouldn't say that.
- Not much of a turn out.
- Well, I don't want the money or the plaque.
I wanna know what this guy is up to.
I just can't figure it out.
Now, he gave $3,000 to Elmer
for the widows and orphans fund.
There's 16 people out there plus a few old friends.
How's he making money, I don't get it.
- Beats the hell out of me.
- Showtime, showtime.
Now just keep the speech short.
I like to keep things moving, okay?
- We wouldn't wanna bore those 20 people out there.
- Just remember, friend, when you go to court
in front of a jury, you are putting your faith in the hands
of 12 people who weren't smart enough
to get out of jury duty.
Thank you very much.
(audience applauds)
- Right now it's time to meet the man who is responsible
for putting all these great benefits together,
Mr. Jonathan Wingate Dolan.
(audience applauds)
- Thank you, thank you.
And now the highlight of the evening,
the Judge Thurgood Marshall Award for distinguished jurist,
goes to Judge Robert Smith retired.
Come out, judge get your check and your plaque
and say a few words.
(audience applauds)
- Make it brief, they're fading.
- How can you tell?
- Thanks.
(audience applauds)
- Great speech, Bob
A little short but just clogged with emotion.
- Right.
- [John] Thank you Judge, that was absolutely adequate.
And thank you, folks, for being with us.
That winds up our program and good night and God--
- Would you believe it, $10,000?
- I don't know, we can hope it bounces
and we can get him for hanging paper.
- It's not gonna bounce, I'm not that lucky.
Why don't you take it and
give it to the people it's intended for
Which is the children of dead policemen.
- Well, that's very noble of you, Bob.
But you still got your plaque.
(instrumental music)
Finally, got you some justice, Hernie.
Rest in peace.
(instrumental music)
What happened to my keys?
- There they are.
- I don't remember putting them there, now.
- Want these, you left them at the office last night.
- I did?
- If you hadn't left us watching the car, Chancey,
you'd probably misplaced it too. (laughs)
- Ah.
- What?
- I know how you do it.
I just figured it out.
- Do what?
Making money on those corny PBL benefits.
- Widows and the children get the money. Chance.
- You oversold the house.
- I oversold the house, it would have been a riot--
- No, no, no, no, no
no, riots, no, riots,
'cause nobody goes to a policeman's benefit, huh, Moch?
- Nobody.
- Bob?
- Well, me and the wife, we go every year.
- I'm talking about the average person, Bob.
They just buy the ticket, they throw them away.
And you could have sold 10,000 of them
and you still wouldn't have filled the house, huh?
- There is no law against that, is there?
- It isn't a question of the law, man.
It's a question of integrity, is nothing sacred?
What's next, wooden nickels?
(laughter)
(talking over each other)
- You guys gotta get a life, you know that?
(upbeat music)