[waves crashing]
[music]
[plane taking off]
Allahu Akbar!
[music playing in
the background]
Allahu Akbar!
[music playing in
the background]
Allahu Akbar!
[glass shattering]
[indistinct yelling]
I swear to God.
Allahu Akbar!
[indistinct yelling]
[sirens wailing]
[indistinct
announcement over P.A.]
Would you like
some pretzels, sir?
[baby bawling]
Peanuts, pretzels?
I don't know, how about you do
us a favor and shut these kids up.
[baby screeching]
Best I can do is a stiff drink.
You got people paying good
money for cramped seats,
overpriced drinks, and
terrible customer service.
Oh, we do have pure wine.
As far as flying these days is no
better than taking the damn bus.
You know, you're right, a
screaming kid on an airplane sucks.
But you know
what's worse?
What's that?
Some overgrown frat boy sitting
in coach thinking his 200 dollar
ticket entitles him to extra
legroom, free champagne,
and the right to stare at
my ass every time I walk by.
You want peace and quiet, slick?
Next time, shell out a few bucks and
get a seat up front with the big dicks.
[baby bawling]
Peanuts or pretzels, sir?
Four write-ups, a professional
standards review, and now this?
Montine, do you enjoy
being a flight attendant?
I need the job.
Then start acting like it.
Your name shows up on
my desk one more time,
I got no choice
but to ground you,
permanently.
[school bell rings]
- Good boy!
- What about breakfast?
Huh!
[paper rustling]
- Get something at break, okay?
- Okay.
Good boy!
Maliq!
Mr. Hassan!
I'm the executive director
of the Ibn-Tanea School.
Have you heard of it?
Should I have?
It's the most academically
competitive Muslim school in the country.
Mr. Cameroon have
tested Omar IQ.
Doesn't he need my
permission to do this?
He scored a 158.
Is that good?
Mr. Hassan, we are prepared to
offer Omar a full scholarship to attend.
Full scholarship?
That's right.
Shukriya.
[foreign]
His tuition and housing will be
fully subsidized by our endowment.
Oh, no, no.
No, Omar does not need housing.
He lives with me.
Maliq!
The school is in Los Angeles.
I understand this would
be a difficult decision.
Maliq!
I know you take Omar
with you in the taxi,
all night.
Brother Maliq,
this is not about me.
It's not about you.
It's about your son.
Omar
mine,
it's God.
The school will be a
great opportunity for him.
When Omar's mother was killed,
I never made a bottle,
never changed a diaper.
But I swore to
myself that I would,
I would raise my own son.
No matter what
I had to sacrifice.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm late for work.
[bustling traffic]
Did you know that some
dogs can find their way home
from over a
thousand miles away?
I'm not getting a dog.
If you get a dog, you could leave
me at home at nights, when you drive.
What, you and the puppy dog
are going to fight off the robbers
and the criminals
by yourself?
[honking]
I'll get us out of the
apartment, okay beta?
And buy a house with a yard.
So we can play soccer.
I hate soccer.
I'll buy a house with the
the biggest laboratory,
so you can do all
your crazy experiments.
Like that?
Cab, yo!
Tuck down!
[foreign]
[intermittent beeping]
[breathes shakily]
How's she doing?
Just as happy as a
bird with a French fry.
Ain't that right, Miss Milly?
I'll be in the TV room,
if you need anything.
[mumbling]
Mom!
What'd you say?
[mumbling]
Mom?
Have you seen my husband?
No, Mom, it's me
and Montine.
What did you say
your name was?
Montine!
I like that name.
[laugh]
I heard you the first time. I
heard you the second time.
Now do not call us again. I will call
you when I'm ready for you to push.
I shit you not. This
guy comes off the mic.
As soon as he
does that, we hear:
"Air Asia, we are ready to push."
The guy cues the mic and says,
"Air Asia, I said
no talkie talkie."
[laughing]
[somber music]
[door closes]
[knocking on door]
[plane taking off]
[screaming]
[sirens wailing]
Late night, huh?
What?
Late night?
Yeah. Yes,
Pull over here.
You wanted to go
to Tompkins Square.
[clocks gun]
[intense music]
[plane takes off]
Careful with
your money, okay?
I packed you some food
in case you get hungry.
Why can't you
come with me?
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't worry, beta.
I will just have
to finish my job,
make little more money, and
then I'll be in Los Angeles with you.
You're gonna miss my birthday.
I'll make it up to you.
All right? I promise.
We'll celebrate your
birthday on the beach.
I hate the beach.
Mr. Omar!
He needs to wear
this on the plane.
It's got your name and
your dad's phone number
on in here in case we
need to call him, huh?
He doesn't like
strangers to touch him.
Well, he's not getting
on the plane without it.
I'll put it on for him.
All right.
It's time to board, so.
[indistinct
announcement over P.A.]
Oh!
[gasping]
I'm going to be
late for work.
You're going to
miss your plane.
Come.
Come on! Jaldee
If you ever need me, you call
me on our special phone, okay?
And I'll be there to help you.
You remember how it works?
[somber music]
[foriegn]
Abu?
Abu!
[somber music]
Let's go, kid.
Okay, fine.
[somber music]
[plane takes off]
Hey, folks on the flight deck.
We've reached our cruising
altitude at 36,000 feet.
Expecting a nice ride out
to Los Angeles this morning.
We invite you to sit back,
relax, and enjoy the flight.
[intercom beeping]
Yes, what is it?
UM in 32F locked
himself in the lav.
Which one?
[knocking]
Open up!
[lock clicks]
What's the mater, kid?
You're scared of flying?
No.
So, what's your issue?
I don't wanna go to LA.
Locking yourself in
the lav isn't gonna
make this plane land
anywhere different.
Just make your ride
a whole lot smellier.
[slams door]
Come on, kid.
Open up!
[lock clicks]
He's not goin' anywhere.
He'll come out
when he's ready.
Okay!
[whooshing]
[lock clicks]
[door creaks]
[music]
[phone ringing]
Hello.
How is she?
She had a rough
night. How are you?
I'm fine.
We were so
worried about you.
I said I was fine.
Excuse me.
Um!
Are we in Los Angeles?
Hello!
[clattering]
What are you doing? I...
I... I have to call you back.
What are you
doing still on board?
I fell asleep.
You fell asleep?
Where?
In the bathroom.
You were in there
the whole time?
We landed with
a kid in the lav.
- Oh, no!
- I thought you checked.
You told me it
was all clear.
- That's what Jackie told me.
- And you didn't verify?
[scoffs]
What are you standing
there for? Come on. Let's go.
[sobbing]
[indistinct chatter]
What happened?
Why did we land?
Wait here?
Right here.
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct announcement over P.A.]
Excuse me!
[indistinct chatter on T.V.]
ago in Lower Manhattan,
when the first of two planes
crashed into the north tower
of the World Trade Center.
And you can see the smoke
billowing out of the towers now.
[indistinct chatter on T.V.]
I told you to wait by the
Okay, all right.
I won't touch you again if you
don't run away again, all right?
Okay! Come with me.
Come on!
All of the flights are canceled.
No. No planes today. No fly.
That the UM from flight 189?
And?
I'm only responsible
for the kid until we land.
I want to talk to
the supervisor.
Look, I got a line of
people to deal with.
I can't babysit some kid?
Just take him
back to Ops!
Come on, let's go.
I need to get back to New York.
Kid, you are not going
anywhere anytime soon.
The entire country
has been grounded.
All right?
Come on!
Please, I need
to see my father.
Let's go.
Please see
the information desk!
Come on.
[phone ringing]
Can I help you?
I have the UM from the-
Hang on! Hang on!
Larry!
Larry, make sure
you tell Dallas
we're gonna need extra
staff down here ASAP.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
Stand by one. What are
you doing with a kid in here?
Well, the gate agent told
me to bring him down here.
Yeah, well, I'm telling you
to get him the hell out of here.
- Paul, you there?
-Stand by one.
He is not my
responsibility once we land.
Listen, all UMs are supposed
to stay with a crew member
until we can figure out how to
get them back to their parents.
So find another crew member.
Do you want to
keep your job, Miss?
What am I supposed
to do with him?
I don't know.
Take him to a hotel,
let him watch cartoons.
I need that equipment count now!
I know, I know.
I'm doing it.
All right, kid.
Come on. Let's go.
[phone ringing]
Oh, my God.
Oh!
[phone ringing]
[door closes]
[indistinct chatter]
[knocking on door]
Okay kid, look!
In case, you didn't
realize, we've got a little
bit of a national emergency
going on here, huh?
Listen, this is no time to
pull some childish prank
and lock yourself
in the bathroom.
- Leave me alone.
- Can't do that.
Look, I'm on probation
with my airline.
You know what that means?
Well, it means if I
lose you, I lose my job.
You don't want me
to lose my job, right?
Mmm?
See, we're stuck together
whether we like it or not.
[door creaking]
Kid, I swear to God, if
you don't open this door,
I'm going to kick it down
and drag you out of there.
Come on!
My father has two jobs.
What?
He drives
the taxi at night.
And works at a
restaurant during the day.
So your dad's got two jobs?
What the hell are you crying about?
The restaurant he works at is at
the top of the World Trade Center.
[sniffling]
[music]
After he dropped
me off at the airport
he was going to work.
Take me home.
[sobbing]
Please.
[beeping]
We're sorry.
Your call cannot
be connected.
Please check the
number you have dialed.
The lines are still
down. Just wait here.
I need a car.
-We're sold out.
That kid over there. I've got
to get him back to New York.
- It's kind of an emergency.
- Honestly, I got nothing.
What about the
other locations?
Can you call and see
what they have available?
Ma'am, there are thousands of
people stranded here this morning.
I got 25 cars total.
Hell, you'd be lucky to
find a car in this whole state.
I'm sorry.
Come on kid, let's go.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
[phone ringing]
Hello!
Montine!
Paul Riley, from Ops.
Oh, hi.
Sorry things were
so hectic earlier.
You and the kid get
settled in, okay at the hotel?
Yeah!
Oh, good.
Well, we tried
contacting the kid's father,
but lines are still
down in New York.
We got no idea how long
this flight ban is gonna last.
Okay.
Um!
I'm guessing it could
be as long as a week
What room are you in?
Huuh, what room?
Um!
Well, I gotta put
it in the kid's file.
Yeah, room 914.
All right. 914.
Copy that.
The view is much better
out the window, kid.
[tires screeching]
Next.
What's good here?
I don't know, burger, I guess.
Make it a double.
Well done. Blacker the better.
Is that all?
Double Stoli on the rocks?
Uh!
Just kidding.
Whatever the kid wants.
I'm not hungry.
You gotta eat something.
Just get him a burger
and fries, I guess.
I don't eat red meat. It doubles your
risk of colon cancer and heart disease.
Just whatever, a
frickin' grilled cheese.
What!
You said a bad word.
I did not say a bad word.
Did I say a bad word?
Uhh!
You said order the
grilled cheese.
I did not say
I said frickin'.
That's a bad word.
It's not a bad word. Trust me,
there's a lot worse I coulda used.
My abbu says it's a bad word.
Okay, fine. All right.
I said a bad word.
Just give the kid a fucking
grilled cheese sandwich.
Omar, wait up.
Omar, I'm sorry I
said a bad word.
[car honking]
Omar!
Are you kidding me?
I said I was sorry.
What more do you want?
You're not a very nice lady.
No, I'm not a very nice lady.
You wanted nice, you shoulda hired
Mary fucking Poppins to take you home.
Yeah, I know.
I said a bad word.
[music]
♪ See, I've been
riding roughshod, ♪
♪ and I haven't taken names, ♪
♪ and I've been
running ragged, ♪
♪ looking for that flame. ♪
♪ I've been burning bridges ♪
♪ I've been flying planes, ♪
♪ and I've been
turning circles, ♪
♪ not making things. ♪
♪ See, ♪
♪ I've been riding roughshod ♪
♪ They don't mean a thing, ♪
♪ nothing to tell about it. ♪
♪ It's different all the same. ♪
♪ Yeah. I've been ♪
♪ riding roughshod. ♪
♪ No pain. ♪
♪ No more gains. ♪
♪ Lighting one of the another. ♪
♪ Hoping they make a change. ♪
[music]
♪ I've been riding roughshod. ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah! Oh, no, no. ♪
♪ It's all right. ♪
♪ I've been riding roughshod. ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. ♪
♪ Ain't got nobody. ♪
♪ I've been riding roughshod. ♪
♪ Now, now, now! ♪
♪ It's all right. It's ♪
♪ all right It's all right. ♪
Hey, you get up!
Get up!
You're not allowed to do that.
But I have to do my
Kiev Namaz.
Not on my bus you don't.
- Who you with?
- What?
Your mom,
your dad?
He's with me.
Well get him back
in his seat, now.
He's not bothering anyone.
- Excuse me!
- I don't want him on here.
Me neither!
- He's a kid.
- I don't care.
They train 'em young. I
seen that on 60 Minutes, lady.
[scoffs]
I didn't know 60 Minutes was popular
with the trailer park crowd these days.
Lady, you got three seconds
to get that kid in his seat,
or I'm tossing both of you
off this bus at the next stop.
Fine, I'll worry about the kid.
Now, why don't you
do us all a favor,
and take your ass back up to the
driver's seat and get us to New York.
[bus drives by]
Way to go, kid!
Me? I'm not the one who
yelled at the bus driver.
Do you understand what
happened this morning?
You might wanna cool it
on the Allah, Allah routine
for a little while, huh?
- Where are you going?
- Get a room.
A room?
I've been up for
about 22 hours now,
the last nine of
which was on a bus.
that smelled like the
underside of a toilet.
You can stay out here if you
want, but I'm gonna get a room.
How are we going to
get back to New York?
I'll figure that out after a
hot shower and a cold drink.
Civilian airliner loaded
with innocent victims
were hijacked and
used as guided missiles
against the Twin Towers of the
World Trade Center and The Pentagon.
Tonight, bodies are being
pulled from the rubble.
Hospitals are still
receiving victims,
and the streets of Lower Manhattan
are filled with people desperately
looking for their lost
loved ones who were in
or near the building
when they collapsed.
And on the steps of Capitol Hill,
as Republicans and Democrats-
Turn that crap off.
Which side of the
bed do you want?
Kid, you're making me nervous
standing there like a zombie.
I can't sleep
in a bed with you.
Fine. I'll sleep on the couch.
As long as we're stuck
together, I've got a few rules.
I don't want to hear a peep out
of you after ten and before seven.
There is no burping, no farting,
no booger picking.
You flush after you poop,
you put the seat down
after you take a pee.
Oh,
and I sleep with
the air set at 65.
So I hope you bought
a warm pair of PJs.
Excuse me.
Go to sleep.
I realize I don't even
know your name.
Montine.
Thank you for taking me
back to my abu, Montine.
[music]
[somber music]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[somber music]
Tonight, I ask for your prayers
for all those who grieve,
for the children whose
worlds have been shattered,
for all whose sense of safety
and security has been threatened.
And I pray they will be comforted
by a power greater than any of us,
spoken through the
ages in Psalm 23.
Even though I walk through
the valley of the shadow of death,
I fear no evil.
Freakin tragic, huh?
This is a day when
all Americans...
[laugh]
What's so funny?
I said a bad word.
Don't ask. Inside joke.
You want another?
Yes please.
You'll all forget.
Trust me, a few years from
now, no one'll remember.
What?
April 19th in 1995.
What happened
April 19th 1995?
Okay lady, whatever you say.
Make it a double slick.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
[man on TV] One of the
most tragic days ever!
[phone ringing]
You've reached the
voicemail of Maliq Hassan.
Please leave a message.
[laugh]
Um, um...
Mr. Hassan,
This is
uh, Montine McLeod.
I was the, um,
I was the flight attendant
on your son's flight.
He's with me.
Omar is with me,
and he's safe and I am
bringing him back to you.
Um!
I really hope
that, uh-
goodnight,
Mr., Mr. Hassan.
Assalamualaikum Warahmatullahi!
Ameen... Summa Ameen.
Hmmm..
Good morning.
My father told me to thank
you for bringing me home.
You talked to him?
Yes.
When?
I just called him.
What else did he say?
Was he near the building
when it happened?
Yes, he said he
was really scared.
He's okay?
Of course, he is.
He told me he'll be waiting for me
at our apartment when we get there.
Oh, you better get going.
I'm gonna get you home.
How are we going
to get to New York?
We could take a taxi.
Do you know how
much that would cost?
A lot.
It would cost 1,716
dollars to take a taxi.
What!
It's 857 miles from
Evansville to New York.
But how do you know that?
I was studying the map last
night after you went to sleep.
Two dollars to start, and two
dollars per mile, multiply by 857.
Are you some
kind of genius?
I just like learning about
lots of different stuff.
All right, I understand.
Looks like we're
gonna have to find a car.
Come on. Come on.
She may not look like much,
but she's got a lot of life left in her.
How much?
700. That's on
account of all the graffiti.
You replaced these belts?
Ma'am, I can assure
you this vehicle's had a
thorough inspection
from my maintenance staff.
Just because I don't
have a penis doesn't
mean I've never
worked under a hood.
Okay, I'll tell you what.
I'll toss in new
belts and I'll knock
off 15 percent, we'll
call it an even 600.
15 percent of 700 is 105.
That would make it 595.
[laugh]
That kid's good at math.
And the average discount for
all unsold retail merchandise
in the United States
is 12.2% per month.
You know, I think it's best that we
talk finance with the little lady here.
You wanna make this deal,
looks like you're gonna
have to deal with him.
Okay, uh...
What number you got
in your head, little man?
350!
This baby blue books 900.
Price just dropped at 325.
If I were you, I'd
close this deal quick.
Shit!
All right.
♪ Time You Want Again ♪
♪ by Damon Aaron playing. ♪
[♪♪♪]
Must be fun to be
a flight attendant.
It's okay.
Get to see all those
different places.
Oh, yeah. Madison and Raleigh,
Madison and Milwaukee,
Madison and Tampa.
There is interesting things to
do and see around every city.
Kid, listen. You give me a good
bar and a clean set of sheets,
I'm a happy camper.
Do you have a family?
Do you have a husband?
It's a complicated answer.
Is that why you
don't wear a ring?
It's not really any
of your business, kid.
[♪♪♪]
Hey!
We gotta pick a
name for this car.
A name?
Yeah, I always name my cars.
Why?
I don't know. Just-
[♪♪♪]
How about, Betty?
Yeah.
That's cool.
[♪♪♪]
At this hour, there's mounting
evidence that Islamic fundamentalists
may be responsible for the
coordinated terrorist attacks
on the World Trade
Center and Pentagon.
As each new report comes in,
there's a growing sense of anger
directed at the Moslem world.
An anger that has left
many innocent people
of the Moslem American community
worried for their own safety.
How old are you, kid?
Ten, it's my birthday.
Today?
Yep!
Well then why didn't you
say something sooner?
This young man
turned ten today.
And?
Don't you have
some sort of cake?
I don't eat cake.
How about a hot fudge sundae?
I don't eat ice cream.
Just bring the sundae.
If he won't eat it, I will.
Ten is a big birthday.
Double digits.
Why do you drink so much?
I don't drink so much.
A drink or two a day.
No big deal.
Just take the edge off.
Take the edge off what?
Sometimes things
happen in life that
are hard to deal with.
Is your husband
Told you it's complicated.
- Did he leave you?
- Yes, he left me.
Why?
I don't know.
Didn't make sense then.
Makes even less sense now.
So drinking helps you to not
think about the things that hurt?
You got it, kid.
Maybe I should
have a drink, too.
[scoffs]
There are these boys in my
neighborhood that make fun of me.
You know, what
you do with bullies?
Run?
No.
You bully them back.
Not when they're five
feet tall with mustaches.
You're right.
When they're five feet tall
with mustaches, you run.
[chuckles]
[music]
♪ When road ends ♪
Is this music rock and roll?
I guess you could call it that.
What kinda music do you like?
I don't know.
I'm never allowed to listen
to American music.
You've never sat and
listened to a record?
No.
Danced around the
living room to The Beatles.
What are The Beatles?
Well, you're
kidding me, right?
What about Elvis?
Yeah, of course.
Everybody knows Elvis.
Goodness. Starting to get
a little worried there, kid.
♪ Road ends always
thought you'd be by my side ♪
Can I tell you a secret?
Lay it on me.
I think Elvis is cool.
Is that right?
But my Abbu says that listening
to Elvis leads to sinful thoughts.
He's right.
Some music does
lead to sinful thoughts.
Trust me kid, some
music can get you through
the absolute
darkest nights of life.
♪ In case you need to
find your way home ♪
Here.
No. I can't.
In case you change your mind, there's
about 15 tapes to choose from in there.
Most of them are sin-free.
♪ Road ends ♪
♪ I always thought you'd
be by my side, though ♪
♪ Road ends ♪
♪ How will I know ♪
[music]
[cars driving by]
[foreign]
[phone ringing]
Hello.
Hi.
Hey, I got a question for you.
How many times
a day do you pray?
Well?
Yeah.
Is she okay?
How far away are you?
Up, up, up!
- What're you doing?
- We're leaving.
I didn't get to
finish my prayers.
Get your ass in the car now.
What happened?
Why are you so angry?
Got to make a stop.
- A stop, where?
- Marion.
Where's Marion?
Just outside of Cleveland.
That's north.
- New York is east...
- I know Geography, kid.
It's completely out of the way.
Deal with it!
Please, my father
is waiting for me.
You'll be thankful.
You'll be very, very
thankful that you have
somebody waiting for
you when you do get home.
[car door closes]
[engine revving]
[music]
Even though I walk through
the valley of the shadow of death,
I shall fear no evil.
For thou art with me.
Your staff and your rod.
[inhales deeply]
They comfort me.
[music]
I was thinking
we'd have a funeral at
the church on Sunday.
That's not what she wanted.
Can I go out?
Out where?
Just for a walk.
Sam.
What?
We have company.
It's just Aunt Montine.
No offense.
No worries. I get it.
Okay. Well, clear your plate.
And take Omar with you.
[plates clinking]
Seriously?
End of discussion.
[scoffs]
Go.
If he's coming, I'm
leaving right now.
[door closes]
Nice kid.
He's all right.
Have you thought about
how you're gonna get
him home now that--
Now that what, Will?
Well, there's a lot to
deal with now that mom--
The funeral.
Her bills.
All her stuff.
I'm only staying the night.
So did your dad really work
in the World Trade Center?
Yeah.
Is he dead?
No.
Called him this morning.
He said he's waiting
for me to come home.
Nice.
You ever smoked?
No.
You wanna try?
Smoking's really bad for you.
Oh, well, thank you,
Captain Obvious.
So, what kinda
music do you like?
I don't know.
What do you like?
Mm.
Clash
Social D
The Replacements.
Yeah.
I like them, too.
Um
And Elvis.
He's pretty cool.
Elvis Presley?
Yeah.
Are you kidding?
No.
Elvis is lame.
That her old T-Bird?
Yeah.
I remember the day
she drove that off the lot.
So proud of her
shiny new car.
Montine.
She deserves a proper burial.
And you need to be there.
[scoffs]
You go on and throw a big
shindig at the church, Billy boy.
That's what
you need to do.
[chuckles]
Said my goodbyes long time ago.
I won't be there.
I don't need to be there.
What if I told you I
needed you here?
I'll probably tell
you to deal with it.
Just for one time if you could think
about someone other than yourself.
Well, that's rich
coming from you.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
I'm not perfect.
I've sinned.
And I've been humbled.
But I'll tell you what.
I've been here with
my mom day after day,
feeding her, talking to
her, changing her diapers.
Oh ho, so you win the
best child of the year award?
I'm not looking to win an award.
I did it for love.
Do you remember what love is?
- If Michael were here--
- Yeah, but he's not.
He's gone.
And there's nothing
that you or your prayers
or your Holy Jesus did good to
bring him or mom or any of them back.
You just go on preaching
and preaching, man.
It seems to be
what you're good at.
[music]
[indistinct chattering]
Quit staring at people.
Sorry.
Where's your mom?
She left us.
Two years ago.
Why would she leave you?
Well.
When my dad was a
new preacher in town,
he decided to attend a little
too closely to one of the sheep.
You know what I mean?
No.
Look.
My dad did some stupid things, and
he got himself thrown out of the church.
So we moved into
my grandma's house,
and he started preaching
downtown to a bunch of crackheads.
And my mom split and ran.
Left us both.
I'm sorry.
Whatever.
At least, I get a stupid Christmas
card from Belgium over here.
What?
You remind me of her.
- Who?
- Montine.
Oh gross!
That bitter old lady!
I think she's just sad
because her husband left her.
Is that what she told you?
You finally got a
boyfriend, Sammy girl?
[crowd giggling]
What's up with
the silly hat, dude?
[sighs]
Shut up, McDonough.
Hey, dude, I'm talking to you.
It's not a hat, it's a topi.
A toe cheese?
[crowd giggling]
Check out the little
dude's toe cheese.
[laughing]
Where you going?
You got a building to blow up?
I asked you a
question, rag head.
Hey leave him
alone. He's just a kid.
It's okay, Sam. I know what
to do with bullies like him.
[crowd booing]
And I know what to do
with dirty little Arabs like you.
[chuckles]
What's so funny?
I'm not Arab, I'm Pakistani.
Huh! And there's a difference.
[chuckles]
You don't know the difference
between Arab and Pakistani?
[slaps]
Stop it! Get off of him!
Omar, please just stop!
[somber music]
Yeah!
[music]
All right.
Where were you two?
What happened, is that blood?
We were just at the
park. And all of a sudden--
Sam!
What?
How could you let this happen?
Well, it's not like I
really had a choice.
Well, you took him to the park,
you were responsible for him.
Yeah. And you took
Uncle Mike to the building.
Does that mean you're
responsible for killing him?
- Samantha Jean McLeod!
- What?
Apologize to her.
No.
Yes. You apologize
to her right now.
No!
Look, ever since it
happened, all she ever does
is look at me with those
angry eyes like it was my fault.
So if you want to blame
me for her blackened heart
and for getting Omar
beat up, then fine.
Fine. Just blame me for everything.
[door closes]
You, okay?
I don't think it was such a
good idea to bully the boys.
Let's get you cleaned up.
[water trickling]
I'm allowed to touch you
when you're bleeding?
No.
Now here, take this and--
What are you going
to do with that?
Who is Uncle Mike?
Michael was my husband.
And you told me
that he left you.
He did.
April 19th, 1995.
He was working in
the federal building.
Oklahoma City
I dropped him off that morning.
Handed him his lunchbox.
And told him I'd pick
him up after work.
I was running late for some
stupid aerobics class and
I forgot to give him a kiss.
It's interesting that some of
the most important moments
in your life happen when
you're not even looking.
I'm really sorry.
Me, too.
You missed a
spot there tough guy.
Oh.
[knocking on door]
Are you okay?
Is the couch comfortable?
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Goodnight, Omar.
Excuse me.
You can talk to God, right?
We all can talk to God.
But you're a holy man.
You've a special, direct
connection with him.
That connection
hasn't
exactly been
working so well lately.
But--
Why does God let
bad things happen?
[sighs]
Well,
some people think that
God created the Earth and
everything that happens
after that is just chance.
Others would say that
things happen because
of man's free will.
Sometimes we make good choices,
and sometimes we make bad choices.
But--
I think there's
some mystery to it.
Because there's
some things that
happen in this world that
we just can't
fully understand.
Like what happened
to Montine's husband.
Yeah.
Like what happened
to Montine's husband.
[somber music]
Allahu Akbar.
[music]
Hey.
- Let me help you.
- I got it.
[sighs]
Hey, aunt Montine.
I'm sorry about what I
said to you last night.
I think I can find space in my
blackened heart to forgive you.
Okay, cool.
Well, I'm not really into
the whole goodbye thing.
It's no problem.
Okay.
Take good care of your dad.
[scoffs]
Yeah.
Somebody has to.
She hates me.
Now, I'll tell you a secret.
All 15-year-old girls
hate their fathers.
All big sisters can't
stand their baby brothers.
I'll be back on Sunday.
Hey, I'm sorry again
about those creeps.
It's okay. It's not
really your fault.
[car engine revving]
You know, if you tell Aunt Montine about
the cigarettes, I'm gonna kick your ass.
[music]
[door opens]
Why you going in that apartment?
It's just a kid. He's
excited to see his father.
His father ain't been
home since Tuesday.
Tuesday?
He worked at the Trade Center.
It's a shame, really.
He seemed like a nice guy.
[door closes]
Okay. What's going on here?
You told me
you talked to him.
I did.
Yeah. And he said that he would
be here when you got home, right?
That's what he told me.
So why'd that lady just say he hasn't
been here since it happened, hmm?
Where is he?
I talked to him on
the special phone.
Special phone?
It's right here.
It's what?
My Abbu taught me that
we all have these invisible wires that
connect us to the people that we love.
[sniffling]
And so whenever
you wanna talk to them
all we have to do is
[sniffling]
pick up the special
phones inside our head
[sniffling]
it's like they're
right there with us.
Oh, my God!
You had me believe
that everything was fine.
You brought me here based on
some imaginary phone in your head?
It's not an imaginary phone.
It's real.
[somber music]
No, nothing.
Are you sure?
Ma'am, there's no Maliq Hassan
who has been either
positively identified--
Is there some kind of
form that I could fill out
so you call me when
you do find him?
Ma'am if he was in Trade Center
when it fell, they ain't gonna find him.
Sorry to be so blunt. I
got eight lines holding.
You see this kid?
It's his father
we're talking about.
You got a father, right?
Yeah.
So just promise me
you will call me if--
Write down your number.
[phone ringing]
What's this?
Take the kid to the
child services office.
I'm sure they can help you.
Let's go.
How do you spell his name?
O-M--
No, no. I got the Omar
part. His last name.
Hassan.
H-A-S-S-A-N.
Okay. How old are you?
Ten.
Any other family?
No.
Any aunts, uncles?
Grandparents?
I think I have an
uncle back in Pakistan.
I don't understand why
I can't stay with you?
Now, kid, I live in a crash pad.
What's a crash pad?
Well, it's an apartment
with like ten bunk beds
scattered all over the
living rooms and bedrooms.
You...
You live with that many people?
No, the international
girls just usually
sleep all day because
they work the red eyes.
Domestic girls come
stumbling in after they
bars all closed.
And first come, first serve.
So the beds are full, you gotta
just curl up on that dirty old couch or
toss a blanket on the floor.
It's not exactly
home sweet home.
Why don't you get
your own place?
I don't want my own place. I--
It's too quiet.
You know, sometimes on
my days off, I go to the airport
and just get on whatever
flight is taking off next.
I spend the night in the hotel
and flight back the next morning.
Why?
Because as long as I'm--
on that plane or at
the airport or hotel,
I've a purpose.
You know, a reason
to get up in the morning.
If there's
anything of his you want, you
might wanna pack it up now.
[phone ringing]
Hello.
You wanna tell
me where you are?
I'm, I'm sorry. What?
Where are you?
Who is this?
This is Paul Ehrlich
with Ops in Longview.
Shit!
Yeah. Shit's right.
I ring the hotel.
I ask them to give me room 914,
what do you think they tell me?
I don't know.
There is no room 914.
So where the hell are you?
[phone ringing]
So you made the
unilateral decision to drive
the unaccompanied
minor back to New York?
Actually, we started out on
a bus, but we got kicked off.
And then, I made the
unilateral decision to drive.
You may think that this is
amusing, but I can assure you I don't.
You violated almost every rule we have
regarding the care of unaccompanied minors.
Yeah, well, the rule book kinda got
tossed out the window Tuesday morning.
Perhaps by you, but we
still have an airline to ride.
Yeah. And I had a small
child who was all alone and--
With legal obligations to adhere
to and consequences if we don't.
Do you have any idea what
could have happened if he got lost?
Or if he had an accident?
The lawsuits that
we'd be liable for?
Lawsuits?
Is that what this is about?
Who's gonna sue you?
This meeting is over.
Mr. Al Katani will
take Omar from here.
Oh, really? Who are you
afraid is gonna sue you?
I mean, his only family
member is probably buried
under a billion tons
of steel and concrete.
What about Omar?
Termination paperwork.
And I'll need to get your ID.
Probably he'll end
up in foster care.
He's not going to a foster home.
He's staying with
Mr. Al Katani tonight.
And then, he's booked on a
flight to LA tomorrow morning.
Oh, why?
There's some school there.
That's what his
father wanted for him.
That's where
he belongs now.
We like to thank you for all
what you've done with Omar.
And we ask God
to bless you with
happiness, health,
and a state of mind.
Say good bye.
Have some time with him.
So you gonna be a good kid?
I bought a little
surprise in here for you.
But don't open
up till you're alone.
I don't want you to get in
trouble with the big man.
Thank you.
For everything.
Omar Habibi time to go.
Say salam.
Salam.
[door opens]
[music]
[foreign]
How can we apply this
to our situation now?
When the Prophet
Muhammad's son died,
he said that eye shed tears,
and that the heart is grieved.
But we will not say anything
except which please our Lord.
Masha'Allah!
Omar, you have a wonderful heart.
Follow it.
Will take you to the right path.
Good night Omar.
[door closes]
[lock clicks]
[unlocks zipper]
[sound]
♪ Playing Lay Me ♪
♪ Down by Damon Aaron ♪
[♪♪♪]
[phone ringing]
Yes. Hello.
Thank you very
much for coming.
Omar said he wouldn't go
to the airport without you?
He locked himself
in the bathroom.
He's got a thing for bathrooms.
[knocking on door]
Hey kid, open up.
[lock clicks]
We gotta quit
meeting like this.
What's the matter?
Tried to call my Abbu on the
special phone this morning.
He didn't answer.
This early?
Probably he's still asleep then.
Look kid, here's the deal.
Losing things,
losing people that you love,
it hurts.
There's gonna be days when
you think you can't possibly
stand how much it hurts.
Honestly.
You'll feel like your heart's
gonna explode from the pain.
Then you wake up the
next morning and you
open the blinds and
you just keep going.
For a while, you're just
living in that space between.
Between what?
Between the last
time when you saw him
and the moment you
can finally say goodbye.
After a few years, you'll
crawl into bed one night
and realize you don't even
think about him at all of that day.
But then, every once in a while,
he'll come to you in
your dreams at night.
And the warm thought of him
will wake you in the morning.
Will you walk me
on to the plane?
[music]
And for that little tiny
sliver of the moment,
he's right there
by your side again.
And nothing...
No other person, no distance or
time can take him away from you.
[somber music]
[closing score]