- No! No!
- Wakey, wakey.
Here comes the tickle monster.
Come on, it's time to get up.
Good morning. Be
careful, please.
- Are you really gonna
go all by yourself?
- I still have to do it.
- But aren't you afraid?
- I'm gonna be okay.
- But what if you're
not back in time for-
- Good morning.
How you feeling today, Mia?
- Fine, thanks.
- Good.
I was thinking of having
a birthday dinner for you.
18. It's a big deal.
I remember just yesterday
you were a scruffy teenager
arriving at my house.
- Yeah.
Well, thank you.
But really, I don't
need anything.
I really don't.
- Oh, come on.
It's good for all the kids.
You're gonna be an adult.
Come on. It'll be nice.
- I think I'm gonna
run in to the library.
- Okay.
- There are some
books I wanna get.
Well, get some
for when you're at the
hospital too, okay?
- Yeah, sure.
Hey, do you think I
could borrow some money
for buses and, you know, snacks?
- Okay.
- Pretty please.
- Yes, yes, yes.
- You're the best.
- I know.
- Thank you. I'll be back
before lunch, Mrs. R.
- Okay.
- Thank you. Mwah.
- Bye.
- So kids,
what are we gonna do today?
- Hey man,
it's been a while.
Can you believe I've already
been home for three weeks?
I'm so bored. Come over.
You can't ignore me forever.
- Morning.
Cream or butter?
- Thanks, Mom, but.
- Right. Not hungry
today either.
- Hey, buddy.
Ah, well, um, we talked
to Josh last night.
Seems like he's doing
a little bit better.
- He asked us about you
again and we told him-
- Yeah, I know.
I'm gonna go see him right now.
- Oh, I think he'll
appreciate that.
- Yeah.
- Have you responded to
the scholarship letter?
Come on, Kyle, they are not
gonna hold your place forever.
- Well, then they should
give it to someone else.
- No, this is not-
- Honey.
Honey, you have the whole
summer before you have to go.
Sign the entrance enrollment.
Then see how you feel.
- I don't think I'll
be back for lunch.
- Hey, here, take this with you.
Here you go.
- I don't know what to say.
- Why did you
have to say that again?
- He can't throw
away his soccer scholarship.
He didn't go to
graduation, fine,
but bailing on his scholarship?
- You've got
to give him more time.
It's only been a few
months since the accident.
He'll come around.
- I hope so.
- Hey,
you get lost or what?
Said you're coming hours ago.
- Yeah, I- I walked.
- Hey, don't,
don't worry about it.
I know it looks bad, but
it feels a lot worse.
So, um, where've you been?
- First two editions
of "Sun Eater."
- Thanks, dude.
You're the best.
So have you talked to them yet?
Noah's parents?
They've called a bunch of times.
They wanna talk to us.
You still can't remember?
You know, what
happened before the?
Me neither.
They say it's normal.
- I'm so sorry, boys,
but the, um, physical
therapist called,
he's gonna be here any
minute, so I think you should.
- Yeah, yeah, of course,
um.
I- I'll come back later.
- We haven't summoned the
courage to tell him yet,
but he may never walk again.
It's a blessing that you didn't
get more hurt than you did.
Just, just look at you.
There's barely a scratch on you.
And Josh, he's just broken.
And Noah.
Noah.
There's not.
There's not an
hour that goes by.
Not an hour goes by that I wish
he hadn't gotten into
that car with you.
I wish he hadn't gotten
into that car with you.
And Noah.
Just look at you,
not a scratch on you.
He hadn't gotten
into that car with.
Not a scratch on you.
- Help!
- Hey! Can you hear me?
- Oh, oh, ow! Oh.
- Are you all right?
You passed out.
Are you feeling better?
- Get it off me, get it off me!
Gross. Ooh.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, it's, I- I'm usually
not this hysterical.
It's just that, um,
when I was a kid,
a lizard crawled
into my bed once.
And, you know, when
you're five years old,
that could be
really traumatizing.
- People don't scream when
they're about to pass out.
- No?
- No.
- Okay, well, I'm epileptic
and so I can always tell
when I'm about to faint.
And because of that, I
scream because I get scared.
Hold on, hold on a minute.
I just, I think
that we should talk.
- Just mind your own business.
- No, no. Don't you get it?
You are my business.
If I let you do what I
think you are about to do,
I will never be able
to forgive myself.
And your mother would never
be able to forgive me either.
- Just go home.
- No.
- Fine.
- No. If you jump,
I'm gonna jump.
- What the? Hey, stop.
- Do you believe me now?
Monkey see, monkey do.
- This has gotta be a nightmare.
Just go away.
- Never.
Ooh, it's unlocked.
- Gimme my phone back.
- Mm-mm.
I'm gonna text myself
so I have your number.
- Who are you?
- My name's Amelia.
Amelia Faith, but
you can call me Mia.
Hi.
- Finally.
I was getting worried.
- I'm so sorry. I just,
I- I lost track of
time at the library.
- Mia, just be honest with me
and you better not have
your fingers crossed
behind your back.
- Maybe we should try
another counselor.
- No, come on, Lisa,
it has been months
and he's getting
worse day after day.
And he won't talk. He won't eat.
I mean, he barely even
looks at us anymore.
Hey.
- How'd it go with Josh?
- I knew it.
- Hey. If it isn't
my favorite foster sis.
How's Mrs. Rothswell doing?
- She's good.
Hey, can I ask you a favor?
Can you still do your
responsible mother voice?
Hi, my name is Mia.
I'm a really good
friend of Kyle's.
- Oh.
- Him and I
were having a
conversation the other day
and he said that he's obviously
going through a hard time.
- Right.
- And he really felt
like he needed to get away.
So I just thought that, um,
it might make you feel better
if you could speak to my mom.
- Yeah.
- Dammit.
- Hi.
- Hi, Mrs. Faith.
It's just such a surprise.
Thank you very much, Mrs. Faith.
We'll be sure to let him know.
Such an amazing offer.
Oh? Yeah, he's been going
through tough times.
I. Ah-huh.
Here he is now.
- Oh.
Yeah. Thanks, Mom.
Okay, bye.
She is so chatty.
Hey, so I was just
filling your parents in
on what we talked
about yesterday.
- Uh?
- With you saying that
you needed to get away.
And my mom inviting you to spend
some time with us in Spain.
She's a photographer, a
really, really good one.
And so she travels a lot
and she's been there
for a week already
and she says that we're
just gonna love it.
- She seems really nice.
But Kyle, honey, why haven't
you ever told us about Mia?
- Because I just-
- No, no.
No, no.
You're not gonna tell
them how we met, are you?
That is so
embarrassing.
- Okay, so you're saying
that you wanna travel now?
- Mm-hmm, he said that
he would not miss it.
- Can I talk to Mia in private?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm trying to get
your parents on board
for you to come to Spain.
- Spain?
- Yes. Spain.
The place between
France and Portugal.
Come with me for 10
days. All expenses paid.
Just get outta town
for a little while.
- Forget it.
- Okay, look, your
parents are very nice,
but they also seem very
concerned for your wellbeing.
I could tell them
how we actually met
or you could come with me.
And if you still wanna kick
the bucket after the trip,
I won't stop you.
Deal?
- Mom, Dad. Mia's leaving.
- Okay, look, no, you
can think about it.
You don't have to decide now.
You can just let me know tonight
or, or maybe tomorrow.
I'll be back.
Well, it was really
nice to meet you guys.
Thank you so much.
My mom, she just
really wanted me
to meet you guys in person.
There are so many, you know,
crazy people out there.
She just.
- Of course.
- It was a pleasure to meet you.
- Really nice meeting you.
- Um, hon, just to let you know,
your, your shirt's
on inside out.
- Oh no, I do that on purpose.
- Oh!
- Yeah.
It makes me feel like I'm a
little bit less conventional,
or, or something.
- Oh.
- Oh, wait. Hey, Kyle.
Don't forget to text me a
picture of your passport
and all that jazz.
We leave in three days.
- I'm gonna kill you.
- Yay. Bye.
- Why do you think he never
said anything about her?
She's lovely.
- He hasn't told us
anything in three months.
- Come in.
- Hey, buddy.
Your mom and I just
finished reading this.
We thought you might
get something out of it.
Hey, you know what?
I got an idea.
What do you say that you
and I take a soccer ball,
hit the field, you
can work on your PKs.
I don't think you can
score on me today.
- No, I'm okay.
- Okay. Plan B.
There is a big
FIFA match tonight.
You, me, pizza.
Watching it together
on the couch.
- Not tonight, okay?
- Son, I know what
you're going through
is incredibly challenging,
but you can't stay locked up
in your room day
after day, hiding.
- Can we please not do this?
- No, we are.
We're gonna do this right now.
You've been pushing
us away for too long.
Something has to change.
Do you think that if
you get outta here
and you go to Spain,
that that's gonna help?
'Cause if you do,
I want you to go.
- No, I don't wanna go.
- You don't wanna go?
You know what, what
do you wanna do?
You wanna stay in here for
another three months, moping?
- What do you want from me?
- I want my son back.
I want you.
- He's gone, Dad.
- What?
Kyle.
Here.
Go find him.
- This is for you.
Looks pretty. Like you.
- Do you really have to go?
- Yeah.
This is my chance to
get some answers, Becca.
I hope you can understand.
Hey, come here.
I have to tell you
something really important.
My best friend once told me,
no matter what happens,
no matter where I am,
there will always be
somebody somewhere
who is glad you were born.
Okay? So don't be sad.
- Why are you smiling?
- I just got some good
news about my trip.
- Good morning,
ladies and gentlemen.
On behalf of the
captain and crew,
we would like to
welcome you aboard.
Our flight to Madrid,
Spain will 13 hours-
- I am so excited.
I've been planning
this trip for years
and I've been thinking
about it, well, forever.
Have you ever had a dream
and it finally comes true
and then you just don't
know what to feel?
That is exactly what
I'm feeling right now.
Please take a moment
to review the safety data card
in the seat pocket
in front of you.
- Hey, hey, maybe we
ought to watch this.
- To
fasten your seatbelt,
insert the metal fitting
one into the other,
tighten by pulling the
loose ends of the straps.
Should the cabin experience
any pressure loss
stay calm and listen
for instructions
from your cabin crew.
Oxygen masks will-
- Oh! Cool, thank you.
- Place the mask
over your mouth and nose.
If you are traveling
with children, make sure
your own mask is on first
before helping them.
- It's my first
time on an airplane.
It's actually my first
time outside of California.
Isn't that so exciting?
I've always wondered what it
would be like on an airplane.
How big up-ahead
storage would be?
I thought it would be
smaller than this, actually.
I was pleasantly surprised.
- Oh, here it is.
- Ah!
- So you're the girl who
booked the Tuc Tuc a year ago.
- Mm-hmm.
You like to plan ahead.
So I guess that's Noah?
- No. No, Noah couldn't make it.
- Oh, okay.
- Ah. But this is Kyle.
Kyle Thompson. Here is his info.
- Bueno, then if you can
give Noah his receipt,
then I will just add Kyle
to the paperwork, and yes.
Okay, this is for you.
Let's go see the van.
- Okay.
- Here it is.
Fully equipped,
exactly as advertised.
You have a kitchen,
you have a stove,
uh, the bed on the back,
and you also have
Bluetooth connection,
if you want to listen to
music while you drive,
it'll be perfect.
And I guess that's
pretty much it,
so, uh, see you in 10 days.
Oh, could you please take
care of her for me, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- You must be crazy if you think
that I'm getting in
this thing with you.
Especially with you
behind the wheel.
- No, I don't know how to drive.
You're driving.
- The hell I am.
- Hey, hey, nobody turns
off my favorite song.
It's a good song.
- You know, on second thought,
I think that we might
need to renegotiate
the terms of our agreement.
At this rate I'm gonna
need like a month
to hit up all the places
I'd like to visit.
Oh, come, come on.
You're really not
gonna ask me anything?
Nothing about this trip.
Nothing about me.
- Okay, okay. We
can talk about you.
Or not.
- So, I bet you're wondering
why I'm taking so many pictures?
They're for my Photolog,
"Expiration Date."
You know? Expiration date.
It's like a metaphor.
Okay.
How about this? I am starving.
I bet you are too.
Um.
Okay, um, the next exit,
there's a restaurant
that has 4.7 stars.
Yeah, this exit.
Kyle.
Kyle! Kyle!
- Don't ever do that again.
- I'm sorry, I
just thought that-
- Just shut up!
Stop thinking. Stop talking.
Just stop.
- Okay.
I'll be inside.
- Ah, I think
you mean pollo, chicken?
- Oh, si.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Pollo.
Something else?
- Ah, yeah.
Uh, a muffin?
- Of course.
- Por favor.
- So
are you gonna tell me
what this trip's about?
- He speaks.
Are you okay?
Do you need me to call an
ambulance or something?
You must be delirious.
- So?
- So this trip is
about finding my mom.
- Finding her?
Didn't she talk to my parents
about meeting us out here?
- No, that was, uh,
that was my foster sister.
- What?
- Yeah.
Yeah. The thing is,
is that I don't.
I don't know my
mom. She left me.
Hey, but the cool thing is,
is that it's my birthday.
And how awesome would it be
if I got to meet my mom on
the day that I was born?
Happy birthday, Mia.
- Thanks.
- So where does this
mom of yours live?
- Well, over the last two years
I've been doing
a lot of research
and I came up with
10 mother candidates.
The first is in Segovia.
- Well, looks like you'll
meet her pretty soon then.
We just passed a sign that
says six kilometers to Segovia.
- Six kilometers?
No. No, why didn't
you say something?
No, I can't meet
my mom like this.
I brought my favorite
shirt for her.
I- I have to change.
I can't believe that this is
finally happening right now.
I mean, the mom is here-
- Mia, curtain!
- Look, I'm sorry, I just,
this is my favorite shirt and
I got it just to meet her.
God, get yourself
together, Mia Faith.
- It's getting a little
late, don't you think?
I mean, we shouldn't
just be barging in
on somebody unexpectedly
at this time.
I mean, they could
be having dinner.
- Still pretty light out.
Plus, I read they have
dinner pretty late.
- No, we just landed
today and I'm exhausted.
You know, I booked us
a place for tonight.
Maybe we could go
there and get some rest
and then we can go
meet her tomorrow.
- Happy birthday, Mia.
- Kyle.
Oh, come on.
Don't tell me that
you like to sleep in.
Kyle?
No. No, no.
Come on.
Pick up.
What? Where were you?
- Oh, good morning to your too.
I was taking a shower
and on my way back I
got us some breakfast.
- And you just took
all your stuff with you
to go take a shower?
- Oh, actually, yes.
You were out cold
and I didn't wanna be
grabbing stuff outta my bag,
making noise.
- Oh, so you weren't
planning on leaving me
and just taking off?
- Of course not.
Deal's a deal, right?
Hey, watch the chocolate.
- Thank you.
Thank you for staying.
- Ah! No, no, no.
How did that happen?
I spilled the hot chocolate.
I'm such a klutz, I
spilled it everywhere.
- I'm so sorry.
- What am I supposed to do?
I can't show up to
meet my mom like this.
Oh man.
I can't believe this happened.
It's just this is
my favorite shirt
and I really wanted to wear it.
- Hang on. I
think I got an idea.
- Why you stopping?
- Come on. We gotta get
you some new clothes.
- No, I'm fine, really,
I'll figure something out.
- "I'll figure something out."
I'm not lending you my clothes.
- I can't.
Really, I'm on a very
tight budget this trip.
- Well, consider it a
belated birthday gift.
- No. No, I can't accept it.
- Of course you can.
Plus, my dad gave
me his credit card
and if he sees I'm not
spending any money out here,
then I dunno, he'll call
the embassy or something.
- No.
- Okay, fine. Whatever.
- You're crazy. Did you
buy the entire store?
- You need clothes.
I couldn't made up my mind.
- Okay, but I'm paying
you back every penny.
Thank you.
- You're not wearing
your clothes inside out.
- What for? They're new.
What's this?
- Yeah, yeah, I know
you can't accept it,
but it's my birthday
gift to you.
Happy birthday.
- Oh! Thank you.
What do you think?
- Too big. Let's go
get you new ones.
- No. No, I love them.
I've never had any before.
- Ray-Bans? It doesn't get
more classic than that.
- No. Sunglasses.
- Vamos?
- Vamos.
Okay, one down.
Which means we're one
mother closer. Right?
It's still pretty early.
Got a lot of rounds to make.
What's the next address?
- No luck?
- No.
- Ah, my mom asked for pictures.
I just thought she'd liked
the street, that it's pretty.
- Oh, and here I thought
you wanted to immortalize me
in one of your drawings and
needed my picture as a model.
Silly me.
Oh!
Oh. Wow.
Nice moves.
Too bad those kids
aren't scouts.
You could get a scholarship.
- I had a scholarship but I
didn't sign the paperwork.
- Why not?
- Got tricked to going
into Spain with some girl
trying to meet her mom.
Let's get a nice lunch on me.
What are those?
- Just my vitamins.
- Hm. You know what I don't get?
- Hmm?
- How the heck you were planning
on making this trip work
if you don't know how to drive?
- My best friend was
supposed to come.
He really wanted to
help me find my mom,
but he couldn't make it.
- And you still have to tell me
how you came up with this hit
list of mother candidates.
- Okay, so my former foster
brother turned hacker
helped me look into it.
She's from Spain and she was
a former exchange student
in California.
You know, he actually
helped me find this.
- So what, you just like
searched up every woman
with this name in Spain?
- Yeah. And the States too.
Fortunately there weren't many
women with that last name.
That, and then Spanish women,
they actually never
lose their maiden names.
I just got really fed up with
all the unanswered questions.
Who was she?
What happened to her?
What's her family like?
What's my family like?
This is the only
thing I have of hers.
- That's really pretty.
- Yeah.
- And at least you have
like foster siblings, right?
- 24. I moved around a lot.
12 different homes in my
18 years in the system.
- That's a lot of homes.
- Yeah, but none of
them are real homes.
Not like yours.
I've officially aged out
of the system now anyway.
But Mrs. Rothswell did say
that I could stay with her
until I go to college.
- Gracias.
Oh, what are you doing?
I said I was gonna pay.
- I just wanna see
how much I owe you.
- No. My treat means you
don't have to pay for it.
- I know that's what
it means. I just-
- Oh, sorry.
- Um. No, it's okay.
Kyle!
- Noah Green is your friend
that was supposed
to come on this trip
and you didn't think to
mention that fact to me?
What is this? Some
kind of sick joke?
- No. No, he was my best friend.
He set this whole trip up.
- And you choose to bring me.
The reason he's gone.
What do you want from me?
- I don't know.
I recognized you at the park
and when I saw
you about to jump,
I- I thought that
I could help you.
I thought that maybe we
could help each other.
Kyle, I am so sorry.
We met in photography class
a few summers ago.
We just hit it off instantly.
He bought the plane tickets.
He helped me save my money.
He even found the van.
- We were in the, uh, the
same grade growing up.
I remember playing freeze tag.
And in first grade we were
on the same soccer team,
but, um, he stopped playing.
And then, uh, we, we'd see
each other in the halls
and, and nod, and that was it.
I wish I had known him better.
- He was a one of a kind human.
This says that the sand
dunes are unmissable
and that there's gonna be
a meteor shower tonight.
- English?
- American?
- Si, American.
- License and registration.
- Oh yes. Yes.
- Do you know why
I pulled you over?
You were driving too slow.
Too slow.
First time, warning.
Second time, fine.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay, okay.
- Ola.
You have to be the
only person under 80
to be stopped for driving
too slow.
Let's go, gramps. Vamos!
Can you smell it?
I've died and gone to Venus.
- You're certainly
from out of this world,
so makes a lot of sense.
- Let's
get in the water.
- Are you nuts? In your clothes?
- Oh, come on! Come
on, live a little.
Come on.
- I think we should have dinner
before we miss
the meteor shower.
- Yeah.
- You, you are such a nerd,
get outta here!
- What's your favorite
place in the universe?
Mine is Venus.
I wish I could just
think about being there
and boom, I'm there.
- What's your deal with Venus?
Why you like it so much?
- On my Venus, there's no war,
no pain or hunger.
On my Venus there aren't parents
who don't love their
children, or even.
- Death?
- Death isn't such
a scary thing, Kyle.
- You know when you're dead
you can't laugh anymore,
or hang out with your friends,
or fall in love,
or eat a hamburger.
Death sucks.
- It was an accident.
- I lost control of the car.
It was me.
I was the one that
was behind the wheel.
And I wasn't even supposed
to be driving Josh's car.
- Kyle, Noah would not
wanna see you like this.
- I don't know that.
And you can't ask him.
And it's not even just Noah.
My friend Josh,
I don't know if he'll
ever walk again.
Who can live with that? Not me.
- Kyle, there has to be a reason
that you made it out okay
when the others didn't.
This world, it can
be really harsh
and really bad
things can happen,
but you cannot give up
because you made a mistake.
You've been given
a second chance
to make a difference
in this world.
It's all in how you look at it.
I could be really upset
that my mom left me.
Or I could just be happy
that she even had me.
- I wish I never existed.
- Hey.
Noah used to tell me,
"There will always
be somebody somewhere
who is happy that
you were born."
Kyle?
- Mia!
Hey! Hey, it's been two hours.
When on Earth are you
gonna tell me something?
- Uh, are you with Amelia Faith?
- Yeah. Is she okay?
- Yes. Yes, don't worry.
It happens with people
in her condition.
We are discharging her now.
- Wait, wait, what condition?
- Oh, I thought.
Well, in that case it's better
if she tells you herself.
- Hey. Hey, are you okay?
What condition was that
doctor talking about, Mia?
- I'm fine. Just
forgot to take my pill.
- Yeah, your vitamins.
When are you gonna tell me
what's actually going on?
- Okay, what's going on
is that I have a
genetic heart defect.
There. Boom.
So it's fine. I'm releasing
you from our agreement.
- No, no, I'm, I'm not
gonna just up and leave you.
We had a deal, right?
It's fine. I'm
used to it by now.
- No, Mia!
You have an awesome chauffeur
for the next couple
of days, so come on.
- Mrs. Rothswell?
There's something
I have to tell you.
- Okay. Who are you avoiding?
- My foster mom.
- Why?
- I kind of ran away.
In that I didn't tell
her where I was going.
- Why not?
- Because Mrs. Rothswell
wanted me to stay home
and have the surgery.
- Wait, hold on. What surgery?
- I had an operation
scheduled for this week.
- You decided to travel
to Spain instead?
- My doctor said it was
perfectly safe for me to travel.
And what's the point of
waiting my entire life
just to die on an
operating table
before I get to meet my mom?
- How dangerous is the surgery?
- Half of the people die,
but half of them live.
- Are you, uh, are you scared?
- Death has never
really scared me.
- Then what are you
afraid of, Mia Faith?
- I guess what I'm afraid
of is dying invisible.
If you don't make a
difference in somebody's life,
if you don't even try
to change the world,
then what's the point
of ever being born?
Of ever living?
- Hence your Photolog.
- Yeah, I guess.
- Okay, so how many views?
- No idea.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
- Gimme your phone.
- Okay.
- Hm, oh. No wonder here.
Your account was on private.
Why didn't you tell
me about your heart?
- I guess I just,
I wanted to see what
it would feel like
to be a normal girl for once.
- Hold that pose.
- You're seriously taking
pictures right now?
- Come on, we've got
moms to meet. Let's go.
- Well, this is the last mother.
- She has to be the one.
- I guess our journey ends here.
Um, you know, you're,
you and your mom
are probably gonna have
a, a lot to talk about.
So in case I don't get
another chance to tell you,
I just.
- Wait, um.
Let's just enjoy this moment.
Wait, hi! Hi!
- Excuse me.
Excuse me.
- Hi. Hi!
- Si?
- Maria Astilleros?
- I'm sorry to bother you.
Do you speak English?
- A little rusty.
I haven't really practiced
since I was an exchange student
in the USA a long
time ago in New York.
- Wait, did you
say, um, New York?
Oh, I, we were
looking for somebody,
but, um, but we were wrong.
I'm sorry.
- Excuse us.
Thank you so much. We're
looking for someone else.
Sorry.
- Okay.
- It's not her.
- Mia.
- Kyle, I,
I just need some space.
- But.
- Mia's phone. Please
leave a message after the beep.
- Mia, where are you?
I've been waiting a long
time. Please answer.
Have you guys, um, seen,
uh, blonde hair, uh, uh.
- Mia's phone. Please leave
a message after the beep.
The next campsite
is two hours away.
- I got a better idea.
- Let me check
if there are any
available rooms.
- Mia, look.
- It's beautiful.
- You are in luck. We
just had a cancellation.
It's a room with
a king size bed.
- Okay.
Whoa!
Kyle,
this is crazy nice.
Wow. It's so beautiful.
This room is amazing!
This is so cool.
This is bigger than
my whole house.
This is so nice.
What's up here?
Oh my God.
It has
a claw-foot tub.
I love claw-foot tu.
Oh, and a nice cozy robe.
Oh, that's so nice.
Hey, do you mind if I
take a bath before dinner?
- No, of course not.
I'll go call my parents
and get us a table.
- Okay.
Hi, Mrs. Rothswell.
I know, I know.
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to scare you.
Yeah, Yeah, I'm fine.
No. No, I- I haven't
found her yet.
Yeah. Yeah, it's still ticking.
Sorry, I dozed off.
- All too much excitement
for one day, I guess.
Nice dress by the way.
- Thank you.
- I- I- I wasn't sure
what you wanted, so.
- Thanks.
- So, uh, listen, uh,
before we go home tomorrow,
maybe we could do
some site-seeing,
go to a nice restaurant-
- Home?
No, I can't go home. I
have to keep looking.
- For what? I mean, we found
all the names on the list.
- Yeah, yeah, but maybe I
made a mistake or something.
- You can't be serious?
Mia, listen, you
have to go home.
You need this operation.
This isn't some kinda game.
- I know, but I have
to keep looking.
- You can't keep putting
your life on the line
looking for someone who,
who might not wanna be found.
You've done your best, Mia.
I'm sorry.
- I know. You're right.
But I just wanna
look her in the eyes
and I wanna ask her
why she didn't keep me.
Ask her how she
could just abandon me
and act like I
never even existed.
- Well, maybe she did it
because it was best for you.
Maybe she thought that
you were better off
with someone else.
- You don't understand.
- No, you don't understand.
You know, maybe if you stopped
obsessing over some woman
who did nothing but
give birth to you,
you'd actually start
turning your attention
to the people who
really care about you.
- Kyle.
I might be wrong, but I
need to see this through.
Just gimme three days
and if I don't find her,
I will go home and
have the surgery.
I promise.
- Three days, Mia.
No more.
- And if anything goes wrong.
- Hey.
- If anything goes wrong,
I'll see you on Venus.
Good morning.
- Morning.
- Sorry, I didn't
hear you get up.
- Oh no, I didn't
wanna wake you up.
Hey, so I've been thinking
a lot about your mother.
And Mia, look at
your mom's signature.
What does it say?
- It says Maria Astilleros.
- Or what if it said
Maria Ostilleros?
Look, what if the A
was actually like an O
and they just mistyped it?
Oh, then I want you
to look at this.
Open it.
- It's the same as my necklace.
- It's from that small town.
And I looked it up and there's
a lot of Maria Ostilleros',
but there's only one
that lives near there.
- Oh my God.
- And I just found an address.
You know, we still have
two more hours to go.
Why don't you get some sleep?
If I see anything really
interesting, I'll wake you up.
All right?
Hey, you gotta see this.
Hey. Hey, Mia.
Mia. Mia?
Hey, Mia? Mia!
Can I please get an
update on Amelia Faith?
- Excuse me? Are
you Amelia's friend?
- Yeah. Is she okay?
- She's stable for now.
However, her heart is very weak.
I understand she's scared
of undergoing the surgery,
but if she doesn't, she'll die.
- How, how long do you
think she can hold out for?
She's supposed to get the
surgery when we get home.
- She could last
a month, a week.
We just don't know.
But definitely she can't
fly in her condition.
- Can I see her?
- I need you to convince her
to let us do the surgery.
- Yeah. Yeah, sure, of course.
- Could you
take her ID to the nurse
so they can fill
out the paperwork?
- Yeah.
- Kyle? Please,
you have to help me.
- Why is your
ticket only one-way?
You never intended on having
that surgery, did you?
What was your plan, exactly?
You just keep going
until you find her?
Waste away until
you do. If you do.
- No. Kyle.
- No. Tell me it isn't true.
Please tell me you're
gonna have that surgery.
Dammit, Mia.
You'd rather just give up
than risk what, exactly?
Having someone love you?
Or loving someone yourself?
- You don't understand.
My heart has an expiration date.
- Then explain that to me.
- I don't want them
to open my heart
until I get to meet my mom.
- What about me? What about us?
- That is not fair.
I shouldn't have to
choose one of you.
- I- I can't do this.
- Kyle!
- Help! Help, help!
- Bro, check this.
- Bro, chill, I'm driving.
- Funniest
things I've seen in-
- I'm being serious.
- Just look at it.
- No, chill.
Oh!
- Hey.
- It's all coming back.
- I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I couldn't bring myself to
tell you, but it was me.
It was my phone.
I was totally wasted and
I showed you that video.
- And, and I looked at it.
And, and I tried to get
around that motorcycle.
It was an accident.
So you just gotta learn from it.
And, and forgive yourself.
- I'm sorry, Kyle.
- Yeah, me too, Josh.
Mia!
- Kyle.
- I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry too.
- I can't even begin to imagine.
But I wanna be by your side,
and I don't care if, if it's
for an hour or, or for years.
It don't matter. As
long as I'm with you.
I'm gonna take you
to meet your mom.
- Really? Aw.
I just need a couple of hours.
- But I need you to
promise me something.
I need you to promise
me that you'll fight.
That we'll, we'll come back
and you'll have the operation
and you'll do everything you can
to get through this for us.
- Okay. Okay.
- Thank you.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- Ola?
- Hi.
- Hi. Can I help you?
- Yeah, I came all the
way from the United States
because I'm looking for my mom
and I was wondering if
maybe you recognize this.
Ola, Mama.
- Amelia.
- Right, one more thing,
then we'll head back.
- It's amazing.
- If things didn't
work out with your mom,
this was my backup plan.
- I waited for that
moment for so long
and I had so many questions,
but when I got to that door
today, none of it mattered.
All I could think about was you.
- Oh, and one more thing.
- My song?
- May I have this dance?
- Yes, you may.
- I'm scared.
- I'll be right
by your side, Mia.
- This is all your fault.
- I was never afraid to
die before I met you.
I don't wanna miss this.
- Mia? Mia!
No, no, no, no.
Mia? Mia?
Mia!
Some people change
your life forever.
Some people make you strive
to be a better person.
Some people help
you find yourself
right when you're
ready to give up.
Some people aren't invisible.
Now, someone
special once told me
there will always be
somebody somewhere
who is happy that you were born.
Well, this is it.
- Oh! Please, uh,
be careful driving.
Are you sure it's safe?
- Yes, it's not like this
is my first road trip, Mom.
- I am proud of you son.
You take care of yourself.
- Yeah.
- Okay. Get outta here.
You only got two weeks
to get to Boston, so.
You sure you can
drive this thing?
It's harder than it looks.
- I had a pretty good teacher.
- I thought my trip
to Spain was about my past,
but it was really
about my future.
To find someone who
makes my heart so full
that it could burst,
but in a good way.
I've always looked
at Venus as a place,
but it turns out my
Venus was a person
and not the person I
thought it would be.
One who made life
worth fighting for.
- No. Put your hands
on the steering wheel.
- Okay. This right here.
This is what it must
be like on Venus.