(INDISTINCT CHATTER AND LAUGHING)
CHILDREN: Ooh.
CHILDREN: (EXCLAIMING) Ooh.
And that was Richard Wilson.
We'd also like to thank Billy Rattree for his nativity scene.
(LAUGHING)
And next up is Jonathan Grant with a song for us all.
(CLAPPING)
I know how you do all those tricks, Wilson.
Dogs do tricks, Billy.
I do magic.
-Oh, yeah? -Yeah.
Billy Rattree, are you causing trouble again?
I'll get you, magic boy.
Back to your seat.
Will you show me how to do your magic?
M-magicians never tell their secrets.
But, but, if you were my assistant, you'd have to know how to do them.
Your assistant?
Sure. All the great magicians have assistants, you know.
You are a good magician.
I'll be the greatest magician in the whole world.
Someday.
Janis, get out my appointment book.
I want you to move my 11:00 to 11:30.
Oh, did that package arrive?
Came in this morning.
Great. Okay.
Change my lunch with the Turner people from 12:30 to 1:30.
Shift my 3:00 with Global to 4:00.
My 4:00 with National to 5:00.
And my 5:00 with Worldwide to 5:30.
Thanks, Janis.
(GRUNTING)
What d'you get 'em? Barbells?
That is a custom-made cappuccino machine.
Oh.
Merry Christmas.
(GASPS) Oh, thank you.
I found it in an antique shop.
I thought because you used to do magic...
The shopkeeper said it belonged to some old magician.
Carter the Great, I think he said.
Good morning.
Like the outfit?
Mother let me open one present early.
Er, Janis.
Thank you.
Oh, it came.
Yeah. Arrived from Italy this morning.
Oh, daddy is going to love this.
You aren't thinking of wearing that with your wedding tux, are you?
No. No, no. It's a gift from Janis.
Oh, good.
Guess what? I found the perfect place.
For?
For the wedding.
Oh.
Oh, oh, right.
You look tired.
You know, I wish you'd just jet up
to the country house with us now instead of driving.
Planes are a far safer form of travel than cars.
When they figure out how to make a plane
out of whatever they make the black box from, then I'll fly.
(SIGHS)
Why don't you just come up with me?
It'll only take four or, five hours.
You know long drives make me nauseous.
Let me see the ring again.
(GASPS)
I wanna be the first one to put this ring on your finger.
Richard. Richard, don't be silly. Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
I had it on my finger when we tried it on in the jewellery store.
You only have to wait till Christmas.
Mmm, I can't wait to see daddy's face
when you stand up at the big dinner and you say...
GEORGE: Buttons.
Hi, daddy.
Your mother's down in the limo. I'll join you there.
Oh, okay.
I'll see you tonight, okay, pookie?
Bye.
Oh, there's a dossier on the Yamashitsu.
Familiarise yourself with the company.
I'm inviting some of their execs up for Christmas dinner.
Oh, they're gonna be there at the house?
Business doesn't stop for Christmas, Richard.
I wanna nail down this merger before the New Year.
(CHUCKLES)
I'll see you tonight then.
Shouldn't be too long.
Not if you were flying.
(SONG PLAYING ON RADIO) # Merry Christmas, baby
# You sure did treat me nice
# Merry Christmas, baby
# Bought me a diamond ring for Christmas
# Feel like I'm in paradise
# I feel mighty fine, oh
# Got music on my radio
# Feel mighty... #
(SPARKS CRACKLING)
Oh, no.
Oh, oh, oh. Not the roof.
(SCREAMS)
Please. Stop!
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
(METAL CLANGING)
MAN ON RADIO: If you think it's cold out there now, folks,
weatherman says it's gonna get worse tomorrow
with a big Canadian cold front moving in on us.
But, hey, if you're willing to brave the chill,
head down to the Slygo bar tonight
for the annual Christmas Talent Contest
and your host, with the most, wild Willy Williams.
Right now here's a little music to keep you warm.
You a magician or something?
Er, no.
Er, as a kid.
It was a gift.
Can you, er, can you fix the top?
I need to get somewhere tonight.
That depends.
I bet you feel pretty damn important
driving that foreign car around.
It's a company car.
Maybe it's the fuse?
Well, if it was a Ford,
I bet you I'd have a fuse in stock now, wouldn't I? (CHUCKLES)
If I could just use your phone.
You gotta show me a trick first.
Look, I really need to get in touch with...
What's it gonna hurt?
You said you used to do magic, right?
Do I know you?
No.
Come on.
One little card trick.
It's Christmas.
Hey, this isn't one of them fake decks, is it?
They're your cards.
Oh, yeah, right.
Memorise the card and place it back in the deck.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Then you're just gonna do some fancy stuff that I'm not gonna see.
That's the general idea, yes.
If you're so magic, tell me my card.
The ten of diamonds.
-No. -It is so!
Phone box five miles down the road.
See! It is the ten of diamonds!
I only count five little diamonds on this here card.
One, two, three, four, five.
I'd say that makes it the five of diamonds, wouldn't you, Mandrake?
(BELL TINKLING)
Duty calls.
Hi, Gus.
Fill her up, Billy.
Where you headed?
Slygo.
Where the hell is that?
Forty miles north of here.
Can you give me a lift there?
BILLY: He's off duty.
Stay out of this.
I'm never off duty.
I have
$43.
Oh, it's at least a 60 buck cab ride.
Do you mind?
Do you take plastic?
The devil's business card, you mean? Never.
But, you can pay me the rest by getting my gas for me.
Deal.
Er, my car's in the garage. Do you mind getting my stuff out of the back?
Oh, okay. Let's see, it, er, comes to,
$350.
What?
The pump says $19.
Well, the balance is what you owe for the estimate on your car.
You looked under the hood for two minutes.
And then there's the little matter of the damages.
It's a pile of junk.
One man's junk is another man's nativity scene.
I'm not paying.
Fine. I've got your car.
Fine. I can't drive it anyway.
-GUS: (GROANS) -Fine.
I'm not open again until after New Year.
(SOFTLY) Fine.
(GROANING)
Giving somebody barbells for Christmas?
Let's go.
(ENGINE REVVING)
The name's Gus.
Richard.
Richard Wilson. Thank god you came along when you did, Gus.
Do you believe in God?
What?
You just thanked him a moment ago.
Well, it was sort of a figure of speech.
(PLAYING ON STEREO)
In the beginning, God created the Heaven and the Earth.
And the Earth was without form and void and darkness...
And he said I will seek that which was lost, and bring again that...
And after three days and three nights,
He came down from the mountain.
GUS: (RECITING ALONG) And the shepherds gathered at his feet.
-Then He said unto them... -(STEREO STOPS PLAYING)
Behold
Slygo.
(CHRISTMAS MUSIC PLAYING)
Merry Christmas, Officer Dunlop.
Same to you, Gus.
Have you asked Celia to go out yet?
No, not yet.
But, her mother asked me to the house for Christmas Eve dinner.
Wow.
I'll see you later, Gus.
Merry Christmas, Richard Wilson.
Same to you, Gus.
# It came upon a midnight clear A glorious song of old... #
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
Thank you.
Richard. Where are you?
RICHARD: Look, er, my car broke down and I'm stuck.
So I'm, I'm gonna get a room and rent a car in the morning.
OPERATOR: Please deposit 25 cents for an additional minute.
SARA: Richard? Hello? Listen, sweetie,
Okay. Well, listen, honey, I need to know about booking the hall.
Excuse me?
Do you have a quarter?
Yeah.
Er, could I borrow it?
I'll expect it back.
SARA: Hello?
OPERATOR: Please deposit 55 cents for an additional minute.
Fifty-five cents?
Look, um, I, I will call you when I get to my room.
Hello?
Richard?
Excuse me.
Where's the hotel office?
End of the bar.
Right.
Yeah?
I want to rent a room.
It's 43 a night.
MAN: Hey. Hey, can we get some service down over here?
(CHUCKLES)
I can't believe this. I, I...
I've lost, I've lost my damn wallet.
You take cheques, right?
You have ID?
Um, excuse me, I just told you I lost my wallet.
Yeah, don't give up the day job, boys.
Hey, let's hear it for the band, huh?
Weren't they confident? Huh?
Boo.
Come on.
Ah, yeah.
All right, folks, it's talent show time.
Lost?
No. I'm stuck here.
MC: Hear me on the radio today?
-(CHEERING) -I know the feeling.
I lost my wallet and I need 43 bucks to get a room.
MC: Settle down.
Well, don't look at me. You cleaned me out with that quarter.
MC: Huh? All right.
Do you have any special talents?
I'm sorry?
MC: All right!
It's what we all came for, folks, huh?
It's Slygo's annual Christmas talent show, huh?
Remember, folks, that, er, tonight's winner gets a crisp $100 bill, huh?
All right, yeah.
What exactly do you have to do to win that 100 bucks?
Fart into a balloon and play The Star Spangled Banner on the cheeks of your ass.
At least that's what won it last year.
MC: None. They're too busy screwing the sheep, huh?
-MAN: Boo. -MC: Come on.
Knock knock.
AUDIENCE: Who's there?
-MC: O J? -AUDIENCE: O J who?
MC: Where were you when they needed a jury?
Come on.
That's my sister, Celia.
She did that guy's hair in four minutes.
MC: She hails all the way from right here in Slygo.
Here you go.
-Sign up here. -MC: And she's class.
All right, folks, let's give a big hand, and I mean a big hand
for Big Judy.
Come on!
(WIND HOWLING)
Yeah, all right, folks, huh? Yeah, all right.
Hey, before we introduce our, our last act to you folks,
give it up for last year's winner, Billy Rattree. Huh?
Come on, yeah.
Has it been a year?
God, God ...
I'll get you, magic boy.
All right. Settle.
Your last act of the evening, folks, is a, er, musician.
He's from out of town and he needs the 100 bucks to pay for his hotel room here.
Ha, ha.
So here it is, your last act,
Richard Wilson. Come on!
Good luck.
Come on!
Good crowd.
That's, uh...
MAN: Sit down in front there, Billy.
...magician, actually.
I'm gonna need an assistant, someone from the audience.
Why? Can't you wipe yourself?
(LAUGHING)
How about you?
Yeah, you'd be perfect.
Ladies and gentlemen, how about a big hand for my brave assistant.
MAN: Yeah, come on.
-(ALL CLAMOURING) -Yeah, go on.
(CLAPPING)
That's it, don't be shy. Step right down.
Terrific. Thank you very much.
Have a seat.
There we go.
-MAN: You're good, Fred. -Terrific.
What's your name?
Fred.
Hello, Fred.
MAN: Attaboy, Fred.
Now, Fred, I need you to, uh, raise a finger for me, please.
Okay, now what I need you to do, Fred, is to raise a finger of your other hand, please.
Now place that finger in that hole.
Wonderful.
Okay. Now, Fred, the name of the game
is to keep your eye on the ball.
Okay? So come a little closer.
Here we go. Come a little closer.
A one, a two, a three. Which hand?
-Left. -Very good. Great.
Okay, now we're gonna go a little faster this time. All right?
Keep your eye on the ball.
A one, a two, a three. Which hand?
Right.
Wrong.
But, close.
So we'll give you a little bit more to go for this time. Okay, Fred?
Keep your eye on the ball.
Remember, what do you need to do, Fred?
Keep my eye on the toilet paper ball.
Terrific. Okay, here we go.
A one, a two, a three. Which hand.
Right.
Almost. But, not quite.
So I'll tell you what. This time we're gonna give you the "big kahuna".
You know what that means?
No, I don't study Hawaiian.
That's all right, Fred, neither do I.
All right. Here we go.
One last time, Fred. What do we need to do?
Finding the giant toilet paper ball.
That's exactly right.
Okay, here we go.
A one, a two, a three.
Which hand?
Both?
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
I guess we can say that this trick
went over your head.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
Ladies and gentlemen, how about a big hand for my assistant, Fred?
Thank you very much, Fred.
Thank you all.
Hey, hey, yeah, all right.
All right, the ballots are in and it's time to announce
the three finalists for tonight's talent show, huh?
Our first finalist:
Juggling Dave!
(DRUMROLL)
Big Judy, the glass eater! Huh?
Yeah! Yeah!
And the magician guy.
Yes.
Okay, finalists.
Okay. Now, by applause,
The winner: Big Judy!
-Here's your 100 bucks. -(BOOING)
What?
Hey, hey, my decision's final.
What? She ate glass! Come on!
Okay, no line dancing for a week. Huh?
Wanna play hard ball?
Tough luck.
Well, she did eat glass.
Going home for the holidays?
I wish.
With my fiancée's family.
She's not technically my fiancée.
Sh, she will be in two days.
It's a long story.
I just live, er, 20 minutes away.
If you wanna come there and crash for the night?
Thanks, but, I'll figure something out.
Well... (CHUCKLES)
You can't sleep out here.
20 minutes from here you say?
Yeah. My brother's coming to pick me up.
(CAR RUMBLING)
Thanks, Fred.
Hey, it's Christmas.
-So they say. -(HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(HORN HONKS)
Let's go, bro! It's almost pumpkin time.
Dennis, this is Richard.
He's coming home with us.
(MUSIC AND CAR TURN OFF)
Did you ask dad?
Just open the trunk, Dennis.
What you got in here? Barbells?
Dad's gonna be torqued, man.
"Torqued?"
Look, if this is gonna be a problem...
There's no problem.
Well, I don't wanna be an inconvenience.
Especially to someone who's gonna be torqued.
He won't even know you're there.
Well, what if he's up late catching a movie or, something?
He doesn't watch TV.
Not since he blew a hole in it with the shotgun.
Relax. Relax.
Er, he just mad at Phil Donahue
about the show where he wore a dress.
Who didn't shoot their TV that day?
You want him to stay the night?
Dennis.
You either drive us home,
or I will tell dad that you got your girlfriend pregnant,
and that she's shacked up with you in the basement.
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
(HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(LOUDLY) So how long have you been a magician?
Uh, I'm not.
I'm an executive with the Billings Group.
(GRUNTING)
Well, you were just great up on stage tonight.
Just great.
Thanks.
(MUSIC STOPS)
That's my sister. Celia.
(SNOW BLOWER RUMBLING)
Oh, shit, dad's up.
(ENGINE TURNS OFF)
(SHOUTS)
(GROANING)
Dad, this is Richard.
He needs a place to stay for the night.
Merry Christmas, sir.
Oh, fuck this.
-(ENGINE STARTS) -(GROANING)
What did he say?
You remind him of Donahue.
MOM: ...Jimmy.
Say, "Jimmy".
I thought you said your dad would be sleeping.
-He probably heard the turkey outside. -Say, "Jimmy".
I didn't catch what language he was speaking.
(CLICKING TONGUE)
That's because it's his own language.
Is there a phone I could use anywhere?
Yeah, but, who are you gonna call this late?
-My, er, fiancée. -(WHISTLES)
Jimmy.
Hi, mom.
Oh, Freddie. I was getting worried.
It's almost midnight.
Mom, this is Richard.
Oh, one of Freddie's school chums?
(CHIRPING)
I graduated ten years ago.
Are you a fruitcake, man?
I'm sorry?
Richard's a magician, mom.
Freddie's cousin Yuri was a musician.
Terrible what happened to him.
Oboe accident.
Don't ask.
Richard needs a place to stay for the night,
so I'm gonna put him up in Nana's room.
I'm not putting anyone out, am I?
-She's dead. -I see.
Okay, but, don't stay up too late. It's a school night.
I'm thirty.
Say, "Jimmy". Mmm.
She swears that she heard the budgie say Jimmy once.
She keeps trying to repeat this miracle.
They, er, keep it this way to remember.
Remember what?
Medical expenses.
(HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, uh,
Dennis.
Don't your parents mind that?
It's a welcome change, actually.
He, er, used to like the Bee Gees.
Just kidding.
You'll find that the tent muffles most of the sound.
At least it did when Nana was yelling for help.
I'm not kidding.
We, we didn't know anything until after dinner.
Anyway, the music will stop
when he and his sleaze bucket girlfriend start boffing.
Oh, you mean the one your father doesn't know is pregnant
and lives in the basement?
Yeah. Susan.
You see, she's stuck here because of the...
I'm sorry, stuck here because of what?
(GUNSHOT)
-(ENGINE RUMBLING) -(CLUCKING)
What the hell was that?
-What? -Sounded like a gunshot.
-No. -Yes.
No. It's just a snow blower backfiring.
Oh.
Well, look, you're probably beat.
Why don't you get some sleep
and we'll talk in the morning.
Yeah. I, uh, I need to get up early
and go into town, rent a car.
My, er, fiancee's expecting me.
Yeah.
My brother will have to drive you into town
because Susan smashed up my dad's car.
Fine.
See you in the morning.
Oh, well. Thanks again, Fred.
(CREAKING)
(SIGHS)
-(KNOCKING) -FRED: Richard?
(CREAKING)
Just one more thing.
Lock the door.
(CREAKING)
(CLUCKING)
(GUNSHOT)
Oh, shit.
What?
I have some good news and some bad news.
The bad news is that Susan took Dennis car out this morning
and she hasn't returned.
Great. What's the good news?
My sister cut and dyed your hair.
This,
this is crazy!
Why would she do this? It's...
it's only one side.
I'm guessing you were probably sleeping on the other.
This is good news?
Yes, it is good news.
It doesn't look
half bad.
You think this is funny?
Who, in their right mind,
comes into someone's room in the middle of the night and cuts their hair?
My sister Celia.
You see, she dreams of being a hair stylist
and when she sleep walks, she cuts hair.
Doesn't even remember doing it.
I told you to lock the door.
Pinch me.
-What? -Just pinch me.
Maybe I'm dreaming.
Ow.
Are you dreaming?
No.
(FOOTSTEPS)
Dad, you remember Richard?
(SHOUTS)
(DOOR BANGS CLOSE)
Hates your hair.
(CUCKOO CLOCK CHIMING)
Oh, I like your new dippity-do.
-Hey, mom, do I smell bacon? -(CHIRPING)
Freddie, you know Jimmy doesn't like the word "bacon".
Oh, now you've made me say ba... B-A-C-O-N.
I've found the perfect Christmas tree.
It just needs a little trimming.
Speaking of trims, Richard, Celia, Celia, Richard.
Oh, I did that to your hair.
I'm very sorry.
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
Go get 'em, dad!
Oh, no. Thank you. I never eat breakfast.
(GUNSHOT)
But, I am feeling a bit peckish.
I really, really need to use your phone.
There's one down the hall in the den.
(GUNSHOT)
Thanks for blowing it, Celia.
What did I do?
The guy's a magician.
A real magician?
Yeah. Saw him at the club last night.
(DIAL TONE)
(LINE RINGS)
SARA: Hello.
Sara?
Richard, where are you?
Outside of this town called Slygo.
I booked it.
-What? -The hall I was talking about.
Good. I'm in a bit of a situation here.
Oh, you found the phone.
Who's there with you?
What? No one.
But, I, I heard a woman's voice, Richard.
Just me here. I'm all alone. No one else but, me.
(WHISPERS) This is a private call.
Oh.
What do you think?
Food stations or, a fixed meal?
I'm all for it. Look, I'm at this house.
Sara?
Sara? Hello?
Hello?
Richard?
Hello!
Great, the phone just went dead.
Hmm, does that when it storms.
You know, my parents designed this room
after they went to Vegas on their second honeymoon.
Sometimes pictures just aren't enough.
Who's Sara?
My fiancee.
Why did you lie to her?
I didn't lie.
What, you mean about me being alone in the room?
She gets upset.
I dunno, it was just, it was more like a white lie, you know.
Oh, a white lie.
What colour's truth?
-"Truth?" -Yeah.
I don't know.
I think truth is a rainbow.
-Really? -Yes.
You know, they say when you see someone's true colours, you're really seeing them.
And to see someone's true colours, means to see the truth.
So truth must be many colours.
Don't you think?
I never thought about it.
You were probably too busy with work.
My father worked.
It was his job to put the snow in these snow bubbles.
And then he got replaced by a robot.
I guess no one's job's safe these days.
That's the truth.
This one is my favourite.
I could watch these for days.
They're like little windows into other worlds.
Fred said you're a magician.
Yeah. Well, used to be.
Oh. How do you stop being magic?
You ask a lot of questions.
How else do you get a lot of answers?
Good point.
I bet you started as a kid, right?
Yeah, when I was around ten or, so.
That's what's great about being a kid.
You can dream about becoming whatever you want
and no one can tell you you can't 'cause you believe.
Doctor, astronaut, an Indian chief.
I mean think about, if no one ever grew up,
there'd be so many Indian chiefs.
Guess I, er, experienced your dream last night.
DAD: Celia!
Coming!
Can you do a magic show for my father?
I really can't stay.
Teach me, then.
-(MUMBLES) -(CHUCKLES)
(WIND HOWLING)
(LINE RINGS)
What?
OPERATOR: Collect call from a Mr Richard Wilson.
Will you accept the charge?
Richard?
Ah, yes! Er, George.
Er, Mr. Billings, sir.
-(GUNSHOT) -Where the hell are you?
Richard, the, the Yamashitsu executives are arriving here tonight.
I'll be there soon. It's just, uh...
(GUNSHOT)
(EXCLAIMING)
Help...
Richard?
...me.
Oh, God, he's gone again.
You didn't tell him anything, did you?
I told him about himself.
Oh.
Did you mention the curse?
He's going to teach me magic.
What? You?
(KETTLE HISSING)
'Cause Dad will never believe you having magical powers.
I'm the one who has to go to Paris, Fred.
Celia, we all want this curse to end.
Are you a little warmer now?
Yeah, thanks.
Good.
Er, Dennis.
Listen, could you run me back to town?
Yeah, you're gonna have to run.
Susan just wrapped my car around a stinking lamppost.
My gifts, my bags!
God damn curse! I was almost out of here!
-What happened? -I wiped out.
What the hell do you think happened, chucklebutt?
Who invited the Selsun blue guy?
Oh my God, my bags.
Hey, hey. Rachini Garabini.
We've gotta stop meeting like this.
Where are my presents?
Sorry, I didn't get you anything this year.
RICHARD: Wait!
Billy I need a ride.
Thousand bucks.
Or, a trick.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
Ow.
That's a hell of a fall, Richard.
Wow.
How are you? Are you okay?
I am in a circle of hell...
(SHOUTS) that Dante never even dreamed of.
Be that as it may,
Uh, my aunt and uncle are coming over for dinner.
-Yes. -They have a car.
Yes, they have a car.
Let's go inside and take care of you.
-Warm clothes? Warm clothes? -Get you warm.
FRED: No, it looks good.
Apparently it belonged to Liberace.
Besides, it's either that or you'll have to wear Dennis clothes.
Fine, fine.
So, how long will it take for my suit to dry?
Would a suit be "delicate", "permanent press" or "normal dry"?
Normal, I guess.
So as soon as your uncle gets here,
-you can give me a ride straight into town, right? -(DRYER BEEPING)
I have a confession to make.
I arranged with the MC that you would lose the contest.
After you knew I needed the money?
Well, I need your help to lift the curse.
"Curse?"
The curse of the...
wild turkey.
"The curse of the wild turkey?"
As long as the turkey is around our house, we, we can't leave.
In fact, we have to be back by midnight.
My nana put this curse on my dad.
They didn't get along.
But, my dad believes in magic.
Real magic.
And I thought you could convince him that you have powers,
then he'd believe that you can lift the curse.
You're serious?
I was thinking a magic show.
Something small, just to get him interested,
and then tell him that you'll lift the curse.
Look, Fred, I, I, I'm sorry about this family curse and all,
but, I've really gotta be getting back.
I, I, I've got Japanese executives coming over to discuss a possible merger.
I am announcing my engagement.
I am giving my father-in-law a cappuccino machine.
You can't exactly leave.
What do you mean, "Can't exactly leave"?
The curse is on anyone who stays in the house past midnight.
I can't even believe I am having this conversation.
Well, why do you think Susan can't leave?
She stayed over one night with Dennis, that was six months ago.
Now come on, it's worth a try.
For Celia's sake.
And what's she got to do with it?
She likes you.
She does?
What am I saying?
This is ridiculous. I don't even believe in curses.
You're still here, aren't you?
When's dinner, Mom. I'm starved.
As soon as Uncle Henrick and Aunt Bonnie arrive.
(MUMBLES)
He's not a Nazi.
I, er, think I'm gonna try to use that phone again.
Oh, lines are still down. That happens when it...
Storms. I know. I know.
Celia, I think it's time for the tree.
Fred, why don't you help your sister?
Maybe Richard can help me.
Uh, okay.
You let me know the minute that your
BOTH: uncle arrives.
Oh, maybe you'd better give him Dennis hat and coat.
RICHARD: Does everyone in the family believe in this curse?
We believe in the curse because my dad believes.
I love this sound.
It's like rain on a tin roof. It's soothing.
It soothes.
Love it.
You live in the city, right?
-Yeah. -Yes.
I love cities.
Lots of buildings.
Lots of people.
And lots of hair.
Ever since I can remember, I've wanted to the world's greatest hair stylist.
-Really? -Yes.
I wanted to be the world's greatest magician once.
Well, you still can be.
I don't think so.
How'd you and Sara meet?
Was it full of romance and mystery and...
No.
Uh, actually we met through George, er, Mr. Billings.
Her father, he's my boss.
Oh. Okay.
Does your family like her?
I, er, my parents were divorced when I was little.
Haven't seen my father in a long time.
I don't know where he is.
Really?
Mother died ten years ago.
This was supposed to be the first Christmas
I was gonna spend with the family in a long time.
I'm sorry you're in this mess with us.
Oh, no. Actually, I, I, I don't mind.
I, I always wanted to cut down the old Christmas tree.
Really?
Then you know what, Richard?
Here's your chance.
Do you always decorate the tree before you chop it down?
Well, you wouldn't buy a pair of shoes without trying them on, would you?
(CHUCKLING)
I'll let you do the honours.
On one condition.
Name it.
Teach me magic.
Well, you can't really learn magic quickly.
Oh, please, I have to try.
Just something simple.
For my father.
Okay, I'll show you one. But, just one, though.
Yes, yes!
Like it?
This is great.
Isn't it?
I fixed it up myself.
Does Paris have some special meaning?
It has the world's greatest hair stylists.
Even have my ticket.
Ready to fly, I guess.
Soon as the curse is lifted,
I'll be on my way.
Boy.
I really look stupid, don't I?
Depends on how you look at it.
Would you like me to work on it?
I, I don't think we have the time.
Well, I'm fast.
And I'll throw in a shave.
(BAND MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC ENDS)
How was that?
That was great.
It was good for me, too.
Okay.
My turn.
Show me the magic.
This is all you need.
(SOFTLY) Watch closely.
You're gonna teach me that?
It's easier than it looks.
It's the simplest things that fool us most, isn't it?
I used to spend hours in front of the mirror practising.
Then we have something in common.
Yeah. I guess we do.
You do it over and over again in front of the mirror
until you can't detect the magic.
The mirror never lies.
Oh, there's one more thing.
Before I show you how it's done,
I need you to take the magician's oath.
Oh, I know. Never reveal the secret.
-Never tell anyone. -Right.
But, you're telling me.
Don't tell anyone.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Paper over glass.
So when I lift the fore paper and the glass...
-Magic. -Magic.
You are wonderful.
Just wonderful, Richard.
It just takes practice.
I'll never reveal the secret.
There's hardly enough secrets left in the world
and people need to wonder, you know?
Yes.
She must be pretty and smart.
Yeah. Who?
Your fiancée.
Sara?
Yes. She is.
And you're in love with her?
Of course.
Did you feel it just grab you and shake you? Like...
That's what I think love should be like.
Sudden, unexpected.
Just like... (EXHALES)
Yeah.
Takes you by surprise.
It's like the opposite of magic, you know.
Now you don't see it, now you do.
DAD: Celia! (MUMBLES)
I'm getting dressed.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Merry Christmas.
Coo-ee. We're here.
Oh, yes. (MUMBLES)
Oh, Bonnie. (CHUCKLES)
And Henrick. (CHUCKLES)
Hello, Freddie.
It's Fred. Hi.
Nein.
Sorry we're late, but, Henry's Mercedes broke down again.
How did he get here?
I commandeered a taxi.
We had the Bible read to us by Charlton Heston.
It wasn't Heston. It was some guy sounding like God.
I wish it had been a longer trip.
I'd like to have heard the ending.
The hero dies.
No?
We thought that Dennis could drive us home after dinner.
Susan smashed up his car.
Then we will have to call the taxi later.
Phone's out.
You mean we might have to stay overnight?
God inhuman.
That nice Officer Mikey is coming over for Christmas dinner.
Is he really?
Then he could drive us back to town.
I have some good news and some bad news.
Not this again.
The good news is your suit's dry and my uncle's arrived.
The bad news is perhaps we should have used "delicate".
-And they took a cab. -(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
A cab?
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
(SHOUTS) No.
-(BIBLE PLAYING ON THE STEREO) -RICHARD: Hey! Wait!
No!
No! No!
(CRYING)
(CAR RUMBLING)
Evening.
Hello, officer.
You, uh,
you live around here?
No, actually I'm from out of... (SCREAMS)
-Shut up, puke. -"Puke?"
Yeah, puke.
Hey, you're that musician they told me about
from the bar last night, aren't you?
Magician, actually.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO)
Well, look at that.
Oh, that. Er, this is not my jacket.
Well, you can just save that for the judge, sonny.
What? You're making a big mistake.
I'm stranded here, you see?
Oh, you're stranded? (CHUCKLES)
Judge won't be back till after New Year's Eve, buddy.
Well, if you would just listen to me
you would understand that this is all a big mistake.
Yeah, I'm listening. I'm listening for a good reason to break in my new night stick.
-In you go. -(GROANS)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Merry Christmas, Mikey.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, Celia.
Merry Christmas, Mikey.
Now I don't wanna alarm anyone, but, I just apprehended a suspect down the road.
(GASPING)
(GROANING)
So, because of booking procedures,
I'll not be able to make, er, Christmas Eve dinner.
Well, maybe I'll make you a little doggie bag to go. Mmm?
Well, you know, I'm partial to your cooking, ma'am.
This is all so exciting, Mikey.
Ah, it's all in a day's work, ma'am. All in a day's work.
Hey, don't move, puke.
(GASPING AND SCREAMING)
Mikey.
Celia.
Step aside.
This man is a dangerous drug addict.
He's not dangerous.
I found contraband in his coat.
Hey, why is he wearing my jacket?
That your jacket?
No. No, mine's dark brown with, er... Never mind.
Richard is a guest, Mike.
He's a guest?
Yeah, guest.
Hmm.
(ALL GASPING)
Here we are.
DENNIS: A fine pig, ma.
FRED: Can you pass the white puffy substance?
This is lovely.
Oh, boy.
FRED: Uh, is this my beer or your beer?
Oh, everyone, wait for the blessing from nana.
AUNT BONNIE: Oh, yes, nana.
(MUMBLING)
ALL: Amen.
Oh, Susan, you do remember Henrick and Bonnie?
From our game night a few months back?
Sure. Who could forget the person you slaughtered in Monopoly?
Just a silly parlour game.
MOM: Bonnie was last year's Monopoly champ.
Could you pass the potatoes, please, Susan?
DENNIS: Hey, are there any bacon bits?
-(SQUAWKING) -DENNIS: Poor bird.
MOM: Dennis.
I'm sorry, Mom.
You'll forgive me when you open your present.
MOM: Oh.
Take a fucking picture, Uncle Horny.
Er, so, what kind of business are you in, er, horn... er, Richard?
FRED: He's a magician.
-MOM: Oh. -A musician?
No, a magician.
I heard, Freddie.
What instrument do you play, Richie?
Skin flute?
Piano.
AUNT BONNIE: I met Glenn Gould once.
Under very strange circumstances, I might add.
What, doing him on the tour bus?
AUNT BONNIE: Well, it was a rainy night in New York.
I was desperately trying to hail a cab on Park,
and when one finally came along,
who should run out and grab it before I can get in,
but, Glenn Gould.
One of the foremost pianists in the world.
Like Dennis. One of the foremost penises in the world.
Tell them what you did next, dear.
It doesn't matter.
These perogies are wonderful.
They're not perogies.
No, really, I think they would love to hear what you did next, dear.
I lost my head, that's all.
-DENNIS: What d'you do? -Nothing.
Come on. Tell them what you did.
I slammed the car door on his hands.
There, you satisfied?
There's lots more food.
Er, do you have any more of these, er, perogi things?
They aren't perogies.
I'll have more. After all, I am eating for two now.
What the hell did you kick me for?
(SHOUTS)
Oh, nothing, dear.
Er, more perogies?
I think police work must be so fascinating.
Your sense of satisfaction in crime stopping,
your sense of self-worth in serving your community.
Your sense of anxiety when Donut World runs out of Bavarian creams.
That reminds me of my time in the, er, Austrian Resistance.
We were holed up one whole night in a barmer's...
Er, er, farmer's barn.
(MUMBLES)
I was not a Nazi.
Hey, hey. Isn't it present time?
-CELIA: Yes. -MOM: Oh.
Yes, yes, we have to open them before midnight.
I am so anxious to find out what I got from Susan and Dennis.
We open our gifts on Christmas Eve.
We used to do that, too.
Oh.
I saved you the final Christmas ornament.
I, I don't want to interfere.
You're not interfering. You're part of the family, Richard.
At least temporarily.
The chicken shit should have just bit the bullet and flew up here in the first place.
Maybe we should call the police.
Or, a psychiatrist.
Oh.
Buttons.
Dennis.
AUNT BONNIE: I love presents. Ooh.
This is a good shape
Wow, thanks, Uncle Henrick.
Every boy needs a good pair of boots.
(MUMBLES)
DENNIS: Oh, more ammo.
I knew you were running a little low.
Thank you, Susan.
Open yours, ma.
Er, that...
That
looks Italian.
If I'm not mistaken, er, custom-made.
Oh, thank you, Susan.
AUNT BONNIE: Beautiful.
And Dennis.
Yes, officer. I believe he's in a town called
"Slowgo".
Right.
Mom,
Dad, everyone.
Uh...
Come here.
I wanna ask for Susan's hand in marriage.
Oh.
(GASPS)
UNCLE HENRICK: Mazel tov. Both of you.
MOM: (GASPS) It is wonderful.
Oh.
It is nice, isn't it?
(MUMBLES)
Hey, hey. Watch the stomach, watch the stomach.
Susan.
(MUMBLES)
This calls for a celebration.
Double espressos for everyone.
MAN: (ON RADIO) Radio 4-76. Come in, Mike.
This is 4-76.
Look, I will write a cheque for a $1,000, in your name,
to the Slygo Policemen's Benevolent Society
if you would just give me a lift.
I have an APB out for missing persons.
Look, all I need is a lift somewhere
so I can catch a ride home.
Now what would Celia think of that there, mister?
I don't know what you mean, Mike.
Well, I'm not stupid.
Well, let's not jump to any conclusions.
Look, there is nothing going on.
I'm engaged to someone else.
Sorry, big fellow.
No can do.
(CAR STARTS)
(SIREN BLARING)
I told you.
What?
The curse.
(WALTZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREAMING)
(WALTZ CONTINUES PLAYING)
May I cut in?
It was last dance.
Sorry.
Oh, I was practising.
I wish I had your touch.
Come sit here.
Right.
Well.
Put your hands on top of my hands.
Okay.
RICHARD: You need to relax.
Just
let it happen.
It should be second nature.
When you don't think about it,
you're free to enjoy it.
You're right.
The mirror never lies.
-Celia! -(GASPING)
I was just getting under the bed. I was just going to bed.
Did you, um, did you need something?
(MUMBLES)
Yes, it was a good day. Good night.
Oh, that was close.
Yes, it was.
Well, uh.
What?
I, uh, guess I should get back to my bed.
Yes. Okay.
Oh, Richard.
Yeah?
You might wanna put something in front of your door.
(SNORES)
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Good night.
Good night, Celia.
(TURKEY CLUCKING)
(GUNSHOTS)
UNCLE HENRICK: Didn't you have the key, liebchen?
Well, I thought you locked the door.
Any luck, dear?
Let it go.
Please, dear.
For everyone's sake.
(SIRENS BLARING)
(BIBLE PLAYING ON THE STEREO) Joyful is the man that findeth wisdom,
and the man that geteth...
Ha! That's a 'G' note, bonbon.
Oh, Richard.
What do you want me to make for you for breakfast?
Anything you like.
Uh, okay, er, how about some scrambled eggs and some...
You know the stuff that sizzles.
Sausage?
No. Uh.
It comes in strips
and crinkles when you fry it.
Oh, you mean bacon.
(SQUAWKING)
Oh, dear.
CELIA: Good morning.
-Morning. -Good morning.
Wish me luck.
(SOFTLY) Good luck.
Er, if I could have everyone's attention, please. Fred.
First of all, I'd like to apologise
to Uncle Henrick and Aunt Bonnie about their hair.
I'm sure you were shocked when you woke up this morning.
(WHISPERING) Looks so beautiful. I'm amazed.
And now something very special for my father.
Dad.
Magic.
There's a soft spot in the table somewhere.
(GASPING)
Magic. Magic.
-FRED: She did it. -(POLICE SIREN BLARING)
I saw how you did that. You just dropped the glass on to your lap there.
Dennis.
Well, you did.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
MOM: (SOFTLY) Oh, dear.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
I've got orders to get you into a cab and on your way home, Mr. Big and Tall.
Uh.
Listen, er, there's one more thing I, I, I just need to do.
No. Got my ord...
Five minutes.
Thank you, Richard.
Okay.
Some people are cynics.
Mmm-hmm.
(GASPING)
FRED: Magic. Magic. He did it, yeah.
Uncle Henrick.
-Dankeschoen. -Bitte schoen.
Susan, could I borrow your ring?
This good one?
Yeah, the good one.
Thanks. It's beautiful.
I know.
Uh, mother, would you mind going in the kitchen
and bringing me a wooden spoon, please?
Terrific.
Now, Dennis, would you mind holding this for me?
-Yeah. -Thanks.
Put it in your fist, concentrate on it. Okay?
And, Susan, could you, uh, hold on to this side, please?
And, Bonnie, would you hold on to that?
Terrific. Now we're all gonna count to three. Okay?
ALL: One, two, three.
Dennis, open your hand.
(GASPING)
Wow.
(APPLAUSE)
DAD: (MUMBLES)
(CONTINUES MUMBLING)
I'll try.
Okay, I'm gonna need a big box, two mirrors and some bird seed.
Okay, bring it over here.
# Jingle bells, jingle bells jingle all the way
# Oh, what fun it is to ride in a taxi cab today, hey...
Okay, this bag of potatoes is the turkey.
(GASPS)
Oldest trick in the book.
Gobble. Gobble gobble.
# ...Oh, what fun it is to hear the meter tick away #
(TICKING)
Come on in.
DENNIS: Oh, yeah.
Have a seat everyone.
Did you do this?
And now, for your magical enjoyment,
it is my pleasure to introduce to you
the magician,
Richard Wilson.
DENNIS: Yes.
(WHOOPING)
DENNIS: Go get 'em, Richie.
(OLD MOVIE MUSIC PLAYING)
DENNIS: Oh, my God.
Yes! Yes!
But, you only showed us one side. Let's see the other side.
-Ow. -Idiot.
Shut up, Dennis.
Well.
CELIA: (WHISPERS) You're such an arsehole.
-You did it. -Ah!
-UNCLE HENRICK: Wonderful. -He did it.
He did it. You rule.
AUNT BONNIE: He did it. He did it.
Oh, yeah.
Shh, shh, shh.
I...
(MUMBLES)
The curse.
The curse is officially lifted.
(CHEERING)
It's time to get going.
Thought the toilet paper ball was great.
Thanks.
Wah. Thanks, man.
SUSAN: Excellent.
You're a real magician, Richard.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas.
Wow.
Merry Christmas to you.
Hey, let's go.
You can open it later.
Celia, I...
You have to go.
Yeah.
Good luck.
You, too.
GUS: I couldn't bother you for something to nibble on for the road?
Richard.
What are you wearing?
And you, you changed your hair?
One side is
bluish.
I was probably sleeping on the other.
-What? -Nothing.
Oh. Well, I'm glad you're here.
Oh, thank you. For me?
Actually, that's for me.
Oh.
Cute.
Everybody's at the table already.
GEORGE: We're, we're very lucky that Richard's here.
He's afraid of flying.
I'm afraid to fly, too.
Richard's been studying up on everything there is to know about Yamashitsu.
Haven't you, Richard?
Yeah.
I think it's time.
For what?
Our announcement.
You have the ring, right?
(CLEARS THROAT) Everyone.
Richard has something he'd like to say.
Uh.
Yeah.
I wanna show you all something.
Would you please excuse me?
Larry, some more sake for our Japanese friends.
Why are you doing stupid tricks?
This is supposed to be special, Richard.
It's our first Christmas together.
This isn't Christmas.
This is a Board meeting.
Why didn't you make the announcement?
Sara,
I can't marry you.
What?
Richard, I've been planning this.
Sara.
Sara, please.
This would be a mistake for both of us.
A big mistake.
I fell in love with you for all the wrong reasons.
I know this because...
I know this because I've fallen in love with someone for no reason at all.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Get back to the table, both of you.
It's Christmas, for Christ's sake.
Richard just told me that he won't marry me.
What?
He's in love with someone else.
Where are you going?
You can't leave.
We haven't made the merger.
We didn't come here for business.
We came for Christmas.
But...
Gentlemen, come on. We can cut a deal here.
This merger's a natural.
Billings and Yamashitsu. Or, Yamashitsu and Billings, it doesn't matter.
It's a marriage made in heaven.
-Come on, gentlemen. -(HUMMING)
GEORGE: Here, here's what we'll do. If you want...
I can't remember the last time I had sushi.
Care to join me?
Where you headed, Gus?
Anywhere the customer wants.
Don't have any money.
Hey.
It's Christmas.
Yes, it is, Gus.
Yes, it is.
Hallelujah.
(CAR STARTS)
GEORGE: Oh, God.
(CUCKOO CLOCK CHIMES)
(MUMBLES)
UNCLE HENRICK: Yes, yes.
What a good idea.
Oh, Celia, we're all going on vacation, to Las Vegas.
I'm going to Paris.
Dad,
I've wanted this since I was a baby.
I've dreamed about it.
Please give me your blessing.
(MUMBLES)
I love you.
(GRUNTS)
Pleasure.
Bye.
Bye, Mom. Bye, Dad.
I love you all!
-We love you. -Love you, too.
-DENNIS: See you, kid. -MOM: Bon voyage.
DENNIS: Bye, sis.
UNCLE HENRICK: Goodbye.
Take care.
RICHARD AND GUS: # Four calling cards Three French hens
# Two turtle gloves
# And a cartilage in my left knee #
Oh, oh, boy. Am I glad you guys came along.
I'm stuck.
I need a lift.
Gee, I think I saw a call box about ten miles down the road.
Look, Richie, I liked your damn tricks, okay?
Dogs do tricks, Billy.
I do magic.
RICHARD AND GUS: (CONTINUE SINGING)
# ...Gathering winter fuel #
-Thanks, Gus. -Merry Christmas.
Same to you.
What are you doing back?
Where's Celia?
Ah.
She went into town to catch the last bus to the city.
She's on her way to Paris, Richard.
What?
I have to stop her.
I have an idea.
(MUMBLES)
-Bye, Mikey. -Goodbye, Celia.
Celia!
Stop the bus.
(SCREAMS)
(CRASHING)
(EVERYDAY WILL BE LIKE A HOLIDAY PLAYING)