When shall we three meet again,
in thunder, lightning, or in rain?
- in thunder, lightning,
- Thunder, lightning,
in thunder, lightning, or in rain?
When shall we three meet again?
Open locks, whoever knocks.
- Open locks, whoever knocks.
- When shall we three meet again?
- In thunder, lightning or in rain.
- When the hurly burly's done.
When shall we three meet again?
In thunder, lightning, or in rain?
When the hurly burly's done.
- When the battle's lost.
- When shall we three meet again?
When the hurly burly's done.
In thunder, lightning, or in rain.
Fair is foul and foul fs fair.
- When the hurly burly's done.
- When the battle's lost.
When the hurly burly's done.
Fair is foul, and foul is fair.
When shall we three meet again?
In thunder, lighting, or in rain?
Fair is foul, and foul is fair.
Hover through the fog and filthy air.
Fair is foul and foul fs fair.
- Hover through the fog and filthy air.
- When the hurly burly's done.
Fair is foul, and foul is fair.
When the batfle's lost.
Hover through the fog and filthy air.
Open locks, whoever knocks.
When shall we three meet again?
- In thunder, lightning, or in rain?
-When they hurly burly's done.
Robbi?
When the hurly burly's done.
- When the battle's lost.
- Open locks, whoever knocks.
Robbi?
Open locks, whoever knocks.
- In thunder, lightning or in rain.
- Open locks, whoever knocks.
Open locks, whoever knocks.
Is that what...
That makes you happy, huh?
You fucking like that?
You better start fucking cooperating!
You fucking hear me?
Start fucking talking!
- When shall we two meet again?
- ll do, If do and I'l do.
Like a rat without a tail,
Il do and I'l do...
Hover through the fog and filthy air.
Hey, Jones, what's up?
So I guess I have to make
friends with the Lance Corporal.
Don't even expect me to be your friend,
cause we're on the same...
I'm friends with Lise, too.
I made friends with the Lance Corporal.
That's right, you smack ass.
You're trying to kiss my ass.
You want me to fucking give you
a good word, give you a good report.
He's not a good place to look,
because I've been friends with him
since the fucking first day
of hoot camp.
Open locks, whoever knocks.
1 don't know the answer
to your question.
I've been recommended about three
times out the last eight months.
Do you have a tank score?
That'll do it to you.
That'll do it to you!
You see, listen, listen, listen.
Hey, listen.
Will you listen for a second?
All this shit adds up.
Who's gonna guard the body, marine?
lam, ma'am.
Il go out there and get it.
Okay, I think that wraps things up.
We can take off.
Yes, ma'am.
We can get outta here now.
Roger that.
1 got non-rec'd on the next
eight months.
That's bullshit!
You know, they're probably...
I mean, sparks shot out of her
ass and everything.
Screw that, no way.
There's no sense
who got the better of who,
he's gonna be sitting in jail.
Yeah, now his life's fucked.
Him and Schrader.
He had that kinda stare
in his eye, too.
Schrader, you never knew
which way...
What was that guy
that used to be with 2-7?
What was his name, the crazy one?
No, the other crazy one.
That went down and faked the craziness.
Look, billet.
Yes, I availed of them
for the last year and a half,
two years.
- Squad leader?
- Yep.
And what did you get?
About four, four or five,
somewhere in there, average.
Four or five what?
- Four, five, six?
-I mean...
- Four, five what?
- Four, five, two?
- Four five, three?
- [don't know.
- Yeah, I was fucking wasted, man.
- And you sill got non-rec'd?
Did you get non-rec'd?
Mills, did you get non-rec'd?
For 4.5and 4.4 or five or
six or whatever you got?
Yeah.
You got non-rec'd?
Yep.
But what are we doing here now,
right now?
What do you train for every day?
Some third world fucking country.
We're protecting our interests.
No shit, but that doesn't...
-Yeah.
- Korea?
What the fuck do they have for us?
- Nothing.
Just cause I'm friends with...
There's no way you should even
trust anyone with that stuff.
Even Greg said I should
keep my guns out of his house.
Lance Corporal McCreary?
So who's gonna ride with him
back on base?
A, I don't want that in our house.
B, I don't feel like trying to
track your wife down...
looking for like maybe 1000
dollars worth of stuff...
Wear a bag though!
Is O'Hara the one that
fucking lives in my room?
Hey doc,
Il fuck anything that walks.
The day after y'all leave.
That's just like a ceremony
for all these racks.
You can pass,
you can drive a Hum-V.
They're gonna say Kank that,
you can do that later,
you're outta here.
And they got Phelps down
as a driver.
Recon my eyelids!
Me and you,
it'l probably be just me and you...
If Phelps goes on leave,
then I'l just slide ride
into that fucking Hum-V.
...it has been tabulated.
1 guess it has been higher
then what mine is.
It goes from your rifle range
to your pro and con.
So, open shoot today?
Combat shoot, combat course?
Stick your feet in there, sir.
You gentlemen
think this is a tea party?
Why don't you do some paperwork?
Yes, ma'am.
Why don't you get the
clipboard out of the there,
out of my vehicle, start on that.
- Sergeant?
- Yes, ma'am.
Why don't you keep an eye on him?
Marine, if you're tired,
maybe you should get some sleep.
Yes, ma'am.
This one girl that works in the back
of the bar, she's hot as hell.
Yes, ma'am.
Little sideshow for you,
with your drinks.
Back home at the bar they got...
give them the tip,
they all wear like,
old ties,
and like a tux setup.
Maybe give ‘em a tip,
they jump up and hit a bell
or whatever.
It's good to have a little
sideshow with your drinks.
Who's on the the range today?
I've had my fun,
you've had your fun...
You fucking like that?
Do you like that?
Huh?
You fucking like that?
Do you like that?
Me and this clown were
joking around...
like, with this dead Iraqi.
Itwas cool, it was great.
It was great to have a dead
Iraqi there.
It was awesome.
Alpha...Delta...Bravo.
On Johnson's bed,
that's just supposed to be water
but there's more piss stains
in the garage.
Johnson just
leaves all his stuff there.
I mean, why don't you leam...
So many people got divorced,
and just took everything.
I was like,
I'm getting a storage spot,
1 don't trust anybody's marriage.
Did he ever
get the TV back from Laura?
O'Hara, O'Hara...
Just let it go.
You know what he said to LeHood,
he went to pick up his orders,
yesterday, leave orders,
and he's screaming
at me for half an hour
for why the barracks messed up.
He's like, I'm a Lance Corporal,
you know?
Staring off into space.
Staring out into space.
But I don't know if you gotta pay,
usually they've got a sale on,
but I don't know.
I'm sure you could put on layaway
and still get the 10 percent off.
But most of the time if they
give you the deal,
you gotta buy it right out,
like my shotgun,
I had to buy, pay off
completely to get the deal.
Yeah, they said you
don't put it on layaway
you're not gonna get
the 10 percent off.
Ten percent off it was like
470 dollars.
Over and under, American Arms.
Oh yeah, overseas.
She had a baby right
before he left, the second one,
19 years old, she shacked up
with a guy from 3-7.
Went on leave to Idaho,
stayed there,
and now he's going to Okinawa,
and she's staying there for six months.
He can't get ahold of her,
and uh...
Scale of dragon, tooth of wolf.
Hark I am called.
Of the ravined salf sea shark.
Root of hemlock...
Gall of goat and slips of yew.
Like a helibroth...
Double, double, toil and trouble.
You can't see shit all day,
you're out there all day,
just freezing your ass off,
Alright, our next contestant is...
Mondo!
Mondo is our next contestant here.
Well, you know how
these scumbags are.
1 yanked him around a little bit.
Our shift's about to end,
are we gonna have to wait around here
for NIS to show up?
Well, yeah, one of you guys
is gonna have to wait around...
He hasn't said a word.
What time did y'all call your NIS,
did y'all call them right away?
Uh, we called an NIS...
Go on now Mondo, don't be shy.
They've seen it all before.
There's a crowd
Gathering round the courtyard
You see there's gonna be a babe
When the sun goes down
The baboon' blood.
Thrice the striped cat hath mewed.
Peace!
The charm's wound up!
Thrice, and once the
hedge pig whined...
In the poisoned entrails throw...
Do you guys know
who he was with?
I mean it looks like this guy's alone.
If he had somebody with him,
we didn't see anybody else.
I don't know, that fucker
looks all disoriented.
1 think there's something
wrong with him,
he hasn't said a word.
Oh, Mondo!
Now we know why they call him Mondo!
That's her blood all over him?
Is that her blood all over?
Yeah, I'm assuming.
1 didn't see the cuts on her,
but she's got blood on...
He hit her a few times on the head,
there's some...
she looks like she's got blood
coming out of her head.
Hey man, show ‘em your boner!
What do you think, Billy?
Feel free to make sure
that it is a bulge,
and not a roll of toilet paper.
Alright, that was... Mondo!
Show 'em your boner!
And next, coming to us from the
great state of Arkansas is Jim!
Pretty open area out here though.
Right now...
Stupid motherfucker
couldn't even get a shovel.
Came out here with...
Now [ would advise you
to take my advice
I'm not saying same things twice
You better be a...
jail or something...
he's wasting his life away.
His life is just now fucked.
Maybe he's a smart man
and he's gonna find a great lawyer.
Anything wrong...
...claim he's mental or something.
- Yeah, of course.
-Butit's only...
Yeah, that's still...
even if you do that
you just do it in a plusher place.
You better believe that
You better believe that today
I'm gonna let you know
That I ain't gonna let you stay
Hey hey hey
[ain't got...
..a 14 is about as big as my arm.
-APXis uh 15?
-15.
The only thing,
they don't carry good pistols.
They don't carry Smith and Weston,
they don't carry any Sigs.
Just Colt and Kruger.
Kruger's got a big contract with them...
I just wanna get pissed tomorrow.
He's got a down home
country western bulge,
you can't wait to see.
Spencer...
show ‘em something!
[ guess they wanna see your tattoo,
and not your balls!
I believe one of the adults,
one of the judges
asked if it came in an adult size.
He was in the house with me,
but uh...
they just shot at his car.
Oh, here he comes, ladies!
Smaller handle...
Yeah, the one with
the smaller handle.
I wanna get that one.
Put it on layaway on the 15th
when the sale starts.
Can't put it on sale.
What an idiot, what the fuck was
he thinking trying to cover her up?
Thus do go about, about...
Sorry...
Thrice to thine and thrice to mine,
the 3 sisters hand in hand...
The cat hath mewed...
Thrice and once the
hedge-pig whined.
And thrice again to make...
Travelers of the sea and fand...
The 3 sisters hand in hand...
Travelers of the sea and fand.
Thrice to thine and thrice to mine.
Trice to thine...
Three sisters, hand in hand...
Is that a grade A Arkansas boner?
Yeah, I ain't cried once
in 28 years
But I musta been
savin' up all my tears
When that damn...
You like that?
Do you like that?
Do you like...
Do you fucking see this!
Do you like that, do you like that!
Do you like that!
Huh?
How's that fucking smell,
huh buddy?
Huh?
Fucking, you see what
you've fucking done?
Fucker.
Fucking like that?
Shoulda never been...
You like that?
Huh?
Do you like that?
And I know I should have
picked you out
About a 100 times before...
Slime ball.
Why the hell'd he drive with
her right in the car?
Anyone can look down and see him.
Truck or something.
Right in the back of the car.
...can do it anyways...
..how little she was...
...ver saw him again...
Okay...
1 don't recognize him.
From all the blood,
it looks like,
alot of the wounds might have
been on the back.
I'l show you all the patience...
You fucking like that!
Qur next contestant,
coming to us from parts unknown,
and a total combined bulge weight
of somewhere over 10 pounds.
Maybe she cheated on
him or something.
Sergeant?
Yes, ma'am.
This guys looks nuts, ma'am.
He doesn't know what's going on.
Get some back up, and call NIS.
1think he's a section A.
At least that's what he fold me.
It's Andy!
[ tell some sweet thing
Stepped into the rain
Say now boys you know
This one pretty thing
[ plan to keep...
Yes, ma'am.
Yeah, I got on the hook,
and I already
touched base with NIS.
They sure are taking their own
stinking time getting out here.
Double, double, toil and trouble.
Mirror, mirror.
Show his eyes,
and grieve his heart.
- Double, double, toil and trouble.
- Mirror, mirror.
My little spirit see...
Mirror mirror, on the wall.
Who's the fairest one of all?
Just like dark combat.
Shooting and popping off,
go down, sit down...
third Sunday.
So what else causes it?
Bad day at work or something?
He was over there digging
a shallow grave or something.
A shallow grave?
And then we seen him
cover up the body.
You guys have to rough him up
or anything? Just go for it.
Well, you know how these
guys are, scumbags.
And I mean,
I'm assuming that's his wife, so.
I doubt if anybody else
would be that mad at her.
..gun should go over
there in the hoot, sir...
Tell you the truth,
I kinda can't watt...
You take off, you stop,
you grab off to the side.
..these boys there,
they started beating the shit out of her.
He tried to scalp her,
but he didn't do a very good job.
Real nice night out here tonight.
I'm tired.
What are you gonna be
doing after this?
I don't know, what are you gonna do?
Depends.
Depends on what?
Hey, O'Hara...
- In a hard cell.
- Yeah.
He's still gonna do the time,
they ain't gonna ever let
you out of there.
Big house either way
you look at it.
They'll just kick your ass out.
He was trying to cover up.
Right in the back of the car.
Not the smartest guy.
I think everybody could see
if she was in the back seat,
1 don't know what he was thinking.
You would think this freak would
have stuck her in the trunk.
The temperature is 55 degrees,
the relative humidity 80%,
the barometer stand...
So she got porked
down right in the stomach.
- Son of a bitch, fucked her up man.
- Yeah.
With highs that will be in the upper 50s
and Jow 60s for most areas.
I'had a dream last night.
I was dreamt I was walking
through this big house.
It went on forever.
I walked through rooms
and rooms and rooms.
At the end, there was a door,
in the door there was a room.
An auditorium and a stage,
balconies of seats.
And I looked up to the top,
it was like nine stories high.
I walked up to the top of
the balconies to look down,
and it umed into a
space shuttle, flew away,
everybody was gone,
and I was gone.
Robbi?
I don't even
know this marine's name.
This way.
Dispatch, dispatch.
Sending, over.
We've got a Charlie Delta Jane Doe.
Roger that sir, out.
This body's
really starting to stink.
I don't know,
maybe she was cheating
on him or something.
I have no idea, but he tore her
pretty bad with that knife.
Obviously there's really something
wrong with this guy.
1 mean look at how he carried
the scene out there.
He's fucking out of it,
he's gone.
Yeah, I wouldn't think
she'd put up much of a fight,
I mean, considering the
size of that bad hoy there.
Good morning.
Morning.
What time is it?
7:30.
Where you going?
She's knows she's
gonna get money out of him.
Digging a grave out here
with an E-tool.
I mean, it's daylight out here.
Yeah.
I have a meeting.
I have a few meetings.
Pretty hot day.
Mhm.
Its really clear.
I'm assuming
that's probably his wife.
She was probably
cheating on him or something.
I'l call, and see what
everybody's up to?
Uh-huh.
Either that or she
gave up the fight.
Blood all over
the interior of the car.
A truck or something drives by,
it's pretty obvious.
I don't work until 4,
is it alright
if I stay around here?
Pretty noisy up at the barracks.
Okay.
Mirror mirror, on the wall.
Who's the fairest one of all?
She doesn't have any wounds
up front...
It couldn't
have been a pistol,
it didn't leave any exit
wounds, we know that.
Wonder if
she put up a fight or not.
I have no idea,
her hair looks pretty mangled.
She looks mangled overall.
He got her from behind.
Hey you guys know what a,
you know what made these wounds?
There isn't a reason
for somebody to be
out here like this
at this hour of the morning.
- I'm waiting until...
- This guy, his lifes over.
It really never, there
was never real travel
in the dream, it was just,
I was there all of a sudden,
and I knew I was in New
York for some reason.
- Rest in peace!
- So we just had no clue
where anything was at,
but we knew we had to be there...
Gall of goat and slips of yew.
..fo different places,
we'd eatin
bars or something.
- Rest in peace.
We bumped into that,
we kept on bumping
into people from my childhood...
- Peace!
The Charm's wound up!
...maybe high school, or kids
around the neighborhood.
And finally we ran into one guy,
and he said he had a lot
of room in his hotel, so...
You right now.
You fucking stupid motherfucker.
Fucking look at that pussy.
Look at that!
Come here!
It was probably his wife,
maybe it wasn't his wife,
maybe it was his sister, or...
It got out of hand I guess.
I don't know,
1 don't know how it came up...
- Rest in peace!
...we just knew each other.
So, we just left right away.
You know we talked to him, he said,
"You can stay here."
- My little spirit see.
We were like, "Fine."
She may have fought back.
You guess his wife or what?
She looks pretty small.
The Lord is my shepherd.
- So we finally
end up in the building we
were supposed to be in,
it was like a fever house...
- Rest in peace!
Goodness and
mercy shall follow me...
When we were walking up
there was just,
crowds of people walking toward us...
- With our Holy Charity.
-...sfraight onto us.
- Rest in peace!
Yeah we found him, he was
out there about 50 meters,
so we had alittle...
Obviously not the world's
smartest marine,
you know what I'm saying?
He give you any trouble
- Yeah.
-...when you first found him?
Yeah, I roughed him up a little bit.
1think this guy's a wise guy.
Now they're doing card tricks...
Thou anointeth my head with oi.
The other woman's just running around...
- My cup overflows.
...doing nick nacks and stuff.
The Lord is my shepherd.
Finally I just knew I
wasn't supposed to be there...
- He makes me lie down in green pastures.
-..50 I just left.
So that goodness and mercy
shall follow me.
And I finally made it back to the hotel room...
- Surely goodness and mercy shall.
-..and my friend from...
-..with roses...
-..this guy, that, we knew each other...
-...all the days of my life...
I shall dwell in the house of the Lord...
-...from back home or wherever
we knew each other.
-...Forever, Amen.
And then he was telling
us that the management
put more people in the
room for some reason.
Looks like he stabbed her a few times.
Huh?
They're coming
over there, they're trying
to figure out what's going on.
But they kinda like the
show that's going on.
So they're just staying with us.
Now we're just walking down the street.
- Rest in peace!
Alot of people coming with us,
so we didn't know what
to do, and we didn't have
any plans, but I said...
You fucking see this?
Do you fucking see this?
Huh?
You fucking like that don't you?
Get in there.
Get in there, motherfucker.
- I didn't to be with them...
- Rest in peace!
-..and I was trying to get away...
in a foggy cloud...
- Rest in peace!
You fucking hear me?
Where'd you find him?
He was over there digging
a shallow grave or something.
Stuff like that so...
Were they dressed up?
Just kinda casual,
just like a normal person.
- Lullaby...
...and goodnight...
- So they didn't have costumes?
No, not at all,
just regular jeans,
jacket, type of thing,
blue jeans, maybe slacks, and--
You fucking like that?
Huh?
Do you fucking like that?
- Surely goodness in mercy shall follow me.
-...my cup overflows...
I shall dwell on the house of the Lord.
- Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me.
-..and we came up on the back streets of...
He leaves me beside still waters.
.. Thou art with me.
-..there's a guy chewing gum...
- Restores my soul, my life.
- He just makes this big
bubble gum kite,
with all these different bubbles...
Do you like that?
Do you fucking like that?
Huh?
Get NIS on
the road, ASAP, over.
Roger that, out.
That's her blood all over?
It makes me sick,
boy, look at that shit.
Look at it.
Look at that shit!
Flinch, so I can fucking break your neck.
With all the blood on him...
Ithrew the wallet when
I was searching her,
I threw the wallet at the Captain's feet,
50 she's probably got the ID.
Hopefully she's got it.
Any ident...
What about the body?
Any ID on her?
-No.
- Got a ring on,
0 I imagine that's his wife.
She's bad, but...
He got all the violence out on her.
Now at this point there's just a lot...
- Forever.
-...of people on the streets...
Rest in peace!
... lost my friends from here.
I wonder how long
we've been out here today?
Start fucking talking!
Like it was just confusion,
like, we showed up late
for whatever it was.
Do you understand these rights?
Maybe you folks can stick around
for a little while and
make sure nothing comes up.
- Morning ma'am.
How about seeing some salutes?
Sure, ma'am.
How about seeing
some salutes, marines?
Yes, ma'am.
Dispatch,
dispatch...
- What's the word, ma'am?
-..Sergeant Little.
DOA.
- Roger that.
- We've got a Charlie Delta Jane Doe, over.
How long you guys been out here?
We discovered the suspect
at 05:50 this morning.
Hi, what can we do for
you this morning?
Something in the car you
might wanna check out.
NIS is really dragging ass.
Mhm.
Hark, I am called.
My little spirit see,
sits in a foggy cloud
and stays for me.
Morning, ma'am.
Lullaby...
and goodnight,
With roses...
Lullaby...
With lilies...
and goodnight...
Baby's sleeping...
With roses...
You make me sick.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say,
can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
You have the right to talk to a lawyer
and have him present with you
while you're being questioned.
If you can not afford to hire a lawyer,
one will be appointed to represent you
before any questioning if you wish one.
The Lord is my shepherd,
I shall not want.
He makes me lie down
in green pastures,
he leads me beside still waters.
He restores my soul.
He leads me past...
Thy rod and thy staff,
they comfort me.
Thou preparest a table before me
in the presence of my enemies.
-...In the presence of my enemies...
Thou preparest a table before me
in the presence of my enemies.
-...In the presence of my enemies...
In the presence of my enemies.
I shall dwell in the house
of the Lord forever,
Amen.
Rest in peace!
Anything you say, questioning,
if you wish one...
Covered through the fog and filthy air.
With roses bedight...
Rest in peace.
You have the right to remain silent.
Fucking move.
In the fucking car...
Don't fucking think about moving.
Don't do anything fucking stupid.
Fair is foul, and foul is fair.
- Rest in peace.
- Fair is foul, and foul is fair.
Rest in peace!
- Rest in peace!
- With the hand that opens
and the key that locks.
-...and the key that locks.
Put him in the car!
I'm talking to you.
Let's go!
Get your fucking ass up here.
Fucking let's go.
Come on!
Don't make a fucking stupid move.
Let's go!
Do you see this shit?
Get in there motherfucker.
Fucking see this?
Rest in peace!
With our Holy Chartty...
Can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
- Rest in peace!
- You have the right to
talk to a lawyer and...
You better start cooperating right now.
Who's the fairest one of all?
With roses bedight...
is baby's wee bed.
You better fucking
start coopering right now.
It gives you a fucking
hard on, doesn't it boy?
See this ma'am?
You wanna tell me
what's going on, marine?
You fucking hear?
Can you fucking hear?
Come on.
Get over there.
Come on, fucking move!
Move!
Hark, I am called.
My little spirt, see.
Sits in a foggy cloud and stays for me.
Right now!
You better start talking.
You hear me?
Maybe we should
take this marine for a little walk.
Yes, ma'am.
-Huh?
- Okay.
Okay Sergeant.
Sergeant!
Fuck.
You shithead, you wanna tell me
what a dead woman is
doing in your car?
You fucking hear the Captain?
Huh?
Fucking head down.
You're done moving!
Don't fucking move!
Toad that under cold stone,
days and nights hath 31.
Sweltered venom, sleeping got,
boil thou first within the
charmed pot.
Now, on your fucking face!
Get on your fucking face, now!
Get down, now!
Spread eagle!
Excuse me, ma'am,
you're not gonna believe this,
but we have a dead woman in the vehicle.
Take him down, Sergeant,
I'l cover you.
Peace, the charm is wound up.
Check it out Sergeant.
Yes, ma'am.
What's going on here, marine?
I said, what's going on here, marine?
Wanna tell me what you're doing out here?
Is that your vehicle over there?
Is that your vehicle?
When shall we three meet again?
Robbi?