[swing creaking]
[girl sobbing]
[blood dripping]
[sobbing continues]
♪ Ominous music ♪
[sniffles]
[chain clinking]
[grunting]
♪ Ominous music continues ♪
[girl gagging]
[swing creaking]
[clock ticking]
♪ Upbeat music ♪
WOMAN 1: Fifty hours.
WOMAN 2: Fifteen?
WOMAN 1: Fifty, 5-0.
[woman 2 sighs]
WOMAN 3:
Did you do at home?
WOMAN 1: Oh, hell no.
And thank God, you know...
WOMAN 3: Oh, that's right,
because you had the whole...
WOMAN 1:
Tear.
WOMAN 4:
Uh-huh, yep, same with my sister.
WOMAN 1:
Oh, and the little surgery to fix it?
WOMAN 4: Ugh.
WOMAN 1: Woof.
WOMAN 4:
Oh, and going to the bathroom after?
WOMAN 1:
Forget it. For months.
WOMAN 2:
I had a cyst on my vagina last week.
WOMAN 5:
Ugh. Size of a golf ball.
WOMAN 4:
Did they drain it?
WOMAN 2:
Longest needle I've ever seen.
- [balloon pops]
- Ha!
[giggles]
WOMAN 1:
But it'll all be worth it.
WOMAN 4: Mm-hmm, that's right.
WOMAN 5: Of course, it will be.
WOMAN 2:
And the best part is design superstar
Ella Patel herself will be doing
the nursery for me,
personally.
WOMAN 1: No.
WOMAN 4:
Stop it! Stop it!
WOMAN 1: No.
WOMAN 4: Shut up, shut up!
This is all I hear everywhere in town.
Ella Patel Designs, Ella Patel Design.
I told her
I didn't wanna know a thing
just as long
as there's a crib in there.
Years of trust built off
of holding each other's hair
back in college.
I saw your feature in Tribeza. Stunning.
Oh, my God, I almost died
when Shauna told me you'd be here.
I need you to do my lake house.
FIONA:
Yeah, well, she can't fit you in.
Our girl's graduated to resorts.
She just beat out
all the major firms.
- Hey, whose kid is...
- Oh!
- FIONA: Babe?
- Hey, are you okay?
Yeah. You wanna feel?
No, thank you.
It's a baby, El, not an alien.
Ella, when are you
and Aidan gonna have kids?
Ella, when are you and Aidan...
Ella doesn't want kids.
Why don't you want kids?
- Well...
- Yes, you do. You want kids.
Um...
- But family is everything.
- I have a family.
Don't worry, your clock will kick in.
I mean, what do you do all day
without kids?
♪ I get so close ♪
♪ When I'm climbing
through the valley ♪
[moaning]
♪ I feel it most ♪
And we should get that installed
as soon as possible
'cause I know that would
make them so happy.
Hi, Rosie. How you doing?
- My little Meal Angel.
- It's good to see you.
♪ Where forests grow ♪
♪ Colors dance for us so brightly ♪
♪ I found my home ♪
♪ Hear the ocean whisper to me ♪
No, no.
Children are the best thing
that will ever happen to you.
[branch snaps]
[boy screams]
- [body thuds]
- Oh my...
♪ Ominous music ♪
[knocking on door]
Hi, Ella.
I'm Dr. Webber.
Nice to meet you, Dr. Webber.
My husband, Aidan Patel,
speaks so highly of you.
Says that you are the best of the best.
We all love Aidan
down at the hospital.
Keeps things light.
[Ella chuckles]
I like him too.
So we're just here for your annual?
- ELLA: Yes.
- Okay.
[chair whirring]
Okay, we're gonna start
with your breast exam.
- Mm.
- Tender?
Just around my cycle.
Mm.
Um, my mother passed away
from breast cancer
when she was my age.
That's why Aidan wanted me
to start seeing you this year.
Hmm.
Go ahead and scoot down for me.
Are you, uh, taking
any kind of birth control?
I stopped taking birth control
when I was 35
'cause of the breast cancer thing.
DR. WEBBER:
Ah.
ELLA:
So we just use condoms.
[gel squelching]
[scraping]
Ugh.
[lid snaps shut]
Just a little pressure.
Are you and Aidan planning
on starting a family?
Just don't think
I'm quite ready yet.
All done. You can sit up now.
[groans softly]
[sighs]
Everything looks good.
But you're 37?
- Yes.
- Mm.
It's technically geriatric,
so, unfortunately, you don't get
to be not quite ready yet anymore.
Well, it's not that I'm not quite ready,
it's that I just actually
don't want children.
I never have.
I keep waiting for my clock
to start ticking.
I wake up every morning
hoping that today will be the day.
But it just hasn't happened.
I think I actually
don't have a clock.
- It's just...
- All women have a biological clock.
Maybe yours is just broken.
MAN:
Well, there she is.
- Ella Patel.
- Hey, Harvs.
I bought 'em out of every copy.
[Ella chuckles]
Sweet.
Hey, I got your order
already in the back.
Huh.
[camera shutter clicks]
[chuckles]
MAN 1: His what?
MAN 2: Femur.
MAN 1:
His what? What, what is that thing?
MAN 2:
Yeah, thigh bone.
MAN 1: No.
MAN 2: Right through his skin.
MAN 1:
But he's okay?
Oh yeah.
I mean, uh, emergency surgery
and he's gonna be in a cast
for a couple months,
but, uh,
you know kids,
they bounce back.
From your mouth to God's ears.
You, you get me anything this week?
[whispering] Hospital grade.
JOSEPH:
Oh.
[bag unzipping]
Pens.
I keep telling you,
we have way better swag now, Dad.
We have, uh, iPad cases, totes.
Oh! No, I like my pens.
JOSEPH/ELLA:
Are you kidding me?
This is caviar.
You brought him more pens.
- Wow.
- I cleared out, like, six boxes
of those things
from his office last week.
So? Oh, my God.
That looks great, what is that?
Beluga.
Beluga Caviar and pens.
What did I do to deserve this?
Mwah!
Well, we could all
be dead tomorrow.
Don't say that. You do not say...
What's wrong with you?
Pull your ears right now.
Pull your ears.
- There.
- Right.
That looks amazing, babe.
Look at the two of you,
you're both so wonderful.
You, you're the best cook I know.
And you have a beautiful home,
you have wonderful careers.
Look at you, you're crazy
about each other. Mm?
Only one thing, there's a couple
of empty chairs at the table.
Dad, can we not?
Can we just enjoy this meal?
Her mother and I,
we would've had more.
We would've had six,
we would've had seven.
We loved each other that much.
But, you know, she was sick,
she was too sick.
Not about how much
you love your spouse, Dad.
JOSEPH:
You know, her grandparents?
Ah, that's all they ever wanted,
they wanted a big family.
Can we not bring
Zadie and Bubbie into this?
Yeah. Ah, I'm sorry
you don't want to hear it.
I'm sorry
that makes you uncomfortable.
But really, their story
is also your story.
And it is a story
that is much bigger than you.
[chuckling] It's a story that started
when the fish first crawled
out of the sea.
It's a story about becoming primates,
becoming humans.
It's a story about your ancestors
who survived thousands of years.
Survived the camps.
For what, for it all to end
right now, with you?
- [thumps table]
- Dad.
Well, I'm just speaking reality.
There's not a lot of us left.
I just have to go.
[clock ticking]
AIDAN:
Just enjoy dinner, okay.
I don't want you getting riled up.
It's not good for your heart.
JOSEPH:
She's the reason my heart aches.
She's why my heart aches.
[sniffles]
[inhales deeply]
[Ella moans]
[kissing]
[drawer rattling]
[panting]
What's wrong?
What's happening?
[moaning]
We can't do this 'cause of your dad.
It's not just him.
It's everyone, everything, everywhere.
So fuck it.
Let's just do it.
Let's have one.
[Aidan scoffs]
Romantic.
Well, you want a family, so...
Not like this.
I want us both to want one
or I don't want one at all.
Well, then you're probably
shit out of luck, Aidan.
Yeah, I know, El.
We've been through this
a million times,
and every time I tell you,
as long as I get to be with you,
I'm happy, with or without kids.
I wish I believed that.
I really wish I believed that.
I don't know what else
you want me to say.
There's nothing to say.
There's nothing that people
haven't been saying
since we were married
10 years ago,
when I was fresh and shiny
and chock full of eggs.
I just... I-I am about
to be 38 years old, Aidan,
and I am out of time.
I'm out of time.
Why do you seem surprised by this?
We both knew this day was coming.
And there's no magic potion
out there that's gonna fix you.
Fix me?
Come on, El,
I didn't mean it like that.
You know that.
♪ Somber music ♪
DR. WEBER:
All women have a biological clock.
Maybe yours is just broken.
Broken?
As in, can be fixed?
Big article about it
in the journals recently.
Uh, been looked at as a fertility issue
for the first time.
Could be as simple
as a hormonal imbalance.
And if you find the right balance,
perhaps your clock
will start ticking after all.
New bio tech firm doing
a clinical trial this month.
Want me to see if I can get you in?
Thank you.
It's just, I have this huge job
that starts next week.
In person.
The dates are just...
DR. WEBER: Sure. Um, well, look.
I don't usually do this,
but you are Aidan's wife, so...
Here, here's my cell,
if you change your mind.
Huh.
[door closes]
AIDAN:
You almost left your portfolio.
ELLA:
Lifesaver.
AIDAN: Knock it out
of the park, gorgeous.
ELLA:
Thank you. Love you.
AIDAN:
I love you too.
Call me.
ELLA: I will.
[Ella chuckles]
[car door closes]
[seat belt clicks]
[phone line ringing]
ELLA: [over phone]
Hi, Michael.
So, I, um, I have some bad news.
Something's come up,
and I have to pull out
of the job.
I'm leaving the project.
I know.
I know you really took
a chance on me and...
No, this was my dream job.
Yes. I know how this looks
and the position it puts you in.
I'm so sorry.
♪ Foreboding music ♪
♪ foreboding music continues ♪
[knock on door]
Mm-hmm.
I know. It's insane.
Yeah, it's a lot.
You know what?
Don't even worry
about it right now.
Hi, I'm Dr. Simmons.
Ella Patel.
Well, I'm grateful you're here, Ella.
This is my study we're conducting,
and anyone who volunteers
their time is much appreciated.
Thank you.
Well, let me break down
the next 10 days for you
so that you know what to expect.
First off, my background is
in obstetrics and gynecology
with an emphasis on the cognitive side
of fertility issues.
I have seen too many women
like you over the years
just pulling their hair out, miserable,
because they don't want to have children.
But after hearing their stories
and knowing their medical history,
I have become 100 percent convinced
that this is
a fixable physiological issue.
The idea is simple.
It is the singular evolutionary goal
of a species to procreate.
That is our purpose, right?
- Right.
- Which says to me that
because you are otherwise
physically healthy,
your system is just a little off,
chemically, mentally.
No different than someone
with depression. You follow?
- Sure.
- So the whole goal of this trial
is to get you back realigned
with your natural state.
And what does that involve?
A multi-pronged approach.
We administer medication,
a newly engineered synthetic hormone...
- Synthetic?
- A regimen of pills.
The same naturally occurring hormones
that already exist in your body,
just formulated
to up your desire for kids.
And we pair that course
of treatment with CBT,
cognitive behavioral therapy.
Sorry, how much
can you really accomplish
with 10 days of therapy?
So we use a very targeted approach.
Intense, but effective.
And look, this trial is just
a jumping-off point.
Don't expect to leave here in 10 days
with baby fever.
I'm not a magician.
But we can refer you
to someone good after,
and you can continue
the work if you choose.
- Hmm.
- Hey.
You showed up today.
Hardest part is already over.
Tonight, just relax
and let modern medicine
do the rest.
Uh, did, uh,
Cara show you the dining room?
The food here
is actually really good.
Fresh.
Okay then, I will see you tomorrow.
Dr. Simmons.
I might be a tough case.
You're not a case to me, Ella.
You're a human being,
and the best kind, too.
What kind is that?
A woman.
[chuckles]
[door closes]
♪ Foreboding music ♪
♪ foreboding music continues ♪
[exhales]
I just don't want
the responsibility.
And... being constantly covered
in throw-up,
cleaning up shit.
Like, that's your reward?
That's if you even make it
through the birth.
DR. SIMMONS:
What do you mean by that?
"Make it through the birth."
Like, if you make it through
your pelvis separating,
or the vaginal cysts.
Clogged ducts, the blood, shit, pain.
DR. SIMMONS:
Well, there are meds for that.
[scoffs] Yeah.
Hard pass on a giant needle
in my spine.
DR. SIMMONS: You know,
it's highly unlikely for a woman to die
or suffer lasting side effects
in childbirth these days.
But why take the risk?
DR. SIMMONS: Have you ever considered
that you might have tokophobia?
Tokophobia?
A pathological fear of pregnancy.
I didn't know there was
a technical term for it,
but... yeah,
I'm terrified.
And yet you chose to come here
to conquer your fears.
That must mean a lot to your husband.
[chuckles]
He doesn't know that I'm here.
Oh.
Interesting. Why not?
Because what if it doesn't work?
Now, a diagnosis is good,
but it's meaningless
unless we uncover why your phobia exists.
What drives it.
Okay.
DR. SIMMONS:
Don't be nervous.
You're just gonna look at some cards
and tell me what you see.
ELLA:
Like a Rorschach test?
DR. SIMMONS:
Similar.
Some women see more than others,
but the amount doesn't mean anything.
Sit with them.
[exhales softly]
♪ Ominous music ♪
[exhales sharply]
Are you seeing this?
DR. SIMMONS:
Tell me what you're seeing.
A very tall woman.
DR. SIMMONS:
Anything else?
Oh.
DR. SIMMONS: Yes?
A pile of...
A-a family of... of dead bugs.
Spiders.
A grandfather clock.
Yeah.
Anything else?
Hmm.
No, nothing else.
What do they all mean?
We will get to the bottom
of that tomorrow.
[pills rattling]
[clock ticking]
[thud]
Well, I guess we should start
with the easy one.
Okay. Let's start with the easy one.
My dad has a massive
grandfather coffin in his living room.
It's a very important family heirloom,
our one and only.
DR. SIMMONS:
And why is it so important?
'Cause it's the one thing that they...
Finish that sentence?
Recovered from their home
after the war.
And who is they?
My grandparents.
Survivors. Birkenau.
That explains why you called it
a coffin a moment ago.
I didn't call it a coffin.
You called it a grandfather coffin.
Why do you think
it symbolizes death to you?
Is it possible that
what that clock symbolizes
to everyone else, survival, is meaningless
if you as an only child
make no heirs to pass it on to?
Perhaps it feels like
a physical representation
of the final resting place
of your family's storyline.
A coffin.
Okay.
And the spiders.
Uh, you said you saw a, a pile of...
A, a family of, uh, dead bugs.
Well, that one seems
pretty easy too now.
- Tell me.
- Well, that's how they did it.
They called us bugs
until people believed them.
You exterminate bugs. Insects.
And when they were done,
they just piled us.
One on top of the other.
It's uncomfortable
to talk about, isn't it?
Horrifying. The ultimate evil.
Why do you say that?
"The ultimate evil."
[chuckles]
Well, I hardly need to tell you.
Uh, six million...
Yeah, but there have been
far greater numbers,
genocides, than that.
So why do people consider
this one the worst?
Because things were good.
This happened amongst wealthy,
educated, cultured people.
Modern people,
between neighbors and friends,
husbands and wives,
doctors... and patients.
So deep down, people understand
that if it happened there and then,
it could happen here and now.
That scares the living shit out of them.
What one might be willing to do
to another human being
if society simply
gave them permission.
And you... struggle
with the concept of bringing
a child into a world like that.
Anyone who doesn't
isn't paying attention.
And the very tall woman?
No clue.
Okay.
Very good work today.
Now, before we end,
I want to talk to you about
the results of your blood work.
The numbers are what
would be considered low.
It won't be impossible
for you to get pregnant,
but in order to accelerate the process,
I would like to offer you
the option of an implant.
Implant?
We are finding it highly effective.
When?
On your last day, we would do
a simple procedure, painless,
Valium, and implant a small device
that would dispense additional hormones
in conjunction with the pills.
ELLA:
And how long does that have to stay in?
DR. SIMMONS: Well, the good news,
actually, is that, uh,
it's not meant to come out.
Permanent.
[clock ticking]
[ticking continues]
[slams book shut]
[ticking stops]
[clattering]
[ticking resumes]
[sighs]
[loud ticking]
[gears rattling]
[exhales]
WOMAN:
Day six?
Sorry.
Didn't mean to scare you.
[lighter clicks]
[chuckles]
Thank you.
Day five.
You?
Last night.
Get my implant in the morning.
Feels like graduation.
Don't worry.
It really does get easier
once you make it through The Tank.
Aah!
[gasping]
[bones crack]
Aah!
[phone line ringing]
AIDAN: [on phone]
You got service.
[chuckling] Aidan.
AIDAN:
What's wrong?
[sighs] Uh, I don't know. I just...
Rough day.
AIDAN:
Meetings not go well?
Yeah, no, they, they went well.
I just...
I just really wanted
to hear your voice.
AIDAN:
Yeah.
I don't think
I've ever gone this long
without talking to you...
since we met.
Yeah.
AIDAN:
I miss you.
Tell me.
Tell me what you'd do to me
if I were there right now.
The tank is systematic desensitization.
There's really nothing to be scared of.
We tailor every experience
to the individual
and whatever mental blocks
they're working to overcome.
♪ Foreboding music ♪
Water temp okay?
[water sloshing]
Yes.
DR. SIMMONS:
If it ever gets to be too much,
you just press that button right there
to release the hatch.
Any questions?
I just kinda...
DR. SIMMONS: Yep.
Get in and close.
You can set your robe on the bench.
[door closes]
♪ Foreboding music ♪
[water sloshing]
[breathing softly]
♪ Calm music ♪
[Ella chuckles]
[baby cries]
[Ella cries]
[whimpers]
[baby cries]
ELLA: Ah!
Hello,
I'm Dr. Elizabeth Simmons,
and today we'll be learning
to perform maintenance
on a working clock.
[groaning]
We'll be using a wrench, pliers,
and tweezers
to reset the cog
behind the pendulum.
[Ella groans]
Aah! Aah!
I wanna get out!
I need to get out! Help!
Let me out!
Dr. Simmons, let me out!
[door opens]
[gasps]
[soft growl]
[gasping]
[thud]
[muffled chatter]
- Oh God.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Do not try to stand up.
I examined you myself,
but the paramedics are
on their way just to be safe.
Ella, listen.
I understand that the tank
can be very traumatic,
but that is the whole point.
And the stronger the reaction,
the better the outcome.
And for what it's worth,
I thought you were magnificent in there.
You made it through the whole video.
Not many women do.
You were watching me?
Of course. This is a clinical study.
- We monitor everything.
- So you saw the...
- Who is she?
- Who is who?
- The woman.
- Annika?
No, no, the, the, the woman
who came at the end.
Yes, Annika.
- No, that was not her...
- The nurse who did your intake
the first...
I'm happy to show you.
Look. Look.
[Ella groaning]
ELLA:
Let me out!
Can somebody hear me?
Dr. Simmons, let me out!
Let me out!
ANNIKA:
Ms. Patel, are you okay?
[Ella gasping]
ANNIKA:
Ms. Patel. Ms...
Help! Somebody help us!
Dr. Simmons.
No. U-Uh...
No, I wanna go.
I wanna go home. I...
Yes, tomorrow.
No, I'm done
with this experimental bullshit.
May I remind you, Ella,
that this is a voluntary program
that you signed up for,
that women in pain sign up for.
Well, it doesn't work.
You just sat on this couch
and watched scenes from a birth
without even blinking.
The therapy fixes your fears,
and the hormones fix your desire.
It works.
Paramedics are downstairs.
If they take you in,
you can't come back.
Policy.
[door opens]
[pills rattling]
[door closes]
Implant can cause
some discomfort with insertion,
so... Valium.
Is everything alright?
[chuckles]
Yeah, I'm just gonna pass
on the pills.
Oh, I wouldn't recommend that.
Yeah, I'm still feeling a little...
From my fall.
And Dr. Simmons
said it'll be quick, so...
Okay.
She'll be in shortly.
[door opens]
[door closes]
♪ Ominous music ♪
[metallic clattering]
DR. SIMMONS: Deep breath.
[deep breaths]
[gasps]
You alright?
Fine.
Okay.
Two pills daily,
same time every day.
You'll be receiving check-in calls from me
to track your progress.
And wait at least three weeks
before you have intercourse, okay?
Okay.
Hey. That's it.
You did it. It's done.
I really believe in a couple of weeks,
you're gonna think coming here was
the best decision you ever made.
Thank you, Dr. Simmons.
[door slams shut]
♪ Ominous music ♪
[exhales]
[inhales deeply]
Aah!
Ah.
She's not real.
♪ Ominous music ♪
[heavy breathing]
[retching]
[groaning]
♪ Foreboding music ♪
[barks, growls]
[barking, growling continues]
AIDAN:
What are you barking at, you nut?
What's he doing?
AIDAN: What are you doing?
That's your mother, you lunatic.
Jesus, welcome home.
See what happens
when you leave us for too long?
We lose our goddamn minds.
Mm.
Hey, gorgeous.
Hi.
You okay?
Mm-hmm.
You feel a little clammy.
Oh. Just long drive.
Hmm.
Low blood sugar.
Gonna get something to eat.
Okay. Well, I want
to hear all about it.
- Mm-hmm.
- I've got a bottle coming to temp.
Mm.
[switch clicking]
DR. SIMMONS:
Hello. I'm Dr. Elizabeth Simmons.
And today, we'll be learning
to perform maintenance
on a working clock.
We will take the clock apart,
reassemble it,
and then put it in beat.
So that it will run reliably.
[whispering] I missed you.
[kisses]
[Ella chuckles]
[Ella moans]
[heavy breathing]
Wait.
I... Um,
I'm actually exhausted
from the week and the drive.
AIDAN:
Okay.
Whew. Is it hot in here?
AIDAN:
No.
I'm gonna get some water.
[lid opens]
[exhales]
Phew.
Ugh.
[eggshell cracks]
♪ Ominous music ♪
GROUP: [singing]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Ella ♪
[all cheering, applauding]
[blows]
Assholes.
[Shauna chuckles]
Help me.
- Yay!
- Woo!
SHAUNA:
So, when do you start the install?
On the resort?
Not quite sure.
SHAUNA: Okay, but you'll do
the nursery first, right?
Of course.
Ella, you've been saying that
for months.
You really don't have to do it
if you're too busy.
We completely understand.
No, no, absolutely.
I-I'm sorry.
Just superstition.
Superstition?
Jewish superstition.
We don't set up the nursery
until the very end.
Why?
Because the universe knows
when you're happy,
and it doesn't like that.
[scoffs] Jesus, El.
ELLA:
We have a vengeful god.
Who I very much don't believe in.
So, yes, I will start tomorrow.
Promise.
Well, you better.
Can I...
You wanna touch it?
ELLA:
Is that okay?
Yeah, of course.
[humming]
El?
♪ Ominous music ♪
Oh, my God.
Shauna, don't move.
SHAUNA:
What?
What is it?
Don't move.
I got you.
What?
ELLA:
Just stay still.
Don't move.
AIDAN:
El?
Ahh!
AIDAN: El! El!
I'm not feeling very good.
Ugh.
Oh.
[whispering] I think we have to go.
AIDAN:
Okay.
ELLA: I'll be back tomorrow...
SHAUNA: Wait.
ELLA:
...to start the nursery.
Thank you.
[sighs]
SHAUNA: Oh, okay, love you guys.
AIDAN: Love you.
FIONA: Is she okay?
AIDAN: Yeah, she's fine, she's fine.
Just tired.
SHAUNA:
Let me know what time...
Aidan.
Harvey?
HARVEY:
Yes, sweetheart?
Why'd you change everything around?
Huh?
I can't find anything.
Yeah, I didn't change a thing.
Harvey, this is where
the blues are.
I'm looking for sky blue.
This is where the blues are.
Yeah. Aisle three.
You're in the right spot.
Right. Sorry.
[phone buzzing]
HARVEY:
Hey, holler if you need me.
[buzzing]
Hello.
DR. SIMMONS:
Ella, how are you?
Dr. Simmons?
DR. SIMMONS:
It's your one-week check-in.
How are things going?
Right, yeah, good.
But...
DR. SIMMONS: But what?
I don't know. I'm not...
DR. SIMMONS: [chuckles]
Baby crazy.
I can feel the beginnings of it.
- DR. SIMMONS: Good.
- I can.
Which is so, so great.
DR. SIMMONS: Good.
It just...
I'm not quite there yet.
DR. SIMMONS: Give the hormones
a few months to fully kick in.
Thought you said I don't have
that kind of time.
DR. SIMMONS: Are you experiencing
any negative side effects?
Vertigo, insomnia?
If I was?
DR. SIMMONS:
We'd stop the meds immediately.
So I'd be disqualified.
DR. SIMMONS:
Well, it's not pass/fail, Ella.
This is your health we're talking about,
so I need you to be honest with me.
Are you experiencing any side effects?
Hot.
I'm hot.
DR. SIMMONS: Perfectly normal
as your body adjusts.
Okay, let's up your dosage.
300 milligrams per day,
that's truly the limit.
- Don't miss a dose.
- Okay.
DR. SIMMONS:
Call if anything changes.
- Otherwise, we'll talk next week.
- Okay.
DR. SIMMONS:
Oh, and Ella?
Yes?
DR. SIMMONS:
Happy birthday.
Thank you, Dr. Simmons.
♪ Ominous music ♪
[ratchet clicking]
DR. SIMMONS:
Hello.
I'm Dr. Elizabeth Simmons.
And today, we'll be learning
to perform maintenance
on a working clock.
We will take the clock apart,
reassemble it,
and then put it in beat
so that it will run...
We will be using a wrench, pliers,
and tweezers.
We will take the clock apart...
So that it will run reliably.
[knock on door]
SHAUNA: El?
Don't, don't, don't.
Yeah, yeah.
Don't, don't. I just...
I don't want you to see it yet.
SHAUNA:
Okay.
Wanna take a little walk with me?
Need to stretch my legs.
Yeah. Sure. One second.
[panting]
[groans]
[chuckles] No peeking.
SHAUNA:
Where's your crew?
ELLA:
This one's all me.
My gift.
SHAUNA: I cannot wait.
[keys jingling]
[phone buzzing]
- You want me to get it?
- Yeah.
Ah, unknown.
Uh, I'll take it. Here.
- Huh?
- I'll meet you in there.
Okay.
- Got it?
- I got it.
Dad, we're here.
Hello?
DR. SIMMONS:
Hi, Ella, Dr. Simmons here.
Hi.
DR. SIMMONS: Two-week check-in.
[clock ticking]
JOSEPH: They decided to take me off the Plavix,
and now he's decided
to put me on something called...
It's some... Uh, it's some empire.
AIDAN: Empire?
JOSEPH: Byzantine or something.
I don't know.
They come up with these ridiculous names.
[ticking continues]
AIDAN: Persantine.
JOSEPH: Persantine, yes.
AIDAN:
Okay, uh...
[muffled conversation]
Look, this is you and your mother.
You couldn't have been more than,
I don't know,
you're probably
two days old here.
She was so excited
about becoming a mother.
Which reminds me,
I have to call your mother back,
because she promised to bring me over
the whatchamacallit stuff
I love with the pistachios.
[laughing] I love it.
AIDAN: Okay.
JOSEPH: And... Oh, look at you here,
oh, my God, how cute you are!
My little flaterl.
AIDAN:
Flaterl?
My little butterfly,
my little butterfly.
And somebody's bar mitzvah,
I don't know whose.
And something... What's under here?
Oh, my God.
I have been looking
for this photograph for years.
Who is that?
What? Well, you...
Well, you know who this is.
- No, I don't.
- Yeah, this is your grandmother.
This is the first picture
that she had taken in America.
Well, it's understandable.
I mean, you don't recognize her
because she's only 80 pounds here.
She just came out of the camps.
[panting]
She's horrifying.
- What?
- El.
That woman lived a horror story.
Yeah, well, I never wanna hear
her story again.
Well, you can close your ears
and you can close your eyes,
but you can't outrun her.
We trace our line through the women,
through the matriarchs.
Her story is in you.
- It's your legacy.
- Quite the inheritance.
What?
Let me tell you something, Ella.
When somebody receives an inheritance,
they can either graciously accept
what's been given to them,
or they can piss it away.
They can just piss it away.
Don't do that.
- And you, my ungrateful child...
- Don't do that. Don't do that.
- ...you've chosen to just piss it away.
- Dad, stop. Just stop.
Stop, Dad.
- What about this? Us!
- No.
- Not that one. Not that one.
- Piss us...
- No!
- Piss us away.
The entire family line.
ELLA: [crying] No. Stop.
I'm trying, Dad.
[sniffles] Uh.
I promise I am trying.
[Ella crying]
DR. SIMMONS:
A regimen of pills.
The same naturally occurring hormones
that already exist in your body.
Just formulated to
up your desire for kids.
Don't miss a dose.
[gasps]
[clattering]
[keys jingling]
[groans]
[panting]
[keys jingling]
[knocking on door]
[doorbell ringing]
FIONA:
Jesus. Okay.
El?
I left something in the nursery.
[coughing]
SHAUNA:
El?
No, Shaun, it's not done yet.
- Don't come in here, it's not done yet!
- Don't touch me.
[gasps]
What the...
Oh, my God.
El. What is this?
Is this some kind of insane joke?
I told you not to come in here.
It's not ready yet.
No, I mean, what is this?
Just got confused.
Ella, I am due in a week.
Where am I gonna put him?
Where am I gonna put my son?
I just wanted him to bring him home.
Somewhere beautiful.
Somewhere safe!
What is going on with you?
Where did you go?
Where did my friend go?
I went t-to a place
so that I could catch up.
So that we could do this together.
Be moms together.
I just... needed a little bit of help
because this doesn't come naturally to me.
SHAUNA:
No, no, stop with that shit.
- I don't wanna hear it anymore.
- Hear what?
How it doesn't come naturally to you
when all you have to do
is spread your legs to make it happen.
That's how easy it could be for you.
That is something that I will never have
with the person that I love.
I don't get to have that.
And it hurts.
Oh.
It hurts.
Ohh!
Fi! Oh.
Fi. Fi, my water!
It's so beautiful.
What the hell are you doing?
What are you doing?
[muffled]
Stop it. Stop!
What is wrong with you?
Ella, what the fuck
is wrong with you?
- I wanna see it.
- Don't, don't touch me.
- Just let me see it!
- No! No!
Fi, get her out of here!
- ELLA: Give me the baby.
- No, get off of her!
Get off of her!
ELLA:
No, I just wanna see it!
[indiscernible shouting]
Let go of me!
[Shauna crying]
I just wanna see...
I just wanna see the baby.
FIONA: No! No!
ELLA:
Just let me see...
FIONA:
No.
[both grunting]
[panting]
[phone buzzing]
Dad, I can't.
JOSEPH: Ella?
[shaky breathing]
Dad?
JOSEPH: I fell.
Shit, stay right there.
I'm coming.
[phone line ringing]
JENNY: [on phone]
Dr. Patel's office.
Jenny, It's Ella.
JENNY: Oh, hi, Ella.
ELLA: Is Aidan there?
JENNY:
He's already in surgery.
ELLA: Can you have him call me as soon as he gets out?
JENNY: Yes, of course.
ELLA:
Dad?
Dad. Dad?
JOSEPH: Oh.
ELLA: Oh God.
JOSEPH: Oh. Aah.
ELLA: Oh.
Does your arm hurt?
JOSEPH: Yeah.
ELLA: Do you have chest pains?
JOSEPH: No, I don't.
ELLA: Where's the ambulance?
JOSEPH: No ambulance.
I didn't call an ambulance,
I called you.
ELLA:
What? Are you kidding me?
Dad, you can't do that,
you have to call 911.
JOSEPH: Don't get mad at me.
[clock ticking]
♪ Ominous music ♪
[muffled indiscernible chatter]
[continues indistinctly]
[muffled] Shut the fuck up!
DR. SIMMONS:
Hello.
I'm Dr. Elizabeth Simmons.
And today, we'll be learning
to perform maintenance
on a working clock.
We'll be using a wrench, pliers,
and tweezers
to reset the cog
behind the pendulum.
JOSEPH:
Ella, stop! What are you doing?
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
[glass shattering]
JOSEPH:
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
[panting]
I couldn't hear you, Dad.
What were you saying?
- AIDAN: El?
- Kitchen.
I tried you back
on my break, but...
Dad fell.
Is he okay?
El, what happened?
ELLA:
He's okay, I'm okay.
Just cut my hands on some glass.
Glass?
I... destroyed the grandfather clock.
I tore it to shreds.
I couldn't take it anymore. And he...
Oh, my God, Aidan, he's so mad at me.
It's okay. It's okay, it's okay.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's okay.
He's been a lot lately.
This, this was bound to happen.
You lost it for a minute.
Don't feel bad.
Will you check on him later?
Of course.
But let's get you
cleaned up first, okay?
- I wanna look at your hands.
- Okay.
Okay, come on.
It's okay.
Mm.
- Hey, gorgeous.
- Mm.
Hi.
I want a baby.
El, you can't have a baby
just to please him.
No. No, I don't care
what he says anymore.
I don't care what anybody says.
I just care about you
and us.
I want a baby with you, Aidan.
Look at my eyes.
You always said you'd be able
to tell when I was ready.
[chuckles]
But...
How long has it been?
Since I left?
- Two weeks.
- Mm-hmm.
You haven't let me near you since.
Longest we've ever gone.
It's driving me crazy.
[whispering] Give me a baby, Aidan.
Yeah?
Yeah.
[both moaning]
Aah! Fuck!
What?
- AIDAN: Oh!
- Oh!
AIDAN:
Fuck! Oh!
Oh God, there's,
there's something sharp in there!
Oh! Ow!
- What's in there?
- Oh! Oh, I...
El, what's in there?
Oh! I'm bleeding.
Here, here.
El, what are you doing?
Ice, I need ice!
I don't know, I don't know.
I'm so sorry. I-I...
- Gauze, I need...
- Oh!
There's a roll in my bag.
Okay. Um, uh...
[grunting]
[Aidan grunting, panting]
Where is this bag from?
[panting]
I don't know. Hospital swag.
No, this is their symbol.
Do you know these people?
Do you know what they're doing up there?
Aidan?
Aidan.
Don't be upset.
- No.
- Just-just listen to me.
I met Elizabeth at a convention.
She's cutting edge.
The best of the best.
That's what you said about Dr. Webber.
Who you sent me to
because you were worried
about breast cancer.
Right, Aidan?
That's why you sent me to her?
Because you were worried
about... breast cancer?
I just wanted the option
presented by someone objective.
Someone who could talk
to you objectively
so you could decide yourself
if you wanted to go.
Because I never wanted
to pressure you.
Well, aren't you a fucking hero?
[screams]
Oh, whoa!
Fuck you, Aidan!
Fuck you!
AIDAN:
Ella, where are you going?
I'm going to see the best of the best!
[tires squealing]
♪ Dramatic music ♪
- Simmons. Where is she?
- Ma'am, I can't...
Shit.
Elizabeth.
Elizabeth!
DR. SIMMONS:
Ella?
Take it out.
Now.
Why don't we, why don't we go
to my office to discuss...
No, we're not going to your office.
We're going to the exam room,
and you are gonna take
this goddamn implant out
right fucking now.
That implant is not meant to come out.
But it can come out, right?
No.
It would damage you permanently.
You would never be able to have children.
And what makes you think
I would care about that?
Because I know that you want them now.
Because my program works.
[sobs]
You want a baby.
[crying] I do.
I want a baby more than anything.
It's okay, Ella. It's okay.
Hey. It's okay.
It's okay.
Alright. Let's sit down.
This is great news.
So why all the tears?
Because I think I'm getting divorced.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
- So how am I going to...
- Honey.
You don't need a husband
to have a baby,
you just need sperm.
I'll set you up with an IVF specialist.
We'll get you pregnant in no time.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Okay.
Now let's go to my office,
get you all cleaned up.
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
- Okay?
[softly] Okay. Alright.
Okay. Alright.
Good, good, good.
No. It's not real.
Let's go to my office, Ella.
You said you weren't a magician,
but you are.
You have made me see things,
feel things.
Have they told you
about the side effects?
Of course, they haven't.
And we are so desperate
to be normal
that we are willing to white-knuckle it
through anything.
Hey.
It's okay.
It's not real.
The spiders, the clocks,
the insane tall woman.
My wanting children.
[crying]
That's a delusion too.
Isn't it?
What you're experiencing is
the most natural thing in the world.
[crying] No!
I was natural!
I am natural however I am!
Take it out.
Take it out now.
No.
Fine. I'll take it out myself.
Ella, Ella! No!
[speaking German]
Ah! Ah!
I can do whatever the fuck I want.
[groaning]
[gasps]
[screaming]
[panting]
[sirens wailing]
SHERIFF:
Ella Patel?
We got a runner!
♪ Dramatic music ♪
[sirens wailing]
[phone buzzing]
Never call me again.
AIDAN: It was me, Ella.
I called the cops.
What?
AIDAN: I went to check
on him like you asked.
Get out of the vehicle!
Put your hands in the air.
AIDAN:
I saw what you did.
You called the cops
because I-I destroyed a clock?
Are you kidding me, Dad,
you can't do that.
You have to call 911.
Don't be mad at me. Don't be mad.
What's the matter?
Are you in pain?
You came.
Of course. I came.
I thought this was it.
I saw them. I saw them all.
- Saw who?
- The whole family line,
even the fish that crawled out of the sea.
But they wouldn't have me,
because I'd done wrong,
I'd done you wrong.
I shouldn't have said what I said to you.
You're spending
your inheritance wisely
by telling a different story.
A story that's full of love and happiness.
- That's all that matters to me.
- Mm.
No.
JOSEPH: Yes!
No, that's not true.
JOSEPH: You know what?
You want to redo the kitchen,
redo the whole house.
I'll live in one
of your fabulous resorts
during construction.
All I care about is in my final years,
I'm together with you
and I see you happy.
- No, that's not fair.
- What?
I already gave it up.
- I gave it up. I...
[mouthing] Shut the fuck up!
[clock ticking]
[crying]
♪ Somber music ♪
[inaudible]
AIDAN:
Ella.
SHERIFF: I repeat, get out of the vehicle!
AIDAN: El?
El?
[indistinct police radio chatter]
[handcuffs clicking]
[sharp breath]
[water sloshing]
[splash]
♪ Somber music ♪
♪