>> It had been the worst summer
of my entire life.
Granny received this order
of two dozen chicks
the very day I finished
the sixth grade.
Most folks think
that baby chicks are cute
and fluffy, well they're not.
They bite.
It seems impossible, I know,
but they do it somehow,
the little devils.
They pick and peck and hurt.
They make you bleed.
>> Tiger, what's taking
you so long?
There you are.
About time you got back.
You got a lot to do before
your daddy gets home.
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> Okay, I've done ten
of them, mama.
Is the birthday
cake ready yet?
>> Corrina, you've asked me
that five times in
the last 20 minutes.
>> Sorry, mom.
>> Tiger can finish
the potatoes.
You go on upstairs
and wash your face.
You've got chocolate
around your mouth.
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> Tiger, are we gonna play
pin the tail on the donkey?
>> Not now, mama.
Maybe after supper.
>> Okay.
>> Like I said, the summer
was not getting off
to an auspicious start.
My granny taught me
that word.
As far back as I can remember,
she taught be a word a day.
"Auspicious" was one
of my favorites at the time.
>> After you finish,
you better check on them pigs.
It looks to me like
homer's off his feed.
>> Yes, ma'am.
Off course,
I was only 12 then,
and there was a whole lot
of things I didn't understand
about the world
the way I do now that I'm 13.
>> Oh, corrina.
>> Yes, maw?
>> You put on your party dress
and bring down some ribbons.
I'll fix your hair real nice.
>> Okay, mama.
>> It was my grannie's birthday
and we were preparing
for a celebration.
Nothing too exciting,
mind you, although I was looking
forward to that chocolate cake.
>> Oh, it looks really good,
corrina.
>> I got a present for you, ma.
I did you a picture.
>> Oh.
>> See, it's you and me, and
dorie Kay when we was little.
>> I almost forgot
about dorie Kay,
seeing as how she's not here.
It's really nice, corrina.
[ Car horn honks ]
>> Lonnie.
Lonnie, you're home.
Come inside. We got cake.
>> Mr. Thompson gave me
some of his special
camellias for your
mama's birthday.
>> Oh, they're so pretty.
That's gonna be a surprise,
Lonnie.
Come on, we got
a surprise for mama.
[ Laughs ]
>> Look, ma.
>> Oh.
>> Look what Lonnie brung you.
>> Oh, how lovely.
>> Uh, camellias, ain't they?
>> Louisiana lady camellias.
The only ones in
the whole world.
>> Mr. Thompson said
I could bring them home for
your special day, miss Jewel.
>> Well, thank you, Lonnie.
>> Sit down, daddy.
We've got a delicious meal
for this auspicious occasion.
>> Happy birthday to you,
happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear grandma,
[ Blows ]
[ Clapping ]
>> Saturday morning,
after a week of rain,
the sun finally
came out again.
But my life still seemed
to have a cloud over it.
Dull, dull, dull.
[ Car approaching ]
>> Then aunt dorie Kay came
to visit and everything changed.
Aunt dorie Kay.
>> Hi, sugar.
Oh, goodness.
Tiger Ann Parker,
let me get a look at you.
You are growing up into
such a young lady.
>> What are you doing here?
>> Well, I couldn't miss your
grannie's birthday, could I now?
>> Dorie Kay!
Dorie Kay! Dorie Kay!
>> Oh, corrina.
Whoa, you almost
knocked me over.
Hi.
>> Oh, goodness.
You're as pretty as a picture
in one of them lady's magazines.
>> Oh.
>> Isn't she, tiger,
isn't she pretty?
>> She sure is, mama.
>> Well, it's so nice
to see you, corrina.
>> I missed you.
>> Welcome, dorie Kay.
>> Why, thank you, Lonnie.
It's so nice to be here.
>> I wasn't expecting
to see you.
It's been a while.
>> Well, I thought I'd come
for your birthday, mama.
>> My birthday was yesterday.
>> Okay, come inside,
before you get them city clothes
all messed up.
>> Should I get your bags,
dorie Kay?
>> That would be lovely.
They're right in
the front seat there.
>> Oh, I like that one.
Look at her hat, and her hair,
and her hair looks kind of
like yours.
>> You have such
a good eye, tiger.
>> I like that one.
Can I cut that out?
>> Sure.
>> Okay.
[ Car approaching ]
>> What's that?
>> Well, it looks
like a truck to me.
Are you expecting
something from Mitchell's?
>> No, ma'am.
It must be a mistake.
>> Well, why don't
you go see, honey?
>> Excuse me, sirs, but do
you have the right house?
>> For the family of
Jewel Ramsey and Lonnie Parker?
>> That's our grandma and daddy.
That's US, that's US.
Would you like some iced tea?
>> What is that?
What's in there?
>> Hold on, corrina.
You best take that box back.
I didn't order anything
from Mitchell's.
>> According to this here paper,
ma'am, it was ordered
and paid for
by miss Doreen Kay Ramsey.
[ Laughs ]
>> What'd you get this for?
>> I got it for
your birthday, mama.
It's your present.
>> It's so big.
>> You didn't have
to get me nothing.
[ Shouting ]
>> Oh, you two.
My goodness.
>> That's mighty kind of you,
dorie Kay.
That musta cost you
a whole lot of money.
>> Oh, it didn't.
>> How do you get
the picture to come on?
>> You plug it in, corrina.
Look.
>> Nothing's happening.
>> Oh, you have
to turn the knob.
Tiger, would you like
to do the honors?
>> Yes.
This is the most exciting
moment of my entire life so far.
>> Right now, something never
before attempted on television,
an amazing test
of automatic washers
right here in our studio.
Here's Betty furness with
a trial of the washers.
>> Yes, tonight you're gonna
see a trial of four
of america's leading
automatic washers,
including the laundromat,
to see just how well they wash
and rinse your clothes.
These four ladies are four
leading club women from
the New York state
and New York City
federation of women's clubs.
And they're here
to represent you.
>> One, two, three.
>> Okay, tiger,
go get her, tiger.
[ Growling ]
>> Oh, corrina.
>> Well, that's the kind
of action we like to see
at Hollywood regional stadium.
Bang, out of the ring.
Out of his corner
came red Berry.
>> You spent too much.
>> I was trying to get you
something nice for your
birthday, something that
the whole family could enjoy.
>> Well, we sure could
have enjoyed a new toaster.
You should be
saving your money.
>> Well, I work hard,
and I spend sensibly.
>> I suppose it's sensible
to have a colored maid
that cleans your apartment
and cooks your meals.
>> It most certainly is, mama.
I mean, most days I wake up
at the crack of dawn, I'm not
home until late in the evening.
If I didn't have magnolia,
I'd never get
a home-cooked meal.
>> I don't have a maid
in my kitchen.
I best cook my own stew.
>> Mama, why do we have
to argue about everything?
[ Laughing ]
>> Tiger, stop that silliness.
I need you to help me here
in the kitchen.
Tiger, now come on in here.
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> You want to wrestle?
[ Laughs ]
>> Okay, now, you be good,
and you take care
of your mama, okay?
>> I will.
I'm gonna miss you, too.
>> I'll miss you, too.
>> Corrina, this is
the last one, honey.
>> Don't go.
>> I'll be right back, okay.
I'll see you real soon.
Oh, honey.
Now, you take care
of your mama, okay?
>> I will.
>> Corrina, you stop
you're crying.
You're gonna make me cry, too.
>> She'll be fine.
>> Bye.
>> It's okay, mama.
>> I miss her bad.
>> I wish we could go
and visit her in Baton Rouge.
It must be so exciting
living in a big city.
>> Uh-oh.
>> What's the matter, daddy?
>> Rain.
>> Mrs. Thompson said
it's a perfect day for a picnic.
>> Nope. It's gonna rain.
You hear them frogs?
>> No.
>> You gotta listen
more careful.
I...
I keep telling you, tiger,
if you watch and
you listen to the earth,
it talks to you.
>> It's never talked
to me, daddy.
>> Not talk like,
"how're you doing today?"
But it's different.
>> Different.
>> You know how spiders
build shorter and thicker
webs before a storm?
>> Yeah.
>> And grasshoppers, they chirp
loudest when it's hot?
>> I reckon that's true,
all right.
>> Them frogs, well, they croak
real loud right before a rain.
It's gonna rain, soon.
Listen good, tiger.
>> Nothing.
>> Don't worry,
one day you'll hear.
[ Thunder ]
>> Abby Lynn, when's your new
swimming pool gonna be ready?
>> Any day now, Jesse Wade.
>> We have
the sweetest new calf.
My daddy says that
I can keep her as a pet.
I'm calling her pansy.
>> We used to have a goat
named buttercup.
[ Laughing ]
>> Well, friends, as
the old saying goes,
"if you want to make god laugh,
tell him your plans."
[ Chuckling ]
>> Thank you, sister arlette,
for arranging
this impromptu recital.
You children sing with
the voices of angels.
And when those sweet voices
reach heaven, well I know that
the rains will cease,
so we can enjoy our picnic.
>> Amen, amen.
>> Stand up, stand up
for Jesus
ye soldiers of the cross
let tyre's royal banner
it must not suffer loss
from victory unto victory
his army shall be free
till every foe is vanquished
and Christ is lord indeed
>> hey, tiger.
>> Jesse Wade.
>> Want to hit a few?
>> Nope.
>> What's the matter with you?
>> Nothing.
Just giving up the game.
>> What?
>> You heard me.
>> Well, that's stupid.
You can hit the ball farther
than anybody in satter.
Have you lost
your golden swing?
>> Of course not.
>> That's it, isn't it?
Tiger Ann Parker
has lost her golden swing.
>> I can outbat you any day.
>> I'm not so sure
about that any more.
>> Where do you want it to go?
Name the place.
>> Right over there.
>> Hurry up.
I ain't got all day.
[ Chickens clucking ]
>> Now, doesn't that
make you want to play?
>> Nope.
>> What?
Are you crazy, tiger?
You got sunstroke, or something?
>> Jesse Wade, a girl has
to grow up some time.
>> I don't think that will
be necessary, Rick.
I've got my key right here,
someplace.
>> Oh, that's too bad.
I could have been a hero.
And I could see
the headlines, now.
"Extra, extra, small boy climbs
down through chimney,
rescues family."
[ Laughs ]
[ Banging, chickens squawk ]
>> What in tarnation?
>> Fox.
>> The baby chicks.
>> Come on, shoo.
>> Shoo!
>> Where's all
the other baby chicks?
>> A possum must have got them.
>> Oh, poor babies.
>> You're mighty quiet,
young lady.
Do you know anything about this?
>> Yes, ma'am.
I'm afraid I left
the gate open this afternoon.
>> Then I'm afraid
you owe me two dozen chicks.
>> That's fair, granny.
But I haven't got any money.
>> Then you'll just have
to earn some, starting bright
and early tomorrow morning.
>> Morning, ladies, Lonnie.
>> Good morning, Otis
>> good morning.
>> You'd best stay
out of shorty's way.
He be in one of his moods.
>> I want these out of my way.
>> Well, I best get to work.
>> Bye, Lonnie.
>> Lonnie.
>> Mr. Thompson.
>> Morning, miss Jewel,
miss corrina.
And you brought a helper.
How are you doing, tiger?
>> Just fine, Mr. Thompson.
>> Well, it's my pleasure
to have Lonnie Parker's
daughter working here.
Do you realize your daddy
has never missed
a day on the job
since he was 15 years old?
I wish I had ten more like him.
>> Where's Jesse Wade,
Mr. Thompson?
>> Sleeping.
Arlette thinks he'll break
in two if he lifts
a finger around here.
>> I sure do want to thank you
for those Louisiana
lady camellias, woodrow.
They're the prettiest
things I ever seen.
>> Totally my own creation, too.
Eight years in the making,
they was.
>> Oh, well, I declare.
>> Got a man in Dallas
very interested.
I could make a nice
little sum of money.
Well, you ladies take care.
It looks like it's gonna be
a scorcher today.
>> Oh, here, put these on.
>> Thanks, mama.
>> Oh, granny, I'd die if
Jesse Wade saw me in this thing.
>> Well, you'll just have
to take your chances, child,
because if you don't,
you'll be freckled as
a leopard by the end
of the day.
Now, come on,
let's get to work.
[ Laughs ]
>> Refreshments.
>> Oh, that's mighty nice
of you, Mrs. Thompson.
>> Merci, Jesse Wade.
>> You hear about
Abby Lynn's new swimming pool?
>> Swimming pool? No.
>> That one's a carriage
with three horses.
>> It looks like a dragon to me.
>> It's a carriage, tiger Ann.
>> Why do you always have
to be right about everything?
>> It's not a carriage,
it's not a dragon,
it's a cloud, Jesse Wade.
>> Well, I don't see
why you have to get all
riled up about it.
>> Maybe because I gotta
work out there where
it's hotter than
the fourth of July,
and it's not even my fault,
because I'm not the one
who made me hit the ball
at the hen house
and leave the gate open.
>> I didn't make you
do anything.
>> How come you've never done
a lick of work in your life?
>> What's that got to do
with anything?
>> Just answer me.
>> I was sick.
>> That's when you were a baby.
The way I figure it,
if you can hit a ball
and run a few bases,
you can do a few chores.
You're just spoiled,
Jesse Wade Thompson.
You're a big mama's boy.
>> And you look stupid
in that goofy hat.
>> It's a sunbonnet.
>> You still look stupid.
>> Get back here,
you big mama's boy.
[ Laughing, chattering ]
>> Turn. Race ya.
[ Laughing ]
>> Hi, tiger.
>> Hi, miss Harris.
>> Hello, corrina.
>> The books was real good,
miss Harris.
>> Yeah.
>> I especially liked
the one about that nice bull.
>> Ferdinand?
>> Yes.
>> The words was real hard,
but my tiger read it to me.
She reads real fine.
>> Well, you go choose
some new books.
>> Okay.
I might want to take
that ferdinand book again.
>> You going to wear
the one you wore?
>> Yes, lavender
with little stars.
>> I remember.
[ Chattering ]
>> I'm gonna have
a swimming party.
I'm sending out
the invitations in the mail.
Mama bought me special pink
envelopes with little
white roses on the back.
Why, hello, tiger Ann.
>> Hi, Abby Lynn.
How is patsy?
>> Patsy, don't believe
I know a patsy.
>> Your calf.
>> That would be pansy.
She's fine, thank you.
>> Tiger.
>> Tiger Ann, I think
your mama's looking for you.
>> Tiger, where are you?
>> Oh, oh, I didn't know
where you were.
I thought you forgot me.
>> It's okay, mama. It's okay.
Let's go home, okay?
[ Laughing ]
>> Your turn.
>> No, thanks.
>> What's the matter?
>> Nothing.
I just don't feel like it.
>> Well, you kicked rocks
when we came.
Why don't you want to play now?
>> Because, I don't feel
like it.
>> Why are you mad at me, tiger?
What'd I do, tiger?
>> Mama, why'd you have
to go make a fuss
and hugging me back there?
>> Oh, did I squeeze you
too tight? Did I?
>> Just forget it.
>> That's all there was, granny.
One was broken.
>> Oh, that noise box is
spooking those hens now.
Your mama is spending too much
time in front of that thing.
>> I know.
Yesterday, when daddy came home,
she didn't even notice.
I could tell his feelings
were hurt.
>> Well, this morning,
I asked her to help me
hang up the wash.
You know what she said?
>> What?
>> "To the moon, Alice."
Now, that doesn't
make any sense to me at all.
So I figure it comes
from that noise box.
>> I don't see how anyone
with an ounce of sense
could like a dumb puppet show.
>> You mean anybody
but your mama?
>> I didn't say that.
>> Your new word for today
is prevaricate.
It means to lie.
>> I'm not lying.
>> It also means
to speak evasively.
Did somebody say
something about your mama?
>> Not exactly.
>> Well, they either did,
or they didn't.
Now, which is it?
>> I left her in the bookmobile
when I went into the gym with
the other kids,
and she got scared,
and she came running at me
all wild and crying.
>> And you were embarrassed.
>> I want to go to Abby Lynn's
swimming party so bad.
But now I know
she'll never invite me.
>> Well, if she wouldn't invite
you because of that,
then she isn't somebody
you want to be your friend.
Oh, tiger, people are
afraid of what's different.
But that doesn't mean
different is bad.
It just means different
is different.
>> I wish that...
>> What?
What do you wish, child?
>> I wish mama
wasn't different.
>> Sometimes I do, too.
[ Chickens clucking, cheeping ]
[ Groans ]
>> Granny! Granny!
>> What is it?
What's wrong now, child?
>> I'm bleeding.
>> Did that rooster turn on you?
>> From inside.
I'm bleeding from inside.
>> Well, I'll get some rags.
You've got the curse.
>> The curse?
>> From now on, you can look
forward to it every month until
you're too old to have babies.
And then thank the lord,
it's over.
That's the only good thing
I can think of
about getting old.
>> I'm ready, ma.
>> Ma's gonna show me
how to make BlackBerry pie.
>> What's wrong?
>> I'm bleeding, like,
I got the curse.
>> Oh, tiger.
Tiger, I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
>> It's a curse.
Grandma just said so.
It's a curse.
>> Oh, that's not true.
It's beautiful.
Well, I mean,
it's kind of messy,
and sometimes your tummy
hurts bad, but, tiger,
I couldn't have had you until
I was bleeding every month.
And having a baby,
having you, well,
that was the best thing
that ever happened.
Oh, I love you, tiger.
[ Singing ]
>> I got a lot of work
to do in the garden.
I want you to be
in charge of lunch.
>> Granny, do you think
it's unusual I'm so flat?
>> Child, you're 12 years old.
>> Not for long.
Abby Lynn Anders
wears a brassiere.
The same with Annette gills
and carlene hutson.
I can't even fill up
this baggy old swimsuit.
>> Well, my mama always said
that trees bud at different
times in the spring.
>> Well, spring has come and
gone, and I'm still not budding.
>> You will be.
You're on your way
to becoming a woman now.
>> I can't really ever
imagine becoming a woman.
Granny, would you say
I was pretty?
>> Pretty, don't you go
wasting your time thinking
about that kind of nonsense.
You're smart,
and that's more important.
You going down to the creek?
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> Well, it's hot enough for
a swim, that's for sure.
Just make sure
that you're back in time
to fix some lunch.
>> I will be.
[ Knocking ]
>> Oh, goodness,
that Jesse Wade is so forgetful.
Were the two of you supposed
to go to the swimming party
together?
>> Swimming party?
He already left for
Abby Lynn's house?
>> Yes. I'm so sorry.
Do you need a ride, mon Cher?
>> I'll be fine. I can walk.
I'll see Jesse Wade later.
>> Well, have fun, tiger Ann.
>> I hate you, Abby Lynn Anders,
I hate you.
>> Tiger.
Tiger.
I looked all over for you
at Abby Lynn's.
After a while,
I asked where you were.
When she told me you
weren't invited, I left.
>> Great. Now, everyone knows
I wasn't invited.
>> Oh, I'm sorry.
>> It's not fair.
I didn't do anything to them.
>> Her pool is no big deal.
This is much nicer.
>> Tiger.
Tiger, tiger!
Tiger?
>> TV : Loosens dirt,
floats it away,
yet lestoil leaves no film,
grit or scratches, even for
highly polished surfaces.
Cleaning with lestoil
is quicker, easier,
more economical.
>> Tiger?
>> It's so easy when
you use lestoil.
[ Yawns ]
[ Knocks ]
>> Come in.
Can't sleep?
>> No, ma'am.
Granny, when was
the first time you were kissed?
>> Oh, my goodness, I swear,
I never know what is gonna
come out of that mouth of yours.
Now, what in the world
would make you want to ask me
a question like that?
>> I'm just aiming
to find out about life.
A girl has to know
about these things.
>> Oh, well, nighttime's for
sleeping, not for chattering.
Come on, turn off the light.
Get it bed.
Lay here, here you go.
Tiger, I've been thinking
about what we talked about
the other day, about your mama
being different.
Well, the thing is,
your mama may have
a simple mind,
but her love is simple, too.
It flows from her like
a quick, easy river.
Now, you may not understand
that now, but one day you will.
Turn over.
[ Chuckles ]
You know, when I was young,
my best friend
was Rowena Johnson.
And she was my maid of honor.
Well, Rowena was
flatter than a pancake.
But all the folks they thought
she was the most beautiful gal
in the whole county.
>> What?
Jesse Wade, what do
you want now?
>> I was just walking.
It's a free country.
>> Well, walk someplace else.
>> Tiger Ann, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have kissed you,
not so soon, anyway.
I kind of sprung it on you.
>> Sprung it on me?
Jesse Wade, I never
thought of you that way.
Why did you have to go
and ruin everything?
>> Well, it's just
that I'm kind of mixed up.
>> I'll say.
[ Screaming ]
>> Ma!
[ Crying ]
>> Go call Dr. Randall.
I'm getting my daddy.
>> Daddy, daddy!
>> The doc's here, and
an ambulance is coming, too.
[ Sobbing ]
>> Don't touch me.
>> Doc, miss Jewel's sick.
>> Let me take a look
at your mama, corrina.
>> Give mama some medicine
and make her feel better.
>> It looks like miss Jewel
died of a heart attack.
>> No.
[ Sobbing ]
No, you give me
back my mama.
>> Corrina, corrina.
>> You give me back my mama.
>> Corrina, I'm sorry, we have
to take your mama away now.
>> No, no, mama.
>> Let's take her inside.
>> Mama!
[ Sobbing ]
>> Tiger?
>> Go home, Jesse Wade,
just go home.
>> So Lonnie, make sure that
corrina knows that if she needs
anything, she just has to ask.
>> You take as much time off
work as you like, Lonnie.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Tell tiger I'll come visit.
>> I'll do that, Jesse Wade.
>> You take care, Lonnie.
>> I wished I could turn back
the clock and change things.
I'd forget about that
stupid swimming party.
I'd forget about
Jesse Wade kissing me.
I'd help granny more.
I'd watch her real careful
and make sure she wasn't ever,
ever sick with her heart.
>> Oh, come here, baby.
Oh, that's all right.
That's okay.
Tiger, listen to me, listen.
You're gonna be okay.
All right?
I know it's hard.
I'm here now.
You're gonna be okay, sweetie.
It's okay.
>> Dorie Kay, I'm really sorry
about your mama.
>> Oh, well, thank you, Lonnie.
Now, how is corrina?
>> In bed.
She put on her mama's
old green nightgown,
and she's just lying
there crying her eyes out.
>> Oh, dear.
>> She don't want to talk to me.
>> She don't want to talk
to anybody, daddy.
>> Dorie Kay, what do you
do when somebody dies?
>> I don't want you
to worry about a thing, okay?
I'm gonna take care of
everything.
Honey, could you
go grab me a phone book?
And Lonnie, I need you
to fire up that stove.
We need to make a nice,
warm supper.
There's enough food here
to feed an entire army.
>> I'll get some wood.
>> I didn't cry at the funeral.
I had to be strong
for mama and daddy.
But nothing seemed real.
And the only thing I wanted
to hear no one could say.
>> There's a lot of people
at your house.
>> I didn't need you
to tell me that.
That's why I'm here.
I don't remember
inviting you to join me.
>> Tiger, do you want me
to just disappear, or what?
I don't know how
I'm supposed to feel about you.
>> I don't really want
to talk about this right now.
>> I'm real sorry
about miss Jewel.
>> Yes, that sounds perfect.
Okay.
Well, you just bill it to me.
Bye-bye. Now.
Corrina? Corrina?
Oh, come on, now.
That is enough, corrina.
Now it's time to get up.
Lonnie went to work,
and tiger's got the house
looking all beautiful.
Now, come on,
we have things to do.
>> Ma's dead.
She went to heaven.
>> That's right.
Ma is dead.
But you are not.
And Lonnie's not,
and I'm not,
and neither is tiger.
Now, what kind of mother lies
in bed when she has
a child to tend to?
>> Oh, no. I've been bad.
>> Corrina.
>> Tiger's gonna be angry at me.
>> I'm not mad at you, mama.
And you're not a bad mother.
You've just been real sad.
>> Oh, baby.
[ Sobbing ]
>> Now, I made it
real simple for you.
There is the total.
>> I don't rightly see,
dorie Kay.
>> What don't you see, Lonnie?
>> How do you know
how much to pay?
>> It's right here
on the paper, Lonnie.
It clearly shows
the total owing.
>> Why, why do they give you all
them numbers if they only want
you to pay one of them?
>> Now, I heard you talking
about how many plant cuttings
you've made at work, how many
eggs the hens have laid.
What is the difference
between those numbers
and these numbers?
>> It's just different,
dorie Kay.
>> Why?
>> Them numbers, when I look
at them, well, they,
they dance on the page.
>> They dance on the page.
>> My mama always said
I couldn't finish my arithmetic
at school
because I was retarded.
I guess that must be it.
I could talk to brother Dave.
>> Yes, you could.
You could talk to brother Dave.
>> Like when your mama gave
miss eula all them butterbeans
last year, and miss eula made
them calico curtains
for tiger's bedroom.
>> I'm not sure I see
the connection, Lonnie.
>> I could mow the church lawn
one day a week,
and brother Dave,
he could write up these
here bills one time each month.
Do you think that's fair?
>> Yes.
Yes, I do.
>> Mm-mm.
Honey, do you like that flavor?
I could order you
a different one.
>> No, I'm fine.
>> You're a little thing,
like me.
I fill up really fast, too.
>> What did you want to discuss
with me, aunt dorie Kay?
>> Tiger, now that your granny
has passed, things are gonna be
quite different for you at home.
>> I'm really gonna miss her.
>> Well, I'm not
just talking about that.
>> Oh.
>> Honey, your mama and daddy
are the salt of the earth.
They are sweet,
and loving, and kind.
But the most
that can be asked of them
is that they look
after themselves.
>> Now, I think with some help,
they can do that.
So I've decided
to ask my maid, magnolia,
to come out for the summer
and to help them out.
>> Oh, that's good.
>> Tiger, I've got an idea.
>> What?
>> How would you like to come
to Baton Rouge with me to come
get magnolia?
We'd stay for just
a couple of days,
and you'd get a taste
of life in the big city.
>> But what about mama?
>> Well, your daddy will be at
home at night, and I'm sure
miss eula can look in
on her during the day.
Oh, honey, your mama
will be just fine.
>> I'd really like to, but...
>> No buts.
We'll have the best time, sugar.
I'll take you sight-seeing.
We could go to
a fine restaurant or two.
You need a little holiday
away from all this.
This is my present to you.
[ Gasps ]
>> Oh, my goodness.
Corrina, you scared me
lying there like that.
>> Mama?
Mama?
Why don't I turn on
the TV for you?
I bet a lot of your
favorite shows are on.
>> It's mama's TV.
>> I know she'd like
for you to watch it.
>> Well, guess what, corrina?
You're gonna have a visitor.
My maid magnolia is gonna
come and take care of you.
Won't that be nice?
>> Hm.
>> She'll treat you
like a real queen, corrina.
She'll wash your clothes,
cook your dinner,
take care of the house.
Now, the best part is,
I'm gonna take tiger with me
to go pick her up.
>> Are you coming back?
>> Of course, mama.
I'll only be gone
for a few days.
>> Now, I need
to call Otis' wife.
Do you know her name, corrina?
>> Willie Mae.
>> Yes, Willie Mae.
I'll need to call her and ask
if she has a place
for magnolia to stay
in the colored quarters.
>> Then I need to call
miss eula.
Oh, I hope she does not keep me
yakking on the phone
with all her nonsense.
>> Well, that's it.
Everything's all loaded up.
Goodbye, Lonnie.
>> So long, dorie Kay.
Thank you for coming.
>> Okay, now, don't you worry,
corrina.
I'm gonna
take good care of tiger.
>> I'll see you soon, mama.
>> You're my special girl,
tiger.
Don't you forget that.
>> Granny used to say that
wanting adventure was foolish.
And I hated to disagree
with her, especially now.
But I was sure looking
forward to this adventure.
>> What?
Oh, do I have lipstick
on my teeth?
>> No, I was just thinking.
>> What about?
>> You don't seem sad,
aunt dorie Kay.
>> Sad?
>> Like mama.
Don't you miss grannie?
>> Oh, I lost my mama
a long time ago.
You know, it wasn't easy
being your mama's sister,
honey.
I had a lot
of responsibilities.
>> I know mama can be
a lot of work.
But she can't help
the way she was born.
>> I have so much
to show you, honey.
I think you're really gonna
like Baton Rouge.
Honey?
Honey, wake up.
We're here.
So, what do you think?
>> I feel like I just
stepped into one of them
Hollywood movies.
[ Laughs ]
>> Home, sweet home.
>> Eat your heart out,
Abby Lynn Anders.
>> And in the bathroom,
you just turn on the faucet
and the water comes out,
as hot as you like.
No trips to the well, or taking
a bath in that old aluminum tub
on the porch.
>> So you know, last week on TV,
I saw some lady taking
a bubble bath.
>> Well, tonight you can
take one.
Come on, let me show you
your room.
>> Well, do you like it?
>> I love it.
>> Oh, good.
I didn't know if it would be
too much, or...
Well, why don't you
make yourself comfortable
and get unpacked?
And I'll make US a snack.
>> Okay.
>> Daddy.
[ Honking ]
>> Well, look at you.
Now you look like you
really belong in Baton Rouge.
>> I can't thank you enough
for all these fine things,
aunt dorie Kay.
>> Oh, listen, honey,
there's something
I've been meaning
to talk to you about.
I don't go by dorie Kay here.
>> Oh, you don't?
>> No, I go by
my given name, Doreen.
And I'd like for you
to call me that, too.
>> Okay.
I might slip up once in a while,
but I'll try real hard.
>> You know, tiger,
you can really reinvent
yourself in Baton Rouge.
That's what I did
when I first came here.
>> How?
>> Well, let's see, I used to
practice all the voice patterns
of ladies on radio commercials,
and then I would study
different fashion magazines
for all the latest styles.
And I even went
to expensive restaurants,
and I would order some tea,
and I would just sit,
and I would watch the way
people with class ate.
[ Whistle ]
>> Hm.
I, I guess I shouldn't do that.
>> Sometimes I shudder to think
what I looked like
when I first came here.
The clothes I wore,
and my hairdo,
oh, goodness gracious.
>> You're just about perfect,
now, aunt Doreen.
You're the most sophisticated
person I've ever known.
>> Oh, well, thank you, tiger.
[ Music playing ]
>> I made you some cocoa.
>> This is you
and my mama, isn't it?
>> Yes.
>> Mama's eyes,
they look different.
>> Different?
What do you mean?
>> Like, like
they're seeing more.
[ Music stops ]
>> When your mama was younger,
she knew every
nursery rhyme by heart.
One of my first memories of
corrina is of her laughing
and reciting "Jack and Jill."
And then at the end,
we would both go tumbling,
and tumbling.
>> Mama was born smart,
like regular kids?
>> Yes, she was.
>> But what happened to her?
>> Well...
When I was very young,
I used to climb everything.
You couldn't
keep me on the ground.
And even though corrina
was only six at the time,
she would follow me around
like a mother hen,
making sure that I didn't
hurt myself.
And so one day my mama,
your grannie, left the ladder
leaning up against
the old oak tree.
>> My oak tree,
where my swing is?
>> Yes.
And so I went climbing up
the ladder,
all the way to the top,
and I grabbed
hold of this branch.
And corrina came up after me.
And she reached out for me,
and she lost her balance,
and then she fell to the ground.
She broke her arm, but it was
her head that got hurt the most.
And the doctors said
that she would never,
never get right again,
and that she'd always
be like a six-year-old.
Mama never forgave herself
for leaving that ladder out.
And she never forgave me
for climbing up the tree.
>> Why didn't anyone tell me?
>> Oh, honey.
Well, your grannie didn't
want to talk about it, ever.
And I didn't have
much memory of it myself.
>> How did you find out?
>> Well, when I was about
your age, I was feeling really
frustrated because I had to take
corrina with me everywhere.
And it's a terrible thing
to admit, but I was
embarrassed by my sister.
And so one day I was going
on and on about
how unfair it all was.
And mama sat me down,
and she told me the whole story.
And that was the only time
she ever talked about it.
Honey, I cannot tell you
how much guilt I felt.
>> But you were a baby.
It wasn't your fault.
[ Singing and humming ]
>> Good morning, miss tiger,
you want some breakfast?
>> Yes, ma'am.
And if you don't mind,
I prefer to be called Ann,
I feel it's more auspicious.
>> Well, all right,
then, miss Ann.
And you can call me magnolia.
>> Pleased to meet you,
miss magnolia.
>> Where is aunt dorie--
aunt Doreen?
>> Working.
She's a working girl.
And I guess you could
say I'm her working girl.
Did your aunt tell you
I'd be coming by today?
>> No, ma'am.
>> Mm-hmm. Busy, busy,
she's always too busy.
Hold on a minute.
You haven't said grace.
I guess you and me
be seeing a lot of
each other this summer.
Your people ain't
fussy folks, are they?
>> Oh, no, ma'am.
>> Good, cause I can't
take no fussy eaters.
I'm making one dinner
for everybody, that's it.
>> We eat almost anything,
except snails.
I read in this book once
that they eat snails
in Paris, France.
>> I don't have
no snail recipes.
>> I hope your folks don't
get too used to my face.
As soon as I can,
I'm headed home.
Didn't sign on for no long trip.
>> You, you you are my evil one
you, you, you
you are my evil one, baby
>> look.
[ Whistling ]
>> Hey.
Movie star!
Nice glasses.
>> Can I help you,
miss magnolia?
>> Unh-unh, your aunt pays me
to do the laundry.
If I don't do it, there won't be
no chicken in my pot.
You know, if you're that bored,
you could go to
the post office for me.
Your aunt needs her bills paid,
and she's out of stamps.
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> Here are the envelopes.
Now, the post office
is up three blocks,
and across the street.
You be careful, child.
This ain't tatter.
>> Satter.
>> Satter, tatter,
what's the difference?
This is a big city.
You don't talk to no strangers,
you hear?
>> Don't worry, miss magnolia,
I'll be right back.
>> You sure you want to cut it?
>> Well, do you have any idea
how you'd like it cut?
>> I can do any of these.
>> Can you do this one?
>> Hepburn, huh?
I can do that blindfolded.
>> Have you ever had
your hair cut?
>> Well, not in
a fancy place like this.
Grannie always trims--
trimmed my hair
on full moon day.
>> What?
>> On a full moon day.
If you cut your hair on
a full moon day,
it'll grow back faster.
>> Where are you from?
>> Satter.
>> Well, miss satter,
don't go telling anyone
around here that story.
>> Okay. You can look now.
>> I told you,
just like the magazine.
>> I really like it.
How much do I owe?
>> Two dollars, but
your hair's still wet.
>> It's all right.
I can dry it when I get home.
Thank you.
[ Car honks ]
>> Miss magnolia.
>> Oh, lord.
>> I'm so sorry, miss magnolia.
>> Good grief, child,
I was worried
when you didn't come right back.
>> I'm so sorry.
>> I heard you the first time.
What have you done to your hair?
Your aunt is gonna kill me.
>> I wanted to reinvent myself.
>> Well, at least you done
cut it on a full moon day.
>> Evening, miss Doreen.
>> Evening, magnolia.
Where's my niece?
Honey, are you hiding?
Your hair.
>> It wasn't my idea.
>> I love it.
>> You do? Really?
You don't think my nose
looks too big?
>> No.
Oh, you look very sophisticated,
doesn't she, magnolia?
>> I'm gonna go get ready
before I miss my bus.
>> Well, this calls for
a celebration, huh?
>> Guess what?
I've decided to go by the name
Ann, while I'm here, anyway.
>> Well, goodbye, tiger,
and hello, miss Ann Parker.
>> It sounds real nice.
>> It sounds really nice, Ann.
>> Really nice.
>> You're having a good time,
aren't you?
>> The best time
I've had in my whole life.
>> Well, you know,
if you wanted,
it could be permanent.
>> Permanent?
What do you mean?
>> I mean, you could come
and stay with me.
We can fix the guest bedroom up
just the way you liked,
and you could even
go to a fancy private school,
with uniforms, and everything.
>> You'd really like it
if I lived with you?
>> Oh, yes, very much.
>> It sounds great, but...
>> Oh, you, you think about it.
Just consider it, that's all.
Well, this is fine, huh?
Girls night out.
>> Do you have a boyfriend,
aunt Doreen?
>> Oh, I'm much too busy.
I don't think any man
would want me.
Why do you ask?
>> I was just wondering.
>> Did my mama,
did your grannie mention this?
>> No, it was miss eula.
>> Miss eula?
Well, you tell her the next time
she asks that I'm doing
just fine on my own, thank you.
>> That's what grannie
always used to say.
>> She did?
>> Whenever miss eula would go
on the way she does,
granny would always says,
"one thing I can count on,
is my gal dorie Kay.
She has a good head
on her shoulders."
I didn't mean to make you sad.
>> You didn't, honey.
You made me very happy.
[ Doreen sobbing ]
>> Now, don't forget, I want you
to really think about
what we discussed.
>> I have been, aunt Doreen.
>> And if you decide that's
what you want to do,
I'll come pick you up
at the end of summer, okay?
>> Bye, aunt Doreen.
>> Oh, give your mama
a big kiss for me, okay?
>> Bye-bye.
>> Okay, um...
>> You're gonna be okay.
>> Oh, magnolia,
thank you for doing this.
>> You call me, okay?
>> Okay.
>> Bye, aunt Doreen.
>> Bye, Ann Parker.
>> Even though it had only been
a few days, it seemed like
a lifetime ago
that I had left satter.
I was coming back
a different person.
>> Watch your step, ma'am.
There you go.
>> Is that gonna be
enough for you?
>> Yeah, I'm fine.
>> Okay.
>> It sure is hot.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Miss magnolia,
do you have any children?
>> I got a son.
His name is Michael.
>> How old is he?
>> Nineteen next month.
I guess I'll miss his birthday
this year, the first time ever.
>> What kind of work does he do?
>> Well, he's real good with
his hands, he likes to make
bird houses for me.
He don't have
a job right now, though.
These days, the world is
a hard place
for a young negro man to live.
>> What do you mean?
>> Your folks know you're
planning to live with your aunt?
>> How'd you know about that?
>> I got eyes and ears.
>> Well, I haven't
decided anything yet.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Satter.
>> Daddy!
>> Don't worry, it'll grow back.
>> Daddy, this is miss magnolia.
>> How do you do?
>> Welcome, miss magnolia.
Thanks for bringing
tiger home safe.
>> Glad to do it.
>> This way.
>> Thank you.
It sure is pretty,
this place called satter.
[ Flies buzzing ]
>> Lord, almighty.
>> It's not always like this.
It's just on account
of grannie dying.
>> Corrina,
miss magnolia is here.
>> Hello, miss corrina.
I'm magnolia.
>> Where's tiger?
>> Here I am, mama.
>> Your hair.
>> Mr. Lonnie,
I'm getting tired
and fading quick.
You mind if I settle in
for the night and
start fresh tomorrow?
>> Of course not.
It's been a long day traveling.
>> Is your name Mr. Lonnie?
>> I could take you over to Otis
and Willie Mae's now,
if you want, miss magnolia.
>> That would be right fine,
thank you.
I'll see you bright and early
in the morning, miss corrina.
>> Miss magnolia,
how did you get here?
>> I walked.
Ain't nothing
but a little piece.
Besides, you get to see one
of the good lord's miracles
that way.
>> What miracle?
>> The sunrise.
Pinks, purples, oranges.
The good lord sure knowed
how to bless each day.
What you doing up so early?
>> My daddy asked me to help out
at the Thompson's this week.
That's where he works,
at the Thompson's nursery.
>> Well, your grannie sure
knowed how to keep a kitchen.
I ain't had to hunt for a thing.
I like your mama and daddy.
>> Mama used to be
like other people.
But she had an accident,
and she was--
>> I don't need
no explanations, child.
I told you, I like your folks.
>> Morning, tiger.
>> Morning, Jesse Wade.
>> Jesse Wade, you're up
mighty early.
>> Yeah, my daddy wanted me
to help out
with all the Louisiana
lady camellias, and all.
>> Lonnie, I'm heading out to
Dallas, be back in a few days.
Keep an eye on things
for me, will you?
>> Yes, sir, Mr. Thompson.
I'll be mighty proud
to keep an eye on things.
>> Tiger, you sure do look
different somehow.
I guess you're growing up,
just like Jesse Wade.
See you in a couple of days.
Bye, son.
>> Bye, daddy.
>> Let's get to work.
I'll show you how
to make cuttings.
>> Well, my, my, my, looky here.
>> Morning.
>> Hey, Lonnie, this here's
a plant nursery,
not a kiddie nursery
[ chuckles ]
>> Now, you take these
here cuttings.
>> That's all?
You just stick them in the sand?
>> What happens to them?
>> They get roots on them.
Ain't that something?
>> It sure is, daddy.
>> Well, we take the cuttings
with the roots and we transplant
them in the liner shed.
That's that old shed
over there with no walls.
>> See, that way
they get the sunshine,
but they stay in the shade.
>> That's quite a system
you got there.
>> Well, when they're ready,
we put them in a gallon can
and they go in the hot house.
>> And when they get too big for
the pots, well, then we plant
them in the field.
>> I never knew there
was so much to it.
>> Well, when we're ready
to sell them,
we go and we dig them up
and we cover the root ball
with burlap.
>> I'm not sure
I can remember all that.
>> Oh, it ain't
that hard, Jesse Wade.
I can help you
if'n you get stuck.
>> Come on.
>> Please, Mr. Bus driver,
can't I come in?
>> Hm.
>> Mommy, you made
my pony tail too tight.
>> Where did you learn
to do that?
>> My cousin Vernon.
He says all the kids
in Lafayette are doing it.
Why did you go
and cut off all your hair?
>> It's not all cut off.
Did your daddy really ask you
to come help out at the nursery?
>> Well, he did need the help.
And I thought
you might be here today.
I wasn't sure if you'd
be mad or not.
>> Jesse Wade, I'm sorry
I told you to leave me alone.
I wanted to take it back
the minute I said it.
It's just you acted so mushy.
I want to stay your friend.
>> Me, too, tiger.
>> Hi.
>> What happened to mama?
>> Well, she had a nice bath.
And then she helped me put
some clean sheets on the beds.
And then she drew me
a picture of all
the baby chicks
you used to have.
My, but she's
a joy to be with.
>> When I was your age,
my mama laid down and died.
And I had five younger brothers
and sisters to take care of,
and I done it.
>> Your mama needs you,
and you need her and your daddy.
Anyway, she's gonna be
feeling better any day now,
you just wait and see.
[ Thunder ]
>> Oh, lord all that laundry.
>> I'll get it.
>> The barn's shut tight.
>> It's getting from bad
to worse out there.
Miss corrina, I bet you can
finish these here dishes
by yourself.
>> It's all right, I can do it.
>> Like, I was saying,
miss corrina, it sure
would be a help to me
if you was to finish up here.
>> I want you to
get home safe, magnolia.
I can do them dishes.
>> Well, now, I knew you could.
Would you ask your daddy
if he would be so kind
as to give me a ride?
>> Okay.
[ Birds chirping ]
>> TV : Take soothing
pepto-bismol
and feel good again.
>> Look, it's a dress code.
>> What is it, Lonnie?
>> Something's happening.
>> What is it?
>> I, I don't know.
Since the rain stopped,
I seen birds in every tree
around the house,
blue jays, and Robins,
and sparrows.
They've been chirping
and tweeting like they was
trying to say something.
>> Listen.
[ TV stops ]
[ Birds chirping ]
>> That's pretty.
>> Oh, that new calf's
named pansy.
Abby Lynn gets to keep her
as a special pet.
Daddy?
Why are you going so fast?
>> We gotta gather up all
the gallon cans we can find
and carry them over
to the liner shed.
>> What for?
>> Something going on, tiger.
>> Lonnie, Jesse Wade
said you needed to see me.
Anything wrong?
>> Mrs. Thompson,
I can't rightly say for sure,
but it seems to me that
something mighty big
is gonna happen.
>> What do you mean?
>> There were these birds that
landed in our tree yesterday--
>> birds in a tree, huh, well,
that's a strange sight,
all right.
>> There were millions of them
whooping and hollering.
This morning when
the sun came up, they just left.
>> I don't exactly
understand what you mean.
>> I reckon them birds,
they know something.
>> Oh, yeah, they knew
if they kept it up,
they'd have every cat
in satter after them.
>> What do you think
it means, Lonnie?
>> I think a really big storm
is coming.
And the birds knew it,
and the cows, too.
>> Cows?
>> The Anders' cows, when we
went past them this morning,
they was all bunched
together in the field.
>> Oh, I've heard of cows
doing that.
Well, do you think that
has anything to do with
the hurricane they're expecting
over in Cameron?
>> Yeah, I bet it does, mama.
>> Why, that hurricane's
nowhere near here,
Mrs. Thompson.
We might get US some rain,
but that'll be about it.
>> And what do you say
we should do?
>> I reckon that we should
get these Louisiana ladies
safe, because Mr. Thompson
spent a lot of time,
too much time to see
them just washed away.
>> Okay. Let's get started.
What do we do first?
>> You're not gonna
listen to him, are you?
He's simple.
He's an idiot.
>> My daddy is not an idiot.
>> Mr. Thompson
left Lonnie in charge.
Now, you do what he says.
>> Well, I ain't taking
no orders from no idiot.
>> Then you had better leave.
>> All right, then.
Come on.
Come on, Milton.
>> If you feel the same way,
Milton, you are
welcome to leave.
>> I'm sorry, shorty.
I got a family to feed.
>> We'll see what Mr. Thompson
has to say.
>> Well, let's get started.
What do we do first?
>> Mrs. Thompson,
if you don't mind
getting your house dirty,
I was thinking that
that would be the best place
for the plants.
And I reckon we can put down
some sheets of newspapers
so as we don't mess
up your house too much.
>> Oh, don't worry
about the floor.
Let's get going.
Vite, vite.
>> Watch out.
[ Wind whistling ]
[ Laughs ]
>> It's starting.
Mrs. Thompson,
I think tiger best
get home and be with her mama.
>> Okay, of course.
Now, I'll understand
if you need to leave, too.
>> No, ma'am.
Mr. Thompson told me
to keep an eye on things,
and that's what I'm gonna do.
>> Are you gonna be
all right, tiger?
>> I'll be fine.
>> Now, tiger, take
the short cut through the woods.
>> Okay.
>> You want me to go with you?
>> No, Jesse Wade, you best stay
here with your mama.
>> Hurry, tiger.
>> Okay, I will.
>> Tiger, be very careful.
>> I will.
[ Bleats ]
>> Pansy.
>> What are you doing here,
pansy?
>> I better get you home.
Come on.
Come on, pansy.
>> Get on up there, come on.
>> Come on, pansy,
come on, pansy.
>> What are you doing
with our calf?
>> I was returning her.
Next time I'll leave her
to blow away in the hurricane.
>> What hurricane?
>> This one.
>> Where'd you get
your hair cut?
>> In Baton Rouge when
I went to visit my aunt.
>> It kind of looks
like Audrey hepburn.
>> How'd you get out, pansy?
>> This is wrong.
It's wrong.
She should have
come home by now.
>> Now, miss corrina,
she's on her way.
Mrs. Thompson said she only
left a short while ago.
>> My tiger is fast, though.
She is fast.
It don't take her this long
from the thompsons.
>> Well, being in a panic ain't
gonna make things any better.
>> I got to go look for her.
>> No, no, no, you can't
go out there, not like this.
That won't make things
any better, no, no.
No. You stay here.
Having the both of
you running around in this.
[ Screams ]
>> Tiger!
Tiger!
>> Here, mama, over here.
>> Tiger!
>> Mama! Mama!
>> Mama, over here!
>> Where, baby?
>> This way!
>> Hold on, I'm coming.
>> Mama, here, mama.
>> Don't move. I'm coming.
I'm here, baby.
I'm here now, baby.
Oh, my baby, my baby.
>> Mama.
[ Sobbing ]
>> Oh, mercy.
>> Magnolia, are you all right?
>> No, lord, no.
I'm not all right, Mr. Lonnie.
Did you see any sign of tiger
or miss corrina on your way?
>> They're not here?
>> No, sir, they're not.
Tiger never did
get back from the Thompson's,
and, and miss corrina,
well, she just up and took off
right in the worst of it.
>> Oh, no, I got
to go look for them.
Call Mrs. Thompson.
>> I've been trying, but
the line's been down
for at least--
oh, my lord.
>> Hey. Hey.
>> Let's go home.
>> Corrina?
>> Look.
>> It's grannies bonnet.
>> Let's go inside
and get some dry clothes.
>> I can feel her here.
>> I can, too, mama.
>> You can?
>> That's good,
that's real good.
>> Well, it's been quite a day,
quite a day.
[ Laughs ]
>> As we sat down to dinner,
a feeling swept over me,
sweeter and warmer
than anything I had ever known.
And despite all the pulled up
trees and broken branches,
I felt my head
and my heart clear.
I was home, and that's
exactly where I wanted to be.
I guess you could say
that's the end of the story.
But it isn't, really.
Life has a way
of surprising you.
Things always keep changing
and growing,
kind of like cutting
your hair on a full moon day.