Buddy, forward.
I know. I told him, you know.
Of course you've got
your agenda and all that,
but the grant money's
drying up fast,
and it's unconscionable
that you...
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
MAN: In or out, pal?
I'm sorry.
(BLUES MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
Is that all
the further you've got
since 7:00
this morning?
Hey, it's your
lookout.
If the job takes
two days, two weeks,
I could care less.
These steps need
to be sanded and resealed.
Boy, you got
some brass peach pits,
makin' a friend work off
a promissory note.
You think I wouldn't rather
have a qualified painter?
I had to have
some periodontal work done.
Okay, so I happen to be one of
the 18 million unemployed right now
without a safety net.
What am I supposed to do,
let the teeth rot?
You don't have a safety net because
you haven't worked for Ringling Brothers
or any other kind of gainful
employment for over 10 years.
With my heart murmur?
Here's your Henry's
Compound for the roof.
Oh, yeah.
Your high-pressure nozzle?
Don't lose this one.
(MUSIC STOPS)
Hey, they're about
to play a half hour of Willie.
Yeah, yeah.
(DIAL TONE)
(DIALING)
(LINE RINGING)
YOUNG JOSIE: Hello?
Hello. Is, uh,
is Megan there?
Just a minute.
Bingo.
Mom, there's some man
for you on the phone.
MEGAN: Okay, well,
just hang on a second.
Hello?
Hello, Megan?
MEGAN: Uh-huh.
It's Jim Rockford.
Jim?
Oh, my God, Jim!
YOUNG JOSIE: Who's Jim?
MEGAN: Now, what have I asked
you when I'm on the phone?
No, no, that goes in the sink.
Uh, is that a daughter?
Yeah. I have a son, too.
God, it's been like,
what, 15 years?
Yeah, at least.
You know,
I was on campus today.
At the Psychology Department?
You're kidding.
Yeah.
I, uh, I was at
a client meeting.
I didn't get the job,
but, uh... Aw, geez.
We passed in the elevator.
What?
I was shocked into silence.
You know, the last time
we talked,
you and Michael
had moved to Atlanta.
Well, I'm back.
I'm divorced.
Oh?
Yeah, me, too.
It'd be wonderful
to see you. Uh-huh.
In fact,
it's my father's birthday Sunday.
We're throwing a party for
him at his Santa Barbara house.
Why don't you come?
Oh. Uh, you know,
I, I don't know.
Uh.
Okay.
Yes! (LAUGHS)
Hey!
Is that Jim Rockford?
Frank, I feel like I'm crashing
your hootenanny here.
Oh, no, no.
Just what I need,
another birthday, huh?
By the way, this is not
Parkinson's induced.
And I didn't trip over
my walker, either.
Newest grand kid just got me
with the Similac.
Oh, boy.
(CHUCKLES) Come on.
Yeah, you know,
I was, I was glad
to hear Megan say
that you might show.
Hey, I'll bet the Reagan
years were good to you, huh?
S&L investigations,
defense contractor fraud.
Matter of fact.
(LAUGHS)
Well, 1, uh,
I sold the talent agency.
It's part of UTA now.
I'm enjoying myself.
Hey, waiter.
Yes, sir.
You were supposed
to bring lime slices
to the lady in the black
dress 10 minutes ago.
Never mind.
It's a little late now.
Come on, Jim, I'll take you
to my favourite daughter.
Guess you heard the marriage
of the century is over.
ROCKFORD: I never heard it
referred to as that.
FRANK: Someday I'll learn
to shut my big mouth.
Megan.
It's Jim.
ROCKFORD: Hi, Meg.
Jim?
FRANK: Here people,
I brought the limes.
Put any tips
right here in the bowl.
It's so good to see you.
(ROCKFORD CHUCKLES)
Jim, uh, this is my sister,
Josie. Hi, Jim.
Dougherty people!
There's a function
at the junction.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Forgive me, Godfather.
Hello, Patrick.
MEGAN: I didn't think
you were going to make it.
Oh,
I'm sorry. I had a client meeting run late.
Uncle Patrick!
Oh! Come, here, doll face.
MEGAN: This is my
daughter, Josie.
My cousin, Patrick.
Jim Rockford.
Jim Rockford?
Megan's
"road-not-traveled"?
Oops.
Patrick.
Oh, Jim, Molly. Molly, Jim.
Hi, Molly.
Let's see. No,
we're at the wrong table.
We are, we're at
Ice Station Zebra.
Say good-bye to the nice people. Bye,
everybody.
MEGAN: Bye.
How's your dad?
Rocky died
late last year.
Oh, no.
I'm so sorry.
You two had such a
special relationship.
I miss him.
He was always
a major fan of yours.
Really?
He was funny that way.
He wasn't an educated man,
but, uh, his judgment
of people was usually dead on.
Hmm.
Of course, he called me
"sonny" right up to his death.
Well, that's parents.
Will and I are bored, Mom.
We're gonna go
down on the beach,
see if there are
any people doing it.
Excuse me?
Grandpa doesn't want anyone
on the cliffs because of the erosion.
Now, say hello
to Mr. Rockford.
This is my son, Daniel.
It's Jim. Hi, Daniel.
Hi. MEGAN: What's
your sister doing?
She and Kate
are acting like dorks.
YOUNG JOSIE: Hey, Daniel,
come here!
He's quite a guy.
You think so?
(CLINKING)
That's good.
Clinking.
Oh.
We've heard many grand
and heartfelt tributes
to Francis Dougherty today.
From his children,
in particular.
And, uh, while I'm not
a member of that august body,
I'd say I'm about as close
as one can get
without the requisite advanced degree
from Yale and prescription for Prozac.
(PATRICK CHUCKLES)
MAN: Ooh!
But because of that,
he has, to his credit,
six extraordinarily
accomplished,
if annoying, children,
a legacy as fountainhead
of one of the most powerful
and, uh, blah-blah-blah,
literary and talent agencies
ever to exist in this town.
As, as Frank
himself once said,
he never met a control
issue he didn't like.
(ALL CHUCKLING)
Whoa!
Hang on.
(PATRICK LAUGHS)
When my, uh, father,
his brother,
died,
my uncle was there for me.
He tried.
So, the part everybody likes,
we get to drink.
Here is to
Uncle Fountainhead.
Uh, happy birthday.
WOMAN: Whoo! Yeah!
Happy birthday!
WOMAN: Patrick! Whoo!
I never heard you mention
your cousin before.
Really?
He's kind
of a fixture.
Your brother Peter's
an interesting guy.
What does he do?
He's an entertainment
lawyer.
You know, he went into
the family business.
VALET: Gold Fire bird!
I don't think he
likes it very much.
Oh?
Are we there?
Well, that's me,
right here.
Well...
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
I'll call you
tomorrow, okay?
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Bye, Jim!
Bye, Josie.
Grandpa's gonna
kill you.
Why don't you
shut up?
(MOLLY SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
WOMAN: Is anybody hurt?
Hey, are you
all right?
I don't believe this!
(MOLLY GROANING)
Molly, are you okay?
Let me help you.
What the hell's
the matter with you?
Look what you did, ace!
ROCKFORD: Oh, you pulled
right out in front of me!
What, are you blind?
Well, I'm not ripped
on blow and Herradura,
I'll tell ya that!
PATRICK: What'd you say?
You were slapping
the backboards
when you got
here today.
Want to say
that again?
I'll say it again.
I got about 100 witnesses.
FRANK: Patrick!
Hey, son, don't do that.
Patrick, for God's sake.
(PATRICK GRUNTS)
ROCKFORD: Here you go,
Patrick.
PETER: Patrick,
that's enough!
Patrick, you already had
your license taken away!
PATRICK: Let go of me!
You stupid...
MOLLY: Patrick, stop!
Patrick.
Stop.
(MOLLY WAILING)
FRANK: Thank you, Patrick.
Excellent choice
of birthday present.
I don't suppose I could
get some of that coffee
without paying
for it?
That's all right.
That's why I brought
two cups.
(LAUGHS) I see you met
Mr. Wong last night.
It's not worth
talking about.
No cream, huh?
Oh, Jimmy.
Man, I tell ya,
sometimes I wonder,
what does it all mean?
What?
ANGEL: Well, I mean,
don't you ever wonder?
Take me.
Here I am, my age,
with nothing,
cleaning aluminum siding
on my best friend's house.
Angel, you are so full
of self-pity.
Oh, well, thank you,
Reverend Schuller.
I spent the evening with somebody
who lost her sight in a car accident
at the age of 15.
You should see
her attitude.
That shrink you were bumping
back in the early '80s?
If you had to spend
10 minutes of your life
as a blind person,
you'd...
You know what
she said to me?
Dodger Stadium's
dark most nights?
Look, Jimmy, I hear
a sermon coming on,
and I just don't feel...
She said that she was
in Las Vegas at a convention,
uh, with her guide dog,
and she was outside the casino.
Some guy comes up,
pats her on the head,
stuffs a 50 in her hand,
and then runs away
before she can
give it back.
Yeah? So what's the point?
Can you imagine
the humiliation
of somebody treating you
like a rabbit's foot?
Hey, I knew
this little chick, Jim...
Who's this?
(GROANING)
MOLLY: Babe, don't say
anything to provoke him.
Ugh, are you listening
to me?
Hey!
Look, I'm sorry.
You didn't call the police,
and I appreciate it.
I would've done
jail time.
Your cousin
asked me not to.
Now, get the hell
out of here.
Where do you get off
talking to me like that?
I gotta go work.
This is my parking lot.
I own it.
I discovered this whole
stretch of coastline.
I'm Balboa, okay?
You don't like it?
Hi.
I'm Molly.
Looks like sucky work.
All right,
all right. I was somewhat drunk last night,
but I was not high,
I swear.
I care less if you shoot
up your foot powder
or mix dragster fuel
with pear grappa.
Just don't come
around me or mine.
The shame is that
if they find you
with your face
in a shag rug,
it's gonna tear up
your cousin pretty good.
Well, actually,
Megan's the one
that suggested
you and I talk.
Sure, she did.
The facilitator.
Okay. But also, I, I need
a private investigator.
(SCOFFS) I'm supposed
to work for you?
Well, she said
you didn't have a job.
She said what?
She meant for now,
I'm sure. You know.
There's an actor client of
mine dropped out of sight.
Actor client?
Yeah.
I'm a personal manager,
uh, here.
Uncle Frank flypaper
you to the payroll?
No, I'm on my own now,
for over a year.
It's a small but
selective client list.
Jack Nicholson, huh?
Oh.
Hootie & the Blowfish?
All right, who, then?
Well, Molly, for one.
I also represent fitness
guru Pablo Cohen,
and the writing team
of Schneider and Frolov.
Okay, listen,
the client I'm worried about
is named Ykaterina Stepashin.
She's Russian. Major
film star back in Russia.
Unfortunately, she still hasn't
been able to break through here.
That's why I'm worried.
She's been so depressed.
I am not working for you,
and you can tell your cousin
I do not need a personal
manager. Especially not her.
My career's doing just fine.
Fair enough.
She's certainly tried to play
therapist with me enough times,
and it does wear thin.
She asked you
to ask me to find
this Russian
as a personal
favor to her?
Excuse me.
I'm looking for
a Ykaterina Stepashin.
Uh, I'm told
she's a regular here.
Performs on occasion.
English, no.
Ah.
Ah, yeah.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Ernesto!
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
¡Alto, alto! Para el jefe.
Su boss man. Mi teléfono.
(ROCKFORD SPEAKING SPANISH)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
Oh, hi,
Josie. How are you? Hi, Jim.
Come on in.
(DOOR CLOSING)
May we offer you
something to drink?
Uh, no,
thank you, Josie.
AUTOMATED VOICE: 7:10 p.m.
I'm fine. Hi!
MEGAN: Hi.
Let me just get them set up with dinner,
and I'll be ready.
Okay.
Great.
These guys and
their cousins
are flying off
to Atlanta tomorrow
to spend summer vacation
with their dad.
Oh, really?
His new house
has a pond,
and we're gonna swim
and catch leeches and stuff.
And we're not afraid
of those leeches, are we?
Not any more.
(CHUCKLES)
FRANK: Hey, Jim.
Oh, hi, Frank.
Oh, I don't know, ...
I can't get that
Nintendo working.
Well, thanks
for trying.
I wish you'd stay and have
dinner with Daniel and Josie.
Oh, nothing I'd like better,
but no can do.
Did I hear we're still going
on about those leeches?
Nope. It's all over
and settled.
Because, as I said, there couldn't
be that many in a spring-fed pond.
Anyway, all you have to remember
about leeches... Okay, Dad, it's settled.
You know, in the Seabees,
we used to burn "em off with cigarettes...
Okay, Dad, thank you!
Don't shush me, Megan.
I'm trying to explain
to the child
there's absolutely nothing
to be afraid of.
I know that.
FRANK: Of course you do.
MEGAN: About time, dude.
I know.
Mark got locked out
of his house.
Mmm-hmm.
His mom will take
our turn driving carpool.
Good.
Josie, egg?
Wide, two o'clock, Mom.
Thanks.
FRANK: Jim, uh,
I have to apologize for my
nephew's behavior the other day.
I guess every family
has its Swamp Thing.
I never said
you didn't have a job.
I said
you were available.
Oh, available.
Excuse me.
Well, aren't you?
I do not need
a personal manager.
Stop repeating yourself.
You're so proud of that line.
Well, what's his problem,
anyway?
Patrick is very sweet,
and bright.
He's written
great screenplays,
which, of course,
Hollywood doesn't get.
He graduated the highest ever
in Peace Corps language training.
He's lived in Africa
and, and Russia.
He gave me
a phrase book.
Well, he speaks
it fluently.
He was one of the first capitalists
in there after the '91 coup.
He knows Yeltsin.
I could tell
from his driving.
You two were
always so close?
I was in love with him.
He was my big cousin,
you know?
So tell me
about your marriage.
You're not running
this session.
You first.
Oh, boy.
Well...
(EXHALES)
Michael and I still love
each other.
I don't know.
He's a very angry man.
More so every year.
But time, kids,
dueling careers...
You know,
the usual suspects.
Well, speaking of kids,
yours are terrific.
They're much more responsible
and self-assured
than most children
their age.
Well, they've had to be.
But thank you.
So talk!
About your marriage.
Well...
Kit's a great person,
and the whole thing convinced me
that I just don't want those
kinds of complications in my life.
Especially not at this age.
Boy, I'm with you there.
Hey, Dennis.
I was just in the area.
Oh, how's the cyst?
You want to see it?
I'd have nothing
to compare it to.
See you got an office
with a window.
Listen, I, I was just
wondering,
if possibly you could
do me a favor?
I'm gonna say this again,
it's not the same
old department.
Things are different now.
The King thing, 0.♪...
Our reputation's
in the toilet,
our response time is now a
matter of public amusement.
Okay, Dennis,
take a chill pill.
No, it's not,
"Okay, Dennis," okay?
We're overloaded,
yet the same negative voices
come in here asking for
special consideration.
I just thought, as a friend,
you might be happy to see me working again.
Okay, what is it?
Hmm.
My dry spell's
over, Dennis.
It's my favourite kind
of gig, too.
Skip trace.
Of course,
it's your favourite.
I use our MCT links.
Seven out of 10 times, I turn your
missing person, you collect your mark-up
without leaving
your rocking chair.
"Y" Katerina Stepashin.
Uh, the work.
And a friend asked me to.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm answering
your question.
I didn't ask you a question.
You said,
"Why Katerina Stepashin?"
It's her name.
Oh, no, Dennis, no.
The "Y" is pronounced, "Yuh."
Yuh-Katerina.
It's Yuh-Katerina, not "Y."
Oh.
ROCKFORD: Damn!
(SIGHS)
Jimmy,
it's Angel. It's 12:15. Make that 12:17.
I'm gonna work for your bud,
Pat Dougherty.
He's got some
DMV issues.
Needs a driver.
And, and I guess what,
uh, I'm saying is, I quit.
(BRAKES SCREECHING SOFTLY)
(CAR DOOR OPENING)
(CAR DOOR CLOSING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
Yeah,
I'm coming.
Yeah?
You are searching
for Ykaterina Stepashin?
Who are you?
Did you find her yet?
Did you have some information
you wanted to impart?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Who?
(ROCKFORD GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Who engaged you
to find her?
Oh, yeah. (STAMMERS)
Patrick Dougherty,
Patrick Dougherty.
Where is Pat?
Well, at home.
That's where he works out of.
Oh, no.
Hey, don't! (GROANS)
You must try harder.
I don't know.
(SCOFFS)
Oh, you play golf.
On occasion.
Oh, Boris Andreyevitch
is a scratch player.
Boris Andreyevitch.
What?
Did you find
Ykaterina Stepashin?
(GROANING)
Did you find
Ykaterina Stepashin?
No.
No, it's the truth.
(GROANING)
(ROCKFORD BREATHING HEAVILY)
Do you know where
Pat's family lives?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
I have to go now.
I wish I didn't have to
leave things on such basis.
Oh! (GROANS)
(EXHALES)
(HORN HONKING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ROCKFORD GROANING)
Megan? Megan, it's Jim.
Michael said he'd call
as soon as
the children landed.
Oh, you worry so much.
They'll all be fine.
Even my
horrific daughter.
Come on, Buddy.
Thanks a lot, Josie.
I'll talk to you later.
JOSIE: Bye, sis.
MEGAN: Bye-bye.
(ROCKFORD GROANS)
Oh, no. (EXHALES)
Who's there?
I'll take the cans out
in the morning.
Jim?
All right, the guy
dressed in Fila,
the tall guy called him
Boris Andreyevitch?
ROCKFORD: Yeah, right.
I finally reached Molly.
She says she hasn't heard from
Patrick since yesterday morning.
BECKER: Molly's the
girlfriend? MEGAN: Yeah.
Here's some more ice.
She was pretty terrified.
Are these Russians going
to come after all of us?
(ROCKFORD GRUNTS)
These guys must've had
KGB training.
The North Korean Shiatsu.
What'd you tell them?
That's what scares me.
I can't be sure.
Ma'am, uh...
Uh, did you warn family
members of the possible danger?
Yeah.
They were all
really upset.
Thank God my children and my
sister's children just went back East.
Patrick, he writes great
screenplays that nobody gets.
Did I mention that, Dennis?
(DEVICE CHIMING)
And you have no idea
who these men could be?
No.
Patrick knows
so many Russians.
He did some film financing
over there, I think.
And then for a while he was
exporting Soviet Army overcoats.
They were kind of hip
a couple of years ago.
He knows Yeltsin.
You just won't stop, will you?
(SIGHS)
I tried Tevas.
You ever wear 'em?
If not, you got
a treat coming.
Officer Burgess tells me that
the neighbors haven't seen
anything out of the ordinary
all day.
How about a tall guy,
whacked out on Haldol,
staggering around
with a handgun?
Was there one?
I wouldn't stay here,
ma'am, or report to work.
Oh, that's great.
What am I supposed to do?
Pack a bag.
We'll deal with it.
What does
"We'll deal with it" mean?
Your Y-Katerina surfaced.
St. John's Hospital, OD.
Satisfactory condition.
This tall Russian guy came
to my trailer looking for you.
His name,
Gennady Koblets.
Koblets, Megan.
Remember that.
No, you can't
tell him I'm here.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Russian, nyet.
I'll give it to you.
Look at this.
It's for you.
It's Cartier.
See diamonds?
It's pear-cut.
No, no, thank you,
please.
Look, Gennady,
is he Russian Mafia?
Yes.
Yes, Russian Mafia, yes.
Uh, KGB?
Uh, originally?
MVD.
Interior Minister.
Medal, yes?
Hero of Soviet Union.
Now. (SCOFFS)
(IMITATES SCOFFING)
A changed man,
in business for himself.
Soviet Union. (SCOFFS)
Gennady, is he friends
with Patrick Dougherty?
Yes.
He is my manager.
So nice.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Model Inc.
Moscow Art Theater.
Six years.
So Patrick was supposed
to get you established.
To help you.
Mmm, yes.
He meet,
met to me many people.
But I don't work.
Gennady was screaming.
I swallow many capsules
with vodka.
Is this your first
suicide attempt?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
How sad. (EXHALES)
Gennady is, is angry.
He, he wants you back.
He's very mad at Patrick.
Please, don't tell him,
Detective sir.
I have a seat assignment.
As soon as they lets
me go from here,
I am returning to Moscow.
Tomorrow.
(GASPS)
Your arm!
Hey.
Take it.
It's Venice. Fendi.
No, no.
Gennady give it to me.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Really. No, no,
no. Look. It's very,
very, very... Look,
we're not going to tell him
where you are,
so just take the coat.
ROCKFORD: We're going to have to call
your father and tell him what's going on.
Just stay there.
Nurse!
Ah.
ROCKFORD: Hey, Frank.
MEGAN: Daddy, what are you
doing still here?
Aren't you worried?
No.
We're headed
for New York
first thing
in the morning, anyway.
Want a drink?
No.
I'll have some wine.
A little red,
if you've got it.
Yeah, sure.
MEGAN: I'm going
to sit down.
Anyway, I've met
Gennady Koblets.
And he's not
a complete moron.
I have to believe
he realizes that
if he touches
any one of my family,
I have the kind of friends
who can and will single
him out for the cold room.
Dad, he wants
to kill Patrick.
I said my own family.
I'm not talking about Patrick.
Anyway, he doesn't want
to kill him.
Punish him a little, yes.
Thank you.
Go a little Cossack
on his dumb ass.
Well, who knows, maybe he can
succeed where Betty Ford,
the Jesuits and the rest
of us have failed.
Here we go.
Megan, the man
is 43 years old.
Flaky son of a bitch!
Uh, how do you
know Koblets?
Through Patrick.
Yet another attempt to get
the nephew up and running.
(FRANK EXHALES)
A year ago, Koblets had some 15th century
St. George icons from the State Museum.
I have friends
who are collectors.
I made some introductions,
helped Patrick
with the negotiations.
I can't believe this.
That art is the patrimony
of the Russian people.
Pat Trimony?
Didn't I used to represent him
when he was married
to what's-her-name?
I'm delighted you
find it so amusing.
(SIGHS)
Do you wish me to help your
cousin in his battle with life?
Huh?
'Cause, frankly,
I'm a little confused about my role.
I need to go
to the bathroom.
You all right?
Yeah, yeah.
(FRANK CHUCKLES)
She's really something,
isn't she?
Oh, she's somethin',
all right.
Notice the way
she took me to task?
(FRANK LAUGHS)
None of my other kids
have that much spine.
No, those leeches aren't
waiting for you, honey.
Leeches can't think.
I miss you, too,
and I wish I could be there
to hug you to sleep, too.
(EXHALES)
Did you get to go
to Ben and Jerry's?
Oh.
It was because you were
thinking about those leeches.
Try and remember Jo
in Little Women.
That's right, she has the same name as you,
and she was very brave.
Well, I love you, too,
Jo-Jo-bean.
Bye-bye, sweetie.
Oh, my father,
pain in the ass.
Yeah, well, Rocky
would've done the same.
Nature lectures.
Toughens you up.
This was his place, huh?
Yeah. His studio.
Of course all he ever did was bring
his buddies up here on the weekend
and they'd watch games
and barbecue kielbasa.
Well, I can't unload it,
but I still pay
the taxes on it.
It's a nice smell.
Pine trees.
If it shelters us
from the Interior Ministry
until we can find a way
to talk Koblets down,
then it'll have
paid for itself.
Okay, Buddy. Night.
Go lie down.
Let's not have
that conversation
about you taking the couch
and I take the bed.
Well, you sleep
where you want.
My bad back cuts into
my chivalry these days.
Why did you call me?
JOHNNY: This professor
works with Dimitri Kalcheim,
the Russian expert.
FESTA: Okay, bring him down.
Yo, Professor.
Mr. FESTA will see you.
FESTA: Professor,
what can I do for you?
Mr. FESTA, I appreciate
you seeing me.
Do you mind?
Uh, Mr. Kalcheim
is a, an avid reader,
and he was, uh,
looking through
the large-print edition
of The Times,
when he spotted
an article
mentioning both you
and a Mr. Koblets.
Koblets?
Yeah, I know him.
The paper said that you and
Mr. Koblets had partnered up
to purchase
Atlantic City property.
That partnership
did not eventuate.
Whole time they slipped us
the blini.
They're lower
than the silverfish.
Russians.
It's like
Averell Harriman.
I'm sorry?
FESTA: He was ambassador
over there.
He said, "With the Russians,
you're always buying the same horse twice."
JOHNNY: They ripped us off
for $18 million.
Let me tell you something
about the Russian Mafia.
They're violent,
they're sociopathic.
And a bath once in a while
would be nice, too.
Oh, that's not true,
Rich.
What? Are you gonna
contradict me?
This is
a socio-cultural thing.
I think it's so cold
over there,
taking a shower is not
instilled in the young.
I think it's up to
the individual.
I mean, Koblets with me
was always well-groomed.
(SIGHS)
You don't know
where Mr. Kalcheim
could contact Mr. Koblets,
do you?
To the right
enterprising party,
I'd be willing to pay into the four
figures for that same information.
Is that right?
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
You're not up yet?
Mmm. It feels good.
Were you able
to reach Patrick?
Uh-uh.
Still no answer,
and nothing on my service.
(ROCKFORD SIGHS)
You've just been
lying here, huh?
I took Buddy out,
but it was too cold.
Oh, and I,
I banged into something
and broke it.
I think it was a bowling
trophy or something.
It felt like a little man
with a ball.
Anyway, he fell off
his stand.
I'll make us some coffee.
Uh, you like tea, right?
Listen, about last night...
Oh, please.
Not the first thing, huh?
Okay. Then get back in.
(SIGHS)
That's not in.
Come here.
We got to get moving
pretty soon.
Okay, soon.
I like this.
Smelly old cabin,
hanging in bed,
no job to go to.
You should have run off
with your cousin.
(LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY)
You know, this is
the problem with LA.
Never get
any show days.
So you're
liking this, too?
The being here part,
with you?
Very much.
(BIRD CHIRPING)
That one bird,
the high one,
goes exactly
every 17 seconds.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
ROCKFORD: You want
some Corn Flakes?
Okay.
I want to take
a quick shower.
Water's pretty brown.
Uh-oh.
I'm going to try
Patrick again.
See if he's checked in.
(LINE RINGING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: You have reached the
personal secretary mailbox for Doctor...
(BEEPS)
Megan, hi.
This is Rochelle.
Uh, the numbers
haven't been crunched yet,
so don't bother...
(BEEPS)
PATRICK: Meg, you nut.
Ten messages on my machine's
a little excessive,
don't you think?
Jim.
It's Patrick
on the phone.
PATRICK: Here I think I have
a whole host of important calls,
and they all
turn out to be you.
But seriously, there's nothing
to worry about. I'm fine.
I spent the night
at a client's, Pablo Cohen.
He, he was great
about it.
And yesterday
I kept movin' around.
Even maintained
a full schedule of meetings.
I mean, I got a lot
of work done.
Uh, I'm sorry if this
caused you any hassle.
I know Gennady Koblets.
It'll blow over.
I just talked to Molly.
I'm gonna pick her up,
and we'll chill
at Two Bunch Palms for a
couple of days. I'll call ya.
Molly's.
Get dressed, Megan.
What are you
thinkin' about?
Josie and Daniel.
I hope they're having
fun with their dad.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CAR HORN HONKING)
Damn. Buddy? Buddy,
baby, are you okay?
(BUDDY WHIMPERS)
He's okay, he's okay.
You stay right here.
(MAN GROANING)
Oh, Angel?
Who's that?
Call an ambulance.
I'm hurt!
Angel!
Jimmy. Oh, God, it's horrible
back there, it's horrible!
What is?
MEGAN: Jim?
What's going on?
You all right?
Everybody okay?
Yeah, yeah. I'm okay. Shoulders.
Well, that's the seat belt.
That's good.
Here, get out. Come on,
Buddy. ANGEL: Oh! Oh!
(ANGEL GROANING) Oh!
Stand right by the car.
Oh. Help! Somebody
call 911!
Man injured!
Angel, you're all right.
Now, get out and help her.
Why can't she help me? I'm
losing cerebral fluid. Angel, just do it!
Don't move me! Don't move me!
PATRICK: No, please.
(MOANING) Molly, honey.
ROCKFORD: Oh, my God.
(MOLLY GROANING)
(WOMAN SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON PA)
BECKER: I'm going to want you to look
at some pictures, when you're up to it.
MOLLY: Call my mom.
She lives in Reno.
She's in rough shape.
One or both perps raped
as well as beat her.
It's not clear.
Oh, God, Molly.
No, please.
Koblets?
Apparently not.
She knows Koblets. Two men.
Russians.
Maybe that
Boris Andreyevitch guy.
I'm so sorry
about all of this.
Jim, what
they did to you...
You've got no reason I can
remember to call me Jim.
Koblets blames you for
not getting Miss Stepashin's
career on track.
Is that the assumption?
Yeah.
Things started out mediocre,
then promptly went in the toilet.
Ykaterina finally
split on Gennady.
That's when Mr. Dougherty hired
me to try and salvage the situation.
I felt bad for the guy.
Then he does this to Molly
to get back at me?
Koblets and Miss Stepashin hit LA,
they seek you out for representation,
and your fee is,
what, the usual 15%?
Yeah.
Well, uh...
Well what?
Well,
I was forced to ask Gennady
for 100,000 cash.
I told him I could
deliver a Golden Globe.
See, Ykaterina's movie,
The Guard Shack,
had a little heat on it from
the Azerbaijan Film Festival.
Oh, Patrick.
I'm in litigation on my
screenplay, Megs.
I owed $40,000 on
those overcoats.
The Golden Globe
isn't for sale.
(YELLING) I know that!
Megs...
It's not my best
judgment call, I know.
But I am doing pretty
good at this.
Don't tell Uncle Frank about
the Golden Globe thing.
Oh, Patrick.
Pleasing Dad's the least of
your problems right now.
I've seen enough.
Oh, Dennis.
What, what?
Hey, Dennis.
I gotta make a call!
ANGEL: That you Jimmy?
Jimmy?
Angel?
Oh, God,
Jimmy, I'm blind.
(WAILING) I'm blind!
You are not blind.
I can't see. I can't see!
Angel, you just have
a minor concussion.
They're keeping you
overnight for observation.
My eyesight's perfect, right?
Now, don't lie to me, damn it!
Angel, you were telling blind
jokes, and now you're scared.
Jimmy, do me a favor.
Ask Mr. D
if I still have the gig.
Mr. D doesn't
have a car any more.
Oh, sure, same old
Angel Martin luck!
Now, what am I gonna do, huh? Plus,
he owes me two days' pay.
The girl's gonna live, Angel,
just to put your mind at ease.
How's the food here?
She say?
ROCKFORD: Boy, your cousin's
areal piece of work, I'll tell ya.
Just go on ahead,
if you have to walk that fast.
I worry about Patrick.
I don't need for
you to understand.
ROCKFORD: Well, that's good,
because I don't understand.
Yeah, well, too bad.
ROCKFORD: Up, Buddy, up.
MEGAN: Buddy?
Down boy.
Down, Buddy, down.
Let me ask
you something.
Was I right?
Were you two kissing cousins
more zany than I could guess?
Do you know how ridiculous
you sound? How I sound?
Listen to you,
rationalizing and babying a parasite
like that. He wasn't always this way.
Oh, big so what?
After high school, Patrick was accepted
at Harvard on a National Merit Scholarship,
SATs in the high 15s. There's
no shortage of fools at Harvard.
Especially Harvard. Everything he
achieved he did it all without a father.
Oh, he had your dad.
Yeah.
He had my dad.
Oh, hey.
I'm sorry.
This is really hard for
me to talk about.
It's all right.
I should
probably tell you.
My parents
owned a second
house in Sun Valley.
Look, if you don't want to talk about it,
don't talk about it.
And every holiday,
there we were,
my family,
friends of my parents,
the cousins, all kinds of friends
and roommates from school.
There was a separate
guest house.
Easter break in 1971.
There'd been really
great spring skiing.
At this party,
Patrick was there,
I was there,
my brothers and
sisters, assorted boyfriends.
I was going out with this guy
named Tony Herndon.
Get away from
my girl, Patrick.
I remember he had these little
gold flecks in his eyes,
and I thought that
was so amazing.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
Also, there was this guy,
Jeff Kravitz,
a friend of my
brother's from Yale.
Some people say
Jeff Kravitz started it.
It doesn't matter now.
Freeze, oinky boy!
(GUN CLICKING)
(BOYS LAUGHING)
BOY: Guys, put it away.
(INAUDIBLE)
(GUN CLICKING)
(GUNSHOT)
(INDISTINCT SCREAMING)
So I always just say I lost
my sight in a car accident.
Otherwise, when people
meet Patrick,
or even in the way
they relate to me...
It's just a lot easier.
June of that year,
he made his
first suicide attempt.
I told him if he left me here
like this, I'd kill myself.
Which was probably stupid,
but I was 15,
and I couldn't think of any other
way to stop him from hurting himself.
My father...
There's no way I can
even begin to convey.
But Patrick and I became even
closer after that.
I guess
because we were both so
isolated by everyone, you know.
Each in our own way.
Can you understand?
Sure.
So we are like lovers,
I guess.
It's like a private club
of only two people.
The Easter 1971 Club.
(SOBBING)
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
MEGAN: Boy, I slept
great last night.
I love this place.
ROCKFORD: That would
make Rocky happy.
But I gotta find Koblets so
we can all get on with our lives.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
There's that same bird.
You hear it?
Every 17 seconds.
(SINGING IN RUSSIAN)
Oh, hey, Dennis.
Man, I just get on days.
Oh, I really appreciate this.
How long you had this
place staked out?
Just long enough
to find him, Dennis.
I'm here to interview
one of your customers.
Police business.
MAN: Yes, sir.
Uh, I better
get my manager.
Mr. Koblets? Uh, Lieutenant Becker,
police department.
Mr. Koblets, Mr. Rockford here
says that on Monday morning the 11th,
you invaded his home in Malibu
and proceeded to assault him.
Is that true?
You understand
English, sir?
I was to his home.
You were?
We talked.
But assault? No, José.
You tell him the truth, Koblets,
or I'll... Hey. Hey, Jim...
Just once, and you're
out on the street.
Mr. Koblets,
Mr. Rockford also says
that there was an individual with
you wearing a Fila, a warm-up suit.
The interrogation expert.
Boris Andreyevitch?
No. Ah, I'm
sorry, Lieutenant,
but I went alone
to offer this man
help in investigation.
He left his card with old friend of mine,
the maître d right here in this restaurant.
Now I'm accused
of assault?
What assistance
did you give him?
Only moral support.
I didn't know anything.
(MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
Do you know
a Molly Hiroki?
(WOMAN COUGHING)
Gentlemen, let me present
Valeriana llovna Koblets.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
BECKER: Hello, ma'am.
Uh, she doesn't speak
English at all.
But, boy, she enjoys
her visit to LA.
Molly Hiroki
was sexually assaulted
and beaten at her house
on Thursday.
Sexually assaulted?
Where were you that afternoon?
With my mother. BECKER: Where,
with your mother?
Disneyland.
Where else?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Pirate of the Caribbean.
But this teacup ride
on her stomach...
(LAUGHS)
She was undoubtedly
out in the car
with him when they
came by my place.
Maybe on their way
to, uh, Knott's Berry Farm.
She's gonna swear that there
were no two other specialists.
She was in the car.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
The department will be taking
an active interest in you, sir.
Did you tell Mother
it's your wish
to be buried
at Frontierland?
BECKER: Come on, Jim.
ROCKFORD: All right, Dennis.
I'm looking
for Dr. Adams.
Mmm-hmm.
MEGAN: Hi.
ROCKFORD: Hi.
Well, here it is.
Hey, this is
very impressive.
I'm very proud
to be here.
Let me just finish up
some stuff.
I thought maybe we'd go
to Valentino's, my treat.
Oh, well.
Oh, I spoke with the
children in Atlanta just now.
Guess who went swimming.
Oh, hey, that's great.
Here, have a jelly bean.
So, you think Koblets might
actually decide to cool it, huh?
Well...
Oh!
I was going to
send that tape.
He knows he's got
some scrutiny on him.
MEGAN: Or was Danny
going to send it?
What is going on here?
What?
You're running around
speed-rapping
like you're about to give
birth to a pound of coffee.
(EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
I spoke with Michael
in Atlanta just now.
The last couple of weeks,
we've been talking about
the possibility
of getting back together.
A lot of this has to do
with the children, you know?
I got it.
Their situation
isn't typical, you know.
I said I got it.
Oh, don't be like that.
Like what?
You're gonna do
what you're gonna do.
Uh, don't expect me
to sit here
and scrunch up my hankie
over your children.
They've got everything.
And you know what?
It is none of my business.
It's just so complicated.
And that's exactly what
we agreed we didn't want.
Oh, right. And you called me
to compare notes.
You're the one
who got sexual.
Oh? You complaining?
Oh, please.
Well, I'm glad
I forced the issue.
And the sex was great,
by the way.
(EXHALES)
I don't feel like going out
to dinner any more.
I don't feel like going
to the concert.
Well, that's stupid. We have the tickets,
they're hard to get.
Ah, well.
I don't see how we could have
anything approaching a good time.
Maybe your sister
wants to go.
Oh, Jim.
(JIM SIGHS)
Send me a Braves cap.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
Heel.
That can't be
my sister already.
ROCKFORD: You stay
back here.
Oh, you're not
gonna believe this.
It's Patrick.
(DOOR OPENING)
Jim!
Didn't Lieutenant Becker
tell you to lay low?
How low can you go?
Meg, you nut,
I used your Hide-a-Key.
I hope you don't mind.
Yes, I mind.
You bust in here when
everybody's all nervous and terrified.
(MUSIC STOPS)
Don't you ever think?
I wanted to let you all know
that Molly is doing much better.
I was with her
at the hospital all day.
Well, that's good.
PATRICK: And the situation
with Koblets is,
is pretty much
resolved.
I thought maybe
we could all celebrate.
Well, I know celebrate is not
exactly the right word,
considering
the circumstances.
Did Becker say
everything was resolved?
Well, he told me
what he said to Gennady,
and then I spoke
with Gennady. What?
Well, on the car
phone, Megs.
I said everything
had gone beyond the pale.
He agreed.
And I made
some assurances.
He will never harm
a follicle on the head
of anyone I care about
ever again.
What did you say to him?
Oh.
The emotional
Russian soul.
It's, it's always complex
dealing with them,
but he's okay now.
I, uh, got some things
for Molly.
Her favourite CDs,
a nightie.
Oh, Meg, I got
something for you here.
Here, here.
It's the Chieftains.
Long Black Veil. Sinead is on there,
and Van the Man.
It's a little
Dougherty roots music.
You mind if I listen
to this later?
No, it's...
Sure.
(PATRICK EXHALES)
Look, uh, I know we had
areal ugly situation,
but we're alive,
and, and life is always
worth celebrating, right?
Well, I mean,
the situation is improved.
I can understand
how you'd like to see
some prosecutions
handed out.
Way up there
on my letter to Santa.
I would just like to urge
everybody to let things lie.
What do you think?
Are you leaving?
Yeah.
How come?
Josie and I are going
to a concert.
Right.
I'll call you.
(DOOR CLOSES)
COMMENTATOR ON TV: He's
crossed pretty well this season.
He's batting
.328 against him.
Bagley's waiting. And the 0-2 pitch...
Slammed into the gap
in right center!
Foley's running over.
Maggio's on second,
crossing to third!
He's coming around
to score.
He's being waved in,
the ball comes in.
The play's to
home plate in time!
Nailed him right...
(CAR ALARM RINGING)
Come with.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What about
my golf clubs?
(BORIS SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
ROCKFORD: Those clubs
cost me 1,000 bucks.
Come on, guys.
(BORIS SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN
OVER RADIO)
(BORIS SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
ROCKFORD: Somebody call
the cops, would you?
Somebody call
the police!
(BORIS SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
ROCKFORD: Don't any
of you people speak English?
Put him in room.
Lock the door.
(STATIC BLARING)
(ROCKFORD EXCLAIMING) Oh, hey!
Hey! Hey!
What do you want
from me?
(STATIC CONTINUES BLARING)
(SCREAMING)
Where am I?
Megan. Megan,
it's me, Jim!
It's okay.
Come here.
There's a piano.
It's a piano.
This is white noise.
In six to eight hours you
cannot organize your thoughts
or walk for a while.
You can't do that
to her.
(STAMMERING) She
can't even keep her balance
if she can't hear.
I know how you feel.
That's why she's here.
One of you will decide
to help me.
Help how?
It is time now
to stop delaying.
We need Patrick.
Well, Patrick said you
and he resolved everything.
Patrick is a very
difficult man,
and yet I'm fond of him.
But, you know, he has
his chemical dependencies
and cannot be relied on.
We don't know where
Patrick squirrels off to.
KOBLETS: / understand.
In a few hours,
I will for sure know
what you know.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(STATIC BLARING)
ANGEL: Have a good day, now.
Good luck to you, sir.
That's right, everyone's
a winner here, ma'am.
Oh,
you're not kidding! It's true.
Rub my lucky spot,
right here.
Mr. Lucky,
that's what they call me.
Thanks for playing,
ma'am.
Oh, you're welcome.
Hello, folks!
How are ya?
Uh, excuse me.
Am I approaching the
Montebello Public Library?
This is
a gambling casino.
Oh, heck.
Everybody wins!
(STATIC BLARING)
(INAUDIBLE)
ROCKFORD: Hey, hey,
I know that guy.
MEGAN: What?
ROCKFORD: He works
at that Russian club.
Hey. Hey!
Hey!
(VACUUM CLEANER WHIRRING)
Remember me?
El detectivo?
(MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
(INAUDIBLE)
(STATIC BLARING)
Bring him to me.
Bring him here.
(INAUDIBLE)
BOY 1: Do you need
some help?
Just keep moving, sonny.
You're scaring my dog.
Come on,
baby. You were out here yesterday.
Was I?
Hey, how'd you lose
your sight, mister?
Bomb squad.
BOY 1: Wow.
It's okay, boy.
Hey, that's not a real
blind person's thing.
BOY 2: Yeah,
that harness dealie.
It's the French version.
Yeah, right.
Suck your skate!
Oh, bogus!
BOY 3: Loser
Yo, man.
Nice wedgie!
Oh, this dude's
a fake!
BOY 1: Hey.
BOY 2: He's running, man!
BOY 4: You better run,
Jackson!
(DOG BARKING)
Woo!
(STATIC BLARING)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
What is it?
Be right back.
Megan, stay there!
FESTA: I want my 18 million,
you son of a bitch!
Oh, God.
(BORIS SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN)
(GUNSHOT)
FESTA: Professor?
MEGAN: Yes? What?
(BORIS SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN)
(GUNSHOTS)
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: 2:00 a.m.
Buddy? Buddy?
Oh, good boy!
Good boy!
There you are!
Such a good boy!
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Koblets, Gennady. Searching.
Well,
this thing is amazing. Yeah.
It also has a scanner
that can convert
the printed page
into speech,
so I can read books.
I'll be damned.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Koblets,
Gennady. Eleven files.
MEGAN: Okay,
now I can't skim this,
so this thing's going
to have to read
all 11 of those files
in their entirety.
(AUTOMATED VOICE
SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN)
What's on the screen?
Cyrillic type.
What about now?
AUTOMATED VOICE: English.
Translating. ROCKFORD: Well, uh...
Well, it's English.
It looks like 11 titles.
Uh, look like
newspaper articles.
MEGAN: Okay. You're going
to have to skim it.
Uh, "Interior Ministry
Man Awarded..." That's 1981.
"Officers Awaits...
"Pair Released After
Questioning in Death
"of US Trade
Representative."
Enter eight.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Eight. Enter.
Moscow. Two former Interior
Ministry officials were released
after questioning
in the hit-and-run death
of Miles Melvoin,
US trade representative.
Melvoin died after attending a party
at the home of Patrick Dougherty,
President of Mos-wood
Film Financing Consultants.
Pause. ROCKFORD: "One of those questioned,
Gennady I. Koblets
"was also a guest,
but had left earlier.
"Koblets and Melvoin
were known to have disagreed
"on Mr. Koblets'
alleged attempts
"to divert
American aid money."
Now, this murder,
your cousin must hold the smoking gun.
Something that would get
Koblets executed.
Right.
A major miscalculation.
You don't blackmail
a man like that.
Patrick must have
threatened him
to make him
leave us alone.
(ROCKFORD EXHALES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey, Dennis,
this is a print-out off the Internet.
I think you should
look at it.
I want to talk to you about
your behavior the other night.
Step into
my office, please.
What? Hello, Lieutenant.
Over here.
Here's a chair
right here.
Okay, thanks.
Down, Buddy.
ROCKFORD: Dennis.
BECKER: Close the door.
(DOOR CLOSING)
Sean!
You're coming back to the house,
aren't you, Jim?
I think I'll be
heading home.
Why?
Maybe you can't handle any
more of the party-hearty Doughertys.
FRANK: All right.
Thank you for coming, Jim.
I'm truly sorry about the
death of your cousin, Megan.
Thank you.
Good-bye.
Bye, Josie.
YOUNG JOSIE: Bye, Jim.
Curb.
What are you doing?
Yearly maintenance.
Thought I'd come out,
maybe we'd have some lunch.
What's your problem?
I don't have
a problem.
I got
the afternoon free,
I'm offering
to buy you lunch.
You got to make
a problem out of that?
Thank you.
Yeah, it's really
cold out here.
This Dougherty guy,
real faccia brutta, huh?
What do you think
happened? Happened?
Well, we find two plane
tickets in the guy's pants.
His girlfriend
is on the way over,
they're gonna meet,
and they're gonna take off
like a couple
of free birds.
So?
LA is bigger
than both our butts
put together.
Two Russians
from Minsk, Pinsk,
they just find a motel
where Patrick is hiding out?
Tell ya,
that Megan Adams.
One beautiful woman.
It's over, Dennis.
I figured.
(EXHALES)
She's getting married again.
How about lunch?
Let's do it.
MAN ON TV: Shapes,
sizes, and colors
at unbeatable prices
through this weekend only at all
of our 16 locations. (RATTLING)
So hurry...
(TV TURNS OFF)
You're gonna love it here.
ROCKFORD: Angel!
(DOG BARKING)
Angel!
(GUNSHOT)
Ow!
Oh, the skin's
all scraped off!
(ANGEL GROANING)
Ow!
Whose dog is that?
I can't keep him, Jimmy.
Not at my place.
It's not fair to him.
Oh, when did you
start sharing your oxygen
with another life form?
(GROANS)
I thought I would do
a good deed,
and I went
to the pound,
but I was only putting
my own selfish concerns
ahead of what's good
for the animal.
It's loneliness, Jimmy.
Yeah, what was it,
Angel? A seeing-eye scam? Jimmy...
You're not dumping that dog on me,
you got that?
He's your dog,
and you're gonna take care of him.
If ever hear
you gave him away,
I am gonna feed you
the rest of his Friskies,
and then I'm gonna
break your face!
Okay, okay!
Get in here.
Get this dog some water.
Okay, okay.
Oh, and there's some almost-gone
bologna in the fridge, too.
Oh, you mean all the time
I was working here,
there was food
rotting in there?
And did I get any? No.
Well, the only problem
I can see
is, uh, what's gonna
happen to that dog
if you get held in jail?
What's that?
If the cops choose
to call it that,
it's accessory to homicide.
Accessory to my colon. What
are you trying to lay on me?
Well, you gave up Patrick
Dougherty, didn't you?
You drove him,
knew his routine.
Is he dead?
Oh, I'm sure
you can make a case
that the Russians
tortured you.
Anyway, it's probably not a
charge that you'd get indicted on.
I didn't twist
nobody's cap.
You didn't point them
to Patrick's motel?
I haven't seen Mr. D
since the accident.
I've been in Garden a, man.
I've been, I've been
at the poker palaces
trying to raise your 900.
Oh, yeah, raise me my 900.
Well, raise a pillow.
You'd have come in for some.
Look, Jimmy, that is
what Larry is for.
Frankly, I'm insulted
that you would think
that I might try to...
Shut up, Angel. Stop it.
FRANK: Come on, come on!
You got to work it
harder than that
if you're gonna make
that team at Harvard-West lake!
Pull! Pull!
Ah! You... You little... You!
(YOUNG JOSIE LAUGHING)
YOUNG JOSIE: No!
(FRANK LAUGHING)
Whoo! Whoo!
No.
Oh. (LAUGHS)
I'm going up to the house
to, to get my paper.
YOUNG JOSIE: Okay.
DANIEL: Marco!
YOUNG JOSIE: Polo!
FRANK: Jim!
Frank. I'm sorry
to startle you.
The housekeeper
let me in the front gate.
No, it's all right.
I, I don't think Megan is
around right now, Jim.
I think she went down
to the beach with her sister.
Oh, that's all right.
I, uh...
I don't want to talk
to Megan yet.
Oh? You all right?
What is it?
It has to do
with your nephew's death.
(FRANK SIGHS)
You haven't been here.
I have never seen her
this bad, ever.
Well, Patrick was
the main character
in the story
of her life.
Maybe it's finally
having to accept the fact
that it's not
going to be rewritten.
Ever.
YOUNG JOSIE: Hey, Grandpa,
come and watch
me and Daniel jump.
Did, uh,
Megan ever express
any anger at her cousin
over the accident?
No.
No?
No, I think she realized,
even as a young girl,
that her injury
gave her the power
to completely
obliterate that kid,
and I think
it frightened her.
Oh, she raged
at other things.
Therapists.
Physical obstacles.
Parents.
Ah, it's to be expected.
They'd been soul mates.
Stayed that way.
Don't ask me how.
What about you?
I was too harsh.
I knew it even when
I was doing it,
but I couldn't
stop myself.
You saw it. Set him up,
knock him down.
You're very frank about it.
YOUNG JOSIE: Grandpa,
watch! That's my name, Jim.
Did you tell
Gennady Koblets
where he might
pick Patrick up?
I mean, Patrick talked
to you constantly.
He craved your approval.
You know, I like you
well enough, Jim,
but you better take down
that social worker shingle
or you could be facing
a lawsuit.
This girl that he loved
and hurt so badly,
she couldn't give him
what he had coming to him.
Patrick hated himself, Frank.
(SCOFFS)
(CHUCKLES)
You know
my other children, when their
when their kids' school
pictures turn out badly,
they go into a tailspin.
She has never seen
her daughter's face.
Her son's.
MEGAN: Daddy. Is he right?
Why don't you
answer me?
Oh, Daddy.
How long
could we go on?
He was so unhappy.
So tortured.
Holy God, Dad.
Oh, my God.
You were his father.
The job fell to you.
Why me?
No, that's the wrong question.
All you can do is keep going
and carry what
you have to carry.
But you didn't.
You didn't, Daddy.
You taught all of us
to do that,
and in the end, you didn't.
Megan.
You and Mom dragged me
kicking and screaming
from my room.
You made me want to succeed
and have a life.
And now I can never
speak to you again,
never see you again.
Hey, Grandpa, check it out!
(IMITATES GUNSHOT)
Megan, what the hell
are you saying?
How can 1? How can I let my
children be around your influence now?
Megan, you Kids,
and your children,
you're everything
to me. You know that.
Was I such a disappointment?
Such a horrible tragedy to you
that you had to murder?
Because I don't feel
like that, Daddy.
I don't feel
like I'm a tragedy.
(INDISTINCT POLICE
CHATTER OVER RADIO)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Your boss is inside.
He kicked me out.
Well, I'm aware
of that.
Frank Dougherty told you
he met with the Russian here?
No, they called him
from here.
He didn't set up
the killing,
he just told them
what they needed to know.
Captain, are you
with the manager?
McENROE: Roger that.
What've we got?
A Boris "A" for Andreyevitch
Makshinov is registered.
Let's do it, sir.
McENROE: Roger.
What do you think
you're doing?
Well, Dennis, ...
Stay!
OFFICER : Gentlemen, I want
to clear this area, please.
Stand back.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Please, stand back.
He's taking a schvitz.
I'll head back
to Division, all right?
I want to check
with the Russian Consulate.
Folks, clear the hallway,
please.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Mr. Makshinov?
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(GUNSHOTS)
OFFICER 1: Police! Freeze!
Drop the weapon! Drop it!
Put your hands on your head!
Drop the weapon!
Drop it, I said!
Drop it!
OFFICER 2: All right, ma'am,
it's all over, it's okay.
Out of the pool!
Out of the pool now!
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
On your face.
On your face!
Where's Gennady Koblets?
(WHISTLES)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Uh, that's Moscow.
I got it!
Everybody fan out
and search
the surrounding properties.
I'll stay here
with the suspect.
Move it.
Mr. Rockford.
Get up.
Not only have you used methods
of torture against several citizens,
including a
visually-impaired woman,
but just now you assaulted
Mr. Rockford
over a minor altercation
concerning your
shower sandals.
What?
Where's you hypodermic
needle now, huh?
This is your chance
to escape.
(GRUNTING)
Well, don't quit on me now.
You're doing real good.
Let me show you this one.
We have a search
in progress.
Yes, sir.
(BORIS GROANING)
(WATER SPLASHING)
(PHONE RINGING)
(GRUNTS)
Hello?
(DIAL TONE)
(PHONE RINGING)
ANSWERING MACHINE:
This is Jim Rockford.
At the tone,
leave your name and message.
I'll get back to you.
MEGAN: it's me.
That was me
who hung up.
(SIGHS) I'm not going
to Atlanta.
I'm confused.
Probably not thinking
clearly right now.
I need to pull
myself together
and, and talk
to somebody.
(SIGHS) I need
to talk to you,
so, okay, call me
if you want to.
Bye.