Can I have a beer, please?
Okay. Uh... Cerveza.
Grande. Por favor.
Big one.
Cerveza.
Grande.
Oh, yeah.
One more.
No hablo inglés, gringo.
Uno mas.
And I'm not a gringo.
Gringos are American.
No inglés.
No, I don't speak Spanish.
I don't know
what you're saying, mate.
No, thanks. I don't--
I don't-- I don't drink.
Esto está en el casa.
I don't drink.
No, thank you.
Tequila.
I know what it is.
I just... No. Gracias.
Irrespetuoso.
You know what?
Fuck it.
Why not?
I'm already dead anyway.
Uno tequila.
Órale!
Oh, that you understand.
Salud.
Cheers, big ears.
Whoo!
All right, uh...
Hola.
Come on. Keep going.
You speak English?
Poquito.
Háganse a un lado, muchachos.
Hasta la vista.
Sorry.
I don't speak Spanish.
Troublemaker.
If any of
your kangaroo bullshit
comes back to bite you
and my daughter is involved...
well, I think we both know
how that one ends, yeah?
Hey, gringo!
You're here.
I work here.
Questionable.
All right. Where
do you want me?
In the back of my limo.
You're a cheeky fuck,
you know that?
Watch the door, el gringo.
Gringos are American, Javi.
So?
So where am I from?
Austria?
England?
Australia. I'm only kidding.
I'm only kidding. Relax.
You just gonna
take up space
or actually uh, you know,
security guard?
All depends.
On?
On when Javi gets me a beer.
Nice precedent to set here.
Gotta keep
the employees happy.
Oh, yeah,
you're a poster boy for happy.
Yeah.
Señor Happy, looks like
you're on the clock.
What'd you say?
You want some?
Little shit.
Okay.
Chill. Relax.
Do not spit in this.
- Hey!
- Mommy!
Okay.
Here we go again.
I know, but I love it
when he does this.
Damn it, Hector!
Go to sleep. Go to sleep.
Okay, everybody,
here's the skinny.
In a couple of seconds,
Hector here is gonna wake up
and he's gonna realize he has
a gun pointed to his head.
That's when I will
stand him up at gunpoint,
grab the backpack
that I came here for,
and slowly, him and I
will walk towards the door.
Bien?
Hey.
Morning, sunshine.
Okay. Up we go. Up we go.
All right. Grab the bag.
There. Thank you.
Now you all seem to understand
English pretty fucking well,
so I don't think
I need to spell out
what happens
if there are any sudden moves.
Bag, please.
Okay. Go, go, go, go!
Whoo!
Jackpot, baby! Look.
How much?
All of it.
Bebe estás sangrando.
Huh?
You're bleeding.
Babe, I-- I don't understand
what you're saying.
Sorry.
My head, bro!
What the fuck
was that for?
You boys are making
the tequila sick.
What's the point
of coming to Mexico?
Culture. Beautiful sights.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Boo.
Yeah, fuck you.
Eat shit!
See you around like a donut...
See ya round
like a donut, fellas!
Baby. Baby, wake up.
Wake up. Baby!
Baby?
Wake up.
Baby, wake up!
We gotta run! Now!
Now!
We gotta move!
Faster, baby.
Babe, stay down.
Great.
Don't move.
You're alive.
Oh, my head.
Yeah, that hurt.
It's dead in here, papi.
We need some música.
Can you, um-- Can you
change the song, please?
Oh, come on.
She's one of yours.
Javi.
Relax.
Better?
Yeah.
Yo, how'd we do?
Not bad for a Tuesday.
And how'd I do?
Oh. Do bouncers get tipped?
Mmm. Mm-hmm.
How much
do they get tipped?
Beer money.
Gracias.
You keep kicking out
these frat boys
before they drunk enough
to tip, papi.
That's exactly why I'm here.
Who the hell
put this shit on?
Not me.
Mmm.
Oh, no.
Don't put it on me.
The point of you being here
is to prevent any trouble.
That's what I do.
I prevent trouble.
Fine line, cabrón.
Not drunk enough, and they take
their big, green, beautiful
dollars down the street.
And if they're too drunk--
Are you paying attention?
This is about you.
Thank you.
They fuck up my bar
by you using them
to mop the floor.
So a bouncer,
and a cleaner.
How can you go wrong?
You're so hard-core, bitch.
It's my bar, bitch.
One for you.
And one for me.
To us.
There he is.
Cabrón.
Ah!
Uy, uy, uy.
Esteban?
See you tomorrow.
Not-- Not if I see you.
Not if I see you what?
Mm-hmm.
First. Not if I see...
Never mind.
Good night, papi.
You sound
sort of funny for a gringo.
That's because
I'm not a gringo.
I told you that already,
Mom.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot.
You traveled a very far way
to Mexico. Why? Why Mexico?
I-- Yeah.
I know why Mexico.
But why stay here,
besides my daughter?
I feel like America
would suit you better.
The land of hopes and dreams.
That's why you came there
in the first place, no?
That's where everybody goes
when they're running
from something.
And you?
You seem like the type of gringo
that's always running
from something.
I don't know what, though.
Again, not a gringo.
That's not really the point,
blanco.
You left Australia because
you were running away.
Broken family?
Maybe, but no,
that's not it.
Mmm. Oh.
To find yourself, or maybe
to run away from yourself.
Ay, but wherever you go,
there you are.
That's a bit cliché.
Mm-hmm.
Donde quiera que vaya,
ahí estás.
It sounds better
in Spanish, verdad?
Everything sounds better
in Spanish.
Mmm. You moved to America
to find the American dream.
And yet, you end up
working as a drug mule
for a Mexican drug cartel.
And poof, there you are,
standing in front
of yourself again.
But...
you literally dodged
my bullets.
And any man
who can survive my bullets...
can take care of my daughter.
Well, with all due respect,
your daughter takes care of me.
Oh.
That's sweet.
Sí.
Ay, ya.
That being said,
any of your kangaroo bullshit
comes back to bite you
and my daughter is involved...
well, I think we both know
how that one ends. Yeah?
All right.
Just let me be.
Yeah.
All right. Stop. Stop.
Do you give up?
Yes, I give up. I give up.
Hey, Marco.
Good to see you too, man.
You good?
I'm good. You good?
Yeah.
All right.
Hair of the dog, huh?
Ah. It's the only cure, mate.
Mmm.
The only cure.
Cheers.
So, last time I saw you,
you were hired to kill me.
No.
Yeah.
You were hired to kill me.
Oh, yeah.
I knew it was something.
Ah, it was something.
You've looked better.
Javi calls it...
homeless chic.
Wasting away again
in Margaritaville.
I'm not wasting
anything, pal.
Mmm.
I finally found a place
I feel like I can be happy in.
Oh... yeah.
Yeah.
Reminds me
of something I lost.
It's my way of staying close.
So how'd you find me, Marco?
There's a storm coming.
Okay, Batman.
I've known where you are
for a minute.
Problem is,
now everyone knows.
'Cause you got a big mouth.
That's not my style, brother.
You know me. Mm-mmm.
Yeah, I know you.
She's alive.
What?
Valentina.
Don't do that.
Valentina is alive.
Marco.
She's alive.
I've seen her.
Marco, you're
fucking with me.
Come here.
No. How? How?
You left too early.
I've seen her.
Her-- Her mother is keeping
her on the compound
like a fucking damsel
surrounded by a dragon.
I'm gonna take you to her.
You back
working for Victoria?
Bitch wants me
just as dead as you.
Well, maybe not
as much as you.
And I have friends.
Had friends.
You said you've seen her.
Okay. What's in it for you?
My honor. My loyalty.
My respect.
And?
Seventy-five grand.
There he is.
Here I am.
Now, do I look like
I have 75 grand?
No.
No?
No, you don't.
But you do.
You stole from Victoria
and got away.
How could you spend
that kind of money down here
without getting noticed?
Times are tough, brother.
As soon as
Romeo finds his Julieta,
I'm getting out of Dodge.
And we're square. Deal?
I hope you're ready to dig.
What?
Please.
I don't understand
what you're saying.
I said you have
too many cavities, gringo.
Consider this a free
dental appointment.
Hey, isn't this
sort of how we met?
Please.
I would be a lot less scared if you speak in English.
Please, please.
Please. Ple--
You're just
gonna leave me here?
Walk until
you can no longer walk.
Please!
Please, no. No! No! No!
No, no, no, no.
Please! No, no, no.
No! No, no, no, no.
No!
You read Spanish?
Let me try.
Saciar La Sed.
Do you understand it?
No.
So the next time
I take her out,
we're starting to
get more comfortable
with each other.
I decide I want to take
her to a horror movie.
Start breaking down
some physical walls.
You know what I mean.
If there's a spooky part,
she reaches over,
grabs my arm,
rests her head
on my shoulder.
By scare three or four,
that armrest is up,
my arm is over her shoulder.
You know what happens next.
But she tells me
she doesn't do horror movies.
Or, like, she hasn't
since she peed her pants
when she was a kid.
She doesn't like 'em.
Perfect.
I can be the hero.
"Don't worry.
You're safe with me.
I got you, babe."
Sonny and Cher.
Ugh. She likes me.
She feels comfortable
with me. She trusts me.
So we go.
The joke's on me.
By the first scare,
she digs her nails into
my arm so badly I bleed.
Scare two,
she bit my shoulder
with her mouth.
Last scare, my arm is
finally around her shoulder.
She gets
so fucking freaked out,
back of her head bops up
and hits me right in the jaw.
My tooth is still loose.
What's funny?
I think
the girl's an easy mark.
What do you mean?
Like putting spiders
in her bed
or putting limbs in places
like her drawers or something.
Leave her cryptic texts
that say,
"Are your doors unlocked?"
And then don't respond
for, like, days.
She'll be so scared
that she'll fall
right into your arms.
The hero, just amplified.
Why didn't I think of that?
Bienvenidos, gringos.
What can I get for you?
Dos cervezas, por favor.
See that?
Even in your native tongue.
Two beers. You got it.
And keep it open.
Oh, man.
We don't really do that.
Oh. I'm really thirsty.
Open. You got it.
No problem.
Sis.
Qué pasó, mija?
You know your rule,
"If you see something,
say something"?
Uh-huh.
See something.
Like ghosts?
No.
Those gringitos?
What are you doing?
Click, click. Bang, bang.
They got guns, bitch.
Why are you telling me?
We have security.
Yes, I know that.
But he's not here.
Yeah,
just a little bit deeper.
Little more.
Nice.
Hello?
Hi. You busy?
No. I can talk. What's up?
Can you come in early?
No, I'm... busy.
Fuck do you do?
You need something, Javi?
It's just...
you're so good at your job
as a security guy.
You're the best security guy.
I only feel safe
when you're here.
Javi, what's going on?
Okay. Don't panic,
but two guys.
Both armed with guns.
At the bar?
Yeah.
Are they robbing it?
No, they just opened a tab.
Do we do that?
No, but when I saw
la pistola,
I stopped paying attention.
Okay, Javi.
I need you to listen to me
very carefully. Okay?
Are you parked out back?
Always.
Are you with Jackie?
Claro, papi.
The two of you
need to go out
and get in the car.
The limo.
Go out and get in the limo
and come and get me. Okay?
Well, who's gonna
watch the bar?
Now, Javi!
Are we in trouble?
I'll explain later.
Just get here.
Don't draw too much attention.
"Don't draw
too much attention."
Let me get that.
What the-- Hey!
We gotta go.
Why do we have to go?
I'm going. I'm going.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm digging.
Why?
For the money.
It's right here.
Yeah, it was in the closet.
Why the fuck
am I digging then?
Because it's fun
to watch you sweat, Marco.
What an asshole!
No time to argue.
We gotta go.
"No time to argue."
We gotta go now.
Digging holes
that we don't need.
What is this?
I think
we've been stood up.
Yeah, because
no one likes you.
They're dust.
Yeah. I see that,
you stupid fuck.
What did I do?
You let them get away.
You left
the fucking tab open.
What does that have to do
with anything?
Get in the fucking car,
Duncan.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Someone want to tell me
what's going on?
Hi, I'm Marco.
Hi, I'm Jackie.
Nice grip.
Now, can someone
please tell me
what the fuck is going on?
Those guys at the bar.
With guns.
They're looking for me.
And anyone around me isn't safe
until I figure this out.
Figure what out?
The less you know,
the better.
This is starting to sound like
some real dark
underworld-type shit, papi.
Wait a second. Is this
some real dark underworld--
Am I gonna die?
Am I the driver?
Javi--
Wait, wait. Those guys.
The gingers.
The what?
The white boys at my bar
that Javi said had guns.
Wait a sec.
They were gringos?
Not tough-looking ones either.
Javi, you know
what gringos are, right?
Papi, white boys
from America.
And that's what they were?
Freckles and everything.
What the fuck is going on,
Marco?
I don't know.
Maybe the old lady
wants to diversify.
We need to make a stop.
Anything else, gringo?
Yeah.
You can take your hand
off that shotgun
and give me a thousand pesos'
worth of gas.
Oh, and a pack of Durry's.
On the house.
Cabrón!
Sorry, Tío.
Again?
Mop that shit up.
Before I come at you like
a candle burning on both ends.
Miguel!
Yeah, Tío.
Take the gas cans with you.
I'm sorry, Tío.
Useless.
Sorry about the shotgun.
I don't remember
if we were cool or not.
You never know with us.
I think three years
is long enough.
I heard you were dead.
Hmm.
But then I heard you weren't,
but you could be.
I'm glad you're still kicking,
mano.
Yeah, you know me.
I kick until my legs don't work.
Then I realized with you
and you-know-who's history--
I've been away.
And now?
I'm back.
You know what happens to me
if I help you?
I do.
I'm done with all that.
I'm clean. I run a business.
I have a family. I'm happy.
I know the feeling.
But then,
I wouldn't even be here
if it weren't for you.
I'm gonna help you.
But the minute your taillights
are out of my sight...
I'm gonna give you 30 minutes
before I call it in.
Valentina's alive, Ramon.
Follow me.
It's safer for you
if you learn
how to speak Spanish.
I already know
Mmm.
No, I don't think so. No.
I do.
That's a number.
What?
Uh...
That's a bad word.
You say it all the time.
I know, but...
Try again.
Okay.
Stop it.
No, no, no, no, no.
Stop it. You're like--
Say it with me.
Okay.
Repeat with me.
Okay. Go.
Valentina...
See?
That sounds good.
Mmm.
I'm halfway
through Rosetta Stone.
Who is Rosita Stone?
What?
Who is she?
Why are you laughing?
It's a book.
Book.
Yeah. I learn Spanish.
Well, I'm not
that far through it.
I said you just need
to hang out with more Mexicans.
Hmm.
You're such a white boy.
You know that.
But I'll teach you.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Huh?
Retired, huh?
Insurance policy.
This is everything.
Hasn't been touched
in three years.
She better be worth it.
She's everything.
Come out
with your hands up!
We have you surrounded!
Don't look at me.
I was with you.
Okay,
what the fuck?
Ah, lookee here.
Surrounded?
Yeah, man. Why the fuck
did you say surrounded?
It's what
you're supposed to say.
What who's supposed to say,
the bomb squad?
It doesn't fucking matter.
Both of you shut up!
Damn Mexican standoff
in my own gas station.
Sir, we don't
mean to intrude.
If you'll just be a doll
and drop your gun,
we'll take these three
and be on our way.
Three?
Why are you taking him?
Marco Antonio Benitez
is wanted in four
different countries.
No, dumbass. Him!
This man's now wanted
for helping two fugitives
avoid arrest.
Miguel?
He can't even mop
the fucking floor.
Wait, who?
Marvin, who the fuck is that?
Who's who?
The guy you're pointing
the fucking gun at.
This is Javi.
That's not Javi,
you idiot.
I'm Miguel.
Hola. Me llamó Javi.
Fuck!
You guys
are really bad at this.
What the fuck
do we do now, man?
I don't know.
What are we supposed to do--
We're gonna die.
Everybody okay?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You guys gotta jet.
You guys go!
What about you?
Don't worry about me.
You're no good to her dead.
Cover us.
Vámonos, vámonos!
Get in! Get in!
Go, go, go, go!
Tío.
It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Tío.
Okay. Nuh-uh.
I'm gonna take a break.
You're such a pussy.
How fucking dare you.
Fuck you.
This shit is different.
It hurts.
Just hurry up.
This shit,
it's gonna be on you forever.
You already have tattoos.
Yeah, but I was drunk
every time.
You want a beer?
Yes.
Too bad.
I'm already done, güey.
It looks pretty good.
It does, actually. Yes.
Well... I think
we are forever now.
Yeah.
Looks like
you're stuck with me.
Mmm.
...you still have to prove
to me you're worth it.
Oh, is that right?
Mm-hmm.
You know something,
you're worth it.
What the fuck was that?
A fucking ambush.
Someone tipped her off.
Ramon's a lot of things,
but he's not a rat.
Who the fuck is her?
Victoria Ventura
De La Cruz-Santana.
What?
I take it
you've heard of her.
Yeah.
Everybody's heard of her.
How do you know her?
I just know her.
How?
Like I fucking
know her, Javi!
I'm sorry.
Look, I didn't mean
for any of this.
Man, I did good
back there though, no?
Yeah, mate. You did good.
What! You don't fuck
with Javier Manuel!
Okay.
Should I drive?
No.
Are you sure?
I... Okay.
What is this?
Where are we?
My abuelito's old cow farm.
It's off the grid.
No one's finding us here.
Mmm. Where's Abuelito?
Heaven.
I'm sorry, man.
Nah. He was
a mean old man anyway.
Oh, fuck him then.
Wow.
Power?
It's a generator situation.
Are you turning it on?
One sec, man.
I just got in.
Can I put my shit down?
My shit's down.
It's in the shed out back.
I know you don't think
I'm going out there
in these shoes.
I'll go with you.
Jean-Pierre.
I stepped in a pile
of my own dog's shit today.
Now I know my little Pepito
would never shit
where I was walking
on purpose.
So why am I stepping in shit?
Don't we have someone for this?
He's not doing his job, boss.
No, he's not
doing his job at all.
Kill him.
My little Pepito.
I miss his face.
He's a cute puppy, eh, boss?
The cutest.
I heard you stepped in shit.
Barefoot.
Ooh. The worst.
You have something for me?
You don't need to count.
I know.
Do you remember
when we first met?
Yeah, of course.
It's a shame.
She was pretty.
Very pretty, boss.
I wanted no survivors.
And yet here you are.
I made a call to a bar,
my bar,
right outside the border
to intercept you...
That's a rough bar.
I'm lucky
Valentina was there.
She interfered
with my business.
She knows better.
She's your daughter.
The only reason
she's still alive.
Was it a coincidence
that she was there?
Maybe,
but I don't think so.
When it comes to you,
I don't think
there are coincidences.
You got stabbed tonight.
Fuck!
It's nothing.
Well, I bet that nothing only
missed a vital organ by what?
Mere centimeters.
Anyone else would have
probably bled out,
but not you. No.
You can shoot the boy.
You can blow this boy up.
Whew. Fuck.
But he just won't die.
Well, I'm sorry
to disappoint you.
Mmm.
You're gonna break
your daughter's heart.
This gun left
my daughter fatherless.
Do you think that I can't kill
some pretty-boy drug mule
who has been nothing
but a thorn in my fucking side?
I'm not a drug mule anymore.
Why do you think that is?
Because
I'm difficult to kill.
And you would lose
your best guy,
which means
you would lose your money.
Your best quality.
I feel like
you're getting a little cocky.
And I feel like you're using
my daughter as a shield.
What do you think
your life would be like
if I decided to separate
the two of you?
I am going to marry Valentina,
even if it kills me.
I'd prefer to do it
with your blessing.
I've showed you my loyalty
and I have proved to you
that I will do anything
for your daughter.
We only have one more deal
left on our agreement.
And I hope that deal
still stands.
For all of our sakes.
A threat?
Ooh, no.
Please.
I would never threaten you.
We're family, after all.
That's a lot of guns.
Gonna need 'em.
Must've made
a lot of mistakes.
I only ever made
one mistake.
I fell in love
with the daughter
of a very dangerous person.
Falling in love,
that doesn't
sound like a mistake.
That wasn't the mistake.
The mistake was
believing her mother.
Victoria?
She took everything from me.
I'll head out with Marco
in the morning.
You and Jackie stay here
and lay low for a while.
I'm on the journey now, coz.
Yeah.
Any other day,
I would just be at the bar,
slinging beers for people
I don't want to know,
who don't want to know me.
But today, I'm on the run
with my friend.
For my friend.
To rescue
the love of his life.
It's fucking--
It's romantic, man.
Javi, this isn't--
And I'm the getaway driver!
Papi, I get to be that guy.
I never get to be that guy.
So you're stuck with me.
And I get the big one.
We have to leave tonight.
It's already set.
You think
this is your last one?
How many guns are you bringing?
Going out with a bang.
She has an army.
Why are you going alone?
Because she's testing me.
And if you fail?
I'm tired of running,
Valentina.
If we run,
she's just gonna find us.
And if she doesn't,
we'll still just be running.
She won't let me go.
A deal's a deal.
And my mother is a liar.
I will do anything
to keep us together.
Valentina, we don't--
we don't have
any other options here.
And if this works...
she said she'd walk you
down the aisle herself.
If it doesn't work?
It's like a chainsaw.
Just pull harder.
Oh, no, I know. I've-- I've--
I've used those for...
other things.
I'm not a lumberjack.
Maybe the gas is old.
What?
You seem to know a lot
about generators.
I own a shitty bar
in a small town.
Power's always out.
All right.
Oh, fuck!
So... who was that woman
at the gas station?
I have no idea.
So how long
you two known each other?
Him? Oh, uh,
we used to work together.
Doing what?
This and that.
Mostly that?
Mostly that.
So... what happened?
Our boss--
Victoria.
Victoria. Yeah. She hated him.
I mean, she hated everyone
who worked for her,
to be honest.
Would punish us
for stupid things.
Make us clean up
her dog's shit.
Things like that.
But not him.
Oh, no.
He was the fuckin' best.
A beast.
Also... impossible to kill.
Like a fucking roach.
And she hated that about him.
She wanted him dead?
Oh, since the moment
she laid eyes on him. Yeah.
So why didn't she do it?
Someone was protecting him.
Her daughter. Valentina.
She loved him.
And he loves her.
"Loved"?
Well, she doesn't know
he's alive.
And he didn't know she was alive
until I showed up.
So...
why did you show up?
I owe him.
I said it was for the money,
but I owe him.
You know the dog shit duty?
It was my turn one day,
and I said, "No, fuck it.
I'm not a fucking lackey.
I'm a goddamn
professional assassin."
As you can imagine,
that didn't sit well with her.
Who did she send after me?
The one person who could
actually pull it off.
Thing is, he didn't show.
He took the money,
took her daughter and they ran.
And the fucked-up thing
is that I would have done it.
I would have taken the money
and put a bullet in his head
if she asked me to.
That's why I showed up.
I am alive
because he has honor.
And honor is something
you show up for.
You wanna try the genny
one more time?
Yes, I think I will.
Did I do it?
That wasn't the genny.
Shit.
How did they find us?
We gotta go! We gotta go.
What the fuck?
Fuck.
She found us.
Marco!
Javi!
Did you think I would miss
my daughter's wedding?
Valentina.
There's only one target
that I have never hit.
I'm begging you.
I love him.
No, Mama.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Valentina!
You ready to be
the guy, Javi?
Yeah.
Who the fuck are you?
Oh, fuck.
Papi?
Javi.
No, no, no.
You're all right.
Papi.
Shh. You're okay.
You're okay.
You're okay. You're okay, buddy.
Yeah, you're okay.
I got to be that guy.
You, uh-- You are that guy.
Yeah.
You're that guy.
I'm that guy.
No. No, no.
No.
No! Stop! No!
No, no, no, no.
No.
I didn't know.
Bueno.
Sí.
I'll check
if he's still available.
Oh, you don't wanna talk?
I get it. That's okay.
Maybe you just listen then.
Did you really think that
you could get back to her?
Did you really think
I would let that happen?
You were my big fish.
And anyone who knows me knows
I always catch my fish.
But you refuse to die.
And so my fish
falls off the hook.
And who catches my fish?
My only daughter.
The only person
I love in this world
besides myself.
You can imagine the moral
conundrum this puts me in.
There are many things
in this world
that you can't control.
Life. Death. And love.
You fell in love
with the wrong person.
That is--
That is not your fault.
No. What is your fault
is that
you were supposed to die
the day that I found you.
But you cheated. You ran.
And because you cheated,
my daughter was placed
in the line of fire.
Holy shit.
This is like
Romeo and Juliet.
And we both know
how that ends.
I wanted to kill you
for a long time.
But what would my daughter
think if I did that?
I did make the order
that got my daughter killed.
But miracles, they happen.
Some people get second chances
and I'm getting mine.
And I'm going to make sure
that you never get yours.
You will never hold her
in your arms again.
Or your son.
My...
My what?
Oh.
You didn't know.
Why couldn't you
just let us go?
We were so close
to a new life.
A new life?
My daughter's life was perfect
before you came into it.
She never needed
anything from you
and she never will again,
and neither will my grandson.
Everyone around you dies,
except you.
And I think it is time
for everyone around you
to go into remission.
No.
You told me
I just had to watch him.
Please.
I don't want to do this.
But I owe her.
I owe her a lot.
You know what it's like
to owe her.
And maybe one day,
I'll be laying where you are,
but not today.
I'm sorry.
I love it here.
It's where I feel happiest.
Sitting here next to you.
What is it?
I don't know
what's going to happen.
We never know
what's gonna happen.
Two worlds that collided.
For a reason.
And what's the reason?
So that we could
build a new world.
A better one.
And if it doesn't work?
If we want it to, it will.
I want it.
Me too.
What happens next?
Now I take care of you.
If any
of your kangaroo bullshit
comes back to bite you
and my daughter is involved...
well, I think we both know
how that one ends, yeah?