Emma.
Wake up, Emma.
Emma. Wake up.
Momma?
Yeah. Shhh.
We're going to go
chase the sunrise, ok?
Ok.
But you have to be quiet.
Come on, sweetie. Up, up.
Give me your feet.
There you go.
Good girl.
Go grab your backpack.
Come here. Come here. Come here.
Put your backpack on.
Don't forget your
rhino. Ok sweetie?
Come on.
Ok.
Come on up.
Here we go.
Take off your backpack.
Keep your rhino.
Where's Daddy?
It's ok, love.
It's just a girls trip, ok?
Ok.
You want to see
the countryside, right?
Where Mommy grew up?
It's going to be great.
It's going to be
really really great.
Alex, don't!
Give me the keys!
Come here, bug.
Come here.
Let's get you back inside
and give Mommy a moment.
Shhh. You have to be quiet.
Why? What is it?
We're in the night forest
where it's always nighttime.
And when it's nighttime
all the bad feelings come out.
Brrr. I feel cold.
Maybe I should sing
a song to keep us warm.
No. Shhh. Don't.
The bad feelings will hear you.
They're everywhere.
Quick, we gotta make it
back to the castle before...
Ha ha ha!
Oh no! The Mud Witch!
I can grow anywhere!
My dress is the ground!
What were you thinking?
Stop.
Just stop.
What? And leave you alone?
Leave you alone so you can grab
up everything and yank it out of
my life?
Oh, like you care.
All you care about is
your writing and your career.
Forest fairies, eat this dress!
Yum, yum, yum!
Are there any bugs in it?
Lots!
Delicious!
Every time I have a deadline...
Every time I have a hard burn
you pull something like this.
You don't see anything
I do around here?
Stop making this about you.
About me?
About me?!
You were gonna take Emma.
Emma, sweetie.
I thought you were playing.
You know you shouldn't
be playing on the stairs.
But I needed space
for the night forest.
Come on.
Let's get you back to bed.
Here we go.
Why was Mommy crying?
I don't know, bug.
It's complicated.
Your mother is a
complicated woman.
And she has her moments.
And you have to yell at her?
I shouldn't have yelled.
But yelling isn't the only thing
that makes things mean.
The important thing is
that we work through it.
We clean up the mess.
That's right.
Family is work...
Just like anything.
Maybe we should
get Mommy flowers.
Maybe we should get Mommy...
Like, a purple flower, or...
Some color she
hasn't seen like...
A rainbow flower or
a unicorn flower.
You see colors like that?
When I dream sometimes.
Wish I could dream like that.
It'd make writing my book
a heck of a lot easier.
Tell you what...
Tomorrow, when you're
done dreaming...
We'll go and we'll see what
we can do for Mommy, ok?
Ok.
I love you, Daddy.
Love you too.
Goodnight, bug,
I'll be on the couch.
You do whatever you want to do.
The moon is big.
That's a full moon.
It doesn't happen every night.
I wish I could go there.
You can.
I could take one of the clouds.
Yeah.
But clouds drift so...
You need a way to make them go
where you want them to go.
Now...
Close your eyes, love.
Close your eyes.
And float far away.
No, I can't forget this evening.
Or your face as
you were leaving.
But I guess that's just
the way the story goes.
You always smile but in
your eyes your sorrow shows.
Yes, it shows.
Night, beauty.
I'm done now, Alex. I'm done!
Nice. Real nice, Sara.
You scream and you yell.
You poor victim!
You treat me like garbage
in front of our own daughter!
You push and you push...
And I shove back and
then I'm the problem?!
You're the one who wants
to destroy this house.
I just want out!
You want out?
All right.
Fine! You want out?
Say goodbye to the credit cards!
Good mooch off your parents
and see how far you go!
Sorry I'm such a burden to you!
Sara, with everything
I've got going on...
I cannot be responsible
for your feelings.
Stop saying that!
Then do something for yourself!
I just want you to listen!
Stop!
No, stop!
Emma, sweetie.
No, I'm never going to
talk to you ever again!
Dispatch 17-24 to
Ambulance 12-49...
What's your status?
Ambulance 12-49 to Dispatch...
We've arrived at
the residence...
Confirming Y92.
One female girl, five years old,
breathing but unresponsive.
Possible head trauma.
Both parents on scene.
Call number 16-0-7-5.
17-24 Dispatcher to
Ambulance 4 and medic...
Engine 2 to scene.
Call number 16-0-7-5.
Dispatch 17-24 to
Ambulance 12-49...
What's the chief complaint
and situation?
MS 12-49 to Dispatch...
Proceeding with medical.
Administering I.V. for
adrenaline boost.
What did we do to our baby?
Oh god.
It's ok, baby.
It's ok.
She's going to be okay.
Is she going to be ok?
No, no...
One, two, three.
Can you please be
careful with her?
Sarah.
Can you...
We just need to stabilize her
neck in case there's any damage.
She could be bleeding.
Please, Ma'am, stay back.
No, no, no.
Please don't tie her down!
Sara!
Do not!
Alex! Can you tell them!
Mommy! Daddy! I'm here!
Stop it, Alex! Stop it!
Daddy!
I'm here!
I'm here. Mommy!
Listen to me...
Sara!
This is my baby! Stop!
Mommy!
Let them do their job, baby.
Let them do their job, ok?
Mommy.
Don't cry.
Can you put her on
her side please.
I'm right here, Mommy.
She likes to sleep on her side.
Can you put her on
her side please?
Alex, please tell them she
likes to sleep on her side.
No!
What did we do?
Emma!
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Hey!
You're ok! You're ok!
Momma.
There was something
in the water.
Something got my leg!
Everything's ok.
I'm right here, ok?
Nothing got your leg.
You're trying to stand up, bug.
Did you feel yourself
trying to stand up?
What I want you to do...
I want you to kick
your feet, alright?
Ok.
I want you to kick your feet
through the water, alright?
Pick your feet up.
Now kick yourself
through the water. Ready?
Kick your feet. Kick your feet!
Now move your arms.
Move your arms too!
Move your arms!
There you go!
Yes!
Keep going!
There you go. You're
doing it, Emma!
Look at that!
What? What are you doing?
You're doing it!
Doing like a champ!
- Daddy! Come watch me!
- Wow!
Look at you, bug!
You swimming on your own?
Yeah!
Are you holding on to her?
Not anymore.
There you go, buddy.
Want to go to Daddy?
Yeah.
Ok.
Ready?
Set!
Don't forget to kick your feet.
Go!
Emma?
Hey little beauty.
It's ok.
Mommy's here.
Wherever you are, Emma.
Be strong.
Be brave.
It's gonna be okay.
Well, I can't forget
this evening...
And your face when
you were leaving...
But I guess that's just
the way the story goes.
You always smile but in
your eyes your sorrow shows.
Yes, it shows.
I can't live...
If living is without you.
I can't give anymore.
I can't live...
If living is without you.
I can't give anymore.
Thank you, little girl.
Again, again!
I'm afraid you'll have to wait.
Is it broken?
I'm afraid so.
Everything can't
work all the time.
I wish I was home right now.
My Mommy's so sad I'm not there.
Are you lost, little girl?
I'm sorry to hear that.
Can we call them?
No, we can't call them here.
But I do know where you can.
But it's far away and high up.
How will I know
where to find it?
If you listen just right...
You'll hear the signal.
You'll know it.
If you ever get lost...
Consider the future...
Imagine how you get there.
Thank you.
Uh oh.
You woke it up.
You better run, little girl.
Go. Now.
Let me see how fast you can run.
You sit up so straight
when I read to you
stuffed animals and
some of your toys
all kinds of things from home...
I am so sorry...
Daddy, he's been
working here too
working so hard for us...
I love you, sweetie.
This way! Straight! Straight!
Alright. Straight, alright.
- Which way am I going?
- This way! This way!
Why would I go
over to the wall?!
Oh, my nose! My nose!
Left, left, left!
You're guiding me
into the walls.
This way.
Alright, here we go.
Hop up here.
Oh, you silly goose.
You're a silly goose!
It's so dark in here.
Yeah, we're using
a lot of power.
Just getting used to what we
can do with the new house.
Does the house need batteries?
The house doesn't use batteries.
It has its own power
it draws from the city.
Electrical power.
Like lightning.
That kind of power.
Sara?!
That do anything?!
The walls are scratching.
Maybe it's a spider.
Or maybe it's...
Grandpa's teeth.
And they're trapped
in the wall...
And they're chattering around
until we come find them.
It's probably just a
squirrel or a raccoon.
Yeah, it got trapped in there
whenever the house was empty.
Can we fix it?
Sure.
Of course.
Every problem has a solution.
Voila.
I brought you some things.
Just toys and a few books.
I know you probably feel like
you're in some far off place.
But I want you to
feel like you're home.
The doctor said it's good
for us to talk to you.
For you to hear our voices.
I remember when you
were just a little thing.
And I would wonder
how you saw me.
A blurry shapeless thing?
Was I a darkness?
I always tried to
do the right thing.
For you and for your mom.
Every day I tried
to take care of her.
But it's all such a mess.
You have this idea
of yourself...
I'm never going to make
it to you like this, Daddy.
How things are
going to turn out.
And then you grow up...
And you look around
and everything is different.
I loved that it was
just me, you and Mom.
Maybe I never showed
it the right way.
Maybe I wasn't around as
much as I could have been.
You brought nothing
but beauty into my life.
You were all the good things.
You are all the good things.
Life doesn't stop.
Bills don't stop.
I don't know our insurance
is going to...
I'm on my way, Daddy!
Left! Left!
Now we're moving!
Mommy?
Hey sweetie.
What are you doing?
I'm celebrating.
It's my birthday today.
I didn't know it
was your birthday.
You're losing all
of your balloons.
I'm just watching
them dance, sweetie.
You know when I was your age...
I couldn't wait for my birthday.
I looked forward
to it every year.
Grandpa would set
up the barbecue and...
Grandma would dress
the entire yard.
Tables with glitter,
ribbons and balloons...
And the backyard would
just go and go and go.
We didn't even need shoes.
We just let the
grass clean our feet.
You want to go get some cake
and blow out candles for wishes?
You know what I wish for, love?
What?
I wish you could
have what I had.
What did you have?
The fields and the woods
and the open air.
You want to go somewhere?
It's okay, sweetie.
There's nowhere to go anyway.
Made you some tea.
The tea always tastes funny
when you make it.
I can't even boil water right.
It's not about that.
It's about the right
amount of honey.
Mine tastes good because
it's made with love.
Yours tastes like
you're just doing it.
So you can get back to
whatever it is you care about.
I didn't create a deadline
to annoy you, Sara.
No, you do your job,
and I'll do mine.
Hey bug.
Take really good
care of Mommy, ok?
And in those eyes...
I'd see all the things you'd do.
I figured you'd either be a
rockstar or marry a rockstar.
Bring some dirtbag home...
And I'd have to put up with him.
Watch him stomp his muddy boots
all over the place.
That stuff seems so far away.
Hello.
It's so dark in here.
Can you play some
music, little lady?
I thought I knew you.
You're the new maid.
You'll have to
clean up the mess.
Scrub-a-dub dub.
Scrub, scrub, scrub, dub.
Scrub, scrub, scrub,
scrub, scrub...
Scrub, scrub, scrub...
Scrub, scrub, scrub,
scrub, scrub...
Scrub, scrub, scrub...
Scrub, scrub.
There's no immediate
soft tissue damage.
At least that we can
see in the imaging.
And there's no other way
to tell what's going on?
Any other tests?
Unfortunately we just
can't see brain function.
And her breathing is slowing?
That's correct.
If her breathing
continues to deteriorate...
Her heart could literally stop.
Jesus.
She's strong enough.
I don't want one of
those things over her face.
Sara. Please. Just
listen to him.
There is a procedure.
An ECMO.
Essentially, we
funnel out her blood.
We filter it, we oxygenate it,
then we introduce it into her
system.
The new reoxygenated blood could
cause the brain to suddenly wake
up.
Ok, well that's something.
Ok.
Think it over.
Don't do that.
Don't you dare do that.
Sara, calm down.
You want to cut her open?
Go ahead and try.
But you going to have
to cut through me first.
You want to talk about it?
You want to have a rational
discussion about this.
Oh, you can't be
nasty here, right?
Because people might hear you?
Please.
You want me out of here?
Then you're going
to have to drag me out.
You can help her.
You can help her be strong
by being strong yourself.
You need to get some sleep.
Try to rest.
And then what?
Then what happens when
she's all alone in the dark?
We can talk about what to do.
We can be proactive.
Consider things.
I love you.
More than there are
stars in the sky.
I love you more than
there are stars in the sky.
Mommy.
No.
No!
Ha! Hack-a-doodle!
Hack-a-doodle, knock-a-knockin!
Knock-a-doodle knock-a-knockin!
Knock-a-doodle, knock-a-knockin.
Momma, can you get
up and play now?
I'm bored.
You've been sleeping
for like ever.
Mommy's so tired.
Why don't you just
come cuddle me, ok?
Ok.
I know a game.
But you're going to have to
close your eyes for this, love.
Ok.
Ok?
Close your eyes.
Inside your mind I want you
to start to draw a picture.
I want you to imagine
the most perfect day.
Let's start with the weather.
Is it warm or is it cold?
It's warm.
That's good.
And how does the air
feel on your arms?
We're floating.
Perfect.
And when we're floating, what
do you see when you look around?
I see a cloud boat.
Oh, that sounds magical.
And who's on the boat with you?
You and me.
And where's Daddy?
He's not there because
he doesn't make you happy.
Are you ok?
You...
Don't blink.
Don't smile.
You smiled!
You're blinking!
You did it first!
- You did it first!
What's that?
Sara!
It's Daddy.
We gotta hide.
Go deeper and deeper in here.
Come on. Go under the blankets.
Sara!
It's almost noon.
Are you still not up yet?
Yeah, I'm...
I'm here, Alex.
Come on. It's not healthy.
Get out!
Hey!
Daddy?
Are you ever going
to stop working?
Emma, I told your mother
not to let you down here.
I've been working all day trying
to provide for you and this
family.
And I have a few extra hours
to work on my novel...
Which is what I
really want to do.
I just need to be left alone.
So please...
Please...
Don't interrupt me.
We who are three...
We see it crimson.
We see red.
We see something.
Something different.
We see something long ago...
A sheltered young Princess...
Who knew nothing
beyond her castle walls.
Birds would glide past her
window and she would say...
If only I knew what it was
to be so alive, so free.
Years passed slowly
for the Princess.
Until her father and mother, the
king and queen, were struck...
By viral intestinal tract
infections from a bad poultry
epidemic which...
Swept through the
kingdom that summer.
Holed up in her tower, the
Princess nearly went mad with
loneliness.
Endless tears clouded her eyes.
Darkness filled her heart.
Her despair knew no end.
Until one day she heard
something down in the courtyard.
A sound so free
it shook something loose.
The sound of children.
And at once the Princess knew
what would cure her loneliness.
To become a human child.
The Princess sent for
her five best scouts.
Bring me the most powerful
witch in all the kingdom!
The scouts roamed the land,
scouring the rims of the
kingdom...
Until one morning, they came
across some magical great Crane.
Bah!  the Crane boomed.
For years I have searched for a
place where no one would find
me.
Who disturbs my solitude?
The scouts dragged the magical
great Crane before the Princess.
And from the
Crane's severed head
perched on its dead tongue
sat a golden
shimmering Witch Toad.
The Witch Toad gazed
into the Princess's heart.
And knew her one true desire.
Each child in the
kingdom fell silent.
Their bright, shining spirit...
Stolen.
With each passing day the
Princess's hunger for children
grew.
And without the
singsong of children
the kingdom faded
into a gray and lifeless place.
And for the first time in her
life the Princess felt light,
and free.
Like a feather on the wind.
But then time passed.
First days
weeks
years.
Every night the Princess found
herself sitting alone in her
tallest tower...
Not daring to speak.
Instead she patiently listened
for one sound of happiness
one sound of life.
It was a sound which never came.
Hey.
Can you help me?
It's ok.
Come on.
Wait here. I'm going
to go get my radio.
Emma, sweetie?
I'm so sorry I couldn't...
I couldn't be there.
Everyone is trying so hard here.
All the doctors.
Everybody.
Sometimes I think he's just
telling us what we want to hear.
They were hoping
you would wake up.
That the procedure would work.
But the doctors are
seeing any change.
I knew they wouldn't.
But I know how strong you are.
And I know deep in my bones
that as much as we do here
it's up to you.
You have to find a
way out of the dark.
And when you do, I'll be here.
Come follow me.
Emma, listen to me.
Just pull yourself up.
Pull. Pull yourself up.
Don't use me. You can do it.
You can do it.
Come on. You can.
No, I can't.
I'm letting go.
No, no!
You got it. Emma.
Emma, you got it.
I'm going to let go and you're
going to climb up all by
yourself.
All right. I'm going to let go.
But you're gotta pull.
Ok, pull.
Use your own strength.
You're doing this
all by yourself.
You can do it.
You can do it. That's it.
You've got it.
Pull.
That's it.
So good.
Keep pulling.
You did it!
I see you.
I see you. You did it.
All by yourself.
Ok. Ready? Ok?
I got you. You did so good.
So strong.
That's you.
I know you can hear me, beauty.
Across the stars.
My voice will carry...
I miss my Mommy and Daddy.
Where are they?
I'm trying to call them.
But we're floating
the other way.
I don't think I'm ever going
to see them again.
Ever, ever again.
You know...
After all the voices in
my kingdom went quiet,
and whenever I would
get sad or feel lonely...
I would lock myself in my room.
And I would stay very still.
And I would think about
what friends would be like
if I had them.
What their names would be.
The jokes they would tell.
What their laugh would be like.
I wanted so much
to be loved by others.
That I never learned to
love anyone but myself.
I never learned how my love
could bring people closer to me.
I wish I knew more
when I was young.
I wish I had known
more when I was young.
I wish I had known that the
world was bigger than how I
felt.
I wish I had known
that the world was bigger
than how I felt.
Then there would
still be beauty.
There would still be magic.
Well, I suppose if you...
Yeah.
I mean, it's only been
two months, but...
It's a really
interesting experience.
Really?
Yeah.
That's what you're calling it?
Interesting. Very interesting...
Yeah, well...
It was such an interesting
moment. Between us.
Thanks for coming.
I really appreciate that.
Yeah, I would've
been there sooner
I know you are.
But you've done it before and...
Can you lift me?
Of course.
No, I...
Can't forget this evening.
Or your face as
you were leaving.
But I guess that's just
the way the story goes.
You always smile but in your
eyes your sorrows shows.
Yes, it shows.
No, I can't forget tomorrow.
When I think of all my sorrow.
When I had you there...
But then I let you go.
And now it's only fair
that I should let you know...
What you should know.
Mommy.
I hear you.
My love.
I'm here.
Emma?
Mommy.
My love.
Hey, stay with me.
I'm right here.
It's ok.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, Emma.
I want to go home.
It's ok, Emma.
Hey, I need your help.
I need your help.
I want you to imagine
the most perfect day.
Can you do that for me?
What does it look like?
What does it look like, Emma?
Emma?
There you go.
Stay with it.
How does it feel?
The most perfect day.
Can you picture it?
See it for what it is.
You're just all empty.
Emma?
I know you can still hear me.
Focus on the details.
The moment.
Picture it.
Clear as a memory.
Clear as today.
Now
tell me the story
of your perfect day.
I'm still in my PJs.
We get up really, really early
before the sun is up.
Momma?
Yeah. Shhh.
We're gonna go chase
the sunrise, ok?
We have to be extra quiet
because we're the only ones
awake.
Come on up.
Here you go.
Take off your backpack.
Keep your rhino.
We get our best things
and our favorite toys,
so we can play all day.
What?
I look outside,
and I can see the whole sky,
and the full moon.
There is a face in
it smiling at me.
The face is happy.
So I hum a song.
And all the stars start dancing.
Then the moon and stars
shine on the water.
Twinkling like lightning bugs.
It smells like soggy shoes.
But that's okay cause
we're outside...
And it's suppose to smell
like soggy shoes and things.
We find a spot under a big tree.
And we grow a house
out of the mud.
You're making blueberry tea
and ice cream stones...
While me and Daddy play.
He never has to work.
So we play all the time.
And then Daddy skips a rock
all the way across the water.
Until it hits a
toad in the mouth.
And it burps again and again
without saying excuse me.
And no one can find us because
we're so far in the forest.
And no one knows we're there.
Mommy's in!
There's nothing but magic.
And you and Daddy
can't stop smiling
because you're both so happy.
And then the nighttime
knows it's over.
So it rolls on its side and...
Yawns itself to sleep.
But then the sun peeks out.
A perfect morning
to a perfect day.
No, I...
Can't forget this evening.
Or your face as
you were leaving.
But I guess that's just
the way the story goes.
You always smile but
in your eyes your sorrow shows.
Yes, it shows.
No, I can't forget tomorrow
when I think of all my sorrow.
When I had you there
but then I let you go.
And now it's only fair
that I should let you know...
What you should know.
I can't live if
living is without you.
I can't live.
I can't give anymore.
I can't live if
living is without you.
I can't live.
I can't give anymore.
No, I...