- Stop moving it!
- I'm not moving it.
I thought you were moving it.
- No.
- Then it
must be the spirits.
- Please
try and be serious.
- Okay, fine.
- Are there any
spirits here with us?
That's it! We're done!
Do it yourself!
- Laura! You know I
need you for safety.
The devil's not gonna
fuck with a virgin.
Okay, fine. I was
totally moving it.
- It's not funny. Viola!
How are we supposed
to contact anyone
if you're messing
around with it?
- Relax. It's just a game.
Where did you get this
one? It looks really old.
- It was this
weird store in town.
- You think it actually works?
- Yeah, I kind of do.
I used it last night and
someone came through.
- As if!
- I'm serious.
- Oh yeah? Who'd you contact?
- You're gonna think I'm crazy.
- Too late.
- I think it was Mary Blackwood.
- The witch of Hazel Street?
Okay, fine.
Let's see what the old
hag has to say tonight.
- I don't think
that's a good idea.
- We want to speak to the
spirit of Mary Blackwood.
Are you there?
- You heard that?
- Most definitely.
No one else is home?
Are all the doors walked?
- I think so.
It could be Tim! He said
he was gonna stop by.
I wouldn't put it past
him to try and scare us.
- And when were
you gonna tell me
you took that trifling
man whore back?
- He promised me the
rumors weren't true.
- Oh, he promised?
Because he's always been nothing
but 100% percent truthful
since you met him.
- I know you don't like him.
- Sweetie, I know he looks like
he got off the casting couch
of Dawson's Creek,
but he has the personality
of a box of hair.
Come on, let's call his bluff.
- What if it's not him?
What if it's something else?
- Like who? Mary Blackwood?
- Tim!
- So original, Timothy.
- It worked on you, Vi.
- What the hell
are you doing here?
- I came to steal my girlfriend
back from your clutches.
- Which girlfriend?
- V, stop!
- I didn't know you girls
were raising the dead.
- Sure are.
You gonna join us ore
are you too scared?
- Let's do it.
- Tim, no, you don't have to.
- Come on, babe. It'll be fun.
Who we contacting?
- The witch. Mary Blackwood.
- Yeah, I thought she
was an urban legend.
- No, it's public record.
The people of the town
hanged her from the tree
and then burned
her body to ashes.
- All right.
Come on, Mary Blackwood,
take a break from
being Satan's whore
and show us that
hagged face of yours.
- I didn't do it. I swear.
- Relax. It was probably
just your breaker.
Where's your fuse box?
- In the attic.
- Of course it is.
- Tim, no, maybe you shouldn't!
- Hello? Is someone there?
- Laura, are you okay?
- When I used the
board last night,
I just wanted to know if
Tim was cheating on me.
- What'd it say?
- It said yes.
- See?
Even a dead witch
knows he's trash.
- I was so mad, I told her
I wanted Tim to be dead.
- Same, girl.
What's the problem?
- Last night I had a
dream that he was dead,
killed by the witch,
and it felt so real.
- It's fine.
It was just a dream.
- Tim!
- Laura, he's just
messing with us.
- Tim, this isn't funny!
No!
It's her!
It's the witch!
Who are you?
♪ This invented madness
- Oh, good morning, Sarah.
- Morning, Viola.
- Oh, I guess "mom" is
too formal these days.
- Morning, mother. Better?
- Yeah.
Can I make you a little
coffee? Something?
- That's okay. I
have to get to work.
- Ugh, I get so
worried about you
working at that bar so late.
I wish you could
find something else.
- Yeah, well, I
don't love it either,
but how else am I gonna
get a place of my own?
- Yeah, I know you're
really not happy
about being back here.
I'm sure your stepmom's
place was so much bigger.
- It was, but I kind
of got the feeling
she wanted me out of
there as soon as possible.
- What makes you say that?
- She told me she
wanted me out of there
as soon as possible.
- That rotten woman.
To her own stepdaughter?
- Mom, it's fine.
- No, it's not fine!
I'm gonna call her.
I'm gonna give her
a piece of my mind!
- Just forget about it.
She said I remind
her too much of him.
- Honey, I'm sorry.
- Okay, I have to get to work.
- He was like, "Bro, I
heard all that screaming
in the room and everything."
I was like, "Yeah, that was me."
- Now you need to rub
some of that charisma off
on my little brother here.
- Oh, it's definitely
coming, man.
It's going on tonight.
Ain't that right, baby?
- Yeah. You ready to pop
that cherry, little brother?
- I don't know.
- I'm gonna
get 'em together.
Don't you worry about this, man.
I'm gonna get some titties
in your face, okay?
- Great! How long
have they been here?
- Long enough to make me
thankful I'm not a breeder.
- We should all be so lucky.
- And, tag, you're it.
- Don't do me any favors.
- I'll be your best friend.
Your very, very best friend.
- You're already my only friend.
Hey, guys.
- Good to see you, Sarah.
- Hi, Eric.
Sarah, our favorite beer witch.
- Clever, Caleb. Never
heard that one before.
- Oh, come on, darling.
You don't have to be so uptight.
What's the matter?
Need to get laid?
- Hey, come on, Isaac!
- Hey, hey!
I was just offering
my services.
- I'd rather join a convent.
- Asshole.
- Is that funny to you?
- "You asshole!"
- Look, I'm sorry about
him. He's he's just drunk.
- I didn't realize that
was an excuse for assault.
- I didn't mean to say it was.
- Are we done here, Derek?
- Look, I just wanna say
I'm really glad you're back.
You know, after you
left for New York,
I just never thought
I'd see you again.
- Things didn't
exactly go as planned.
- I'm sorry to hear
about your dad.
He was a really good guy.
- Thanks.
He was.
- You staying with your mom?
- For now, until I
find a place of my own.
- How is she?
You know, last I
heard she was...
- She's doing just fine.
- Fuck.
- Oh, Sarah!
Hey!
Hey, my little baby
brother Asher here,
and he needs a date.
You know anyone you
can hook him up with?
- He's joking. I don't...
I don't need help.
- Oh, nonsense!
Hey!
- No, no, no. He's right.
Hey, but listen. no good girls.
They ain't no fun.
- No, we need someone who's
gonna keep him on his toes.
A real witch, one
might say.
- Isaac, stop.
- No one asked you, Derek.
What do you say, Sarah?
Think your mother still has
Mary Blackwood's number?
Or we could just dust
off the old Ouija board
and get your dad to
grab it for us.
- Isaac, that's enough!
- It's okay, Derek.
I'm sorry, Isaac,
but the only single girl I know
is my good friend
Liz over there.
- Ugh.
- But I'm pretty sure her
dick is bigger than yours.
- Shit!
- All of yours, in fact.
- Oh, shit, is that
right?
You wanna find out?
- Caleb, if I wanted
your comeback,
I'd scrape it off the
back of Isaac's throat.
- The fuck?
- Stupid!
- Hey!
That's enough!
You boys, you're outta here.
- We haven't finished
our drinks yet!
- Oh, these?
- Jesus Christ!
- Out now, all of you!
- What the fuck?
- This ain't over!
Not by a long shot.
- Okay, Liz.
- Sorry.
- Hey, you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Sometimes it's okay
to just not be fine.
Sometimes it's okay
to scream or cry
or punch someone in the teeth
'cause they slightly
inconvenienced you.
- Just being back here
and serving guys like that
makes me feel like
such a failure.
- Honey, most of those
boys have had an easy life
because of their families.
You've been through hell
and seen the other side.
That's a success, not a failure.
- I haven't thought
of it like that.
Every time my mom looks at me,
it makes me feel like
she's judging me too.
- Sarah, I'm not gonna
tell you what to do,
but my parents kicked
me out when I was 18.
I never spoke to them again.
Your mom wants to
be in your life.
What are you afraid of?
- I guess I'm still embarrassed.
- Hey, you're over a year sober,
something to be proud
of, not embarrassed by.
- I'm still learning how to
be around people, you know?
- Yes.
No one gets that more
than I do, believe me.
But this whole self-deprecation,
self-isolation bull shit,
it's not gonna make
anything better.
- You're always
right. You know that?
- Yeah, I do.
Ride home?
- No thanks. I like the walk.
- You're out of my way anyway.
Get home safe.
- Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
It's just me.
- Derek! What the hell?
- It's a good thing you're
not too trigger happy
with that thing.
- Why would you
sneak up on a woman
walking home alone in
the middle of the night?
- I was just trying
to catch up with you.
Sorry I scared you.
- Well, I'm not sorry I
almost burnt your eyes out.
- Not even a little bit?
- Maybe just a smidge.
What do you want?
- Look, I just wanna
apologize for my friends.
You know, they're douche bags.
- You are the company you keep.
- Okay. I deserve that.
- Why do you hang out with them?
It must be exhausting.
- I mean, it is, but I don't
really have anyone else.
Asher's been there
since the sandbox,
and Isaac's always
looked out for us.
- It's okay to
outgrow your friends.
- Yeah, but it's not that easy.
Isaac's dad gave me a job
with the construction company,
so it's not really wise
to get on the wrong
side of the family.
But maybe if I had someone
else to hang out with.
- Are you asking me out?
That's so sweet.
No.
- Wait, what?
Why?
- Because you asked me
to eighth grade formal
and then dumped me
for Julie Henderson
when you found out she
Frenches on the first date.
- I have to make it up to
you then, if you'll let me.
- Kind of just been trying
to do me recently, you know?
- No, I've been doing me too.
Every night, in fact.
- A masturbation joke. Clever.
- Thank you.
I've been work-shopping
it. What do you think?
- I'd avoided it
as a pickup line.
- Look, I just wanna say I
am really glad you're back.
- Oh, isn't that cute?
- The hell do you guys want?
- Hey, man, we just wanna
offer the lady our apologies
for the misunderstanding
earlier, that's all.
- Save your breath.
- Just get back
in the car, guys.
- Oh, no can do, Romeo.
We have unfinished
business with Sarah.
You think you can just
treat us like shit
and get away with it?
- I call 'em like, I see 'em.
- Don't touch her!
- Hey, where the fuck you going?
Motherfucker!
Hoo-hoo! Shit!
God damn!
I always knew he was
thick-headed.
- Cute.
Not so tough without your
little girlfriend around, huh?
Hey, Asher!
Get over here little brother.
My friend here
looks a bit thirsty.
- Yeah, I think she
could use a drink.
- I am a bit thirsty.
- Fucking bitch!
Get her!
- Come on, come on, come on!
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Bitch!
Where the fuck'd she go?
- Behind you!
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey.
Hey, no, no, please, God, no!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
I didn't wanna do this.
I just want the guys
to accept me.
- Hey, that's enough, Isaac.
- Keep him over there!
No smart-ass comment this time?
- Come on, man.
Let's get outta here.
- I'm not done yet.
- Isaac, come on, man!
Let's go!
You wanted to teach her a
lesson, and you did, all right?
You proved your point!
Shit.
- I think that's a sign from
above to get out of here.
- Look, I'm with him, Isaac.
Let's get outta here, man.
- Fine.
- Hey, what are we
gonna do about Derek?
- Let's get him in the car.
- Watch your ass.
Get up!
Get your ass up, man!
- Good evening.
How can I help you?
My goodness, you're hurt!
What happened?
- This group of
guys attacked me,
and then I woke up
and I was alone.
- These men that
did this to you,
what would you like
to see done to them?
- I don't know.
I guess I should call the cops.
- Oh, you can.
But what's to stop them from
doing this to another girl?
How long would they be locked up
before they were
back on the streets?
- I guess I hadn't
thought of that.
- And that's if
they believe you.
These men have money,
maybe strings that can
be pulled in the town
to get them out of trouble.
And you.
Well, you have a past.
It's written all over you.
What if you could stop
these men for good,
teach them that they can't
just get away with everything?
- In a perfect world.
- It is a perfect world.
There are other
ways to make sure
someone gets what they deserve.
- How would I do that?
- Come sit and rest.
Have you ever used a
spirit board before?
There are pathways in this world
far beyond your imagination.
- It's just a game, right?
- I can assure you it's no game.
Have you ever lost someone
you wish you could have had
a few more moments with,
wish you could speak
to one last time,
a family member perhaps?
- I guess.
We all have someone we wish
we could talk to again.
- Some of the boards
even provide a pathway
to righting what's wrong.
Karma exists, and
so does vengeance.
- Look, I appreciate
you helping me out,
but it's getting late,
and I just wanna go home.
- Oh, suit yourself.
I certainly hope you
get home safe this time.
- What do we have to do?
- This board belonged to
a very powerful witch,
one who was murdered for
crimes she didn't commit.
Her sorrow and pain loom heavy.
But she requires a sacrifice.
- What kind of sacrifice?
- Your blood.
- What the hell?
- Sit.
Sarah, I said sit.
You'll have to repeat
after me, understand?
- Yes.
- I summon the spirit
attached to this board.
- A woman wronged,
a woman betrayed,
a woman with vengeance
in her heart.
- A woman wronged,
a woman betrayed,
a woman with vengeance
in her heart.
- Talk to her, Sarah.
Ask her if she's here.
Tell her what you want.
- Hello, spirit.
Are you here with us right now?
What is your name?
M.
A.
R.
Y.
Is this Mary Blackwood?
- Keep on going, Sarah.
You can't go back now.
- I want the men who
attacked me tonight
to know the pain that I felt,
to feel frightened,
hopeless, vulnerable.
Can you help me.
- Run along, Sarah.
The door has
already been opened.
- Hey, beautiful.
You need some help?
- Yes.
I would love your help.
- So what do you have in mind?
- You killed him.
- What?
- You ran away.
- No, it wasn't like that.
- You left him alone to die.
- No!
No! Please!
- Shh.
Now go and find peace.
- Sarah.
- You can catch flies
with that thing.
- Sorry. Didn't get
much sleep last night.
- How'd the rest
of your night go?
- It was fine.
Went home, took a bath.
Liz, you've known
my mom for a while.
- Yeah.
Yeah, since I was a kid.
She used to babysit me.
- You know about
what happened to her?
- I know what people have
said happened to her.
- Did she ever talk to you
about that night at Laura's?
- No, sweetie.
She didn't really talk to
anybody after that night.
- Do you know anything
about Mary Blackwood?
- Yeah.
I mean, I know what's
in the museums.
Her husband was cheating on her,
and when she found out, he
accused her of being a witch.
She was hanged on
that large tree
that's still in the
street, and then burned.
Her husband then married
his mistress a month later.
You know, the worst part of it
is that she had three daughters,
forced to grow up
without their mother.
- Do you believe the
stories about her?
- I mean, it depends on what
stories you're talking about.
Do I think that she
practiced witchcraft?
Maybe.
They said that she
had this spirit board
she used to communicate with
the energies of the earth.
But do I think that she's gonna
come back every couple years
to seek revenge on this town?
I don't know.
Look, I knew your mother
very well before that night.
And after that night, she was
a completely different person.
She saw something
that messed her up.
- Her therapist thinks
it was all in her head,
that Tim and Laura
killed themselves
after a fight about him cheating
and mom went into
shock finding them.
- Hm.
That's certainly a less
complicated explanation.
Sure.
But if you talk to some
people in this town,
they'll tell you
that Mary Blackwood
has some kind of secret,
underground cult of witches
that still worship her,
helping her haunt this
town for eternity.
Boo!
Should see your face.
- I'm gonna go check stock.
- Okay.
- Sarah?
Hey, Sarah!
- Derek.
- Jesus!
- Sorry, man.
- Did you follow me here?
- You weren't answering
my calls or texts.
- Yeah, for a reason.
Goodbye, Asher.
- So I'll see you
home later on tonight.
- I'm not coming back.
I got a new place to crash
until I find something
more permanent.
- Please, just...
Just talk to me, Derek!
I mean, you're my best friend.
- We're not friends. Asher.
We haven't been for a while.
We're just two people
that grew up together.
- Look, I told
them not to do it.
I tried to get 'em to stop.
- You could have killed her.
- But we didn't! She's fine!
- How do you know that?
- I went to the
bar earlier today,
looked in the window,
and she was fine,
so no harm, no foul.
- If that helps you
sleep better at night.
- You know I just want
them to accept me,
like I was one of
the other guys.
- Why, Asher? Who
the fuck cares?
Be you.
Because whoever you're trying
to be, I don't like it, man.
I was always your
friend, no matter what.
- Please, Derek.
Hey, I'm so sorry.
You gotta forgive me, man.
- Try forgiveness
with someone else.
I'm done.
- Hey.
Derek.
- So is that wedding
ring attached for good,
or does it come off
for special occasions?
- Well, I guess that
depends on who's asking.
- Derek!
Hi!
How are you tonight, hot stuff.
- Hi, Louise. Thanks.
- Oh my God, you smell so good.
Are you wearing Prada?
- I'm not wearing anything.
- So it must be
your natural musk.
Yum.
Hey, you should buy me a drink.
- Maybe later, Louise.
Listen, can we talk
about last night?
- I'm working.
- I'll wait till
you're done then.
- Whatever.
- Hi.
- Hm.
- Another round?
- You better make it a double.
- You all need to find Jesus.
- Hello?
- Asher.
Asher.
- Jesus!
- Not quite.
- Yeah, I think she could
use a drink.
Stupid bitch.
- Help.
Someone.
Please help me.
- Are you frightened?
- I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Asher.
- Hey, you okay?
Sit down.
Please, God, I don't wanna die.
- God?
No.
No God.
And no heaven.
There's only rot!
- Sarah?
- Are you okay?
- Seriously, I'm fine.
I just got dizzy.
- You shouldn't be on your feet.
- I'm okay.
- Sarah, it's a slow night.
You could take the rest
of it off if you want.
- Are you sure?
- Of course.
Go home, get some rest.
- Maybe you're right.
- Come on. I can walk you home.
Look, are you sure you don't
need a doctor or something?
- Why would I need
a doctor, Derek.
- Sarah...
You were right about them.
I don't need them as
friends, any of them.
Whatever you need, I'll do it.
If you want me to go to the
cops, I'll tell them everything.
- No. No cops.
I don't want anything
like that involved.
- What do you want me to do?
- Stay away from them.
Keep yourself safe.
- And what about you?
- I can take care of myself.
- Look, I know you can.
I like a girl who can
take care of yourself.
- Well then I've got
the perfect one for you.
- Yeah?
Who's that?
I really didn't
need to see that.
- I bet she Frenches
on the first date.
- Still haven't forgot
about that have you?
- Not a chance.
- She looks all right.
I tell ya, man, last
night I thought she was-
- Yeah, I know, Caleb.
- You think she's
gonna go to the cops?
- I don't know.
I feel like if she was, she
would've done it already.
Still, though, we
need to make sure.
- What you mean, "make sure"?
- I'm gonna follow her,
put a little fright
in her, you know?
- No. Nah, man, fuck that.
No. Count me out, dude.
- Excuse me?
- No, Isaac, I'm serious, man.
Look, I'm getting tired
of this shit, all right?
I've got too much good
going in my life right now
just to fuck it up for your ego.
- Hey, she insulted all of us!
You damn right she did,
and we kind of deserved it!
What the fuck you
got to prove, man?
Huh?
We're not in high
school anymore.
Life has stakes now,
fuckin' consequences.
- Damn it.
No, you're right.
You're right, it does.
Let's not do anything.
Let's just go home.
All right? We'll wait.
Wait for her to tell somebody.
Then what's gonna happen, huh?
What do you think?
You remember how every night
your dad used to beat
this shit outta you,
and I was the one,
hey, listen to me,
I was the one who snuck you
into my house to protect you.
- That's what we're doing? Okay.
You were there for
me. You protected me.
I remember that. Yes, I get it.
- Who's gonna protect your
when I'm behind bars, huh?
- Look, man, just leave
the girl alone, all right?
The shit's over with, man.
We should have never fucked
with her to begin with.
- You kidding me?
What, you just wanna
walk away now, huh?
No, no, we're already in this.
Hey, look, if I get one
more charge against me,
just one, it is over for me,
and it'll sure as shit
be over for you too.
- Fuck that.
- No, no, you look at me.
I am not gonna let that
little bitch ruin our lives.
Okay?
Get your head in the game.
- Who are you?
- Asher.
A woman wronged.
A woman betrayed.
A woman with vengeance
in her heart.
- Bad dream?
- Mom?
- Sarah, when you
came back here,
I thought that we
had an agreement
that we were gonna be
honest with each other
about everything.
- What are you talking about?
- I just got off the phone
with your stepmother.
- I told you not to call her.
- I didn't.
She called me.
You had a letter
sent to her place
about a court date next month?
- That letter is
none of her business.
- No, but it's mine.
Breaking and entering?
Destruction of private property?
Sarah, were you using again?
- God, mom, no! It
wasn't that dramatic.
Dad and Lydia were fighting,
and I just didn't
wanna be around it.
I thought it was abandoned.
Turns out I was wrong.
- Well, when were
you gonna tell me?
I mean, what, you thought
I wouldn't find out?
- Yeah, kind of.
That was the idea.
I didn't want you to overreact.
- And she told me
that...
you were stealing from her.
- Gimme a break! That woman
leached off of dad for years.
I just borrowed a couple
bucks for the subway.
- Oh my God, Sarah.
What happened to you?
You were my little girl.
- Come off it, mom.
You were never
there as a parent,
and I was never
your little girl.
You were always too obsessed
with her to even notice me.
- With who?
- Mary Blackwood.
- Stop it.
Don't say-
- Why?
Why were you so afraid that
she'd come back for you?
Do you know how to stop her?
Is there a way to stop her?
- Mary Blackwood is dead.
She's been dead for centuries.
I know she's not real now.
Tim and Laura killed themselves.
I know I should have
listened to your father
and gotten therapy,
and I'm sorry
if this affected the way
I've raised you for so long,
but that's over now.
She's not coming back.
- But what if she did?
What if she did come
back, but not for you?
- What do
you mean by that?
- I have to go.
- Sarah, wait a minute!
Sarah, please tell
me you're not saying
what I think you're
saying.
- I'm sorry I
never believed you.
I don't wanna drag you
back into this again!
Derek?
What the hell?
What's wrong?
- I didn't know
where else to go.
- What happened?
- It's Asher.
He's dead.
- What?
- I'm sorry. I shouldn't
have come here,
not after what they did.
- No, Derek, wait!
What happened to him?
- They think it was a suicide.
- I saw Asher.
I saw him in my dream.
- What are you talking about?
- Derek, I don't think
he killed himself.
- Another!
- Do you really think that's
a good idea right now?
- My little brother is dead.
You have a better idea of what
I should be doing right now?
- Hey.
Take it easy.
- When I woke up, I
thought it was a dream.
It felt so real,
but it couldn't be.
- You think that you conjured
the spirit of Mary Blackwood
and now she's trying
to kill everyone
that attacked you that night?
- Look, I know I sound crazy.
I know I sound like my mother.
- No.
- But the dream I had
last night was so real.
And if I'm right,
you're in danger too.
- Why would you say that?
- I saw you last
night in my dream.
Dead.
You were hanging from a noose.
You don't believe me, do you?
- No, no.
I do.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I had the same dream of being
hanged, and it felt so real.
I woke up and I
was still in pain,
and I looked in the
mirror and I saw this.
- Oh my God.
- It still burns.
- We have to stop her, then,
before she can kill anyone else.
- How do we do that?
- I wanna go back to that
shop where I met that woman.
She told me the door was open.
Maybe she knows how to close it.
- Okay.
- Come on!
Damn it!
- Are you sure this
is the right shop?
I mean, the place you described
is kind of dime a
dozen in this town.
- It was here, I swear!
She took me into the back room
and made me touch the board.
- Well, if we can't
find the board,
then we're gonna have to
come up with another plan.
- We have to warn
Isaac and Caleb.
She's gonna go after them just
like she went after Asher.
- I always thought
you were cute.
I loved watching you play
football on Friday nights
and tackling all the tight ends.
- Is that so?
- It is so.
Hey, Caleb.
- Caleb!
- Pull up a chair.
I'll buy a drink.
- No, no, no, man.
Let's go on and get
you home, all right?
It's been a long day for you.
- Oh, fuck that.
Me and Louise were just
getting reacquainted.
- Yeah? Well, say
goodnight, all right?
Come on, man. I'll call you cab.
- I'll call you a
cock sucker.
She tell you to come get me?
- Come on, Isaac.
Don't start that.
- No, fuck all of you!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Isaac, calm down, man.
Listen.
Asher was a good kid, all right?
We all know that.
But there was no way
you could have known
he would do something
like this, all right?
- You really believe
that suicide bullshit?
Yeah right.
- All right, Isaac.
So what else was it then, man?
- I tell you what it was.
It was that bitch Sarah.
She's a nut just like
that mother of hers.
I'm telling you, she's after us.
- What the fuck, man?
- What the fuck
is going on here?
Are you fucking
hearing yourself, man?
You know what? Go
on your own trip.
I'm through with this shit, man.
Through with you and
your fucking ego!
- You know what?
I think I will get outta here.
I'm gonna find Sarah.
End this now.
- Hey, Isaac, come on, man.
- Hey!
- Come on, man!
- I'll see you later.
- Whatever.
- I'm glad you're here.
- Caleb.
- Do I know you?
- Perhaps.
- Show off.
- Stomp that bitch,
Isaac. Yeah.
Uh-huh.
You can't fuck with us!
What the fuck?
- Do you feel hopeless?
- Hey!
Hold it right there,
you psycho bitch!
No one kills my customers!
- Why?
When he would leave you to
die if given the opportunity.
- What the fuck?
- Stand.
Men have hurt and
taken advantage of
you your entire life.
Do not numb the pain any longer.
Take back control of yourself.
- We're too late.
- Liz!
- Sarah.
Hey.
- Don't move.
- What happened?
- The stories.
They're true.
Viola was right.
Mary Blackwood is real.
She's one tough bitch.
- Call her an ambulance.
- What are we gonna
do about the witch?
- We're gonna get that board
and send that god
damn witch back
to whatever hell she came from.
- How do we do that?
- I have a pretty good idea.
- What the hell?
Hey, it's you.
You lost?
You need me to take you home?
- I am home.
- You sure you live here?
- Come.
Join me.
- Don't have to tell me twice.
You forget to pay
the heating bill?
This isn't your house, isn't it?
- It shall be our house.
Together.
- You like that, you
fucking bitch?
- Where did you go?
All right.
You are so beautiful.
- Disrobe.
- Yes, ma'am.
Okay, I can get into this.
- Oh no!
No!
Sarah!
God. Oh my God, Liz!
Oh my god.
Oh my God, she was here!
She was here, wasn't she?
- Mary Blackwood.
- Where's Sarah?
- She went to get
the Ouija board.
She's trying to stop her.
- Are you vulnerable?
- What?
No! No!
- Don't get soft now.
- What the hell is
Isaac doing here?
- We might be too late for him.
- Sarah, wait.
Isaac!
Are you in here?
Oh, God.
Isaac.
- Derek.
- Let's just find the board.
- In my dream it
was in the attic.
What's wrong?
- I'm fine.
- No, you're not!
It's definitely in this room.
It's over here.
She's close. We have to hurry.
- You ready?
- Not at all.
Let's do it.
- Mom?
- What are you doing
in here, Sarah?
- I have to stop her!
- We can't be in here, baby.
I can't be in here.
- I have to send her back
before she comes for Derek!
- What do you mean
send her back?
What did you do, Sarah?
- I brought back Mary Blackwood!
All these years, you were right!
We should have believed you.
- Well, real or not,
I should never have let her
control my life the way she did.
- Then help me.
- I don't know if I can.
- I opened the door. You
can help me close it.
- That's not the way it works.
You don't think she's
gonna stop with Derek.
Once she does your
bidding, she comes for you.
You only close the
door when you die.
- What?
- Yeah, that's what
happened to Laura.
- We can still talk to
her, bargain with her.
I need you to help me.
- You can't bargain
with Mary Blackwood.
She's pure evil.
- Mom, please. We have to try.
- You're right.
This ends tonight.
I summon the spirit
attached to this board,
a woman scorned,
a woman betrayed,
a woman with vengeance
in her heart.
Mary Blackwood,
my daughter brought you
back from the afterlife,
but she left the door open.
I command you to close
the door and leave!
What do you want?
- H.
E.
R.
B.
L.
Her blood.
- We should stop.
- No. We have to keep going.
Mary Blackwood, will you
take the blood of another?
- Mom, what are you doing?
- It's okay, honey.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Don't worry.
Will you take my blood?
- Mom, no!
Mary Blackwood, I know
you were innocent.
I know you're angry.
I want you to be free.
Let go of the anger, Mary.
Leave this realm.
- Derek.
- Don't cause anyone
else any more pain.
Don't cause my mother
the pain you felt
when you were taken
from your children.
Close the door!
Is she gone?
- She's gone.
You've made her close the door.
You did it!
- I knew you could do it.
- Your blood is next.
You have been avenged, Sarah.
Join me
for eternity.
- Mary, get your
hands off my daughter!
- It's too late.
No more games.
- Burn in hell, witch!
- Derek!
- Honey, honey, don't look.
Let's just get you
outta here, okay?
- You were gonna
sacrifice yourself for me.
- Of course. I'm your mother.
I'd do anything for you.
- The Ouija
board! It's gone!
- Oh, it's destroyed forever.
- Are you sure?
Mom?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
- Good evening.
How can I help you?