(airplane engine roaring)
(upbeat music)
♪ You really gotta ♪
♪ You really gotta be here ♪
♪ I'm from a city where we stand alone ♪
♪ And when you're black you can get shot ♪
♪ When it flash look
like the camera's on ♪
♪ And niggas dodging first 48 ♪
♪ For us to make it out the
ghetto, we could hardly wait ♪
♪ I love the trait ♪
♪ But the sounds that it make ♪
♪ Kay is gunning ♪
♪ His shades running through alleyways ♪
♪ Hoping there's better days coming ♪
♪ We raise youngins to be grown men ♪
♪ So if they ever see jail ♪
♪ They can at least
stand on their own 10 ♪
♪ Stand on their own ♪
♪ I love Houston like I love kids ♪
♪ 'Cause every nigga in the H ♪
♪ Really just wanna be hood rich ♪
♪ And HPD be on their bullshit ♪
♪ All of my niggas
doing time in the cell ♪
♪ Feel like my hood flip ♪
♪ And even kids in the burbs
wanna flip them birds ♪
♪ Smoking loud, riding on
wheels, sipping to serving ♪
♪ And me, I'm just doing me ♪
♪ Only time will tell ♪
♪ To live and die in the H on bail ♪
♪ To live and die in that
H is the place to be ♪
♪ You gotta be here to know,
you really gotta be here ♪
♪ You really gotta be here ♪
♪ To live and die in that H ♪
♪ Is the place to be ♪
♪ You gotta be here to know ♪
♪ You really gotta be here ♪
♪ Where everybody wanna be ♪
♪ To live and die in the H ♪
♪ Where every day we try
to better ourselves ♪
♪ Sometime we chase after the
bag and get ahead ourselves ♪
♪ They don't make 'em like they used to ♪
♪ So many die in my city ♪
♪ Crying some shit I can't get used to ♪
♪ Hope to see heaven ♪
♪ We got heavy hearts ♪
♪ We lost a lot, but fell in
love with the deadly parts ♪
♪ From Fifth Ward to West
the Banks and Yellowstone ♪
♪ The motor park from Jurassic
Park, the ache is on ♪
♪ Don't take it wrong ♪
♪ If they ask you where
the fuck you from ♪
♪ Why outta towners checking
in whenever they come ♪
♪ And welcome home to the
natives that was doing bids ♪
♪ More than half of those we
lost, so your memory lives ♪
♪ So many tears ♪
♪ So many years we went overlooked ♪
♪ Fighting for freedom and praying ♪
Come on O.G.
It's your turn, man.
You taking too much time, man.
What's up?
(anxious music)
(player scoffs)
Waited all that time to make that move.
Probably taking all that time,
'cause you know his time is up.
Because he know I got him,
exactly where I want him.
Aggressive move.
(inmates chattering)
Do you have any idea how I was able
to hold down the street to
my city for all that time?
This nigga go stalling and shit.
What's up, man?
I figured out the key to life.
- Um-hmm.
- And it was real simple.
See now, you don't have to be
the strongest or the smartest
or even the quickest to
be epic in this life.
What you gotta be then?
(foreboding music)
The richest.
(blows thudding)
(foreboding music)
Whoa, whoa-whoa, whoa-whoa-whoa.
See the thing about paying
somebody to protect you,
it's that there's a price to
be paid for that protection.
It ain't fear, it ain't
love, it's just money.
And the funny thing about that
is that there's always somebody with more.
(blows thudding)
Can you get this cleaned up for me please?
I got you.
Go on and clean this shit up.
No mess.
(body sliding)
All the walls is talking.
Oh, yeah?
What they saying?
They saying them white folk is
about to give you your walking papers.
They just told me.
How you know already?
Nothing happening
here I don't know about.
I ain't got shit on the outside.
You know how that go.
I know how that go.
Give him that.
That's a number.
When you get outside,
I want you to call that number.
When you get to Houston,
I want you to let them know who sent you.
They gonna take care of you.
Okay, bet.
(hands slapping)
What you want us to do
with the one that's still on payroll?
You can't trust a soldier
that's only loyal to the dollar.
So go on and send him with his homeboy.
(person chuckling)
♪ It's that early in
the morning time shit ♪
♪ It's that shit all
the hustlers listen to ♪
♪ When they get up in
the morning, they go ♪
♪ And all I know how to
do is give it to 'em ♪
♪ From the centerpiece, nigga ♪
♪ That's all I ever needed ♪
♪ What happened to ambition
when people had dreams ♪
♪ And vision was essential
'fore we ever had streams ♪
♪ The hustle that they showed
us, it never went unnoticed ♪
♪ And music meant more than
just medicine in a soda ♪
♪ Went from brushing my ways in the pen ♪
♪ To brushing shoulders with
bosses from every region ♪
♪ Whose range is above rover ♪
♪ The dope game's over ♪
♪ We love that cocaine odor ♪
♪ That rat's running with snakes ♪
♪ And they both got the same motive ♪
♪ So we stood for what ♪
♪ They never pay us what they owe us ♪
♪ Went and locked us up ♪
♪ It made us greater from the shoulders ♪
♪ People hate to love ♪
♪ Remember everybody told us
they won't play your songs ♪
♪ 'Cause niggas scared
you gonna expose 'em ♪
♪ We was whipping cups just
trying to get some extra ♪
(knocking on door)
Mr. Smith, wake that ass up.
Baby, it's time to go.
(Clarence groans)
[Clarence] Yo, where we going?
Calm down, Clarence.
It's not gonna take too long.
Don't worry.
What you got going on?
Just gonna have you meet a few people.
(Clarence sighs)
Fuck.
(foreboding music)
(guard chuckles)
[Guard] Yeah, bitch.
You expect us to believe
after being locked up
with Tomas Jeffries for five
months that you didn't get
a shred of information
that will bring forth
on the indictment of the Jones Brothers?
Woman, what you think this is?
You think you can just throw me
in prison with Tomas Jeffries
and he gonna trust me
with this deepest secrets?
(dog barking)
You knew it wasn't gonna go down like that
when you sent me in there.
Please tell me again, why
did we send him in there?
Obviously, he wasn't
man enough for the job.
Hey.
You know why you sent me in there?
Yeah, why is that?
Because anybody else would've
come out in a body bag.
Hmm.
Did you get anything we could use?
You already know the answer.
So, this is what we need to
know about the Jones Brothers.
(car engine roaring)
Lamar Jones, the eldest of the brothers,
and although we have no physical proof,
word is Lamar is the
brain of the operation.
Did six years for drug
distribution when he was 18.
But since he's been out, his
record has been squeaky clean.
Lamar owns a rehabilitation facility
where he teaches the neighborhood kids
how to box and play sports.
But we have an informant that tell us
Lamar is still very much
into the narcotic game.
♪ Try to force you to
move things by 10 a week ♪
♪ So pay attention ♪
♪ Street's too quiet, the
bears might do a sweep ♪
♪ Welcome to The Bricks ♪
♪ Just the realest this shit finna get ♪
♪ When you niggas pull up better ♪
♪ Tell us, homey, who you with ♪
♪ If it ain't a dollar on the block ♪
♪ We'll get it out a bitch ♪
♪ If the plug ain't coming up ♪
♪ Drozzy bringing in the shit ♪
♪ 9601 ♪
(engine revving)
(uptempo R&B music)
♪ She says she knew I was ♪
♪ She could tell just by my aura ♪
♪ I said you lying queen, you lying ♪
♪ Don't you see all this before ♪
♪ See my face and at the source ♪
♪ Was smoked and I'm a forest ♪
♪ Fool, light it you a tourist ♪
♪ Niggas plotting making a rolls ♪
Okay, don't look yet,
but the guy talking to the bartender,
that's the middle brother.
(upbeat rap music)
Deidrick Jones.
That's their star safety from high school.
Boy got a full scholarship
to go to college.
He was plagued with his all field problem,
aggravated assault,
possession of a firearm.
The list goes on.
College coaches tried to cover it up
until they send him back home packing.
We got intel that says
Deidrick is smuggling
over 500 kilos a month
through his company trucks of course.
But every time we try to seize 'em,
we came up empty.
♪ Guaranteed to make you rich ♪
Goddamn, boy, fuck
happened to face, bro?
(foreboding music)
[Officer] Last but not least,
Marcus Jones, the
youngest of the brothers,
but definitely probably the most infamous.
(doorknob clicks)
Last year, some guys from
the east side cartel tried
to rob him and a shootout occurred.
Say, homey, man we got a whole
situation going on right now, man.
(upbeat rap music)
Fix it.
Man, this dumb-ass nigga got robbed, man.
No he didn't.
[Officer] Word is Marcus
shot two suspects on the spot
and ran two blocks just
to gun down the other.
The only motherfuckers I
know getting robbed is bitches.
You a bitch?
So, that make me a bitch then.
That's what I thought.
(dramatic music)
(man groans)
(man groaning)
Now, go get my motherfucking money
Man, get your bitch as up.
(man coughing)
Get your ass outta here.
If that nigga don't
have my money by tomorrow.
Shit, you know what I'm saying,
small talk, big action.
Gotcha, homey.
Got off on self defense charges,
'cause he was shot six times.
Police found him unconscious at the scene.
(dog barking)
(gun clicks)
(birds chirping)
That number Tomas Jeffries gave you
belonged to several burners.
We believe was purchased by none
other than his son, Melvin Jeffries.
Melvin and the Jones
brothers have a jaded past,
and if there's any angle
that we can play here,
it's through Melvin.
That's right.
It's said that Tomas brokered a deal
for his son's protection
with the Jones brothers.
You know the deal is
Tomas would give up a few
of his distribution routes,
as long as they cut a 50/50
deal with his son, Melvin.
Sounds like y'all have all
the information you need.
No, no, no-no-no-no.
You see nobody's gonna testify
against the Jones brothers.
All we have right now is a few crackheads
and felons lying and telling stories
to try to reduce their sentence.
Look, we need something concrete,
a wiretap or video surveillance,
something that's gonna
prove that this thing's
being orchestrated by the brothers.
Now we're gonna give
you a long leash here,
because we don't need
any chances of detection.
But if you need us,
you call us on this phone.
That it?
Mother.
(inmate shouting)
[Reporter On TV] But
first, we have the news.
It was a grim day in history.
The horror was unforgettable,
but so was the courage.
Coming up, one man remembers
how a massacre changed so many.
This is not what we agreed upon.
I cannot tolerate murder in
your cell in the broad daylight.
Would you rather it was me covered
in my own blood, laid
out here on the floor?
How's Tammy?
She like the new car?
Your story better stick,
'cause one inaccuracy,
this whole thing goes bad.
All right, don't forget.
If it goes bad, it goes
bad for both of us.
But don't worry,
contingencies have been taken.
What about that other thing?
How's that going?
The seeds have been planted.
Now we just waiting to see
what kind of fruit grow.
No more bodies.
(metallic tapping)
You think we can trust that nigger
Clarence on the outside?
I think-
Don't think, don't.
Don't think.
(inmate shouting)
[Reporter On TV] Coming
up next, a man gets more
than he bargained for
when he falls in love.
So you was locked up
with my old man, huh?
How he holding up in there?
He all right?
Man, your old man runs that prison.
He's straight.
(chuckles) Of course, he does.
So what do he say about me?
He talk about me a lot or no?
(sirens blaring)
You know he don't let me call him,
paranoid or some shit like that.
He's smart to be.
Hell, yeah, he talked about you,
all the time.
He proud of you.
So look, he wants me to
put you on with our partners.
Yeah?
Who are they?
And the first lesson you'll
learn from me today is this.
Don't ever ask about them,
not to me, not to anybody.
I like to know who I'm dealing with
before I get my hands dirty.
Everybody ain't built the same out here.
True, but if words gets out
that you asking those questions,
man, it ain't gonna matter.
Look man, all you need to know is this.
You listen to me, you'll
make a lot of money.
But all money ain't good money.
Now, I know you've been hanging
around my old man too long,
'cause I ain't never met
a dollar I ain't like.
(gentle music)
(door creaks)
(gentle music continues)
(plastic crinkling)
(birds chirping)
I'm about to introduce
you to my girl, Kenya.
She's the common ground
between my family and the partners.
So, you don't do business
with them directly?
Long story, but we ain't
got the best history.
And on top of that, them
niggas trust is shit.
Heard.
(dog barking)
(knocking on door)
(blinds clanking)
Hello to you, too.
Hey.
What you got for me today?
Huh, yeah, right.
Where the money at?
This Clarence.
He was locked up with my old man.
Came to Houston to see how
the real hustlers do it.
Nice to meet you, Clarence.
I'm Kenya.
Nice to meet you, too.
Well look, glad to see
y'all getting along and shit,
'cause he gonna be
staying here for a minute.
- What?
You can put your bag in, in the back.
It's cool.
What the fuck, Melvin?
Look, this ain't no motherfucking daycare.
I'm not about to be
watching no grown-ass man.
You ain't look like
you was having a problem
watching him to me.
Look, don't let him out of your sight.
If he checks out,
and you say we can trust him,
then we bring him in.
And if not?
Shit, either way he's out of your house.
Fuck!
I didn't know.
I know, but it's cool.
I just don't like surprises, that's all.
But you're here now.
That's the restroom through
that door over there.
There's a shower and everything.
If you need anything, let me know.
(Clarence sighs)
We already talked about this.
Come on, man, just let me see him.
Look, you said I could see him.
[Melvin] I told you
how this shit gonna work.
My way or no way.
(Clarence clears throat)
Fuck, you understand?
(Kenya whimpers)
Just, just let me see him.
I just wanna see him.
Look, I promise I won't leave this time.
And fuck all that.
You lucky I ain't kill you last time
and left you on your cousin doorstep.
The shit you're doing,
the shit is uncalled for.
It's different this time.
How the fuck is different?
I did everything you asked.
'Cause you ain't have no fucking choice.
Look, we got some unfinished
business with your uncle.
When that's all wrapped up you
get to see your fucking son.
Fuck.
(Kenya cries)
(somber music)
(car engine revs)
(melancholy music)
Who was that?
Nobody.
Just go back to bed.
(Kenya whimpers)
(melancholy music continues)
(skillet sizzling)
(utensil rattling)
Ahem.
Hmm, just made yourself at home, huh?
I'm sorry.
I just thought you needed
a home-cooked meal.
You cook?
Pancakes and eggs.
What?
It's not gonna kill you.
It's not that.
I just never had a man cook for me before.
Well, good.
Then I'm the first.
(chuckles) Nah, nigga you ain't special.
Nah, I mean, if I'm the first,
then I'm the best.
Well, if these eggs ain't
good, you're disqualified.
All right, all right.
(laughs) I'm back in the game.
You gonna try this too?
It's good, ain't it?
(Kenya chuckles)
Yeah, winning.
♪ I ain't got no time for
no fuck shit, no time ♪
♪ No, I ain't got no time for ♪
♪ I ain't got no time for
no fuck shit, no fuck shit ♪
♪ No-no, no, no, no ♪
♪ Just 'cause you don't see
it don't mean I ain't got it ♪
♪ If a nigger ♪
Don't forget we got a meeting tonight
at the Club Hernandez now.
10 o'clock, right?
Oh I forgot to ask.
What's the name of that fine
bitch that work for you in the club?
I got a bunch of fine
ass bitches that work
for me at the club.
The one I wanna fuck.
How the fuck we supposed to know?
You wanna fuck every bitch in the club.
Right.
What the fuck's so funny?
'Cause I know who you talking about.
Who he talking about?
The new girl with the big old booty.
Nicole?
Little bro, don't even waste your time.
You cut or something?
The fuck you looking at me for?
I don't know.
I don't know either,
but I'm gonna fuck the bitch, too.
Straight up.
(both laughing)
You crazy.
♪ If I ain't had no action ♪
♪ They wouldn't even be calling, calling ♪
♪ All this overthinking got
me really exhausted, yeah ♪
I'm about to go inside.
Don't leave this car and don't
let nobody see you in it.
Look man, I know y'all got
your ways of doing things
and I get it.
I feel like I'm wasting my time.
You know the people that run this show,
they don't play and the amount
of shit that's going on,
it could get you a thousand years,
and we don't take no chances.
Hmm.
Scared money don't make no money.
Yeah, all right.
(papers rustling)
(text clicking)
(compartment clicks)
(window whines)
Hop in the driver's seat.
Follow me.
All right.
(car engine revs)
(engine rumbling)
Let's go.
What about the car?
It'll sit there for a couple of days,
then it'll disappear.
Let's go.
(engine rumbling)
(upbeat music)
Gentlemen, a toast.
To better business,
better sex,
and better luck.
(speaking in foreign language). Salute.
Salute.
(glasses clinking)
(upbeat music continues)
[Marcus] Kenya, I need to holler at you.
Okay, about what?
Who the fuck is this nigga, man?
Ah, shit.
I'm right here man.
You can ask me.
Yeah.
Whoa, whoa, whoa-whoa-whoa.
I got it, I got it.
Come on.
I don't like that Black
motherfucker either.
Playing with fire.
[Melvin] Let me get you a drink.
- Really?
- What you mean, really?
Who the fuck is that nigga?
Look, it's nothing.
All I know is that Melvin
brought him to the house
and said Big Dog wanted him to
get familiar with the family.
That's it.
Whose family?
If I find out your stupid ass lying,
next time you see your son
it'll be on a motherfucking T-shirt.
(upbeat club music)
(traffic humming)
(distant rap music)
What's up, homey?
You good?
Yeah, I'm good.
That nigga ain't good.
Man, that nigga's a bitch.
Might as well give the glizzy
to my T-Jones, we're gonna
send this nigga out there.
Fuck you!
I ain't no bitch!
Chill out, man.
We know you ain't no bitch, man.
That's that boy, Red, talking that shit.
That's what he do.
But what we do need to know,
if you down with this play or not?
Yeah.
Listen, homie, them niggas
stole from the family, man.
The family, homie, you hear me?
This shit a no go, man.
(rap music on radio)
Look, them niggas figgin' to
come out, man, in a minute.
What's up, you down with it or no?
(chuckles) Man give me this pistol, man.
Don't worry about it.
Don't even trip, homie.
Everybody ain't no killer, you hear?
Chill out, relax, homie.
Good, relax.
Bitch ass better be here
when we get back, too.
Crazy, man.
What you talking about?
I can't believe you still
buying that stuff, man.
What you, what you need that stuff for?
Them gas station pills way better
than them narco, nigga.
Trying to tell you.
You crazy as shit, man.
Matter of fact, I'm finna go
slide to the house right now.
Go take a couple of them hos.
Go knock this bitch back here,
for real, nigga, straight up.
See that's why you keep
having girl problems.
How?
How, nigga?
All that lying you be doing?
Lying, who lying?
You lying, nigga.
Man, I be hearing you on the phone talking
to them hos, telling them
how much you love 'em.
Getting 'em all to fall in love with you
and stuff like that, 'cause
they think you in love.
But they don't realize that your trash ass
buying pills just to fuck 'em.
- Man, come on.
- You ain't shit.(laughs)
You ain't- (guns firing)
[Red] Fuck you, pussy
ass nigga, family, nigga.
What the fuck?
(door clicks)
(rap music on radio)
[Red] Oh, fuck, man, look!
[Driver] What happened???
(Red laughs)
(gun firing)
Bitch ass!
(Red laughs)
♪ All I ever wanted was a million cash ♪
From the the lady at the end of the bar.
(upbeat rap music)
(Clarence sighs)
I'll be right back.
♪ All I ever wanted was a million cash ♪
♪ All I ever wanted was ♪
What are you doing here?
Just checking progress.
Can I get you another round?
Let me get another round of whatever,
I'm sorry, I didn't catch your name.
Monica.
Give me another round for, Monica.
So, I was just like,
girl, better you than me.
Kenya?
You're not even listening to me, girl.
Girl, you ain't doing nothing
but telling other people's business.
Babe, don't be mad 'cause
I always got the tea.
♪ All I ever wanted was a million cash ♪
How about you spill it
all when I get back, okay?
I promise I'm gonna listen to you.
I'll be right back.
[Friend] This bitch.
Jamie Hernandez is in town,
and we got a wire tap that says
one hell of a load is coming in soon.
You need to find out when and where.
[Kenya] Let's go.
Okay, rude, we were talking.
Okay, and now y'all ain't.
Let's go.
[Kim] What the hell is her problem?
Wow, that girl was rude.
[Marcus] Whoa, whoa
whoa, whoa-whoa-whoa.
What now?
Where y'all think y'all going?
You and your friend need to go upstairs.
(club rap music)
♪ Bust your head, boy ♪
♪ Talking all that gang shit ♪
♪ A big sign, boy, I been ♪
♪ Nigger pop a shit ♪
♪ Been getting it bag all,
there's some niggers upset ♪
♪ Bullshit talking boys, I
drank all the honey, honey ♪
♪ Yeah got them demon
in me, too, hey, boy ♪
♪ So eat your ass up like
a motherfucker lunch ♪
♪ All my nigga demons and
they all got the munchies ♪
♪ I swear we all thugging ♪
♪ And we're all in the jungle ♪
♪ At the creek bed, ♪
♪ Marijuana got it coming ♪
♪ If you want the stress ♪
♪ Nigga I can run it ♪
♪ Zion big business when I hit the bitch ♪
♪ I'm in the wind ♪
♪ Diamond dancing on me ♪
♪ Blue hundreds all in my pocket ♪
♪ Feeling good, ain't have to
see the code pocket rocket ♪
♪ Chop a hood on that ♪
♪ And so got a find another body ♪
♪ That nigga ain't sing ♪
♪ That nigga done fuck around ♪
♪ And seen too many bodies ♪
Said you was locked up with Tomas, huh?
Yeah for a few months.
Few months?
Where you was before that?
Was in Kansas.
Did a three year bid then they
see me up with the old man
for my release date.
Kansas?
Man, my partner was
locked up in Hutchenson.
I heard of Hutchenson,
but I was up there in El Dorado.
Must've made a hell of impression
if old man for him to send you here.
Tell you the truth,
I don't know what I did.
The old man ain't talk
about the outside much.
So the old man ain't
never said nothing about us?
I don't know who us is,
so, nah he ain't say.
But be real with you,
I came out to make some money.
- You did?
- And I ain't seen none yet.
Good.
Get him the fuck outta here.
What the fuck you waiting for, nigga?
Kenya, hold up a second.
What you know about him?
Just know before you answer that,
if you vouch for Buddy,
y'all gonna share the same fate.
I mean he's cool, but something's off.
What?
I'm just saying, he's nice, respectful.
You can tell he ain't been
through the shit we've been through.
He the law.
No he's not.
I ain't saying all that.
You ain't have to.
All I'm saying is that he's
nicer than what I'm used to.
Look, we trust your uncle.
He wouldn't send the feds our way.
I know that.
But I don't know him,
and I don't trust shit I don't know.
And what you want me to do about it?
Get to know him like only a woman would.
Eventually he'll start pillow talking
and tell all the business.
But, if he check out,
show him the kingdom.
(rap music)
What happened? I don't understand.
We was good.
What did they tell you
to make you wanna stop?
I don't understand.
What happened?
Look, I don't wanna,
I don't wanna talk about it.
I know.
I know you just met me, all right.
Hey, I know you just met me,
and I'm not gonna tell you to trust me.
Hell, I don't know if I
should be trusting you,
but what I do know is you
deserve better than that.
Oh yeah?
How you know what I deserve, huh?
I know you don't deserve that,
not from them, not from anybody.
And who you supposed to be.
My knight in shining armor?
That's what you're using, right?
I never leave you, bae.
I love you bae, going on shopping sprees
and trips every month.
I'll never hit you, bae.
I treat you like a queen, bae.
That's what you're saying, right?
Fuck outta here.
Wow, somebody really fucked you up,
and I get it.
And you get the short end of the stick
time after time again.
But you don't deserve that.
I do deserve it.
You have no clue who I am.
Then tell me.
Why you so scared?
Because if I tell you, you
gonna hang it over my head.
Why would I do that?
Because that's what y'all all do.
That's exactly why I want you to leave.
Just leave.
What?
Get the fuck outta my house.
Why you acting like this?
Because every time I
start to feel like this,
I'm always left feeling.
♪ Day and night ♪
♪ You don't ever hit me in the day time ♪
♪ Think about you all day, all night ♪
♪ Boy you make it hard
for me to play nice ♪
♪ Think twice ♪
♪ Maybe someone else don't feel right ♪
♪ Maybe we're wrong but it feels right ♪
♪ Hey, 'cause he could
never love me like you do ♪
♪ He might been miss him
and think about my perfume ♪
♪ I'm the one you call on when
your pants were falling down ♪
♪ So baby both be honest,
yuh, just be honest ♪
♪ Do you think about me in the shower ♪
♪ Talking on the phone for hours ♪
♪ I do you wrong, but
let me do you right ♪
♪ If I hit your phone,
would you stay the night ♪
♪ Do you think about me on Monday ♪
♪ Fuck around at night
while three by Sunday ♪
♪ I do you wrong, but
let me do you right ♪
♪ If I hit your phone, ♪
♪ But would you stay the night ♪
♪ I do you wrong, but
let me do you right ♪
♪ If I hit your phone,
let me stay the night ♪
I'm gonna go get a towel.
♪ Gripping my hair while
you grabbing my waist ♪
♪ Tell me you love it ♪
♪ You love how it taste ♪
♪ Hold up ♪
♪ I need a nigga who know that ♪
♪ I'm a look bad, so don't do me badly ♪
♪ 'Cause nigga you know
that I'll go down hard ♪
♪ Don't let you paste ♪
♪ You be a fool if you let
a good thing go to waste ♪
♪ Gripping my hair while
you grabbing my wasye ♪
♪ Tell me you love it ♪
♪ You love how it taste ♪
Fuck.
(Kenya screaming)
You know I can tell that
you're different, right?
Yeah.
How?
How can you tell I'm different?
First, let's talk about
what happened last night.
Mm.
- Mm-hm.
(both chuckling)
But I can tell you had
some good in your life.
I mean, unlike mine.
Hmm.
Anyway.
I can tell by the way you walk,
the way you talk,
and how you treat a woman.
And everything you say, so genuine.
Look,
I know I just met you but,
I feel like you're the
only person I can trust.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What's up with old boy who
came over here the other night?
What you mean?
I mean y'all used to date or something,
'cause I mean from what I saw,
things seem pretty personal?
Can we please talk about something else?
Yeah.
Let's talk about how you can trust me,
but you won't allow me to trust you.
What?
Clarence.
What are you doing?
I thought you was different.
So you saying I'm not?
No, you not different.
You just like every other
girl running around here,
dumping her problems off on
anybody who willing to help.
I put myself through that shit before.
I ain't doing it again.
From now on, whatever energy
I get, I'm giving back.
What are you even
talking about Clarence?
You know what I'm talking about.
Exactly.
(Kenya cries)
What's going on?
I can't say anything.
Look, my son life depends on it.
Where is your son?
(cries) I can't tell you.
It's complicated.
What's complicated?
(somber music)
Tell me something.
When I was younger
I had a baby.
My baby daddy wasn't shit,
but I loved him so.
I guess I wasn't shit either.
He stashed a brick in
my car for a drop off.
But later that night a friend of ours
came to our house and
told me he was murdered.
They shot him over a fucking chain.
I grabbed my keys
and hopped in the car
and rushed out the house.
I tried to get to where he
was as soon as possible.
It wasn't until I got there
I realized I,
I'm just gonna be raising my son alone.
That I actually forgot my
baby at home by himself.
So I hop back in the car,
and I started speeding on the freeway.
Just trying to get home to him.
Just to make sure he was safe.
But on my way I got stopped by the cops.
They saw the blood all over my clothes,
so they decided to search the car.
And they found the dope.
Yep.
But we got a friend.
He claimed he was so
fucking loyal to Blaze.
He took the charge.
He said it was so I
could get home to my son.
(Kenya crying)
When I got there
my baby was,
he was sleep.
He was safe, sleeping all peacefully.
But the fucked up part is,
I've been paying for it ever since.
What that got to do with old boy?
Marcus?
His name is Marcus.
He's one of our friends too.
But the guy who took the charge,
it's Marcus's big brother at the bar.
They've been controlling
my life ever since.
(Kenya crying)
I got you.
(foreboding music)
♪ She said she knew I was that nigga ♪
♪ She could tell just by my aura ♪
♪ I said you lying, you ain't blind ♪
♪ I know you see all this before ♪
♪ You looked up being real ♪
♪ You see my face in at the source ♪
♪ Want smoke then I'm a forest ♪
♪ Move light if you a tourist ♪
♪ Nigga plotting, making arrangements ♪
♪ To send your family to that florist ♪
♪ Bad bitches like Kamora
at the Waldorf Astoria ♪
♪ I got love for all my
niggas and their babies ♪
♪ I'm a warrior ♪
♪ Like Draymond and Stef ♪
♪ Niggas play around be
step like a fraternity ♪
♪ That bitch might think you cute, ♪
♪ But she attracted to that currency ♪
♪ You getting left on read ♪
♪ She text her nigga back with urgency ♪
♪ Start sucking when she saw me ♪
♪ Said that was an emergency ♪
♪ 'Cause Louis V is burgundy ♪
You ready for this shit?
I'm just saying, 'cause
once this door is open,
and it's closed, it's
gonna be hard as shit
to get back to the other side.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
(knocking on door)
♪ Guaranteed to make you rich ♪
♪ Inspiration when I'm
whipping up these licks ♪
♪ Everyday was like Christmas ♪
♪ When I started wrapping gifts ♪
This right here is
what we call the factory.
This where all the shipments come in first
before they broke it down
into two different groups.
That over there?
That?
That's what stays in the city.
And this, this is what we ship out.
How you ship this out?
Now that's the answer that
nobody in this room knows.
Hell, not even me.
So how do the police
not know about this place?
Hmm.
We're always under surveillance.
So how we move is important.
Detective might see a woman
walking the sub apartment,
but it's all just the front,
because we own 70% of the building.
We have underground tunnels that are
for each and every operation.
Workers go into one door
and then go into an apartment
that no one knows about.
So the police would have to raid
every apartment on the first floor.
Exactly.
What about the cash?
Second floor.
So what's this place called?
This?
This is called the gardens.
Hmm.
Looks like a nursery.
You know these are the
apartments that I grew up in.
For it to be so-called
for the poor people,
shit I never seen so
much money in my life.
You know, if I can grow into
a rose from this concrete,
it ain't shit you can't do.
So when do we get started?
All right.
There you go, my man.
You started the moment
you walked into my home.
♪ Legacy, since you been ♪
♪ Let me talk to 'em ♪
Hell yeah.
♪ Excuse me or sue me ♪
♪ I'm only responsible for
making rapping great again ♪
♪ When they didn't know
that was possible ♪
♪ A prophet, a poet
penmanship's unstoppable ♪
♪ Hit home with every song ♪
♪ They only visit when it's conjugal ♪
♪ I am who I am ♪
Man, we gotta get these
motherfuckers to the guard.
Already, shit let's make it happen G.
♪ It's not a facade, rap game God ♪
(knocking on door)
(foreboding music)
Ooh.
Damn Kenya, you get finer and finer
every time I see you, I swear to God.
Goddamn Nook, and you say
that every time I see you,
I swear to God.
Shit, and we mean it
every time we see you too.
I appreciate it, I think.
Anyways this is-
- Clarence.
I mean what, the nigga working with us,
and we don't know who he is?
We got it from here.
I'm good.
See what I'm saying?
He straight.
Yeah, but he don't know y'all like I do.
Say a prayer, he don't find out.
You hear me?
I'm good.
Man, she know she can get that dick.
I promise.
Anyways, what's up man?
Let's go take this ride.
You hear me?
Boom, let's move.
Scram nigga.
(door thuds)
(inmates laughing)
(inmates chatting)
Miguel.
What's up?
I thought we was on the same page.
What do you mean?
Tomas, we're friends.
I was told that your
brother was seen in town
setting up a meeting with my competition.
Is that true?
It's not so much a competition.
I mean you're here for another 10 years.
Look, besides you're
making millions of dollars
just sitting on the sidelines.
So, man, just play your part.
Play my part.
The brothers are taking your place.
So what was once yours is now theirs.
Man, just be happy they allow
your precious son the luxury of life,
because we both know
you and I would not.
(person chuckling)
Shit.
What the fuck is this?
Work nigga, what?
You think you got 20,000 in your pocket
just for fucking the boss man niece?
Crazy.
Fuck wrong with this nigga?
What we supposed to do, bury the body?
We? We ain't doing
a motherfucking thing.
You going bury that
motherfucker, you hear me.
Time to get your hands dirty, nigga.
Come on man, let's go smoke this blunt.
I don't know why they always stick us
with these new ass niggas.
- Last nightSouthwest Houston.
- Guess you saw the news, huh?
[Reporter] Local pharmacy
owner, Sonny Patel,
was beaten and gunned down.
Who do you think it was?
[Reporter] Police are saying
he may have been robbed of several cases
of prescription narcotic medication.
[Reporter] I'm looking
at who I think it was.
You know there was
nothing I could do, right?
But you could have told me something.
Give me a heads up.
Anything.
A heads up?
Clarence, look, I really, really like you,
but you know there's no way I can mix
business with pleasure.
If they found out I was
giving you information,
man they'll kill me.
And you know I got too much to lose.
You know no matter what
I'm gonna protect you, right?
From who?
Marcus?
Not just him,
anyone or anything.
You're so cute.
(phone vibrating)
(soft jazzy music)
(elevator bell dings)
Look, just remember, don't
ask no questions, okay.
Just try to blend in and have fun.
I mean this is a very,
very important event.
All the important people are here,
and you're this close to
being a part of the family.
Don't fuck this up.
(soft lounge music)
Put me in the game, coach.
(laughing) So I heard
that the owner of this house
is a Mexican drug lord.
And he throws this party every year
just to get in good with the locals.
Excuse my wife.
Alcohol seems to give her
a bit of a imagination.
No, it does not.
Whoever it is, I heard he's loaded.
Yeah, perhaps I heard he had
bits of powerful friends as well.
(gasps) Is that the mayor?
Excuse me.
I'll be right back.
Follow me.
(soft lounge music continues)
Fucking serious.
Listen, I'm not here for you.
There's a girl inside who
didn't make it to check in.
I was hoping to see her here,
but there's no sign of her.
Did you check the safe houses?
Nothing there.
I'm starting to think
maybe her cover was blown.
Well what's her name?
Maybe I can dig something up for you.
You don't trust me.
That's not protocol.
We protect all our deep
covers with 100% anonymity.
And that's the only way we can keep it.
Cut the bullshit, Kim.
You know as well as I know,
as deep as these guys' pockets are,
they have ways to find out other links.
Hell, you can be a link just
as much as any one of us can.
Give me a name.
I'll see what I can do.
Nicole.
Wait, Nicole.
- You knew her?
- No.
I'm just trying to remember
where I know that name.
Probably the other day at the bar.
She was the one serving the drinks.
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were seeing someone.
What?
Your girlfriend, she
must be a lucky girl.
Sorry, I imposed.
Yeah, no problem.
Nice seeing you again.
Who's that bitch?
Oh no, that was just some woman I met
at the club the other night.
She said she knew me definitely,
but I don't remember her.
Besides, I had to tell
her I was seeing someone.
I like how you don't make me crazy.
Crazy, with all these people here?
Shit, about 40 more seconds,
I was gonna fuck it up for all of us.
Anyways, they're about to have a toast.
I wouldn't miss it.
I finna to go to the ladies room.
I'll meet you up there.
- All right.
- Okay.
May I help you?
I know exactly what you are.
And what am I, little girl?
You just like all the other women.
Want something that don't belong to them.
Girl, your man is too young.
I was just looking for
a little excitement.
I got your excitement, bitch.
Wow, you had me fooled for a second.
Look at you with that beautiful dress.
You look amazing.
For a second I thought you
was a respectable woman.
You can take the bitch out the hood,
but you can't take the hood out the bitch.
(foreboding music)
(Kenya groans)
That bitch.
As mayor of this amazing city,
I'd like to celebrate
these two brilliant men
for helping Houston continue its reign
as one of the finest
cities in the country.
Between the countless donations
and the heartfelt contributions
with the inner city youth,
these two have achieved
their very own day.
So congratulate these two
by giving them a big round of applause
and here for today,
being known as Jones Day.
(audience applauding)
Wow.
Thank you for such a
prestigious honor, Mayor.
Appreciate it man.
Looking forward to continue
to building this beautiful
place we call home.
Thank you.
(audience applauding)
I'd like to thank
everyone for coming out.
I'm sure y'all didn't come to hear
about all the contributions
that my brothers
and I have done for the city.
Y'all come to celebrate a good year.
And what better way to
do that other than party?
So let's party, turn up.
♪ Let's see how y'all bang ♪
♪ This that big old drip ♪
- Let's take this shit over.
- Nigga, we already did.
♪ She wanna make a movie on my headphone ♪
♪ She wanna sit on dick ♪
♪ Mix her off white with the fish scale ♪
♪ Just hit a big old lick ♪
♪ This that big old drip ♪
♪ Mix it off white with the fish scale ♪
(person speaking Spanish)
Ciao.
Everything all right?
Yeah, will be, if we can
handle the new shipment.
New shipment?
I ain't green light a new shipment.
Neither did I.
But evidently my people back home
have a load that never
made it to its destination.
Fuck it.
Send it back.
It's not that easy.
You know this, Lamar.
You can't just send back 600.
You can't just ship 600
kilos back to Mexico.
You know this.
You know we don't work like this.
We need time.
Speaking of time,
when that shit supposed
to get here anyway?
Two days.
Not happening.
What's not gonna happen?
Hernandez trying to
force a shipment on us.
Not happening?
Did you forget how powerful my family is?
What do you think they're
gonna say if you say no?
Sound like a you problem.
Are you ready for what might happen
if you don't take the shipment?
Crazy.
I think I speak for my
brothers when I say this.
You love doing business
with you and your family,
but we don't take orders
or lay down for nobody.
Look, Lamar.
No one's asking you to
lay down for anyone.
Consider this a favor for a favor.
And what exactly do we get
in return for this favor?
See?
Now, we're talking.
When you take the load-
- If.
If we take the load.
If you take the load,
all 600 kilos will be given
to you at half the price.
And after that, the next five shipments
will be delivered to you.
I'll take full risk
and responsibilities for all deliveries.
If we decide to do this,
we do this under our terms.
Absolutely under your
terms, gentlemen. (laughs)
Now, if you don't mind,
I'm gonna go catch up with
a few ladies downstairs.
And Dedrick, man, I
always love your parties.
You never lack the essentials.
Oh, yeah, and what's that?
(inhales) Pussy. (laughs)
This guy, man.
Listen, I need an answer by the morning.
(rap music)
So what y'all think?
I mean, it ain't how things usually go,
but half off, that's a lot.
Shit.
You know how I'm rock,
and I'm ready for whatever.
It's a big risk, man.
Risk?
What shipment we ain't
had ain't been a risk?
It's either gonna come with bullets
or in handcuffs, man.
Yeah, but our system
cut 90% of that risk down.
Bullshit, two days ain't
enough time to set up shit.
Man, what's that shit Pop used to say?
When confused with a choice,
go with what helps tomorrow,
because
That's where we headed.
Facts.
Shit, Pops ain't never led us wrong.
You right about that.
But tomorrow, let's figure out
how to make this shit happen.
Let's get it.
We do this shit right,
we can be bigger than
the fucking mob ever was.
Babe.
We should go see that new
movie that's out today.
Which movie is that again?
Deep Cover?
(laughs) No, I think
the name of that movie
was In Too Deep.
- Where is-
- Judging by the tail
we put on her, she's meeting Marcus.
But you need to be worrying
about where she's gonna go.
You know, I'll be honest with you.
I'm highly disappointed in you.
William Shephard,
or what is it you calling
yourself nowadays?
Clarence.
Since you've been on this
case, you've given us nothing.
Not one thread of the
information that we can use
on any one of the brothers.
So since you can help us indict them,
we're just gonna go to
the next best thing.
Oh, you act like you don't even know
what she talking about.
Kenya Thompson.
It's all there in the folder.
Distribution of narcotics.
Mmhm.
- Conspiracy.
- Mm-hm.
Threatening a government agency.
Oh and my favorite,
the murder of Layla McKinney.
Who?
[Kim] Keep looking.
You may know her as Nicole.
Ah, she didn't kill Nicole.
See the fact that you didn't
even acknowledge her being dead,
but you were reacting to the girlfriend
tells me everything I need to know.
Look, you know how hard
this say is pen, right?
And you told me to get information
on the brothers, not Kenya.
Now if I get Kenya outta the way,
how am I gonna get to the brothers?
There's no other way, and you know that.
I know you think I'm in too deep,
and that's fine.
But don't penalize me for
being great at my job.
(officer laughing)
Once I get something that can stick,
you'll know I'm on your team.
You have 24 hours
to get us some valuable information.
If not by the 25th hour,
your precious little girlfriend will be
on her way to a federal facility.
Her son will be in a group home
or wherever they send kids these days.
And you,
you might just find yourself
behind bars with her.
You know what, Will,
I ain't gonna lie to you.
I cannot help you this time,
but you can help yourself.
Get us something
real solid.
All of this go away.
Come on, Kim.
Let's go get something for lunch.
Fuck.
♪ I'm legacy ♪
♪ Niggas switched on who I started with ♪
♪ But things changed ♪
♪ Bloody niggas knew my heart ♪
♪ But they don't feel the same ♪
♪ Getting dark, it's getting
harder to conceal the pain ♪
(knocking on door)
What's up nigga, you
gonna answer the door?
♪ Switch on the glick ♪
New ass niggas.
♪ I hope this music make a way for me ♪
♪ If they wanna hear my
story gotta pray for me ♪
What's up, I got the text?
Everything okay?
Yeah, everything good.
I was just making sure you good.
I'm good.
All right, well look I got
some people waiting on me.
I'll me back up with you later.
All right.
You here to trap or make love, nigga?
Man, mind your business, man.
Hey bro, for real.
I think they got some top secret
shit going on, you hear me.
Shit, gotta be.
Why you say that?
'Cause all them niggas
pull up at the same time?
Man, that shit don't go, bro.
What you think going on?
You ask a lot of questions, nigga.
You feel it.
Nigga, we don't get paid
to ask no questions on what.
Fuck we get paid for then?
In a minute you gonna find out.
For shit sure.
[Reporter] Fighting broke out overnight
between rival factions along
the Israeli Syrian border.
Hey, baby.
I am so, so, so tired.
[Reporter] And 13 civilians.
How was your day?
Boring as shit.
[Reporter] Reported to have made it back
to their headquarters.
What did you do?
Nothing.
Just did a bunch of drop
offs and pickups all day.
That's it?
Yep.
You should be happy.
Did I told you the
deeper you get into this
harder it is to get out.
Like quicksand.
What?
Nothing.
Anything worth mentioning?
Yeah, but I gotta question first.
[Reporter] Animal rights
activists have been pushing for-
- If I asked you, drop everything
and run away and start a new life with me?
What about your son?
About that.
So I spoke with Marcus today.
He told me after I do
this last drop with him,
then I'll be able to get my son.
Last drop.
Dang, all these questions.
But you know what, they don't even matter.
He wants me to run a
decoy shipment with him.
Decoy shipment?
[Reporter] Was out for
three hours in Eastern Metro
because of down-
- He said we were gonna do a drop
and sit and wait.
[Reporter] No injuries were reported.
Cleanup is expected to
take at least two days.
Then after that I'm done,
completely done.
[Reporter] And there was another
drive by shooting today downtown.
I can only get my hands
on like 50 Gs though.
It's something.
[Reporter] Unconscious but
expected to recover fully
and should be able to help with-
- What?
I've been saving this
for about three years.
[Clarence] How much is this?
About 2.2.
Million?
Look, we can take this
money, start a new life.
Hell, I can even put my
baby in private school.
And make more babies.
Ooh. Come here.
[Reporter] Chances are we're
in for another riot tomorrow.
The benefits of laughter.
It's no secret that...
Clarence, we figured
you see things our way.
What you got for us?
Not much really.
But it might be something.
It's gonna have to be, because
it's the best I've got.
There's gonna be a decoy
shipment going out tomorrow.
Are you kidding me?
A decoy load?
He's a fucking waste of time.
Hey.
And think about it.
Why would they go through all that trouble
with the decoy load
unless they didn't want
to get caught with the real thing?
Continue.
So the decoy load is meant to send you
in the other direction
of the real shipment.
So all you have to do is figure out
which one is the decoy load.
So you know who the decoy is.
All right.
But you gotta promise me
that you won't put charges on Kenya.
Done.
We never cared about her anyway.
We just needed you to do your job.
You know what?
Hold on one second.
Everything's gonna be just
fine, if you can stop this load.
Kenya will be exonerated of all
charges predated from today.
Kenya and Marcus are
gonna be in the decoy truck.
Now, I don't know where
the real one is going,
but I know it's not going be with them.
You better hope this checks out.
Go ahead.
We got movement.
You see what I see?
Kenya and Marcus.
We gonna catch them red handed.
We got 'em.
[Dispatcher] 911, what's your emergency?
Oh my god, oh my god.
I just saw a man force a
white woman into a car.
[Dispatcher] Have you been harmed?
Are you okay?
Uhhuh, uh-huh.
[Dispatcher] What is your location?
We're going down I-10 west now.
We're following them.
[Dispatcher] We're sending units now.
Okay.
♪ Hope you get well ♪
♪ Ill world, lot of zombies out ♪
♪ Niggas, run up on you
with them skillets ♪
♪ Try and fry you out ♪
♪ Big drip on my halo ♪
♪ You can't drive me out ♪
♪ She say she heard
about that fish scale ♪
♪ And wanna try me out ♪
♪ Open up that package ♪
♪ Breathe it in ♪
♪ Get that in your soul ♪
♪ Call me Dr Cb ♪
♪ Food for thought,
put that in your pole ♪
♪ Eat it up, activate your blessing ♪
♪ Stimulate your focus ♪
[Police] Go, go, go, go.
(sirens blaring)
FBI, hands up.
(intense music)
All this over a funky ass dice game?
Don't worry.
This is just my happy ending money.
Search everything.
(ominous music)
Waste of tax dollars.
(ominous music continues)
I appreciate it.
You did everything I asked you to do.
Don't I always come through for you?
Oh, I been meaning to
ask you about old boy.
Who, Clarence?
You love him?
We vibing.
Just vibing, huh?
Did you know he was a cop?
(soft tense music)
A cop?
Nah, I don't believe that.
I mean, ain't no way he a cop.
He can't be a cop.
The crazy part I know you ain't know.
A cop.
No.
All that fucking pillow talking.
You ain't leave me no
motherfucking choice.
Come on, Marcus. (cries)
You know I ain't know he was a cop.
Marcus, come on.
Marcus, you been knowing me my whole life.
That's the fucked up part, Kenya.
I really trusted you.
You know you don't
have to do this, right?
You don't.
You don't have to do this.
Marcus, please.
(Kenya cries)
Look, I'll disappear, all right.
You know it don't work like that Kenya.
Can't betray my brothers for you.
Marcus, you know I
didn't know he was a cop.
Marcus, you know I didn't know that.
Marcus, please. What about my son?
If you kill me, who's
gonna take care of my baby.
Marcus, come on.
Fuck Kenya.
I don't know.
(Kenya cries)
(somber music)
(gun fires)
(downcast music continues)
(knocking on door)
Yo, what's up fellas.
It's about Kenya, man.
Come on.
What happened?
You still trying to
see how we live, huh?
Of course he is.
Do I have a choice?
(gun cocks)
Not today.
See, the homie got killed
for fucking with your punk ass.
So now you gotta live with that.
And Kenya?
Man, I'm gonna miss that ass.
(guns firing)
(Clarence moaning)
Go get them bricks out the truck.
All right, all right.
What you wanna do about old girl?
Leave her.
Damn.
(phone buzzing)
Hey, yo, boss.
[Speaker] Hey man,
that thing you wanted to be taken care of?
It started.
Check mate.
(sirens blaring)
They set us up,
and we took the bait.
Ooh, I can't believe it.
I'm gonna find his ass,
and put his ass under the prison.
You wait and see.
(sirens blaring)
They ain't set you up, Kim.
(gun fires)
I did.
(sirens blaring)
What you wanna do
with these three, boss?
Let 'em go.
But from now on I'm running this show.
♪ I told them go with they mood ♪
♪ And moneys in their motivation ♪
♪ To murder some niggas ♪
♪ I took the top of a
coup, detachable roof ♪
♪ Yeah, that's a convertible, nigga ♪
♪ I was right there on the stoop ♪
♪ I'm able to shoot when niggas
pull up with them pistols ♪
♪ Was kill or be killed ♪
♪ Somebody got killed and I
was just thankful they missed ♪
♪ I pray to God every night for a meal ♪
♪ So I can take care of my children ♪
♪ I ask for protection ♪
♪ No weapons shall prosper ♪
♪ God, keep me safe when I'm touring ♪
♪ If they stop the bus on the interstate ♪
♪ We gonna be late for
them dinner plates ♪
♪ Nothing less than 25 ♪
♪ I ain't talking about percentage rates ♪
♪ I hustle my ass off,
like a year straight ♪
♪ No days off, bring the stash out ♪
♪ On the king size with the eff and in ♪
(Clarence gasps)
(soft tense music)