They thought about everything they'd been through.
The perilous swamp, the treacherous
tower, the darkness of rainbow caverns.
They stood together, exhausted from their adventure.
Rex stared in her eyes for a long time.
Then his great green lips curled sadly back from his fangs,
and his voice was soft as he said.
It's too bad it couldn't have worked out between us.
But at least we'll always have Tar Town.
You gotta to be pulling my tail.
That's your idea of a dinosaur story.
Let me see that.
It's my story, and it's a serious artistic statement, okay?
Arachnophobia alert.
Spiders where?
Timmy, you brat.
Made you look.
See what else is in here.
Timmy, don't! Give it back crater face!
Dear diary, oh, I am so in love with Mick.
He's almost as handsome as Rex.
- Jamie.
- I swear he's making it up.
- Oh, would I wouldn't give just the hold his..
- Timmy?
hand.
Hey, let me see that.
Hey, hey, no, please.
Ow.
Hey, these are just dinosaur stories.
You little horn head.
Program dimensional access.
Primary power on.
Check.
Hey, code orange.
Remote access.
Check.
- Goggles.
- Goggles
Ready?
Ready.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, my.
Oh, Dana.
Oh.
We've done it.
You got the new tape?
Dude, volcanic!
Come on, Tim, put it on.
As long as you apes, remember who's in charge here.
- Okay. Here it comes, here it comes.
Yeah.
This is the best.
THUNDERIN'!!!!
See, Jamie, you're going to be a real writer. this is what you gotta write
You know, Dinosaurs is about this really awesome world
where your friends are saurs..
who will take a chunk out of anybody who skates ya.
- We've broken the laws of time and space.
- Yes!
We've made history..
Oh, It's so beautiful.
Splendid.
Here, send it out for molecular test today.
10 points over the time.
10?
Oh, my God!
Gil!
Our plane leaves at 10!
The conference on inter-dimensional physics. Remember?
Oh! Right!
Wait a minute.
Dana, it's perfect.
We've got the data.
We've got the proof.
Right.
It'll be the dissertation they'll never forget.
They said it couldn't be done.
We can just make it.
Okay.
- We leave everything set up.
- Uh-huh.
And then when we get back, you'll be ready for the final test.
Sending a living being!
We have twelve minutes and five seconds to pack.
Right.
Gil..
Hurry.
Right.
I'm gonna get you, saur.
Hey, kids.
What's going on?
Oh, you guys are gonna ruin your eyes
- If they weren't already ruined.
- That better?
Sunshine.
A Sunday morning.
You know, it's a beautiful day outside.
You two should be out enjoying it.
Dad.
It's Saturday.
And there's three of us.
Hm? Oh.
So there are.
Hello, Dick.
It's Mick.
Right.
- Hi, Jamie.
- Hi, Mick.
Timmy, may I see you a second, please?
Sure.
Thank you.
You kids wouldn't believe what we accomplished in the lab today.
- Gil, let's go.
Oh! Right, gotta go.
- Okay, you have the keys?
- Yeah.
- Two sets.
- No how to work the washer and dryer.. the alarm..
- Yeah
Okay. You have to have the hotel number.
You have your father's beeper number.
Yeah.
Anything else..
Dial 911.
What about 976?
Excuse me? Gil?
Your mother and I are putting a lot of trust in you here, son.
We don't want any primate business while we're gone. Alright?
Okay, dad.
You can stay here, or, you can stay at Dicks.
Micks.
Right.
Oh, and remember, whatever you do, don't do it alone.
Okay.
Oh, and Timothy, Timothy, don't watch cartoons all day, okay?
What's wrong with watching cartoons?
Wait, your mother's right, Tim.
A boy your age should be out.
Oh, splitting atoms.
Or, whatever it is boys do.
What's wrong with doing what I want?
Oh, well.
Because the world doesn't revolve around Timothy Shepard.
Now, I don't have to tell you to stay out of lab, do I?
Oh, the la.. oh, no, don't worry, I'll take care of it.
Kiss?
Thank you.
Hey, guys.
I got this volcanic idea.
- Hey, hurry.
- Careful.
- Right.
Be careful with that.
We're going to watch dinosaurs on the big t.v. in the lab.
Timmy, didn't you just get busted?
I mean, we could get caught.
Come on.
All right, come on.
All right, I'll tell you the code, and you punch it in.
Oh, no.
Not definitely not.
You know I'm not good at these things?
Ever since a broke my sister's calculator when I was ten, I just..
Gotcha.
You didn't think I was gonna tell you the code, any way, did you?
Oh.
I knew that.
I did.
I don't know about this, Timmy.
It smells like orange juice in here.
Hey, Mick, move that pedestal aside.
Whoa.. Check it out.
The ultrasaurus of televisions.
Yeah, cool, huh?
I know your parents are supposed to be, like, these brilliant
scientists or something,
but I always wondered how they make a living in here.
Oh, we're still living off royalties from those solid
drape runners they patented a long time ago.
Timmy, are you sure you know what you're doing?
Yeah, don't worry.
I think you guys are ready to clam up and watch.
Wow, grippin'.
Can't wait for the sequel.
You just gotta turn it on.
Timmy..
positive you know what you're doing?
Do you want to see dinosaurs or not?
Yeah.
This is great.
Uh, Timmy?
What button did you push, Timmy? Shut it off!
Oh! What's happening?!
I feel nauseous.
Your parents are really gonna kill you now, Timmy.
That was no earthquake.
Hey, what the hot lava is going on here?
It's a.. it's a..
No way.
Yes way.
It's Forry, and we're in dinosaurs.
Except it's like 3D now.
I thought you needed special glasses or something for 3D.
Look, you can't pull anything over on me.
Uh-uh, I know you apes gotta be rocky spies
and it won't do you any good to try and get it out of me.
Hey, what kind of rocky are you anyway?
Pay attention when I'm talking to you.
Hey guys, guess who's coming to dinner.
Hey, let me take a look.
The Rockies!
Hide.
N- n- no, this way.
Let me get by here, if that saur's in here, will find her.
He ain't got a prayer.
You there.
Yeah, I'll find that saur.
That saur is mine.
This is messing up my hair.
Bear..
Bonehead..
Through there.
Ooh, You be a good Bear, Baby.
Knock 'em dead.
Aw, come on.
What do you want now, Link?
You already stripped Saur City bare.
And all that's left is women, children, and
us little guys who are no use to you.
My my.
Such hostility.
And ill timed too.
Considering I just saw that escaped saur run out of here.
Wait, Link, don't hurt him.
I mean he is kind of cute.
Kinda reminds me of my Bear.
Where is that saur?
Get lost, you Cro-Magnon moron.
What.. What's he mean by that?
Uh, well, uh, he means Link that,uh,
you're very highly positioned on the evolutionary
chain of the Homo Sapien kingdom, for a Neanderthal.
Compliments will get you no place.
Well, that depends on the approach.
Doesn't it?
You adorable little creature, you.
You now tell the Missy where she went.
No chance, Babe.
Listen here.
Sooner or later, we find all of you who try to escape.
Just, uh, tell us where she went.
- Get down
- and it'll go, uh, easier on everybody.
Go, jump in a crater.
I got her.
Link, I told you we'd find her in the power station.
Take me back. But let my son go home.
He's no use to you!
That's my Bear.
Come on.
Wait a minute, you're taking a hatchling?
That's not all.
Wait, if you take that, the cooling units on the lava tanks won't work.
And we'll be looking at it complete meltdown of Saur
City in less than 24 hours.
Ain't you an Einstein.
That's the idea, birdbrain.
Mr. Big's been shutting this city down for a while.
'bout time somebody finished it, once and for all.
Oh.
Somebody's got to stay here till meltdown starts
to make sure they don't try any, uh, lizard business.
You got it, darling.
Come on, let's go.
See you later, darling.
I'll be back.
Woo, woo, wow.
Back to the tower, boys, Mr. Big's waiting.
Quiet.
Talk about natural gas.
This way
No, Timmy, this way.
Are they gone yet?
Yeah.
Hey, wait a minute.
Aren't these the door we came through?
But there was stuff spinning. And lights.
Mm, there's nothing here.
Except for darkness.
Wait the fuse.
When the Rockies took the fuse, something happened.
I'll take fatal mistakes for a thousand, Jamie.
Who is someone we'll never listen to again?
Ding ding ding.
Who is?
Timmy.
Who me?
Come on, let's go find Forry.
Now, Mr Big gives me a reward.
Dude, this is all your fault?
are you crazy?
After all I've done for you?
You should be thanking me.
Get a life, Mick.
We're in dinosaurs for a roarin' out loud.
Come on, you always hated the Rockies.
But this is your big chance.
To do what?
Get my intestines wrapped around a tree by some Neanderthal?
No, I think not.
Timmy's gone bye-bye.
Think about it.
It's a cartoon, right?
We know everything about this place.
We're in control.
Let's have some fun before we go back to Dullsville.
Jamie, you want to meet Rex..
We know he's going to stomp the Rockies.
We know he's in Tar Town.
Let's go get him.
Total meltdown, the end, finite, it's over.
Why me?
Hey, there's Forry.
Hey Forry.
You think you can't fly. 'Cause you got hurt.
But we know it's all in your head.
We'll help you learn again, if you come with us.
First you hominids waltz in here without an explanation.
You insult me.
And by the way, Who are you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm Timmy Shepard and this is Jamie and that's Mick.
Hey, Forry.
Mr.. Forry.
Do you think maybe I could have your autograph before we leave?
You're kind of my hero.
Right.
I'm probably going to die under molten lava in 24 hours.
And I have to spend my day with a bunch of crazy apes.
Why me?
If you'll excuse me now, I've got to get out of here.
And I suggest you do the same.
Because the lava is starting to go.
What's happening in there?
Red.
Bubbling.
Hot.
Lava.
Boiling, Lava.
Scary.
I'm scared.
I want to go home.
Four, you've got to help us.
Kids, I got my own problems.
In the cartoon, you're the one who goes to Tar Town to get Rex.
To stop the Rockies and save Saur City
Yeah, right.
Now you're going to take us too.
Sure, Tar Town. Tail pit of the world.
There's no way they there since the Rockies took over the train.
Great.
24 hours, we'll be jacuzzi'ing in hot lava.
Wait a minute, look at this.
Why can't we go this way?
No way, Doll.
Why not?
Forget it.
Extinction Grove.
What's that?
It's like a graveyard.
Whoa.
Time out.
Graveyard?
Wait, lemme think?
No.
No, I don't remember there ever being a graveyard in the cartoon.
Must be an episode we haven't seen yet.
So, why can't we go that way.
I mean, it's just a stupid old graveyard.
Nobody's been that way in a millennium.
Once they go in, no reptile is ever left.
Alive.
Dead dinosaurs tell no tales.
Well, we have to get the fuse to get home, right?
And we have to get Rex to help us get the fuse.
It's decided then.
We're going through the graveyard.
And you're coming with us, whether you like it or not.
Hey, what are you doing? Watch the wings.
Hey you, you five fingered ape. Hey, put me down.
I'm not going to Tar Town. I'm telling you it's a really bad neighborhood.
Trust me, guys.
Let's have fun, Mick.
Great. More fun.
Aw, don't be so petrified.
Oh, why me?
WOW!
Mr. Big's tower.
I can't believe it's real.
Hey, can't we talk this over, guys?I mean, graveyards, Tar Town, Rex.
And what makes you think you'll help us anyway?
Hey, hey, hey, are you guys listen to me?
I can't wait to see what it gives you, Bear.
Yeah.
Hi.
Well..
Yeah..
We got you a steg-saur.
And a bonus too.
Who led the search party?
I did.
My Bear found the saur.
Come forward and receive your reward.
Thank you, thank you.
I hope you enjoy it.
That's right.
Want a light?
Give it to him, Small.
Whoever was most anxious to capture the saur
was probably the man who let her escape in the first place.
I won't tolerate this kind of inefficiency.
No way! Huh-uh!
Let this be an example for discipline.
I'll have no more foolish games from you idiots.
Do I make myself clear?
Yes, Sir.
Good!Take her away.
You're mine now.
Take it outside, mammals.
You are a Cro-Magnon moron!
You don't have to butter me up.
Put me down, Link.
- Link, put me down.
- Meltdown soon...
Hominids and their great ideas.
So much for evolution.
Extinction..
Grove.
You go through there?
Here, take Forry.
Stop, locked, and, blocked.
Sorry, guys, we're moving on.
If we head for the high ground now, we might make it before the lava comes.
Not so fast, Forry.
What are you doing, Tim?
You were saying, Forry.
Ah! This place is cool.
Yeah, cool.
As in, goodbye cool world.
I wish Tops and Rex were here right now.
What makes you so sure they're going to help us anyway?
Rex and the folks in Saur City don't exactly see eye to eye.
I knew I shouldn't have got out of bed this morning.
Oh. Mick.
Hey guys..
maybe..
maybe Forry's right?
I warned you guys.
I wonder why this was never in the cartoon.
It's too scary for kids.
Boy, this is great.
This is better than a dinosaur story Jamie ever wrote.
Lost..
we're lost..
we're definitely lost.
But how do we get across?
Easy.
How about if I just wait here?
No way, Forry, we need you.
Oh, it's great to be needed.
Water..
I've always hated water.
When I was six, I went swimming..
my brother's held my head under water..
My brother's friends held my head under water.
Oh! I love water!
Oh yeah! just love it!
Bring on some more for me, huh?
Like I'm not neurotic enough already.
I need somebody to put water in front of me.
- Oh, this is just-- GAH!!
- MICK!
Timmy! Do something!!
- Where'd he go?
- Wait, I can't see him.
Mick!
I knew it!!
- There he is!
- Someone do something!
Mick!
Timmy, grab him!!
Mick?!
There he is! Come on, Mick! Great! Grab on, Mick!
Timmy!
Grab him!
Something's got my leg!
Hit it, Timmy!
I knew we'd never make it out alive.
Kill it!
HIT IT!!
WE'RE DINNER!!
Where is it?
Let's not wait to find out!
This way.
No, let's go back.
Come on, go!
Timmy!
What are you staring at?
- AAHHHHHH!!
Come on. Come on. Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
Do you guys realize that was a Messosaurus?
Boy genius.
Forry, are you OK?
Oh.
Sorry, Forry.
Dames are all alike.
They all drop you, eventually.
You guys, we made it.
Great.
I really hate this place.
It's not what I expected.
What's a matter, Timmy? I thought this was your favorite part.
I doesn't smell in cartoon.
Besides, have you looked at your hair, lately?
Man, anybody got a comb?
Where's my cave?
Apes!
Sorry.
It's OK.
You know, your hair looks kind of cool that way.
See Forry, this place is OK.
That'll teach you to cheat, you scumscale!
You guys are crazy.
Hey! Some loser just knocked over our tip jar.
Hey, hey, you didn't pay for your drink, Jerko.
Get a life.
Read 'em and weep.
Not so fast.
- Full Cave.
- Way to go pal.
- Plate 'em and slate 'em.
- Ooh, yeah.
- Look at that!
- What are those?
What bunch of freaks?
Looking for action, big boy.
Hey, when does the show start?
You gonna bet any time this year, huh?
Lizards and Saurians, The Sharp Fang is proud to present.
Raquel and her Million B.C.'s
WOW! what a babe!
Hey, Hairless.
- How'd you like to do the vertical stomp.
- Well, I..
I just love soft, pink skin.
Mick, help!!
Come here, Sugar. Come here, come on, come here.
Gimme a primordial ooze, heh.
Hey, I want one of those..
Are you sure you can handle it?
Yeah.
I tried to warn ya.
- Oh God, I'm so thirsty.
- Wait, you guys?
One too many, huh, babe?
Hey you guys, that was Tops.
Who?
Tops.
He's like Rex's Barney Rubble.
Who's that?
Anyway, he looks like a hustler from here.
- If that's Tops
- Then that must be Rex.
Come on.
Hey, where are you going?
Hey, queen of claws is high.
Hey Tops.
Tops pal, we need your help.
We need to talk to Rex right away.
Do I know you?
I hope not because you guys are so pink and hurts to look at you.
Hey, it's kinda dark down here.
Look, we're here on important business.
Now you, I know.
The little birds that can't fly.
Hey, who are you calling a bird?
Talk money and I won't call you a bird.
Look, this concerns the fate of Saur City.
The Rockies you've been picking almost everything we have
and now they're going to melt the city down.
Right, I'll bring the marshmallows.
So you're not even going to help?
Wait a minute.
You guys always help.
Like, remember the time in episode 12
when the Rockies took over, Primeval Park, and they rousted "Old Steg".
- And you guys had to swing from those vines to save him.
- Wait a minute, Rex?
These guys are wacko.
Look, Rexy and I are doing fine.
It's not our problem, babe.
You know, I'm really disappointed in you.
The Rex I used know, I would have leapt at the chance to get out of this
dump and be a hero.
But, the truth is, you only think of yourself.
Like someone else I know.
Considering how those leaf eaters in Saur City feel about my father,
they're not going to back me to fight against the Rockies.
And I can't take all the Rockies myself.
So, you're a coward, too?
Rockies!
Big trouble, big trouble.
It's looks like a disgrace to evolution.
You know, I heard this is the place where all the toughest
saurs in Tar Town chill.
But I guess what I heard must be wrong.
Because I don't see nobody comes here
just a bunch of yellow reptiles.
Take this ugly scale head for example.
Would you..
Now I heard all the Tyrannosaurs were dead.
But I guess the real truth is, they all turned into fossil disease. Like this.
I know you Rockies don't have tail brains like saurs
but I always thought you had at least one brain.
I wouldn't be talking about brains if I was you.. Saur.
Yeah. Yeah.
'cause that was one stupid thing to say.
You know something, I wondering how many people would
still bet on a half extinct sour who's nothing but the cowardly
offspring of a traitor.
He hit 'im, he hit 'im. See that? Did you see that
He hit 'im, square in the jaw
THUNDERIN'!!
Mick! MICK!
- You want me to do violence?
- Just get rid of him!!
Wow, I got a loaded gun.
Hey!
I dare you to do that, again!
My glasses!
Hey! Who's gonna pay for this mess!!
Eat my scales.
- Mick..
- Oops.
Thanks.
Oh, man.
Gimme claw!
I don't believe it, I never saw such a bunch of sissies!!
You know, she's right, Tops.
This place is a dump.
Wait a minute, Rex, you can't be thinking of going.
I got a better idea.
We could make a lot of money here in Tar Town.
Has it ever occurred to you, there's more to life than just money?
Well, no.
But, what about the Rockie Patrols?
I know a secret way to Saur City.
Come on guys.
Hey, Link.
I think you should see this man.
He just came from Tar Town, and he's got a story you'll want to hear.
Yeah, there's a Tyrannosaurus headed
for Sour City and a Proto-Cerotops and
the little flyer from Sour City.
Now listen, we tried to stop 'em the best we could.
Well, well, I came to check the construction
and got something even bigger.
Big, big, big.
I think it's time to show the citizens of the Saur City the
follies of insurrection, especially when
my plans are so close to fruition.
Right.
What does that mean?
What it means is I want you to
organize a squad to take that Tyrannosaurus
and anyone who's aiding him.
We'll start with a little flapping eruption first.
And I don't care what condition we take them in.
Do I make myself clear now?
As ice boss.
Good, big plan, big big plan.
Listen, listen, uh, I hate to ask you this really, but
didn't I hear someone mention something about a reward.
Come to my office.
Can I offer you a cigar?
Oh! Oh! The lava's coming!!
What are you? A bunch of tourists? Run!!
What's going on Forry?
They're evacuating the city before the power plant goes.
We should have until dawn though. Come on.
Wow.
Ooh, a treehouse
Yeah, what do you guys think?
It's beautiful.
Hey, Mick, you go first.
Put me down, Timmy.
You guys take the long way up and I'll meet you at the top.
Top floor, guys.
Forry I'm next, right?
Hey, this guy's got bats in his bellfree.
Let's get this party started.
Don't fall, Mick.
It's not funny.
Tree's really tall.
Yeah, only thing missing is Tarzan.
Aw.. Stop with the small talk, will ya?
I got company here.
Just light the place up.
Rad.
Oh, Wow.
It's even better than it is in the cartoon.
Hey, watch out who you're calling a cartoon, Timmy.
Yeah, what's your angle?
Come on, Tops.
But we don't know anything about them.
Let's fix that.
What about your world?
Well..
There are more buildings.
Schools.
Yeah.
Video stores.
And book stores.
Lots of people.
Grandparents?
Parents.
Language teacher, Mr. Ham.
Home.. it's not fair.
Mick..
What's with them?
We got a few minutes, I'm going to hang.
I think I'm going to go keep an eye out for the Rockies.
Guards at the base of the tower, change just before dawn.
That's when we'll make our move.
Great.
What do we do till then?
Do what Forry's doing.
What's wrong, Mick?
What's wrong?
Jamie, we could be stuck here for the rest of our lives.
We won't be.
We'll get back.
I used to be afraid of heights.
I'm not anymore.
Hey, what's with the glacier face?
Mom and dad's experiment's sent us here.
Maybe there's other worlds too.
Maybe everything we make up has a life somewhere else.
Like hobbits, sandworms, Captain Nemo.
Why should I have to go back to Dullsville?
You've changed since you've been here.
Yeah?
Well, you look different.
And, um, you don't complain as much as you did before.
Oh.
And you were really good in the fight.
What?
Was I as good as Tops?
And Rex?
You were better.
Yeah?
Come on, there's something I should show you.
Come on.
- Where are we going?
- You'll see.
There is no need for me to hide any longer.
Allosaurus' shall rule the world once more.
The reign of terror begins.
What's that?
Skull Island.
We're going into the heart of it.
Who is that?
My father.
This place was once the center of Saur City
where the people built monuments to their greatest leaders.
Traitor?
I was barely out of my egg when my father
fought the battle that freed us from the Allosaurus'. And the people
of Saur City presented him with the key to the city gates.
But one Allosaurus survives.
Mr. Big.
He attacked again and..
my father made a deal with him.
He turned over a source city right in front of the city gates.
They left this key lying in the dirt.
What's so important about the dumb tower?
Nobody knows for sure.
All I know is this is the last good thing left of my father.
You see Timmy, this world's not so perfect.
Guess none of them are.
Tonight's your lucky night.
You get to see Link start action with his big club.
Yeah, that's not the kind of action I had in mind.
How's about a good luck kiss?
You big lug.
Let's go, fellas.
Get out of the way.
Knock 'em dead, Rockie.
Did you hear something?
Get up in the tree house.
Come on!!
Timmy?
Rex?
Timmy..
Rex, over here.
Where are you?
Got to go up to the tree house.
Go, go, Timmy, run, get out of here.
With you now pal.
THUNDERIN'!!
Ow!
come on, boys!
Gimme claw!
We laid 'em out like turtles.
THUNDERIN'!!
Ah! Gimme claw!
Tops?
Come on, Tops, company's coming.
Oh my caps, and I just paid them off.
Come on, Tops. Tops?
Oh no. Not again. Come on, Tops, they're getting away.
Who, hit me?
Boy, does that smart.
AH! NO!
GET AWAY!!
Where you goin'? Get after them.
Mr. Big wants to see you now.
Oh, no.
Get away, you Rockie.
What is that power? I must have that device
Keep an eye out for those saurs. They could be hiding anyplace.
I wanted to see me, Mr. Big?
What's happening, Link?
Why isn't this over by now?
I don't know, Sir.
They seem to have some kind of power. Our men seem helpless.
I want it badly.
I know, but, th..
I want it now, Link!
NOW!!.
Yes, Sir.
Mick, get out of the way.
There's too many we're dead.
It's okay, Nick.
Got the remote control.
How'd you do that?
Come on, let's get back the dock.
- Stay here, I'm gonna check on Jamie.
- Okay.
- Wait! Where's Rex and Tops?
- I don't know, you better wait for them.
Help!
Let go of me, you ape!
Put me down.
You'll be sorry, you, Neanderthal!
Hey, what's with all the ruckus?
Where's Timmy?
You mean, you guys don't know where he is?
The Rockies must've gotten Timmy.
I could hear him screaming for help.
That means they got the remote too.
What's a remote?
You know, the thing Timmy was zapping everybody with.
They'll take it to Mr. Big, and then we're really in trouble.
He's right, they'll take him to the tower.
Hey, if we're going in there, we better go in undercover.
But how?
Come on.
Come on!
Gimme that, you green gorilla!
Ow!
That's it, huh? Doesn't look like much.
Maybe we should test it first.
Wait! That's it. We're over!
There's definately something missing, Link.
Tell me how this works, or I'll pat you with
steak sauce, and throw you to the meat eaters
You don't scare me, Link.
I'll never tell.
Oh, really?
Then maybe Mr. Big will give you a reward.
Hurry, there's not much time.
Going down!
I sure hope Timmy's down here.
Dungeon!
Sub-basement.
Check it out, Mick.
There's only two of 'em.
They sitting beneath a bell. Looks like some kind of alarm.
Hey, Mick, is that Rhamphorhynchus in your coat?
Are you just happy to see me?
would you cut with the jokes I'm roasting in here?
Look, we gotta figure out a way to
lure those sentries away from the bell.
Hey, I got an idea.
Uh-Uh, uh.. No way, guys. Uh-Uh.
Excuse me, boys?
I was looking for somebody who was supposed to be getting off.
Duty, I mean.
I was really counting on some company tonight.
Now, now, boys, there's no need to fight.
We can all party together, right?
Come on.
I don't like to wait.
Yes!
Thunderin'.
You were supposed to lure 'em back so that we can knock 'em out.
Sorry, guys, guess I didn't need the help.
I like her style.
Little Miss Muffet.
Makes her first knockout.
- Timmy?
Timmy?
I'm coming.
I'll get you out.
Okay, hold on.
Ease it up a little bit.
Timmy.
Here we go.
Oh, boy.
Rex.
Don't you recognize me, Rex?
How ironic, my father was a traitor in a prison of his own making.
I know this will be hard for you to accept Rex, but please hear me out.
Big allied with the forces of the Rockies.
And he had a potion that could bend anyone to his will.
You were drugged?
And forced.. to hand Saur City over.
The only thing that's kept me going all these years
is thinking of you, Rex.
Father.
No, there's no time. We must destroy the tower.
There is one last chance to stop him.
Help me, Rex.
Jamie, give me the keys quick. We've got work to do.
Beneath our feet is an immense lava pool held back by a cap.
It will take me a few more moments to open it.
I'll help you.
No.
You must help your friends.
I'll follow you soon.
Come on, Rex. We're gotta to go.
It's the only way.
Father!
Oh.. Help.. Please..
Come on, hurry. You guys go ahead.
I'll work down here and then take the next car up.
Come on, come on.
Comming...
Now, all we got to do is find that fuse.
And Timmy.
You guys realize how big this tower is?
Where do you even start to look for either one?
Dungeon.
This is your floor.
This is your last chance.
How does it work?
Go jump inti a tar pit.
Enough of this!
Give him the potion.
No.
You won't use it the way you did against my father, Big.
Well, this is an unexpected pleasure.
The son of Cain, I presume.
And as in ineffectual as your father.
- Don't come any closer if you value this little ape.
- No, no, don't listen to him!
Get ready to grab that rope.
Not this time..
Useless fool.
You better hide, Forry.
The remote.
Not so fast
Hand it over.
No.
I got it now..
Way to go, Doll!
- Top Floor!
- Uh, money please.
- Okay, okay.
- Thank you very much! Top flloor.
Get 'em, Rex.
Come on, Rex.
Throw him into the pit.
Step, please.
Tops!
Hold on, Mick!
TIMMY!!
You okay, Timmy?
Are you alright, kid?
Yeah, help Rex.
Rex! I'll be right there, pal!
Get 'em, guys!
You hairless, humanoid, little bimbette.
Technically, you neanderthal trollop..
Wait, Timmy.. batteries.
Go get it, Timmy.
Over here, nope, over here!
Sorry..
This is for Saur City!
And this one's for my father.
Hey, Big!
Later, Dude!
Wow.
Good shot, kid. Beat me to it.
I'm free..
I'm free!!
Gimme claw.
That guy was the pits. Hope that's where he went.
Guys, we got a problem here.
What's wrong?
This fuse is the power for the whole building.
If I disconnect it, the elevators won't work.
So we'll take the stairs.
But we can't take the stairs. This is too tight.
We've got just enough time to make it back to Saur City.
You bet we'll make it.
But how?
You guys take the elevator now, and I'll
fly the fuse down when you reach the bottom.
- But Forry. You can't.
- Come on, Timmy.
Let's get out of here.
Look, kid, your concern is touching.
To say nothing of a new direction.
But get out of here now.
Good luck, handsome.
Hubba, hubba.
Happy landing.
Wow.
What are you doing with them?
EVOLVING!!
That's one giant leap for woman kind.
Help that elevator.
Ground floor, going down.
Oh, my God.
Hey, uh, I'm sorry. I hope I didn't rough you up too bad.
That's okay.
The more on our side, the better.
Ground floor.
Get out of my way.
Hey, can you see Forry?
Talk about a crash course.
Come on, Forry, use your wings and fly!
Well, here goes nothing.
I can still fly!
Hey, meet you in Saur City.
Oh, I knew your could do it.
My hero..
Quick, guys, let's take the train.
Get aboard.
Father.
Rex..
We gotta go.
What are we waiting for, Tops?
Nothing anymore, pal.
Get out of my way.
I'm sorry, Rex.
He-he-he, I'm flying, he-he-he.
We made it.
Rex, you know he's a hero again, don't you?
But he's gone now, and, I've been wrong all these years.
But Rex, that doesn't matter now.
You know the truth.
You'll have a good memories of him for the rest of your life.
Come on, hurry.
Right behind you, Rex.
Hope Forry made it.
Hey, wait up.
Allow me.
Way to go, sister.
It's about time you guys got here.
He's stinking up the place.
I think I got this just about fixed.
Are we gonna make it?
I hope so.
If not, we're all gonna be doing the molten mambo.
Sure, you don't need any help with this?
It's gonna be like a only world back home.
That's okay.
I almost got it.
Well, you're king of the dinosaurs now.
Remember, Jamie, we'll always have Tar Town.
Good luck, Rex.
Kick some tail, huh?
You got it.
I'm gonna stay with you, Rex
I could be your scout, you know, take care of stuff for you.
I'm even pretty good in the fight now.
Timmy, what about the people in our world that would miss you?
Don't we count for anything?
Or is this still just Timmy first?
You guys would actually miss me?
Of course we would.
So would your parents.
They love you, Timmy.
The decisions up to you, Timmy.
Think hard, Timmy.
Come on, I want to be a part of something.
You are, you always have been, but you have to go back.
We'll miss you too.
Here, take this.
This way you'll always have the key.
Go, go and be a king in your own world.
I'll be back, someday.
Come here, come here and give the Missy a kiss goodbye.
Keep cool, kiddo.
I almost got it.
IT WORKS!!
For Saur City, maybe.
Not for us.
I don't get it.
Maybe you'll get your wish after all, Timmy.
Come on, Timmy. There's gotta be another way out of here.
Maybe there is.
In fact, maybe the answer's not the fuse.
Well, it's worth a shot.
Use it wisely, kid.
THUNDERIN'!!
Goodbye, Timmy.
Goodbye, Rex.
Bye.
Don't wait, Timmy.
Don't go, please.
What about all the fun we had?
Don't you wanna stick around for a while?
Timmy?
Where is he?
Don't know.
Thought he was right behind us.
My gosh, he didn't make it back through.
You alright?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
He check out the tube.
Wanna light?, Wanna light? Wanna light? Wanna light?
You can turn that thing off, better than you turned it on.
Come on, you guys, let's go.
Timmy, are you all right?
Yeah, we're great.
Well.. Ah, who dressed you kids?
Mr. Big's Dungeon.
What's that?
Is that a new shop with the mall?
What? You don't like it?
It's the newest thing in fashion.
Whatever to jeans and t-shirts.
Wait, so how was conference?
Oh, ah.
Well, they didn't believe us.
They thought it was a new way to make orange juice.
So I'm afraid we have a lot of work
to do before we send a human through.
What's so funny?
Dad, don't be mad, but I gotta show you the raddest thing.
Come on, come on, you're not gonna believe this.
You're not gonna believe this.
Did you go in the lab?
We told you not to go in the lab.