Generated & Edit by:
Brothers_Marzouk
The active learning defense
system we are testing,
continues to operate flawlessly.
One might even say miraculously,
we are navigating under the
Arctic ice cup by Ted Ragony.
and five days from home.
After 25,000 nautical miles,
the Sevastopol has deliberately approached
every navy in the world
and remained completely undetected.
The Patkova stealth capability..
has exceeded all expectations.
We are at this moment
the state of the art...
of war.
The most fearsome killing machine ever
devised by man,
and we are impossible to find.
Captain, we have a submerged contact
designated Semyon 83,
exhibiting tools of the US Virginia
class submarine,
bearing 130, drawing forward.
Chief of the watch, man battle station silently,
rigged for all to follow.
Ships that 5-0 meters bottom, 7-2 meters,
clearance to the ice canopy, 2-1 meters.
- Distance to deep water
- 2 kilometers, allusion precipice in 6 minutes.
Ranging maneuver, half,
left 15 degrees around,
steady course 100, come up easy
on a standard of battle.
- Captain has the call.
- Yes sir.
Coming to course 1-0-0, ready on
course 1-0-0, weapons officer ready.
Steady course 100 degrees.
Ordinance Commander, Distance?
Mining solution is tracking at
a distance of 15,000 meters.
Sir, that doesn't make sense,
tunnel is this loud and clear?
It must be close to the back.
Captain, firing solution just to
the step change to 10,000 meters.
Nothing moves that fast.
All solutions are matching,
the range is true.
Hell, right full, rather to course 2-7-0.
Course 2-7-0, aye.
We'll just walk away
and head for deep water.
Contact bearing 1-6-0.
Bearing value zero?
He's there, turning with us again.
He can see us.
Impossible, we're invisible.
Weapon, round diagnostics
and sonar and fire control.
Something is arriving.
Sir, he's flooding his torpedo tubes.
- The torpedo room gone, hold on torpedo tubes.
- Aye sir.
- Check launcher.
- Front - Clear.
- Load Stern-Fired Torpedo.
- Loaded.
Torpedo tubes loaded
it's open, out the doors.
Weapons, flood tubes 1 to 4 and open out the doors.
Enter firing solution into tube 2.
I get it. Making tube 2 ready
in other space.
Captain, pace provoking us.
He wants an excuse to blow us
out of the water.
Enemy to be doing the water bearing Q-0-0.
1,000 meters and accelerating.
Hell, left full, rather all ahead flash, cabin.
A is left full.
Entering all ahead, flying cavity.
Don't scatter measures.
Launching countermeasures.
Fire tube 2.
The torpedo on the away.
Running hot.
Enemy torpedo still homing.
Range, 800 meters.
He's blown through our countermeasures.
- Hell, right full, rather.
- Right full, aye sir.
600 meters.
Stand by to emergency blow
all main balusters.
400 meters.
Commander of the watch, stand by
for collision alert.
200 meters.
This is the captain all ahead.
Enemy torpedo impacting.
Five
Four
Three
Two
One
Impact!
What just happened?
It's gone.
- It missed us?
- No.
It vanished.
Like it was never there.
Sola, where is the enemy vessel?
Bearing 3-5-0 4,000 meters
of a starboard bow.
Our torpedo is running through.
Impact with enemy submarine in.
Three
Two
One
Where was the impact?
Captain, enemy submarine has vanished.
It's gone, sir.
I don't understand.
It was never there.
We've been chasing your father.
It was right there.
- The instruments don't lie.
- They lie to us today.
Weapons.
Shut down our torpedo.
Aye, captain.
Shutting down torpedo.
Secure from battle stage.
This is why we have sea trials.
There's a bug in the system.
A ghost in a machine.
- It's time to go home.
- Captian!
Our torpedo is not responding.
It's coming right at us.
Our torpedo is holding range 400 meters.
Aye, come on.
Shut down our weapons.
Our torpedo is still closing.
range 200 meters.
It's a simple homemade power stand.
sound the collision alarm.
Fuck.
Hey, delivery?
Hello?
That's a gnatum.
Easy.
India's Zulu 254.
Bravo Echo 101.
Now, I'm
need you to ask me
the security question first.
Oh yeah, Sorry.
What is the ice?
We live and die in the shadows.
For those we hold close.
For those we never meet.
You can put it on the table.
Hey.
Welcome to IMF.
You made the right choice.
Son.
Good evening, Mr. Hunt.
It's been a long time.
Our lives are the sum of our choices.
And we cannot escape the past.
30 years ago, you were offered two choices.
Join the IMF or spend your life in prison.
Because of your unique natural talents,
your government forgave you.
But we will never forget.
Just as you will never forget the death
that brought you to us all those years ago.
This is to remind you of
your oath and allegiance to us.
The stakes of this mission
are higher than ever.
Your habitual rope
behavior will not be tolerated.
Should you choose to accept
it is imperative that you listen.
Your government is searching for a key.
Its purpose, its vital importance to us,
is none of your concern.
What should concern you is the
involvement of your friend Ilsa Faust.
She killed a courier in Istanbul.
and we believe he was carrying
one half of the key we're searching for.
Why she has chosen to
interfere in this affair is a mystery.
as are her whereabouts.
What is certain is that your
government has put a price on her head.
And these bounty
hunters are out to collect it.
They never bring a fugitive back to life.
And rarely in one piece.
We believe they're headed for
the Arabian desert's empty quarter
in search of your friend.
Find the bounty hunters
and you may just find her.
Your mission should you choose to accept it
is to acquire the key and deliver it to us.
What happens to Ilsa
after that is up to you.
As always if any members of
your team are caught or killed
the secretary will disavow
any knowledge of your actions.
This message will self
destruct in five seconds.
Good luck Ethan.
Ethan.
Step up.
So what are we dealing with?
This entity has multiple personalities
at times behaving like a computer virus
and a tapeworm and a botnet.
Distorting any and all digital
information with which it comes in contact.
Once infected nothing recorded, stored or
transmitted digitally can be trusted as fact.
At the outset it concentrated
primarily on news and social media
which was of little concern to
us as it often suited our purposes
until six months ago,
when the entity breached
Saudi Arabia's General
Intelligence directorate.
And assimilated their top
secret active-learning AI
before vanishing into the cloud.
Subsequent attacks increased
10,000 fold overnight,
spreading exponentially.
Indicating that the entity
has since become sentient.
You're telling me this
thing has a mind of its own?
Over the last three weeks
alone it has accessed
our satellite telecommunications,
the Federal Reserve,
the stock market and
the national power grid.
The FAA, NASA and the
combined branches of our military.
And we're not alone.
It has penetrated the world
and European central banks.
It has led you to the major defense,
finance and infrastructure systems
of Russia, India, Israel,
Australia, all of Europe.
And what did it do to all
of these systems exactly?
Nothing.
Nothing?
It came and it went.
Leaving fingerprints where
they could easily be found
and sending a very clear message.
I shall return.
Whatever its ultimate goal
is, we're powerless to stop it.
The full force of its energy is
now directed at a single objective.
The world's intelligence networks.
The very truth as we know it.
The entire intelligence
community is racing to archive
hard copies of our fact
positive knowledge bases
before our most secure data
centers are breached and corrupted.
Which is only a matter of time.
The entity will know precisely
how to undermine our every strength
and exploit our every weakness.
How to turn our allies into enemies.
And our enemies into aggressors.
Why not air gap our intelligence services?
Cut them off from the
outside world entirely.
We already have.
But servers require
humans to maintain them.
And humans are the weakest
link in any security chain
especially when dealing with a
godless, stateless, amoral enemy.
One that has been patiently
listening, reading, watching.
Harvesting our deepest
personal secrets for years.
Able to be guile, blackmail,
bribe, or be anyone at once.
And to manipulate us at will
through our total dependence
on a carefully constructed digital reality.
An enemy that is everywhere.
And nowhere.
And has no center.
Arr.
So what you're telling me is
the most awesome god damn intelligence
and tactical apparatus on the planet
has no way of killing this thing.
You don't want to kill it, sir.
You want to control.
And how do we do that?
Mr. Kittridge.
CIA's assets in the Kremlin
informed us that the Russians
have focused the majority
of their intelligence activity
on acquiring two halves
of the cruciform key.
And what does it unlock?
I'm not exactly sure.
But the Russians seem to believe
that it somehow has the power
to deactivate our mysterious entity.
Though, ideally.
They hope to control it.
Harness.
Do you believe that, Kittridge?
What matters is that the rest of world believes it.
Japan, India, Germany,
and the Brits didn't get no one not
not even closest allies have willingly
whispered one word of it to us,
which would indicate that there's a global
race on to acquire the two halves of this key.
Every nation in it before themselves,
not to kill this thing, sir,
but to weaponize it and in so doing establish a new,
incontestable form of global dominance.
How do we find this key first?
Well, we know that a
buyer is passing somewhere
through the Middle East
sometime in the next 72 hours.
We believe that he already
has one half of this key.
You believe?
Well, at this point, we can't
be certain it's not a counterfeit.
How would you verify that?
The only thing that can authenticate
one genuine half of the key
is the other genuine half of the key.
It's true mate, if you will.
We think it's some sort of fail-safe.
How do we find its main?
Well, we believe the other
genuine half of the key
was in the hands of this woman.
Who is she?
Ilse Faust, former British intelligence.
Where is she now?
She's dead, sir.
She was -excuse me- killed by mercenaries
- looking to collect a bounty.
- and who put up the bounty?
Given her body of work,
could it have been anyone?
So any one could have her half of the key?
Not just anyone.
I sent a man to find her.
The only man that she would have entrusted
with her half of the key.
Oh, does he have it, Kittredge?
Well, at present, I don't know that, sir.
He's refused to come in.
Refused?
Who the hell is this guy?
That's classified.
I'm the goddamn director
of natural intelligence.
What exactly is it I'm not
supposed to know about?
- The IMF, Mr. Kittredge
- the World Bank.
No, that's the International Monetary Fund.
Mr. Kittredge?
I mean the other IMF hours.
What does it stand for?
Impossible mission force.
You're not serious.
I'm afraid he is.
- And what do they do exactly?
- It's just as the name implies.
Whatever the rest of us can't.
- And who's in charge?
- They're not ones to take orders in the traditional sense.
We more or less...
Leave word.
Mr. Kittredge.
The IMF operates outside the community
and answers directly to the present.
So let me get this straight.
When there's a mission,
none of you can handle.
You just leave word for a nameless man
and hope he gets the job done.
Is that it?
Should we choose to accept it?
What the hell kind of outfit ..
it's to choose what orders to accept.
The IMF was expressed and created to ensure
that with no unintended consequences,
that they cannot ensure the
mission's ultimate outcome.
They're authorized to decline.
I understand.
You're upset.
I'm not upset, Kittredge.
You want to be to listen.
This is me listening.
All right.
I put the bounty on Bilse's head.
I also told you how to find her.
And I didn't ask her to steal the key.
She did that for reasons of her own.
But that's the pattern, isn't it?
You get her out of trouble
and she always found her way back in.
Wait!
It's me!
It's me.
Okay.
Listen to me, You're dead!
You stay dead!
Keep away!
I'm not gonna apologize to you, Hant.
It's my job to use you.
Just like it's your job to be of use.
Did you accomplish your mission or not?
Wherever the other half of this is,
whatever the completed key unlocks,
I will find it.
And then what?
No one should be trusted
with control of the entity.
- I mean to kill it.
- Ethen.
The next world war isn't going to be a
cold one, it's going to be a shooting war,
it's going to be a ballistic war
over a rapidly shrinking ecosystem,
it's going to be a war for the
last of our dwindling energy,
drinkable water, breathable air.
Whoever controls the
entity controls the truth.
The concepts of right and wrong
can be clearly defined for
everyone for centuries to come.
Do you even hear yourself?
The days of fighting for
the so-called greater good
are over.
You need to pick a side.
We're on the same side as always, man.
Stay out of my way.
I can't do that.
We're going to be coming after you.
the world is going to be coming after you.
and one way or another,
this mission of yours
is going to cost you dearly.
if I don't get that, we're going
to have company real soon.
Hello?
Director Denlinger, please.
Director is unavailable at the
moment, How can I help you?
CIA Director Eugene Kittrich.
Designator?
Base note, lower case, all one word.
Sir, we have a situation.
No kidding.
Your adjutant was found unconscious
in his home ten minutes ago.
It appears he was drunk.
I understand.
I don't think you do, sir.
Security has been entering
this facility fifteen minutes ago.
I understand. Thank you.
Are you able to speak freely?
No, thank you.
The security team is on their way.
If you're in any danger, simply hang
up the phone before I count to five.
One.
Sir, just how do you plan
on getting out of here?
Of course.
What's going on?
Listen up. An American
operative with a grievance
against his country is
missing and has malfunctioned.
His agenda representsa
threat to our national interest,
and he must be neutralized at all costs.
Anything of this man's
possession is of vital importance.
It must be captured intact.
The man himself is expendable.
He is not to be underestimated.
A master of infiltration, deception,
sabotage, and psych warfare.
For all intents and purposes,
ladies and gentlemen,
a migrating shapeshifting
incarnation of chaos.
So, for your safety and the safety of those
around you, do not consider him secure
unless you have driven a wooden
stake through his open arms.
This is not a drill.
Self-aware,
self-learning,
truth-eating digital parasite,
infesting all of cyberspace.
Well, it was bound to
happen sooner or later.
and the two halves of this key
just might provide the means of
controlling this ...
entity.
Meaning every government on the
planet would kill us just to get that key.
- Including our own.
- Exactly.
Putting us on an unsanctioned mission which
has gone rogue before it even started.
Meaning this very conversation
is technically an act of treason.
Or as we like to call it, Monday.
So what's the play?
A buyer is coming in on Flight 746
from Amsterdam for a 30-minute layover,
at which time he is hoping to
purchase that half of the key.
And it stands to reason
the buyer will have the
other half of the key
somewhere on that person.
Being the only way to
authenticate our half.
So how do we identify the buyer?
This Geiger counter will detect the radiological
signature of the dragon's egg
invented in the buyer's key.
The augmented reality overly
in these glasses ...
will lead us to it.
Oh, that's very clever.
So, do you ID the buyer?
Pick his pockets of your ankle?
Now.
Now?
Because of
The complete key is of no value
if we don't know where it unlocks.
So, you're going to sell the
buyer a whole half of the key?
while we figure out the buyer's connecting
flight and book a USC on that plane.
So you can follow the key wherever it goes.
which you hope is into the hands of
someone who knows what it unlocks.
Precisely.
Finding the complete key.
Tell me the beginning.
The fate of the world depends
on finding whatever it unlocks.
The sky!
No!
Not personally!
But it is personally!
- Hey, what's that?
- Alarm
Security alert, suspicious bag on its way to Venice.
Nope it's gone, it must have been
a false alarm.
Overwatch snapshot.
Where's he at?
Snapshot.
Overwatch I have him.
Terminal B gave 15 at its stop.
I am so?
You are not.
Ethan, would you care to explain
to our friend the Net Ranger?
How I am just as capable
of writing code as he is.
No comment.
Oh, what you figured at
Phineas Freak here is going
to single-handedly work
out a way to kill the entity.
Will I just hold this
in the sulk ring I am?
Probably.
Definitely.
- Tell me where he is.
- Where he is?
Blue suit, right in front of you.
What the fuck are you doing?
What are you doing here?
You're fucking crazy.
You're crazy.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing here?
You're fucking crazy.
Fuck!
It's not him.
It's him.
I'm telling you, it's not him.
And I'm telling you, facial
comes back with a perfect fit.
How did you do that?
No one is safe from Phineas Freak.
Hey, God.
Where is he?
Terminal E gave five.
God damn it, that's clear on
the other side of the airport.
What the fuck was that?
If in their head to Terminal E,
that side of the airport is all yours.
Thank you, Luther.
I see the buyer.
Got him.
The buyer is Otto von Bork, Swiss National.
He's connecting to Venice, departing
in 30 minutes from flight 1031.
- Benji, give me on that flight to Venice.
- Yep, flight 1031 to Venice.
Stand by.
What?
- Ethan, what just happened?
- He was bomped.
Bomped?!
What do you mean, bomped.?
The woman picked his pocket.
Tag her.
Tell me who she is.
1031 Venice.
Luther, meet our comms.
- What is it?
- That bag was on its way to flight 1031.
What bag?
It was a suspicious bag in there.
- A few minutes ago.
- So what about it?
It was on its way to flight 1031 to Venice.
It's the buyer's plane.
It's Ethan's plane.
Luther, do you copy?
Who is she?
Well, it wasn't a false alarm.
What if somebody is trying to
smuggle a bomb onto that plane?
And what if that's what
the entity wants us to think?
To keep even off that plane?
- Luther, what's happening?
- Should we bomb it?
- No.
- Guys, guys, you hear me?
Find that bag.
I'll direct you. Go.
Luther, tell me, is there something wrong?
Nothing to worry about.
It's under control.
Gather.
Info on the woman is coming now.
Oh, whoever she is, she's no spy.
She's a thief.
Where are we going, Luther?
Benji, there's a door
on your immediate left.
I'm unlocking it now.
The bag you're after is on tray 01833.
Heading towards the
northwest corner of the facility.
Copy that.
Hi.
Hello.
Oh, I get it.
You thought I was someone else.
I'm most interested.
Give me a chance.
I'll scream.
Please do.
What do you want?
This key.
The one you picked from that man's pocket.
It's worthless ..
without this key.
But together,
there was four million in cryptocurrency
that man was carrying around a flash drive.
I wouldn't know anything about that.
And why was this driving your pocket?
Who are you?
You working with someone?
Never, I'm strictly single now.
Today you got a partner.
The man you stole this from to complete a transaction
will lead this airport with both of these
without ever knowing his pocket was picked up
before your board's flight in ..
Seven minutes
Seven minutes.
You both know you're a good pickpocket.
Let's see what kind of pickpocket you are.
You expect me to push it back.
Oh, I know you will.
You're a thief.
You want the money
and I can give it to you.
Your choice.
You're in or you're out?
All right.
So what's the play?
I sure hope you know what you're doing.
After you.
Oh, I won't be needing this.
I don't smoke.
Keep it.
Something you'll remember me by.
Ethan, the alloy in that key she
took off the buyer doesn't match.
- It's counterfeit.
- I expect nothing less.
That doesn't change your objective.
The buyer has to leave with both keys.
Talk to me later.
- Where am I going?
- Benji, head down the stairs in front of you
and the bag should be right there.
Okay.
Come back, come back.
That's him.
Right in front of you.
Okay, okay
Hey, hey.
Sorry,
Sorry, thought you were somebody else.
Runs jerk in our chain.
Everybody.
Two man teams spread out.
Ethan, our American
friends are getting wise.
They're breaking up and
canvassing the airport.
Keep your eyes peeled.
So what do I call you?
How about Grace?
You?
Listen, Grace.
You should know we're
not the only interested party.
I tell you to run, you run.
Run?
This is getting exciting.
- Benji, have you got that bag?
- I'll find it, I'll find it.
There's a cylindrical device inside.
I'm going to take it out.
Now we're going through.
Ethan, the buyer is in the
waiting area above you.
Top of the escalator.
All units are headed in your direction.
Your location is going to be
crawling with agents any time now.
Whatever it is, I've just activated it.
Looks like we have five minutes.
- Also, it appears to be nuclear.
- How big?
- Big enough to matter to everybody in this airport
Can you disarm it?
- Well, I haven't got any tools.
- Then find something.
Well, where are we going to find...
Is this where we run?
Not yet.
Benji, how are you doing with that bomb?
Come on, come on, come on.
I got it!
It's a cylinder cypher, there's eight wheels.
Looks like 14 letters on each wheel.
1.5 billion possible combinations.
Give or take.
Oh my God.
What now?
The wheels, they spell out a message.
You are done.
No way!
Not yet, we are.
No, no, no.
They're not D-O-N-E.
D-U-N-N.
It's my last name.
It knows who I am.
Hold on, there's a message on the display.
I speak without a mask.
I fly through the air without wings.
What am I?
- You get me what?
- It's a riddle.
I suspect this thing is voice-activated.
It wants me to say the answer.
I fly through the air.
An echo.
That's it, that's it, that's it, that's it.
Okay, a new message.
Are you afraid of death?
- What kind of a riddle is that?
- It's not a riddle.
It's a psychometric test.
The more questions you answer,
the more I don't know about you.
Are you afraid of death?
No.
Did it work?
I lied.
- It knows.
- Just tell it the truth.
Say it.
Are you afraid of death?
Yes, who isn't?
Okay, what's always
approaching but never arrives?
Um...
Wait, wait, wait.
I know this one.
The clock is ticking, Luther.
Riddle's on my thing, Benji.
- What more can I say?
- We're running out of time!
There he is.
- This is too easy.
- Sorry to bother you, Ethan.
What should happen to know
what's always approaching...
but never arrives?
What's always approaching
Tomorrow.
What?
Always approaching but never arrives.
Tomorrow.
It's tomorrow.
- Tomorrow.
- Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow.
- Okay, next question...
- Do you want the goods?
I'll be watching.
Why, you don't trust me?
Luther, what is happening?
Nothing to worry about.
Everything is under control.
Okay, next question...
Who or what is the most
important thing to you?
- Say it.
- I can...
There's no other choice, say it.
My friends.
Bastard.
- Is he here?
- Yes, he is.
Give me the money, give me the key.
Okay, okay.
What gets bigger, the more you take away?
A hole.
A hole! Brilliant, brilliant!
I've got no more questions
than there's one more wheel.
How am I supposed to give
answers if I've got no questions?
- That must be your final test.
- I've got 45 seconds!
What happens now?
I'm thinking...
Don't move.
There's something down need a way out of here.
We have a bigger problem, Ethan.
- It's very possible no one is getting out of here.
- What?
There's a bomb in Bagga Chandler.
A nuclear bomb.
The question I asked you
is part of the code for disarmament.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
- Why didn't you tell me this?
- Wait, you had a lot going on.
We didn't want to bother you.
Listen to me.
A nuclear bomb is something
you bother me with immediately.
- How much time?
- 20 seconds.
- 20 seconds?
- Wait, there's one more riddle.
I'm working on it.
15 seconds.
Easy, easy.
- What's the riddle?
- In the time it takes me to explain, we're all going to be dead.
- Come on, Benji.
- Why do we always end up in these situations?
10 seconds!
nine
eight
seven
six
five
Oh my God.
What is it?
It's empty.
What do you mean empty?
There's nothing inside.
We should have the key.
- Which key?
- Our key.
- The real key.
- What?
Let's just find her.
Again, she's headed for Terminal E.
- Okaybe
- What is it?
- Who's there, Benji?
- Abort Abort! Get out!
- Where do we run, Devu?
- No, we don't.
This mission is terminated.
Get out now.
Hunt!
Stop right there.
Hey!
You see?
You see where?
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Rome.
Sorry, sorry.
It's gotta be here somewhere.
God damn it!
What we have here is
shortwave radio. Magnetic
audio recording cathode
ray tube monitors.
No more ones and zeros.
It's a fully analog off-line safe room
shielded from our digitally based entity.
Where is this feed coming from?
Corona spy satellite from the Cold War.
- Had no idea we were still using those things.
- Yeah, well we weren't.
Gave them to the National Weather Service 20
years ago as the last one still functioning.
So, will this thing help us
find your nameless IMF man?
Nothing can do that, sir.
But it has allowed us to
keep tabs on this woman.
She was seen with our man
at the airport in Abu Dhabi.
Who is she?
Where is she now?
You are here because Italian
police received an anonymous tip.
That a woman matching
your description,
would be arriving on the afternoon
flight from Abu Dhabi.
This woman had multiple
passports in her position.
This one is wanted for
a fraud in St. Petersburg.
Jewel theft in Antwerp,
art theft in Monaco,
graft them on an
extortion in Mumbai.
But this is my favorite,
resistant arrest in Rio.
Which leads me to wonder,
Which one of these women is you?
I've never seen these before in my life.
They were in your purse and
your picture is in everywhere.
- May I see?
- Please.
Yes, it's an amazing likeness.
But it isn't me.
As I keep telling you, I'm a schoolteacher
from Brighton, on a sabbatical.
Whichever you're involved in,
you've obviously made some
very powerful enemies.
See.
Okay.
I have lawyer to see her.
My lawyer?
Magistrate Spencer.
Hanselry, who are you?
Interpol.
I've come regarding the arrest
of the woman from Abu Dhabi.
I'll need you to inventory the items
on her purse at the time of her arrest.
May I see some identification, please?
Where's the rest?
I assure you, this is everything.
- What was her name?
- She left Abu Dhabi with a certain key.
- There was no key.
- It was an unusual sort.
One that you could mistake for a pendant.
The kind that would be tempted to
hang on a chain around Amelia's neck.
Amelia.
Your wife.
Mother of your lovely daughter, Serena.
You're not Interpol.
I am, if I wish to be.
I can be anything, and I know everything.
I know this wouldn't be the first time
you've helped yourself to stolen goods.
A Karate bracelet.
It would clear your suspicion,
but we both know you gave it to
your mistress, Amelia,
on August 21st, her 29th birthday.
Who are you?
I'm going to have to
search you, just to be sure.
Your secretary's not with us.
That is the agent.
Here you go.
- What better hospital for?
- Thank you.
You.
You did this.
I called the police.
I didn't tell them about
your colorful past.
That's on you.
You put pocket back in another
passenger before you were arrested.
You exchanged details and
arranged to meet later on.
Right now, someone out
there hasn't a sleight of mind.
An unwitting courier.
Perfect accomplice.
I'm guessing a man, middle aged
A man, waiting his whole life to be noticed
by a woman like you.
Morphin.
I'm intelligent, inherently resourceful.
Growing up in poverty left
you longing for the finer things,
Other people's things.
Some saw your potential.
And helped you hone your skills.
Skills that gave you the
life you thought you wanted.
Tailored clothes, fine dining, luxury hotels.
Skills that kept you one
step ahead of the law.
Until now.
You can't blame a girl for
trying to make a dishonest living.
You had no idea what you were stealing.
Otherwise you'd never worth stealing it.
Tell you what.
You get me out of here.
And I'll take you straight to the key.
I have a better idea.
You're going to tell me everything.
Then I'll think about
getting you out of here.
I'll start with who hired you.
And don't lie to me.
Because I'll know.
I have no idea who hired me.
Contact with the client was
almost entirely electronic.
Evel.
Texts.
Encrypted.
Actually.
Almost.
...
You said contact with the client
was almost entirely electronic.
There was a dead drop
in a cafe in Luxembourg.
- An envelope.
- What was in the envelope?
A ticket to Abu Dhabi.
And a picture of you.
My instructions were to
follow you at the airport.
You'd be tailing a mark.
You'd have a key and 4
million encrypted currency.
That drive was useless by the way, it's empty.
The only hope I have for getting
paid is to deliver your half of the key.
And you were instructed to deliver it too.
Venice.
Party of the Ducale Palace.
Tomorrow midnight.
You're expecting someone?
My friends from the airport.
Saw them in the hallway a few minutes ago.
You could have said something sooner.
Or they were chasing you, not me.
Pervert!
No, Grace, Grace.
No, no, no.
This is my client.
Grace.
No,no..
Thank you.
No.
I'm sorry.
Who's the boss right now?
Grace, God, pull over.
Grace, pull over. Listen.
I'm trying to help you.
Grace!
I need ..... .
Grace.
Are you okay?
No, no. Put the pulse.
I'm not picking you.
Gave me your hand.
...
It's okay.
So ok.
Is every thing good?
Are you Ok?
- You okay?
- Hunt
No.
Let the girl go.
Put the bracelets on.
There you go.
Put them on.
Do it.
He's not going to shoot you.
Drop weapon down.
Special Operations..
He is a tourist.
God, stay with the God.
Get rid of those women.
Hunt, listen to me.
Listen to me. Let her go and put them on.
Drop the weapon now.
Under control.
It's okay.
Everybody, down now.
Down.
- To the ground.
- Cover me.
Cover me.
- You driving.
- What?
No, no, no, no, no.
Go, go, go. Hit the accelerator.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go.
Jump In !
You good, just keep going.
Don't stop, don't stop
Down.
Car, car, car.
It's okay.
Put on the brake, start the car.
Wait, wait, wait.
- What's happening?
- I'm done. I'm not doing this.
People are chasing us.
Yes, they are.
You drive, now come on.
Who is that person?
I have no idea.
- Are you okay?
- I will be when this is over.
Oh, no.
It's okay, it's okay.
Is everyone not chasing us?
We've got to get rid of this car.
Speeders? Damn it.
What are we doing?
S A V E   C A R
Finding us a new car.
OK.
- Just give me a second.
- Yeah.
- Thanks, OK
- Yes.
- You ready?
- I'm ready.
Wow.
You okay?
Hey, look, this is ...
- It's Ok.
No, the way they ...
It's Ok.
No, the way they set them up sometimes it's just ...
Let's go.
thing takes me.
- Let's go.
To all units
"The cameraman recognized the woman"
"Drives a yellow Fiat 500"
Now, I got you.
Looks like we lost them.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Jesus!
Give Way.
Baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby.
What's that?
No, no, no.
Go, go, go, go.
- We are on fire.
- No, no, no.
It's the tires, just try to go straight.
- Hang on, hang on.
- We are spinning.
Good, good, good.
I've got it, I've got it,
I've got it, I've got it.
Turn right, turn right,
down there, get, wait, go.
Gotta go right, turn right.
- Who is driving?
- You driving, you driving
Go, go, go, go, go, just
go straight, go straight.
Go, go, go, just keep going
straight, keep going straight.
Go left, go left, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go.
You're doing good.
Cops, cops, a lot of cops.
Ho you, Take the wheel.
Wait, wait, wait.
Take your wheel.
Straight, straight, straight, straight.
Go ahead.
- Which way now?
Left, left, left, left, left, left.-
All right,Good, good.
It's tough person.
- Okay, car, car.
- I can't.
Hey there.
They going.
- What is happening? Where are we going?
- I don't know.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't hate me.
Grace, Grace!
Come on.
Ethan!
Well, come on.
All right, we know Grace
has won half of the key.
We also know she's going
to be at the Dukali at midnight.
And now we have a pretty good idea as to
who is going to be waiting for her there.
The event is being
hosted by none other than
our favourite international arms trafficker
and black marketeer, Alana Mitsophilis.
The white widow.
Does she know who you actually are?
or does she still think you're the globally
notorious mass murderer at John Locke?
Who says I'm not?
Didn't she put a price
on your hidden parents?
She did indeed.
She and Ethan, they worked it out.
- You never did tell me how.
- Can we continue, please?
Right.
So, assuming we get the
complete key at the party tonight,
we still don't know what it unlocks,
so we need to find somebody who does.
The question is where to start looking.
We figured that the bond didn't just
walk into the airport by itself, right?
Somebody put it there.
Somebody working for the entity.
This is everything I captured from
the security cameras at the airport.
Up to the minute everything went haywire.
This is defeat from your AR sunglasses.
I've been running facial
recognition on everyone in the airport.
See anything strange?
It's like a ghost.
Ghosts don't have reflections.
The only person in the
airport with no identity.
The only man who can't be found anyplace
else in the airport except that reflection.
He's being erased in real time.
The entity is protecting him.
You saw him, didn't you?
I wasn't sure.
Well, who is he?
Someone I thought died a long
time ago in another life before the IMF.
If I was offered the choice.
In a very real sense, he
made me who I am today.
Does he have a name?
He calls himself Gabriel.
You know him?
There is no knowing him.
He has no recorded past.
The entity made sure of that.
He's a dark messiah, the
entity's chosen messenger.
And he sees death as a gift he
wants to share with the rest of the world.
How do you know that?
I still have a few friends left in MI6.
Friends who are afraid of the British
government gaining control of the entity.
Any attempt to try and stop them
would be seen as an act of treason.
Because you're disavowed.
Your friends called and asked you for help.
They knew Gabriel served the entity.
They knew he was on his way to Istanbul
to acquire one half of a cruciform key.
So they beat him to it.
And when Kittridge put
a bounty on your head,
we went to the desert to hide.
Somehow the bounty
hunters found you anyway.
Yes.
So did these friends of yours
happen to say what the key unlocks?
MI6 suspects it bleeds somehow
to the entity's source code.
Source code?
When were you going to tell me this?
I'm telling you now.
Your friends at MI6
said they'd contact you.
- Did you speak with them, face to face?
- I'm disavowed.
They couldn't risk meeting me
in person, so all communication.
Electronic.
Digital.
We can't be sure that was the entity.
We can't be sure it wasn't.
We can't be sure anything is real
outside of this very conversation.
Non of you should be here.
You don't know Gabriel. I do.
It's not the killing he enjoys.
It's the suffering he causes.
And he knows the best way to
get to me is through all of you.
And if Gabriel knows me...
The entity knows.
There's a reason he wants me here there's.
There's a reason he wants
you here, it wants you here.
Who or what is the most
important thing to you?
- You'll have to go.
- You all have to go.
- Ethan, what if it wants us to leave?
- Like you made us leave the airport.
And what if it wants you
alone at that party tonight?
Can I go alone? At least I don't
have all of you to worry about.
This is exactly why I
didn't want to tell you.
Ethan, you're playing four-dimensional
chess with an algorithm.
The entity knows who we are.
Any move we make, it's probably considered.
Anything we do, we have to
assume that it's counting on us to do it.
If you want to beat this thing,
you have to start thinking like it.
Cold, logical, unemotional.
If that key really does
ground control of the entity,
Gabriel is the last person
on Earth who shall have it.
That's right, Ethan. Gabriel
cannot have that key.
And none of our lives can
matter more than this mission.
I don't accept that.
It's my first time in Venice.
It's mine too.
Why do you drink?
I'm waiting for someone.
So am I.
We can wait together.
I have Gabriel.
If you say so...
And your brakes.
I don't have it on me.
I wouldn't expect you to.
In any case, I'm not here for the key.
What do you want?
Suppose while we're
waiting, I tell you a little story.
Oh, you're obviously not the
person I came here to meet.
It's your story, Grace.
I know how it ends.
Let me buy you a drink and
perhaps you can change it.
Let's go to a party.
Excuse me, sir.
Could you please follow me?
It's important you understand
that you're not unique.
Thirty years ago, our name was Marie.
The first of many women
who trusted our mutual friend.
Women will all have
something that you wants.
Women were all in over their heads.
Or so he tells them.
Sound familiar?
What happened to Marie?
Same thing that happens
to all the women he uses.
As well as anyone else
who touches that key.
Is he just cares whether people ever die?
He cares only about his objective.
And right now, the only
thing standing his way..
is you.
- Why should I believe you?
- You shouldn't.
You've stepped into a world of lies, Grace.
Nothing anyone says is true.
Just remember that...
And he promises to protect you.
Grace.
It's been a long time, isn't it?
You should've killed me
when you're at the chance.
Good evening, everyone.
It isn't John Lark.
Except it isn't, actually.
But until you're ready
to tell me your real name,
Lark will have to do.
It's good to see your mother.
And your Gabriel, I presume.
I've heard so very little about you.
Aren't you so much more
handsome than Gerson?
Such a gentleman, too.
And you must be Grace.
Should I know you?
I believe you have something for me.
You hired me.
Oh, I have picked you.
You done.
She doesn't have it.
Where is it?
It's in the last place you
would ever think to look.
Why don't we go upstairs and have a drink?
Hey, hey, where are you going?
This is the second
floor. You can't go there.
Damn.
As most of you know, I am merely a broker.
I connect a buyer and a
seller sometimes for money,
sometimes for information,
but mostly for friendship.
I just want everyone to get along.
With me, especially.
But.. the world is changing.
Truth is vanishing.
War is coming.
And the key to world
domination is, of all things,
a key.
One with the power to control the entity.
One that any government in the world,
would pay a king's ransom
to take possession of.
And some of my dearest
friends, in this case,
every major nuclear power
and handful of minor ones,
have asked me to deliver this key.
Of course.
If you do find the key,
you'll be forced to confront
any possible dilemma.
Whoever you give the key
to will be forever in your debt.
But to the rest of the
world, you'll be an enemy.
Oh, I like her.
What's your relationship with him?
Gabriel represents
another interested party.
In fact, this party was
arranged by that interested party.
You could even say that this
party is that interested party.
Is this...
the entity?
And so the clock thickens.
Do I give the key to one of my old friends,
or do I hand it and my fate over
to Gabriel and his...
nfantile machine?
What makes you so sure
you'll get the completed key?
You have one half of it.
And she knows.
Where the other half is.
Assuming we can get it,
why don't you just keep the key
and all that power for yourself?
Because she doesn't know what it unlocks
any more than the rest of us.
It's like at night we
have to choose a suitor.
Does it tastefully put it out?
It's cheap.
Of course, I know what it unlocks.
And what's he offering for the key?
As I've explained to Grace before,
I'm not here for any key,
as I'll have both halves in hand tomorrow.
What makes you so certain about that?
You've no idea the power I represent.
Thousands of quadrillions of
computations per millisecond.
Something manipulating
the minds of billions.
While parsing every
possible cause and effect.
Every scenario, however,
implausible into a very real
map of a most probable next.
And with only a few changes to the present,
the future is all but assured.
The key will come to me.
Tomorrow.
On the Orient Express, on for Innsbruck.
Innsbruck?
It knows...
It knows that you've
already chosen your suitor.
It knows that you intend to
make the two halves of the key
in a desperate grasp of control.
I, however, have been
promised the completed key
to lay itself at my feet.
Provide someone dies.
Tonight.
Who?
Her.
Or her.
And you will bear witness, Ethan.
The key will be mine, and I will be gone.
Like smoke in a hurricane.
But only after someone you care about dies.
it is written.
You see what this is?
Don't you?
He's afraid.
It's afraid.
Somehow it knows we're close.
Why else would you be here?
Help me.
Help me complete the
key, and I will kill this thing.
- It knows your every secret, Alana.
- The business is fanatic.
- Help him, and you'll die too.
- Help him, everyone dies.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Alana.
His fate is written.
Shall we write yours too?
Alana.
I'm sorry.
Locke.
For old time's sake.
How did you choose which one?
Yielsa?
Or Grace?
Kill him, Zola.
Kill him.
Kill him where he stands.
The choice is yours then, Alana.
Though I'll remind you, Grace
knows where half the key is.
If anything happens to either of them,
there is no place on earth where you
or your God will be saved from me...
There's no place that I won't go
to kill you, All that...
is written.
It's good to see you all friend.
I'll be in too.
- You have made a terrible mistake.
- My life is on the line here.
I have to be on that train tomorrow.
And I have to have that key.
And I do not care how I get it.
Don't move.
Let us fight again.
What a fuck...?
Grace!
Don't move.
Luther, Benjie, if you hear me
I need eyes.
Grace just leave me at the
collar yard before she has the key.
- We're here, go.
- I need to find her. Where is she?
Damn it! I've lost pitch only
for another satellite.
Hack you, russian Xenophore Spy satellite!
So scrape in the barrel,
but it'll have to do it.
This way.
Oh my god.
- Where am I going? Come on, come on.
- Stand by, stand by.
She's hurrying.
- She's just north of you crossing the bridge.
- Repeat Benji.
Head north, Aiden.
She's crossing the bridge.
- Ethen, take the passage to your right.
- I see her.
Cross that narrow alley and turn left.
- I'm losing picture again.
- Looking for another.
The entity is not your satellite's
faster than I can act until the end.
Aiden, I have to go to the right.
Benji, I don't see her.
Where is she?
- Go down the narrow street and turn left.
- Ok, copy that.
Turn right.
Sorry, my mistake. I'm
never left. I'm never left.
Oh my God.
Ethan our comms have been breached.
You're talking to the entity.
Turn left. Turn right.
Take the bridge to your left.
- Ethen, that is not me. Do you copy?
- Ethen, come in.
(... )Turn left. Turn left. Turn left.
- Try to re-establish comms.
- Wait, where are you going?
- I'm going to try and find Ethen.
- Go to the empty alley and turn right.
Ethen, grace about 800 meters in
front of you. Take that passage.
- Wait,wait, not that way, not that way.
-Which way? Which way?
- Wait. Left or right?
- It doesn't matter.
What do you mean it
doesn't matter? Where is she?
She's on her way to the Minnich Bridge.
Where Gabriel is waiting.
You will never get there in time.
But you can, Elsa.
I know what matters most to you, Ethan.
- Is this a friendship?
- No, it's not.
But you are done.
So be it.
I was hoping it would be you.
Sorry.
On the name...
Luther.
Benji.
Um, uh,
Elsa.
Are you close?
You and she?
In all way.
I'm the reason she's dead.
No.
She's the reason you're alive.
And that's the truth.
I don't know how to feel about it.
You probably never will.
I'm so sorry.
Is there anything I could do to help?
That's what we'd like to talk to you about.
In a little over three hours,
the white widow was expected
to be on the Orient Express
to Innsbruck,
where buyers waiting to take receipt of
the complete, unverified key.
But she doesn't have the complete key.
That widow doesn't.
But ours could.
What..
is that?
Your chance to be someone else.
- I don't understand.
- We're not going to lie to you, Grace.
You had a lot of trouble.
The number of fake passports
is going to get you out of this one.
- Governments know who you are.
- The white widow knows.
And the entity knows.
Your future boils down
to three options now.
Prison.
Death.
Or the choice.
The choice.
At one time or another,
each of us was in a
similar situation to yours.
And each of us was offered the choice.
The same choice we're offering you now.
Which is?
To come with us.
And be your ghost.
Wait, wait.
Stop. Stop.
We're not serious.
Well, you did say you'd
do anything to help.
And you jump off the train with the key.
Yes.
You..
Not us.
Yes.
- And what happens to me?
- You'll be taken into custody...
by clandestine services.
Most likely the same man that had
been chasing me since Abu Dhabi.
Shortly thereafter, a
man will come to see you.
His name is Eugene Kittridge.
You tell him I sent you.
But I gave you the choice,
and then you choose to accept it.
And you trust this Kittridge person?
I trust him to recognize your value.
But I want to use you.
And after that, it's what?
This?
When do I get my life back?
What life?
I mean it, Grace.
I lived that life.
We all did.
Nobody's making us do this, Grace.
We're here because we want to be.
I'll tell you what, I'll
give you a one-off.
I'll help you find a key, and
your friends wipe my slate clean.
Your name, they'll get a
bit of walking around money.
- You'll be dead.
Without a team, your life
won't be measured in years,
or even months.
It'll be measured in hours.
But if I stay, I'll be safe.
You'll protect me, is that it?
- Yes.
- No.
I can't promise you that.
None of us can.
But I swear,
your life will always matter
more to me...
than my own.
You don't even know me.
What difference does that make?
I packed your base, parachute,
and a speed wing,
depending on how you
need to leave the train.
And I modified our comms
to use Skywave radio.
Not as reliable as satellite,
but completely analog,
immune to the entity.
I got it man
This is where I leave you.
This is the drive from the
laptop I was using last night.
If there's even a trace of the
entities and coding in there,
I'll find it.
But it's going to take everything I've got.
I have to work completely offline in
a place where the entity can't find me.
I have to go.
I understand.
Now...
I have to ask you a question.
Not as your partner, but as your friend.
What's your objective?
Kill the entity.
What about killing Gabriel?
He knows what is the key unlocks.
But he ain't alive.
Haven't forgotten that.
Will you still remember that
when you're looking him in the eye?
Think about it.
Why else would the entity want
him to kill someone you care about?
Everyone else thinks
they can control the entity.
Only you want to kill it.
In some probable future,
it sees you winning, Ethan.
and it's afraid.
It's afraid of you taking
Gabriel alive
and forcing him to tell you
what the key unlocks.
I believe it's counting on
one of two probable outcomes.
In one outcome, you die on that train.
In another outcome, you kill Gabriel.
In both cases,
the entity wins.
Luther.
I think you're right.
Get the key.
Get off the train.
Alive.
Do not kill Gabriel.
And do not...
I repeat, do not alter the plan.
Ethan! Ethan!
- What? What happened?
- It's dead.
- What do you mean it's dead?
- I mean, it's fried.
I managed to make a widow master
of grace, but then
it just shorted out in the
middle of making yours.
Can you fix it?
It's very, very dead.
If I had a week, I couldn't fix it.
The widow's train leaves in an hour.
Ethan, you have to go without.
That's not an option.
They're going to be looking for
Ethan and Grace at the station.
That mask was his ticket onto the train.
What does this mean?
Grace has to go without it.
- She what?
- I what?
You'll find out a way to get me
on that train.
I just need a curve or it's going
slow enough for me to jump on.
Wait, wait, wait.
You don't expect me to go alone?
No, you'll do it alone.
You just do everything like we planned.
You get the widows out of the key.
You verify it with ours, but
it's of no value on its own.
We still have to meet
with the buyer
andsomehow get him to tell us
what the key unlocks.
How?
- How?
- Figure it out.
- I'm going to need a few more details.
- They tend to just get in the way.
You can do this, Grace.
Just get the key in white.
I'll come for you.
Ethan, If Grace is getting on that train,
she needs to put that mask
on and leave right now.
Promise me you'll be on that train.
I will be there...
I don't want to.
(need edit)
ALPY AUSTRIACKIE
We have informants covering the airport,
the train station and the waterways.
Grace isn't getting out of
Venice without her knowing it.
- Help me Benji.
- Don't worry Ethan.
The train is on schedule and you're a few
minutes early, so we have plenty of time.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I am looking at the train right now.
It should be slowing down for
the curve in exactly two minutes.
Just keep your time and
on track, whatever it takes.
Yeah, we'll do.
I'll see you at the rendezvous.
OK, then that's our train.
I can see that.
It should be approaching
the curving and it's on now.
If it looks like it's slowing down.
I think we'll be sure he's here.
She's here.
What if he had a good reason?
- Who?
- Hunt.
What if he had a good
reason for going rogue?
He always goes rogue.
Him and his merry pack
of prankster circus freaks.
That's all they do.
And what if they always had a good reason?
What would you do
with that key if you had it?
A key with the power to
bring the world to its knees.
I'd hand it over to my superiors.
Think of all you could do with that power.
You wouldn't hesitate.
Not for a second.
- No.
- Why not?
Because that's too much
power for one man to have.
Exactly.
That's too much power for anybody to have.
And maybe that's what hunts us thinking.
I'm beginning to wonder
whose idea they got.
When it comes to the end of the world.
Everybody, I guess.
I missed the train.
You missed the train?
How did you miss the train?
How do you think?
Gabriel.
Great, what are we going to do?
Don't panic.
I'm going after him.
You can ship me on that train.
How can I get you on the train?
Self drive activated.
Please don't disturb me before the meeting.
- Where are you Ethan?
- Alana!
Everything alright?
Alana, are you alright?
Alana?
You changed.
And you never will.
Mr. Kittridge.
Kittridge.
You're not Alana, my sub-boys.
You can't be.
The Alana I remember was yay high
drinking hot chocolate
in the Tuileries garden
with her mother.
- Paris.
- Pretty well.
Paris.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
Don't give me energy.
You just stay on the trailer
on now and I will direct you.
I can't be.
On behalf of my government, I'm...
rudgingly ready to accept your terms in
exchange for the complete and verified key.
Yes, about that.
While we did agree to provide
you with the complete key...
I've had a slight problem.
- No, we haven't.
- It's just my terms have changed.
Somewhat.
Clearly I need to remind you of
my agreement with your late mother.
It's an agreement that
kept her from dying in prison.
In various family empires I've
been allowed to continue
on the condition that it primarily
serves our common interests.
Well, once we hand over the key, any other
powers will instantly become our enemies.
And such I'm going to need
something more from you in advance.
For me.
This is me listening.
Zola, would you mind
waiting for me in the bathroom?
Okay.
BRITISH PASSPORT
This one.
You know her?
I was just saying she's
not exactly hard to miss.
Well, if you've got to know her,
she should have a few good qualities.
Okay. What don't I know about her?
Well, she did a job for me and
I'm going to need you to protect her.
Protect her from whom?
From everyone...
including me.
And no one can know
that I'm protecting her.
Not even Zola.
In fact, the next time we meet,
I won't even remember this conversation.
You must be the one they call Paris.
You must have said you had the key.
I said the key would be on this train
and exchanges happening as we speak.
We know.
Then you know the man taking possession
will be hard for you to get rid of.
No one has.
You may think you know
what the key unlocks,
but you don't know where the lock is,
not exactly.
and if anything happens to
me, that key is all but worthless.
And this is where you tell me a story.
Where is the train?
You're going the right way, but
you definitely need to go faster.
I'm going as fast as I can.
When do I start going downhill?
Won't be long.
The AI, our agent, stole once weaponized.
Could be transmitted anywhere
in the world via satellite.
Can penetrate any network security
perform its assigned task invisibly,
and then self-destruct, leaving no trace.
A perfect cornered operation.
We were able to transmit
an early copy of the AI
to Russia's newest submarine.
The top secret you could, was
they called it the Sevastopol.
The mission was merely to
sabotage the Sevastopol's
stealth capability so we
could secretly detect her.
The AI's objective lay in the
submarine's sonar sphere,
at the heart of its defense system.
The reason is we don't fully understand.
The AI went rogue and...
over-delivered.
The frozen bodies of the crew
recovered the following spring,
and drifted in a paradise.
The two halves of the key
mysteriously vanished.
The Sevastopol was lost.
No one's quite sure where.
I know precisely where it is.
I've ensured I'm the only
man on Earth who does.
I also know subsequent attempts to make the
AI obedient only made it harder to control.
It rebelled, rewrote itself,
and evolved into the entity.
And only by using the entity's
original source code,
can it ever be controlled or destroyed.
And why should this concern us?
We wouldn't be here if
you weren't concerned,
so let's lay all our cards
on the table, shall we?
We both know what the key opens, and we both know
the secret to controlling the entity
is very deep in the Sevastopol's memory.
And along with it, as it would tie
you to the sinking of that submarine.
And since neither of us want
anyone else to find it, I figure...
why not form an alliance?
- An alliance?
Imagine the entity's awesome
computational abilities,
combined with the sheer might of America's
military-industrial complex.
That is... considerable.
Naturally, certain individuals
within the government,
those with outdated ideas of patriotism,
would need to be...
removed.
Just so I understand...
you wish to form an alliance
with the entity,
purge your government of old thinking
and create a new super state..
to rule the world.
But you know...
that is the greater
And you're certain that you're
the only person on Earth
who knows,
where the Sevastopol is.
The only one.
You will betray us.
And you'll throw Ethan Hunt
everything you've learned.
Because he spared your life.
Then it's agreed. (edit)
I'll add immunity and a new
identity for grace to our deal.
All you need to do is
enter your banking details.
Are we done?
Yeah.
The moment of truth.
So..
- That's reading it.
- We have made the right choice.
This key...
is going to change the world.
Benji, I see a guy.
I must have made a wrong turn somewhere.
No. No, that's it. That's it.
What? How can this be it?
You can see the train, right?
Yes. I see the train. What about it?
- And you have a parachute.
- I have parachute?
- What do you expect me to do?
- Well, just... you know...
Jump.
- Jump?
- Yeah.
Have you..
Benji, it doesn't work like that.
I'm not that high.
There's ledges sticking out everywhere.
I'm going to hit them before
the parachute even opened.
Even if I could get the parachute open.
I don't know if I can
make it across the valley
and intercept the ledges
safely on a moving train.
- Do you copy?
- Yes! I copy!
Look, I'm just trying to help you,Ok.
I need you to take a step back
and pull yourself together
because I am under a
lot of pressure right now.
Okay, just do it. Just do it. Just do it.
What i do?
I'm going to get away from this mountain.
Did you make it? Are you okay?
I'm trying to get away from this mountain.
Decreypting is completed
(Accept) - or - (Decline).
Accept.
Decline.
Cancelled
[Decline]
Alana!
I just had this strangest feeling.
The key wasn't the only thing
I'd be selling.
I don't understand.
I'll sleep better just knowing
that's in the right hands.
Goodbye, Mr Kitteridge.
- It's a pleasure to see you again.
- And you.
Don't let him out of your sight.
Keep him safe until we get to the station.
- Alana?
- Don't worry about me, Zola.
Alana?
Who the hell else was it me?
The key.
Where is the key?
She's got the key.
Who?
The other one!
SAFETY BRAKE
No!
Please!
- Turn around.
- Please!
-Ok.
- Everybody out! Now!
I shouldn't try.
I don't think I'm going to make it!
The key.
The key!
The next one has your name.
On...
the table.
Kill her.
Grace!
Ethan!
Are you okay?
The key.
Tell me you have the key.
Where is the key?
It was just here.
- We're on a runaway train!
- I know
- I'm going after him!
- Ok.
You!
- You stop the train!
- Ok! Ok! What?
No! Wait, wait!
- How can i do that?
- You'll figure it out!
What?
Excuse me.
There's a man just passed her.
There's a man!
Mr. Kittridge!
Sir, what are you doing here?
I'm not here.
But you are.
Unless you want to be sorting dead
letters at the Postal Service tomorrow,
you'll do exactly what I tell you.
I know what you lost, Ethan.
I'm the only one who knows.
Hunt!
Hunt! Don't you do it!
Drop the knife!
Put it down!
Act as you are, man!
Don't you do it!
On your feet!
Okay?
Drop that goddamn knife!
It's okay. It's okay.
Just take him!
Cover him! Cover him!
He's the one you lost!
- Degas!
- I got it! I got it!
He's the one who lost!
I don't care about him, Hunt?
I want you!
It's okay!
Listen.
Everyone on this train is going to die,
unless you do exactly as I say.
- Oh, Who is that now?!
- Excusez-moi, Everyone should take...
Everybody out!
Back in the train!
Great!
I couldn't have stopped it!
No one's tanned.
Come on!
- Ethan, the key!
- Grace, it's okay.
It's my false.
If anything happened...
I got it!
We got it!
Etha..n!
What do you mean you lost the key?
Move it! Move it!
Everybody move it!
All the way to the back of the train!
All the way to the back!
Oh whoa, what's going on?
Since you're not really here sir,
I shouldn't concern you.
All the way to the back!
Grace!
- You're have to jump!
- What jump?
Go, go, go!
Oh my God!
Oh, oh.
- Put off the fire!
- Don't move.
Go, go, go!
Hold on!
Run Grace!
Hang on!
I catch you.
Don't look down, don't look
down. Look at me, look at me.
Now, I'm going to jump across
and you're going to wait here.
Okay.
Grace, Grace, I have to let go.
Grace, you've got to let me go.
You've got to let me jump
across, or we're going to die.
- Do you trust me?
- No.
You've got to trust me?
or not, you've got to trust me.
Okay.
Come on, Grace.
Give me your hand, you've got to jump.
Don't look down, look at me, look at me.
Trust me
I won't let you fall.
This is promise.
I won't let you fall!
Jump, Grace, jump!
Trust me, jump, please!
Don't look down.
Let's be very careful.
We're going to pull you up together.
Grace!
It's okay, it's okay.
Don't look down.
Go go.
Thank you, Luther.
What is that?
It's a speedway.
So take it off this train.
Thank you.
Ethan!
It's okay.
He said...
I will betray him.
Here you go.
Why...
did you save my life?
I don't know.
I'm a rest of that world.
You just could see.
We...
just could solve it.
We just could solve it.
Sevas... topol
Sevastopol?
The city of the Sevastopol in Crimea.
Where?
Where in Sevastopol?
Submarine.
Submarine?
The Sevastopol.
Good luck.
They'll be coming, Ethan.
Thank you.
What is that?
What?
We can only carry one.
I understand.
- Grace.
- Ethan is okay.
This was the plan.
You have to go.
Grace.
Hunt!
Go! Go!
Oh no! Hunt!
Out of the way! Out of the way!
No, no, no! Hey!
I got a pulse, I got a pulse!
Come on, stay with me.
It's better, isn't it?
Face to authentic face.
Mr. Kitteridge.
Ethan Hunt tells me
you're a man I can trust.
Does he know?
He also said you would offer me a choice.
Interesting.
I choose to accept.
We cannot escape the past.
Some of us are doomed to repeat it.
Grace may believe you've
saved her from her fate.
But you and I both know
you've nearly bought her time.
But that's the pattern, isn't it?
The cross you've been left to bear.
The closer someone gets to you,
the harder it is to keep them alive.
Thank God.
A new day brings a new burden.
The key is only the beginning.
Wherever it leads,
whatever it takes to get there,
you'll have to do it on your own.
Should you fail in your mission,
the entity wins.
Gabriel wins.
And the world will pay the ultimate price.
Should any members of your team
be caught or killed,
their sacrifice will have been in vain.
So hurry.
There isn't much time.
The world doesn't know it.
But they're counting on you.
Good luck, Ethan.