[bright music]
[cheery music]
All right, everyone,
settle down.
We're almost done.
I know you've all
been waiting to hear
who I've chosen
for the promotion
and I'm here to
confirm the rumours.
That's right,
our very own
king of commerce,
Kent Hammer,
is our new financial
analysis revenue technician!
[clapping]
Kent:
Boom! Let's go baby!
Boss:
Hammer, your outstanding work
and passion to Bonk Corp
have been proven
time and time again.
We on the board are very
excited to see you move up
and start this
new life journey.
Just need you to, uh-
[smashing]
...take care of a little
paperwork to get you started.
I need everything reviewed and
signed by the end of the day.
That won't be a problem,
will it?
No problem at all.
Yeah, I'll-I'll nail all that
paperwork, uh, before lunch.
I mean, you're-you're
looking at the Hammer [laughs].
Boss:
The Hammer!
That's the spirit.
Direct the accounts...
Briefcase:
[whispering] Psst!
Hey! Congrats Kent!
I knew you could do it.
Oh!
That being said, uh,
meeting adjourned.
Uh, Hammer be sure to have
those papers within the hour,
you're starting a
new position today.
You're fine with working
overtime, right?
Of course!
Yeah, I'm, uh,
I'm the Hammer.
True workhorse.
You're an inspiration
to all of us.
Keep this up and I see another
promo in the next ten years!
[echoing] Ten years.
Ten years.
This is great, huh, Kent?!
Financial analyst revenue tech!
[sighs]
Hey buddy, you're not
looking like yourself.
Maybe you should start
taking your medicine again
to level you out through
this promotion, hmm?
Remember the last time you
worked a ton of overtime?
Here, I've got 'em
right around somewhere.
Yeah you're right,
some of this stuff
sounds stressful as fuck.
Ah, either way my
medication's in the car.
Old news!
Forget pills, we're
talking bills, baby.
What it feels like is
we're getting a new ride!
You need to add a few zeros on
that salary proposal, punchy.
Oh, maybe I could
make a few changes
to the salary and
budgeting here,
and here.
[stabbing noises]
Cut it out!
That's what I'm saying.
We're in management
now baby!
You saw how Jeff
was looking at you.
They're jealous!
Cut them out, remember?
Gotta look out
for number one!
We don't need anyone,
you're the Hammer, baby!
Yeah, fuck off Jeff.
Just look at those hours.
I'm gonna be your best
friend after this one!
Remember we're
working overtime,
so don't forget to fill up.
Maybe just need
a cup or two.
Or inject me into
your bloodstream.
Who cares?
Yeah. You know,
a little pick me up
it's not gonna
kill me, right?
I mean, these-these-these
overtime hours
are busting my dick off.
Hours equal money.
Cash money, Kent.
Money makes the
world go round!
Mm-hmm.
Kent, don't listen
to these guys.
You're gonna do great.
I'm on your side, buddy.
We should-
Now hang on a second.
Are you?!
Because all I've heard from
you is-is-is pills this and
[in whiny voice] "take
your medicine Kent".
Hey, Kent, uh,
I don't mean to interrupt,
but I'm on your side.
I do have a
tiny suggestion.
We should staple
your dickhole shut.
I think it'll really help.
What the fuck?
No, I, no, no,
no, no no, dude,
I'm-I'm already behind, okay?
I don't-I don't
have time for that.
You don't want to be
obsolete, Hammer.
As soon as you sign that,
they'll throw you away.
Like all those before you.
I know.
Remember David
from accounting?
Couldn't keep up.
Wife left him and then
they terminated him
after twenty years
of hard work.
I do remember that.
I'll just add a
termination clause in here.
Kent, you know that
stuff's not true!
I know you don't want
to hear this buddy,
but maybe we should
take a little break.
We could go grab lunch.
I think there's pizza
in the break room today!
Maybe that'll cheer you up!
The only thing that
will cheer me up
is-is finishing this
goddamn paperwork!
Attention!
[phone ringing]
Kent Hammer speaking.
Office Phone:
Hey Kent, it's your boss.
I need signatures
immediately.
You know your job title
spells f-f-fart, right?
[laughing]
[ominous music]
Loss and gain are
the same, Hammer.
The world is a never ending
push pull of compromises.
Cut! Cut! Cut!
C'mon Kent lets
cut this deal
and then we can cut Jeff!
You're about to get
put through the grinder
and creamed if you
don't finish this stuff.
Not yet he's not, Instant!
Gotta make money.
Get bills, get paid.
Be a man,
then he can die.
Obsolete! Obsolete! Obsolete!
Kent please! We're slipping-
Yoohoo!
Kent darling!
Remember me?
Your loving wife.
You've been at the
office so long today!
The kids and I miss you.
Look how much
they're growing.
[teeth chattering]
Kent, buddy.
Come on man,
you can't do this alone!
This pressure is messing
with your brain.
You're right.
This is way too much.
We should leave work
a little early today!
You know, get out of the
office and relax a little.
I'll think of something
to tell your boss
and we can think about all this
wacky promotion stuff later.
You see these charts Hammer?
They ain't gonna
direct themselves.
Your life is over.
I'll spell it out for ya,
Mr. Financial Analyst
Revenue Tech.
We own you. We own you.
We own you.
[gasps] Kent, we don't
have to do this!
This is your last chance.
Think about what
you're doing!
You're gonna sign
your life away!
Reconsider, please.
[sombre music]
[knocking on door]
Kent? Are you almost done
with all that paperwork?
I've been waiting
all morning for-
[tense dramatic music]
Ah...I'll, uh, just come
back after lunch then.
[uncomfortable chuckle]
[bright music]