And there are many practical applications
to this idea of chaos theory, which holds
that there are identifiable and
predictable movements
in nonlinear systems.
The world's first consumer product to
exploit chaos theory
was a washing machine.
This machine produced
cleaner and less tangled clothes.
The key to the chaotic motion.
There's a point where Uncle Alvarez
hanging in the hall
Nobody wants to look at it
But Uncle Alvarez sees us all
Oh, imaginary accomplishments
Hey, hey, hey, you visionary guy
You might even shake bands of presidents
Better send a postcard
and keep the family quiet
He's not really part Cherokee Indian
He didn't fight in the civil war
He's just you, Gina is a guy
Oh man, over this fucking, Washington
Avenue soup strip
they got going over there
It's one of those fancy, beautiful things
This little kid, this
little spoiled brat kid
They got balloons, they got a big pet
with the clowns walking around
But then the birthday boy
himself, okay, he comes in
Can you pick me up a
motor rider over there?
You know what I'm saying?
A real live, old drone fucking elephant
Okay, but the elephant's
walking back in the truck, right?
Hi, can you see her?
Hey, Mike, Mike, come on,
come on, come on, come on
I want some mustard
We need some more cup of beer
Cup?
Cup, right here
Oh, Julie, we need some more cups
I want some more cup of beer
Okay, I'm going to get some more
I don't know who was that
Julie, we bring some cups out
Yeah, okay, come in, one sec
Frank, I just called the board
The September expansion has pitched well
Frank Bernstein, lifetime five-hundred
Julie!
Yep, not just a minute
Hey, Julie, you going to
join the party or what?
Yeah, okay, come in, one sec
Yeah!
That's how you play the game, right?
That's how you play the game, Justin!
I'll take my time
A while, so go ahead
Okay, here's a little sign
Lam shook the Lo and
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE]
Thank you.
Oh, I want to carry it yourself.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You can't compare the amount of energy
that the sun expended by making an
analogy to baseball.
[CRACK]
[SCREAMING]
The sun was, let's say,
the batter up at the plate.
The reverse gravitational pull or
repulsion of the sun.
Nice barbecue, huh?
[INAUDIBLE]
Well, in the most simple terms, we
would have been hit out of the park
and cleared into the next country.
The park would be our universe.
Fuck of this.
Oh, science move.
It would have sent us into this--
Yeah, good.
Four games on.
Yeah?
[CHATTER]
Here we go.
[GROANING]
--like babies.
I love you.
Good night.
- What are you saying? - Home?
- Oh, nothing. - Sick?
- No, no, it's a way sick. - Oh!
(laughing)
- Hey, where you going? - What?
- Huh? - Oh, sorry.
(laughing)
I'm doing that for the rollover.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- How's that? - It's okay. - How's that? - Good.
- Yeah? - One second.
- Oh, okay. - Second?
- You smoking? - Yeah, thanks.
(sighing)
(door opens)
(phone rings)
Hello?
Yeah, 16th, yeah, I remember.
Okay.
- It's not fair, it's my turn.
- Mom! - I get it first.
- Mom? - Mom?
- Mom? What's the matter?
What's the matter with her?
- She was okay this morning, right?
- Yeah.
- Julie, she won't talk.
- I told you. - Well, I
just want to try it, okay?
- Hey, Julie, it's me. - But we tried it
for like half an hour.
- Okay, well, I just want
to try it again, all right?
So Julie, Lisa came over
and she got me, she said, uh,
she said something's
really wrong with you.
What's wrong with you, honey?
- I told you.
- Did you have a fight
with Rick? - She won't talk.
- Lisa. - What? - She's not gonna talk. - Lisa. - What?
- Do you guys want to like,
you know, go up to your rooms
and give us some alone time?
Just leave us alone, all right?
All right?
- Okay. - Yeah.
- Okay, Frankie, come on. - So, Julie, how's things?
It's not so good, huh?
Can you hear me, Julie?
Okay, if you can hear me
like, um, I don't know,
wiggle your feet or wave or something,
I gotta know you can hear me.
Okay, okay, okay.
What's wrong with you, honey?
What you got in your hands, Julie?
Is that what's wrong
with you, got in your hands?
Yeah.
Oh.
Hi.
- You what? - I've had a lot.
You don't wanna what?
I don't wanna be stupid no more.
But Julie, like, I
mean, you're not stupid.
Yeah, yeah, no, you're not stupid at all.
You got two kids, you got a house.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, if I don't mind.
Thank you.
You don't wanna sh--
what's all over your eye?
You wanna maybe just go see a movie?
I don't know. Go to the mall.
Go see Jana or something.
I wanna-- I wanna-- I
wanna tell you something.
Yeah? Okay.
I hope you don't think--
Wow.
Hoboken high school G.D. courses.
Environmental constraints and
development and construction.
All right.
Computer class.
Okay. - I wanna go.
Do I wanna go to a computer class?
- No. - No.
Were you having a memory lapse?
'Cause you were never so
great in school, honey.
This isn't like school. It's computers.
How do you think that rocket ship Voyager
measured the wind velocity on Neptune
and those radio
emissions from the heliopause?
We wouldn't have known nothing about that
if it wasn't for computers.
Where'd you learn that stuff?
I've been watching TV all day.
Channel 13, nature
programs, beginning physics.
I've been reading.
Magazines.
Omni, discovery, you know, science ones.
Every time I go to the grocery store, I
buy one or two, sometimes three.
How long have you been, uh-- how long
have you been buying this magazine?
A couple years. Maybe even more.
Well, why didn't you tell me?
I was scared that
you'd think it was weird.
Well, yeah, it is weird. See?
No, it is. It's
really-- you know, it's weird.
See? You're my own best friend, and I
feel like I don't even know you.
I should have told you.
Now I'm afraid to ask
what else you've been hiding.
- Oh, Jesus. - Yeah.
- These are all
science magazines. - Yeah.
See, I try to figure out what the
articles are saying. I really try.
But, you know, maybe if I had to teach it
to explain it to me, you know?
- Release of the
excitatory-- - You know what?
- You're my transmitter. - You don't even
have to go back if you don't want to.
- Where? - The class.
You could even leave
before the end if you wanted to.
You really want me to go, huh?
I really-- I mean really, really.
Well, yeah, sort of weird,
but what time does it start?
Um, it's Monday. Monday, 5 o'clock. Okay.
Monday, we're walking.
I haven't tried harder than I've ever
seen anything in my life before, okay?
- You're old. - Okay?
- Dan alert. - What?
Hey, lock the door already.
Hello.
Open the door.
- Hey, what's up, little captain? - Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Playing game, boys.
- Playing that game by
all day again, huh? - Yep.
- Where's your mother? Is she home? - Um,
I beat your ass going to the game today.
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
The thing is, you're
playing all day like that.
Give me some more.
Here, here.
- Oh, but that, um... - What?
I love you.
- Oh, that's nice. I love you,
too, okay? - I and that. Look.
- Oh, jeez, I can't believe you got me
that shit. Okay. - No,
but you can't go in there.
- Why? - Uh, surprise.
- Yeah? What kind of
surprise? - A really good one.
Okay, well, I'm ready. Bring it on.
But it's not ready
yet, so you gotta wait.
Well, you know what? I guess it'll be
okay, so I'm just gonna be out.
But Dad, you're not
allowed to go in there.
What's going on?
What, is it my birthday or something?
I don't want to surprise you.
Let me just wash my hands.
Since when are you little
Miss Betty Crocker here?
Just today.
Not ready yet, though.
- Let me taste. - It's not ready.
I gotta put eggs in it.
I gotta put water in it.
It's not done yet, is it?
It's not bad, though.
- Hey, how was your
math test? - Got an A.
An A? Nice. And how
was basketball practice?
- Math's no good. - You
just keep at it, all right?
You never give up. That's all it takes.
Why not?
- What? - What we were talking about.
- Julie. - Just be asking.
I'm eating.
I want to know the reason.
Computers, son.
But I want to.
Why? What are you gonna
do? Start your own website?
Maybe.
I surf the internet. See?
Wait a second. Did I miss something here?
The bill gets called, I was gone.
You left the message saying you want to
come work at Microsoft
or something like that.
Why?
Because I said so, okay?
You know, we can't
afford it anyway, okay?
- We could charge it. - We're not gonna fucking touch the credit card.
Okay? Now stop.
Good.
Julie.
- Julie. - Yeah?
- Come back here. - Okay, one sec.
- Yeah? - Come on.
- What? - No hard feelings, okay?
- Come here. - What?
Come here. Come here.
- Okay? - Yeah.
- Okay? - Hey, get a room.
- Come on. - Let's--
This is true love, okay?
It's a bit deal, guys. Just--
Welcome. Welcome to
Introduction to Computers.
A long time ago, when computers were
young and as huge as dinosaurs,
there existed a man named Lorenz.
He was a scientist, a
meteorologist at MIT,
and believed that computers
could predict the weather.
And I don't mean a quick five-day
shot-in-the-dark situation
you have on the 6 o'clock news where they
say, "Sunny and warm tomorrow,"
and then all of a
sudden you have a snowstorm.
I mean really predict the weather.
Excuse me. Are you in the second row
there? What's your name?
- Claire. - Claire.
We were about to have a break, Claire.
I wonder if you could put away the
newspaper until we have the break.
- I'll read and listen
at the same time. - Good.
So Lorenz used 12
variables in an equation
that he programmed into his computer to
try to make weather formulations.
And then one day, just to save time,
he reduced one of the
variables just by a small amount.
Just to save time, went off to have his
coffee, his morning coffee.
And when he came back
to his weather machine,
he found that his
shortcut had changed everything.
He saw from the printout, clearly, that
weather could never be predicted.
It was chaos.
Tiny things change everything.
Why, the flapping of butterflies' wings
could sometimes, maybe
other times not, produce
a change in air pressure that could
change the direction of the wind
that could bring on a storm.
In other words, if you go outside after
this class and whistle,
there's a tiny infinitesimal chance that
you could create a tornado
that would rip the roof off your house
and change your life forever.
So after this class, just do it.
Go outside and whistle.
And remember as you're doing it, how tiny
things can change everything.
Lights, please. We have some lights.
Thank you.
Miss Tamaranda, I just wanted
to thank you for your class.
I loved it a lot. Well, thank you.
I mean, I've never loved anything as much
as I loved you, class.
Well, thank you very much.
Okay. Thanks.
I like to...
She...
Bye.
So, you're not going to tell
Mike about the class, right?
I already told them.
Oh, well, please tell
them not to tell Rick, okay?
I thought you told Rick.
I thought Rick said
yeah, and it was okay.
Oh, listen. When you get home,
please make sure you
tell Mike not to tell Rick.
So Mike's not going to be home anyway.
Again?
Yeah, you know, I guess
every couple has a rough patch,
and we have one big, long one that
started the day we got married, right?
It's good he's not home anymore,
'cause, you know, all
he's ever done when he's home
lately is just sit on
the couch and be swale.
You know, Rick watches a lot of TV, too.
Yeah. Well, Mike's stiffer
than TV, and then he snores.
Rick clicks his teeth. That's worse.
Oh, man. The other night, I thought I
heard a train coming.
It wasn't a train. It was him snoring.
It was so fucking loud.
Well, Rick has the end room.
Mike has pimples on his ass.
Rick forgets to brush his teeth.
Ew. Mike smells pretty bad.
He smells like a locker room.
Mike smells clean. He wears a broom.
Yeah, I like your own boots, all right.
But he yells a lot. I
mean, I say, "Can I do this?"
No. "Can I do that?" No.
Okay. See? He was very interested.
Okay. Thank you for coming.
We'll come talk to you tomorrow, okay?
Okay. All right.
Would you have a lever?
No, man. I would leave my own.
I was just making fun of him. You know,
it's the way I get it out.
Okay. Good night.
Please do not go to the locker room.
You have third period study hall today.
You must report to the gym.
Julie, what are you doing in here?
Okay. Here's what I was
thinking about, though.
Functions are like an oven.
And what you put in the
variables, you let it bake,
and then what comes out is something
different. Is that it?
One second.
How long have you been working at this?
Only about three
weeks. I love it, though.
Wait. Here it is.
Here it is. I wanted to show you this
gorgeous picture of fractal.
You've learned all
this in only three weeks?
Did you ever think
about going to college?
Me?
Well, sure.
There's a class here you could take,
help you pass the G.E.D.s, and then you
could apply for college.
Rick wouldn't go for it.
Do you always do what Rick says?
No!
What are you doing? Stop it!
No, Matty, don't!
I didn't tell him to come back in here!
It's helped you grow up, okay?
You're out of your mind, you know that?
I'm gonna teach you a
lesson this time, okay?
See, our life is
without me for a change, huh?
You're a freakin' lunatic!
Fuck!
You're responsible for
your fuckin' actions, okay?
So this is the end of it.
This is the end for me, okay?
You got it?
Shut up, Rick!
You know what? I'm teaching
you a fuckin' lesson, okay?
Lisa, Lisa!
You gotta make money to spend money, you.
You know what? You are
fuckin' done with me, Julie!
You know what? I'm
not bullshittin' around!
Stop it, dad! Come back here!
You gotta keep actin' out
like this bullshit, okay?
I'm done with putting up with your
bullshit, all right?
Everyone out there!
Stop it and take care of your kids!
That is it! I'm not
bullshittin' around, all right?
Okay, so go ahead and put your time!
Mom, that's a weird matter! You're crazy!
Fuckin'... You're... You're lying!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
I can't believe... I can't
believe you fucking did that!
It's better this way!
Right, Mom?
Hey! Oh, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Were the kids okay?
Yeah.
Well, 'cause I heard
yellin' all down the street.
Yeah.
Your little neighborhood heard it.
You got a lot of stuff
out on your front lawn.
Yeah.
You're not yourself, Julie.
I'm not myself.
What is that?
Julie!
Okay, so what are you doin'?
What does it look like?
I'm gonna go loop with Daddy.
You can't!
I can't!
But you don't know where he lives!
I'll find him!
Wait, is Daddy gonna live here no more?
She kicked him out! She threw all his
stuff out the window!
Julie?
He was making fun of me!
You shouldn't have
told him about your class!
Oh, you told him that class.
Yeah, I snapped. I don't know.
It was your own fault
he was making fun of you.
I... told him I was thinking about
getting my high school diploma,
and I thought maybe I could apply to
Jersey State College.
And, um, I've been thinking about this
and thinking about this, and--
And then Dad told her crazy woman she
kicked him out of the house!
So that's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna go to college.
I'm gonna be a computer scientist.
Ah, don't worry, Claire. I mean, we're
gonna-- we're gonna be fine.
We're not gonna starve. I'll get a job.
What kind of job are you gonna get?
Well, I-- I can-- I can do things. I
learned-- I can learn things.
Well, honestly, though,
what can you, like, do?
I mean, just-- I'm asking.
Um... how much is in this?
Um... what do you mean?
How much money is in
the checking account?
Your father didn't balance it yet.
So why don't you?
You know how to do this?
Don't you?
You don't know how to
balance a checkbook?
I... Claire doesn't either.
No.
I knew it! You're fucking retards!
- Lisa! - Shut up!
- Why don't you mouth like this? - Well,
only retards don't know
how to balance a checkbook.
- Lisa? - Only retards of two kids,
and no job, and no way to get a job, and
then kick their
husbands out of the house.
You fucked it up, Mom! You just totally
fucked everything up!
You shouldn't talk to me
like that. No. I mean...
I guess just, like, leave
her alone for a while, right?
How am I gonna keep us alive? I don't
even know how to balance a checkbook.
- Mom? - What?
I know how.
Frankie, you're the best.
Yeah, but look, they
taught us in fifth grade.
You add up all these numbers here, and
then just subtract them by these ones.
- Look, right here. -
It's really easy, Claire.
- Yeah, it's easy. - Add and subtract.
- Yeah. - That's it.
- Yeah. - I feel really fucking stupid.
You're the best.
Mom, like, how are you gonna get a job?
You don't know how to do nothing.
(phone beeping)
Hi, I'm...
(sighs)
Okay. (phone beeping)
Eight.
Okay.
Hello?
Hi, is this Clean Bright Clean Agency?
Hi, yeah, I'm calling about the ad and
the paper for the cleaning lady.
Yeah, what about it?
Yeah, hi.
Well, I've never cleaned professionally,
but I'm pretty good
at cleaning lampshades
and frames.
The only thing is you just gotta be
patient with my oven cleaning, because...
(phone beeping)
- Acme cleaning service.
Hi, I'm a cleaning lady. I'm very good.
Okay, may I have your name?
Uh, Julie.
And your last name?
Julie.
(phone beeping)
Johnson, Julie Johnson.
Arnie.
Julie, is that you?
Is Rick there?
I know he's there.
Arnie, tell him that he's got kids.
Kids, tell him he's got
bills to be paid, okay?
Tell him he's got kids.
(phone beeping)
Oh, man.
Okay.
Um...
Is Claire back?
Oh, my God, where the hell is she?
(phone ringing)
I know, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, Mike, I'm sorry.
Okay, look, I mean, just, can you just
tell her to come, just come right over,
tell her to come right
over, tell her not to,
tell her not to put anything
down, tell her to put her...
Hold on, goodbye, one second, yeah, bye.
Um, I'm standing by the
path, train rush hour.
You know, all those
yuppies rushing off the train.
Anyway, um, I said who
needs a cleaning lady,
five of them gave me the numbers.
Five yuppies in 40 minutes.
Mom, you gotta call him right now.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Oh, um, Mom, I need basketball sneakers
for practice tomorrow.
Okay, all right, we'll
get them in the morning.
Okay.
Can I have some more Clips?
Eat your food, Lisa.
Not peanut butter.
I like peanut butter. Unbelievable. I mean, besides tasting retarded,
it's got all the nutrition of sawdust.
All this stuff Jupy calls peanut butter.
Lisa.
I bet there isn't even one
peanut in the whole gallon jar.
I bet there isn't even a shell.
It's full, Lisa.
No, it isn't.
Jupy manufactures this stuff as a plot to
stump poor kids' brains.
Why would they do that?
So that when they grow up,
they won't mind
working from an minimum wage.
Just to be honest, I'm not gonna be part of no Jupy plot.
I'm not gonna get my brain stunted.
Besides, I want to lose more weight.
You lost weight?
Two pounds. My friends are so jealous.
You're gonna gain it back, okay?
I don't want to gain it back.
Eat your food, Lisa.
Make me.
I'm telling you, eat your food, okay?
Try and make me.
Lisa?
See, you can't. Only Dad
can, and he's not here.
You're right. I'm telling you, eat your food, okay? He's not here.
You're right. He's not here.
Like, maybe he's not
ever gonna be here again,
which leaves me as the only
person who's gonna pay the bills
and make up the rules
and put food on the table,
even if you think that
food is stunting your brain.
-Julie? -Okay!
-I'm saying eat. -No, I'm trying to eat.
-Eat, Lisa. Eat. -Oh, oh.
Clem.
I left.
What?
Well, if you could kick
Rick out, I can leave.
So, uh, you inspired me. I left.
-You left? You-you're home? -Yeah.
Where are you gonna go?
I was just dead.
I've been sitting in the
whole book of the cinema all day.
I've been trying to figure it out.
Anyway, I don't know. I
don't know where I'm gonna go.
I figure all my other
friends are married,
and, you know, their
husbands live at home,
so maybe I could stay with you guys.
You're staying with us?
Well, yeah, if you love me,
I mean, I brought some stuff.
I brought, you know, this and this.
You got money?
Yeah. Good, 'cause
first thing in the morning,
we need charts and basketball shoes.
-You gonna let me stay? -Of course.
-Come on! -Oh, good.
-Come on in. -Okay.
-Get your stuff in. -Get out of here.
-Are you okay? - Here ends my life
High and mighty life
I got addicted to the pressure
The constant elevation
My true identity
Faded
I was tired
Of being persuaded
Heart in my heart
My heart is smiling
In the heart, heart in my heart
You know it's a lie
When they catch your eye
And tell you how great
it is that you made it
You made it
Never mind that
You're being downgraded
Continually
I only hope I live to see
The face of God's running over me
Heart in my heart
My heart is smiling
In the heart, heart in my heart
I only hope I live to see  Claire.
You're supposed to be asleep.
I'm not sleeping either.
Yeah.
Then you're supposed to be asleep.
I won't sleep till I
take all my GED tests.
Hm, perfect.
No, come in.
Come on.
What if they fail him, Claire?
I mean, they only let
you take him three times.
Oh, you're gonna pass.
You know, what if you pass him?
Julie, you're gonna pass.
You gotta think positive.
Yeah.
So go back to sleep, 'cause you don't
want to fall asleep in the middle of it.
I know.
So go to bed.
I don't want to sleep.
But you're gonna...
No, no, I don't wanna...
I don't wanna sleep either.
You want me to make you have chocolate?
No.
You want me to make you what?
Sometimes I get these thoughts.
I can't get them out of my head.
Yeah, you thinking about Rick?
No.
About...
About what?
Wasn't that joke that Mr. Miranda told
about decimal points funny?
No, that joke.
I didn't think it was
funny. I didn't get that joke.
Oh, I thought it was funny. I got it.
Are you thinking about Mike?
Yeah.
He was all, uh...
He was all blue.
What do you mean?
Oh, it was career day in
senior year in high school.
All the boys, they were gonna be cops.
We were sitting in a booth,
and they all painted blue.
That's why I saw him.
God, he was just so beautiful.
Beautiful.
They look like a statue.
What happened?
Yeah, I don't know what happened.
I don't know, yeah.
Claire, could I...
No, it's stupid.
What?
No, no, it's stupid.
All right.
But you mind if I sit next to you?
Yeah, yeah.
It just feels good, you
know, sitting next to someone.
Yeah, it does.
Can I sit closer?
Um...
Yeah. Okay, you can go to sleep.
I know, I hope so.
Just go to sleep.
(coughing)
It's been like this all morning.
Did you find it like this?
I'll call the system administrator.
Who?
Fred, the computer guy.
Oh, why don't we wait on that?
Hey, Mr. Miranda.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
Did you take the test?
I took it.
Uh-huh, and did you pass it?
I think I passed it.
You think you passed it?
I don't know.
The grammar.
The grammar. That grammar, yes.
Yes.
You'll call me tonight, you promise?
I will call you tonight,
and my fingers are crossed.
Okay.
Hey, well, let me show you something in
the computer lab, can I?
Okay, sure.
Julie, come here.
I don't suppose you
know anything about this.
Um...
An encryption algorithm.
A what?
She just wrote an encryption algorithm.
Yeah.
Follow me.
Come on.
Okay.
Do you want a Coke?
No.
Do you want some peanut butter cookies or
brought some home from the steakhouse?
I'm not thirsty, okay?
And I'm not hungry.
You're mad.
No.
Yeah, you are. I can tell.
I thought you wanted
to go to Jose's house.
I thought going to Jose's house was your
favorite thing to do in the whole world.
I thought he was your best friend. I
thought you liked going over there.
Yeah, well, it's not.
Okay, well, look, I thought it was.
I mean, why do I have to go?
Why does Lisa have to go?
Hey, Mom needs a night off.
Why the fuck don't you go?
Watch your mouth.
Why the fucking shit don't you go?
Because I want to celebrate
with your mother, all right?
Well, then you don't know
she passed the English test.
Yeah, you know what I know.
Well, then Lisa and me should be
celebrating with her.
Why the fucking shit the hell gave you
the right to celebrate with her?
You need to watch your language. I'm
going to send you up to your room.
You do use language.
You know what? I don't anymore. Me and
your mom made a rule.
Well, when my mom's
here, although she says,
"Don't fucking do what you fucking say."
I mean, where the fuck are you?
Where the fucking shit are you? Jesus
fucking shit are you?
Jesus.
Where were you?
Oh, out with Chuck. Who's Chuck?
My boyfriend.
What happened to Victor?
Oh, he was talking to Susie Malnory in
front of the whole math
class making Google eyes.
Who needs him, you know?
I'm going to go get packed.
Yeah.
Frankie, how about tomorrow night?
I'll get out of here and you
can be along with your mother,
and you guys can celebrate together.
Whatever.
Can you solve this limit? Can you?
No.
Fuck. Here.
Use your algebra to solve that limit.
Okay. Okay.
Ah, correct, girl.
And?
Can you do this one?
Okay. Okay.
Very good.
Yeah?
Study it.
Why?
You need to know everything
in there to get into Stevens.
The science college. You
think I could get in there?
Absolutely. They have
a scholarship program.
They'd pay me the two to you. Chemistry,
physics, biology, calculus.
I really could get into Stevens.
You could get in anywhere you want. MIT,
whatever. Full scholarship.
You don't realize the capacity you have.
Here. Let's look at some of these.
Mr. Rand, are you like the
best teacher I've ever...
Um... Um... I just want
to... Can I ask you something?
It's, um... It's personal.
Yeah, sure.
I feel... I've never
felt this way about, um...
I'm explaining this.
I think I'm in love with this person, and
I'm in love with this person,
and I really got to
put it out of my mind.
I mean, I just got to
put it out of my mind,
and I should, but I can't,
and I don't know what to do.
I'm just... I... Yeah?
I think I know who you're talking about.
You do?
Yeah. And this person
likes you very much as well.
Is attracted to you, is
very attracted to you.
And sometimes feels in a mutual way.
But I must confess, I, um...
I once had a romance,
or an affair, I suppose.
I would have to call it an affair.
With a student, an adult
student, not unlike you.
And, um... I hurt the student very badly.
My wife... She, uh... She
still hasn't gotten over it.
I can't say that I've gotten over it.
In fact, every morning,
when I look in the mirror,
I can't stop asking myself.
Mr. Miranda?
Students just shouldn't
fall in love with teachers,
and the teacher shouldn't
fall in love with students.
It... It, uh... But it
does happen. Oh, it does.
The student's not really
in love with the teacher.
You have to understand.
They're in love with the subject matter.
They don't realize it.
Oh, of course, the teacher does often
seem larger than life.
I understand that.
But at home, I have to tell
you, when I'm not teaching,
I'm just a normal, boring guy.
Take it from me. I'm so
boring that I even bore myself.
Um... Do you think I'm in love with you?
You're, uh... You're not?
I'm sorry.
Well, is that so unusual?
Yes. I'm sorry.
It's been known to happen.
Mr. Miranda?
I'm sorry.
It's Claire. I'm in love with Claire.
Claire?
My friend Claire.
Oh. Right.
You're...
What?
Disgusted. Not at all.
But it's...
What?
Averted. What? I don't think so.
Everybody says it's...
No, I'm not... I'm not everybody.
Really? I mean, I've had many students
come to me over the years.
Many? Mm-hmm.
What are you selling?
Oh, I don't know.
Not much, I guess. I suppose I say...
Some people.
It's just the way they are.
Yeah, you know, there's this girl,
Charlene, in high school.
And, um, something written,
"Dike and the Lock and the Lock"
and everybody was just really mean to her
and calling her pervert
and they're like, "We're not gonna stop
till she stops being perverted."
And that day that that was on the locker,
everybody was laughing.
Were you? Were you laughing?
They let you stay here. And when you go
out, just close the
door. It'll lock behind you.
Where are you going?
You have some work to do.
Hey.
Hey, Mom, congratulations.
No, don't say that. I
think I flunked the English.
Come on, you always think you're so
stupid, but I know you're smart.
Bye.
Mwah. Bye.
Get drunk, get rowdy. You could use a
little rowdy-ness. You
know what I'm saying?
Don't I get a kiss, Frankie?
No. Frankie, don't be an ass face.
Okay.
-Claire? -Hey.
Hi. Did they call?
-No. -No.
What are we gonna do about Frankie?
Yeah. I don't know. We'll figure
something out, right?
We'll figure something out.
-Hey, do you think that's
that? -Oh, my. Oh, my gosh.
Hello?
Yeah.
Yeah?
-Who was it? -Mr. Miranda.
-You didn't pass, right? -No.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, I did.
Man, this shit is hard. You
know, you can take it again.
No, I know. I passed.
You passed? You fucking passed?
Oh, my God! You fucking passed, sure!
Oh, you fucking passed.
Oh, my God. Look what I did.
Look what I made. Look what I did.
Oh, my God. What is this?
Um...
I thought we were just
gonna go have some spaghetti.
-You don't like it? -I do like it.
-This is-- It's beautiful. -Yeah.
-Yeah, it's beautiful. -Good, 'cause I
want it to be beautiful.
That is beautiful.
Good.
Well, 'cause, okay, even more than, uh,
than you pass than the G.E.D.,
I wanted to celebrate 'cause I got
something to tell you.
Really? 'Cause I got
something to tell you, too.
Yeah? Yeah.
-Okay, tell her. You go
first. -No, you go first.
No, I couldn't. I couldn't either.
-Hey, you wanna have some wine? -Yeah,
let's have some wine.
Mmm. Thank you, Joy.
God, it was awful in there today.
I was so busy.
There was one woman--
I swear to God I was
gonna take her bowl of chili,
I was gonna shove it in her face.
She didn't leave a tip.
She ran me back and forth,
and she didn't leave a tip.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Sighs ]
So, maybe we both have the same thing to tell?
Yeah, maybe. No, we don't. No way.
There's a chance?
Okay, well, maybe there is a chance.
I'm hoping on that chance.
Okay, maybe there's a chance.
Okay, I'll go first.
Okay, like, I don't miss Rick anymore,
and I'm not gonna be able to tell you. I don't miss Rick anymore, and...
I've been thinking about someone else.
Who?
Like, all the time. Like, every second.
Okay, who is it?
It's you.
Okay, but...
What's going on here?
Claire?
No, I mean, you were over my feet,
and you got something else on your mind?
No, no, forget -- forget
I said it, Claire, please.
So, wait, the whole time
I've been living in this house,
you have, like, dirty,
nasty thoughts about me?
I've been --
No, just forget I said it.
Please, forget it, please.
No, I'm not gonna forget you said it.
No, I thought you were my friends.
I am your friend.
You liked me for me.
I do like you for you.
I can't believe you did this.
I just --
I can't believe it.
I mean, we were having so much fun.
Jesus!
Fuck!
Ugh. Ugh.
Claire?
Claire, can you hear me?
Claire, I want to -- I
want to say something.
Can you do something to let
me know that you can hear me?
Please don't be mad, Claire.
Please don't move out. Please don't move out.
I don't know how you could, you know,
say something like that to me
or expect me to know what to say.
Okay.
I do like you for you, okay?
I mean, that's the whole point.
But -- but please don't move out,
because we'll just -- we'll forget the
whole thing ever happened.
It's gone. Never happened.
Can I tell you what I
was gonna tell you before?
Sure.
Well, I was gonna tell you that, um,
I'm gonna quit my job at the steakhouse.
And I'm gonna start
sitting into Mr. Miranda's class,
and I'm gonna try and pass it to E.T.
And then I want to study to be a cop.
I mean, if Mike and Rick can be cops, I
don't see why I can't.
Does that bother you?
No. Why would it bother me?
I don't know, 'cause Rick's a cop.
No, it doesn't bother me.
Have you ever been with a woman?
No.
Have you ever thought about it?
Until?
I thought about it.
Really?
Yeah.
I thought about it in high school.
On and off.
And I thought about it
in junior high school.
All and off.
I thought about you.
Why did you say something?
I don't know.
It's wrong.
You know, it's perverted, and it's wrong,
and it's dirty, and it's
perverted, and it's wrong.
You know, you get these thoughts, you
gotta get 'em out of your head.
We gotta get out of our heads.
Julie.
Hi.
I'm sorry. I'm late.
That's okay.
I had three tables full of kids.
Hi, guys.
- Good luck, man.
Long time.
- Yeah, well this one keeps me going.
- But, it's just like Grand Fucking
Central around here.
- I'm gonna get it later.
- Min, Min, Min!
- Fucking want a cigarette?
- Can I have one?
- No, I'm not gonna have one.
(sighs)
- I wish we could have some privacy.
- Yeah, yeah.
I, uh, I thought about you today.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm. - Mm-hmm. - All day. - I guess I am.
I guess I thought about you too.
- Yeah.
- Couldn't stop.
(baby crying)
- I wanna hold your hand.
- Yeah, it's a fuck.
- I know.
- It's a fucking man. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
- It's a fucking Macy's is what it is.
- Fuck, I want a cigarette.
I'm not gonna have one.
I don't wanna taste like an ashtray.
- You didn't taste like an ashtray.
- Yeah, it did.
- No, you didn't.
No, you tasted like Sprite
with, um, like a little charcoal.
- Sick.
- I love the way you tasted.
- I wanna hold to your hand.
- But it's a park.
- I know.
- If we were home.
- Yeah.
I'm thinking about it.
- Stop.
- Nobody can stop us from being here.
- I'm thinking about it.
- Yeah.
- You're not doing anything.
- We were a mess last night.
Like a disaster, right?
- But then, when I touched
your face, do you remember?
- Mm-hmm.
- I touch your face now, in my mind.
- Can you feel it?
- Yeah.
- Don't think.
- Okay.
I'm touching your hair.
I'm touching your neck.
I'm touching your mouth.
Your mouth.
It's soft.
- You're soft.
- All over.
- I can remember.
- I kiss you all over.
Okay.
- I'm kissing you back.
- I'm kissing you all over.
- Okay. - I kiss you all over.
- You smell like roses.
- You smell good.
- Yeah.
Tell me.
- You smell good.
Like baby powder.
I never knew there could be so much.
- It's so cold.
- It's cold.
- It is cold.
- Let's go.
[music]
- Hey, Sally.
- Hey, Chloe.
- How are you doing?
- Good.
Good.
- How are you doing?
- I have chicken wings.
- I'll smell it.
- I haven't seen you in so long, right?
- Yeah.
How are you doing?
- So, you want to ask her to come?
- Oh, yeah.
You know, we're going to go
to the mall at Parama's after.
We'll just look at earrings
and I don't know, hang out.
- Have coffee, you know?
- Coffee?
Yeah.
No.
Do you want to come?
- No, I don't need earrings.
- Yeah, yeah, I heard you.
- You know, just last night I was hanging
out with Mike and Rick,
and I was like, "Oh, that's really hurt."
- We're just trying to improve our lives.
- Oh, yeah?
You know, most people
just join a gym for that.
She's a bitch.
These puzzle pieces look like fractals.
A fractal isn't a puzzle.
- What is a fractal?
- Okay, here it is.
The simplest geometric object
that could be called a fractal
is a cantoscent, okay?
What you've got is you've
got a line, you trisect it,
you remove the middle
third, you've got two lines,
and you keep doing this on and on,
and what you have is you
have an infinite number
of infinitely small
points that are always arranged
in the same pattern.
- Cool.
How's the studying going, Claire?
- I'm doing an equation.
It's really hard.
- Test it, number two.
Tell us all about yourself.
- Well, my name is Mary Jo Novak,
and I'm originally from
Walla Walla Watch and--
- Wait a second there, Mary Jo.
Walla what?
- Walla Walla Watch and Rick--
- Mary Jo, how can I explain this to you?
No one-- - I'm sorry, I'm sorry. - What's the cleanest to you?
No one is from Walla
Walla Watch and Rick--
- Well, I beg to differ, Rick.
I am from Walla Walla.
- I have never met--
tectonic plates were shifting at an
extremely rapid rate.
In fact, as we look at
the evolution of the planet
from around 8,000 BCE
until the present day,
we see that the amount of
change that has taken place
over the last 2,000 years
is equal to all the changes
up until that point in
the planet's lifespan.
North America and Asia have shifted
further apart recently
at an incredible rate.
In fact, at this rate,
there could be a land bridge
between the eastern
seaboard of North America.
(indistinct chatter)
- Lucky fun!
- Notice how the smoke
flows smoothly off the end
of the cigarette.
Right about here, it breaks
into a kind of wild turbulence.
Like a river flowing down a mountain,
the way it breaks into rapids.
Rapids?
Can we see the slide?
Good.
Now, it's very difficult for
physicists to study turbulence
because like weather, it has no rules.
It's--the motion ever repeats itself.
It's chaotic.
Now, our friend, Lorentz,
he was able to reduce the
turbulence of boiling water
to three very simple variables,
which he was able to
chart and trace over time.
Now, this is chaos here.
There's a picture of it.
It doesn't look like chaos, does it?
Or maybe the look of chaos has a pattern.
- I'm home!
Claire?
He's campy.
Help me.
Claire?
- Claire, I found a way to explain
what I was talking about last night.
Okay.
The mountain is stable.
The falling sand is not.
At one point, the edge of
the mountain is gonna fall,
and when and how,
that's what chaos is, edges.
- I missed my friends.
- I'm--I'm your friend?
- I know.
I--yeah, I used to have more than one.
- We'll get new friends.
- What do you mean we'll get new friends?
I've had these friends for my whole life.
- Okay, I got an idea, okay?
- People from Manhattan make me nervous.
- It's okay.
Once you get there, you'll be fine.
'Cause it's sitting on my body
It's on a tip of buttons
They're looking around
- Tommy has been talking about you.
- Yeah? - Mm-hmm.
- And it is so nice to see another woman
in this boys' club.
- It's a police group. - Oh, sure.
They can't help themselves.
- Yeah.
You're gonna introduce her?
- Yeah, this is my friend Claire.
- I am Claire. - Hi, Claire. Welcome.
- This is my key. -
Glad to have you with us.
- Hey, Tommy, your friends are here.
- Oh, oh, you made it good.
- Mr. Miranda? - Please
call me Tom, all right?
I have a surprise for your treat.
Come on in here. I
want you to meet someone.
- Okay.
- Tommy!
- Robert Sander.
I want you to meet Julie
Johnson, Claire Devaney.
Robert studies
bifurcations and plain-out,
Diffie-O, help me out here, Bob.
- Special admissions, Princeton.
- Call him Bob, please.
- Very nice to meet
you. - Nice to meet you.
- Hi, Bob. - Hello.
- Do you want some
drink? - I would love that.
Yeah, that would be really good.
- Oh, I saw Rogues
and Cashmere years ago.
I was safe to travel there.
- The carpet just needs a major redo.
- So you're not happy with Iraq?
- I think Persian, maybe.
- What about the pad?
- A little casual, but the Feynman
diagrams never go down.
- Well, for instance, only proof is not
only could the onset of turbulence
be mathematically formulated by the use
of nonlinear equations,
but they also showed that
turbulence was directly related
to a sensitive
dependence on initial conditions
and that the turbulence was
described by strange tractors.
- Oh, right. I do. I think I remember.
- Right.
- I bet you have.
[chatter]
- Hello. How are you? Good to see you.
- Good.
- So good to see you.
- Thank you. Yes. I feel great. Yes.
- You didn't talk to
anybody. You got to talk to people.
- I tried to talk to people.
- I don't know. She's sat
alone most of the night.
- They wouldn't talk to
me. I tried really hard.
- All right.
- Fuck. It's Susan.
- Jesus. Fuck.
- Susan.
- What?
- It's fucking Susan.
She can fucking see us.
- What's there to see?
- She can fucking see
us. She's not stupid.
It's written all over us.
- What?
- Just get the fuck away from me.
- I'm not even there yet.
- Just get the fuck
away from me, all right?
Just leave me the fuck alone.
- There's nothing to see. She's--
- She can fucking tell.
- She's stopped. She's
looking straight ahead of her.
- She's pulling away.
- She can fucking tell.
- Claire.
[sighs]
[clanging]
- Yes.
Yes, that's absolutely correct.
Very good.
Have a seat.
You know, I'm a big
admirer of Tom Miranda.
He's very impressed with you.
And I think quickly solving a few
multi-task equations
is very impressive.
But I don't know if
that makes you a genius.
You know, people who make real
contributions to mathematics
are usually young and always under 30.
- You're a little over the hill.
- I don't know if we know
yet what I'm capable of.
- Hey, where are you going?
- Pat, who's Joe?
- Who's Joe?
- My boyfriend.
Oh, Mom, you've got to see Claire.
She looks beautiful.
A photograph
I don't want no photograph
All I want is a photograph
I want to touch you
- Shit.
Two minds.
- What?
I gotta be there 20 minutes.
- Where?
- I'm going to Sally's.
- You were gonna study tonight.
- Okay, well, you know what?
I haven't been invited
over there in a long time,
and so I changed my minds.
- You gotta study, Claire.
- Yeah, not tonight I don't.
- You're not gonna pass the GED test.
- Okay, that test isn't for two and a
half more weeks, right?
- You have a lot to learn.
How do you expect to pass the test?
- Julie, I'm gonna go over to Sally's.
I'm gonna go and I'm gonna
hang out with my friends.
- You bored of me?
- No.
- Then why'd you stay at home?
- Because I'm really
sick of staying at home.
- You bored of me?
- Look, normal people do not stay home
every single night of
their lives, all right?
Normal people go out and
they party with their friends.
- We're not normal.
- Okay, I don't know about you, right?
But I'm normal.
- What do you mean by that?
- It means I want to have fun.
It means I want to have
fun with normal people.
Normal fun with normal people.
And if I have to stay in
this house one more night,
I talk about phase
transitions and fractals.
I am gonna fucking go out of my mind.
- Oh, and what are you gonna
talk about with your friends?
The same things you talk about with me?
Who's having an
affair with who hairstyles?
Maybe sometimes I go
out of my mind with you.
Sometimes maybe I think you're stupid.
- Okay, you are not
better than other people,
Julie Johnson.
You are not.
You can sit around and
you can spout your shit
about fractals and chaos
theory and iterated recursion.
What the fuck, Abba?
But you are not better than me.
- Oh, Jesus.
- What are you doing?
- You want to be with your friends?
Be with your friends.
- You can't go.
- Why?
- 'Cause you weren't invited.
- Well, of course you were me.
They wouldn't even know a thing.
- Julie.
- I won't even look at you.
- Roommate, okay?
You can't go.
- They're my friends too, Claire.
- Not anymore.
No one knows you anymore, Julie.
I don't even know you anymore.
- Okay, but first, can
I show you something?
- I gotta go.
- No, first, let me,
listen, Claire, listen.
Let me show you something, okay?
You're not gonna like it
in the beginning, okay?
But if you can keep
your temper from blowing,
I think when I've got
the whole thing explained,
I think you're gonna maybe like it a lot,
like I think you're gonna like it.
Okay.
Okay, so...
So next year, hopefully
I'll be going to Stevens.
You'll be going to Jersey City College
or wherever you want.
- Look, I need to go
see my friends, okay?
- Okay, but we get new friends.
We get New York City friends, okay?
That's part of it.
Listen, just listen, please, Claire.
Okay, I made this chart because
I was thinking, well, you always say
you'd make a great lawyer, and it's true.
You got great arguing skills.
So I got to thinking, is it possible?
Is it possible we go to college together?
So here it is.
Here.
So you go to classes three nights a week,
and you study the other
two nights and on Saturday,
and then weekend nights and Sunday,
we have it off and we
spend with the kids.
Okay, and then I've divided up the chores
between Frank and Lisa and us
because they've got to
help with the chores.
And then over here, I figured out
how we're going to pay for this.
I've got the grant
and loan possibilities.
I've got information for
you about Columbia and NYU
because Mr. Miranda said they
have great pre-law programs.
I mean, it's tight financially.
I admit it's tight, but I
think we can make it work.
I--
[soft music]
[music fades]
Mom, something's wrong with Frankie.
He was setting trash on fire at the park.
It's true, I know it.
Kay Smith doesn't live with perverts.
We're not perverts.
You still holding hands down by the dock.
Kerry Smith is the stupidest idiot I've
ever knew in my life.
Shut up, Lisa. I don't care.
We wouldn't hold hands.
Are you guys dykes?
No. No, of course not.
Well, I believe you.
Think you guys are dykes.
We are not dykes.
I'm gonna go live with Dad.
Frankie.
Kerry Smith is the stupidest
idiot I ever knew in my life.
[footsteps]
Claire, we're not.
No one's ever gonna
call me that again, so--
Claire, we're not.
No one's ever gonna
call me that again, right?
[footsteps]
[door creaks]
[door closes]
[footsteps]
Is it true?
What?
You and Claire.
[sniffles]
We love each other.
Yes.
That's true.
In what way?
Love is--
Shit.
I shouldn't have told you.
No, you should have.
Do you want a hug?
No.
I just want to sit.
Do you wanna--
[soft guitar music]
Where they have the last ones, right?
And this is where we--
Let me get a very cold one.
I'm gonna--
Bear--
Oh, Julie.
Hey.
The moment I see Claire, it's emergency.
Um--
Yeah.
[chuckles]
Okay.
Yeah.
[chatter]
[soft guitar music]
[footsteps]
Claire?
I saw it.
I'm going to bed.
What?
I'm tired.
Okay.
Um--
You and me, it, um--
It's--
It's, uh, not the same
between you and Mike, is it?
It's none of your business.
You know?
What did I do with my time?
What did I do with my future?
It's just-- It's not any business, Julie.
I'm going to bed.
[footsteps]
[chatter]
Keep moving around.
Pass the ball around.
That's right.
[chatter]
I'm going.
Frankie!
So that's the dike.
What?
Is that your dike model?
[chatter]
That's the dike, isn't it?
Hey, shorty, come on.
Back up.
[chatter]
No white for here.
[whistle]
[chatter]
When's she starting?
I thought we were waiting for Claire.
Starting?
She'll be down.
Okay.
[chatter]
You coming to dinner, Claire?
No.
I fixed you a plate.
No, I'm not coming.
[chatter]
Hey.
How's Frankie?
He's okay.
How you doing?
I'm okay.
Yeah?
Long time, huh?
Yeah.
What are you drinking?
I'm just having a little drink.
How about I take you out
and get you a good bottle?
[chatter]
Yes, you know, I've been
doing a lot of thinking, you know,
where I'm figuring out how to be a better
man and everything like that.
Really?
Yeah.
I've been doing some work, you know?
And like, you know, I
got to treat you better.
I know that now, right?
I got to take you out, you
know, and I got to listen more.
Right.
You know, I don't know
if you know this or not,
but I was real torn up about you.
I didn't know.
I mean, real torn up.
I started seeing a shrink.
Don't tell nobody.
Don't tell nobody, right?
But I mean, this guy, he was on the job
before he started shrinking heads,
so he knows a thing or two.
And he said we could go
see him together, you know,
and work out our
problems, be a family again.
You would like that?
Yeah.
This is good wine, right?
It's better than when
I was drinking today.
Yeah, none more of
that garbage for you, huh?
It's good though, huh?
So Frankie's not
sleeping so good, you know?
I had a little talk with him,
and Frankie, Frankie
thinks you're a lesbian.
No.
Yeah, I should know, right?
Stupid rumor.
Yeah, but you know, that's
why I told Frankie, you know?
I mean, people talk.
They say stupid things.
Yeah, I told him you just can't listen to
that shit, you know?
There's three conditions to chaos.
The first is that it's a
sensitive to initial conditions.
The second is that
it's periodically dense.
And the third is dense transitive.
You know, you lost me there, sweetie.
How can I show you a
computer-generated image?
You know, it's all right.
I don't really care for that
kind of talk anyway, you know?
It's a nice night though, huh?
Yeah.
Beautiful.
It's like you.
Okay, so...
So maybe I could come in
for a little bit, you know?
Not tonight.
No?
No.
Sooner, right?
Hopefully.
Yeah, hopefully so.
Yeah.
Mm.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I got carried away there.
Smell good.
I'm sorry.
About what?
I loved being with you tonight.
I loved it.
And I want to go to
the shrink with the kids,
'cause I want to know how to deal with
them better, you know?
Yeah, so we'll bring the kids.
But we can't be the kind of family that
you're talking about.
Well, why not?
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, babe.
I'm sorry. - Full of ten international delight
flavors. - But no coffee.
She was a suspicious record.
What kind of coffee guy are you?
The best kind.
The kind who can take
your tired ordinary coffee
and make it rich, premium, delicious
beyond your wildest dreams.
Really?
It's time.
Julie, you are flying so far away.
You know, you're flying
into the O Zone or something.
I don't know. I don't want to know.
But it's too far away for me.
I just want to sit back here on the Earth
and wave at you and watch you go.
Don't you want to make
something of yourself?
You know, like be somebody?
Julie, I already am somebody.
We come sit closer.
You want me to sit closer?
No.
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for you.
Do you want to go to the
Museum of Natural History?
They got the butterfly exhibit up.
And, you know, I want to
sit in on that lecture,
Columbia, on the celestial taxonomy,
Friday at seven. Do you want to go?
Do you want to go?
What is it? What's wrong?
She's gone.
Here, it's all right.
Do you want to talk about it?
I want you to sign me.
What?
I want to measure the
distance from here to Alpha Centauri.
Why?
I gotta know.
There was a time I know you like me.
We saw
in all
glorious sight.
Everyone's burnt.
Everything's gone.
What we were then,
now we are not.
So hold back the light.
Do you want to be, want to be?
My darling day.
My darkest hour.
My overdose.
Just ask what you need.
Just hold back the light.
She's gone crazy.
Been trying so hard to be open to her,
but I don't understand what she's saying.
Do what you want to do.
Say what you want to say.
Be what you want to be,
but I can't love you that way.
I can't love you that way.
She's gone crazy.
She's gone so far away from me.
I can't find her no more.
I can't jam in the door.
Do what you want to do.
Say what you want to say.
Be what you want to be,
but I can't love you that way.
I can't love you that way.