["DND" by CerVon Campbell
and John Oates]
♪ Another night I'm up
and I'm sleep deprived ♪
♪ Web MD says I'm about to die ♪
[Marge] That's me.
Large Marge.
Butt too big,
boobs too small,
Generation X-O.
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You can't be such a pussy.
People are going to think
that you're a poodle.
And that's Puker.
-[shutter snaps]
-Huge likes, Puker.
He's a rescue.
Guaranteed.
♪
♪ It's weird
feelin' happy for once ♪
♪ Now that
I don't cut the world off ♪
♪ I been talkin' to God,
I'mma leave it there ♪
[Marge retching]
♪ ...it ain't like you care ♪
♪ I been feeling like
I don't gotta be scared ♪
Puker.
-[indistinct].
-[Puker whines]
[Marge groans]
♪ But who am I anyway? ♪
[sighs]
Hey, Pukes?
One like!
♪ I ain't really
need you people ♪
♪ I'm on do not disturb ♪
♪ So, please, do not disturb ♪
[dramatic music]
[people cheering]
[Cathy] Go! Back!
God-- get back!
[Marge] Coach Cathy.
She was kicked out of Al Qaeda
for cruelty.
Get your ass back!
If club doesn't win
the championship this year,
she's going to open
a tire store.
-[player grunts]
-[whistle blows]
[indistinct clamoring]
[dramatic music]
[Marge clears throat]
Get your big ass in there,
Lemmy.
-This is your moment.
-I have cramps.
Champs don't get cramps.
You wanted this.
But only in theory.
Like sex.
Right. It's overrated.
Come on, get in there.
-[Marge groans]
-Play for the tie. Go.
Let's go,
Blue, let's go!
[Marge] I'd already
given God a few chances.
Like when I asked him
for my period to start.
And then when I prayed
for him to make him stop.
This was his last shot
at redemption.
-[whistle blows]
-[intense music]
[Cathy] Nice pass.
Hey, go. Go!
-[Marge] No. No!
-Steady, Lem.
Get back!
-[Marge gasps]
-[crowd cheering]
What the hell, Lem?
The wrong goal?
[Marge]
God blew it again.
[Cathy]
Are you kidding me?
You so suck.
Sit down.
When someone's a failure,
everybody is a failure.
That's why
communism doesn't work.
Extra practice
Tuesday and Thursday.
[players groan]
Courtesy of Comrade Marge.
This isn't Survivor.
We can't just
vote her off the team.
She shouldn't even
be on the team.
She was going to
jump off a roof.
Why is it up to us
to make her life better anyway?
I mean,
she lives in a frickin' car.
[girl]
She lives with her mom.
[Heather]
Oh, have you seen her mom?
She's gorgeous.
[girl]
She must take after her dad.
[girls snickering]
You've got to drive through
the drive-through, Marge.
Oh, is that what you learned
at Hamburger High?
It's my major.
Major weirdo.
Says the major victim.
Ouch.
Sticks and stones, bitch.
Do you want to die?
Too late,
I'm already dead.
-Excessive, Lem, even for you.
-Well...
Says the man
wearing the purple eyeshadow.
[soft guitar music]
[Marge, sing song]
Good morning. Good morning.
[toilet flushing]
Oh, my God. Wow.
[Marge scoffs]
You're the daughter?
[Marge] And you're in the market
for a well-appointed,
comfortably priced,
tracked home, I assume.
[snoring]
[quirky music]
Hey.
Where are you going?
My trainer charges
if I miss a session.
Hey. Hey!
My mom's card.
You still might want to
buy the house, right?
I know how to reach her.
[Marge] What kind of sadist
names her kid Marge?
My mom. That's who.
Mini Marge Bickford.
Realtor of the year,
five years ago.
Shit,
did I forget to buy milk?
Mm-hmm. It's okay.
I'm off dairy.
Professional courtesy.
Don't say that.
You're beautiful.
I'm fat.
The person you see in your head
is not who you are.
The person I see,
is who you are.
You're trying to sell me.
Everything's a negotiation.
Mm, always be closing, Mom.
That guy
gonna make an offer?
He couldn't even make
the deposit.
Ew. That's so gross.
No utilities, honey.
[sighs] Don't worry.
We'll get there, I promise.
Where is there?
Only seen it
from a distance.
But it looked just like you.
When you're happy.
-Today's your day.
-[both] Go take it.
[gasps] Puker! Oh.
Hello, bobby.
[Marge] It really
doesn't stress me out
that my mom has sex
with clients.
[cooing]
In fact,
the abnormality of it
sort of appeals to me.
It's not sex
in the abstract,
like a lot of parents
talk about.
It's sex in the real.
That mom
can trust me enough to know
is kind of cool.
[school bell rings]
Metaphors be with you.
[Mr. Farnsworth]
Hey, Margie.
-How's soccer?
-It's great.
Really?
Hmm.
Big school, small world.
Yeah, well,
club is really hard.
Well, varsity
would love to have you.
And club is better.
It's the next step.
And because
your father played club.
You know,
it's not his fault
that he was 20 years
ahead of the game.
It's not the part
that I'm blaming him for,
Mr. Farnsworth.
[Mini] Did I tell you
I have an exclusive
on that whole development?
That's how we get to
stay there for free.
No. We're squatters.
We're homeless.
We are a statistic.
No,
we're saving money,
so we can buy
our own place.
We're being frugal.
And by that time,
I will be moving out.
Oh, you discovered my plan.
[Mini chuckles]
It's fine.
I'll just move in with Dad.
-In prison?
-He's not in prison.
-He should be.
-I'm allowed to miss him, Mom.
Oh, please.
You were two
when he dumped us.
He hurts people, Margie.
He's a professional hurter.
And a professional
soccer player.
For, like, an hour.
Which is half
the amount of time
of the best part
of our marriage.
[Marge groans]
That is so gross.
I thought it was destiny,
which used to pass for romance.
I want to know
what it's like
to fall in love
for real someday.
Well, maybe
you shouldn't try so hard.
Hey.
I can't help it
if I meet a lot of men.
Oh, well, this is the part
where she tells us
the heartbreak
in being beautiful.
You know,
sometimes I get lonely, Margie.
Lonely or horny?
[sighs]
What about hornly?
[Mini laughs] Hornly.
That's what I am.
Get out.
[Mini chuckles]
[Mini] Hey.
You're my one in a million,
kid.
Don't let 'em beat you up.
-Mm-hmm. Love you.
-What?
[Mini laughs]
[Mini] No worries.
A 60-day escrow is perfect.
[man on phone]
All right, let's do it.
Let's put it in an offer.
Fabulous. Absolutely.
The first of many.
Thank you.
[man]
All right. Thanks, Marge.
[squeals]
Okay, okay, okay.
Hey, kid.
Your mom's a star.
She just sold her--
[loud crash]
-[heart beating]
-[high-pitched ringing]
[tires screech]
[tense music]
[priest] And if you hold Marge
in your heart,
please do the same
for her daughter,
who she loved
more than anything else.
[organ music playing]
This is what happens
in California.
Frank, please.
[Frank]
If it wasn't for California,
she never would have met--
Let's just say
we wouldn't be here now.
I wouldn't be here,
either.
[Frank] Tomorrow,
we're leaving for Scottsdale.
Can I at least
say goodbye to my friends?
Just be ready
first thing in the morning.
[sighs] I'm sorry.
Your grandfather
always wants to beat traffic.
[footsteps departing]
[somber music]
[Mr. Farnsworth]
Arizona's not that bad.
[Marge] It's
an air-conditioned nightmare.
I hardly even talk
to my grandparents.
You know, they only ever called
to yell at my mom
about marrying my dad.
-I should go live with him.
-In Mexico?
My dad is in Mexico?
I'm guessing.
My dad is in Mexico,
isn't he?
I'm not sure.
How long have you known
that my dad is in Mexico?
You-- you--
[sighs] I can't--
This is between you
and your grandparents, Margie,
you know?
[door slams shut]
[somber music]
[sobbing]
No!
[Brad]
You want me to come?
[Marge]
No. Just wait here.
[car door shuts]
[metal gate rattles]
[soft, mysterious music]
[kiss smacks]
No more chances.
♪
[breathing heavily]
[envelope rustling]
Mexico.
[rooster crows]
[Latin guitar music]
[Jackson groans]
[rooster crows]
Sh-- shut up.
[upbeat percussion music]
♪ Just ways to behavin' ♪
♪ [indistinct lyrics] ♪
♪ And I've shown you the kind of
man that I could be ♪
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
♪ Like bringin'
the sunlight ♪
♪ Out of a dark night ♪
♪ Like a perfect wave
that's waitin' there for me ♪
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
-Hey, buddy.
-Can I swim [indistinct]?
Think not.
You were doing good.
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
-[Jackson laughs]
-[bell tolls]
[music fades]
[Brad]
You don't even have a passport?
[Marge]
You don't need a passport
if you're leaving.
You can't just go and do this.
Marge, it's insane.
If I don't find my dad,
I'm going to be an orphan.
Who's the drama queen here?
Please.
You have family
in-- in Arizona.
-Have you met them?
-No.
They wouldn't like you.
Nobody does.
[Marge] Come here.
-Puker, come on.
-[Puker barks]
What do you want me
to tell everyone
when the federales
find your body?
Um, that it was all
their fault.
This is serious, Marge.
Right?
Like, life-changing serious.
I know.
That's why I'm doing it.
Is it okay to tell you that
I'm really gonna miss you?
Sure.
Can I give you something
to remember me by?
Okay.
How about
if I give you my dog?
-I knew there'd be a catch.
-Nope. No, there isn't.
But, you know,
I googled it,
and, uh, you can't take a dog
into Mexico
without vaccinations.
And that can take
at least a week.
-So, wait.
-No.
I'd whimp out
and I'd end up in Scottsdale.
Goodbye, my little...
There you go. Bye, Pukes.
Gonna miss you.
Bye, Puker.
You still call him that?
[emotional guitar music]
[people chattering]
[Marge] Siri.
Directions
to Lo de Marcos.
[Siri] Getting directions
for low daycare prices.
No.
S-- directions
to Lo de Marcos.
To--
[speaking in Spanish]
[Siri speaking in Spanish]
-What?
-It's very far.
-Gracias.
-You're welcome.
[Marge] Mexico is...
nice.
Pretty.
Green.
And there's a lot of food.
Really good food.
[street din]
[Latin guitar music]
[Padre speaking Spanish]
-[Padre speaking Spanish]
-Go, go, go, go, go!
[all groan]
Hey, Blue!
What are ya doing?
[Padre speaking Spanish]
-[Jackson] What're you saying?
-[Padre] Follow, follow, follow.
Get on her! Go!
[Padre speaking Spanish]
It's like a bunch of kids
chasing a ball.
Guys, I am tired
of looking in this direction.
[Padre speaking Spanish]
No, no, no!
-[all groaning]
-[whistle blows]
Fuck!
Oh, shit!
Oh, come on. Darn it!
[emotional guitar music]
[Marge] This might be one of
the stupider things I've done.
[man speaking Spanish]
All right,
all right, all right.
Yeah, yeah.
Listen.
We are championship material.
We're this close.
We still have four more games
left in the playoff.
Okay?
Yoo-hoo. Okay?
Who's buying
the cervezastonight?
Aw, see?
Oh, you got that one!
All right.
Yo? Again? Okay.
I got the cooler.
[groans]
[grunts] Darn it!
♪
I knew
if I waited here long enough,
you would show up.
Did Elsa send you?
[speaking in Spanish]
No-- uh,
I don't speak the language.
[Jackson] My girlfriend.
No, I don't know her.
I-- I know him.
[Jackson] Hey.
Where'd you get that?
-I inherited it.
-[Jackson scoffs]
I got one just like it.
It's from my mom.
Marge Bickford?
Marge is your mom?
Uh, she was, she...
she-- she's gone now.
Marge died?
How?
The hard way.
Well, when?
Uh, recently.
Wait...
who are you?
I'm your daughter.
You're my daughter?
-Yeah, I'm-- I'm Margie.
-Holy shit!
Are you drunk?
Not as much
as I was a minute ago.
That's all you can say?
-I don't know, give me a minute.
-You've had 14 years.
Wait. You got an ID?
[sighs]
[whispering] Holy shit.
[rooster crows]
[groans]
[Latin guitar music]
[rooster crows]
[sighs]
Oh, boy.
I carried this
in my pocket for over a month.
-You were scared?
-No, I was terrified. [laughs]
I loved your mom so much.
Right up until
she kicked me out.
So, why didn't
you fight for us?
You know, like,
try and make it work?
Because I was in handcuffs
and, um, I just wrecked
the family Porsche.
[clicks tongue]
Where is she?
Oh, man,
you're gonna love her.
She is so--
She's so sweet
and kind, smart.
Like-- I don't know.
What's wrong? You okay?
Yeah, I'm-- I'm fine. I'm--
I'm nervous to meet her is all.
Yeah, she makes me
a little nervous, too.
But-- so,
I'm going to have a cerveza.
You?
Isn't it a little early?
Um, well...
we're on London time here, so...
[grunts]
-[Jackson] Hey, there she is!
-We're not open yet.
[Jackson] Um,
can't beat the service here.
[laughs] Don't worry.
[Elsa]
I'm gonna need some ID
-for your new drinking buddy.
-What?
I don't know what's your plan,
muchachita,
but this guy
comes with a warning label.
-Just so you know. Okay?
-[Jackson] Oh! No, no, no! Elsa!
Sorry. Hold on a sec.
-Elsa! Elsa. Please--
-What? What? What?
[Jackson] Can-- Elsa,
can-- can I-- I'm sorry.
Can I introduce you?
Please?
Just one second
and then you can go
back to work, all right?
Just let me introduce you.
Please. Come on.
Elsa...
this is my daughter.
Margie.
[Elsa] Margie?
I'm sorry. Hi.
-I'm Elsa.
-Mucho gusto.
Mucho gusto.[laughs]
-Margie's visiting.
-For how long?
-[Jackson] I dunno.
-Forever.
-[laughs] Well--
-No, I-- I wanna live with you.
-What?
-If you have space.
Oh, he has plenty of room.
-Yeah, but it-- it leaks.
-Yeah, only in the rainy season.
Well, yeah.
You know, the hard part
is gonna be putting up with him.
-Oh, I'll give it a try.
-[Elsa] Good.
Because Los de Marcos
needs more strong women.
Uh, look, I'm-- I--
I-- I'm a heavy drinker.
[Elsa]
Don't say that--
-[Jackson] I do.
-[Elsa] Stop.
-[Jackson] No, it's bad.
-[Elsa] I just--
-No, I drink a lot.
-You drink-- Don't say that--
-[Jackson] No, it's--
-[Elsa] Well, okay.
Look, will you let me
raise my daughter, please?
-Did he really just say that?
-He did. He did.
Your blood is in her heart,
Jackson.
Oh, my God.
Drama is such a big part
of the culture down here.
[speaking in Spanish]
See? Look, okay.
Just, um, we'll try...
a month.
But...
[speaking in Spanish]
What?
It is his house,
so he makes the rules.
He has rules?
[Jackson] I surf
when there's a swell,
I sleep when there isn't,
so don't set an alarm.
I'll assume that you know
everything you have to know
-about Kotex and condoms.
-Ew.
As far as boys are concerned,
don't bring them home
if they're kooks or creeps.
-Cool?
-Mm-hmm.
-Just humor him.
-[Marge chuckles]
[Elsa]
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Welcome to Lo de Marcos.
This is so exciting.
[birds chirping]
[phone ringing]
I get 10% of any deals
made on the golf course, Frank.
[Frank chuckles]
Yes, it's Frank Nelson.
Frank. It's, uh, Jackson.
I told you
never to contact me.
-That hasn't changed.
-I'm sorry for your loss, Frank.
And the last thing I want
is your sympathy.
Um...
Margie is with me.
Well, seeing
as how she walked out on us
when her mom died,
tells me you two
will get along just fine.
Look, I, um...
Margie's safe and I just
wanted you to know that.
-Okay?
-I'll tell Betty.
[phone beeps]
[Marge sighs]
[intriguing guitar music]
♪
[tap squeaking]
Oh. [groans]
[gagging]
Hey, what's the password?
[Jackson] Broken.
-No, that's not it.
-No. No, as in it's busted.
There's no internet.
How do you not have internet?
I dunno. 'Cause I don't.
Well, what about,
like, Snapchat?
Well,
who am I gonna Snapchat at?
-Um, Elsa.
-[Jackson scoffs]
She snaps at me
without it.
I get all the information I need
just looking out my window.
Nothing works.
Look, my priorities
are to keep this town running,
surf in second,
I'm third.
Where do I fit in?
Yeah, I'm still trying
to figure that one out.
But...
I think I'm gonna love
the challenge.
-Are you going surfing?
-[Jackson chuckles]
You will get to a point
where you won't have to
ask that.
Can you teach me?
[Jackson sighs]
You know, you can't really
teach someone how to surf.
It's like walking.
No one taught you how to walk,
did they?
Well, you and Mom did.
No, we just picked you up
when you fell down.
Walking part
you did on your own.
Help yourself.
[Marge sighs]
[rooster crows]
[thuds]
[clattering]
[upbeat guitar music]
Oh! Oh!
[gasping]
♪
[Jackson] Had enough?
I'm just getting started.
All right.
Waves come in sets.
Here, usually
three or four at a time.
Then there's a lull.
That's when you paddle out.
Now,
you sit off to the side
from where the wave
starts to break.
The part that curls,
okay?
Float on your board,
on the shoulder,
that's that rolling hump
coming out the back.
And rest, okay? Chill.
And watch. Always watch.
Watch for waves,
watch for sharks,
watch the horizon.
Watch your ass.
Cool?
[Jackson grunts]
Nobody surfs
the first day, Margie.
Takes a lifetime.
[waves crashing]
[upbeat guitar music]
Nobody surfs
the first day, Margie.
No. Takes a lifetime.
[scoffs]
You'll get it.
[man speaking Spanish
over loudspeaker]
"La Margies," is that me?
Uh, that's the town crier.
Telling everyone
the latest chisme.
That's you.
-What's chisme?
-Gossip.
Great.
What are they saying?
He's saying...
that you came here
to save me.
Maybe you got that one
backwards.
Maybe.
Hey, there's practice
this afternoon.
-You coming?
-Yeah.
All right.
Well, see you there.
Okay?
[Jackson laughs] Hey.
Nothing hungrier
than surf hungry, huh?
I haven't been able to eat much
since Mom died.
Try drinking.
[Marge] I wonder
how many karma points you lose
for using your dead mom
as an excuse to binge.
[retches and coughs]
I promised myself
I would only do it
when I felt really bad.
[toilet flushes]
Which wasn't great,
because I felt bad a lot.
-[Marge] Hi.
-Hi.
Are you sick?
Seasick.
I went surfing.
How'd that go?
Still waiting
for it to change my life.
Wow,
I see you did the dishes.
Yeah, I'm--
I'm staying here, so...
And you fixed that.
-It's just a bulb.
-[Elsa] Well, don't tell him.
You know, Marge, I...
I used to get sick.
[Marge] From surfing?
No, no, from...
from eating.
You know, Mexico
is the comfort food capital
of the world, so...
you know, who doesn't wanna be
comfortable? [chuckles]
I'm comfortable.
Elsa, I am fine.
Are you? Okay. Good.
[chuckles]
Well, tell your dad
I-- I stopped by, okay?
I will.
Take care of yourself.
-[whistle blowing]
-[upbeat music]
Hey.
[speaking in Spanish]
[upbeat Latin music]
-[whistle blows]
-[Jackson] Control it. Go.
That's it.
Wow. You have a big kick.
What,
you never googled me?
I was afraid to.
[indistinct] college ride.
Signed with Portsmouth,
300K a year.
First season,
started every game.
Met your mom,
got married, had you.
Second season,
learned how to drink.
Uh, wrecked two cars,
got arrested, ruined my life.
Went surfing.
You?
Mm.
Fat, slow, unpopular.
Only ever played
when we were way ahead,
or way behind.
Quit.
'Cause I hated it.
Went to Mexico.
You left out the part
about your mom dying.
These ladies are--
are really good.
[Jackson] Yeah.
I mean, two years ago,
they couldn't kick
their boyfriends out of bed.
But they--
oh, I'm sorry.
That wasn't very dadlike,
was it?
How well
did you know Mom?
You should've stuck around,
you would've liked us.
Well, I don't think
you would've been too crazy
about the kind of dad
I was back then.
[Marge]
What kind is that?
This kind.
Hey. [snaps] Go.
-No, no, no, no.
-[Jackson] Yeah. Come on.
Can't just sit there.
Come on. Go.
There you go, kid.
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
[Padre speaking in Spanish]
Get in there, kid!
-[Marge grunts]
-[Jackson grunts]
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
-[indistinct]
-[Padre speaking in Spanish]
[mellow guitar music]
[Marge] I wonder
if drinking too much
feels as bad
as eating too much.
I wonder
if it runs in the family,
like big kicks.
And quitting.
♪
[speaking in Spanish]
Sorry, uh,
I don't speak Spanish.
[Chilo speaking in Spanish]
I speak English.
Like Harry Potter.
Hey, I saw you at,
um, Tal Ivan.
-What?
-Uh, the tacos.
[Marge] When?
You no remember Chilo?
-Not really.
-[laughs]
[speaking in Spanish]
I, um--
I teach you how to surf.
My dad says that no one
can teach you how to surf.
[speaking in Spanish]
He never meet Chilo.
Come on, I teach you.
-What? Now?
-Yeah. Let's go. Come on.
Uh. Oh! Okay.
[Chilo] Come on! Come.
["Sunshine & Lemonade"
by John Oates]
♪ Give me sunshine
and lemonade ♪
♪ [indistinct] on a holiday ♪
♪ Wanna dance all night
in the soft moonlight ♪
♪ So hot, so high,
feeling just so right ♪
♪ Yeah, I dig it ♪
♪ I burned my tongue
on a [indistinct] ♪
♪ And on top of that,
got a flat ♪
♪ And I broke my heel
trying to change the wheel ♪
♪ Gotta get away,
run to the sun ♪
♪ Have some fun,
there's an ice cold lemonade ♪
♪ Ooh, I think
you know what I'm saying ♪
♪ Keep it back in the
[indistinct] with the fuzz ♪
♪ Make me wanna start
misbehaving, yeah ♪
♪ I think you know
what I'm talking about ♪
♪ Now give me some of that
sunshine and lemonade ♪
♪ [indistinct] on a holiday ♪
♪ Wanna dance all night
in the soft moonlight ♪
♪ So hot, so high,
feeling just so right ♪
♪ Sunshine and lemonade ♪
♪ Watch the sunset ♪
♪ Slipping through
my favorite shades... ♪
My first gringofriend
in Mexico.
Señor Bickford.
Professional football,
great surfer.
Jackson...
mi nueva novia.
[Jackson laughs]
Okay. Hello.
Who also happens to be
mi nueva hija,Chilo.
-Uh...
-[laughs]
When did you get
a daughter?
I ordered one.
Long time ago.
-She just got here.
-I--
[speaking in Spanish]
[object crunching]
[chuckles]
What did he say?
Uh, to be a gentleman.
Huh.
-Jackson is your papa?
-Yeah. [chuckles softly]
You're lucky.
Lo de Marcos
loves him very much.
He-- he brings us pride.
Him?
[soft Latin music]
[indistinct chatter]
So, how many boys
have kissed you?
That's--
I'm not telling you that.
-[chuckles]
-[Chilo] Okay.
So, how many Mexican boys
have you kissed?
[Marge]
It's easy. None.
Well, now it's one.
[Marge chuckles]
All right,
let's bring it in.
-[speaking in Spanish]
-[Jackson] Azus.
Stay positivo.
[whistle blows]
Whistle doesn't even--
bring it in.
Atención.
Come on. All right.
We're two players short,
so everybody's gotta play
the whole game,
but we can do it, okay?
Go ahead. All right.
García, Placencia, Veneda,
Rodríguez, Morales, Guerra,
Martínez, Avalos,
González, Bickford.
-[laughing]
-[speaking in Spanish]
No, no, no, no, no. No.
Mi, mija. Margie.
Okay? All right.
-D-- Dad, no, please, no.
-No, Anna's kid is sick.
No, I will not do it.
Please, please don't make me.
You need a jersey.
Here, wear mine.
[both speaking in Spanish]
[speaking in Spanish]
Mi equipo, yo jofe-- yo jefe?
What is it?
What do I say? Just talk to her.
Hey, you know what,
tell her that she is lucky
that-- that she's a good goalie.
-[speaking in Spanish]
-[tuts]
[speaking in Spanish]
They don't want me here.
I'm an expert at this part.
Oh, Nayeli will get over it.
Eventually. [laughs]
-She's so pissed.
-This is how it was back home.
-I'm not going to do it.
-[Jackson] You have to.
-No!
-[Jackson] Yeah.
My house, my rules,
remember?
-This is so unfair.
-[Jackson] No, you know what?
Eating termites off a stick to
stay alive, tha-- that's unfair.
This is Mexican football.
You know, and you're right
with the drama being a big deal
down here,
so if you humiliate me,
I'm gonna hate you
for the rest of my life.
Okay.
That's what dads are for.
Oh, two days
and you're an expert?
Does this make me look fat?
Proud.
Go.
-[whistle blows]
-[Marge] Oh, my God.
[Jackson laughs]
[Marge] Hola.
[speaking in Spanish]
All right,
let's go, let's go, let's go.
Bickford, go!
[speaking in Spanish]
[Jackson speaking Spanish]
[upbeat music]
That's good, that's good,
stay, stay, stay.
-There you go, there you go.
-[Padre speaking in Spanish]
Open up, open up.
[Padre speaking in Spanish]
Keep with her. Go, go!
That's it,
that's it, that's it!
-That's a foul!
-[Padre speaking in Spanish]
Hey,
how do you say foul?
-Faul.
Faul!
♪
No, no, no, no, no, no.
[Jackson screams]
-Yes!
-[crowd clapping]
Way to go, Nayeli!
[Padre and Jackson groan]
[Jackson] Bien! [grunts]
-Yes! [whoops]
-[Padre laughs]
-Hey! Bien.
-Nayeli!
Ah, she is hard to like,
but I'm glad she's on our team.
There you go,
there you go, there you are.
-[Padre speaking in Spanish]
-Right, right, go, go!
Perfect, perfect.
-[Padre screams]
-[Jackson] Yes!
-[girl whoops]
[Nayeli screaming] Goal!
[Jackson]
Yes, baby! Yes!
-[team screaming]
-Yes! Bien!
[upbeat Latin music]
-[Padre speaking Spanish]
-[Chilo whistling]
Gracias, amiga.
-Not gringa?
-También.
Gringa y amiga.
[Jackson humming deeply]
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Ladies and gentlemen!
We are...
one and one!
[cheering]
[Marge retching and coughing]
[Jackson retches]
[coughing]
-[toilet flushes]
-[Marge sighs]
[Jackson hums]
Ooh. Jesus.
[Jackson whistles, exhales]
You have to start
treating yourself better.
You first.
Don't bullshit me, Margie.
You make yourself sick, too.
Did Elsa tell you that?
-She said it was a possibility.
-[Marge] Yeah, well, I did.
But now I don't.
You still drink.
Yeah, well,
how would I know?
Because you fall down
and then you throw up,
-that's a clue.
-No, no, no.
About your bulimia,
smartass.
I did it to get rid of the parts
me that I didn't like.
And then when it was over,
it was the only parts
that were left.
[Jackson laughs]
That sounds like the lie
I tell myself about drinking.
[chuckles]
There are more parts of me
that I like now.
What, now that Chilo
was being nice to you?
No.
Maybe because you are.
I mean, I jumped
into the middle of your life
and you didn't make me
feel bad about it.
Well...
you're my daughter.
So, when are we gonna
start acting
like we care
about each other?
We care about each other.
Show me.
Stop drinking.
Okay.
Promise me
you'll stop drinking.
[groans]
The only promise
I was able to keep
was the one about
not making any more promises.
[chuckles dryly]
[emotional guitar music]
I'll try.
Okay?
[chattering]
-[drill whirring]
-[Jackson groans]
Here.
The sun will give us
enough electricity?
Guaranteed.
And yet you still
don't believe in miracles.
I do not.
Patrick, I believe in science.
You should give it a try.
Ah, Jesus on a fucking bike,
it works.
Jackson.
What?
What's wrong with riding a bike?
What do you mean,
"What's wrong?"
I mean,
Jesus doesn't ride a...
a fucking bike.
He rides a-- a good bike.
A nice bike.
What?
You need to work
on your tolerance, padre.
-[switch clicks]
-[fans whir on]
[crowd applauds]
-There you go.
-[Padre speaking Spanish]
What is the good people
from Lo de Marcos owe you?
-Uh, same as you always. Nada.
-Come on, please.
-You have a daughter now.
-All right. 50 pesos.
Okay.
100.
Don't spoil me, Patrick.
You know
I don't handle it very well.
[baby cooing]
Hey.
I'll pray for you.
Eh, pray for them.
I'm good.
[calm guitar music]
[speaking in Spanish]
[player speaking in Spanish]
[players yelling indistinctly]
[whistle blows]
[tense music]
[player speaking in Spanish]
[whistle blows]
[Jackson] Yes!
-[upbeat music]
-Yeah!
[teammates giggling]
[teammates whooping]
El Bichos are two and one!
[cheering and applauding]
-[Chilo speaking in Spanish]
-[Padre speaking in Spanish]
Move, move, move, move!
[dramatic music]
Who's marking?
[Chilo groans]
[Jackson sighs]
That was a tough loss,
ladies.
But, hey,
we're still in contention
for the league final.
And maybe
even the friendship cup.
All right?
[speaking in Spanish]
Hey, hey, hey.
Uh, only if it's for good luck.
There's no such thing
as luck.
What about my lucky shirt?
Maybe Chilo
will buy you this.
Oh, my God.
This town is too small.
There are no secrets
at the plaza.
Only chisme.
Chisme, chisme.
Is Chilo a good guy?
He goes to church
and he takes care of his mom.
That matters.
-Is my dad?
-No, he doesn't go to church.
Yeah, but,
I mean, is he a good guy?
He is to me.
You've been good for him,
Marge.
-He's been good for me.
-Is that why he quit drinking?
Well,
I hope that one's for him.
[Elsa] Mm-hmm.
You know what?
I'm gonna miss you.
[chuckles softly]
[Jackson] Yes!
A month ago,
I was a drunk soccer coach.
Hanging out in Mexico
without a peso to my name.
Today,
I'm a single dad.
Hanging out in Mexico
without a peso to my name.
-How does it feel?
-[Jackson] So different.
[Jackson grunts]
You gonna be okay?
Yeah, I mean,
I'm gonna miss you like crazy,
but now that I have
a real dad,
it'll be easier.
Hmm. I'm a real dad now, huh?
Sometimes too real.
I'll take that
as a compliment.
Hey, last night.
Let's, uh--
let's take a walk on the beach.
See me a full moon.
I'll show you where I used to
bang my head against it.
Oh. Jeez. Dad, I'm sorry.
It's my last night,
so I told Chilo we would--
Oh.
[exhales] Okay.
Look.
Be careful on your last night.
Especially
if there's a full moon.
Wha--
we're going surfing.
-Yeah.
Well, you know, you've been
doing a lot of that lately.
I just...
I just hope
he's wearing a leash,
-is all I'm--
-Dad.
Sorry.
Just doing my job, kiddo.
I won't be late.
Not that
it's any of your business.
Okay.
Have fun.
♪
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
Sorry
for being late and stupid.
Well,
you come by it honestly.
-Good surf?
-Yeah. Made some fun ones.
Yeah, naked surfing
-under a full moon...
-[Marge groans]
...is a tradition down here.
And Chilo
is a traditionalist.
Uh, when is--
when is the bus?
I want you to keep it, Dad.
[photo rustling]
[birds chirping]
[vehicle approaching]
[Jackson] Went by fast,
though, didn't it?
It was the best month
of my life.
You know, they're probably
gonna put me in boarding school.
"Sorry, kid, your mom died,
but we have tea times."
[sniffs]
I love you, Margie.
Where's the bus?
Yeah.
How--
[Jackson sighs]
Aw, you know what?
The bus was yesterday.
Yesterday?
Yeah, see,
it's, like, martesis Tuesday,
miércoles is Wednesday.
I always get
the two mixed up.
God.
I wonder how the surf is.
-So, I'm not leaving?
-[Jackson] Not today.
[both chuckling]
But...
no more naked surfing.
What if
there's a full moon out?
Now, don't. Don't even--
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait--
[laughs] Wait!
[upbeat Latin dance music]
[cheering]
[Padre speaking in Spanish]
[all cheering]
[Jackson shouting]
[Spanish reggaeton song playing]
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
[all chanting] Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What's this?
Well,
this is quite an honor.
[Marge] Yeah.
Is Azu getting married?
Hmm. Not yet.
She's only 15.
-She's 15?
-[Jackson] Mm-hmm.
I'm older than Azu? Whoa.
Wow. She's so pretty.
Azucena is inviting you
to her quinceañera.
Her what?
It's a celebration,
as Azucena
is crowned queen of her life,
takes command of her body
and walks into womanhood.
-Is that a translation?
-Word for word.
[Marge chuckles]
You know, I think that Azu
walked into womanhood
a few miles back.
Well, girls grow up fast
in Mexico.
[calm music]
[birds chirping]
You know,
my older sister wore this dress
to her quince años.
And I wore it to mine.
What about
your little sister?
[Elsa] Well,
she wanted to get married in it,
but it didn't fit.
Ah, look who's here.
Quinceañera rule number one.
Never look more beautiful
than the queen.
[laughs]
We broke that rule, big time.
[both chuckling]
Wow.
[water splashing]
[crickets chirping]
[gentle Latin guitar music]
[speaking in Spanish]
♪
[sighs]
[speaking in Spanish]
[all applauding]
And you are the queen
of my life.
How can you know
so soon?
Because I do.
[playing trumpet]
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
[speaking in Spanish]
Hey.
Are-- are you gonna
keep your hair like that?
Yes.
All right.
♪
With your permission,
señor.
Stop with the bowing.
Dance.
That's a miracle.
What, that I haven't
killed him yet?
-Vamos.
-No.
-Vamos, vamos.
-Here.
[upbeat dance music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
♪ Ram-pa-pam-pam,
ram-pa-pam ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Ram-pa-pam-pam,
ram-pa-pam ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Feel the beat
pound, pound... ♪
Hey, keep dancing.
Hey, congratulations.
No, no, no. I'm good.
[speaking in Spanish]
[whispers] One.
[Jackson groans]
[tense music]
[Spanish song
playing in distance]
[indistinct chattering]
[all laughing]
[Marge] Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
[all shouting, laughing]
-[speaking in Spanish]
-[spitting]
Oh, no.
[all]
Dos, tres, cuatro, cinco.
Wait, wait, wait.
[speaking in Spanish]
[Marge]
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
[speaking in Spanish]
Okay, okay, okay.
[all shouting, laughing]
[speaking in Spanish]
[all] Uno, dos,
tres, cuatro, cinco.
[laughing] Your turn!
[screams]
-[all laughing]
-[speaking in Spanish]
[girl 1 speaking in Spanish]
[girl 2 speaking in Spanish]
What-- what's up?
What's up?
-[Azu speaking in Spanish]
-[girl 1] No.
[girl 2]
Should we tell her?
[Azu]
It's just that...
Chilo sleeps
with all the gringas.
Oh, my God.
[Azu] I'm so sorry.
[waves crashing]
Dad.
Dad!
You were right.
Chilo isn't a good guy.
[bottles clinking]
[Jackson]
Wha-- what about Chilo?
Huh?
[Jackson groans]
I'm sorry.
Margie, look,
I've been drinking a long time.
I mean, you don't learn
how to surf in one day.
-[Marge groans]
-C'mon, Margie, it's a process.
We had a promise!
[sobs] And you broke it.
[crying]
You know,
Mom was right about you.
[sobs]
I shouldn't have come.
[footsteps departing]
[somber music]
[street din]
[sobbing]
[banging on door]
[Marge]
My dad started drinking again.
[Marge whimpers]
[engine starts, revs]
[tense music]
[Jackson] Where is she?
Are you still drunk?
-[thudding]
-You hurt my daughter.
[Chilo] And you didn't?
[Jackson panting]
[Marge]
So, are all men assholes?
Mi abuela will think so.
[both laughing]
I can't say, though.
I've never had a boyfriend.
-You're a virgin?
-[Azu] Of course I am.
-Come on!
-I am.
Oh, but if someone
is special, yes.
If I'm getting married one day,
of course.
But until then,
local guys can do it
with the gringas,
I don't care.
I'm sorry.
No, I deserve it.
I was stupid.
Oye.
Weak. Not stupid.
A little bit stupid.
[both laughing]
A little bit, yes.
[laughs]
[keys jangling]
-Hey.
-I have nothing to say to you.
No. It's Margie.
She ran away.
She must be trying
to get back across the border.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know.
[speaking in Spanish]
[Spanish music
playing in distance]
[dogs barking in distance]
[bus rumbling]
[brakes screeching]
Get in.
You're gonna need this.
Let's go find her.
[speaking in Spanish]
Be brief,
don't tell them too much,
and they will let you pass.
-Okay?
-[Marge chuckles]
Thank you
for being so kind to me.
[Azu] Bye.
Oh, and, Marge.
Smile.
[chuckles]
[officer]
Country of birth?
-America.
-Uh, North, South, Central?
Um, North.
-Canada?
-Uh, no. The United States.
Okay. Passport.
Oh, I don't have one.
Uh, you need one.
I'm sorry.
Well, when I came to Mexico,
um, I didn't need one.
And I'm American.
Right.
Well, they don't check, we do.
Do you have
other documents?
Well,
you're undocumented, amiga.
-Um...
-[officer] Next.
[paper rustling]
[engine rumbling]
-Azu.
-What are you doing here?
-They wouldn't let me in.
-But why? You're an American.
An undocumented one,
apparently.
[scoffs]
Welcome to my world.
Follow me.
[upbeat Spanish
dance music playing]
[inaudible]
Hey. We are fine.
But it's not cheap.
-It's 1,000.
-Pesos?
[speaking in Spanish]
Dollars.
Okay.
This is the longest
of long shots, man.
And that's a miracle.
We're looking for your daughter
and you're sober.
-Yeah, barely.
-Barely a miracle?
Barely sober.
You need to be thankful
for the smallest gift.
Trust me.
-And him.
-[groans]
Man,
you make atheism hard.
Dude, that's what I do
for a living.
[road din]
[brakes screeching]
[crickets chirping]
-[speaking in Spanish]
-Uh, the ring.
Oh.
[man] Okay.
[speaking in Spanish]
[Marge]
I haven't lived long enough
to do
a lot of stupid shit,
if you don't count tracking down
my loser dad in Mexico.
But following a psycho
into the desert...
-[smuggler whistling]
-...gotta top my list.
[wind howling]
-[speaking in Spanish]
-Oh, it's lunchtime.
[snorts]
-[thudding]
-[Marge grunts]
[high-pitched ringing,
dramatic music]
[Azu groans] No! [grunts]
[Azu speaking in Spanish]
-Help!
-[Marge] Hey!
[loud banging]
[Marge whispers]
Now come on!
[Azu whimpering]
[both panting]
-[Marge] Wait! Wait!
-[Azu] No, no, no, no, don't!
[necklace jangling]
[eagle calls]
[mysterious guitar music]
[insects chittering]
Oh, come on.
-[Azu pants]
-Are you good?
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Okay.
There's the highway.
We're close.
[brakes screeching]
-Morning, gentlemen.
-Good morning, sir.
Passports, please.
And, uh...
where are you guys from?
San Diego, California.
Bakersfield, California.
What?
-What?
-You're from Bakersfield?
Yes.
I'm an anchor baby.
My parents got deported
when I was a kid.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I get the whole thing.
But you never told me
you're from Bakersfield.
-Yes, I did.
-No.
If you told me
that you were from Bakersfield,
I would have said,
"Yeah, he's from Bakersfield."
Gentlemen.
Oh, thank you, sir.
-We had breakfast this time...
-We've never had breakfast.
-...and then we talked--
-Guys!
-Oh, I'm sorry.
-Let's keep it going.
[engine starts]
[PA announcement] Dr. Foster,
please come to the ER.
Dr. Foster to the ER.
[phone keyboard clicking]
[phone ringing]
Bueno.Azucena?
-Sí, sí.
-[Jackson whispers] Hey!
[speaking in Spanish]
[door opening]
-Marge Bickford?
-Yeah.
Your bloodwork is normal,
but you're very dehydrated.
What happened?
Football injury.
Rough game.
Let's take care
of your eye.
[door creaks open]
[indistinct]
You sure
you don't want to stay?
Totally and completely sure.
But you're here.
It could be so hard
to get back in.
You know who thinks everyone
wants to live in America?
Americans. [chuckles]
Now, it's fine
to be the neighbor.
And I'll keep
an eye on you
while you're keeping an eye
on your dad.
-I've given up on him.
-Don't.
He hasn't given up on you.
[Marge] Yeah, well,
it sure feels like he has.
What is he doing here?
I called.
[Marge] Azu,
you should have asked me.
He was amazingly
not there for me
when I needed him.
He's new
at being your dad.
[solemn music]
Be kind.
I'm gonna need you, Dad.
I'm here.
Come on.
Let's go home.
♪
Jackson.
Los Bichos are going to
the friendship cup in Tijuana.
Let me see that.
We've been selected
as Nayarit state team.
What's it say?
[speaking in Spanish]
-Yeah, I know. In English.
-We're going to Tijuana.
-That's it.
-[Jackson] Okay, cool.
Let's go tell them.
[upbeat music]
[team cheering]
[chattering, laughing]
[speaking in Spanish]
[laughing]
[cheering]
[chanting] !Bichos, Bichos!
[chanting in Spanish]
[all speaking in Spanish]
[cheering]
[Jackson chuckles]
[music stops]
[indistinct chatter]
[speaking in Spanish]
[all cheering]
Gracias, Padre.
[indistinct chattering]
-I told you.
-[Jackson chuckles]
-[Padre speaking Spanish]
-[Jackson] Come on, guys.
Look sharp.
[Padre speaking Spanish]
Is that Lem?
Is that Large Marge?
No, it can't be.
Her ass isn't big enough.
[girl chuckles]
Sure looks like her,
but-- but she looks good.
[girl] I thought
these guys were from Mexico.
They're supposed to be.
Lem's dad lives in Mexico.
Jackson Bickford was the best
soccer player I've ever seen.
All instinct, no restraint.
Looks like he's
El Bicho's coach.
Y'all need to
level up today, girls.
Go. Get out there.
Go, warm up. Let's go.
Come on.
[sighs]
["Ron Pom Pom"
by Kalvaro]
♪
[audience cheers]
[speaking in Spanish]
[heartfelt music]
You already won.
Have fun.
-[speaking in Spanish]
-[clapping]
[sportscaster speaking
in Spanish]
[upbeat Latin music]
-[speaking in Spanish]
-[all applauding]
[Jackson] Move it over!
She's open, pass!
-Yeah!
-[audience cheers]
[whistle blows]
[both cheering]
Attagirl, that was goal!
I'm back.
No, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
-Yes!
-[whistle blows]
[audience cheering]
-All right.
-[Cathy] Good job, ladies!
[chanting]
Let's go back.
Come on. Hurry up!
[sportscaster speaking
in Spanish]
-[Padre speaking in Spanish]
-[Cathy] Let's go!
[audience cheering]
[Jackson]
Come on. Get on her!
[Cathy] Let's go, ladies.
[Jackson] What are you doing?
What are you doing? [groans]
[both] Fuck!
-Feels good. Huh?
-Yeah.
[Padre speaking in Spanish]
[Jackson] Rápido. Come on.
Go, go, go, go, go!
-[whistle blows]
-[both shouting] Hey! Hey!
-[Azucena speaking in Spanish]
-[Jackson] Unbelievable!
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, don't worry.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
-[Azucena speaking in Spanish]
-Come on, guys!
Come on, kid, come on!
[upbeat music]
[cheering]
[chanting] Gringa, Gringa!
[all cheering]
[chanting]
!Bichos, Bichos!
[engine rumbling]
[Marge clears throat]
-Hey.
[Jackson]
So, you beat your old team?
Yeah.
Well, how does that
make you feel?
This feels bigger.
Good answer.
[lighthearted music]
[waves crashing]
We are here...
because of God's grace,
and the promise
that Marge Bickford
will be remembered well.
Humility...
and forgiveness
are the gifts
we leave to our children.
Rest in peace.
Jackson.
"Marge and I came here
on our honeymoon.
Back when
we were so in love.
When life looked easy.
And everything...
was still out
in front of us.
[sighs]
[voice breaking] It's the only
place that I've ever felt whole.
Which is..."
[sighs] Sorry. It's hard.
"...which is why..."
[sobbing]
Come here.
"Which is why...
I came back here.
I need
to thank Marge for that.
And her daughter
for all the love
I'm feeling right now."
[sniffles]
Mom would have loved
you're with me here right now.
She never stopped
trying to make my life better.
And all of a sudden...
it is.
Um...
[Marge sighs]
[bittersweet music]
I love you.
I know.
[waves crashing]
[lighthearted music]
-Thank you.
-There you go, baby.
-Mm. Delicious.
-Oh, forgot the knife.
[phone ringing]
It's your daughter, again.
Hey, kid.
-[Marge over phone] Hi, Dad.
-Say "hi."
-Oh, hi, Elsa.
-[Elsa] Hi.
-How you doing?
-Oh, uh, yeah, I'm okay.
-I just really miss you.
-Good. You're supposed to.
But I'm here.
-Here.
-[Marge] Oh, man, I'm jealous.
-Thanks for getting Internet.
-[Jackson] Oh, no worries.
I actually kind of
like the machine.
-[Marge] Huh.
-Hey.
You're gonna do
great up there.
[Marge]
When are you gonna come up?
-[Jackson] Thanksgiving.
-Wha--
Thanksgiving?
That's, like, a month away.
[Jackson]
Remember, months go fast.
Yeah. Okay.
-Bye.
-[Jackson smacks lips]
Hey, um,
you're that hotshot futbolista
on that full ride.
Uh, maybe.
I'm the hotshot Mexicano
on that full ride, too.
-Um, mucho gusto.
-Mucho gusto.
-Fernando.
-Marge.
[Fernando]
You played for Los Bichos.
Yeah, I did.
[Fernando]
Wow. They're legendary.
Sí.
[upbeat music]
♪ Ooh, come on now,
oh, come on now ♪
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
♪ We can go ♪
♪ Any place that we dream of ♪
♪ 'Cause I know you know ♪
♪ We can spend
the rest of our life together ♪
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
♪ Maybe this is love,
let's kiss and see ♪
♪ I wanna make you
believe in me ♪
♪ Anywhere you wanna go,
I'll take you there ♪
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
♪ If this is everything
you're looking for ♪
♪ You're never going back
to Southern California ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
♪ We can go ♪
♪ Any place that we dream of ♪
♪ 'Cause I know you know ♪
♪ We can spend
the rest of our life together ♪
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
♪ We can go ♪
♪ Oh, we can go ♪
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
♪ 'Cause I know you know ♪
♪ We can spend
the rest of our life together ♪
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
♪ We can go ♪
♪ We can go now ♪
♪ Any place that we dream of ♪
♪ 'Cause I know you know ♪
♪ We can spend
the best of our life together ♪
♪ [lyrics in Spanish] ♪
♪
[music fades]