Uh, you little fucking
- Go, go!
- Dickheads!
You think you're stronger than
me?
I'll eat your fucking face off!
Where's your brother? Where's
that shit?
Come on, come on, come on.
Fucking shit! You little shit,
I'll...
Woo!
You wanna hurry up?
You've been throwing half
shovel fulls all goddamn day!
Sick of it!
Dad's?
Probably looking for it now.
Where are we gonna go, Henry?
Far away from here.
How much money you got?
Not much.
I still gotta stop at Mr.
Barrow's
and get my pay.
We're gonna need all we can get.
- Hey. Mr. Barrow, it's me.
Jacob.
Jacob, how are you, son?
I'm good.
I was just wondering if I
could get my pay for last week.
Yes, of course. Come on up.
I wanna tell you boys a little
more
about the Battle of Khe Sanh.
One of the most important
battles of the entire Vietnam war,
if not in fact, the longest and
bloodiest.
6,000 Marines and their
garrison were held under siege
by the North Vietnamese Army.
And on January 21st, 1968,
shooting-
- I, I'm Sorry, Mr. Barrow,
- and...
but we really need to be going.
Can I please get my pay?
Sure can. My wallet's
on the kitchen table.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Barrow.
Say boys, did you happen to see
the military transport up on the
hill?
I haven't heard one
like that in these parts
for some while, you know.
Peculiar sound, that vehicle.
And Miss Sally told me
it's heading way out north
to Pithole, I suppose.
Pithole, you said. Are you
sure about that, Mr. Barrow?
I just wanted to enjoy the
summer.
Hang by the Creek.
We're finally free.
This is more important.
Come on, Henry.
He's an old blind man.
Who even knows if it's true.
It's worth looking. It's Mom.
I know that, but we
don't even know where.
You heard Mr. Barrow. She's
there.
We're going.
- She left us.
Remember?
She didn't want us, so I don't
want her.
So what would you
rather, go back to Daddy?
Get beat so bad this time it
don't heal?
Keep mowing grass, picking
weeds and shoveling asphalt?
I'm done with all that.
This is our only shot.
Weren't things better when mom
was around?
She just didn't see it.
She'll come back.
- And what if she doesn't?
She will.
This is no time to be scared,
Jacob.
I'm not scared.
Well good.
Listen, we need a better life.
We deserve a better life
with Mom. That can happen.
We know where she is for the
first time.
And we've got no one else.
Okay, if we're gonna do
this, we've got to be prepared.
We've got our backpacks,
but we've got to get creative
and find more supplies.
I have some ideas.
Yeah, I don't now. He
didn't show up for work today.
I don't know what we're gonna
do.
So there I was in
the middle of the camp.
The helicopter camp just outside
Pleiku.
A little after midnight,
February 7th, 1964.
Sorry, but, uh, thanks.
I always love hearing those war
stories.
No problem, boys.
Enjoy the soup and beans.
Okay.
So we're here and Mom
is all the way up here.
It's a hard journey, but
it's definitely doable.
So we'll enter at the viaduct,
then move on to the boulders,
then the lake, then the
pines, and then Mom.
We should get there in a
few days if we're lucky.
W-what is it?
Dead people.
Looks like sacred land,
so don't touch or step on
anything.
Hey! Let's go.
Hey, wait up.
Whatever happened to Becky
Lawson?
What do you
mean, what happened to her?
I dumped her.
She was hooking up with Tommy
Briggs.
The hockey player?
Yeah, the hockey player.
Did you guys, you know, do it?
You're an idiot.
What?
Henry. Hey.
- Mm.
- What,
what's with your neck?
What do you mean, what's with
my neck?
It's not right.
Ah! Shit!
Hand me the gauze.
Yeah, you're just like
your fucking whore brother.
Look at me!
You ever see that before?
It's probably just
some kids messing around.
You want some?
Are you okay?
I can help with that bandage, if
you want.
Mm-mm.
Jacob.
Wait. Wait.
Wait.
No, no!
Henry? Henry!
Henry.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on.
Henry, hey, its gonna be, it's
okay.
You're okay. Come on.
Easy, come on.
Hey, your neck looks pretty bad.
Maybe we should go get it
checked out.
We can always take a road to
town.
Hey Henry, you doing all right?
Henry?
Henry? Hello?
If you wanna ignore me, fine.
This is your stupid
idea. Just remember that.
I just wanted to hang by
the creek this summer.
Is that too much to ask for?
Hey, are you gonna answer me?
What's your problem, man?
Henry!
Jacob!
Are you okay?
I told you not to mess with
anything!
What did you do?
Fuck!
Come on.
Come on, buddy. Come on.
You can make it. You can make
it, Jacob.
Come on. You're gonna walk.
Come on, Jacob.
It's gonna be okay, Jacob.
It's gonna be okay. I've got
you.
I've got you. You're gonna be
okay.
You're gonna be okay. It's
Henry, buddy.
It's Henry. Henry's got you.
I've got you. You're gonna be
okay.
Come here. You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay. I got ya.
The blood of the male.
The blood of the young man.
Hey, you, ah...
You doing all right?
Yeah, I think so.
I think my neck is almost
healed.
That's good.
We don't have to keep going.
Given all that's happened.
It might be time to head back.
Really?
Yeah, sure.
I just thought...
What?
Nah, forget it.
I just thought that if Mom saw
us,
it would make a difference.
Maybe she would miss us or
remember us
or something, I don't know.
Let's keep going.
Yeah?
Yeah.
We don't have to, you know.
I want to.
- Mom?
Come with me.
What are you doing
here? You can't be here.
It's not safe.
We came for you, Mom.
We want you to come home.
Oh, my boys. I can't come home.
I'm sorry.
Why not? Why don't you love us?
What did we do?
Listen to me. He can't see you.
You have no idea the danger
you're in.
You need to go.
- What are you
talking about, Mom?
- Go, go.
- Mom, wait a minute.
- No, listen.
- Mom, slow down.
- Go, go.
- Mom, there's something...
- Go and don't look back.
Just go.
- No, Mom-
- Go!
Hey, they didn't take
your knife, did they?
No, it, it's in this pocket.
Got it. Got it.
We can't just leave.
We've come all this way.
I know. We have to get her
alone.
I know, but how?
We can wait until they're
asleep.
Welcome.
The blood of the young male is
pure.
It has special rehabilitative
properties.
We lust for youth,
and youth we shall receive.
Longevity.
Vitality.
And you could give it to me.
Some people, well,
they would say that I'm
stealing.
But I'm not.
It's not personal.
No. It's just necessary.
These are made out of wood.
Very strong wood.
I'm gonna take this
and I'm gonna pierce it
into your heart.
You won't feel anything.
Don't be afraid.
You're not the first
and you certainly won't be the
last.
Yeah.
Ah.
I sacrifice onto the!
Ah!
You boys may not know
it, but you saved me.
You saved us.
We want you to come with us,
Mom.
I will, in time.
These people need me. I
recruited them.
I need to make this right
with them and with you.
- Mom, please.
- I love you boys.
I love you very much.
And I promise, I will explain
everything to you in time,
but for now I need you
to go and make me proud.
And I will see you again
when our paths cross.
I love you, Henry.
I love you, Jacob.
You know, I'm glad we went.
I'm not so sure.
Why?
Well, maybe you were right.
Maybe we should have let it be.
I'm sorry I pushed you so hard.
No, I'm glad we found out.
Found out what?
That moms still loves us.
Yeah. Yeah, me too.
- Hey, Henry?
- Yeah.
You think we can
hang out by the creek now?
Yeah, I think
that's a great idea.
You know, maybe I can get you
a job with Mr. Barrow.
He ain't so bad.
- Yeah, maybe.