-[gym din]
-[clock ticking]
[muffled rock instrumental
plays]
[exhales sharply]
[foot tapping]
[deep sigh]
[muffled gym din]
[knocking on door]
-Sam, they're here.
-[Sam] Yeah. Be right out.
[ring clatters]
[exhales sharply]
[man 1] Hey let's go, Sam!
[man 2] Yeah, let's go!
[people cheering and applauding]
Delayed flight.
He feels terrible.
[Sam]
What does that mean for us?
He doesn't have all afternoon.
He's got early flight
this evening.
There's some bubblegum chewer
in North Dakota.
-All right, we'll get it done.
-His name's Alec.
-[Sam] Hey, Alec. Sam.
-Pleasure to meet you.
-I am so sorry I'm late.
-[Sam] Don't worry about it.
We'll have you out of here
in no time.
Thanks, Blake. Good looking out.
Wish these things
weren't so fast,
but be assured,
my focus is on you today.
We are so glad
to be here to witness it.
Thank you for involving us
in your world records.
[exhales] All Shane.
Oh, I don't know about all that.
It's good to see
how we do under pressure.
My unofficial manager.
Hey look, I want
to get this on our social.
-You good with that?
-Sure.
[Shane] All right, cool.
Hey, everybody,
it's your main man, Shane,
live here at my gym, the RCC,
and I'm with the incomparable
Sam Johnson
and the World Record
Federation today.
-Give a shout out, guys.
-Hey guys.
Getting ready
to break some records, right?
That's what we're here for.
That's right, we're going to
shatter them right here.
We're going to get at it
at the top of the hour,
so check back in with us.
-[man] You okay if I start?
-Yes.
[Alec] I just have a few
paperwork items to go over.
Make sure we have the correct
names and exercises listed.
Your full name
is Samantha Aiden Johnson,
-is that correct?
-Yeah.
Love the name Aiden.
Thanks. It's my dad's.
I bet he's really excited
to hear about this today.
Uh, he actually
passed away last year.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
-Don't worry about it.
You know,
one of the perks of my job
is that I really
get to learn about
some interesting and new things.
Uh, a lot of crazy things, too,
but I won't get into that.
Uh, but I've really enjoyed
getting to know your sport.
How long have you been doing it?
[Sam] About four years now.
And were you an athlete
before or something?
[Sam] Uh, gymnastics growing up,
-some bodybuilding.
-That's awesome.
[Shane] Let me
sort out the details.
I got this.
Sam, stay in the headspace.
We have to lock in soon.
All right?
I'll let you know
if you need to sign anything.
-All right.
-Okay.
[Alec] Thank you.
-I didn't mean--
-It's fine. You didn't know.
-Were they close?
-Oh, yeah, very.
But she's good.
She's ready for this.
-All right. What do you got?
-Just right here.
All right.
-[Sam] Hey.
-[Monica] Hey.
-Can I pass this to you?
-[Monica] Yeah.
How was class this morning?
[sighs]
Brutal as always, you know.
How are you feeling
about this one?
-We'll see. [chuckles]
-Oh, you got it.
[Sam] Do you have to?
I'm getting
a free month out of this,
so I'm getting it all.
[Sam] Just a month?
[Monica] So this is the one,
over 1,800 pounds in a minute?
How many reps
are you trying to do?
Ten.
-Where does this one fit?
-Less.
Is it still five movements
in 30 minutes?
-[Sam] That's the goal.
-Okay.
I told her she should try
and get some money out of this.
Yeah, she at least talked to
Shane about a free membership.
And for, like, a year.
It's a mock competition.
Just testing my limits.
Yeah, come on, Sam,
what do you get out of this?
You get a sponsorship
with someone?
No way. I want in.
I don't want to jinx it.
Plus, you didn't train
a lot harder.
That's low, man.
This is going to be awesome.
You know, you guys
don't have to stay for this.
-Well it's too late now.
-I wouldn't miss this.
-[Sam chuckles] Thanks.
-[cellphone rings]
-Oh, hey.
-Oh, thanks.
Mom.
[phone chimes]
-Hey, Mom.
-There she is!
My baby, the record breaker.
[scoffs] We haven't started yet.
[Sam's mom]
You haven't?
Late start. Pretty soon, though.
-[woman] Good luck, Sam.
-Thanks.
[Sam's mom]
Are you still warmed up?
Yeah.
Oh, hey. Look what I found.
Did you go through
my box of things?
Things? These are not things.
And yes. Yes, I did.
If I can't be there,
then I want to remember
all the other records you broke.
-Oh, my gosh.
-I am so proud of you.
Everything you pushed through
this year.
I know your dad is, too.
He is smiling on you.
-Yeah.
-[Sam's mom] No, he is.
Uh, got a call
with a new sponsor.
Should, uh, open some doors
if I can do this,
Maybe bring in a little money,
at least help with comp fees.
-That's good, right?
-Yeah.
It's not official yet,
but it should be soon.
Good for you.
You put that money to good use.
Is Charlie there?
-No.
-Hmm.
I understand.
But you know what?
I will be your lifeline.
If you need anything,
just call me.
Will do.
Your dad would say,
-"Go break some records."
Yeah. Thanks, Mom.
-Love you.
-I love you.
Bye.
[gym din]
[machine beeps]
[screw rattling]
[soft whirring]
[upbeat music plays]
Looks like
you haven't started yet.
Cool.
Cool, I'm glad I didn't miss it.
Um, you're looking good,
you're looking ready.
[music plays faintly
on speakers]
[Sam sniffs, sighs]
[Charlie sighs]
-What?
-[Sam scoffs]
Do you remember
the last thing you said to me?
How about,
"Hey, thanks for coming."
How about, "Hey,
I didn't mean what I said."
The only reason you're here
is to save face.
-I'm not here to save face.
-Okay.
I thought
you'd be done by now, but--
[clicks tongue]
Uh, cool. You know?
You got this.
You can totally do this.
-Oh, permission.
-I'm just saying--
If you wanted to talk,
you should have called me back.
Why are you doing this now?
Like nothing's going on.
-I've been texting you.
-You know I hate texting.
What do you want me to do, Sam?
We don't live together anymore.
We cannot pick this up
where we left off.
-I'm just trying--
-[Sam] No.
Hey, Charlie. How you've been?
-Sam, you good?
-Yeah. Okay.
All right, a few more minutes.
I'm going to need
your signatures.
Okay, yeah.
-Be there in a sec.
-[Shane] All right.
Oh, and I like the adjudicator.
He wants to review
a few things when you're ready.
Okay. Yeah,
I'll be over in a minute.
All right. We're getting close.
You never get Fridays off.
Yeah, well...
I did today.
But I'll go if you want me to.
Do what you want.
Look, your dad would want you
to have all the support.
[sighs] I want to stay.
Cheer you on.
So, are you here for me or him?
Sam. Signatures.
Here and here. Make it official.
Bye, Sam. Good luck!
-Good luck, Sam.
-[woman] See ya.
-Thanks, man. See ya.
Did you give him paperwork?
[Shane] Yes.
Toxicology report. She's clean.
Right. Okay, great.
I'll add this to the notes.
Fantastic. Okay.
Just a few things I wanted to
go over before we begin.
Can you turn down
the music for me, please?
[Alec] We will be starting
on the hour.
So, in about ten minutes.
Sam, you'll have one minute
to complete each record.
Uh, starting first
with burpee pull ups.
Second will be wall ball squats.
Third are handstand push ups.
Those are fourth.
toe to bar is third.
Oh, you're right.
I'm sorry. [chuckles]
Third is toe to bar.
Fourth is handstand push ups.
And the last is clean and jerk.
So, uh, all must be completed
in a half hour
for the comprehensive
world record.
Six records in total.
I will be monitoring the clock.
-Do you--
-That one.
O-- okay, great.
Uh, and counting each rep
to make sure that
they're done to completion.
I will also be reminding us
of the previous world records
and what needs to be
accomplished for the new record.
-Sound good?
-Sounds good.
-Yeah.
-[Alec] You ready?
Great.
Uh, Shane,
will you show me the timer.
-one more time, please?
-Yeah, for sure.
Hey, Devin, we should snap
some pictures of Sam
-before she gets going.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
Okay, hold on.
-[indistinct] whiskey.
-Whiskey.
[Devan] All right, go ahead--
go ahead and turn,
like, 45 degree-- Nope, nope.
Other way, other way,
other way. Stop.
[speaking Spanish]
[Devan] Oh, perfect.
Perfect. Got it.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
You're doing great.
What?
[Charlie] Maybe after this,
we can go get a burger?
Fries, shake, usual. [chuckles]
And we can talk.
About what?
Hey, Sam! Clock's ticking.
What's your playlist?
-Uh, jam sesh for that.
-All right.
Jam sesh.
[upbeat music plays on speakers]
All right.
It's got a vibe to it.
[chuckles] All right,
burpee pull ups are first.
So, we wanna get
some nice gap pulls.
Let's do some kips.
We're going to spot our bars,
keep our nice wide stance.
We're going to cut down
on our turnover time
this time, all right?
[Blake] Hey, Sam,
this guy has something for ya.
-[man] Samantha Johnson?
-[Sam] Yeah.
-You've been served.
-[Shane] Hey, what's going on?
-Hey, hey! No.
-[Shane] Hey.
[man] I gotta give it to her.
I gotta give it to her.
Sam, you've been served.
[Charlie] No,
this is not how this works.
[man]
Hey, no. Settle down.
How the heck did this guy
even get in here?
He-- he said he had
something urgent for Sam.
[indistinct arguing]
[Shane] Served?
[somber music plays]
[Charlie] Sam?
-[Charlie] Sam.
-[Shane] Okay, Charlie. Okay.
[Charlie]
Sam, I can explain this.
-[Shane] Sam?
-[Charlie] Sam.
[Shane] Charlie,
hold up, hold up, hold up.
-Hold on. Sam.
-[Charlie] Sam.
[Charlie] [muffled]
Sam, I can explain this.
[Shane]
What was that?
[Charlie] Shane,
this is none of your business.
[Shane] It's taking place
in my gym. It's my business.
[Charlie]
Okay, man.
-Let me explain, please.
-[Shane] Hey. Hey, come on.
[Charlie] Sam, I'm sorry,
That wasn't supposed to happen.
Can you open this?
I need to talk to you.
[Shane] I don't think
she wants to talk to you, dude.
Give her space here. Come on.
-[Charlie] Don't touch me.
-[Shane] Come on.
-[Charlie] Sam!
-[Shane] Charlie.
-[Charlie] I-- I--
-[Shane] Let's go.
-Come on, roll out.
-[Charlie] [indistinct]
Is that why you came?
So you could watch my reaction?
-[Charlie] No!
-[Shane] All right.
[Charlie] No!
I said don't touch me.
[Shane] You're overstaying
your welcome.
[Charlie] Sam, I'm so sorry,
I-- I promise I had no idea
it was going to be--
be this fast.
I-- I thought
I had time to stop it.
You filed for divorce?
[Charlie] It wasn't supposed
to happen like this.
[Shane]
You need to step back.
[Charlie] This isn't
what I wanted, okay?
-[Shane] Come on.
-[Charlie] Don't touch me!
[Shane]
Charlie, let's go.
[Charlie]
I said don't touch me!
That's my wife.
[Shane] You're standing
inside of my gym,
and I said you need to go!
[indistinct arguing]
You asshole.
I can't believe you.
Hey, hey. Sam.
Sam! Sam, stop!
Look, I know it's a lot.
It's a lot. Okay?
Let's take a moment.
Come on, breathe.
Let's remember the big picture.
Everything that
you put into this.
Let's not walk away
from what you're about to do.
I can go tell Alec that
we need a delay or something
and that will be fine,
but I need you
in the right headspace.
-He won't have time for that.
-Charlie.
[frustrated sigh]
Look, there's a lot of rage.
I get it.
Trust me.
If anybody understands, I do.
But there's a big
opportunity on the table
in there for you,
Right? World records.
Maybe sponsorship, who knows?
We wanted to see
what you could do.
We wanted to push you
past your limits.
You're the fittest
you ever been, right?
We wanted to test that.
So, let's test it.
Come on, you leaving right now
is not going to change
whatever's happening
between you two.
Nobody controls
this moment but you.
I want you to remember
what you're doing this for.
Now, I'll get it
if you say you can't.
But...
[Sam sighs]
All right.
Yeah.
Okay. All right.
Game on.
[exhales sharply]
Guys, I-- I didn't mean--
I'm so sorry. I didn't know.
Blake,
you don't have to say sorry.
-Hey, is everything okay?
-Oh, yeah, yeah.
-You good?
-Yeah.
Okay. Leave him behind you.
-Hey, are you okay?
-Yeah.
And you're all right to start
at the top of the hour?
-[Sam] Yeah.
-Yeah, she's ready.
-[Alec] Okay.
-It's game time, baby.
It's game time!
-[people cheering]
-[Shane] [indistinct] away.
[Blake] Hey, Sam,
I-- I can take your jacket?
-Yeah.
-[Blake] Yeah.
Thank you.
-Yeah, of course.
-[Shane] Thanks, Blake.
All right, we will begin
at the top of the hour.
When I start the timer, Sam,
you'll have ten seconds
to ready.
When the buzzer goes off,
you'll have a minute
to complete.
Previous world record is 19.
New world record
we're looking for is 20.
-[Shane] That's right.
-Okay?
We're just seconds away,
you guys.
All right, world record.
[Blake] You've done this
hundreds of times.
-Let's go, Sam.
-[Shane] Here we go.
[chalk powder scraping]
[tense music plays]
[Devan]
Hey, block everything out.
All right? You've got this.
You've got this!
[Blake] You can do this
in your sleep, Sam.
[Sam clears her throat]
[Shane] Nice wide stance.
Spot your bar.
[Alec]
Yeah. You ready?
-Yeah.
-[Alec] Okay.
In ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five...
[timer beeping]
-Go, go, go!
-Come on!
-Nice strong start.
-[Shane] Nice.
-Nice, just like that.
-[Devan] Good, Sam!
-[Blake] Kill it!
Yes!
-Good rhythm.
-45 seconds! 45 seconds.
Don't slow down!
That's right. Keep it up.
Yeah. Good. Good, Sam!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Come on!
-You're doing it!
-[Charlie] Come on, that's it!
-Ten!
-Halfway there.
-Keep going.
-[Devan] Here you go!
-Yeah, yeah, yeah!
-[Devan] Dig deep!
-30 seconds.
-You're doing it, Sam!
-[Blake] Killing it!
-Keep going.
Yes, yes!
Yes. Stay strong. Yes.
-[Blake] Yes!
-Stay strong, Sam. Yes!
-Take it, yeah!
-[Alec] 15.
-20 seconds.
-Uh-huh.
[Blake]
Come on, come on, come on!
[overlapping cheering]
15 seconds.
Yes, keep that chin
over that bar!
-[Blake] Come on!
-Yes, Sam.
-Ten seconds.
-Yes.
-[Alec] 20!
-Yes! Go on, Sam!
-Keep going! Keep going, Sam!
-[overlapping cheering]
Five, four, three, two, one.
[cheering and applause]
[Shane]
You did it! You did it!
-[Alec] 22!
-[Shane] You did it!
[Alec] Congratulations, Sam,
on your first world record.
[Shane] Can we get her
some water, please?
-[Blake] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-[Devan] Way to go, Sam.
-[Blake] Nicely done.
-[Devan] Oh!
-[Blake] How are you feeling?
-I'm shaking.
-[all laughing]
-Well, she looks good.
[somber music plays]
Hey, look, don't address it.
Okay? All right?
Right now, in this moment,
for the next 30 minutes,
this is what matters, all right?
The universe is converging
on you right now, Sam.
And you're strong enough
to hold it, okay?
Are we planning
for about a minute rest?
Are you feeling good
with that time?
-Yeah.
-How are the hands?
-Did they rip?
-All good.
Okay, good. She's ready.
-Let's move on.
-[Alec] Okay, great.
-[all cheering]
-[Shane] Come on. Come on.
[Devan]
Way to go, Sam!
Wall ball squats are up next.
Sam, I-- I never intended
that to happen today.
-I would never--
-We said we'd talk about it.
-We did talk about it.
-No, we thought about it.
[overlapping cheering]
[Shane]
Here we go, number two.
Two world records, here we come.
[Alec]
Okay, Wall ball squats up next.
[muffled] World record was 35.
We're looking for 36.
♪
[Alec]
Starting in ten,
nine, eight,
seven, six...
-[Sam sighs]
-...five, four...
[timer beeping]
-One.
-[Blake] Come on, Sam.
It's a little high. Little high.
-Five.
-There you go.
[Devan] There you go,
there you go.
-[Monica] Right in the pocket.
-[Shane] Catch it.
-There you go.
-[Blake] Yep. Looking good.
-[Shane] Push, push, push,
-[Monica] 45.
-[Alec] Ten.
-[Monica] 45 seconds.
[Devan] Go, Sam.
Come on, that's it.
-[Blake] Go, go, go, go!
-[Devan] That's it!
[Shane]
Yeah, that's it.
A little high. Little high.
-[Alec] 15.
-[Shane] [indistinct] way down.
15, and you're not even
tired yet.
It's a walk in the park
for you, Sam!
-[Monica] 30 seconds!
-[Shane] That's right.
Hit it on that dot,
catch that ball coming down.
Just like you practiced.
Good job. Great job. Great job.
High gear here! High gear here!
-[Monica] 20 seconds.
-[Alec] 25!
[Blake]
Keep it up! Keep it up.
[Devan] Come on.
Push it, Sam. That's it.
[Monica] 15 seconds.
[Shane]
Let's go. Strong finish.
-[Blake] Go, go, go!
-[Shane] Come on!
[Monica]
Ten seconds!
-[Blake] Come on, this is it.
-[Shane] A little high.
-Up the wall. There you go.
-[Blake] This is it.
Five, four, three,
-two, one.
-[Alec] 35. 36!
-37!
-[Shane] Yes! Yes!
-[Blake] Come on, Sam!
-[all applaud]
[Shane] Two time
world record holder
Sam Johnson,
ladies and gentlemen.
[Alec] Congratulations, Sam,
on your second world record.
[panting] What's the time?
[Shane]
We're ahead of schedule.
Don't even worry about the time.
You're doing great.
Doing great. Yes.
Not too shabby.
[Devan]
Good job, Sam. Good job.
[Charlie]
You're doing it.
[panting]
I'm going to need a few minutes.
You got it. A few minutes rest.
We're doing good
in terms of time, yeah.
Look, I'm going to go.
After four years,
this is where we end up?
We can't get into that
right now, Sam.
You got to get back.
I can't pretend
this isn't happening.
[Charlie]
What do you want me to say?
Why? Tell me why.
Because we've gone
different directions.
Look at you.
Look at where you are now.
You got us started
in this direction.
We do this together.
You love this.
I know. And now it's your thing.
-I'm doing this for both of us.
-[Charlie] Really?
You fight more for a trophy
than you do for us.
[Sam]
That is not fair.
You know how hard
this last year has been.
I have been fighting for us,
and you should be
right here with me.
I know, and I tried
to tell you to slow down,
but I can't go there
because it's like an attack.
This is our dream.
[Charlie]
This is your dream, Sam.
People get divorced
all the time.
So?
It's not like we have kids
or a mortgage
that keeps us together.
[Sam]
Do you hear what you're saying?
We don't need kids
or a house to keep us together.
This should be about us.
Am I not enough for you?
Yeah. Maybe you should go.
[Devan]
Hey, welcome back, Sam!
[applause]
[Shane] Let's go.
Let's get back into the zone.
Look, this next one
is a little bit harder,
but we knew this going in.
The first two were just warmups.
-We're going for 42, right?
-[Alec] Yeah, or more.
The last world record
was 41 in one minute.
All right,
we got about 20 minutes.
-You good with that?
-Yeah.
Hey. You got this.
For one minute,
you're going to go all out
and you can do anything
for one minute, you hear me?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Hey.
You good?
[somber music plays]
Yeah. Okay.
All right.
She's good. Let's go.
[Devan] Come on, Sam.
Come on, come on.
[Shane] World record
number three coming up!
-Halfway there.
-World record number three.
Give it up.
-[Blake] Three out of six.
-[Monica] You got this, Sam.
[Alec]
Hey, here we go.
Previous record is 41 touches.
[Devan] All right, Sam.
Come on. You got this.
This is you. It's all you.
-[Sam sighs]
-[Alec] You ready, Sam?
[Sam clears her throat]
[Alec]
Okay, timer in...
ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five, four,
[timer beeping]
-[Alec] One. Two.
-[Monica] There you go. Nice.
[Blake] Yep.
-[Blake] Yep. Keep it up.
-[Alec] Five.
-[Blake] Keep it up!
-[Devan] That's it, that's it!
[Blake]
Looking good.
-[Monica] Looks great.
-[Blake] Yep.
[Devan] Make it look easy, Sam.
Well done. Well done.
-[Monica] 45 seconds.
-Keep that rhythm.
-[Blake] Don't back off.
-[Alec] 15.
Strong core,
strong core, strong core.
[Devan] That's it,
breathe through it.
-There you go.
-[Alec] 20.
[Blake]
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yep. Strong core.
30 seconds. Halfway there.
-[Alec] 25.
-[Blake] Halfway done.
[Devan] Yes.
That's right, keep that rhythm.
Keep that rhythm, Sam.
Looking good.
-[Blake] Breathe.
-[Alec] 30.
-[Devan] Come on, dig deep.
-[Blake] Go, go, go!
[Shane] Get that foot up there.
Get that foot up there.
-[Blake] Push.
-[Shane] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Dig in, dig in, dig in now.
-[Alec] 35.
-15 seconds.
-[Blake] Push.
-Keep going, keep going.
-[Devan] Come on, Sam!
Press it!
Press it, press it, Sam.
-[Monica] Ten seconds.
-[Alec] Come on! 40.
-[Monica] Eight. Come on.
-[Shane] That's good.
-[Shane] 42, 43! Let's go, Sam!
-[overlapping cheers]
-Three, two, one.
-[timer beeps]
[Shane]
There we go!
[Alec] Amazing, Sam.
I counted 42 official touches.
-Your third world record.
-[Blake] Nicely done.
-[Alec] Excellent work.
-[Monica] Oh, man.
-[Devan] Yo!
-[Shane] [indistinct].
Yeah, thanks, Blake.
Take some water when
you need it, okay? Yeah.
Oh, she's so strong.
[all chuckle]
-[Blake] Above and beyond.
-[Shane] Hey, what happened?
-You good?
-Yeah.
-What do I do?
-[Shane] All right.
-Hey, Blake, go get me the kit.
-[Blake] Okay.
And can you turn it down
a little bit?
-[Blake] Yeah.
-How you feel?
-[Sam] Good. Yeah.
-Yeah, you look good up there.
-Thanks.
-[Shane chuckles]
-You don't even break a sweat.
-[both chuckle]
Hey, come on,
let's take care of that.
I gotta say, Sam,
when I saw
what was coming today,
I wasn't prepared for it.
This is inspiring.
Hey, look, we're going to just
take a few minutes here, okay?
We won't take long.
All right.
Take whatever time you need.
All right. Great.
Sam, when you're done,
just show me your hand.
Oh, those are the worst.
All right, thank you.
Gotta trim the skin.
You want to take off your ring?
Ah, I'll just trim around it.
[Shane] Yeah,
but you got to put tape on.
Yeah.
[scissors snipping]
[Shane]
Did Charlie leave?
-Yeah.
-Are you all okay?
I mean...
-Are you safe, Sam?
-Oh, yeah. Nothing like that.
Charlie can't even
smash a spider.
No, we've--
we've been going
at it for a while, and...
obviously,
the separation hasn't helped.
Yeah, for what it's worth,
I don't know if you know,
but Marie and I were separated.
No way.
You guys are the perfect couple.
[Shane]
Fooled you.
-I mean, it was a while ago.
-But you're together now.
We worked it out. You know?
Took a lot out of both of us.
It was a struggle.
And I love her. There's that.
Love fueled us.
Just like you're going to need
some fuel after all this.
It's going to take a lot more
than a protein shake
to save my marriage.
Come on, you know what I mean.
Your dad.
What's something
that he would say to you
in the midst of all this?
Huh?
He always knew
I wanted to be an athlete
-or something growing up.
-[Shane] Mm-hmm?
So he'd always say,
"Somebody's got to do it,
so it might as well be you."
So matter of fact.
And it will be you.
So, let's keep that.
You use that for later.
[Sam scoffs]
-For social?
-No, for the news.
-You didn't.
-What do you mean?
A member of my gym
is a world class
record-holding
sponsored athlete.
You better believe
I'm calling the news.
-You jerk.
-[Shane chuckles]
Hey, look, we only got
a few more minutes, okay?
So let's do
some dynamic stretches.
Yeah. Stay warm, stay loose.
You're taking too much
of a break over here.
-Don't tell me what to do.
-[Shane chuckles]
I'll get your mats up for you.
-Hey, is she okay?
-Yeah, she's good.
So is the goal The Games?
Well, that's where we
anticipate her to leave a mark.
Right, world's fittest person
or something, right?
-Yeah.
-She's never been?
She killed
at the opening last year.
She moved
right through the semifinals.
How did she do?
Well, that's when
her dad got really sick.
Well, he died
right before it started.
She went straight home
and never got on stage.
[music plays faintly
in the background]
[paper rustling]
[somber music plays]
All right, let's do it.
Clock's ticking.
Handstand push ups are next.
It's one
of your strongest sections.
It's gonna be
a walk in the park for you.
All right,
previous world record is 12.
We're looking for 13
complete handstand push ups.
That means your head must come
all the way down to the mat,
arm's fully extended,
or it won't count.
-Okay, are you ready?
-[Sam] Yeah.
[Alec]
All right, timer in ten,
nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four.
[timer beeping]
-[Devan] Go, Sam.
-Here we go. Here we go.
-One. Two.
-[Devan] That's it. That's it.
[Shane]
Let's go. It's okay.
-[Monica] Right back up.
-You got this.
-Three.
-Feel your balance.
[Sam sighs] Reset. Reset.
I'm going again.
My balance is off.
-[Shane] It's okay.
-[Sam] Way off.
Hey, look, this is easy for you,
-[Sam groans]
-Remember? Hey, it's okay.
You got this. All right?
30 minutes, five records.
Doesn't matter
how many times I try, yeah?
[Alec]
Right. Let's go again.
All right, but you don't have
-as much time left after this--
-I know. I know.
-I'm doing the math.
-Okay.
-This is fine, right?
-[Alec] Absolutely.
As long as you're okay with it.
-[Sam] Yeah. Let's go.
-Okay. So, Sam, you ready?
-Yeah. It's good.
-[Alec] Okay, great. Timer in...
ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five, four.
[timer beeping]
-One. Two.
-You go, Sam.
-Sam.
-Three.
Good balance.
-[Devan] Good. Good!
-Nice.
-That's good.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. Good.
Take time to reset,
you're at 45 seconds.
Killing it, Sam.
Come on, Sam. Focus. That's it.
[Blake chuckles]
-Make it look easy.
-Ten.
-Nice.
-Not even against the wall.
-Not even halfway.
-[Shane] Good. Good.
-Yes!
-A little faster if you can.
-13, 14.
-[Shane] That's good.
-[Shane] Keep that back.
-[Monica] 30 seconds.
-[Alec] 15.
-[Devan] Come on, come on!
-Yes! Come on, keep going.
-[Shane] Good, Sam.
-17
-Strong in your core.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-[Alec] It's okay. It's okay.
-[Devan] Breathe, come on.
-[Monica] 20 seconds.
-[Shane] Good. Good.
-[Alec] 18.
-Good. Keep going.
19. 20!
[Shane] You got it, Sam!
You got it!
[Alec] 21!
[Shane chuckles]
This is amazing!
-Last push, last push.
-[Alec] 22.
Post stretch. Come on, come on.
Three.
-24.
-Three, two, one.
-[all cheering] Yes!
-[Alec] Yes!
-[Monica] Oh, my gosh!
[Shane]
How many was that, Alec?
-[Alec] 24.
-[Shane] 24.
[Monica]
Doubled the world record.
All right.
All right, all right, all right.
Sam.
Sam, you all right?
Sam? Hey.
[retching, coughing]
[Sam coughing, inhaling deeply]
[Shane]
Breathe. Just breathe.
[Sam breathing heavily]
Did you fuel up okay yesterday?
Maybe you overdid
a little with the water.
I don't know. Probably.
[sighs deeply]
How much time?
Hm, about seven
or eight more minutes.
[Sam exhales sharply]
So do we add weight to the bar?
Less reps or do we take
some off to do fewer?
We're at 185 already.
It's already pretty heavy.
I don't think
we should go heavier.
Cycling knees
isn't your strongest.
Why is this last again?
Because you asked for it.
[chuckling]
We're pushing
a lot of shoulders.
That was stupid.
Why didn't you stop me?
Well, I tried.
Didn't know
you were going to go all out
on the handstands.
We're going to need you
at 110% for this next one.
You currently
hold four world records.
-One more to go.
-[Sam sighs]
Just a minute.
I just need a minute.
All right, you got your minute.
[exhales sharply]
[Shane]
You ready for this, Sam?
I know you are.
Bar's been chalked
and set at 185.
We're gonna go ten times.
[Alec] Previous world record
is set at lifting 785 pounds.
10 reps at this point
will be 850 pounds.
You ready, Sam?
[exhales sharply]
-Yeah.
-[Alec] Okay.
Timer in ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five, four.
[timer beeping]
-[Alec] One.
-[athletes] Nice!
Great lock off, Sam.
-[Blake] Deep breath.
-[Monica] You got this.
[Alec]
That's two!
-[Shane] [indistinct]
-[Monica] 45 seconds.
[Alec]
Form is perfect, Sam.
[Devan] Come on, Sam. Dig deep.
You got this. Come on.
[Blake] Nice.
[Devan]
Come on, come on, come on!
-[Blake] Good.
-Great lock off, Sam, good job.
[Monica] Nice!
[Blake] 30 seconds.
Less than 30 seconds.
Make it lighter.
We got to start over.
All right,
we're going to start over.
-Let's reset the clock.
-Set it to 150.
-You want it at 150?
-[Sam] Yes.
-That'll have to be...
-She'll have to do
12 reps at that weight.
-12 reps are good with that?
-I know.
-[Shane] 12 reps are good?
-Yeah. Let's go.
Ah, hey, Blake, can you go
out there and just tell them
to hold a beat,
give us a minute.
They can wait inside, but
they got to be in the corner.
Okay, you guys only have about
two minutes left to plan, okay?
All right, this is going
to feel a lot lighter,
so you're going to want
to power through it,
-but just save it.
-Yeah, I got it.
Can we roll camera?
[Shane] Blake,
I need some water for her.
Can we get a water bottle,
please, quickly?
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
[phone ringing]
[Shane]
Last record.
-[phone ringing]
-[coughing]
I cannot talk
to sponsors right now.
Blake, can you take this?
Wait, no, I'll call them back.
-Can someone get that?
-[Shane] What? No.
Just-- Look.
We got to move, okay?
We only have a minute.
-Okay, let's go.
-[Shane] All right.
-Okay, you ready?
-Yeah.
-[Shane] All right, here we go.
-Let's go.
-Hey, roll on this.
-On it.
Timer in ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five, four.
[timer beeping]
-[Shane] That's good.
-[Alec] One.
-Good.
-[Blake] Let's go.
That's light for you, Sam.
Keep a good rhythm.
-[Blake] Seven seconds in.
-[Alec] Two.
-Great.
-[Devan] That's it, Sam.
-Come on. That's it.
-[Monica] Looking good.
-[Blake] 10 seconds in.
-Light drive.
-[Alec] Three.
-Good luck.
-[Alec] Come on, Sam!
-[athletes shouting]
-[Shane] Big hips here.
-[Alec] Four.
-Good.
-[Devan] Good, good.
-[Alec] Perfect form.
-[Blake] 20 seconds in.
[Alec]
Keep going, Sam.
[Monica]
You got this. You got this.
[Devan] Come on, Sam,
you got this, go, go, go.
[Alec] Five.
Good.
[Blake] Okay, you're halfway.
30 seconds.
-[Shane] [indistinct].
-[Alec] Six.
[Monica]
Come on, come on, Sam!
[Devan] Come on, focus.
You got this!
[Shane]
Light drive. Light drive.
-[Devan] Come on, Sam.
-[Blake] 20 seconds.
Coming up on it so good.
-Good lockout.
-[Devan] Push it.
[Alec]
Seven, 15 seconds.
[Blake]
10 seconds left.
[Devan] Come on, come on,
Sam, dig deep. Home stretch.
-[Blake] Nice push.
-[Devan] Come on, come on!
-[Blake] Five, four, three...
-Hey, Sam.
-[Blake] One.
-[Shane] Time!
-Dang it.
-[Shane] Sam!
[groans and panting]
[Shane] Okay, it's all good,
it's all good.
-[Sam grunting in effort]
-You don't need 12.
[weights clanking]
Okay, whoa! Hey.
Give it over to the floor.
Thank you, Blake.
We can cut.
[coughing]
[Shane]
All right, take a minute.
I'm fine. I'm good.
-Amazing work, Sam.
-[Shane] Power through it.
Definitely didn't hold back,
not one bit.
Credible feat.
[Shane] Wrap it up.
Wrap it up, yup. Sam, easy.
[Alec]
Good job, Sam.
[Shane] You came, you fight,
it was a battle
and you still won.
-No, I didn't.
-[Shane] Yes, Sam, you did.
You made four records
in a half hour.
That's probably a record
in and of itself.
The goal was five, it had to be
five in 30 minutes.
Hey, but you did four
and that's already
in the history books, right?
Until somebody beats it,
it needed to be five.
-[phone ringing]
-Don't beat yourself up, okay?
[Blake] Hey, Shane,
it's the sponsors again.
Hey, look, they don't even know
that we started so late.
They probably think we've been
done for a while, now.
What I'm saying is, is that
you still have sponsorship
in your cards.
You shop for the moon
and you cleared the atmosphere.
I'm going to tell them
how amazing you were.
This is Shane.
Aha, yep, she was incredible.
Uh-huh.
[Monica] You did great.
You gave it everything you got.
Okay?
[Devan]
You were so close. I'm sorry.
I know it's not what you wanted,
but what you did today,
only lead athletes can do.
I'm serious, I get to travel
all over the world
and see amazing
world records get set,
but rarely
don't get to see somebody
push their body
like you did today.
You accomplished four
world records in 30 minutes.
15 years, I've never seen
an athlete like her before.
Thank you.
[Shane]
Yeah, she's right here.
-Sam, can you chat?
-Yeah.
Hello.
Hey, Shane, so I just have
a few certificates
and awards to give her,
-but when you're ready...
-Yeah.
We could also
wait for the news crew.
-That might be cool.
-No, I understand.
[Alec]
But whenever you're ready.
For sure.
[Sam speaking indistinctly]
Tell you the same thing.
Hi there. Excuse me.
Brenda Featherstone
from News Two.
-[Shane] Hi, Brenda.
-How are you?
-Good.
-Sam, congratulations.
Such an impressive feat.
Do you think after the interview
you could give us some B-roll
of you moving around a bit?
Yeah, like maybe some cooldown.
Her on a bike
or stretching or something.
Okay. Are there awards
or any commemorations?
[Shane]
That's fine.
-Okay.
-Aha, yeah.
I'm just going to set up
over there
and come by when you're ready.
-Okay?
-Okay. Thank you.
Hey, look.
It's not the end
of the world, okay?
Just take a moment,
splash some water on your face,
drink some recovery drink
or something.
-Shane, I just--
[Shane]
You are a gifted athlete.
You should be competing
in the games and they know that.
That's why they're still
going to provide all the gear
that you're
going to need for it.
An official sponsorship
wasn't a guarantee,
-so it really doesn't matter.
-It mattered to me.
[Shane] We need to get you
on a bigger stage.
That's where it matters.
So, let's work towards that,
okay?
For my comp, we learned a lot.
Now, we know
what we need to work on.
I'm so sorry, Shane.
Hey, what are
you apologizing for?
I should've been able
to do this.
-It should have been easy.
-[Shane] No, no, no, no, no!
Nobody ever said
it was supposed to be easy.
It's painful.
If it's not painful,
then you're not
working hard enough.
We got four wins.
Let's celebrate that.
Keep your head up.
[exhales sharply]
♪
[Shane] Sam.
[Brenda] How do you prepare
for the intensity of the sport?
I show up six days a week,
focus on nutrition and recovery.
And how long
have you been doing it?
About four years now.
More competitively the last two.
So, some have said that
the heavy impact on the body
isn't healthy.
-What do you think?
-[Sam scoffs]
It all comes down to form.
Uh, that's why
I've got Shane here
to watch my technique,
make sure I'm moving safely.
Form is everything.
-Any injuries today?
-Uh, little hand hair.
How does it feel to be
a world record holder?
[Sam sighs]
It really hasn't
hit me yet, um...
I know I set
four world records today,
but I think I'm still
kind of coming down from it.
Yeah, you were struggling
a little bit on the last one.
What was going through
your mind?
[sighs] Everything. Um.
Um, I think
on the previous movement
I came out a little too hot,
used a little too much energy
going into this last one.
So, switching gears here,
I understand your husband
got you into this.
Uh, yeah, he, um--
Oh, I'm-- I'm sorry.
Hold on a second.
Could you restate
the question in your answer?
-Oh, yeah.
-Okay, great.
Keep-- keep rolling.
Keep rolling.
Um, my husband actually
got me started in this.
He-- he was my first coach.
Um...
He was actually
in an accident a few years ago
and hurt his neck
and had to step back.
Hm, that's too bad.
So, now you're the competitor
in the relationship,
but that's great
that he's there to support you.
Who else supports you?
Uh, my dad was my ultimate
cheerleader before he passed.
Uh, definitely my mom.
Um, Shane here.
Uh, it's just an awesome
community to be a part of.
[Brenda]
Great, okay. Uh, great.
I-- I think we got it.
Um, could we see
Sam being awarded
and maybe get some
movements on the bike
-or something like that?
-[Shane] Absolutely.
[Shane] Let's go
with the awards first.
Alec here has a plan to catch.
-[Brenda] Okay.
-[Shane] So we'll do that
and then
we'll grab a few quick shots.
[Brenda] Okay, thanks.
You got this? Okay.
[Alec] On behalf of
the World Record Federation,
it brings me great joy
to honor you today,
Sam, on your accomplishments.
[muffled] The most toe to bar
in one minute,
Sam Johnson. Good job, Sam.
[Alec's voice fades]
Good job.
♪
[muffled] Come on, come on.
[muffled] You're great.
I got a plane to catch.
You did an amazing job today.
-Thank you.
-[Alec] Be proud.
All right, thanks guys, see ya.
Bye.
[Shane]
Have a safe flight.
[Devan] Shane, I will put
all of these on a drive for you.
Got some killer shots,
you're gonna love them.
My man. Can't wait.
Anytime.
You're champion a today.
Well done.
-[Monica] Love you.
-Love you too.
-Bye.
-Call me when you're done.
-Yeah.
-[Shane] Thanks, Monica.
-[Shane] Cooldown?
-[Brenda] Yeah.
I just-- Yeah,
I just wanna see some action.
You can feel free to look
in the camera anytime.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Make it look like you're
working hard a little bit.
Come on.
[indistinct chatter]
-[Brenda] Thank you.
-[Shane] Thank you.
-[Brenda] Appreciate it.
-[Shane] Cool.
[Brenda]
Watch for us tomorrow night.
[Shane]
Yes, looking forward to it.
-[Brenda] Thank you.
-[Shane] Hey, Sam,
you can't just
let a banana take care of you
-after all of that.
-I'll eat more later.
Hey, Shane,
I'm about to head out,
do you need anything else?
-No, I think we're good.
-Okay.
Oh, actually I can clean up
that bar real quick.
-I'll get it.
-[Blake] You sure?
Yeah.
All right, okay. See ya.
Be safe getting home, Blake.
Oh, don't want you
to forget this.
What a jerk thing to do.
-[Sam chuckles]
-[door creaks close]
So?
-So.
-[Shane] You're going to party?
Night on the town?
I'm going to go home.
You got a lot
of nice merch coming away.
Yay, more tops and coupon codes.
-All yours if you want them.
-Nah, I'm good.
Don't forget to take
your certificates,
mount them on your wall
or you can leave them here
if you like.
-Sure.
-Wait, really?
Yeah, put them on the wall
over there or something.
I can't take them,
I mean they're yours.
-Come on, Sam.
-[scoffs] Whatever.
You can borrow them.
You know you want to.
Post those bragging rights
on your social.
-I appreciate that.
-And go home.
I'm going to clean up
and then I'll lock it down.
I don't think
I should leave you by yourself.
Don't pity me.
Seriously.
Go home to your family.
I'll see you tomorrow morning?
Yeah.
[Shane] You sure
you're going to be okay?
All right.
Shane, thank you for today.
For everything.
I was proud of you, Sam.
I mean...
You power through in the midst
of all that stuff happening,
it's not easy.
It's in our fiercest battles
that we realize
what matters most.
I saw you doing a lot more
than just gaining
world records today.
I saw your heart.
It's like the gladiators
of old would say,
"Let me win.
And if I cannot win...
let me be brave in the attempt."
-Night.
[door creaks close]
[outgoing call ringing]
[Sam's mom] Sam.
-Hi, Mom.
[Sam's mom] I've been
waiting for you to call.
-I tried to call earlier.
-I saw.
Janine next door is texting
me every five minutes.
Did you do it?
Uh, I got four.
Ah, that's amazing.
My baby, the record breaker.
You're a pro.
I'm not a pro, Mom.
[Sam's mom]
What's the matter?
I couldn't--
I can't-- I didn't get it.
[Sam's mom]
What do you mean?
I-- I thought
I could get all of them.
I was so close.
That's okay. You did your best.
Wait. What? What is it?
Charlie.
He let me know this time.
He's done.
[Sam's mom]
Oh, honey.
I just feel like,
I let everybody down.
Oh, no, no, no. Hey!
You didn't let anyone down.
No one.
Hey, look at me. Look at me.
You have worked so hard
to get where you are.
You have nothing
to prove to anybody.
You are so strong.
It's not your job
to carry the whole world.
This is about you, nobody else.
And you are enough.
It's going to be okay. Hey.
It's going to be okay.
[sobbing]
♪
[water splashing]
[knocking on door]
Figured you'd be hungry.
[sighs]
I figured you'd still be here.
Is that okay?
The usual.
[Charlie]
Shakes and a melt.
Four.
That's not bad.
Four world records.
Yeah.
That's four more than I have.
They were out
of the spicy fries.
I had to go over
to the one on State.
I think I saw Dale there.
Dale moved months ago.
Huh.
Maybe it wasn't Dale.
Look, the other day we argued
and divorce came up,
and the next day I--
I was upset
and I made a decision.
But it wasn't supposed
to happen like that.
-What a coincidence.
-I came here to talk.
I didn't know
that guy was coming.
Then, how did he know
where to find me
and to come here
at the same time as you?
They ask where you spend
your time.
Please.
[Charlie]
Everything is here for you.
Work, your clients.
Your whole life has been
about this for months.
Of course I said here.
And it just
happened to be today.
I didn't plan an attack on you,
if that's what you're asking.
Do you resent me?
Because I'm here and you're not?
No. I don't belong here anymore.
-I don't fit in. You know that.
-Because you don't want to.
-Because I--
-Chris is here
three days a week
after his shoulder surgery.
Tyson is here
five with his knee.
I'm not those guys.
They're not coming in
to be champions.
I get that, okay?
And I wish
I could throw weight around
like I used to,
I do, but I can't.
-I think you resent me for it.
-It's not true.
You put in three times
more effort than you ever did.
I can't do that.
All the time, all the effort,
you're pushing everyone away,
all the important people,
so that you can be at the top.
You clearly don't get it.
I can't control
much of what happens in life,
but here, I can.
Really?
You know,
I wanted to quit last year.
Why not? Why not quit?
Then what the hell
is all this for?
So, this is worth it?
Pushing everyone aside for this?
Maybe if my dad were still here
or you were still doing this,
I wouldn't be going so hard.
Do not hold this over my head.
I'm doing this for you,
for everyone.
Not that it seems to matter
after today.
Why? Because you didn't get
a few more
-gimmicky world records?
-[Sam] No.
You should not be
worried about records.
-I know!
-Sam, you don't need
world records to prove
that you can do this.
I just wanted you
to be proud of me.
I am proud of you.
-Don't bullshit me.
-I'm not.
We were supposed
to do this together.
We were supposed to open a gym
and go until
our bodies broke down.
-And I beat you to it.
-No, you gave up.
-You left.
-So did you.
After my injury,
I tried to get back into it,
but I couldn't--
I couldn't keep up.
And you treated me
like dead weight.
So after your dad, I thought
maybe she'll let me in.
But you didn't.
You just kept coming back here.
So, I made a choice for you.
Cut me off so that you can be
free to follow your dream.
You don't get to make
that decision for me.
[exhales sharply]
I really, really
wanted the wins today.
Not just for the records.
I thought it would be
a new start for us.
I don't want to do it alone.
You're going to be a pro, Sam.
You don't need me.
I do.
[sighs]
♪
It broke on the clean and jerks.
[Sam chuckles softly]
You could have bought this
from a candy machine.
Yeah.
I wish I could have
seen you at the end.
I threw up
on the handstand pushups.
That blows.
I'm so sorry, Sam.
♪
-[Sam] Wait. Uh.
-Oh, right.
-Thanks.
-Yeah, no.
Better take it out so it
doesn't stink up and joint.
Shane'll appreciate that.
Are you staying at Paul's still?
Yeah, yeah.
-Are you stepping out?
-Ah, no.
-I've gotta get mu stuff--
-Ah, okay.
Well.
[both chuckling nervously]
-Good night.
-Night.
[rain splashing]
-Good night.
-Night.
[siren wailing in the distance]
[timer beeping]
[melancholic instrumental
playing]
♪
[metal clanking]
12. [sighs]
♪
[timer beeping]
[grunts in effort]
♪
[timer beeps]
[exhales sharply]
[panting]
[breath echoing]
♪
[music fades]