(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
LUKAS: Seven dead, 14 wounded.
Some of those aren't
gonna make it.
Incident Room, 10 minutes,
everybody.
I need all the heads of all the
Major Incident Response Teams
in my office, now.
Yeah.
They found six
unused bullet casings,
painted black,
on the station platform.
What is that?
Well, it could be...
Could be a calling card.
Could be he got careless.
Happy Fourth of July.
(DIALING)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
City Hall.
Office of the Mayor.
HAVEL: Is about train
station killings
and what I need city to do.
This isn't hoax.
You finding six black shell
casings on train station floor.
You finding envelope
in front of building,
inside first
newspaper vending machine.
Hello?
LUKAS: All right,
listen up everyone.
Shooter was black,
white, Asian, tall,
short, fat, thin,
clean-shaven with a beard.
Basically, we've got
nothing to go on
except these shell
casings he left behind
and a call he made to City
Hall about the killings.
The call to the mayor
was a recorded voice
and it wasn't
long enough to trace.
HARDY: Excuse me.
This is what we found inside the
vending machine at City Hall.
You the police liaison
I asked the mayor for?
Yeah. Officer Len Hardy.
Washington PD.
Look, anything you
need from the city
or emergency services,
I'll be on point.
Thanks.
All right, here it is.
Listen up, everyone.
"The end is night.
The Digger is loose
"and there is no
way to stop him."
The Digger?
"He will kill again at 12:00
each day for the next two days.
"I am wanting
$20 million in cash,
"which you will put into a bag and
leave it two miles south of Route 66,
"on the west side of the beltway,
in the middle of the field.
"Pay to me the money
by 1200 hours tomorrow.
"Only I am knowing
how to stop The Digger.
"If you apprehend me,
he will keep killing.
"If you kill me,
he will keep killing."
So now we're
dealing with two guys.
And we got less than
24 hours to find them.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(CROWD CHATTERING)
KINCAID: Robby, Shannon!
Come on, eat.
Ugh!
Hey! Guys, can you stop
leaving Marzipan in my study?
How many times I gotta tell you?
All right.
(EXHALES)
Analysis of document purporting
to be from Thomas Jefferson
admitting to paternity of
child by Sally Hemmings.
Document examiner,
Parker Kincaid.
Subject is
a single half-sheet folio
with yellowing
around the edges and with
copperplate handwriting.
Also with...
SHANNON: Marzipan's gone
missing again, Daddy.
He seems to have moved himself
and his cage into my study. Again.
Is that the one
from the president?
- Yeah.
- Is it worth a lot of money?
It will be if I can prove
that it's really by him.
So you can't touch
the paper, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Do you know why we
can't touch the paper?
Because the oil on
our skin can cause a
chemical reaction with
the paper and damage it.
That's right.
What you're looking for is?
I'm looking for
the truth, honey.
And no matter how
clever people try to be,
there's always some little
thing that gives them away.
My job is to find it.
He's there.
He's in the bushes
outside, watching.
Okay. All right.
Show me. Come on.
Now, what do we do when we
think we see The Boatman?
We put on our helmet, our
shield, and we pick up our sword.
That's right. Okay.
I got mine, too. Okay?
Now, where do you
think you saw him?
I mean, I know
he's dead and that.
I know what
happened to him but...
Yeah. It's okay. Just tell me.
There.
He was right over there.
Under that tree.
I saw him from my window.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna cut down
that spooky old tree,
okay?
Yes, Mr. Director. The mayor and
I are coordinating the money.
She's having it pulled
from the city coffers
and we'll take over from there.
Hopefully the money
will lead us to the killer.
So the field where he wants
the drop off is wide open.
And you can see
in every direction,
which means anybody coming to
get the money is gonna see us.
There is no way we can get
anywhere near the drop point.
Okay, looks like
an ordinary canvas bag
but it's woven with strands of
copper, making it an antenna.
Transmitter is in the handle.
So we can stay away from
the drop off with our units
and regardless of
what trick he has,
when he tries to
pick up the money,
we'll always know where it is.
That's right. Now if
he gets rid of the bag,
we've got another
surprise for him.
The bottom of each one is a dummy
bundle with its own transmitter.
There's no way he
can hide this money.
We find the money, we find him.
(SIRENS WAILING)
No ID. But we found
this recorder on him.
So everything is in place.
All roads are closed
within a three-mile radius.
LUKAS: Great. We've got
a hit and run downtown.
Male. No ID.
They found this on him.
HAVEL: Is about train station
killings and what I need city to do.
This isn't hoax.
You finding six black shell
casings on train station floor.
You finding envelope
in front of building,
inside first
newspaper vending machine.
Now we're in
even bigger trouble.
The guy who pulled
the strings is dead.
What about the money?
Lock it up.
We have to assume
that The Digger will
kill tomorrow again
at noon as instructed.
But now there's nobody to
give him his orders anymore.
All we have to work with is the
taped voice of a dead man and this.
I know our guys are
still working on it, but...
But what?
There's this guy...
Parker Kincaid.
KINCAID: All right,
toss it over here.
He ran the Document Examination
Department till two years ago.
Guy's a legend.
We used to call him
The Puzzle Master.
Why did he resign?
Personal reasons.
It's complicated.
We don't have time for complications.
Find me somebody else.
This guy's the best.
He's gonna give us the edge
to stop that son of a bitch
from killing somebody tomorrow.
KINCAID: Okay, be nice to your brother.
Be nice.
SHANNON: Okay. Pass it.
Hey, I gotta go to talk
to these people, okay?
Whatever this is about, Cage...
I assume you saw the news today
about the shooting
in the train station?
I'd like you to meet my
boss, Margaret Lukas.
I can see your shoulder holster.
You know I can't have guns around
my kids, especially my son.
I'm sorry.
I hardly ever watch the news.
Seven dead.
A bunch more in the hospital.
The shooter's primed
to kill again tomorrow.
The only person who
can stop him is dead.
The only clue we have is this.
I resigned. Sorry. You're gonna
have to get somebody else.
Sorry, maybe I didn't
make myself clear.
We need your expertise on the
only physical clue we have
in order to stop
another massacre.
Look, Parker, I'm sorry.
I know you wanted to
make a clean break from
law enforcement...
Look, I have to
get back to my kids.
I can't do anything for you.
Mr. Kincaid, I'm sure
you have your reasons...
I do. Really good ones.
I just can't be involved. That is
a terrible thing that happened.
I hope you get a break.
But it can't be through me.
Look, Parker,
we go back a long way.
I wouldn't be here if we
didn't really need you.
Can we work something out?
You know what happened, Cage.
You know I have my reasons.
CAGE: Yeah, okay.
I just thought it
was worth a shot.
KINCAID: Buddy.
No deal.
(GRUNTING)
All right, we got 20 hours left.
Get me back to the office.
Look, I'm sorry.
This was a waste of time.
We'll see.
Hey, when I told you to put
your things into neat piles,
I didn't mean on the floor.
Are you mad at me?
There is nothing
that you could ever do
that would make me mad at you.
Is everything okay?
Sure.
Will you make a million dollars
if you prove
that Thomas Jefferson
wrote that letter?
If anyone's gonna
make a million dollars
off of it, it's not gonna be me.
Oops!
Where you going?
I have to feed Marzipan.
I need to get his food.
(SIGHS)
It's Mom!
Shannon!
JOAN: Honey!
ROBBY: Mommy!
Oh, Robby! Baby,
I missed you guys so much.
The place was so beautiful.
Right on the water.
And you know what? I am going to
take you there one day, I promise.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, Parker.
Hey, Joan. Come on in.
Oh, umm, no, actually,
we're in a rush.
Did you guys like the presents?
The Barbie was great.
- Dad took back the shirt and got one the right size.
- Don't worry about it.
(SIGHS) Well, I wanted you to
have something till I got back.
So, I will bring the rest
of your presents tomorrow.
Why don't you come in?
'Cause Shannon made cookies.
I would love to, but Jerry's
waiting for me in the car.
We have to go to the kennel
and pick up the dogs.
Poor things have
been caged up all week.
Come here, pumpkins.
One more hug.
(SIGHING)
We're gonna see a lot more of
each other soon, okay? Okay.
Parker, will you
walk me to the car?
Oh, yeah. Come on guys,
get inside. Eat.
You look good.
Jerry's a lucky guy.
You're just saying that.
No, I mean it.
I'm happy for you.
Well, I wish
you hadn't said that
'cause it makes what I have to
do that much more difficult.
I could have let the process
server do this after the holiday.
Motion to Modify Child Custody Order?
No, Joan. No.
This isn't about you, Parker.
I appreciate everything
you've done for them,
but things have changed.
I'm sober now. I've got
my life under control.
Jerry and I, we're
getting married in the fall.
You wanna bring
them back to court
and put them through
all that? Again?
I'm hoping we can work it out
between ourselves
but if we can't then...
We have an arrangement
that works.
You have all the
visitation that you want!
I don't want to be
a part-time mother anymore.
You've had them for
two years, Parker.
It's my turn now. I've got
my life all sorted out.
I can offer them a real home.
This is their home.
A home with a mom and a dad.
I'm their dad.
But I'm their mother,
and I wanna be
with my kids for real.
Not just for a couple
of hours at a time.
And I think I'm entitled
to ask for that.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
KINCAID: Look, I want Joan
to be a part of their lives,
but the court agreed that it's
best for them to stay with me
and nothing's
changed about that.
The timing couldn't be worse.
Robby's having nightmares
about The Boatman again.
Calm down, Parker.
Joan's the one who walked
out of here two years ago
and now she's
getting married again
and she thinks she can just
swoop in and demand custody?
I'm scared, Penny.
I know that she means it.
And I think she's gonna do everything
she can to get the kids back.
Look, I'm just on my way to court.
Just send me the custody order
so I can take a look at it
and we'll go from there. Okay?
Okay.
HAVEL: You finding envelope
in front of building,
inside first
newspaper vending machine.
Inside first
Is about train station killings.
This isn't hoax.
KINCAID: Did you
brush your teeth?
Yeah.
Hmm? Up and down
and side to side?
Mmm-hmm.
You feeling okay, champ?
Is there anything on your mind?
The Boatman.
I keep thinking about him.
Like he gets inside my head.
You know, he can never
hurt you again. Ever.
Not in a million
billion trillion years.
Okay?
Go to sleep.
I'll sit right here.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GUN FIRES)
FRED FLINTSTONE: No, Dino.
No, no, no, Dino!
(LICKING SOUND)
Will you cut it out?
Down, boy. Down, boy!
Hey, what's this?
My dinner on the table and...
REPORTER ON TV:
Thank you, Dave.
I'm here at Union Station
with an eyewitness.
Can you describe what you saw?
People were screaming and
falling and trying to run
but there was nowhere to run to
and the shots just kept coming
and you couldn't tell
where they were coming from.
And everyone was just falling
and screaming and there was no...
You couldn't get away.
Like, no one could get away.
And the shots just kept coming
and he just kept shooting
and shooting and shooting.
REPORTER: Also, among the
seven dead are the parents
of two children,
ages six and nine.
Stay tuned for
further details about
this horrendous
and shocking event.
This is Sandra Weller,
reporting for WNKW.
We are working round the clock with
the FBI and the city police department
to apprehend this criminal.
We are aware of
the next threat to the city
but we have no indication of
what the location might be.
REPORTER 1: Madam Mayor... REPORTER
2: Madam Mayor, do you have any...
Two more victims just died.
Any sign of the materials and
elementals lab report on the note yet?
No, nothing.
But I'll get on it.
Hey, Security just called about
some guy you were expecting?
Welcome back, Mr. Kincaid.
We're expecting a report
from Materials and Elemental
and a psych profile
at any moment.
You'll be working
in the documents lab.
I heard you helped set it up?
Security had my ID
tag already made out.
How did you know
that I'd change my mind?
I saw how important
your family was to you.
I knew you'd think about the
families torn apart yesterday,
and ask yourself what the right
thing to do would be.
It's almost 8:00.
We've got four hours left.
KINCAID: My kids are not to know I came
here to help. Nobody can know. Nobody.
LUKAS: That's a big change from
everyone trying to grab the headlines.
No. I mean it. I had to lie to
them about where I was going today.
Not even the babysitter
knows the real reason.
I got divorced two years ago.
And one of the conditions
for me having custody
instead of my ex-wife
is that I work at home
and I don't do anything
to endanger the kids.
I just found out that the
custody case got reopened.
- Their mother cannot know about this.
- All right, listen.
If you need to do this
anonymously, that's fine by me.
All that matters
is catching this guy.
Okay, without
anyone to call him off,
I suspect he's going to carry
out his orders to keep killing.
Triple espresso with a shot
of half and half, right?
Thank you.
Now, analysis of
the note suggests
that the writer
was foreign born,
been in the country
two or three years.
Poorly educated, at most, the
equivalent of two years high school.
Probable IQ, 100,
plus or minus 10 points.
Yeah. Textbook analysis.
Very impressive.
Very thorough.
And completely wrong.
This guy's not a foreigner.
He's been living here for years.
He's well-educated and
his IQ is near genius level.
Let's take a look at
the words on the page.
Let's see here. Umm...
One might misspeak and say, "The end
is night," but you wouldn't write it.
Not unless you wanted to
throw people off the scent.
The same thing with,
"I am knowing."
Sounds foreign.
Yeah. It sounds fake.
Sounds like he wants us
to believe he's foreign.
Okay, if he's not
from the US though,
why would he write "1200 hours"?
He did that once.
But then here he
writes "twelve."
If he's so smart, what
about the spelling errors?
You mean "their"
instead of "there"?
Well, most people
would make that mistake
if they were
keyboarding at high speed.
But it's much rarer
in handwriting
unless you wanted people
to think you were dumb.
Does the letter
give us anything?
It gives us
The Devil's Teardrop.
The what?
CAGE: Yeah,
I remember that case.
He was a serial killer. He left
notes on the victim's body.
He did what
the writer here does,
places a dot above
his lowercase I's
and makes a small tail upwards.
Could it be the same guy?
That guy was beaten to death
in his cell years ago.
Okay, you've shot down every
theory about who this guy was,
so do you have your own theory?
Not yet.
Come on, the letter's gotta
give you something about him.
What his state of mind was, what
he was likely to have planned next.
I'm a scientist,
not a fortuneteller.
But you said he was smart.
Yeah, well, IQ is measurable.
It's a metric.
I can tell you he's smart
but I can't tell you
what he's gonna do next.
I can't tell you anything
about his character.
The guy is a psychopath.
You can't tell anything
from his handwriting?
Come on!
Anybody who says
that they can analyze
personality from
handwriting alone is lying.
It's like reading
tarot cards and tea leaves.
I mean, it's bogus.
People make a living doing it.
Yeah, people make a living
writing horoscopes.
It's got just as
much to do with reality.
Chief?
I'm gonna have to
use the document lab
if I'm gonna
analyze this further.
Yeah. Absolutely.
(SOBBING)
Strange.
What?
There's no tremble.
Tremble?
Yeah, when people
fake their handwriting,
try to write in a way that
can't be traced back to them,
they're going against
years of muscle memory,
forcing themselves to overturn,
you know, the habits of a lifetime.
Usually that results
in a shaky kind of lettering.
I'm not seeing this here.
Which means?
Well, either he
had ice in his veins
or this is his
actual handwriting.
He was so sure that we would
never even get close to him,
he didn't even
bother to disguise it.
Do we have anything?
Yeah, there's something here.
Under the surface.
Take a look.
Indentations.
He wrote something
on a sheet of paper
on the same pad,
before he wrote this.
Umm...
Here, first column,
lowercase "a-i-n,"
then a space,
then uppercase "S,"
then a space, lowercase "n."
First crime scene?
Train Station?
Second word, three letters.
"T-e-l..."
Nothing more readable.
Telephone?
Telephone company?
Television studio?
Mmm, it looks like the "t-e-l"
comes at the end of a word.
Hotel! Motel?
I mean, this guy was going
for maximum impact, right?
Big targets, lots of victims.
That means someplace public.
Yeah.
Like the lobby of a hotel.
Yeah. Somewhere packed
for the July 4th holiday.
- Near the sights?
- Downtown?
KINCAID: Look, this is
the best I can give you.
There are more letters
down here on the page
but nothing I can decipher.
They may refer to
subsequent attacks.
- I'll just keep working on it.
- It's 9:03.
We've got less than three hours
left. Do you think you're right?
This is my best guess.
We can't empty
every hotel in DC.
HARDY: We won't have to.
Just cover the most
likely targets, right?
The big hotels
inside the city core.
Hope you're right,
Kincaid. Yeah.
We'll put small teams into them.
Tell them what to look for.
Make sure we
don't start a panic.
Hardy, you get the city
police on board with this.
We'll need them as backup.
I don't want any
uniformed officer
scaring this guy off, though.
Just tell them it's based on
the best information we've got.
No problem.
I'll contact the hotels,
have them beef up their own
security personnel as well.
Somebody gets trigger happy, we
get a shootout in a crowded hotel,
a lot of innocent
people could get hurt.
What's the alternative?
We sit here and do nothing?
We gotta get out ahead of the
curve with this guy, right?
I'm just saying that guns
and crowds don't mix.
Look, I know the risks,
all right?
It's a crime in
a federal district.
It's my call. Do it.
(PHONE DIALING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: You have
no messages at this time.
We've got everything
locked and loaded.
All the major hotels covered.
I almost feel bad for this
guy, having you on his case.
Why did you quit?
Three years ago,
I helped track down
a serial killer
called The Boatman.
He used to dump
bodies in the marina.
I investigated the notes he
sent boasting what he'd done
and how we'd never catch him.
I made connections that
got him 10 life sentences.
On his way to jail, he killed
his escort and escaped.
He came to my
house in the night.
I found him in my son's bedroom.
He had a gun.
He was gonna kill him.
He was gonna do
something to my daughter
and make me watch.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GUN FIRES)
I shot him.
I know that case.
My God, that was you?
That was me.
And your son?
Umm...
He was okay, physically.
Emotionally, he's
still working through it.
His memory flares
up without warning.
He has flashbacks
and his imagination
is working overtime.
I'm sorry to hear that.
You have kids?
(DOOR OPENS)
All the units are in place.
Hope we got this right.
(INAUDIBLE)
(RADIOS CHATTERING)
- (GUN FIRING)
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
CAGE: Nine dead, 15 wounded.
He hit the theater
up the street from the hotel.
Maybe that was his plan,
maybe he knew we were there.
Same black casings were found.
Now, two of the agents saw him,
gave chase, but he got away.
This sketch was the best we could do.
That's The Digger.
- LUKAS: What's this?
- CAGE: He's got a scar on his forehead.
Other than that, he just
looks like anybody else.
Anybody else programed to
kill on a dead man's command.
All right, copy it to everybody.
Can you talk to the mayor? She's
trying to put a press release together.
Can you handle it for me? Tell her
we've got a sketch of the suspect
- and we're having it distributed as soon as we can.
- HARDY: Sure.
And we've got the entire
downtown area closed down.
We're searching block by
block, building by building.
You won't find him. He's planned
all his escape routes in advance.
This is still
the only thing we have.
- Materials and elemental.
- Finally.
The main trace embedded in the
letter is brick dust.
Also traces of red clay,
sulfur, granite particles.
- Carbon in the form of ash and soot.
- This give you anything?
Well, not unless
I can cross reference it
with building permits,
environmental reports,
anything that the city might have that
can tell us where this stuff comes from.
Well, we can help with that.
We've implemented
new technologies
that help trace source materials
throughout the district.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
I have to take this.
Penny, what's happening?
The good news is
she's not claiming
you're an unfit parent.
The bad news is she
wants primary custody.
- What can I do to stop this?
- Well, my suggestion would be
that you and Joan
sit down, face to face.
Try to resolve this, maybe agree
to some kind of mediation.
If this goes to court, they'll
put the kids on the stand.
It's gonna be really hard for
them to look across the courtroom
at their mom and say no to her.
It's gonna be even tougher for
you to build a case against her.
The best thing we can do is change
her mind before it comes to that.
I don't know if I can get her
to do that but it's worth a try.
Good. I'll call her attorney
and make the arrangements.
Okay, you arrange it.
I have to go.
All right, well,
we can overlay information
from the city and the suburbs
from a variety of sources.
So where do you wanna go first?
Okay, I was thinking about
the red clay and brick dust.
That could be from
a demolition site.
All right. Contractors would
have to pull permits for that
so it should be
on file somewhere.
Pretty cool, huh? We've made
some progress since you left.
- Next?
- Okay, sulfur.
That's the byproduct
of a lot of things,
including vehicle exhaust.
No problem.
We got an EPA overlay,
which shows where it is
in its greatest concentration.
Generally we use this program to model
nerve gas and biological warfare attacks.
All right, lose the ones that don't
connect with the clay and brick dust.
KINCAID: All right,
particles of granite.
- That could be from construction.
- Yeah, maybe.
I also had to go to a
stonemason's yard last week.
All right, so check stonemasons'
yards, cemeteries, graveyards.
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
Lose the ones that don't
connect with the others.
Still too many choices.
KINCAID: Ashes and soot.
I worked this
case where that was
embedded in the note
of the kidnapper.
And the kidnapper was hiding out
in an old incineration plant.
(TYPING)
- It's not helping.
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
It's my daughter.
- Is everything okay, pumpkin?
- SHANNON: You'll be home soon?
I don't know. I'll be home
as soon as I can.
Is that why you called?
Is Robby okay?
He's great.
You sure?
He was really scared
when he thought
he saw him in the yard.
Yeah. You know what?
It's gonna take
a long time for him
to deal with that on his own.
That's why you and
I are there for him.
But there's
something else, right?
I can tell in your voice.
Is there something
going on with Mom?
You looked kind of worried
when she left yesterday.
Your mom and I have some things
that we have to work out.
Don't worry.
Everything's gonna be fine.
You're sure?
Yeah. Positive.
Give Robby a hug for me, okay?
And help Janet out.
Okay.
You need a hug, too?
I guess so.
I got one waiting for
you when I get home.
Just be a kid, okay?
Stop worrying, that's my job.
I love you.
Hey, boss? So I was thinking
about the soot and the ash.
Why is there so much carbon?
What about the emissions
from a crematorium?
Let's try it.
Crematoriums.
One location.
Satellite view.
There it is.
That's where the demand note
was written.
Name kind of fits. Gravesend.
We find something, it'd be
helpful to have you there with us.
I think what
she's telling you is
we need you for
another couple of hours.
I'm sorry, guys.
So what are we gonna use on him?
Feminine wiles or brute force?
Neither. Leave it up to you.
I'll meet you there.
I know lives are at stake.
But this is why I didn't wanna
get sucked back in again.
Having to choose between
the job and my family.
I respect your decision.
And I know how complicated
these things can be.
Well, good luck. You're very understanding.
You must have kids.
I had a son.
He was just a couple of years
younger than your son
when he died in a plane
crash two years ago.
Oh.
His father was on
the plane with him.
I was Special Agent
in Charge in San Diego
and they were visiting
my husband's family here.
It was a small commuter plane.
It went down in some
woods in bad weather.
There were no survivors.
I'm so sorry.
I transferred here so
that at least I'd be near.
I can't imagine.
It's like your
son and The Boatman.
You know, you just
keep pushing it away,
but it keeps coming back.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
This is Lukas.
Great, I'll be right there.
Couple of uniforms knocking
on doors have a lead.
As a law
enforcement professional,
I'd like you to
stay on the case.
But as my son's mother,
I'd say you'd be well within your
rights to tell me to get lost.
Look who showed up. I signed
them out for you just in case.
KINCAID: All right.
I'll take the vest.
We find this guy,
he's got nothing to lose.
Things could happen fast.
No gun.
These guys were
going door to door
with the sketch of The Digger. Some
guy down the street seems to think
he's seen him coming in
and out of this warehouse.
Let's go.
Kincaid, why don't you hang back a
little bit? Till we make sure it's safe.
It's clear.
MAN: Roger that.
I love what he's done
with the colors in this place.
Get Forensics in here
as soon as we can.
Not even a carton of
milk to get DNA with.
He cleared everything out.
Well, that would fit
with the psych profile.
Everything he does is
orderly and precise.
TV's still warm.
He hasn't been gone too long.
Hey, this looks
like the note paper
that the demand
letter was written on.
It tell you anything?
I can't really make it out. Just
looks like random drawings or doodles.
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
It's stuck.
- (BEEPING)
- This thing's stuck.
Get out now!
He's got the place wired!
It's gonna blow!
- Go! Kincaid!
- I don't wanna damage this.
- Kincaid! Now!
- Almost got it.
- Come on, let's go!
It's all we got.
CAGE: Come on,
it's gonna blow! Hurry up!
Move! Move! Move!
(YELLING)
- LUKAS: Get up!
- KINCAID: Hey!
- (GROANING)
- You all right?
LUKAS: Let's go!
KINCAID: Let's go!
Come on, Cage.
CAGE: Get back!
KINCAID: It's gonna blow! Go!
Go!
We're on it, Captain.
Yeah, 10,000 copies of the
sketch of the perp have gone out.
We're also asking newspapers
and television stations
to run it as a lead item.
Somebody is bound
to see this guy.
Hey, what happened out there?
Place was wired.
Booby trapped.
He must have figured we'd find
the place eventually.
Yeah. Whoever's
behind all this
has been one step
ahead of us all along.
But now we have this. And it might
tell us where the next target is.
It's mainly doodles, but there
seem to be letters underneath.
Can you write this down?
Yeah.
(HARDY CLEARS THROAT)
Okay, shoot.
Lowercase "a,"
"I,"
"I."
"a-l-l"?
Yup.
Lowercase "I,"
and uppercase "N."
"I," "N" for Norma?
Mmm-hmm.
And there appear to be some
indentations on these other sheets.
Some are quite deep,
others are very faint.
Another lowercase "I,"
with a line ruled under it
and four uppercase S's.
Scratch that.
They're dollar signs.
It appears that somebody was
working something out here,
trying to put the final
elements of a plan in place.
Why write it all down?
Maybe The Digger is
not all that smart.
Maybe he needs it all
spelled out for him.
That mark on his head
could be from a head injury.
He needs it all
written down, step by step,
and the dollar signs are there to
remind him what's in it for him.
Does it get us
any closer to him?
It might, if I can decipher
the rest of the scribblings
and fill in the gaps
between the letters.
I need to run this
through a program
that would remove
the scribblings
so I could see what was
originally on the page.
It doesn't give us
a lot to work with, huh?
KINCAID: It's like
a crossword puzzle
where we're missing half the
page as well as all the clues.
How's Cage?
Broke his leg.
Someone else is
gonna have to pitch
in that softball league he's in,
but other than that,
he'll be fine.
By the way,
next time I tell you to move,
move, or I'll leave you behind.
I need to run this
through my lab at home.
You can't do it here?
I've been away
from my kids too long.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to come with you.
Right now that's
the only piece of evidence
we have to our names.
Sure.
It's Margaret, by the way.
(DOOR OPENING)
It's Robby.
The Boatman.
You heard him?
Where did you hear him?
In the garage, moving around.
Okay. Take a deep breath.
Remember your
sword and your shield.
I heard noises and it was
just like the time when...
When he came. And...
All right. I'm gonna go down
and take a look, all right?
Okay?
And Janet's gonna stay here
with you while I do that.
And Margaret's gonna
stay here with you.
Okay?
All right, everyone get
acquainted. I'll be right back.
I'm Shannon.
Are you one of Dad's customers?
I'm one of his
friends from work.
This is Robby.
Wanna say hi?
- Hi.
- LUKAS: Hi.
Hey, don't worry.
Everything's gonna be okay.
(EXHALES)
Hey, Robby, remember that time
when we got sprayed by the skunk?
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
The door blew open and Mrs.
Elroy's dog, Chester, got in again.
- Thanks, Daddy.
- Mmm-hmm.
LUKAS: The Puzzle Master.
The name
an over-imaginative journalist
gave me for
helping solve a case.
But you like puzzles.
I like the challenge.
It bothers me to see
something I can't explain.
Like why my son's possessions
seem to have a life of their own.
This must be tough for you.
My son was as messy
as your son seems to be.
Maybe all boys are like that.
Yeah.
What was the thing
you said to Robby
about the sword and shield?
Something
the psychologist suggested.
It's a way for him to feel
like he has some power,
you know, like he's not
completely defenseless.
He's getting better at it.
It's a slow process.
The divorce didn't help.
Something like The Boatman can
have a real strain on a marriage.
I mean, there were
problems there, anyway...
Well, if there's anything else that
this paper can tell us, I'll find it.
It might take some time, but I'll
work through the night if I have to.
And I know that
there's a deadline
so you can stay
as late as you want.
SHANNON: Daddy?
I'm going to bed now.
Okay, I'll be right
up to put you to bed.
- Good night.
I'll see you again sometime?
Maybe. Yeah.
I'd like that.
Dad works too hard.
He doesn't meet enough people.
She's terrific.
Yeah.
I'm pretty lucky.
From what I can see,
your kids are pretty lucky, too.
Why don't you put
your daughter to bed?
This is gonna be an
all-nighter for me, too.
Just let me know
if you find something, okay?
Hey, I know we're under the gun,
but I need an hour tomorrow,
first thing.
Legal stuff. Gotta sit
down with my lawyer
and my ex-wife's.
I'm sorry.
Do what you have to do.
Thanks.
LUKAS: Kincaid's
made some progress
but he needs to do more work.
Right now,
we're gonna have to proceed under
the assumption that he won't
be able to tell us what
today's target might be.
And that means we continue
doing as we have been
and keep everyone on high alert.
Yeah, Metro will
be doing the same.
We're bringing all live bodies
from neighboring forces,
covering shopping malls,
places of entertainment,
anywhere that large numbers
of the public will congregate.
Hopefully, these headlines
will keep everyone at home.
But if they don't, we need to
be out there protecting them.
Something else.
It appears as though this guy
was ordered to kill three times
and then disappear for good.
And we missed him
at the train station,
we missed him at the theater.
If we don't catch him
in the act this time,
we may never find him.
This is our last chance.
JOAN: I'm not
attacking you, Parker.
This is about what's changed
in my life, not yours.
I'm sure we all agree
you've done a fine job
with Robby and Shannon,
Mr. Kincaid,
but now Joan feels
she's ready to get back
- into their lives as a full-time mother.
- We understand that,
but there's a reason why the
court gave Parker full custody.
That was over two years ago.
I had a drinking problem.
It's in the file.
But I was in treatment
and I'm sober now
and I'm in a stable relationship
with somebody
who wants to have the kids
be with us all the time.
Yeah, but you went on your
vacation without them.
That was the only
time Jerry and I
could get away and
you know that, Parker.
And I would have
taken them with me
but I'm not allowed to
leave the country with them.
That's something
you insisted on.
It's actually something
the court stipulated.
I gave up my career in
order to be with them.
Yes, and that career endangered
the lives of your family.
I learned to be a
full-time stay-at-home dad
and I'm good at it.
BEN: No one's saying
you're not, Mr. Kincaid.
We're just
saying that it's fair.
And it's in the best
interests of the children
for Joan to have
primary custody right now.
We have a child who
is still traumatized
by a violent incident
that happened at the house.
I have a letter
from his psychologist
saying how important stability
is to his complete recovery.
We referred this to a
child psychologist as well.
She said the best
thing for Robby is to be
out of the house
where it happened.
The presence of his father is a
continual reminder of the event.
We also have letters from Joan's
physicians and treatment specialists
saying that she is entirely fit
to assume full responsibility.
KINCAID: What about the kids?
What about what's best for them?
Shannon already asked me
if something's wrong.
She senses what's going on
and it's upsetting her.
Is that where you want them?
Back in court with us
fighting over them?
I've changed, Parker.
I want a second chance.
And I deserve the opportunity
to make my case before a judge.
- Now what?
- We get a court date, we argue your case.
In the meantime,
you don't do anything
to give them any
kind of ammunition.
Like what? Developing
a sudden crack habit?
It would be smart
not to do that.
I thought this wasn't about
me not being a good dad.
It's isn't. But the
playing field isn't level.
Everything being equal, most judges
would give the mother custody.
You know I can't
let that happen.
I'm gonna fight this
all the way for you.
I think we've got a really good
shot, but if this goes to court,
you know as well as I do,
it's a roll of the dice.
NEWSCASTER ON RADIO: Tension in the
street mounts as day three begins.
The mayor's plea
for people to keep
off the streets and not
gather in large groups
has been greeted with resistance
from those who are
determined to celebrate
July 4th in traditional fashion.
Anything less,
they say, is a surrender
to the violence of
the past two days.
What are you doing here?
HARDY: Lukas needs to
know what you've got.
We've got two hours left.
We're running out of time, man.
I know how much time we have.
I'm going as fast as I can.
Can I help you out?
Yeah. Pull your car around back.
And no guns in the house.
All right.
Nanotechnology, all right?
I have a program that
slices one sheet of paper
into hundreds and
hundreds of nanosheets.
It's like slicing a gene
so you can see inside.
Okay.
I printed these up last night.
We gotta comb
through all of these
and see if
there's anything here.
Okay, gotta be honest with you,
I'm not really sure
what I'm looking at here.
It's a bunch of squiggly lines.
Most of it's gonna
look like gibberish,
just let me know
if anything jumps out at you,
any letters or words or phrases,
anything that could be a clue.
Okay.
Yeah, keep moving.
This way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
(SIGHS)
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
It's Lukas.
Nothing?
From any of the units?
Ours? Metro?
Transit Police?
Okay, great. Thanks.
(RINGS)
Yeah?
Really? Nowhere?
Thanks.
Nothing.
Maybe he got cold
feet when he saw
how many guys we had out there.
Could be.
You don't think so.
I'm interested in fact,
not speculation.
You got anything yet?
No.
Just random letters.
SHANNON: Daddy,
can I have something to eat?
Be right back.
Hey. How about
some fruit salad?
Yeah. Can I ask you
something, Dad?
Sure, pumpkin. Have you
lost Marzipan again?
No. I just wondered if I could
stay up for the midnight fireworks.
Midnight? You think you
can stay awake that long?
I'd just really
love to see them.
It's so beautiful and everyone
cheers and waves their flags.
I've stayed up
past 12:00 before.
Yeah. That's a great idea.
Why don't you, me and Robby stay
up and watch the fireworks? Okay?
I'm gonna go back to work now.
So do you think we still need
to go through this stuff?
The guy didn't show, right?
Hey. I don't think we should
drop our guard just yet.
The three days are up.
Shannon just asked me if she
could stay up till midnight.
12:00 midnight.
The demand note didn't
say anything about noon.
It said he was
gonna kill at 12:00.
You really think he'd give us
an extra 12 hours to stop him?
It's also another 12 hours for him
to set up something really big.
We're not done
with The Digger yet.
Listen, you gotta
give me something solid
to go on this time, Kincaid,
if I'm gonna ask the mayor
to keep the whole city on
lockdown for Fourth of July.
HARDY: Okay, wait a sec.
It's the Fourth of July.
Yeah.
How do people celebrate?
And where in DC do
they go to do it?
You found it. You call it.
We think he's gonna hit
the Fourth of July crowd
at the National
Mall at midnight.
Now, I'm just guessing.
I'm not the expert here,
but the word "fire"
kept jumping out at us.
At first we thought
maybe it was open fire,
or maybe he was gonna light
a fire to cover his tracks.
I don't know.
But when Parker suggested
that the attack was gonna take
place at 12:00 midnight, I thought,
"Fireworks."
The kind of fireworks
that they're gonna set off at the National
Mall on the Fourth of July at midnight.
Now, the noise will give him enough
cover to get off a bunch of shots
before anybody raises the alarm.
In the ensuing panic,
he makes his escape.
It fits the MO. The train
station, the theater.
Those are places where a
large number of victims
are herded into one area.
And there's something else.
It's a headline act.
Murder in the nation's capital
at the stroke of midnight.
The writer of that note would
have wanted to go out on a bang.
LUKAS: 300 acres of trees,
jogging paths, public entrances,
buildings to take cover
behind, and targets everywhere.
We'll set up checkpoints on all the main
access points. Here, here, here and here.
Lock everything down, flood the
area with everything we got.
What if he's already inside
any perimeter you establish?
Let's assume you're right. He
thinks he's a step ahead of us.
Except this time,
we're one step ahead of him.
We know what he looks like,
we know his agenda,
and we're the ones
setting the trap.
You make it sound so easy.
But if we guess wrong,
we leave the rest
of the city naked.
You're right.
It's a hell of a risk.
It's one we're
gonna have to take.
Hardy, why don't you go
back to headquarters,
let 'em know what's going on.
I'll contact
the mayor and director
and I'll hook up with you later.
You got it.
Really putting your career
on the line, aren't you?
Probably.
It's all your fault.
Well, that's what
you get when you hire
the best document
examiner in town.
Well, you were Cage's
big idea, not mine.
Sorry you agreed?
Ask me at one
minute past midnight.
We're staying up for
the fireworks on TV.
Can't you stay?
I'm making a cake.
I would love to, Shannon.
I'm so sorry,
I have to go to work though.
Will you save me a piece?
Okay.
Ironic, isn't it? I lost
my family and got a career.
You gave up your career
but get to be with your kids.
Don't get sucked
back into this, Kincaid.
Not at their expense.
No job is worth it,
take it from me.
Be careful out
there tonight, Margaret.
- (ENGINE STARTS)
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
PENNY: Listen, Parker.
In anticipation of
the custody hearing,
the court has mandated home
visits for both you and Joan.
Home visits?
A social worker from the
Family Services Department
is gonna come by to
check on the house,
observe the kids,
that sort of thing.
- It's fairly routine.
- When is she coming?
The visits are supposed
to be unannounced
but a friend in
social services tipped me
that she's likely
to come by tomorrow.
Tomorrow? It's a holiday.
Joan's attorney is pushing the
court hard to move things forward.
You're planning on
being home, aren't you?
Of course.
Penny, are you
going anywhere tonight?
If I can ever get out of here. I'm
gonna go have dinner with friends,
and then watch the fireworks at
the Mall. Why, you need a date?
No. Just stay home.
Just tell your friends
to come over and
have a party there.
What are you saying?
Look, you're just gonna have a
better time if you stay at home.
That's all I can tell you.
Okay? I gotta go.
We're trying to encourage
people to stay home,
but obviously,
it's a big holiday.
And we've assigned
law enforcement
to every access corridor
in and out of the Mall.
And we know what time
the attack's gonna happen,
we know what the likely
MO is gonna be,
and we know what
the shooter looks like.
Maybe this time we're
in the driver's seat.
Way to go!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
- I win!
- Yeah, you do, buddy.
What do you wanna
play next, Daddy?
Let's play that really awesome
game, cleaning up the house.
No, Daddy.
No, it's a tradition.
Anybody who wants to
stay up till midnight
has to help clean up the house.
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(RATTLING)
I know how you feel, buddy.
No.
Oh, my God.
(DIALING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Hi.
- Where are you?
- I'm at a checkpoint near the West Mall.
- Is Hardy with you?
No, he's working
a Metro detail somewhere.
When was the last
time you saw him?
I don't know,
50 minutes, an hour ago?
So you don't know
for sure where he is?
No. No, what's going on?
When he took dictation from me
in the document lab,
he was disguising
his handwriting.
There's evidence of tremble
in several of his letters,
which means that
he was faking it.
But he made a devil's teardrop
on his lowercase I,
the same thing that
is in the demand note.
It's him. It's Hardy.
- (GASPS) - Hardy's the
one who's behind all this.
He's the one giving
The Digger his orders.
Hey. I need to be on the other
side of that door, fellas.
You'll need clearance.
Yeah.
Got that right here.
Up. Move.
KINCAID: It sounds crazy,
but look at the facts.
It was Hardy who led us into
the ambush at Gravesend.
It was Hardy who planted the
clue about the National Mall
and made sure that
I didn't miss it,
meaning that you have
got everybody over there
and virtually
nobody anywhere else.
I'll bet The Digger isn't
anywhere near the Mall.
Why would Hardy?
Where's the $20 million
from the city right now?
It's in the evidence locker
back at headquarters.
Are you seriously suggesting...
Wait a minute. What about
the guy who made the demand?
The one with the tape recorder?
A patsy. Hardy probably told him
that he would cut him in
and then he killed him,
so that we spend our time
running in circles,
looking for the killer,
not the real, live guy
who's still pulling the strings.
I'm on my way there.
Be careful, Margaret.
You said you'd
see Shannon again.
I want you to keep that promise.
Yeah.
(TURNING ON RADIO)
Agent Martin.
I need backup at
headquarters now!
Copy.
Hardy?
Hardy!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING)
Give it up, Hardy!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
Pretty cool plan, huh?
One of the greatest
heists of all time.
And maybe even the greatest.
The Digger. Where is he?
Is he at the Mall?
The Digger?
My old Marine buddy, The Digger,
never met an order
he wouldn't follow.
After that head wound,
the perfect killer.
Where is he?
He's exactly where he should be,
doing exactly what
I told him to do.
(BELL TOLLING)
(CLATTERING)
(SIGHS)
Damn dog.
(GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(GROANING)
(EXHALES)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
Shannon!
Robby!
(DOOR BELL RINGS)
Good morning. Ella Whitaker,
Child Protective Services.
- I'm here to interview your children.
- Uh-huh.
Mind if I come in,
Mr. Kincaid?
No.
Hey.
I won by two goals, Daddy.
Hello, children.
Hi, I'm Margaret Lukas,
friend of the family.
If you don't mind,
Mr. Kincaid,
I'd like to speak
to the children.
Yeah. Of course.
Hey, kids,
can you show me your rooms?
It's okay. She just wants to ask
you some questions.
Come on!
My room's over there.
- What?
- Hardy said he'd sent The Digger on one last mission.
I guessed he was after that
sheet of paper you took from him.
It's the only thing that
physically tied him to the crime.
I brought a SWAT team here
but we were too late.
You'd already taken care of it.
We found The Digger
up there on the stairs.
You were out cold.
For a moment, I thought...
Parker?
Hi, Joan.
Hello. Hello.
Hi.
Joan, this is Margaret Lukas.
She's a...
Hi. Nice to meet you.
I'm a friend of Parker's.
- Through his work.
- Nice to meet you.
If you'll excuse me...
She spend the night?
No.
You sure about that?
Quite sure.
God, Parker,
it smells like you've been
cleaning up a storm around here.
Yeah, well...
Where are the kids?
Upstairs with the social worker.
I'm gonna go bring
them their presents.
What did you do?
This place was a mess. I mean,
there was blood everywhere.
After we did forensics and bagged
the body, I called in a cleanup crew.
They weren't thrilled
about working on the holiday,
but I figured we owed it to you.
They did a pretty good job,
don't you think?
- Yeah.
- I mean, aside from the missing hallway table,
and there's some blood behind the
painting up there on the stairs.
ROBBY: This is my hamster,
Marzipan,
but it's Evil Monster Marzipan
because it's attacking
this little guy.
These are my other friends
and we're in our rocket ship.
We're blasting off.
Yeah. But it's the morning
because the sky is blue.
And this is me,
practicing my fighting skills.
You see?
That's my sword
and that's my shield.
SHANNON: I think something's
going on with Mom
and we might have to move.
I don't wanna move either.
I know Robby doesn't,
but sometimes we have to do
what the grownups tell us,
even if we don't like it.
I think Mom's better now
but don't worry.
I'll take care of you and Robby
if she gets the way
she was before.
Just like Daddy
takes care of all of us.
You've got some great
kids there, Mr. Kincaid.
You've done
a great job with them.
Thank you.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Joan? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Um... Parker,
you know that I love Robby
and Shannon so much, right?
And that I would do
anything for them?
Well, maybe now is not
the time to make a change.
And I'm really sorry. I'm sorry
that I put us both through this.
No. Don't be sorry. I mean,
you're their mom.
And that's never gonna change.
No. It won't.
Can you tell them that I
left the presents upstairs?
Mmm-hmm.
Can you tell them
that I love them?
Okay.
Where'd the table go?
And the painting...
you moved it.
- It doesn't look good up there. It looks...
- No, no.
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Wait. Um...
Hello, darling. Yes, it took a
little bit longer than I thought.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Um... I gotta go.
I... got a hungry
man on my hands.
Thank you.
Everything okay?
Better than okay.
Good.
I guess I should let you
and your kids be then.
Why don't you
spend the day with us?
I don't know,
I should probably...
The kids would love it.
Just the kids?
And their dad.
Sure. I'd like that.
Thank you.
There's something I wanna clear
up with you, if that's all right?
In the lab,
the first time we met,
I upset you somehow.
Offended you in
some way, personally.
Why do you say that?
'Cause I'm the Puzzle Master,
remember?
Whatever I said
bothered you so much
you had to leave the room.
And when you came back,
you were very angry.
I just wanna know
what I said or did
because I wanna see you again.
Before my son got on the plane,
he wrote me a postcard
to tell me how much he loved me.
He must have slipped it
in the box without a stamp,
not realizing,
'cause he was only six.
It showed up in the mailbox
a week after his funeral.
Postage due.
I have it. I carry
it with me everywhere.
I brought it to
a handwriting analyst.
And she said
the shape of these letters
and how they're spaced
shows that whoever wrote this
is very creative and charming.
And brilliant.
No patience for deception.
I know it by heart.
She also said that he has
a great capacity to love.
And that I was very lucky
to have a son like this.
If I didn't have
that to cling to,
I would have lost my mind.
And then you...
You say that it's all nonsense,
that it doesn't mean anything.
But it does.
But you said...
Yeah, but it's what your
son wrote that counts,
not the shape of the letters.
The teardrop "I" doesn't prove
that Hardy was a psychopath.
We can draw that conclusion
from his actions.
Just as what your son wrote
tells us what kind of
human being he was,
how much he loved you,
and what kind of a person
he was gonna grow up to be.
Paper is amazing stuff.
It seems fragile but it lasts
longer than almost anything.
The essence of
your son is on here.
There's a link between you
and him that can never break.
It makes him immortal.
Or as close to that
as any of us are gonna get.
Thank you.
So Shannon tells me you have a
letter written by Thomas Jefferson.
A letter that somebody claims
is by Thomas Jefferson.
That's what pays the rent now,
trying to figure out
what's fake and what isn't.
What the real thing is.
Yeah. I guess that's
what we're all looking for...
the real thing.