Alice!
Alice. Oh, God, there you are.
Are you all right? Huh?
What happened?
Jakey Snyder came a calling,
on account of that debt
he says you owe him
for the rustling job in
Colorado last spring.
I don’t owe him a goddamn dime.
Well, it don’t matter,
because he says he’s going
to burn down this
house with us in it.
Our boy stopped him,
and he went and said
he’d wrangle the money and
get it to Jakey tomorrow.
I tried to stop him, Mike,
But you know, our boy
is getting to the age
where he thinks he can
handle things by himself.
Yeah, and he’s stubborn,
too, just like you.
Where’d you say he was going?
The bank in Sweetwater.
Oh...
I’ll handle that. I’ll
take care of this.
If that little prick comes back
here, you know how to use it.
Lock the doors.
You bring our boy back safe.
I will.
Madame, you got my word.
Put that goddamn thing away.
What are you doing, Robert?
Jakey Snyder said
he’s going to kill us
if we don’t settler your debt.
Jakey Snyder’s full of
shit, and you know that.
We got no other choice, Mike.
I did not ask you to do this.
The fact that you drag
your little friend in there
-into our business? -Yeah.
I can take care of Jakey
Snyder, believe me.
If you’d done any
kind of preparation
or homework on
this goddamn thing,
you would understand
that that bank
has been robbed seven times
in the last six months.
They brought Pinkertons in.
They brought railroad
detectives in.
Every other man on the
street is some kind of lawman
waiting for one thing: for
someone to cross the line.
-I don’t really care.
-Oh, really?
This isn’t cattle rustling.
This isn’t grifting.
This isn’t all that
petty little bullshit.
You rob a bank and you’re done.
Your picture is going to
be on every goddamn poster
from here to Fort Worth.
-I don’t... -Hear me.
Lost time is never found again.
Get your hands off me, old man.
Oh, sure, go ahead
and kill yourself.
You’re making a mistake.
You’re gonna regret it.
-All right, nobody move!
-Jesus Christ.
Chaz.
You wait till they come out.
Hurry up, you’ve got 30 seconds.
No, please!
Mister, get out of my way.
Otherwise, I’m going to assume
you’re a member of this
gang and treat you as such.
No, please. One of those
kids in there is my son.
Give me a chance to
just talk to him.
Do you understand?
Please.
Everybody deserves a second
chance, for Christ’s sake,
Not him.
[women screaming]
Detective Schumacher, move up!
[groans]
Throw your guns out and
come out with your hands up.
And I promise you,
your punishment will be
just and appropriate.
If you go against me,
it will be a death sentence
for the both of you.
Run!
Dolly! I dropped Dolly!
[grunts]
Son, you’re all alone now.
The law’s all around you.
[gunfire]
Jolena!
[woman screams]
Oh, God no! My baby!
You want to end up like
your friend or that old man
who got in my way bleeding
out in the street?
Or that little girl who got
caught in the crossfire?
Please, no!
Let’s make this easy!
[panting]
[gunshot]
[gunfire]
[groans]
[grunts]
Who was that with you?
No one.
Name.
Butch.
Last name.
Cassidy.
Good afternoon.
I understand you have a
safe aboard this train.
Yeah. We do.
It’s in the mail car.
[chuckles]
Ha!
That was one hell
of a rehearsal.
-What do you think, Butch?
-Good.
Except that last part where
you ran up like an idiot
and said my name, Bob.
Yeah, yeah. Sorry about that.
Questions? Everybody
knows their job?
You bet, Butch.
Good.
You do have a conductor
uniform, don’t you?
Of course I do.
All right.
Last thing we do
before we ride out is
Isom goes and cuts the telegraph
wires at the ticket office.
Ben, Laura, this being
your first job with us,
on account of being down a man
with Will Carver
still locked up,
we’re only here for the loot.
Not to kill nobody.
You’re only going to use your
guns if the plan goes to hell.
But no shooting.
-Understood? -Got it, Butch.
Understood.
Half for today and
half for tomorrow.
Thank you, Butch.
See y’all tomorrow at the
Northern Pacific Rail.
Didn’t he say the Southern
Pacific rail the other day?
Yeah, yeah, he did say that.
He’s your boy, Elzy.
I mean Northern, Southern, I
don’t think it matters too much
as long as train comes
in 9:00 A.M., right?
As long as he’s on it.
I mean, he wants the
second half of his money.
He don’t want to be
looking over his shoulder
the rest of his life.
There won’t be much life
left if he doesn’t show up.
We better get out of here.
Got a big day ahead
of us tomorrow.
[neighs]
All right, boy. We’re going.
Train’s early.
Gonna have to catch up to it.
Let’s get it. Hyah!
[train whistle blows]
Let me help you
with that, Ma’am.
You sure it’s wise to
team up with these kids?
They’re a bit soft for my taste.
Uh-huh.
Butch Cassidy.
Breaking all them young hearts.
Butch Cassidy is a good scout
when it comes to robbing
banks and trains.
Always has a solid plan,
always gets the loot.
Nothing ever goes wrong.
There’s nothing to worry about.
I’m reckon that’s all true.
I just don’t see why he’s
so against killing someone.
To each his own, Ben.
As long as Butch
can hold his own.
If it comes to a gunfight.
That’s my girl.
You two knock it off.
-[train whistle
blows] -All aboard!
Wait, wait, who the
hell is that with Bob?
Hold on now.
Hold on.
Elzy?
Let’s just give it a minute.
I mean, maybe this guy’s shift’s
ending and then Bob’s coming in.
He would have said something
if that was the case.
Just give it a minute, okay?
Sheriff!
Butch Cassidy and the Wild Bunch
is robbing the Union Flyer.
We got this. Come on!
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the Union Flyer’s
9:00 A.M. departure for Durango.
Please have your tickets
prepared for boarding.
The Union Flyer?
It’s not even the
same train, Butch.
What are we gonna do?
I’m calling it.
What’s that mean?
We ain’t robbin’ the train now?
Hell, no.
I saw we do this kid.
I need that money.
All these trains
come from Dubois
got a company safe on them.
They’re all headed west
on that rail expansion.
And there will be
something on board.
And we take whatever they got.
Yeah.
Follow me.
Damn it, Curry.
Last call aboard 9:00 a.m.
Union Flyer. Thanks, sir.
Greeting. Tickets, folks.
Don’t do anything
dumb, Mr. Conductor.
We do as planned.
Butch, you sure we
should be doing this?
We don’t know nothing
about this train.
Isom, I’m need you to
calm down and focus.
What we doing, Elzy?
We’re going.
And who might you be, sir?
Name’s Edward. My
friends call me Eddie.
Well, Eddie, wait here a moment
with my friends won’t ya?
-Don’t do nothing stupid. -Yeah.
You, too.
Good morning, everyone.
Now, I’m not
looking to hurt you,
and I’m not after
your possessions.
Just need a little bit of
time and then you’re back
on your way to Durango,
is it? It’s a nice town.
Y’all look like a smart bunch,
so don’t nobody go
trying to be a hero.
Your lives ain’t worth it.
Schofield?
That’s a nice gun, old timer.
Sit tight now.
I got a dilemma I was hoping
you could help me out with.
Which one of these coaches
has a safe on it, Eddie?
Oh, they don’t tell us that.
[gun clicks]
It’s just a few cars back.
Kindly take us there, won’t you?
Yeah.
Knew that seed spitting
sack of shit Bob Meeks
couldn’t be trusted.
Working this shift
all da, Eddie?
-What? -You heard me.
Just you supposed to be the
only one working here today?
I don’t understand what
you’re saying, son, but yeah,
I’m working all day if
that’s what you’re asking.
You’re going to help us
out today, huh, Eddie?
Yeah. This is the car
with the safe in it.
Ain’t going to be no
surprises on there. No guards?
No, No, uh-uh, just the
safe in there, I promise.
Unlock that door and slide
it open for us, won’t you?
Yeah.
Climb up in there and open the
safe for us, will you, Eddie?
I can’t.
No, I can’t. I promise.
Wells Fargo, they don’t
give us the key no more.
Liar.
What he’s saying is true.
Throw some gunpowder
in that keyhole.
-We’ll blast it open.
-Sure thing.
Hey, boss, that
door is real thick.
I’m going to have to
use all the gunpowder.
We’re already here.
We ain’t walking
away from this one.
How big a blast are we talking?
I mean... it ain’t
gonna go beyond the car.
Make sure.
There’s kids and
parents on the train.
I want nobody getting hurt.
You got it.
Ha!
You’re Butch Cassidy.
Yeah. You all the
wild bunch, ain’t ya?
Of course, I should have
figured that one out.
See, Butch Cassidy
don’t kill nobody.
There’s always a first.
Ain’t nobody getting killed.
He knows who we are.
And you won’t say
nothing will ya, Eddie?
No, I ain’t going
to say nothing.
Hey, you know, it
was them Daltons.
Dalton gang done did it. Yep.
I’m ready to blow
this thing, boss.
All right, let’s clear the door.
Where do you think you’re going?
-Nowhere. Nowhere.
-Get over there.
All right.
[explosion]
It’s the Wild Bunch.
We’re being robbed.
Woo-hoo!
Get.
[cheering]
Look at all that money!
You wanted to walk a
couple minutes ago.
-I’m glad we didn’t.
-What’d y’all find?
Oh, it’s a good thing we
didn’t walk on this one.
Plenty of money
for everyone, baby.
Pretty good take, boys.
Let’s get it packed up,
let’s get it out of here.
[gunshot]
What the hell did you do?
He made a run for it.
You couldn’t have ran after him?
I warned him the first time.
I told you there was
to be no killing.
Get that loot packed
up and let’s go.
[laughs]
They shot Eddie.
[laughing]
Oh, yeah, baby!
All right, let’s split up.
Curry, Ben, Laura, you
had east. We’ll ride west.
Meet up at the Hole
in the Wall tonight.
I’ve had enough of this.
I’m going to send a
wire to Charles Siringo
at the Pinkertons.
[telegraph clicking]
Chaz, bring that to me.
What is it, Charlie?
Butch Cassidy.
And his Wild Bunch.
They’ve robbed a train.
And killed a man.
Want me to hold off on
the McCarty’s, help ya?
No, I’ll handle this.
What’s wrong, Butch?
Need to make sure no
one is following us.
Looks like we’re clear.
Sheriff!
Sheriff, you just missed him.
They killed Eddie.
Aw, shit. Which way
did they go, Bart?
Kid Curry headed
east with two of them
and Butch and the other
two, they gone west.
Nobody seems to be able
to stop the Wild Bunch.
We’ll handle it.
You think Elzy’s going to be
all right riding off on his own?
Yeah, he’ll be all right. He
had to lead them off trail,
make sure they don’t tail us.
We should’ve never join up
with Curry and them other two.
They’re crazy.
Killing that old
man wasn’t right.
No, no, it wasn’t.
Ain’t nothing we
can do about it now.
I’ll tell you what we can do.
We never work with them again.
Yeah, when Will Carver
gets out of prison,
we can think about it.
For now, we got to work
with the folks we got.
Otherwise, there ain’t no sense
in calling us the Wild Bunch.
Well, here they come.
Got to get going here.
-Come on, get ’em! -[gunshots]
Gunshots! Hey, hey!
Where are you going?
Someone’s shooting at us!
Come on, Sheriff.
Pick up that gun. Pick it up.
Shame.
[gunshot]
[harmonica playing]
Shouldn’t they have
made it by now?
Maybe they camped out.
Maybe they got caught.
Doubtful.
Or maybe they ain’t coming.
Why wouldn’t they show up?
Because they got a bigger
share of the loot than we did.
No, that ain’t Curry’s style.
He’s violent, but
always keeps his word.
He’ll show.
Yeah. Bob ain’t show.
Let it go, Isom.
Come on, fellas.
What’s with the faces?
I’m not too hungry
right now, Maude.
You don’t know what
you missing, Butch.
Ah, just take it.
Maybe you’ll be hungry in a bit.
Would you look at that?
Sitting around a
campfire, singing songs.
You save some food
for us, Maude?
Yeah, I got some leftovers, Kid.
What about Bob?
He didn’t show. Something
must have happened.
-Anyone follow you? -No.
-You? -No.
Better wipe that look
off your face, Butch.
You killed someone at
one of my jobs today.
I told all y’all there
was to be no killing.
If you hadn’t trusted Elzy to
bring on that bum Bob Meeks,
nobody would have died.
I’m sorry, Butch. I don’t know
what happened, but I trust Bob.
He’s a straight shooter.
As the leader of this gang,
I should have checked
Bob out personally.
Especially after you
and Laura saw him
confuse the name of the rail.
If there’s anyone
to blame, it’s me.
It’s my fault that
he died today.
I’m glad we agree on something.
So we going to split
this money up or what?
All right, then. Isom.
[laughing]
-Yeah! -Woo!
[cheering]
What’ll you buy me?
Ooh, whatever you want, baby.
I’m gonna spend a whole summer
drowning in women and tequila!
♪ I’ve been traveling ♪
♪ All night long
♪ Singing my song
What you going to do with
your share of the loot, Butch?
Retire?
You know ain’t nobody
live long enough
to retire from this, Isom.
Still ain’t answering
my question.
Remember Mike and Alice Cassidy?
Yeah, of course I do. Them
the folks that adopted you.
Well, you know, Mike
has since passed on.
Thinking about buying me a
small ranch near their property
outside of Dubois.
I help Alice out a little on
account of she’s all alone now.
That’s... That’s might
kind of you, Butch.
What you going to do on a ranch?
Someone got killed today, Isom.
I don’t want no more of what
happened today on my conscience.
I mean, it was bound to
happen sooner or later.
Just come with the job.
Feeling guilty
for that conductor
ain’t going to bring him back.
So now that you got
your share of the money,
it don’t matter that
Eddie was killed today?
I didn’t mean it
like that, Butch.
I’m sorry that we killed him.
I’m talking about you,
anyways. This ranch of yours.
Being a rancher.
Chicken, cattle, you
know, cows, all that.
That’s really what you want?
I want to be like Mike Cassidy.
Wake up, do the same
thing every day.
Chores, tend to the animals.
Have real work to do.
Growing up with him, I liked
that things had to get done.
Work had to get done every day.
Every day, I had
responsibilities.
Don’t sound too bad, really.
Owning you’re own land.
My daddy and his daddy,
they spent their whole
lives on the plantation.
I was lucky, I guess.
I got emancipated.
Hell, I might buy a
ranch right next to you.
Gonna have to do a
couple more jobs first.
Remember those numbers.
I got a safe at the Dubois Bank.
It’s the combination to it.
You’re welcome to
what’s in there.
That’s much appreciated, Butch,
but I don’t want no handouts.
That’s... That’s your money.
If you’re serious about
buying some property,
consider it a loan.
Get out now and pay
me back when you can.
I don’t know if I’m ready
for something like that yet.
Suit yourself.
Money’s there if you
change your mind.
Go ahead and hold onto that
for me, won’t you, Elzy?
Where you going?
Go check out some property.
- Y’all gonna be here, right?
- Hell yeah, we’ll be here.
We ain’t going nowhere. We
drank too much last night.
Yeah, we did, babe.
What are your plans?
Ride out to Robber’s
Roost, maybe.
We’re going to help
Harry Tracy on a job.
Careful on them trails.
They’ll be looking
harder for us now.
-Ready? -It’s a new day, Butch.
Get out.
[grunts]
Hold this a minute.
Hey, Karl.
Am I to understand you
got money to buy whiskey
but not pay for a chicken?
Huh?
I said I’d pay him next week.
That doesn’t answer my question.
[grunting]
Okay, I’m sorry. I promise.
[groaning]
I won’t do it ag...
No. You won’t.
Theft will not be
tolerated in Cheyenne.
And I don’t give a
damn if it’s a chicken,
a hog, or a herd of cattle
Now get.
All of you, get.
Come on, let’s go.
You hard of hearing, mister?
So this Karl fella,
is he a big problem
here in Cheyenne?
No. That was his first offense.
[chuckles]
-Did I say something funny?
-No. No.
I just admire your brand
of justice, Mr. Horn.
It’s called the law around here.
Fair enough.
Is there something
you want, Mr. Siringo?
I’m bringing in Butch
Cassidy and his Wild Bunch.
Dead or alive.
You may have heard
that they killed
an elder conductor
over in Wilcox.
Shot him in the back.
They also murdered
some local lawmen.
Yeah, I heard
something about that.
But it was Kid Curry that did
most of the killing, was it not?
Nonetheless.
Wild Bunch needs to
be brought to justice.
Hung by their necks,
every last one of them.
And I wanted to see if
I could recruit you,
Mr. Horn, in my endeavors.
I’m pretty settled in
here at the moment.
Understood.
You know...
The bounty is up to $30,000
for the whole Wild Bunch.
And I would be
willing, Mr. Horn,
to split that reward with you.
50/50.
That’s a lot of money.
It’s a lot of money.
We’re awfully close to
where we did that job
in Wilcox, ain’t we?
You know I want to be
close to Alice Cassidy.
Yeah. I keep forgetting
about Miss Cassidy.
What’s the local law like here?
They know me, on
account of Mike.
As long as I don’t
do nothing wrong
in Dubois, they
look the other way.
And I intend to
keep it like that.
Plus another banker here helped
Mike with all his affairs.
Isom.
You want that money
that’s in my safe,
why don’t you go on and get it?
I told you, I don’t
want no handout.
Ain’t a handout, it’s a loan.
I don’t want no loan, either.
I told you I make
the money myself.
Do it just like you.
When I’m ready.
You gotta learn to
commit to things, Isom.
Going back and
forth all the time,
don’t make up your
head about nothing.
Gonna be the death
of you one day.
Mr. Santiago
Maxwell, how are you?
Good.
I’m Fred Boone. No
relation to Daniel Boone.
-How are you? -I’m good, sir.
I’m Ted... Hiddlebottom.
So we are purchasing
the Bartlett ranch
just on the outskirts
of our little town.
- Correct, Mr. Maxwell?
- Yes, sir, that’s right.
I imagine we’ll be paying
cash for this transaction?
Or will it be in gold?
-Cash. -Cash is still good.
Oh, missing a few pages.
I’ll be right back.
Please, excuse me.
How much does this man
know about you, Butch?
Asking if you’re
paying in cash or gold?
Relax. He’s only asking about...
Don’t tell me to
relax. All right?
Does he or does he
not know who you are?
He knows who I am.
Just like the local law.
Fred altered Mike’s cattle
and horse paperwork.
Never steered him wrong
in all them years.
Here we go. If you
gentlemen follow me,
I can take care of you.
This is the title and the deed,
and I just need your
signature here, here,
here, and here.
How is Alice these days?
I’m hoping to help her out some.
That explains why you wanted
to purchase land there.
You have a generous heart.
Always in the right place.
Now there’s just the
actual money transfer.
Wonderful. I won’t even
bother to count it.
Just kidding.
I’m gonna get some fresh air.
Your friend seems
of the nervous sort.
The money’s all there.
You are now the proud
owner of the Bartlet Ranch.
Congratulations.
- Thank you, Fred.
- You’re welcome, as always.
And please, give my
regards to Mrs. Cassidy.
One more thing for you.
Some cookies from the "wife".
Oh, thank you.
I can’t wait to eat them.
Oh, Mr. Maxwell...
Just a little note
about a gold mine.
Wait until you’re out
of town to read it.
That man is the craziest banker
I’ve ever seen in my life.
Yeah, he might be strange,
but he is helpful.
What do you say we grab
a drink to celebrate?
-You buying? -Of course I am.
I could use a drink.
Hey!
-Sorry, sir. -Watch it.
Thought you said everyone
in this town was friendly.
Don’t know him.
Hey, isn’t that that
fella, Isom Dart?
I think so.
There’s a reward out for him.
Excuse me, sirs.
Hey, get back here!
You say you never
seen them guys before?
Never.
Hey, guess I gotta buy you
that drink another time.
Best to be clear out of
here before they come to.
Yeah, I agree with that.
You want to come back
to my ranch with me?
I got to get back to
the Hole in the Wall and
make sure Elzy and ain’t get
off with my share of the loot.
Be careful now. We’ll
all meet up again, soon.
Of course, Butch.
Hey, I appreciate you
bringing me along today.
It’s been real exciting.
Think about what I
said about the loan.
I will.
Get out of here.
I’ll see you, Butch.
Are you sure it was Isom Dart?
Come on, Sheriff.
Look who it is.
♪ Lord have mercy...
Excuse me, sir. We
need to talk to you.
God damn.
Turn around slowly.
Don’t make any moves for
that gun on your hip.
Now, that’s Isom Dart.
He’s wanted for cattle rustling.
Isom Dart was
arrested in Dubois.
Well, well.
Looks like we’re
going to have to pay
a little visit to Dubois.
You look parched.
Thank you, Alice.
Why don’t you take a break?
You know, it’s
been a while since
you’ve done this kind of work.
I sure wish Mike
could see you now.
He’d be so proud of you.
Oh, you still have
his old pocket watch?
Yeah, I do.
There’s something else going
on with you, ain’t there?
Mike made all this look so easy.
Mike made everything look easy.
But answer me this.
Why, after all them years,
do you want to come
back to what you left?
Alls I know is I
want something more
than robbing banks and trains.
If that makes sense.
Sure it does.
Kid Curry killing
that poor conductor
didn’t help none either.
Mike never killed nobody.
No, he didn’t.
But he sure came close
a couple of times.
Excuse me.
Did either of you lose a horse?
I found a wild one over yonder
hill grazing on my property.
Wouldn’t let me near it.
Must be old Billy.
Let him wander
from time to time.
You’re not worried
someone’s gonna snatch him?
I do apologize for
the inconvenience.
He usually manages to
find his way back home.
Well, I see you’re
working on a fence.
That’s a start.
I’m Alice, miss.
-And you are? -Etta. Etta Place.
-Pleasure to meet you. -And you.
Well, your horse has a name.
I reckon you have one, too.
Robert Parker, miss.
Nice to meet you, Robert Parker.
Could be straighter.
Yeah. Guess I don’t got such a
great eye for straight lines.
That’s an easy fix.
Got some twine?
Rope?
Thin rope.
-No. -I’ll be back.
Think I’m in love.
Robert Parker, you don’t
even know what it’s like
to be in love.
This town smells of shit.
Do you ever say anything
pleasant, Mr. Horn?
How do you want
to go about this?
What I want is to find
out where they are.
No matter what it takes.
I hold now status of law outside
of Cheyenne, Mr. Siringo.
I noticed you don’t wear badge.
So how is it that you attained
your position of authority
in Cheyenne, exactly, Mr. Horn?
Understood.
This is your lucky day.
Oh...
It’s official.
You’re a Pinkerton now.
Thank you for your
help today, Etta.
It was my pleasure.
Always happy to lend a helping
hand to a new neighbor.
As long as I don’t find his
horse on my property again.
That’d be such a bad thing?
How did you get so handy?
Well, my dad was a cattle
man and I was an only child.
He wasted no time putting
me to work on that ranch.
You know, there
was this one time
when Mike was trying
to teach Robert
how to saddle a horse,
all proper and all.
And Robert wasn’t
having none of it.
And Mike was trying to tell him,
a horse keeps air in its belly,
so you got to wait to
cinch those straps.
And Robert snaps back, "I know
how to ride a horse, Mike.
I ain’t no kid."
And he was like 16
years old, mind you.
And what happened?
Well, he spurred ol’
Cinco and he took off.
And sure enough, that
saddle slid to the right
and Robert fell off over
the fence into the pig slop.
It was a mess.
Mike wouldn’t let him come
in the house for a week.
Made him sleep in the barn.
I would’ve done the same thing.
Get out.
[grunting]
[gunshot]
Hey, hey! Watch
where you’re going.
Bob! Bob!
Who you running from, mister?
Move on.
Mr. Horn, Isom’s been sentenced.
He’s going to serve his time.
Leave him be, Sheriff.
You were seen with Butch
Cassidy and the Wild Bunch
at the Wilcox train robbery.
[screams]
I ain’t going to ask you again.
I ain’t telling you nothing,
you goddamn Pinkerton.
I could put a few more
bullets in that leg of yours.
And you will never
use that leg again.
Or you can tell me
what I want to know.
Go to hell, you son of a bitch.
Mr. Horn, no!
[gunshot]
I was hoping Isom
Dart would give up
Butch Cassidy’s location.
But...
I guess I should
have just asked you.
You see, a reliable
source informed me...
that the local
law, that’d be you,
looks the other
way here in Dubois.
That Butch Cassidy
frequents Dubois.
And has for some time.
I’d really hate to
start killing off
fellow law enforcement
to get what I need.
There’s no need for
that, Detective.
Butch used to stay out at Mike
and Alice Cassidy’s ranch.
But if you want the whole gang,
your best bet is to find
them at the Hole in the Wall.
The Hole in the Wall.
That pass out there
in Big Horn mountains?
Yes, sir. I hear that’s
where the Wild Bunch meet up
after a robbery.
You’re likely to
find them all there.
That’s what I hear.
You know where that place is?
Yes, I do.
You know...
I don’t take kindly to the
law overlooking fugitives.
Butch Cassidy never created
no problems here, Mr. Siringo,
Never conducted no
illegal activities.
I would have locked
him up if he had.
I mean, in his defense...
he kind of helped
out around here.
Picking up a hammer
to fix a leaky roof
or give money to poor folk.
He never created no trouble
here in Dubois, I promise.
He sounds like a real saint.
Pick up that trash
off the street.
Yes, sir, I will.
Were those stories Alice was
telling embarrassing you?
Because they shouldn’t.
They’re cute.
No, it just makes you
miss Mike, is all.
Yeah, I miss my parents, too.
Why do you call them Mike and
Alice and not mom and dad?
They ain’t my real parents.
Ran away from home
when I was young,
and I met Mike when I got caught
stealing food from
the grocery store.
He offered to pay for it and
asked me if I wanted
a job on his ranch.
Kind of ended up being
like a father to me.
Guess they sort of adopted me.
Well, that’s mighty generous.
So you live alone?
I live with my man.
Oh.
Where’s he at? When
do I get to meet him?
Well, he’s out of
town for a spell.
I don’t even know
if you’d like him.
Probably wouldn’t get along.
He’s different from
you, that’s for sure.
-How so?
-Well, he’s loud. Very loud.
And he dresses fancy.
Fancy?
Don’t seem like you’d be with
a kind of fella like that.
Yeah, well, I like fancy.
What about you?
-What about me?
-Why don’t you have a girl?
Yes. I guess I just
haven’t made time for it.
Maybe I haven’t met
the right one yet.
[panting]
I say we take our
chances and go in.
Patience, Mr. Horn. Patience.
-Hey, Maude? -Yeah, baby?
I’m through with patience.
[grunts]
You got him.
She’s still moving.
Hole in the Wall. I heard
stories about this place.
Yeah, it looks like someone
was here, but left in a hurry.
Yeah, who knows?
Gunshots look like they
echoed pretty good in here.
I should have
thought about that.
Who is she?
This is Maude Davis,
the woman to the now
deceased William
"Elzy" Ellsworth here.
[Maude groans]
She’s not going to make it.
Now we have to find
this Alice Cassidy.
How do you wish to proceed?
With extreme caution.
Butch... Butch!
I got a visit from
the U.S. Marshal’s
Office this morning.
They said Mike owes
years of back taxes
and they’re going to seize
the ranch for payment.
I can’t lose his ranch. I can’t.
Nobody’s going to take
your ranch from you, Alice.
All right? What’s all this?
It’s all them papers
they handed me
about how Mike owes the
state money and such.
I can’t understand
all this law talk.
Is Etta around? Maybe she can
make some sense out of it.
No, I ain’t seen
her in a few days.
I don’t know what
I’m going to do.
Go see Fred at the bank.
He’ll know what to
do. He always does.
Maybe it’s too soon for
you to go back into town.
You let me worry about that.
I’m a mother, I worry
about everything.
Hello, Alice.
Hello, Fred. So nice
to see you again.
Mr. Maxwell. What’s
all this about?
Alice has a little
paperwork problem
she’d like you to look at.
Let me see what you got.
Our government at times
can be so perverse.
Robbing a widow of
all she has left.
It’s despicable.
And there you go.
These papers officially
state that all
back taxes have
been paid in full.
But I didn’t pay you anything.
These papers say you
did. Right there.
But somehow the funds were lost
in transit to the
governor’s office.
But that’s not what happened.
It won’t be a problem.
You and Mike have
been customers here
since I was a kid,
sweeping up the floors.
You deserve to live
out life peacefully
and not be constrained by
our money-hungry government.
Thank you, Fred.
Hands where I can see them.
Make a move with your gun,
it’ll be the last thing
you do, I assure you.
Place it on the table
for me, won’t you?
Do I know you?
Nope.
I heard a story about a man once
carved a combination to
a safe into his pistol.
You know something about that?
I reckon a lot of men done
that one time or another.
Ooh, careful now.
Our government will
take you for everything.
Howdy, señor.
Would you mind filling
up a bag for me, please?
You know what? Make it two.
Oh, and go easy on the coins,
would you? They get heavy.
What are you looking at?
Your bank’s getting robbed.
Thank you very much, sir.
Have yourself a nice
rest of your day.
And as for the rest of you,
have yourself a good day, too.
It is a beautiful day
outside. The sun is shining.
It’s good to be alive.
Whoo!
That was exciting.
Well, I do have a
claim to file now.
And alert the sheriff.
And those back property
taxes you’ve paid,
they were just stolen.
You see? Everything works out.
Thank you for taking
me to see Fred.
He’s always been
such a nice man.
Are you sure you didn’t know
who that bank robber was?
No, never seen him before.
Are you okay?
Go get on your
horse and ride home.
I’ll catch up to you.
What is it?
Trouble.
You be safe.
Hands up.
Hold it right there.
That’s far enough.
You’re that fella that
robbed that bank, ain’t you?
Why are you following me?
Would you believe me if I
said I wasn’t following you?
No, sir, I would not.
You really ought to think
about removing those
numbers from your
gun, Butch Cassidy.
You told my girl your
name was Robert Parker.
Who’s your girl?
Etta Place.
Should have used that other
name you throw around.
What is it? Maxwell Sanchez.
I’m Harry Longbaugh.
You can call me
Sundance. Sundance Kid.
I know I’m not as famous as
you yet, but I aim to be.
I have some information to
give you. It’s important.
But first, would you mind
putting that gun down?
I can be a lot more useful
to you alive than dead.
Thank you.
Well, what do you
got to tell me?
I have been told from
a reliable source
that the Pinkerton Detective
Agency is looking for you.
Fellow by the name
of Charlie Siringo
and a no good gun for hire,
Tom Horn out of Cheyenne.
-You heard of them?
-Yeah, who hasn’t?
Word is Siringo and
Horn killed Elzy Lay and
Maude Davis at the
Hole in the Wall.
Who told you all this?
There’s an old fella in
the town of Cody keeps me
informed of things,
seeing as how the town
is just yonder of
the Hole in the Wall.
And I’m sorry to
keep on as such,
but I don’t know if you
heard about what they did
to Isom back in Dubois.
What about Isom?
Siringo and Horn dragged
him out of his cell
asking questions about you.
Isom wouldn’t give anything up.
Horn shot him dead. Cold blood.
Heard old Bob Meeks
had a hand in it, too.
Bob Meeks? You sure about that?
From what I hear, he
handed Isom right to him.
You’ve been so holed up
with your new ranch life,
you don’t even know
what’s going on
out there in the world, do you?
You need to be looking over your
shoulder from now on, Butch.
But if you need anything,
you know where to
find Etta and me.
Alice.
Mrs. Cassidy.
Is there by any chance,
anyone with you?
If you’re with the
U.S. Marshal’s office,
I got the paperwork there.
Now leave me alone. You
ain’t taking my land.
We’re not here about
your land, ma’am.
We’re with the Pinkerton
Detective Agency
and we’re looking
for a known fugitive.
[gasps]
A fugitive we were told by
a reliable source was here.
Who?
Butch.
Cassidy.
Butch Cassidy, the bank robber?
Same last name, gentlemen,
but no relation.
Yes, yes, we know that,
but are you expecting
him anytime soon?
I don’t. Why would I?
Then tell us where
we can find him.
I think I already
answered that question.
Mrs. Cassidy...
Just tell us where we
can find him, ma’am,
and we’ll be on our way.
Don’t...
Please don’t make
this difficult.
Is this what you
detectives do now?
Come into little
old ladies homes,
a huffing and a puffing
and making up stories
that make you feel bigger
than you really are?
Huffing and puffing.
Have you ever heard of a man
named Elmer McCurdy,
Mrs. Cassidy?
No, I ain’t heard of
him neither. Excuse me.
Would either one
of you gentlemen
like some tea or coffee?
No, ma’am.
Coffee, Please.
Well, truth be told,
I’d be surprised if you
said you had heard of him.
Elma McCurdy was a lowlife
bank and train robber,
much like your Butch, in fact.
Though not nearly as well known.
And as is the usual fate of men
in McCurdy’s chosen profession,
the day came that he was
shot down in the street
like a rabid dog in a violent
gunfight with the law.
Justice served.
Then the strangest
thing happened.
A man arrived in
town professing to be
McCurdy’s long lost brother.
Identified him as
such, claimed the body.
Took it away.
Ah, but it was soon
learned that man had lied
because, in fact,
McCurdy had no brother.
And that stranger,
he was, in fact...
the owner of a little
traveling carnival show.
You know, the kind that
likes to put on display
dead outlaw’s mummified remains.
Gruesome business, but
no doubt a profitable one
for that little traveling show.
But as a mother, I’m
sure you’ll agree,
such an undignified end to the
life of young Elmer McCurdy.
I cannot imagine how...
ashamed and heartbroken
his mother must have been
when she found out
about all that.
Tell me, Mrs. Cassidy,
do you like.
carnival attractions?
No,
I don’t.
Ah!
Now, if you’ll
excuse me, gentlemen.
Mr. Horn.
[gunshot]
Oh!
Alice! Alice! Are you all right?
What happened?
This is all my fault.
No...
I love you with all my heart.
Hey. Who’s there?
Answer me.
Show yourself.
Mike?
I watched you die
out there, Mike.
I get that, son.
And you better get this.
Charlie Siringo didn’t
want me. He wanted you.
Alice never forgave herself
for not stopping you that day.
Not stopping the both of us.
Her thinking that
you were dead...
I watched her die a little
bit every single day.
Blaming herself.
And laying on the
street dying, almost...
bleeding.
I was sharp enough
to give him an alias
so he couldn’t track
me back to you and her.
I’m not sure they believe me.
They didn’t think
I was reliable.
So you know what they
did? Lock him up.
Put him in the goddamn prison.
Five years. I did my time, son.
Three weeks ago,
they let me out.
I was still afraid that Siringo
would follow me to you.
Siringo still killed
Alice, didn’t he?
Yes.
So why are you here now?
I regretted never being
able to go back to her.
To hold her, to comfort her.
I let her down. That’s on me.
You still ain’t
answered my question.
Why are you here?
You’re the same kid as you
were when you were real young.
Turd-headed big time.
You can get it done.
You still in love with that.
That’ll get you
one day or another.
You go after
Siringo by yourself,
you know what’s going to happen?
You’re going to end up
just exactly like me.
You’ll be in prison.
You’ll do time.
And if that doesn’t happen,
he will find you and
you will be dead.
That’s a chance I’m
willing to take.
So are you with me or not?
No, son. I’m not.
You’re going to let
them get away with it?
They took Alice from us.
Yes, they did.
I’ll handle it again myself.
Just like I did in Sweetwater.
Who’s there?
Reckon I might find you here.
Where’s Ben and Laura?
Away.
Who’s that there?
Some fellow thought
he could cross me.
A couple of Pinkerton
detectives are looking for us.
Ain’t nothing can’t be handled.
I wanted to see if
you and the others
were up for another job.
Yeah, like last time
with your pal, Bob?
No, thank you.
Siringo and Horn
are coming for us
and they ain’t going to
stop until they kill us.
I say we get to them first.
Rob the Southern
Rail down in Folsom.
Ambush and kill them
at the same time.
What happened to
your no killing rule?
They tortured Isom
before killing him.
Bob Meeks had a
hand in that too.
Where did you hear this?
Outlaw I ran into.
Calls himself Sundance.
Never heard of him.
They killed Elzy and
Maude. They murdered Alice.
They killed Alice?
They left a note telling me
that I couldn’t hide from ’em
and I’m gonna kill ’em
with or without you.
Let me see your gun.
So you really got it
in you to do this?
I’ve never raised my
gun to kill a man,
but I’d shoot the devil
between the eyes if I could.
The Great Train robber Butch
Cassidy out for revenge.
I like that.
You can’t let them get away
for what they did to Alice.
But how do you
know they’re going
to show up at the train station?
There’s a banker at the
Wyoming National Bank
in Dubois, handled all of
Mike and Alice’s affairs.
Mine, too. Fred.
He’s a good man.
He won’t readily give
anything up to him,
but we’ve all heard
of Horn’s methods
on getting fellows to talk.
Except for Isom.
So how do you know they’re
going to go to the bank?
Because that note they left me
written on one of Alice’s
property papers from the bank.
Fred gives up the location of my
ranch, which he definitely will,
I’ll make sure to leave
something there for them
that’ll lead them
straight to Folsom.
Whether they show up or not,
you can have all the money.
All right.
You let him go, let’s
you and I get to it.
He ain’t going nowhere.
He’s counting worms.
Come on, I’ll take you to them.
[grunts]
Please. I don’t understand.
What have I done, detectives?
Is that blood?
Now Butch Cassidy
came into your bank here
with Alice Cassidy,
and they had you
forge that document.
I’m sorry. He threatened me.
-I was afraid he was... -[thud]
Ah! I was afraid he
was going to kill me.
That’s not the way he works.
You and I both know
that, don’t we?
Now, you’re not in trouble
for the forged document.
You sold some land at
Butch Cassidy a while back.
I did. But that was a
perfectly legal transaction.
Where’s it located?
Where the road comes to a fork.
Alice Cassidy’s house is on
the eastern trail, right?
So, Butch Cassidy’s
house is off the western.
It’s called the Bartlet Ranch.
You follow the western trail
around down through some
small hills, and it sits at
the base amongst the trees.
It’s a small house.
You can’t miss it.
You wouldn’t lie
to us, would you?
No, sir. Absolutely not.
I would consider
him a friend, but...
Sometimes you have to think
about yourself, right?
One last thing, sir.
Do you happen to
know if Butch Cassidy
has any company right now?
Every time I’ve seen
him, he’s always
been in the presence of Alice.
Sirs...
Whose blood is on the paper?
Just be thankful
that it isn’t yours.
Appreciate your help.
We riding out to
Cassidy’s place?
Not just yet.
Let’s pay a little
visit to Sheriff Beck.
See if he and his men
can atone for their sins.
Please, don’t shoot.
Not to worry, ma’am.
We mean you no harm.
We’re looking for a known
fugitive. Butch Cassidy.
This... This is his
residence, is it not?
Robert Parker lives here.
Mr. Parker and Mr. Cassidy
are one and the same.
I did not know that.
-So is he inside? -No, he’s not.
Move aside, ma’am.
Step down for me.
What is your name?
Ethel. Ethel Porter.
You don’t mind me asking, what
is your relationship to Butch?
Or should I say Mr. Parker.
House is empty.
Your relationship, ma’am?
He’s my neighbor.
I live over yonder.
We met a while back.
He asked me to look in on
the place and tidy up a bit.
And do his laundry?
That’s neighborly of you.
Did he happen to
mention where he went?
He was riding on down to Folsom
to meet up with
some old friends.
Don’t move.
-Do you believe her? -I do.
Only because the
Southern Pacific Railroad
stops there to
distribute payroll.
To the rail construction sites.
That would be a
big take for them.
And she mentioned he was
meeting up with old friends.
It could be Curry and his crew.
Very well could be.
Which means we’re going
to need a little help.
Am I in trouble, sirs?
No, ma’am, you’re not.
Thank you for the information.
Oh, just a little suggestion.
I strongly advise you not to
fraternize with no criminals.
It’s not particularly
good for your health.
Good day.
[chuckles]
Looks like they fell for it.
You okay, darlin’?
Yeah.
Come here, come here.
I’m here.
I’m here. What happened?
I for sure thought
Butch was wrong about
two lawmen killing
Alice Cassidy, but...
Now I believe him.
Yeah, and they’re gonna get
what’s coming to
’em, I promise you.
But now I got to go saddle
up and let Butch know
- they’re on their way.
- I don’t want you to go.
-Why? -I just don’t trust it.
You wanted me to help Butch
out in the first place.
I know, I know, but
you didn’t see them.
They have a devil in their eyes.
I’ve seen them. I’ve seen them.
I just don’t...
I don’t want you getting killed
over his personal vendetta...
No matter how wrong it was
them killing Alice Cassidy.
I just don’t trust it.
I know. I know you don’t.
But I’m not a fan of
giving someone my word
and not following
through on it, Etta.
We may need his help one day.
I’ll come back to you.
[bell ringing]
Bank guards.
Yeah, I see ’em.
I don’t see Sundance.
Don’t need him, anyway.
Horn and Siringo show,
there’s four of us.
I like them odds.
That’s a good score.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
We’ll take it from here.
I’d drop those guns to
the ground. Nice and slow.
Nice and slow.
Good.
Get out of here.
[laughing]
Ooh-wee.
Where are these Pinkertons?
If they ain’t here by the
time that money’s loaded up,
Butch, you’re on your own.
We’re here for the money.
You’re here for revenge.
[trains whistle blows]
[grunts]
This is heavy.
[gunfire]
[horse whinnies]
[grunts]
Whoa.
[gunfire continues]
[grunts]
Ah!
I’ve been shot!
Get over here.
Die, you son of a bitch.
-No. -What are you doing?
I told you I want him alive.
You shoot that girl, you’re
going to jail with ’em.
Do you understand me, Mr. Horn?
Drop that gun or
I’ll put a bullet
in this little girl’s head.
Put ’em down.
Son of a bitch.
Butch!
He’s not gonna shoot.
-[grunting] -Butch!
[laughing]
Don’t you do it.
Don’t!
Oh, shit!
I got him. I got him.
Butch, get out of here, go.
I ain’t leaving you.
You’re worth more to us
alive than dead, Butch.
We’ll get ’em another day.
-Go. -I ain’t leaving you.
Go on. Get.
-Go! -Go.
I’ll draw him away
from us, all right?
[groans]
No, I’ll handle this.
[gunfire]
Take that hand off your
wound and raise it up.
Do you think you can get it?
Get your back up
against the wall.
Now get.
Sheriff Beck,
retrieve their guns.
- What about these three?
- They’re not going anywhere.
Sheriff Beck, watch
them, if you please.
Where the hell were you?
With Etta.
-Is she okay? -She’s fine.
[gunshot]
Ah!
-I got him. -They shot me.
Come on. Come on. Get up.
Well, well, well.
Look at this. This is
a most prosperous day.
Two of the most dangerous
outlaws in the West
at the same time.
Only difference between
the two of you and us
is them fake badges you wear.
Tie them up, Mr. Horn.
-Give me your hands. -Stop.
Holster that gun, Mr. Siringo.
Or you’re a dead man.
Oh, you wouldn’t like
her when she’s mad.
Drop them, boys.
Thought you two could
need a little help.
Turns out I was right.
That’s my girl.
I told you she was lying to us.
I heard about your
methods, Horn.
Is it you who killed Alice?
Yes.
But if it’s any
consolation to you,
at least she died
with some dignity.
Unlike your yellow
belly friends.
Ellsworth, Maude and Isom Dart.
She was shot in the back.
What difference does it make?
She was just
another filthy whore
that had what was coming to her.
Well, so much for the legend
that you never killed a man.
Now question is, what do we do
with Detective Siringo here?
Is it true what Horn said?
You didn’t have
nothing to do with
killing Alice or them others?
Don’t matter, Butch.
He used Horn. He’s
got just as much blood
on his hands even if he
didn’t pull the trigger.
I say we kill him right
now and be done with it.
No, no, no.
Take off your belt, Mr. Siringo.
-Nice and slow. -What? Why?
-Then what? -We tie him up.
And then what, Butch?
What the hell did you do?
He’s going for his holdout gun.
It was either us or them, Butch.
And good damn riddance.
Nothing but a bunch
of filthy cockroaches.
The both of them.
He’s a Pinkerton
detective, Sundance.
Only gonna have more
coming looking for us now.
Well, then we better get
going now, shouldn’t we?
What about all that money
from the Folsom train?
Back at the station.
You didn’t even
get the damn loot?
There’s no way I could have
loaded it up on my horse,
all them bullets flying.
Well, it’d be kind of a shame
to leave all that money behind.
We can go back and get it.
Now we’re making sense.
Thank you for saving
the day, darling.
Whoa.
Put that down.
I’m sorry.
Charlie Siringo threatened
to kill all of us
if we didn’t help him.
You go on and get out of here.
Make sure I don’t see you again.
Didn’t think you’d
come back for us.
Yeah, I came back.
Let’s get you on
our of here now.
Let’s get out share of
the loot and split up
before any more of
the law shows up.
What about Siringo and Horn?
Counting worms.
Killed ’em?
You don’t got to worry
about them no more.
Your take.
What? That’s it?
Come on, fellas. The three of
us make a pretty good bunch.
Yeah, I reckon.
Did you want to come with me?
I mean, it’s not a bad idea.
It’s only a matter of time
before the law comes
looking for us.
Yeah.
They’re going to find
our home sooner or later.
True.
They might even be waiting
for us when we get back.
This ain’t going
to get us too far.
Yeah, we’ll probably have
to pull a few more
jobs along the way.
You up for it?
Oh, yeah.
Well, you know I’m in.
Let’s ride.