Whoa!
Why you always gotta be swinging, huh?
You broke my belt loop.
Gimme a light?
Get your own light.
- Food?
- Yeah.
So, how many cars you steal?
Four. You?
Two. You'll learn.
-I set out for two and I got two.
-Well, why didn't you set out for four?
If I was in a mood for four,
I would have taken four.
I could triple you on your best night
and not even break a sweat.
Mm?
Okay.
-You a gambling woman?
-Lay it down.
Well, we each pull one more.
-First one back to your place wins.
-Wins what?
Well, I win...
you perform a service of an oral nature
involving the scraping of knees
and a sore jaw.
-Betting for sex is desperate and cliché.
-And necessary.
Look, I'm not gonna lie to you,
but on my list of things
I'd rather be doing,
training a rookie outside a grease pit
is about neck and neck with a colectomy.
-I'm not a rookie.
-Compared to me, you are.
Lesson one.
See that skinny weasel inside the diner,
chomping down on chicken tenders?
-Yeah.
-He works for Mitch Murray's chop shop,
which we've been
trying to bust for two years.
Why haven't we?
He's good.
And the girl?
Better.
I'm loyal, respectable,
alarmingly attractive.
I should be peeling down your panties
on a nightly basis.
But, no. It's, "Tony, unhand my thong.
Tony, get your face out of my ass."
Just tell me how long I gotta wait.
Gimme a time frame,
so I don't get bitch-slapped
every time I...
take a crack at your zipper.
You'll get me when you do it.
Do what?
Well, there's something a guy has to do
before I get dirty with him.
Or else I feel cheap and disgusting.
Oh.
So, every guy you've ever slept with
in your entire life
has completed this mystery task.
Every one.
Tell me.
If I tell you,
then you're gonna swear up and down
that you were just about to do it.
You could have been planning it tonight,
for all I know.
But if I tell you, and then you do it,
then I won't believe
you would have done it originally,
and nobody gets nothing, so...
Tell me.
No.
Well, what letter does it start with?
You know, every cop from Maine to Miami
has tried to outdrag this chick.
She's like that stringy cartoon bird.
You could be right on top of her,
then boom, like a bat outta hell,
she's gone and you're standing in the dust
chewing gravel.
It's poems, isn't it?
It's none of your goddamn business.
-That ass is my business.
-Are we gonna bet, or aren't we?
You're scared. You're scared of men.
Oh, Tony, is that you...
Is that you being deep?
Okay.
Johnnie Walker Blue.
And don't roll up in Aunt Ethel's Nova.
Go for a classic. Pre-70.
Sixty-seven.
Don't hurt yourself.
Well, giddy up.
-Come on, honey. Get in the car.
-No!
Come on, please.
-I just wanna talk to you.
-No, Doug. Get lost.
-Come on, sweetie. Just get in the car.
-No!
Come on, please, baby.
-Come on, get in the friggin' car!
-Get lost, Doug.
-I'm trying to talk to you.
-Get off! Get off of me!
Get off of me!
Don't make me smack you again.
Sit in the car.
Just get in the...
Excuse me.
Sweetheart, when I'm talking to you,
you'll know,
because I'll be looking somewhere
in the vicinity of your face.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
Ohh! Ohh!
-You owe me 50 bucks.
-You said Sunday.
I said Saturday.
-Who's your pal?
-Doug. He popped me.
Ow!
-Oh, yeah?
-She stole my wallet!
Oh, yeah. After he popped me.
Brenna, when people lend you money,
you pay it back in a timely fashion, okay?
Ahh!
-Double or nothing.
-What's the bet?
How many teeth come out when I smash
this punk's face against his beamer.
-What?
-Three.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
This bitch steals my wallet,
and you're busting my teeth?
-That's wrong.
-That's right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait.
Wait. Let's think this through, honey.
If there's no debt,
then you wouldn't need to bet.
-In theory.
-So if I gave her the 50,
then we'd all be cool, all right?
Oh, lookit there, Doug.
It's a possible solve.
But far be it for me to explain
a man's chivalrous nature.
No, no, no.
No, no, I'm cool, I'm cool...
Get out of here, punk.
Here's your wallet, Doug.
Thank you.
Oh, come on, Sage.
Enough with the idiot boyfriends,
all right?
Well, he seemed sweet.
6-4-Q-J-A-3.
Brenna again?
You know, it gets me all weepy.
What?
The way you look after her.
-It's a tender thing.
-Someone dusted your Froot Loops, man?
Is that him? You got Doug's address?
Kneecaps?
No, I'd just bust a limb.
Ow.
Jesus.
-What are you doing?
-Calling it in.
You want the whole department to know
that you're getting your ass whupped
by a girl in a Dodge?
-Left! Left!
-No! Right. She's not going left.
-Okay, go right.
-Unh!
Easy, easy.
Oh, Jesus.
Ha!
Whoo-ooh!
-Great.
-Out of the--
My Aunt Gertie could out-drive you
blindfolded on a dead goat.
Yeah? I'd like to meet your Aunt Gertie.
Oh, shit.
Shit! What's she doin'?
Jesus!
She's up top.
Yo! Open the flap.
- You hot?
- Open the flap.
-Sage, I can hear the sirens.
-It's an audio book.
I can't help you, Sage.
You know what?
That's fine, all right?
I'm coming through anyway,
so get out of my way.
Sage, I'm not opening these doors.
-She's here.
-Drive.
-She's right here.
-Would you drive?!
Whoo-ee!
You never come back hot.
What's wrong with you?
But...that is a '66 Charger,
383, four-barrel.
Man, I pity the guy who lost this car.
How you know it's not a girl?
What kind of chick drives around
with plates that read "BADASS"?
One that knows how to pick a Dodge.
Hey, your kid ever finish
that model Chevelle?
Yeah. Got it built, painted...
named after you.
-Really?
-Yeah.
She says if you don't come to
her birthday party, she's not having one.
All right. I'll bring her a piñata.
Sage, you don't wanna go in there.
Sage. Sage--
Well, you're gonna go anyways,
so what does it matter?
Two Mazdas, one vintage Dodge.
Grand.
-Was that you that came back hot?
-Yup.
Look, I pull 30 cars a month, Mitch.
That's five times more
than any potbellied ape
dragging his sack around this place.
I came back hot. I'm sorry.
I pulled it off.
Have you seen the car?
It's a collector. No damage.
Mitch, if you're gonna get your nipples
all in a knot,
I'm gonna take my talent elsewhere.
He came back hot.
Hm.
Are you gonna come back hot?
Here's $500.
Sucks, dude.
Hey, in approximately 30 seconds,
Tony's gonna roll in here
with some pimp's nasty-ass pink Ford,
and I'm not gonna say a word.
Uh-uh.
I am just gonna point
at this exquisite chariot...
and just watch the tears
flow from his eyes.
-Tony took off.
-What? He's been here?
Yeah. He just dropped that Porsche off
about an hour ago.
You're kidding.
Sorry.
You don't have to sleep with him
or anything, do you?
God.
- Blue Label.
- Shot?
-Bottle.
-Bottle?
You, uh, lose a bet?
Never.
Hey, sport, you forgetting something?
I'm having a friend over
and I wanna impress him.
Hey, babe, you win.
Tony.
Oh--
Yo! I'm taking the Charger.
- The hell you are.
- Tony's gonna die.
What, someone's gonna kill Tony
'cause of a Dodge?
-Hey, hey, hey. What the fuck?
-Not kidding.
Wait, wait, wait.
Mitch leaves in an hour, okay?
I'll meet you around back.
-I can't do it.
-Sage, he'll kill you.
Wait. Wait.
It's for the padlock.
Step away from the Charger.
Mitch, listen. Whoever owns this car
has Tony, all right?
And if I don't get it back in 30 minutes,
Tony dies. Please.
I'll buy it back, all right?
-All right. 1,000.
-You only gave me 500.
-I'm asking 1,000.
-I don't have 1,000.
Well then, you don't have a Charger.
I'll pay you tomorrow.
-Get out of my way.
-Get out of the car, Sage.
-Get out of my way, dude.
-Get out of the car!
I'm not kidding with you, Sage.
Get out of the car!
You wanna leave? Fine. Be my guest.
You ain't going anywhere!
Gimme the gun.
Hey. Take it easy, dude. Hey, hey, hey.
If she doesn't go, Tony's gonna die.
Fuck!
Sage!
Whoa!
Unhh!
Unhh! Unhh! Unhh!
Get up!
Unhh!
Tony?
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Tony?
- Whoa.
- Hey.
-Would you look at this place?
-What are you doing?
Yeah. It's friggin' Babylon.
Just wanted to introduce my partner.
Oliver Fitzgerald.
You may recall kicking the almighty crap
out of him earlier this evening.
Fitzy, this here is Sage.
Hey, is that tequila?
Look, I know what you're thinking.
Police harassment. Unlawful entry.
Blah, blah, blah.
But here's what.
Right now, we're not cops.
Okay? We're off duty.
We're just a couple of guys
dropping by for some drinks.
Hmm?
See, my partner here,
he just made detective, so I'm...
I'm showing him around,
introducing him to the local talent.
Listen, Sage, you gotta tell me something.
-Who taught you to drive like that...
-Hey! Yo, man...
Can we do this another night?
What's the matter? You don't like us?
No. It's not that.
I mean, I'm always looking
for an opportunity to do shots
with the local law enforcement,
but tonight's a bit...
Rigorous?
You feel me.
Where's your can?
I'm gonna nail you on this one.
Yeah. We'll see about that, little rookie.
So, how long you been boosting?
-I'm sorry. Boosting?
-Boosting cars. How long?
-No one says that.
-Yeah. What do they say?
If I tell you, will you leave?
-Maybe.
-Yeah? All right.
Zag.
-Zag?
-Yeah. Zag.
Get it? Like zip and zag.
You know, like, "Hey, Lou,
you zag any Fiats tonight?"
"Yeah, Sage. I zagged four of 'em.
Right off 63rd and Main.
"Can't talk now.
I'm off to go to zag a Buick."
You screwing with me?
You're screwing with me.
Hello!
Not for nothing, but your can
reeks like a dead goose.
-Get your hands up where I can see them.
-What's going on, Eddie?
-You guys, listen.
-Relax! Listen...
-I don't care!
-The Charger... I stole it!
-Stay where you are!
-Get your hands away from your pockets.
-What's going on, Eddie?
Get your hands--
Ohh!
Oh, my God.
What's going on?
Sage, what's going on?
Someone did something tonight.
Something really, really horrible.
And it looks like I did it.
And I didn't.
And I have to find this guy...
You know what? It's vital that
you don't tell anyone where I am,
-do you understand?
-Mm-hm.
Well, what did he do?
I can't tell you.
I can't.
Okay. Then come with me.
Come on. There's a hot DJ
at the Green Fiend tonight.
-Please?
-Your lip's bleeding, Brenna.
Shit.
Did you bang him?
Yeah.
Did he cook for you?
Did he cook for me?
Food.
Well, yeah,
he bought me a bag of Ruffles once.
Doesn't count.
Well, why the hell does
a guy have to cook for you?
Why? Because guys see the world
like an enormous barnyard.
-What?
-Pick any animal. Just anything.
-A duck.
-A duck? Okay.
You can be a duck...
floating on the pond,
feathers all fluffed and layered just so.
But the minute that
you give it up for a guy,
you're no longer a duck, you're a hog.
Wallowing and snorting
in your own revolting slop.
But if a guy cooks for you first,
before you spread...
then you're immune to hog status
and you'll forever retain the elegance...
of a duck.
Get it?
So, you never banged a guy
unless he cooked for you?
Hell, no.
-Never.
-Really?
Nope.
Brenna.
Make a fist.
Thumb out.
-Now, go.
-Go where?
Hit me!
- You're high.
- Hit me.
You're high, Sage.
Brenna, have you ever thrown
a punch in your life?
Nope. And that's because
punching's mean.
Right now, there's a thousand girls
just like you,
face down in the gutter,
covered in blood and spit
and a variety of even more disgusting
bodily fluids.
And the only difference
between you and that gutter
is the amount of ruthless
that you pack in your fist.
So get up and knock me out flat,
right now!
I'm going dancing, okay?
I'm gonna kick your ass
if you don't kick my ass.
No! Okay? You can
knock my teeth out with a crowbar,
and I wouldn't lay a hand on you, Sage.
Are you okay, Sage?
I was going to boil some noodles...if--
if you want some.
What?
-It's cold.
-Your leather, really?
Oh! You do love me. You love me!
You love me! Bye.
Brenna, next time you get in trouble,
you're on your own.
Yeah, yeah. Bye.
I'll see ya inside.
Oh, guys, please?
Thank you.
-Hi.
-Nice jacket.
-It's a friend's.
-Oh.
-Your name?
Brenna.
Larch.
-She, uh, she here?
-Who?
-Your friend.
-How did you know it was a "she"?
The way you said "friend".
She's not here.
Huh.
Used to live in Jersey City.
I know all about Sage.
Her father owned a garage on 25th.
After he died, it went down,
left her with nothing.
Eventually,
after a couple of stints with juvie,
she started stealing--
anything from anybody.
-They called her the Banshee.
-Why Banshee?
'Cause you're better off chasing a ghost,
I don't know.
Maybe she's just pissed off at the world.
-Okay, granted...
-Give me one of those.
She zags, but...
she did not cut anybody up.
That requires a special blend of depravity
this girl can't touch.
Jesus, Fitz, you're making a fool
out of yourself.
Therefore indirectly
making a fool out of me. Okay?
It was the girl. Do you understand?
Look, I know she's hot,
got that puppy dog thing going on
when she's checking you out,
but the point is she killed a man,
and we gotta find her.
So, none of this denial-
delusional trip, okay?
Checking me out how?
W-Was she looking at my ass?
God knows how many cars she stole,
and she's just chopped up
some poor jerk-off,
threw you in front of a train,
all in one night, and you're asking me
if she was checking out your ass?
About three or four times.
What the hell is "zag"?
techno music playing]
-Why the Rat King?
-Why do you care?
It tells a deeper story.
We are live on the Web.
How long you known her?
I caught a bus out here
a couple of years ago,
and she was the first thing I saw.
She took to me, you know?
Like a big sister.
Are you going?
Yeah. Got some stuff I want to work on.
You can watch if you're interested.
Okay.
Hey! Hey!
-Do you cook?
-What?
You know, cook?
Sure.
It's a shortcut to the hotel.
Beats walking in the cold.
Oh...
This is Dallas. Leave a message.
Dallas, it's Sage.
I need you to run a plate, okay?
Call you later.
Watch your step.
Some shortcut.
Oh, wow.
Oh.
You know, my mom used to say
I had musical talents.
Come here.
Ow!
I'm sorry.
Ow! Ow!
Some say
the eyes are the windows to the soul.
Incas believe it's a voice,
but only in moments of purest honesty.
Like when?
When you lose control.
Would you mind
if I showed you a dog brain?
Everything you've lived, good or bad,
it's hardwired in here.
Imprinted, locked in place.
You deprive it of its senses
and it gets confused,
you know, cuts loose from reality.
Some say it's the ultimate high.
Have a seat.
Introduce...
certain ELF frequencies...
and you can rewire the brain
to think it's seeing God
Or...the devil.
Your worst nightmare.
And then there's the hypothalamus,
which controls sex and rage.
ELF frequencies can turn that rage...
into love...
a hard-on...or a scream.
-Where did you get a dog brain?
-Last bitch who sat in that chair.
Dallas speaking.
Dallas, I need a plate.
I hear you're in deep with Mitch.
BADASS25.
Yeah, yeah, keep your shorts on.
You know the price on your ass?
I'm impressed.
Are you checking the plate or not, man?
Hey, M.L. Totty, 505 Lytton.
-Great.
What do you need this for--
-Hi, I'm looking for an M.L. Totty.
-Found her.
-Oh, you own a '66 burgundy Charger.
-I sold it.
To who?
I'm coming!
-My maintenance man.
-Is he here?
No, he comes and goes as he pleases.
I don't keep track.
He's got a setup up there in the attic
for when he works late.
-Gotta go. I'm late for my prayer circle.
-Okay, well do you know where he is?
-Why?
-'Cause I want his car.
Don't know. Don't want to.
Jesus ain't gonna give a rat's ass
if we're five minutes late!
What is his name?
Dallas, Sage. I need a number. It's a cop.
No, I'm fine.
Oliver Fitzgerald.
Okay, go.
Uh-huh.
All right, thanks.
-Yeah.
-It's Sage.
Listen, I stole that car,
and there was a note, and it said that
if I didn't bring it back, Tony dies.
So I traced the plate...
Hold on a second.
I'm walking around here
with my balls on fire,
wondering if I'll ever breed,
and you call me up,
babbling about running a plate?
Are you a sociopath or just bipolar?
-I'm not crazy.
-You threw me in front
-of a train?
-I know, but I took it back.
I mean, would a psycho
pass up an opportunity
to watch a cop get smashed
by a speeding train? No.
Well, listen.
If what you're saying is true,
why don't you come down to the station,
fill out a report, and I'll do what I can
to make sure you get a fair trial, okay?
505 Lytton St.
The guy that cut up Tony
used to live there,
and he goes back there occasionally.
How do you know?
I just told you, I traced the plates,
okay? It's BADASS25.
Our best chance at nailing this guy
is through his car,
because he loves the Charger,
and the Charger's wrecked.
I found some garage receipts,
but with no shop names,
but they were all the same,
meaning there is a 99% chance
that the car is either there
-or it's gonna be there.
Why don't you just
come down to the station
and we'll work this out step by step?
No, 'll take the garages
from Washington to Park.
You take the ones from South to Fuller,
you got that?
-Yeah.
And, look...
sorry about your balls.
Yeah.
Get me the juvie file on Sage Rion.
Hey, you seen a '66 Charger?
I hear you're in a world of shit.
'66 Charger. Burgundy.
Have you seen it?
-That's Pete's.
-Who's Pete?
He's a guy from the neighborhood.
Hits a lot of car shows.
-Okay, well, does Pete have a last name?
-I don't know. Pete's Pete.
-Well, where can I find Pete?
-He's up on Nimitz.
-Where?
-It's one of those weird alley entrances.
-I'd have to show you.
-So show me.
Yeah, sure. I just gotta call my boss
in case he comes by.
-Help yourself.
-Thanks.
You gonna get fired, you think?
No. Watch this.
Hey, it's Stick.
Listen, my buddy popped by...
and I gotta take her to see
her sick, decrepit grandma
who just got mashed by a Charger.
Right. Uh-huh.
Cool.
Damn, I'm good.
So, let's go.
Hi, how are you?
My name's Oliver Fitzgerald.
I was here to ask you a few questions.
Oh, yeah. Come in. Here.
Thank you.
I haven't been up there in years.
My back is so bad.
If I went up those stairs,
I'd never get back down.
-So, tell me about Larch.
-Best maintenance man I ever had.
Never see him. He fetched up
on my doorstep several years ago,
looking for work.
I'm figuring on
turning this into a B&B.
There's money there.
Plumbing, rewiring...
man can do anything.
-And he lives in the attic?
-Oh, only when he works late.
I never see him these days.
I think he might have found himself
a lady friend or something.
I came back from a retreat, and he'd been
looking after the place while I was gone,
and I found some panties in the hallway.
Well, they certainly weren't mine.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
- So, how do you know this guy?
- I don't know.
-Well, where'd you meet him?
-Car show.
-Car Classics?
-Yeah.
-Yeah? Six months ago?
That show was canceled, man.
My kids go to bed hungry. Understand?
- It's not their fault.
- Hold the fuck up!
Come on.
You're a bitch.
Hey, I got proof that it's not her.
John Larch. 505 Lytton.
He records his victims.
It's on there.
Hm.
Those death throes are scaring
the hell out of me.
I won't be able to sleep for a week.
Look. Pressure, sound level,
pitch frequency.
This guy has literally made a science
out of psychological torture.
Look. Day one, day two, day three.
Some girl named Denica.
Around that time,
Denica Hodge disappeared.
She lived, like, two blocks from there.
Sage Rion stole this guy's car,
and he retaliated
by killing her boyfriend,
and I'm sure she's next.
-How did you get this guy?
-Ran the plate.
-You ran the plate.
-Yeah, that's what I said.
You ran the plate, you found an address,
you walked in and helped yourself
to his personal possessions
without a warrant.
-Oh, by chance, he wasn't home.
-It's him.
Fitz, I don't know if you're aware,
but I've worked some of the largest
and most complicated homicide cases
-in the history of this department.
-I heard.
Yet I'm out there
doing the chop-shop circuit
with every other ape
who just got his shield.
The most dangerous thing a cop can do
is confuse instinct with wishful thinking.
Why don't you just go there
and check it out?!
Check what? Huh?
Get some rest.
I need a file, missing persons.
Hodge, Denica.
Oh, and while you're at it,
get me a propeller head.
I need some help with something.
Yo, why we gotta sit here
waiting for Kevin?
-Can you kill a woman?
-You know that's not my style.
Well, that's why
we gotta wait for Kevin.
Why don't we just close our eyes
or something?
All right, that's just stupid.
Yeah, I'm looking for a '66 Charger.
You sure?
-All right, thanks.
-Take it to Eddie for me.
-What's this?
-Sage Rion's juvie file.
-That's Sage's screwdriver.
-Ex-screwdriver.
Put it back.
When did a corpse ever have use
for a screwdriver?
-Corpse?
-Oh, you didn't hear?
Oh.
What if one of these cars
accidentally mashes her?
I mean, technically it's an accident.
Guilt-free, painless.
Listen, in this business,
I have to maintain
a certain level of respect.
Therefore, when someone steals from me,
I retaliate with
the most agonizing death possible.
-So that's why we have to wait for Kevin?
-Now you're catching on.
Look, you still gotta get rid
of these bodies, huh?
We're driving a Fiat.
How am I supposed to fit two dead bodies
in the trunk of a Fiat?
-I don't know, Guido. Be creative.
-What do you want me to do,
melt 'em down with some acid
or something? What do you think?
See, I pay you so I don't have
to think about details.
Now, you can rent a van,
you can stir 'em up with pickled relish
and serve them at a potluck.
The point is, you think.
The next person who tries to make me think
gets a face full of slug.
Any questions?
All right now, get the door.
Come on, Mitch. Turn your back on me?
Little bitch!
Come on!
All right. Give me a gun.
Look at what you're making me do!
Let's do this, huh? Let's do this.
Bring a bull.
-Huh?
-The piñata.
My daughter wants a bull.
I'll bring two.
-Jesus.
-I'm screwed!
And it's your goddamn fault!
So you better catch him!
-What happened?
-None of your business.
You gotta see a doctor.
-Do you have tequila?
-Yeah.
-Did you check the garages?
Everything from 83rd to Park. You?
I missed a few.
You still need to check out Lenny's,
Ace's and Fred's.
-Well, let's call.
-They're closed, idiot. It's Sunday.
You just start at Lenny's
and work your way over to Ace's,
and you need to look in the window,
and if you see Larch's car,
you'll find him and you lock him up.
And when you do, my ass is out.
I'm done.
Done how?
Done zagging?
Zagging, yeah.
That's a...word, right?
I don't even know why I'm here.
Yeah. Yeah.
There's something on it?
No, I don't have time to come down.
Just turn it up, let me hear it.
Help me.
So, you grow up with cars?
Hey, leave a message.
Fitz. Eddie. Call.
John Friedling, alias Larch.
No priors, no known address.
Committed to Birch Valley Asylum
ten years ago.
Been out just under three years.
What happened?
Your arm.
Wrecked.
Why do you do it?
-Do what?
-Steal.
'Cause I'm good at it.
You know what I think?
I think...
ohh...
you do it
'cause it makes you feel powerful.
Hmm.
So, how come when a guy steals,
he's slick,
but when a woman does,
she's compensating
for some profound emotional lack?
Because guys have testosterone,
makes you do some crazy, high-speed crap.
[humorless chuckle
I steal for the same reason
a hooker gives hand jobs.
Starts with an "M,'' ends with a "Y,''
and there's an "O-N-E" in the middle.
You know what that spells?
You lost me at "hand job."
Tell me about this.
He lived right here.
-Here in this place?
-Yeah.
With his whacked-out Aunt Twyla.
I don't know what happened to the parents.
His arms and legs were always covered
in burns and infected scabs.
Anyway, every day after school,
instead of coming inside,
he'd go out back
and sit in his dad's Charger.
-Hm.What did he do?
-Nothing.
He just sat at the wheel
until late at night.
Protective Services finally stepped in.
Rumor was Aunt Twyla locked him in a box
every time he pissed her off.
Why did they lock him up?
Because one day he shoved Aunt Twyla
down the garbage disposal.
Who's got the rookie's home number?
If you don't tell me,
I'm gonna make something up.
I saw your file.
My dad was crazy, too, you know?
All the best people have at least
one psychotic parental figure.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
I'm an idiot.
You probably got that, though.
Me and my sister
were eating mac and cheese.
My mom was dead, so I always cooked.
And my dad came in
and he knocked us both out.
When I woke up,
we were in the garage...
in the backseat of the car
with the motor running.
My dad had run one of those tubes in,
you know?
Me and my sis were both tied up.
Reminded me of this picture I saw once
of this rat king.
The rats were forced so close together
that they became a single snarl.
I don't even know if my sister was dead.
It looked like it, though.
She was pure white.
So I just started freaking out.
I just started kicking
and punching at the window
and...next thing I know,
I was on the lawn
and the paramedics were pulling
all this glass out of my arm, so...
Did they get her out?
I can't even remember
if I tried to save her.
Sometimes when I'm sleeping,
I see myself pulling at the rope.
I don't know if it's something
that I'm just remembering
or something I made up.
You know?
Yeah.
-You gonna get that?
-Yeah.
Yeah.
When?
I'll be there.
You're off. They finally listened
to those CDs I found.
They're at Larch's old place now.
I'm gonna go check those garages,
see if I can locate
a current address on Larch.
I'll be back, uh, like, two hours.
You gonna be here?
All right, yeah.
Well, you'll either be here,
or you won't be here.
If you're here, I'll see you,
and if you're not, you're not.
So...there.
Hey.
I'll clean up.
Wake up, woman.
Brenna, wake up.
I'm coming to get my jacket.
Let me out! Please!
Please!
We're live.
Hey, thanks for coming.
Listen, I gotta leave town for a while.
Yeah, I heard.
Got some...got some fucked-up shit.
You know, I got some people
I could hook you up with. Good people.
No, I'll be fine. I'll be fine.
Um, I'm gonna wire some money.
Can you make sure Brenna gets it?
Yeah.
'Cause she's too much of a dunce
to deal with wired money.
Sage, that girl's the only thing you
care anything about in this world,
yet every time you open your mouth,
it's "dummy" or "dunce" or "dingbat."
You realize this?
You know why people hate the world, Sage?
Hm?
Because they want to.
That's beautiful, Dallas.
I'm serious.
I've been watching you
and I know you're a good kid.
Can I borrow your car for a couple hours?
Absolutely not.
Hey.
I'm leaving town for a while.
You don't have to come,
'cause I got no time for shady,
jacket-heisting babes.
I'm gonna leave you this number,
all right?
And I'll call you if I can.
I'm not seeing my jacket, Brenna.
Fitz, it's Sage. Please call me.
-Hey, can I get a tequila?
-Sure.
Have you seen a girl with curly hair
and a rat jacket?
Not since last night.
-Who was she with?
-DJ.
Thank you.
Hey!
Lenny told me
to deliver this car.
Where?
You got his address?
Help me!
Please!
Sage, please.
Save me, Sage.
Yeah. Hey,
his real name is Friedling.
We're running a search right now.
- Yeah, yeah, got him.
- Say again?
El Circe on William,
I'm heading there now.
Touch nothing. You hear me?
Hello?
Brenna.
Where is she?!
Let me out!
Sage, please.
-Help me. Help me.
-Brenna.
Ohh!
Brenna.
-Sage, please.
-Brenna.
Brenna.
-Sage.
-Brenna.
Brenna.
- Oh, my God.
Hold on, Brenna, I'm here.
- I'm here.
-This thing's locked.
-Hold on, Brenna.
-Hold on, baby.
No! Come on!
Unhh!
Oh, my God.
It's me. It's me.
It's safe. Come on. Come on.
-I don't know where he is.
-Don't know where he is.
Come on.
Oh, my God. Come on,
we're gonna get out of here.
Please, Brenna.
Please be strong for me, please.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, no. No, honey. Please, Brenna.
I'm looking for a guy
named John Friedling.
Goes by Larch?
-Don't know him.
-You don't know your tenants?
Look, I'm just the night guy, all right?
I know nobody.
-How many people live here?
-A dozen.
A dozen on what, eight floors?
We only use the bottom three.
John Larch or John Friedling staying here?
-I already asked.
-Don't know him.
-Well, let me see a list of your tenants.
-I don't have one.
Well, what the hell is that?
All right, is there anybody
who strikes you as being a little odd?
-I. Don't. Know.
-Guess.
Suck my nuts, all right?
Unhh! All right, all right. Look, look.
There's this guy, he's a little on
the weird side. He keeps odd hours.
-I don't know how he lives with the smell.
-What room?
-What smell?
-Bad eggs, you know? Graveyard-y.
So, you smell decaying flesh,
but you don't call anybody.
-What room!
-320.
-I thought it was eggs.
-You said "graveyard-y."
Hey, there's an easier way to do this!
Follow him!
Give me the key, now!
Let's go.
Sit down.
Brenna...
I'm gonna tie this hose around you,
then I'm gonna let you down the elevator,
and you have to trust me, okay?
Hands where I can see 'em, drop the pills,
get up slowly.
Come here. Come here, help me.
Move your arm.
Here you go. I've got you.
Let's go. I've got you. All right, go.
You're almost there, Brenna.
Oof.
Looks like
you've been busy here, huh?
- Oh, Jesus.
- Hank?
- What the hell am I looking at?
- It's a meth lab.
I've got you. You're almost there.
-What's upstairs?
-I don't know, I've never been.
You're almost there.
- Sage!
- Come on.
I'd kill you...
but then you'd miss the show.
Brenna!
- I'm still up here.
- Stay put, I'll be right there.
It's okay, it's okay.
You'll be all right.
Sage, please.
We're live.
Welcome to my show.
Aaah!
Piece of shit!
-Fuckin' die.
-No!
- No!
-No! Let me fucking go!
-Easy.
Unhh!
No!
- Oh, my God.
- Stand down.
Show's over.
We're talking about eight bodies so far.
I know it's impressive.
S-Sort of.
Hey, I'm sorry about your jacket.
You crazy?
Yeah, you owe me one.
I'm gonna come later, okay?
They're gonna have
to take her in for observation.
Hey.
How is she?
She's tough.
Am I done here?
It shouldn't be too much longer.
You hungry?
Why don't you come over?
I'll make you some tortellini.
What?
Nothing.
So, how about I drive?