(bright upbeat music)
(electronic music)
(upbeat music)
♪ Please,
♪ You're the one I
want this Christmas.
♪ I don't want nobody but you,
♪ You're the one I
want this Christmas
♪ Can you make my
dreams come true,
♪ You're the one I
want this Christmas,
♪ I don't want nobody but you,
♪ You're the one I
want this Christmas,
♪ Can you make my
dreams come true.
♪ Up in the morning, ♪ Morning
♪ Open my gifts.
♪ You know I'm excited.
♪ Excited.
♪ I'm a less,
♪ I ain't been asleep.
♪ What did I miss,
♪ I missed toe,
♪ I need your kiss,
♪ Where you been?
♪ Where you had?
♪ Where you at?
♪ All I know,
♪ Sad or better,
♪ How you ridding
♪ Side or back?
♪ You're all I'm thinking
♪ And I'm desperate,
♪ All laid,
♪ 'Cause we had
♪ I just want you,
♪ No another,
♪ Always gonna,
♪ Have your back,
♪ Baby, ♪ Baby,
♪ You my lady.
♪ I just got let you know,
♪ Let you know,
♪ You get them but
it flies aside,
♪ All the time write it down,
♪ Oh yeah,
♪ You know I don't want
us to get away get away,
♪ Get away.
♪ I got no play silly games,
♪ No, no
♪ And wrap you
♪ Like and kiss another trail
♪ You're the one I
want this Christmas,
♪ I don't want nobody but you,
♪ You're the one I
want this Christmas,
♪ Can you make my
dreams come true,
♪ You're the one I
want this Christmas,
♪ I don't want nobody but you,
♪ You're the one I
want this Christmas,
♪ Can you make my
dreams come true?
♪ You're the one I
want this Christmas
[DJ Rain] All right.
That was the latest
drop from D and Y.
Please.
Y'all make sure to
go cut that out.
It's a hop and speaking
of hot as hell,
isn't it usually one winter
we're having this year.
Well, not if you've been living
in Georgia all your life.
It's 81 degrees.
It's a hot one right now.
But not as hot as
these phone lines.
Cause it's time to speak out.
Hello?
Who am I speaking with?
And what are you
speaking out about?
[TK] Hello.
What's going on?
My name is TK.
I want to speak about females.
[DJ Rain] Well, first let's
learn the proper term, my man.
Female is an adjective.
Woman is a noun.
So they're not
females, they're women.
[TK] Females.
Women.
A little but they
are all confusing.
Anyway,
I asked my lady what she
wanna do for her birthday.
She said nothing.
That's exactly what I did.
Nothing, that's all I want
to talk to you brother.
Alright, TK.
I'm going to keep
it a book with you.
It sounded like you fell
for the age old trick.
When a woman says she was
nothing on her birthday,
what she's really
saying is that,
even though she
doesn't want anything,
just didn't want you to
show her that you love
and that you appreciate her,
even if she's not
particularly expect me,
it sounds like you've got
some making up to do my man.
All right, that's my time.
This is DJ Rain.
Always raining down to hits.
Before I get up out of here.
I want to wish you a
very special, special,
happy birthday to
my queen Simone,
happy birthday baby.
I love you.
And I can't wait to celebrate
your special day with you.
[Audience] ♪ Happy
birthday to you.
♪ Happy birthday to you.
♪ Happy birthday dear Simone,
Ooh lady.
All right.
(soft piano music)
Simone,
I love you so much.
I love you with all my body,
my heart,
my soul,
you my everything.
I can't imagine my
life without you.
Now I want to know,
nothing more of me, because
you are more special,
so I can make my
Christmas wish come true.
What do you say?
(chuckles)
You want to get married?
Yes.
Just not to you?
(suspenseful music)
Damn (sighs).
(chilling dramatic music)
Is anything just happened?
Nah,
nah,
that ain't just happened.
(chuckles)
Somebody pinch me, because
I must be dreaming.
The hell man.
Nope.
You're awake.
Please tell me not just
propose to my girlfriend.
And she said no.
Actually you said,
do you want to get married?
And she said yes.
But not to you.
Fred.
Freddy.
What? I just want my
boy to have all the facts.
You not helping,
come on.
Hey (indistinct).
Look man,
I know this really isn't
a time when I told you so,
but I told you not
propose to that girl.
No you didn't.
Okay.
No,
but if you would've told me
what you were going to do,
I would have told
you not to do it.
You helping this man or not.
Move, move.
I'm just saying.
Just move on.
Listen.
Bro,
I know you're hurting right now,
we're going to look back at
this moment and just laugh,
you see what I'm saying?
And today is not that great.
Okay.
Rain.
I know that it might
not seem like it,
but today is actually the
best day of your life.
Was she at the same
party we were at today.
I say that,
because now is the time
that you can truly find
yourself and now you
can truly figure out,
what you really
want in a partner.
And when you figured that out,
the right one would
be right there.
And what are you doing?
Calling Simone.
No, hell no.
Give me that phone.
Baby,
please don't leave me.
Baby look,
I need you.
Like I'm begging
like (indistinct).
Baby please don't leave me.
What do you want me to do?
I'll do,
I'll do anything that you like.
Ooh.
Just please don't leave me.
Get that phone..
Please.
Oh, girl.
(crying)
Give me that phone.
Why can't you just
ope your phone man.
Now it's time
to call the night.
Look, I need that.
I need to drive my pain away.
Just give me the phone.
Let's go.
Calm down,
it's okay.
(sighs).
Damn.
Feel bad for him.
He is sad.
Yeah,
me too.
Is this okay now?
Come on man.
(soft piano music)
No.
Do you have anything?
Okay, all right.
(sighs)
Yap.
I just wish,
I just wish that
women be like you.
Not with him but me.
Always,
always there for me.
Love me no matter what.
(crying)
Why did she say no?
Why did she say no to me?
She probably,
she probably realized that,
that she wasn't the
right one for you.
When I know I might
seem like you now, but
Simone did you a favor.
She released you
to find the woman
that God created just for you.
You are one of the most kindest,
the sweetest,
most loving people
I have ever known.
(chuckles)
I remember when we
were in second grade
and I accidentally got
glue stuck in my hair
and you thought it
would be a good idea
to try and cut it out.
Leaving a big ass
hole in my head.
(chuckles)
Man, I was so mad,
but what did you do?
You let me cut a big
hole in you hair,
so we be even.
(sighs)
You are good man.
And you deserve to have
a good woman to love you.
Like you deserve to be loved.
Okay.
(snores)
Goodnight friend.
(door closes)
Damn.
What did I drink?
(chuckles)
Hey, baby you'll never believe
the dream I had last night.
I dreamt I proposed
to you and you,
said no.
(sighs)
One more tequila for me.
(rock music)
(light showers)
♪ I always in a studio.
♪ Every other day.
♪ Every other day,
♪ I never get tired of you,
♪ Yes what she said
♪ But it's not even like that
♪ So why would you think that.
♪ She said it feel like,
♪ Your music comes before me.
♪ She said
♪ You could love me
♪ Like you do music,
♪ Then we go be fine,
♪ Ooh we go be fine.
♪ If yo could love me,
♪ Like you do music,
♪ Then we go be fine,
♪ Ooh we go be fine.
♪ She said eh.
♪ Every time we talk,
♪ Is always about you day.
♪ Music,
♪ It's only to you, it's in me.
♪ What about me?
Crazy.
I heard it was awful.
Turn him down flat in
front of everybody.
So it's probably safe to assume
that maybe Zack
would be here today.
So my have you feeling.
Rain?
Yes boss.
What are you doing here?
I have a show
to get ready for.
I mean,
after last night I just assumed.
(chuckles) Well,
you know what they say
about people who assume,
right?
And I'm not gonna say
cause the boss trying
to kill this job always.
Look,
Rain.
Are you sure where you
should be here right now?
I mean,
after what happened,
maybe you should
take a few days off.
Look boss.
I appreciate you
looking out for me.
The bills still got to get paid.
And love and heartbreak.
Ain't gonna pay the bills.
You feel me?
Now, if you excuse me.
I have a show to get ready for.
(upbeat music)
Yeah,
that was a throwback
during the day.
And now it's time everybody
to think for a second.
Speak out.
This is your chance to
speak about anything
you want to.
Nothing or no one is off limits.
So with that being said.
[DJ Rain] Let's have first call.
Welcome to the afternoon
drive with DJ Rain live.
Who am I speaking with?
[Portia] My name is Portia.
[DJ Rain] Yo,
what's good Portia?
What are you speaking
out about today?
[Portia] Well Rain,
I've been dating my boyfriend
for about four years now
and he just recently
asked me to marry him,
but I haven't given
him an answer yet.
I mean,
I love him,
but I just don't think we're
ready to get married yet.
Oh,
damn.
What do you mean?
You don't know if you're
ready to get married yet?
You've been together
for four years.
How much more time do you need?
[Portia] I just want to make
sure before I made that leap,
you know what I'm saying?
[DJ Rain] No, I don't
know what you're saying.
I need to talk to you
about this account man.
Hey man,
don't you see I'm
doing something.
[DJ Rain] Sounds like me,
(indistinct) mans heart.
You just (indistinct)
big let down,
and a major heartbreak.
You know what?
It's bitches like you to
get in my damn nerves.
You got a good man,
but instead taking
a live with him
you just decide to throw him
away like he ain't nothing.
How about you just do
everybody else a favor
and find the nearest
cliff and take that leap.
Hello?
Damn Rain.
Yes, you hung up.
I guess the truth just
got too real for her ass.
Listen,
it's time to have a music break.
And I know we supposed to play
some more Christmas music but
if I get my jingle bell
right and nobody else did.
So with that being said,
this next genre is
dedicated to all you
whore whore out there.
Especially the ones who decide
to leave a good man during
the holiday season.
You know after this genre
we go follow up Chris Brown.
This hoes ain't loyal.
'Cause they ain't.
Oh, yeah.
It's getting really
up in this bitch.
(phone vibrates)
Hello?
Yeah.
I heard the show.
What are we going to do now?
(soft piano music)
Jimmy just continue to
apologize to the listeners
and let them know that we
are handling the situation.
(man knocking at the door)
Come in.
Thanks Jemmy.
Have a seat.
I'm good standing.
Fine.
Have you lost your damn mind?
Who the hell are
you to be going on
live like that on the radio?
And because of your shit,
our phones are blowing up
with offended listeners.
Plus I got the
FCC on my ass now.
What do you have to
say for yourself?
And look women are bitches.
Okay.
And bitches are evil.
I understand you're
dealing with your heartbreak.
I told you to take
a few days off.
But you were insisting
on not doing so.
So with that,
you should have checked
that shit at the door
before you got on the air.
I'm sorry.
So am I.
That's why I'm going to have
to suspend you indefinitely.
Without pay,
until we decide if we
want to keep you or not.
Look, you can't do that.
Okay, I have a contract.
If you read page three,
paragraph four,
you'll see that I am
in every legal right
to do what I just did.
(object thumps)
(soft piano music)
(sighs) Poor Rain.
I can't believe he went
off the rails like that.
I know right?
He should do that more often.
'Cause that was one
of his best shows yet.
I mean poor, poor, Rain?
You know,
I blame Simone for all of this.
I should go to her house and
bump that half in the face
of what she did to my...
Your,
your what?
Friend,
friend.
That's what I was getting
ready to say before you rudely
interrupted me,
Listen, girl bye.
Instead of trying
to fight Simone
and catch a case,
you need to be taken all
of that pent up aggression
and putting it on Rain.
Caroline, stop it.
I told you Rain
and I are just...
- Just friends.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Save it for somebody with baby
milk still on their bread.
Girl,
I could tell you
got a bang for Rain
and anyone who has eyes
can tell that you two
have a connection.
Well clearly I need
to get my eyes checked
because Rain doesn't
see me like that.
Alexandria.
See that's the thing,
Rain doesn't see
me as Alexandra,
to him Aj.
I mean we grew up together.
I'm always around him
and his male friends.
So, to Rain I'm just
one of the fellows.
Well maybe if you stop
acting like one of the fellows,
he'll take the scales off
his eyes and finally see you
as the woman of his dreams.
(sighs)
(rock music)
♪ Sleepless nights,
♪ Hell of a time,
♪ Where are your arms
♪ We are two in this flight,
♪ Whose side I'll go live
♪ When I shot the man right
♪ It's not all right.
(music continues)
Good game fellows.
Yeah.
Woo.
And Aj.
(chuckles)
Has anybody had from Rain
since the proposal hit.
He hasn't been answering
my calls or text.
Yeah, mine either.
Well I went to spy after
he had that melt down
on the radio last week.
He's a complete wreck.
Oh, how bad is he?
It's so bad.
Rain is looking for
somewhere else to stay.
(chuckles)
We gotta do something.
What do you
think we should do?
Okay, what I think
that we should probably.
I mean,
I think we should set them
up on a whole bunch of dates.
That's not the route
that I was particularly
thinking about taking.
I mean,
they say the best way
to get over someone
is to get into someone.
Yeah.
(chuckles)
Yeah,
yeah.
I mean,
we should each find a
woman that he liked.
He'd go out with a
different woman each night.
I mean he's bound to
find one of he liked,
right?
Yeah.
I think this could be
super clutch because of.
Hey, let's do it.
I mean, come on fellows.
Rain has been truly
broken up by all of this
and she just pushed
him off on some random,
is not going to automatically
fix the situation.
I mean,
maybe we should think about
taking a different approach.
Come on.
- No.
No, I like this.
Hey, hey operation
lady in the streets
and freaking the
sheets on three.
Hey.
- Freaking the (indistinct).
- One.
- Two.
Three.
Lady in the street.
Lady in the street. (mumbles)
No, look man.
We probably should've
came up with something
a little shorter.
Dad is saying.
It's lady in the
streets and freaks.
I mean ain't my fault.
Y'all know how to talk.
(rock music)
♪ Lady,
♪ Have I told you,
♪ I love you.
♪ Lady,
♪ Have I told you,
♪ You give me,
♪ The world to be.
♪ Have I told you,
♪ I love you.
(knock)
Go away.
Oh, what's that?
You said you want us to come in?
All right cool.
We're here.
Hey yo,
you got some eater
brother's starving.
What?
I'm hungry.
And what was that
noise we heard?
Man sounded like some super cat,
dying a horrible,
horrible,
horrible death.
It's painful.
That was me.
My all to Simone.
She hear, has she?
How you doing bro?
I'm lost.
I'm lost than my baby.
I'm lost without Simone.
♪ How sweet though at you
All right, all right.
Okay and.
(indistinct) can't
do a good work.
No, no enough of that.
Thank you, God.
Dude,
you really need to stop
feeling sorry for yourself.
Get your ass up and put
yourself out there again.
Start dating again.
No.
The future misses Rain
Wilkins is out there.
She's not in here.
No, no, no.
If it ain't Simone,
I won't her.
Look,
(indistinct)
Once you've had a piece of
pussy, you've had them all.
Wait.
What?
No, no, no, no.
That's not true.
That's not right.
(indistinct chattering)
Wow.
Why would you just act like
a lady isn't in the room?
I'm in the room.
All right, cool.
Rain, come on men
you got to do this.
Hey, for real though,
you need this.
Yeah.
I mean, trust us man.
This is what's best for you.
Not necessarily.
Look Rain.
If you don't want to do this,
we'll totally understand.
Don't,
don't listen to the negative.
Nancy over here.
You doing this shit?
Speaking of shit,
what is that smell?
Oh,
you need to get your ass up and
go to that shower right now.
I know I wasn't alone.
I'm glad you said something.
Get up.
I was thinking.
I didn't want to say it though.
I don't smell that bad.
Come on, come on.
Rain go.
Go, go.
(indistinct chatter)
Don't cover that up,
you gotta wash your hands.
(indistinct chattering)
Rain, rain some water
in your hands bro.
Even as he walks,
I can see it.
(indistinct).
It's just,
it's just damn.
(rap music)
♪ Big belly rude boy
♪ Skin dark as summer night.
♪ Black man in America,
♪ Some constantly gonna fight.
♪ They profile me,
♪ Yes I'm feeling I'm
kill my grand real life,
♪ They hate with
don't understand,
♪ But I don't give
♪ My confidence
where they feel me.
♪ My home town is what built me.
♪ I'm winning at to
overcome everything
♪ That they put here to kill me.
♪ Put a target on my back.
♪ Police came
hunting for my hand
♪ Cousins told me to
stay out of trouble
♪ Find other ways to
go get that breeze,
♪ A nightmare.
(music continues)
(indistinct chattering)
If you can't
find a real woman.
No, no.
It's okay bro.
What is this.
All right,
he can't do it.
(applause)
Bro.
Man.
(chuckles)
(indistinct chattering)
(applause)
Is that on purpose?
Oh,
no.
(laughs)
(applause)
All right.
Perfect.
(indistinct chattering)
(music continues)
(murmurs)
(rock music)
Hey sexy, what can
I get you to drink?
Hello.
Hello Yes, sir.
What can I get you to drink sir?
I'm fine.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're fine.
You got (indistinct) sort of.
My fumble.
You too are afraid
of drinking something.
No, I'm good.
I'll take a,
I'll take water for now.
Okay.
I feel sorry for them
to come up in here.
Hi.
Hello.
Are you Rain?
It's me.
I mean,
me is him. (clears throat)
I mean, it's is me right here.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Let me get that for you.
Oh, thank you.
Sorry again.
It's okay.
Are you nervous?
Nervous?
All right, Rain.
(chuckles)
I'm sorry.
You see,
I just got out a
serious relationship.
I heard you were dumped.
It's a middle, it's a meddle.
Anyway,
it's been a while since
I've been in a date
so forgive me.
Forgiven.
So, tell me more
about yourself.
Well,
for starters.
I just got out of prison
after doing a five year period
for attempting to kill my ex.
Oh, okay.
This is my oldest
arrange alone.
He's so cute.
He loves to find me.
Oh, and this is my
princess Corona B.
Now she's my heart.
She really looked like me.
People think we are twins.
(foreign language).
(chuckles)
Oh, my God!
There are aliens among us.
Do you wanna know how I know?
Now tell me when
they abducted me?
I told him,
if you ever cheat on me.
I will kill you.
So that's what I did.
Well, almost.
Okay.
And these are my twin boys,
Dallas and Dynasty.
They look like their daddy,
but they still cute though.
Do you here that?
No, I don't.
What did you say?
Did you say something?
I said no,
I don't.
No, not you.
I'm talking to him.
Why did you say?
They told me,
that I was only
a centimeter away
from stubbing him in the heart.
(chuckles)
It's so so clear.
Everything is right here.
Do you want to know
what your future holds?
Yeah.
Tell me this.
Is it gonna be over?
This is the first
nanogram of my (indistinct).
What?
Yeah,
me and the baby we don't
get a long so well.
But you look like a good daddy.
Do you have any kids?
(coughs)
(sighs)
Yes,
he is cute.
I think he might be the one.
Check please.
Yes,
(indistinct).
Just bring the check.
No,
okay.
Yes,
yes.
(laughs).
Yes.
Obviously, not a good idea.
See, I told you.
You did.
So what do we do now?
I don't know.
Don't look at me.
(phone vibrates)
Listen to me.
I'm ready to listen.
I'm not saying anything.
- What you got?
- Nothing,
it doesn't even matter.
I'm listening,
what you got.
Too late.
I have what y'all hear before.
Nothing.
- Come on, now.
- Absolutely not.
What you got?
Nothing.
Damn nosy.
Oh, who was that?
Come on bro.
That's one of hoes?
Dude.
I'm standing right here.
What's your point?
Show some respect.
Ass hole.
Hey yo, listen.
We'll figure this whole
thing out with Rain.
I got to go.
All right.
Well I'm.
Hey, hey man.
Hold on man you my ride man.
Figure that out.
This mother fucker,
figure it out.
(indistinct chattering)
I'm not riding with you.
Come on man.
(indistinct).
Do you want some respect?
(bell rings)
(door opens)
Hey you.
Good morning Aj.
You tell me.
So,
how were your
(indistinct) dates?
Who?
Can't believe I let you'll
put me through that.
It wasn't me.
It was those local
friends of yours.
(indistinct) talk
specifically to them.
I tried to.
But those fools ain't
listening to me.
Yeah.
You right.
Let me keep it brief AJ.
Every time I breath,
I see you.
I don't know.
It's been three years
with that woman.
I gave her my heart and my soul.
It's like,
it's like she inhabits
every cell in my body.
(sighs)
I don't know.
It's like,
it's like I feel less of a man.
I feel empty.
I ain't complete.
Simone,
she's my everything.
She's perfect.
Obviously she must
not be too perfectly.
Don't you like that?
No Aj I'm not trying to get.
No,
no.
Now you listen,
and I know you loved this woman.
And I know you put
a lot of your heart
and your time in
this relationship.
And I understand that it's going
to take a minute for you to
heal from all this
but you can't let
her make you feel
like you are less
than who you are.
Less than what you deserve.
You are a strong,
smart,
black king.
And if she can't see that,
then she doesn't deserve you.
Damn.
I think this is the nicest
thing you ever said about me.
Don't be used to it.
(chuckles)
But now for real take your time.
The right woman will be with
you when the time is right.
And who knows.
She might be right
under your nose.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
I got a bug in my nose?
Ew.
(chuckles)
So nasty.
(laughs)
No,
but for real I'm thankful
I have somebody like you
in my life.
I loved you and I'm
forever grateful
to have you as a friend.
Well I love you too.
Friend.
(ball clunks)
I'm trying to tell
y'all been practicing,
man you ain't believe me.
I'm getting too old for this.
Whatever man.
You might as well go
and retire damn shoes.
These are Michael's.
Is officially broken.
No, no.
(indistinct)
You gotta look.
You got my short.
Man look knee shorts.
Ain't got shit to do.
I was running you up
and down at court.
I was in that (mumbles).
Oh, oh bro.
Pause, pause, pause, pause.
Now, it's good to see
you smile my dude.
I mean, I know it's been
rough with you losing Simone,
and all that.
Yeah.
Crazy days making the bed.
(laughs)
Listen man.
You know you like to date?
No, please?
Nah, seriously don't man.
I take the fall for
that one, all right.
My bad.
It's all good.
I know y'all meant well.
You are my boys.
For sure.
I know y'all
wouldn't do anything to
intentionally hurt me.
You are right.
There is something I need
to talk to you about.
Hold on, did you see that?
(rock music)
- Damn.
Damn, wow!
Did you see that?
Unfortunately.
But her face looks like a
(indistinct) beetle juice.
(sighs)
Dreamboat ass,
shipwreck face.
Bad combination.
Lord have mercy.
(chuckles)
So, what's the issue
you want to talk me about?
Well you don't have...
Dominique.
This would be one
of your many women?
Shut up man.
Elena,
what's up?
Hey you.
How are you doing?
Doing good.
How are you?
I'm doing good.
This is my homeboy Rain Wilkins.
Rain, this is one of my former
colleagues Elena McDaniels.
Nice to meet you.
The pleasure is all mine.
Yo, Elena is one of
the sharpest attorneys
in the region, man.
She was one of the
first women to average.
Okay, okay.
I believe I can tell
him about myself
over dinner tomorrow night?
Are you?
Um,
are you asking me out to dinner?
That depends.
Are you saying yes?
Um,
yes.
Yes.
I'd be on to it.
Excellent.
Get my number from Dominique.
Text me later.
And we'll discuss the dates.
Okay.
All right.
Until then.
See you later.
Same.
My man.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
(rock music continues)
(laughs)
Thanks for bringing that up.
(chuckles)
The girl was acting
like having a conversation
with the civil (indistinct).
Like she was acting
out of a conversations
like the damn spoon,
fork and knife,
when I talk back to her.
What?
It was crazy.
Okay.
That's nothing.
I went out on a date
once with this guy
and his entire
pregnant wife shows up.
So, she obviously
took an Uber there
just to bust his ass.
Oh no, no, no,
but catch this,
her water breaks.
And apparently he doesn't
have a car either,
which I didn't know.
So what did I do?
Drove both of them
to the hospital
so she could have their baby.
(chuckles)
That's crazy.
Exactly.
One of the worst
dates of my life.
But I'm,
(chuckles)
I'm just really
glad that tonight
is panning out to be different.
Yeah, me too.
If I ask you something,
will you promise to be
completely honest with me?
Depends on what you ask.
(chuckles)
No, not like that.
What do you want to know?
Who broke your heart.
Why do you ask?
I mean,
behind the smiles,
the laughs and the
great conversation.
I still see sadness
in your eyes.
I mean if it's too (indistinct).
Oh, no, no it's fine.
I think I can finally talk
about breaking down and crying.
(chuckles)
Her name was Simone,
we were together for
about three years.
On her birthday,
I proposed to her
and she said no.
(signs) No.
Yeah,
it was in front of
friends and everything.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I really loved her, you know.
Like I felt like,
I could spend the rest
of my life with her.
But I guess she had other plans.
Well, that's her loss.
Thank you.
And her loss,
is my gain.
(upbeat music continues)
(computer clicks)
Yo, it was perfect.
The way she looked at him
and the way he looked at her,
you could see instant fireworks.
I think it would work.
Definitely looked
out for my boy.
Good for him.
Now,
when are you going to
come and take care of me?
Oh, (sighs)
Not fair.
We said last time
was the last time.
Yeah,
we said that the last
time before that.
And then the time before that.
Oh, and then that week
before that we said that too.
I mean, how can I resist
you wearing shit like that?
That is a very easy question.
Because you,
you don't want to?
This is wrong.
This is wrong Simone.
Oh my gosh.
Rain is one of
my best friends.
I mean..
And I am standing right
here in front of you
waiting for you to take me.
It's a dangerous game.
We playing Simone.
Good thing I came to win.
(rock music)
(indistinct chattering)
That was beautiful.
(indistinct) one more tonight.
One more tonight.
(chuckles)
It's nice.
(sighs)
Is that Rain and his new boo?
Yep.
That's them.
Damn she cute.
I mean,
not cuter than you.
(chuckles)
Don't start Caroline.
I'm just saying that
could have been you.
Well,
it's not so just drop it.
I'm gonna say hey.
Don't,
don't.
Rain?
Hey,
hey.
(chuckles)
What's up AJ,
Caroline.
What's up Rain.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's skip all the pleasantries.
Who do we have here?
Oh, this is Elena,
my girlfriend.
Hi.
Nice to meet you both.
Likewise.
Girlfriend.
And how long have you
two known each other?
Couple of weeks now,
I suppose.
Isn't that a little
soon to be calling someone
your girlfriend.
What she means
is congratulations.
Glad you found someone.
You deserve to be happy.
Thanks Aj.
You welcome.
I appreciate that.
Mm-hmm.
Come on Rain.
We should really get going.
We don't want to
miss our tea time.
She's taking me to play golf.
I'm about to get my Tiger
Woods off. (chuckles)
Okay.
Yes.
All right, ladies it was
really nice to meet you all.
(chuckles) Wasn't it?
- Bye.
- See y'all later.
They were really nice.
It's all good.
(soft piano music)
Why did you do that?
What?
Gay people's gay man.
She looks like she's
playing for keeps.
And she'll do whatever it takes
to make sure it stays that way.
Even if it means
breaking the rules.
(soft piano music continues)
Hey babe.
I was thinking we could
do tire for lunch.
How does that sound?
That's cool with me.
Whatever you want.
(phone vibrates)
What the hell?
Babe, where are we gonna
eat this tire food at?
I'm hungry.
Yo, what the hell are
you doing on my phone?
How do you even
unlock it anyway.
You know boy,
boy I had your passcode
a long time ago.
Now I answered my question.
Why have you got his
nasty ass text messages
from this hoes?
Huh?
They're not hoes.
They are my female
acquaintances.
Like I said,
hoes.
Simone,
hat's the issue?
Oh, hello.
I left Rain so that we
can be in a relationship.
What the hell is that.
You said the R word.
Look, Dominique,
I'm not playing with you.
I left my three year long
relationship with Rain.
So that I can be with somebody
who I thought wanted to be
with me for the long haul.
I assume that you I are on the
road towards getting married.
Ooh.
You know what they say
about those who are selling.
And if you finish
that statement,
I'm gonna slap that
beard off of your face.
Listen Simone,
I never said we were exclusive.
I mean,
I care about you and I
do want to be with you,
but I'm not trying
to be a lockdown.
I mean,
besides I'm already
sticking my neck out,
risking my friendship
with my boy
to be with you in
the first place.
Did nobody make you
sneak around with my ass?
No.
But you did continue
to throw it at me.
Begging me to take it.
You are nothing but
a low down dirty dog.
(suspenseful music)
(spanks butt)
Wolf, Wolf baby.
Now we still going to
get that food or what?
(chuckles)
You know what?
Why don't you call
up one of your
little female acquaintances?
'Cause I'm sure one of
them wants to give you
their rotten peach.
Pock ass.
Oh,
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Before I forget,
just so that we're clear
and I mean crystal.
This right here.
It's done.
So I guess I said
no all the time.
(suspenseful music begins)
(rock music begins)
♪ Don't switch up on me,
♪ More than the earth can see.
♪ You changing your face boy
♪ That person had
pleasure to me.
♪ You don't love me the same,
♪ My happiness used
to grace my pain.
♪ You changing your face boy,
♪ The only thing I recognize
♪ Is your name
♪ Your secrets could keep back
♪ And fought back
(music continues)
What would you wanna eat?
(indistinct)
Rain,
what a surprise?
What are you doing here?
This is where my introduction
to rocket in class.
What a coincidence?
Not really.
I teach here every Thursday.
You know that.
Semantics.
Listen, are you busy?
Because I would love to
talk to you about something.
Well, I..
He actually is.
We have somewhere
that we need to be.
Okay, good.
So you're free.
Listen, I am so sorry
for anything soar
that I did between us.
I should not have rejected your
marriage proposal that way.
I was a fool to let
a man like you go.
You got the fool part, right?
Excuse you.
You heard what I said?
Look,
I have invested three years
into this relationship.
The boy is mine.
Well,
it's only taken me
a couple of weeks,
to undo the damage
that you have done.
Turning this hurt boy
into a strong mate.
So it all belongs to me.
I bet if he
proposed to me again,
I would say yes
to you this time.
Well,
you're not going to be
able to say anything.
After I knock your teeth out.
Okay ladies, ladies.
Now as much as I love
a good girlfriend
and I do indeed love
a good girlfriend.
You can't be acting
like this in public.
Fine.
You get a boxing ring.
I'll fight that (indistinct).
Okay Simone, stop. all right.
Look,
I don't know what's changed
for you to be acting like this,
but none of that shit matters.
You broke my heart into a
million pieces when you said no.
Now, it's taken some time,
but I finally got to
put back together.
And the stakes to this
beautiful woman by my side.
He's talking about me.
Simone, you made your choice,
and Elena is mine.
But Rain.
Come on baby.
(phone vibrates)
You okay?
Yeah,
I'm gonna get the phone.
Hello?
Oh, hey Scott.
Oh no, I'm not doing
anything tomorrow.
Sure.
Yeah, I can come
into the station.
Oh,
okay.
Sounds good.
Yeah.
I'll see you first
thing in the morning.
Who was that?
That was my GM.
He wants to talk to me
about lifting my suspension
and giving me my old job back.
That's good right?
Rain.
(chuckles)
I believe in you on
my good luck though.
Trust me baby.
Luck has nothing to do with it.
(chuckles)
I'm happy for you.
(suspenseful music begins)
(rock music)
Hey (indistinct).
Oh, boy!
What?
(indistinct)
What the hell!
How's you'll?
Key.
Duh.
(door closes)
You know what?
Not even free to look through
my group (indistinct).
Oh,.
What's up with you.
It's probably dilute.
Put [Interviewer] Down.
You even finish that statement.
(chuckles)
I just got back from station.
Big boy getting his show back.
Nice.
That was awesome.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that
because that dude that
they had replaced,
you took temporarily,
he was starting to
make my ears bleed.
(chuckles)
right.
Now that Danny,
what we said the other night,
we say we like old boy 'cause
he plays a bit of rotation
and we want him to
stay in (indistinct).
Really?
I mean, boom.
I'm glad he's gone.
He sucks.
Anyway.
I'm just glad that you got
your life back together.
Me too.
I truly believe that
having a lady in my life
that's when all the things
turned around for me.
She has really helped to
see the value in myself.
Being with Elena,
it's like a breath of fresh air.
Man, that woman is amazing.
I don't see myself spending
the rest of my life with her.
Oh, damn.
Just think about
the proposal again.
It's not about the
proposal to Elena.
Not yet.
Anyway.
Well, I'm happy for you.
I say we celebrate.
How about a little
holiday kickback?
(chuckles) sounds good
to me and we and where?
Let's do it here, tonight.
What?
Duh,
let's make it happen
Yo, you good?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
See you tonight, okay?
Good.
What's wrong with her?
(upbeat music begins)
(indistinct chattering)
I like this sweater man,
where did you get it from?
(indistinct)
It's nice,
Yeah, it's nice.
I appreciate.
You guys look
really good together.
Yeah, I've heard a lot
of good things about you.
Yeah, she is (indistinct).
I don't think so.
Like, you know.
Girl.
I like him yawn.
(chuckles)
You crazy.
(indistinct).
Like what?
Yeah.
(chuckles)
Try it and draw back another.
I like your breath.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
You are sick.
(bell rings)
Hey, I got it (indistinct)
Yeah,
'cause this is
indeed your kickback.
In due to believe.
Oh, right. Cheers to that.
(chuckles)
(indistinct chattering)
Simone?
(soft piano music)
The hell are you doing here?
I saw that the whole
gang was together.
Friends.
Aj.
Damn, I thought I blocked her.
Hello everyone.
Simone.
What do you want?
Well,
I saw that everyone was
celebrating your new found good
fortune face (indistinct) IG.
Damn I could have someone,
I blocked her.
So I thought that I should
join in on the festivities.
Simone,
you need to leave.
Why is that my dear Dominique?
So that your precious
secret isn't exposed.
Look Simone,
I don't give a damn about
any of your secrets,
whatever game it is that
you're trying to play.
You just need to leave.
I ain't going nowhere until
I say what I got to say.
Why can't you
just accept the fact
that you made the
decision to leave me?
And because of that,
you no longer have a place here.
I'm with Elena now
and we're happy.
(chuckles) Right?
Okay.
If your girl was so happy,
then why is Dominique
paying her to be with you?
What?
You lying.
Nope.
Elena is this true?
I mean it started
out that way at first.
But once I started
to get to know you,
I accepted less payments.
I mean,
I was getting to the point where
I could be with you for free.
(chuckles) Gosh.
Damn.
The tea is hot.
This is crazy.
Yes it is.
Oh,
and how do I know that bit
of information you ask?
No one asked.
I know because I was with
Dominique when he made the call
after we had sex.
What?
Wait.
That's right.
Your bestie and I have
been having sex for months.
He's the reason that
I said no to you.
Damn!
Rain, Rain.
(indistinct) I don't want
to hear anything (indistinct)
right now.
Just let me explain.
(door closes)
(sighs) Simone.
Nothing (indistinct).
Like I said,
I ain't going nowhere until I...
Bitch.
If you want.
Relax.
Yeah.
I ain't finished playing
with his hair yet.
Bye you'll.
(indistinct chattering)
So am I still
getting paid or not?
You ruining the game.
(soft piano music)
(door opens)
(door closes)
Yo Rain, let me
holler at you for a sec.
The only thing I
want to know is why.
Why would you do that to me Dom?
It just.
Look, man.
Simone is one of those
things that just happened.
Bullshit.
Dom you got your slew of women?
You've got your pick
up all these women
you be calling and
texting all the time.
Why did you have to
go sleep with mine.
Look man, I know I messed
up but I'm trying to make...
Or you think...
I got caught up, all right?
It was only supposed
to happen one time.
And then it happened
a second time
and it did happen
multiple times.
I mean, negative shit
was just so good.
Well, you noticed that.
I'm trying to get
your ass kicked.
Listen, man.
There's nothing I can do or say,
explain to you what I did.
I stabbed you in your back
and I'm sorry about that.
You damn ritual.
And the whole thing with Elena.
Look, man, I feel guilty
about what I was doing, man.
And it didn't seeing everything
that you was going through.
I had to do something.
So yeah,
I paid one of my colleagues
to go out with you.
I mean, Elisa bought
you out of your phone
when things looking out for you.
Except for the fact
that my whole relationship
with Elena was a lie.
And my best friend slept with
the woman that I was planning
on spending the rest
of my life with.
Right, that's all over with.
I mean the truth is out Rain.
I'm not kicking it
with Simone anymore.
I broke things off.
I chose you,
our friendship over her.
And so now things are
just supposed to go back to
how they were before, huh?
Exactly.
I mean, come on man.
Do you know how we do,
bros before hoes.
Right?
Yeah, you right.
Cause you see, as of right now,
you no longer my bro.
Hoe.
(suspenseful music begins)
Rain.
(rap music)
♪ Love,
♪ Lust,
♪ Pain.
♪ And the sex.
♪ Dreams,
♪ Fears
♪ Game.
♪ The existence.
♪ Love,
♪ Lust,
♪ Pain.
♪ And this together,
♪ Dreams,
♪ Fears
♪ Pain
♪ And the existence.
♪ Things fall out,
♪ The heartbreaks.
♪ The plot thickness.
♪ A night full of I love
using good riddance.
♪ I told you it would
go this way with
♪ Yo won't listen.
♪ The vision made
me make decisions
♪ That just cause division.
♪ And we ain't even
talking kids.
♪ So baby, who you kidding?
♪ She want a new addition,
♪ But I'm poisoned
work the business
♪ And not be damned the bit.
♪ And that the home
that I don't live in,
♪ All this,
♪ Hey, come over shit is
really sacrilegious.
♪ But you know my heart.
♪ And I just thought
that had a credit.
♪ You can debt it.
♪ If you think I make a sido
♪ At my craft is crazy.
♪ 'Cause you lied the money
and the memories we got.
♪ And yet to think
that you was great
♪ To get to look at you was bad,
♪ But yet to be with
you was better.
♪ And that can never let up.
♪ You moved down to the beach
♪ And still nobody
gets you water
♪ In a different type of water.
♪ I'm just trying to
keep my head up.
♪ I'm not sure what my mind is.
♪ Not my finest.
♪ Let's be honest right now.
♪ Beat a man right now.
(rap music continues)
Aj, what are you doing?
I wanted to make
sure you are okay.
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
Rain I am so sorry
that happened to you.
Yeah.
Me too.
First Simone, and now Elena.
Maybe I'm just need to be
alone for the rest of my life.
Don't say that you are a
good man and you deserve...
Look Aj,
I'm not in the mood to hear
about how good of a man I am,
how much I deserve
to be with somebody.
Who's going to love me
the way that I love her.
Shit getting old enough.
I'm tired.
Just wanna go to bed.
Forget about all this mess.
Rain.
Lock up when you leave.
Good night.
I love you.
I love you too.
I love you more than a friend.
Not like a brother.
I want to be your lover.
What did you say?
I said I never had
nobody to show all these.
Should he show me in
this special way of yeah.
No, no.
That's not what you said?
You said, I love you
more than a friend.
Yes.
Yes Rain.
I love you more than a friend.
(soft piano music begins)
I loved you ever since,
the first day I saw
you in second grade,
I had just moved here and
you were my first friend.
And over the years,
my feelings for you grew,
but did our friendship.
And I didn't want to lose that.
And besides I was
afraid to say anything.
'Cause I didn't think
you saw me like that.
I saw you.
I've always seen you.
And I see you now.
Yeah.
I've always had
feelings for you too.
But like you had in mind,
I didn't want to lose my friend.
My best friend,
the one who's always
been there for me.
The one who encourages
me and builds me up.
The one who loves
me no matter what.
And just to set the
record straight,
I love you more than a
friend and not like a sister.
I think this is about damn
time and I became your mystery.
(chuckles)
(indistinct) without you.
No, it was (indistinct)
We will work on that.
(chuckles)
Hey.
Yeah.
Look up.
(indistinct)
You know what that means?
(chuckles)
Okay,
Rain.
I've always wanted to do this.
So let me show you
how it is done.
(chuckles)
Okay.
Direct me baby.
(piano music intensifies)
And that's the story
of how your mother
and I finally got together.
Come on dad.
I really didn't need
to hear all that.
Oh yeah.
(chuckles)
How do you think you got in.
Teamor dad, teamor.
But what ever happened to
your friend, Dominique,
did you ever forgive him?
I did.
Are y'all still friends?
(bright upbeat music begins)
Son, in life you'll learn
that people come into your life
for a reason, a season
and some for life time.
(bright upbeat
music intensifies)
♪ What a way to spend
♪ Your holiday
♪ What a way to show
♪ The things you cannot say
♪ What a way to make
Sadly the season for
that friendship is over.
How much time does he want
to get to talk to me yet.
(bright upbeat music continues)
Aj, you have a visitor.
(bright upbeat
music intensifies)
♪ When I call you can hear
♪ A friendship is close
♪ Makes me feel you
♪ Everyday can be Christmas
Hey Aj.
Hey Briana.
(indistinct) head
down to the crib
and get your butt beat?
If anyone is getting
their butt beat it is you.
Hey, hey hey.
There gonna be no beating
butts around here,
except for me and your mom.
Ew.
Y'all go on and play.
♪ Everyday can be Christmas
(door opens)
I'll spot you five points.
You ain't gotta
spot me nothing
I won last time remember.
All right.
(bright upbeat music)
Oh, look at them.
They look like we did
when we were that age?
Yeah.
The only difference is
you can never beat
me in basketball.
Boy, but I would
take you right now.
Oh, yeah.
I would take you right
up to that play ground.
Oh really?
I thought you had to get back
down to the radio station.
Oh, baby when you
just didn't remember.
So you make your own rules,.
Mm-hmm.
Now your own schedule.
Okay.
And according to my schedule,
it's 10 o'clock here.
It's 10 o'clock.
It's about time we go ahead
and get baby number two.
Baby number two.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Right now.
(bells ringing)
(rock music)
I love you too.
I love you more than a
brother and a friend.
(indistinct)
I know (indistinct) you get
time in this relationship.
Okay.
(laughs) Yes.
(indistinct Chattering)
After last night,
I just assumed.
You know what they say about
people who assume, right?
(chuckles)
You are sick.
(laughs)
Are you nervous?
I'm sorry I just got out
of a serious relationship.
Sorry.