So, Daisy Bea.
Anything bothering you?
Out of the ordinary?
- Mm. Nope.
- Good.
-And how's Camille doing?
-Uh...
- She's Camille.
- Yeah.
We all just love her here.
A wonderful lady.
Now there's
a bit of pressure here.
Now, Daisy,
still no children, huh?
Not that I'm aware of.
Seriously, though, no kids.
Is that something that you're...
Well, is that something
that you're planning on?
Yeah. Absolutely.
One day. Always have.
Excited about kids.
I just don't want to rush it.
Now, Daisy, I don't want
to sound insensitive here,
but one day...
This is one of those
"Now or never" type situations.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
-Now or never?
-Yeah.
I don't want to startle you
or anything, but...
...another year or so
and, well...
...it'll just get
harder and harder.
Now it says here that you're
still on birth control, right?
-Yeah.
-That's another hurdle.
You don't just have the age
working against you,
but the hormonal imbalance.
What's with all the age talk?
If your birthday
is correct here,
it says to me
that you're not thirty.
Well, I'm in my thirties.
So there's that.
Almost 40?
Right. No. Sure.
Yeah. I know that.
Okay, great.
Then we're on the same page.
Absolutely. Same page.
May want to get
that ball rolling.
-It's Friday already?
-The one day of the month
that they don't all have
their faces all shoved
in their phones.
- Rally! Rally!
- Hey, come on.
Come on, guys. This is a place
of study and focus.
No one cares.
Not to be the bearer
of bad news,
but no one cares about you.
That's not true. I do.
Aw. That's just too cute, Daisy.
Hey.
I'll give it back to you when
you learn to call me Miss Bea.
I'm a teacher
and you're a student.
Learn a bit of respect.
You're not a teacher.
You're a, whatever,
librarian, Miss Bea.
Can have it back now?
It'll be in the counselor's
office after school.
Come on, Sadie. Let's go.
So rude.
Oh, uh,
your art du jour project.
Oh, I always love these.
So what's the latest passion
in the class today?
We are rounding out
our scratch art projects.
Pretty much my favorite form.
It takes a steady hand.
Oh. Cool. You have fun.
So, how's everything
with Stephen?
-It's good.
-That sounds like
a dream relationship.
Well, he keeps, you know,
laying down these little
"Let's take it slow"
-or "Let's go with the flow"
type jabs.
-You should break up with him.
-No, I can't. Just moved in.
-I'm kidding. Wow.
Not even a thought.
That's impressive.
Well, he loves horses, and, you
know, horses are my weakness.
-I think cruising along with
the status quo is your weakness.
-Ouch.
I'm just saying,
if you want different outputs,
you need to try
different inputs.
-You know what I'm saying?
-Mm.
Inputs?
You never want to settle down?
We're still so young, Daze.
Well, that's not what
I've been hearing lately.
All this talk
about settling down
comes from this generation
who graduated high school,
got married and...
oozed out children.
Your mother.
The world is different now.
Sure, but biology does not care
if the world is different.
Believe whatever you want
to believe, and I will be here
to support you.
You gotta teach?
Yep. I got jazz.
You should come sometime.
-I'll think about it.
-I love you.
I love you.
Hm.
Hey, do you need a hand?
-Oh, yeah.
-Oh, awesome.
Oh!
Oh.
You're so lucky to get
to babysit this little prince.
Oh, no, he's mine.
Thanks so much.
Oh, sorry. Bye.
Bye.
- Hey, darling.
- Frank!
-Frank dear.
-How's the--
How's the library?
You need anything?
- No, it's great.
- Frank!
How's the office?
Mm. Stressful.
-Hence the beer.
-Mm.
I guess I have a husband
who's hard of hearing.
Camille. Hello, dear.
You staying for dinner, Daze?
She's going
to the cowboy's house.
That's where I live.
Sort of. A lot of stuff here.
So how is it over there, anyway?
How's Stephen?
I haven't seen him in ages.
Yeah, I know.
I'm working on that.
Oh, Daisy, don't make any plans
for tomorrow night.
-Why?
-There's a photography exhibit
for Jack Palmer.
Up and coming.
Everyone's raving about him.
We can socialize a bit,
rub some elbows,
get you a new job.
-She just said
that she loves her job.
-Yeah, I'm totally fine with it.
The amount of fine you are
with things really concerns me.
7:00 p.m.
Already got us tickets.
Fine.
Mm.
My parents invited you over
for dinner soon.
Your mom going
to be there?
Um, she counts as a parent. Yes.
Mm. Have to think about that.
What do you mean?
It's not that
she frightens me necessarily.
-It's just-- She terrifies me.
-What?
She's just always so nervous.
I think it's her eyes.
Maybe you could get used to it
'cause it could be
a very nice evening.
Come on, Daisy. It's not like
I don't want to be there.
Sounds like it.
It's...
With my last girlfriend,
everything went so fast,
too fast.
Hmm. We've been
dating for a year.
I just don't want
to rush dinners.
Okay? I, I, I just want to go
with the flow.
Hey.
We've got a good thing going.
We do, don't we?
Okay. Same page?
-Mm.
-Do you want to maybe go,
you know...
How, how's that?
That's good.
Awesome.
Well, yeah.
- Hey, can we talk for a second?
- Yeah.
Sure. Now?
Um, never mind. Keep going.
-You sure?
-Yeah. Yeah. Keep going.
I feel like you're not sure.
I'm super sure.
Impressive.
Thanks.
Come on, August. Hurry up.
Hey, where y'all going?
The bell hasn't even rung yet.
We're trying to get
to third period early.
Miss Bonneville has
a big announcement to make.
-Ooh.
-We're hoping
it's a new French easel.
Hm.
All right. Well,
you're all here.
May as well get this over with.
Get what over with?
I'm leaving you.
Wait.
- What?
- I'm so sorry,
but there has been
a blatant disregard
for what I've been trying
to build here
and I, I've had it.
I can't finish this semester.
Starting tomorrow,
this class will serve
as an open study
period supervised by...
I don't know who.
You said you had good news.
No, I said I had news.
You supplied the good part.
So no French easel?
French easel? No. No.
This is, like, our life.
There's just a handful of you.
No one has interest.
I'm exhausted.
I have been fighting
and fighting for years,
clawing to get more funding.
I've invested more time and
money than any teacher should.
I love you kids,
but it's too much for me now.
Surely there's a grant,
or donors or something.
Who are you?
I'm Daisy.
Librarian. Hi.
Oh, yeah, Daisy.
You go find them.
You go apply for them.
I'm finished.
This is bullshit.
Oh, it's like
an exponential crisis.
- Existential.
- Whatever.
Just go take your piss.
Gross.
Sadie, on your way.
Hey, guys, come on.
I know it's a big blow,
but it's not the end
of the world.
I thought you would
actually care.
I do care.
I'm just saying
it's going to work out.
It doesn't seem like it.
Isn't he brilliant?
He certainly loves nude women.
How do you reckon
she got into that position?
Trash compactor?
I certainly admire his gumption,
but he could at least
put some clothes on
at least a few of them.
Oh, but that would be
boring then, wouldn't it?
Yeah, I can't say
you're wrong there.
-Where are you going?
-Food.
You already have food.
That's my favorite piece.
Oh, shit. Um, what did you say?
The portrait
that you're looking at,
it's my favorite one.
So vulnerable.
I'm wondering
how that's vulnerable.
Well, you know,
to expose yourself in that way,
in that fashion,
find the animal within.
It's a woman in some mesh.
So you don't think
there's more to it than that?
The animal thing is interesting.
Maybe that's what
he wants us to think.
-He?
-The photographer dude.
Right. Yeah. Uh...
I had heard that, um...
Someone said she had to stay
in that position
for, like, over an hour.
Much to his dismay, I'm sure.
I don't follow.
Lots of naked chicks.
Well, come on. I mean, that's--
It's all for the art, I suppose.
-Right. The sacrifice.
-Exactly.
I should, uh, talk
to a few more guests,
but this was--
Well, I didn't...
-Oh, Daisy.
-Daisy.
-That's a nice name.
-Thanks.
Why do you have to go and...?
Shit. You're Jack Palmer?
Have a nice night, Daisy.
It looked like
he was flirting with you.
-We have to go.
-What? Why?
I just insulted him.
Oh, it didn't look like that
to me.
-It looked like flirting.
-I have a boyfriend.
Oh, I'll find out
if he's single.
I know I'm saying words,
and there's air
coming out of my mouth.
They just don't seem to land.
Great. Thanks.
Mm. Mm.
Mm.
Oh, handsome.
You all right?
Did I do something?
No. I'm okay.
Mm. Smell good.
Well, ain't it?
It's been a while
since we've, uh,
caught up since the move.
You know, you're right.
It has just been
"Go, go, go," hasn't it?
Well, that's putting it lightly.
What do you want to talk about?
Well, how's life?
It's fun. It's, it's good
now that you're here.
That's about it, I guess.
Mm.
Cool.
Anything else on your mind?
Mm, no, not really.
Mm.
Okay? I'm just gonna splunk
right into it.
I went to the doctor's office
the other day and...
...he said, um, that
I don't have much time.
What are you telling me,
Daisy, are you dying?
No. Gynecologist.
No cancer or anything.
-Just egg stuff.
-Oh, well, thank God.
I mean, don't say eggs stuff,
but, I mean,
good for, you know,
not dying and all.
Yeah, uh, listen,
I'm about to be 40,
and so biology has a way of...
-Oh.
-Yeah.
And he said that
if I wanted to have kids,
I really need to start
thinking about that, and...
I'm not saying "Hey,
let's make a baby right now."
I just...
-Not at all.
-Okay. Well, thank God.
Well, I just want to see
if that was something that...
...you know, you might...
Okay. Uh, I'll be honest.
Maybe, I don't know.
I'd want to be married first.
Um, and we agreed
to take it slow.
And I always liked the idea
of living with someone
for a little while before
I made that decision. So...
Yeah.
Okay. Yeah. No, sure.
You mad at me?
I mean, I've told you
my rationale from the get-go.
Yeah. And I told you mine.
I wanted kids one day.
-Wait a minute. That's not fair.
-No, this is my fault.
I should have talked about this
before my lease was up
and I just moved in.
I didn't know there was
gonna be such a hard deadline.
Gosh, time is such a bitch.
I didn't know that having kids
was that important to you.
Yeah.
Uh, I don't know what to say
right now, Daisy.
Back to square one.
Not necessarily. I--
Do you or don't you want kids?
Yes or no? No gray area, please.
Then you should've said
that from the beginning.
I'll stay with my parents.
Get my stuff out of here.
Wait, are, are we breaking up?
I don't see any reason
to waste any more time.
Well...
-Dang.
-Dang is not the perfect thing
to say right now, Stephen.
I know. I'm sorry. It's just...
Suddenly, I'm not
all that hungry.
Me neither.
What do you think that's about?
Square one.
Miss Bea, are you okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
You guys?
Besides hating life, you mean?
At least you have a purpose.
Not for the next hour.
Not for the next life.
Hey, where's my art du jour ?
Come in.
-Oh, hey, Daze.
-Hey.
I wanted to ask you
about Miss Bonneville leaving.
-I mean,
the kids had just gutted.
-Oh, yeah.
She shouldn't have
said all that.
Wasn't supposed to come out
till the end of semester,
and I was supposed
to make the announcement.
Can't you just give her
the resources she needs
to finish it out?
-That would at least
give us a little--
-You know I love you, Daze.
But this isn't some fancy
high school you pay tuition for.
Or one that pays for supplies.
We're public.
-Yeah.
-And public schools
are a business.
And in Louisiana,
investments are made
in programs with interest.
-Football.
Sports. Hell, women's volleyball
is doing pretty well.
But aside from, what,
eight students
in the arts program,
I hate say it, but who cares?
-Dad!
-I'm sorry,
but when I weigh eight
versus 2,000 fans
in the stands on Friday,
-it's a no brainer.
-During World War II,
they asked Winston Churchill--
They asked him to cut funding
for the arts, and he said,
"But then what
would we be fighting for?"
I'm the one
who told you about that quote.
Well?
It's money. Relevance.
You know I'm a big supporter
of the arts, Daze,
but I also know where I stand as
principal of this institution,
which is, after all...
-A business.
-Exactly.
Is there anything else
I can do for you, hon?
I imagine you have other things
to worry about more than this.
No, I'm trying
not to think about it.
I don't know.
Well, maybe this, uh,
well, change in routine
will help with some perspective.
Maybe you're right.
See you tonight.
I said it already.
You know, I'm exhausted.
I mean, I, I, I can't even
get the most basic materials.
Brushes, good paper,
non-huffable glue, huh.
Coach Davis snaps his fingers
and pfft, your dad
comes crawling.
It's just not that simple,
Miss Bonneville.
You're a grown woman.
Call me Helen.
Okay, Helen, um,
the kids are devastated.
They will find their way.
I don't know that they will
without you.
I mean, can't you just stay
until December?
I don't know. Run through
all the materials and supplies.
A grace period.
Uh, it's all so lifeless,
isn't it?
Politics. Money.
Who cares about getting
a well-rounded education, right?
You know, I think I've earned
the time to paint and write,
- and...
- who knows, maybe even act.
But the teaching no, no.
I've run out of energy for it.
You seem to really
care about them.
Why don't you help them?
I wouldn't even know
where to begin.
You know what I tell
all my artists?
Get creative.
So, first you come to my show
-and you insult
my photography...
-Yeah, I'm sorry.
...and then you're just going
to show up out of nowhere,
-and you're going
to ask me for help?
-Yep.
See? I like that. That's bold.
-Wow. That is
a beautiful picture.
-Hmm.
- Look at that.
They're so cute.
- Yeah.
Smiles are mesmerizing,
aren't they?
Captured it in Angola.
Think it kind of has
this glimmer of hope
in a devastating time.
Through family.
Well, didn't expect that
from you.
Yeah, it's not all naked women.
Unfortunately, your story,
it's not all that unfamiliar
to me.
These arts programs,
they keep getting cut.
It's bit of a national trend.
-Hm.
-So what were you thinking?
Uh, keep in mind, too.
I'm a freelancer.
So, like, schedules,
not really my jam.
I totally get it. The class
meets three times a week,
only for an hour.
But right after lunch.
Eight kids?
What's your play on all this?
I think I'm really close
to two of them.
-You think?
-Yeah, it's hard to tell
with teenagers,
but it was the collective look
that "Armageddon is near"
on their faces
when the teacher quit, so...
-I guess you never know
what they could become.
-Exactly.
-Like, their effect
on the world.
-Yes.
Okay, uh, let's see.
Hmm. It's tough.
I'm saving up for this trip
to Haiti in January,
so I kind of have to hold on
to all the cash flow I can get.
Uh, plus, I got to be some
sort of fiscally responsible.
-I could pay if it helps.
-Oh, no, no, no, sorry,
that's, that's not what I meant.
-It's just like if, uh,
commission were to come up--
-It's done.
-We're paying you.
-Mm. They cut
the funding for the program.
I guarantee the school
is not going to cover the costs.
Don't worry about it.
It's handled. Got it.
-Okay. Uh, how?
-Would that do it?
I mean, I don't know
if I feel comfortable.
I mean, you get to help
some kids uncover
their creative selves
and get some money.
Would that do it?
Yeah.
Okay. See you Monday.
One o'clock.
Monday, one o'clock.
So, he volunteers one hour
every three days,
for the rest of the semester.
Then what?
I don't know.
I figured it's a great start.
It's a good start. I'm just
thinking long term here.
-I don't have
a full-fledged plan yet.
-Daisy.
You're right. I haven't done
anything like this before, so--
-And I understand that--
-You know what?
I'll chew on it tonight
and I'll let you know.
- Daisy!
- Oh, my Lord, Mom. What?
You've been ignoring our guest.
Well... lovely meatloaf.
I'm sorry, Bradley. I don't know
what my mother has told you,
-bless her heart--
-I know you didn't just say
bless her heart.
But she doesn't seem to care
that I just broke up
with my boyfriend last night.
So I'm on hiatus while I try
to help some of my students.
-Not your students.
-My kids, then.
Nope. Don't have
any of those, either.
What's the...
...what's the long term plan
to keep the class?
I'm willing to work
with you here, Daze,
but this is your show,
-and I'm just not going to--
-Show?
Yeah, your show. I'm a very
busy man. So I'm not--
I could put on an art show.
A silent auction,
raise money that way.
Preposterous.
I'm sorry, Bradley.
Get real money for supplies.
Maybe create some more buzz.
-Get more students interested.
-Okay. Okay.
Okay. Date, time?
I don't know. I just thought
of it like five seconds ago.
This is a big distraction,
if you ask me.
- We'll need all the time we can get.
-  -And rude.
December 13th, last Friday
before the end of semester.
Art show.
Just need a time.
I don't know. 7:00 p.m.?
7:00 p.m. it is.
Clock's ticking.
Don't expect my help
with any of this.
Don't worry, I'm not.
You should get back
to your guest.
Ouch.
This is really good meatloaf.
Oh, Bradley, stuff it!
Uh, Miss Bea...
...where's this Jack Palmer guy?
He'll be here.
He's probably just running late.
I hope so.
No disrespect, Miss Bea.
But what if this guy
doesn't show up?
What do you know about art?
Um...
Let me check.
Daisy!
Eat.
I'm not that hungry anymore.
More for me.
So it went well?
It was rough.
But I'm going
to nail it on Wednesday.
Even if Jack doesn't show up.
Yeah, absolutely.
You know, I would start
by organizing this place.
It's got scatterbrain
written all over it.
Mm, yeah, well,
that's Bonneville.
We need a fresh start,
change things up.
Narrow the focus.
Well, let's get started,
shall we?
-We?
-Yeah.
I want to bask
in your newfound excitement too.
Aw.
- Hey.
- Hey, Mr. Bea.
Pulling some after hours, huh?
Yep. About to whip
this place into shape.
I see you've got food.
I'll let your mother know.
Dinner in the classroom.
after a first day,
the life of a true educator.
I'll see you at home.
Absolutely not.
Look, I've come to terms with
the fact that I'm getting older.
So there's a plan C.
You might just like it.
Donor insemination.
We get a jump start
on the process.
I might need your help
raising the child
if Mr. Right
doesn't come along first.
Doesn't have to be A-B-C.
Maybe it's ACB.
That's not the proper way.
I just got off
birth control, Mom.
I'm trying here.
I saw them in the trash.
Why the change of heart?
Does it really matter to you?
How much?
Is tomorrow still looking rough?
These kids need you.
I have no clue what I'm doing.
I mean, you could give me
a paintbrush and I'd try
to eat rice with it.
Here.
Oh, God.
And I may have promised
my dad that we're putting on
an art show in December.
So there's that.
I'm sorry. What?
A silent auction,
you know, to sell the kids' work
to rai-- raise money
for the program. I mean,
I told him that you and I
would put it together.
Do you always speak
for other people
or is that sort of a new thing?
It's a new thing.
Mm.
Cool.
Okay, the hard walkout thing,
it's not gonna work every time.
-That's what you got.
-I told you.
I was hoping for
an after-school shopping trip.
Um, I have a little budget
for that.
Oh.
Whoa, Miss Bea!
Love what you did
with the place!
Yeah. It looks like
someone actually cares.
Uh...
Uh, okay.
Well, we are getting started
a little bit behind,
but that's good.
I always find
that the creative mind
thrives with an uphill battle.
You throw your inhibitions away
and you just-- you go with it.
Some people are going to say
that that's winging it, but...
...I say organic.
Now, do we have
limited supplies?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's putting it lightly.
But...
...you don't need
a high-end studio
to create something
that's visceral.
We will get more supplies
to create a one-of-a-kind show.
But until then...
...this is your centerpiece.
This is what the entire exhibit
is going to revolve around.
What piece?
With those supplies,
and this trash...
...and the time we have
between now and the exhibit.
Tell me something,
but with a sculpture,
All right, guys,
let's get to work.
Uh, what do you want it to say
with the sculpture?
We're not done yet.
When we snap a photo,
we are looking for the way
the light falls. Sure.
Composition. All of that.
But most importantly, we are
looking for a moment in time.
That look on someone's face,
right?
Something you couldn't
manufacture even if you try.
Such a good start
for everybody today.
Really. Just so good.
And scoop, scoop.
Open, open.
Very good. Keep going.
Keep going. Eyes up, boys.
Yep. We're shooting this
within a week.
-Hey.
-How's it going?
-I feel good.
-No, with the kids.
Oh, yeah, they're cool.
I could really use some with
a little less self-awareness.
Chad, buddy, loosen it up
a little bit.
Oh, we have to get back
to the studio, so...
-All right.
-It's nice to see you.
-Yeah.
-Thanks for having us.
Yeah. Bye, Jack.
I know. I know.
Okay, bye.
All right. Let's just do this
all again, shall we?
I was jealous.
Well... Oh, I haven't eaten
anything all day.
Would you want
to go grab something?
Absolutely.
-Okay.
-Yes.
That's all you.
Well, not actually, come on.
-You gotta save some of
that for me.
-Look, those are three berries.
-I'm getting one.
-All right.
Right.
So...
Mm. Been a while since I've
shared dessert with someone.
Yeah?
I haven't been on a date...
...in a long time.
Well, who says
this is a date, mister?
Oh, no...
- Sorry.
- I'm kidding.
Oh.
I have to ask you a question
that kind of
puts me in the gallows.
But...
...you know, uh, about
that check that I gave you.
-Oh.
-I was just wondering
when you were going to--
or if you have deposited it.
You're talking about this check?
Yeah. Great.
So, uh, do you know
when you're going to...?
Yeah.
Wait. What are you doing?
I don't want it.
What do you mean
you don't want it?
I don't want it.
- Well, isn't that the whole
reason why you showed up?
Okay. All right.
Yeah. Well, fine.
I feel like a jerk about that.
Well, you're forgiven.
Thank you.
And...
...I see why you went to bat
for these kids.
They are pretty great, huh?
Yep.
It makes you think, though.
About what?
Like...
...if I had a kid, right?
Like some, you know,
just a toddler running around,
wreaking havoc all over
the place. Or, or if you did.
-Go on.
-Well, how difficult...
...that would make what
we're doing for these kids.
But, uh...
...now, you know,
we're able to help
eight of them.
So, yeah, I mean...
Thank you.
Cheers.
To the kids.
Also to this cheesecake.
-Hey.
-I told you I'm not gonna share.
You do it yet?
Mom?
How long
have you been standing there?
No.
They recommend that you wait
at least a month
so you're off birth control.
Even if I didn't know
that was bullshit--
-Whoa!
-I'd say it has been a month.
Uh, well, time flies, huh?
Do I really need to say
clock's ticking again?
You're single. Fine.
But what about
your ACB proposal?
And you're wasting your time
with that ludicrous art project.
I called all
the insemination clinics.
No inquiries on your behalf.
That's frightening.
Your focus is not
in the right place.
You're acting like you're
living in the glory days again,
Well, maybe 39 is my glory days.
Plus, if it makes
you feel any better,
I went on a date last night
with Jack, and I was happy.
Jack Palmer?
He's a tomcat, a, a, a player.
Everyone knows this.
You seemed all about it
at his art show.
According to my bridge club,
he gets around.
Your bridge club?
You're wasting your time.
You said you wanted a child.
Remember?
Someone to nurture.
I was 16.
Then you were 24
and then you were 30.
Well, maybe I'm not
as with that anymore.
With that?
You're lying to yourself.
-This must be a phase.
-What if it's not?
Well, then,
I want my money back.
No, You know what?
You keep it. It'll help you.
-With what?
-Moving cost.
Rent. Some place else.
Eden!
- Mm.
- Coffee!
Mm. Fine.
I think I need to talk
to Jack about the kid thing.
Daisy, it is way too early
for this.
Fine. Eat a bagel.
You eat a bagel.
Fine, sure.
I waited a whole year
to talk to Stephen
about this and look
where it got me.
It opened the opportunity for
you to meet Jack, who is fun.
And creative.
-And...
-Sexy.
Sexy.
And you just had
your first date last night.
If you go through this
and that guy
doesn't run for the hills,
I will completely question
that guy's sanity.
I just need to know
if it's something
that he wants,
you know, someday.
There's no harm in that.
Okay.
I say this as someone
who loves and trusts
and is consistently
confused by you,
it's a bad idea.
But Jack's different.
I mean, he's kind
and understanding,
and he's in tune with himself.
And I feel like time
is running out for me.
I have this literal feeling.
Okay, I'm going to create
an app that goes
straight to your brain
that warns me
of your next thought
and why you're having it.
Like the weather app,
but Daisy's brain.
-I'm gonna ask him.
-You have selective hearing,
you know that?
Thank you for talking me
through this.
It was very helpful.
Selective hearing.
Bye.
Psst. Hey.
Daisy?
-Lunchtime yet.
-Hmm.
- Uh, about four minutes.
- Oh. Mm.
So I think a guy like you would
want full disclosure. Yeah?
Oh. A guy like me?
I'm potentially about to ruin
something great.
How so?
Simply by talking.
Never knew a civil conversation
could do that.
Look, Daze, if it makes you feel
any better about
whatever's on your mind,
you know, I am an artist, sure,
but I'm rational, you know?
I do listen.
Just spit.
Well, my ex-boyfriend,
about a day before I came
waltzing into your studio--
Oh, no. Jealousy issues?
-Stalker?
-No.
We actually separated after
being together for about a year.
Oh, so it was serious.
-Well, I thought so.
-Mm-hmm.
And we had the discussion
about having kids,
and we decided to just end it.
Well,
that is a...
That's a big relief. I'm really
relieved to hear that.
Wait.
Why?
Well, um...
Okay. So based
on our conversation
from the other night...
Whoa. All right. I just figured
I would get it off my chest.
I had a vasectomy,
like, two years ago. So...
I mean, it's good
to be on the same page,
assuming things
were to move forward,
which hoping they do...
Oh.
Oh, you were the one
who wanted kids.
What made you think otherwise?
We cheers-ed our coffees.
We talked about helping
a lot of kids.
Sorry, I just-- I was completely
under the impression--
So you never want kids
since we're assuming things
from our date?
Okay. Can we slow down? Right?
'Cause this is happening
really fast.
-Well?
-No.
Then no.
I like my life how it is.
And who would be stupid enough
to bring a kid
into this world anyway?
So I'm stupid for wanting kids?
No, I-- No,
I didn't mean that. I just...
Daisy. I mean, we just had
our first date,
and it was an impromptu one.
Where is this coming from?
It's coming from the fact
that I don't have time...
...to figure out
what the hell it is that I want.
I'd love to be with you
for a year.
But then...
...if I brought this up then...
Dream world, it's you
and a kid.
You got a very
unorthodox sense of timing.
We're old. We should be honest
with each other by now.
We're not that old.
I'm really sorry about
any misunderstanding, and I...
I completely understand
where you're coming from.
Stop being so nice.
You're making it worse.
Just rational.
-Business as usual.
-Of course.
Hey, Mr. P, I got an idea
for my third piece.
I'm going to change it up a bit.
Cool. Oh, yeah, yeah.
Hey, can't wait to see that.
Is that sandwich spicy,
Miss Bea? You're tearing up.
Super spicy.
-Hey.
Hey, guys.
Shit.
-You have to go?
-I promise,
I, I didn't plan it like this,
but... yeah.
-Okay. Go.
-I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
Um, Sadie, excuse me.
What are you doing?
So I just got transferred
to this class
because, well, home ec sucks.
Can I come inside?
Uh...
Cool.
There has to be something
you can do, Dad.
Don't call me that here.
Oh, because it's such a secret.
Let me be Frank.
Sorry.
This is kind of funny
because my name is Frank.
I know, Dad.
Sorry.
My hands are tied, Daze.
-She's a bully.
-No, she's a student.
She tortures August and Maddie.
Well, then, it's your duty
as a teacher
to mold her into
a compassionate human being.
-Me?
-Yes, you, Jack,
whoever else is helping.
Jack had to step out
for the day.
Then, quick question.
-Yeah.
-Who's watching your kids?
Oh. Oh, uh...
You're not an artist.
You're an idiot.
Say that to my 5,000 followers.
Hi, all. I'm--
-Excuse me?
-Go hike up your skirt
for another five likes.
-Maddie.
-I mean, I would,
but Daisy's got my phone.
Good. Maybe you can
use your brain for once.
Okay, everybody just stop!
Go back to your projects.
Well, what about me?
What about you, Sadie?
Lord, please bless this food
to the nourishment of our body.
Please watch over Mom,
or please help
Daddy find his teeth.
Amen.
So, um...
...your mom tells me
you're trying to get pregnant.
- Oh, Lordy! Are you okay?
- Stanley, you goof.
Sorry. Sit. Don't get up.
- Oh.
- I'm fine.
- I'm sorry.
I, I, I didn't mean--
- Stanley, stop it.
If only most men
were so forthcoming.
Mom, you're laying it on
a little thick.
You told me to set this up.
So, Stanley, quick question.
Is there an office poll
for when I'll get knocked up?
Well...
- Is she this
crazy at work?
Uh, sometimes. Yeah.
I'm sorry she dragged you
into this.
No, I got a good roast
out of it.
I'm not good
at this kind of stuff.
So I'm sorry
if I acted a fool in there.
No, no, not at all.
It's just, like,
you're real nice
and, and pretty funny
and all, and...
Yeah, I might not be the right
guy for you, but it's just...
- I, I know I'm direct--
- That's great.
Yeah?
It's just-- You know,
I don't want to be 70
when my kid
graduates high school.
Um, could, could
I call you sometime?
Yeah.
Let's take it slow.
We don't have to jump in bed
right this minute.
Yeah. I wouldn't know
what to do if we did.
I'm kidding.
I've totally had
intercourse before.
Hey.
I know today was kind of
a weird one, but, uh...
-...can we straighten
a couple things out?
-Sure.
Okay.
You and me,
we do not always see
eye to eye on everything.
But I think that we had,
or have, a real connection.
- It's effortless and--
- Hey, Daisy!
Late lunch for milady.
-Oh, thank you.
-Mm.
Uh, yeah. I'm sorry.
I should be going.
Wait. Are you sure?
Yeah.
Well, don't forget
we have that meeting
at the venue after school.
So I will, in fact,
see you later.
Great.
-Uh, you're a lifesaver.
-Mm.
Yeah. What's, uh, what's this?
No idea.
So...
...I will need a deposit on the
space no later than the seventh.
It's a popular spot
for Christmas parties.
You all are able to load
in the dock out back
the night before.
However, I will need
everything out
by 8:00 a.m.
the next morning. Right?
I will give you all a minute.
So what's with the photograph?
You seemed to like it.
I did. Thanks.
Then you like my dream.
Sorry. Uh, Hannah,
can we just get, like,
a quick moment alone?
Sure. Uh, my daughter will be
here at seven and then I...
We'll need to leave.
It was right after Angola,
the vasectomy.
Hm.
If I had a kid of my own,
I know that I would love
that kid so damn much
that I wouldn't be able
to focus on anything else
except parenting.
Oh, I see a whirlwind.
Maybe you could do both.
I want to help
thousands of kids over my life.
I know that's not
traditional, but...
...if I could give
that many children
just, like, a sliver
of joy, of hope.
Well, then, that's my dream.
And I meant what
I told you in the library.
I see something
really special with you.
Look, I don't want to be
unfair to your dream.
It's just, for now,
it's too difficult.
Being around you,
knowing all of this...
...that I'm special to you,
it's just...
Okay, so, what do we do?
You've done so much
for these kids already,
so you can just go help
the next ones.
Well-- No, what do you mean?
No, I'm going
to follow through on this.
Plus, you have no idea how
to put on a show by yourself.
Maybe that's good.
Maybe I'll bring a new
perspective to the art scene.
Keep an eye out
for the invite. Okay?
I'd love to see you here.
Sincerely.
I know how I'm coming off.
It's just what I need right now.
You got a real knack
for ending things, huh?
Mom, I'm here.
Jack is our ace
in the hole, Miss Bea.
How are we going to do this
without him?
Everyone just calm down!
Yeah. I mean, we worked
our tails off for this,
and he just cuts and runs?
It's not like that.
It's not on him.
It's on me. Okay?
And why exactly is it
on you, Miss Bea?
What?
Thanks for sitting here with me.
Silence is really nice.
A lot of noise
in my life lately.
-Mm.
-You know
you're killing it, right?
Thanks.
You're really kind.
I saw your dance video.
It's so good.
-Really?
-Yeah. Yeah. Ah.
Oh.
Our venue.
- Hey, Miss George, what's up?
- Daisy.
Hi. Look, I just wanted
to give you a quick call
to let you know that the
gallery, it was already booked
-on the day
that you had reserved it.
-I, I'm sorry. What?
Yeah. Unfortunately,
it's just not going to work out
the way we hoped.
Oh, no, no, no.
You can't do this right now.
No, no. Don't you worry your
pretty little head about it.
I will have
that deposit back to you ASAP.
I don't want my deposit back.
I want the space for the show,
like we discussed.
I mean, the kids, they're
really depending on this.
I am sorry.
That is just not possible.
Well, what about
some other date?
Like, anything other--
You know, I've got
another call buzzing in,
but I'm so glad
that we could work this out.
Work what out?
Thank you so much
for understanding. Namaste.
Hm. That little brat.
What happened?
Yeah. Hi.
I was wondering if you have
any availability in December?
The entire month is full?
Wow.
No, there won't be
any open flames.
Alcohol? No, it's a kids' show.
That's just the insurance cost?
That's--
A little over our budget.
Never mind.
Uh-huh.
Are you actually laughing at me?
It's a high school art show,
and our other venue bailed, so--
No, I...
Please? There has to be.
They're kids!
And goodbye to you too!
Any luck?
No.
Everyone's either blocked or--
Way too expensive?
Yeah, same here.
We'll figure it out, Daze.
Yeah, Thanks so much
for your help.
Oh.
Miss Bea, uh, you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. I, I just hit
a tiny little bump in the road.
what happened?
Well, we lost our venue.
It's double-booked.
What? That venue
was our ace in the hole.
You said that Jack
was your ace in the hole.
Yeah, well, I thought
we lived in a world
- where there could be two aces
in one hole.
What are we gonna do now?
Uh, well,
we'll keep calling places.
Ask around.
You sure that'll work?
Yeah, of course.
- I learned today that teaching
nine kids is pure hell.
-You're living the dream
compared to other teachers.
-Mm.
You could only have
to worry about one.
Just saying.
Remind me, Mom,
where do you stand on the whole
me-getting-pregnant thing?
I forgot.
You miss the library full-time?
I do a little. It was simple.
Life is good when it's simple.
Took me a while to learn that.
Okay. Consider this
a trial run, Stanley.
Just to gauge. Okay?
Just some checkpoint questions.
Do you drink?
Uh, not much, no, uh...
Occasional shot of Boone's Farm
to take the edge off.
And how's your count?
Huh?
Sperm?
Oh, uh...
It's all there, I think.
And do you secretly smoke?
Never once.
Hm.
Oh. Uh...
What?
Nothing.
I've never done
this before, Daisy.
Wait. Really?
I, I thought you said you had.
Well, are you okay?
Oh, it's-- Well,
you know, when you said
you didn't want to hop into bed
this instant,
I, I, I just didn't think
it'd be this soon. But--
-We can wait.
-No.
Let's do this thing.
Okay.
Okay. Wh-- What do I do next?
Phew!
Well, goodnight, Stanley.
Goodnight, Daisy.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Oh, my God!
That felt great.
-Don't look at me like that.
-Like what?
He's nice.
- Yeah.
-  -Oh, my God, I'm so embarrassed.
I miss when you were just
a librarian. I can't keep up.
-Me neither.
-Just think.
He'll remember last night
for the rest of his life.
Which is halfway over.
Maybe you just needed to do this
so you could realize
that you really want Jack.
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah. Let's just hope
old Stanley boy didn't get you
preggers in the meantime.
Oh, my God, I was just kidding.
You used protection, right?
Listen, I, I think
I need a favor.
I, I forgot. I have
a doctor's appointment today.
Okay.
I need you to go to school
and be with the kids
right after lunch.
And keep th-- keep thinking
of venues we can call,
you know, for the show.
What? Daze?
Just breathe, Miss Bea.
We'll get you sorted out. Okay?
Okay. Yeah. Come in.
Hi. Are you Daisy?
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Dr. Upadhya.
Thanks for coming
to see me today.
Okay, look, if I have cancer,
just rip the band aid off
and tell it to me straight.
You don't have cancer.
I knew it.
No, you don't have cancer.
Oh, good. Thank God.
I did look at your lab results.
Your urine analysis was normal.
Your pregnancy test
was negative.
On your pelvic ultrasound,
though,
you did have uterine fibroids
and ovarian cysts.
Given that you came in
in so much pain,
we can't rule out endometriosis.
Good thing I know
what all that is.
It's a fairly common condition,
and until we know for sure,
I can manage it
with some pain meds
which we can send
to your pharmacy.
But the thing I wanted
to talk to you about was,
I noted in your history,
you've never
been pregnant before?
Okay.
Um, is that something
that you're interested in
or concerned about?
Yes.
Wait. Yes.
Will I be able to?
I honestly can't tell you
for sure right now.
I'd have to refer you
to a specialist.
The way
they diagnose endometriosis
is through
a laparoscopic surgery.
But if you're interested
in knowing your fertility,
we can work that up
in a number of ways.
Oh.
This is a lot.
I know. Um, to be blunt
with you, Daisy,
given your advanced
maternal age,
the odds aren't exactly
in your favor.
For what?
So you're almost forty.
A man, he can have a baby
when he's 30, 40, 80.
- Right.
- Women, we're screwed.
Once we hit 35,
we're what's known
as an elderly primigravida.
-Elderly?
-I know. It's gross.
But basically,
it means once we hit that age,
the odds of having
a viable pregnancy
drop significantly.
So it's not impossible,
but we really need
to gauge your priorities.
I have so many questions.
Okay, take your time.
If I have endometriosis,
what are my options?
If it's a mild case,
they often recommend
a surveillance approach.
Everything you say sounds
like Star Trek to me.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Basically, it means watch,
wait and see.
If it's a moderate case,
they recommend
endometrial ablation
or hormone injections.
If it's a severe case, it often
requires a hysterectomy.
I don't want to scare you,
but I really think
we should prepare ourselves for
the worst case scenario here.
- You're ruining
the class
for all of us.
Okay, okay.
Everybody, calm down.
-Calm down?
-It's Sadie's stupid fault
we don't have a venue
because she went
whining to Mommy.
- We don't know that.
- Yes, we do.
We called the venue like
we were potential customers.
There's nothing booked on those
days. It was completely free.
And then we realized,
"Oh, it's her mom."
Well, that's actually
pretty good detective work.
-You bitch!
-What? You're going to cry now?
-Okay, stop it.
-You ruined everything, Sadie.
- What the hell do you have against us?
-  -Hey!
What's with all the noise?
Everything stops this instant.
I don't think I can do
the show anywhere, Mr. Bea.
What? Daze, what's wrong?
How did the doctor go?
Are you kidding, Miss Bea?
You're our third
ace in the hole.
You really need to find
a different metaphor.
Until further notice, I'm out.
Eden, you take care
of everything.
Dad, you do it, or--
Kids, I don't care.
Miss Bea,
you can't give up on us.
I know that
it's been stressful--
-If she wants to go, let her go.
-Shut up, Sadie.
Okay, look,
it's been a long day, okay?
Just go home. Get some rest.
You were the only one
that made this fun, Miss Bea.
Please?
Whoever did that to her work...
...you're better than that.
Daze.
Daze, Daze.
Hold up a second.
Listen...
...I know you're going
through a lot right now,
I mean, with, with the kids,
uh, your mother, the, the show.
But, well, listen,
you can't just say,
"Hey, Eden, cover for me."
I mean, she's not
a registered sub.
I can get in some
serious trouble, you know?
I know, I'm sorry. It's just...
-We lost our venue and--
-W-- Wait, Wait.
-What? When did this happen?
-It doesn't matter.
I've called everywhere.
Everything's booked.
Okay. Okay.
Well-- So what?
I mean, you don't have to have
some fancy gallery, Daze.
I'm sure we'll find something.
It's art.
I mean, hell, you could hang it
from the trees
in the Garden District
or, or burn it
in a bonfire at Dubai.
-You could be very avant-garde.
-Dad.
All right. What about Jack?
-We could use his studio.
-No, Dad.
Whatever. Just don't let this
be an excuse to quit.
All right? Those kids
are counting on you.
So let's buck up,
figure this thing out
and finish what you started.
Dad, it's not just that.
Kiddo, what?
What-- Oh.
You should've
seen her today, Cammie.
She just seemed so defeated.
Well, she can
still freeze her eggs.
All is not lost.
You're not going to bring
that up again now, are you?
I'm just saying.
Let me give you
a little information.
Your daughter is doing
a fantastic job with those kids,
and I can't recall the last time
I've, I've seen her so excited
or lively about anything.
She's been happy.
Hell, the only time
I see her stressed or anxious
is when you're hounding her.
I mean, shouldn't, shouldn't
it be your goal as a mother
to see your daughter happy?
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
I'm going to support her.
Because our daughter
is doing something great.
And I couldn't be
more proud of her.
Hey, you've reached Jack.
Sorry I missed you.
You can leave me a message,
and I'll call you back.
Hey, Jack. Hi. It's Daisy. Um...
I know it's been a minute,
but I had something
I really need
to talk to you about.
Give me a call.
Uh, I hope you're well.
Okay.
We can do this. Yeah.
Oh, Jack. Hey, I'm,
I'm at the school right now,
but is there any way
that we could meet up
in, like, 30 minutes?
I have this huge favor
I need to a--
What?
This is...
Oh, my gosh, Jack.
Pretty wild, huh?
-You are so lucky to be here.
-I know. I know.
You know, Jack...
...you have a real
unorthodox sense of timing.
Why didn't you call me?
They're taking
good care of me here.
And, you know,
with your show coming up,
-I don't want to bother you.
-Hey, no.
Our show?
Yeah, but...
Look, Jack, I'm so sorry
about everything.
I know I've been
all over the place. And--
Daze, you doing okay?
No, no. Don't worry about me.
I do though.
I can't help but worry
about you, like, all the time.
Daisy...
...just talk to me.
I don't think
kids are happening.
But you getting
in the crash and...
...being here now
looking like this...
...maybe it's a sign
or something.
I don't know.
-Now you are talking crazy.
-Ah.
Maybe I am, but...
...I got two pieces
of horrible news today.
And the thought of losing you
was the worst one.
You know?
Does that make sense?
Well...
- ...I'm happy that my pain
can be a sign for you.
Oh, my gosh, I'm sorry.
I just realized
how that came off.
-I'm not--
-I'm kidding.
So what happens next?
Do you...
Wow, Jack, you look like shit.
Hey, language!
Sorry.
Are you okay?
I mean, your wounds kind of
suit you.
Oh, they do, huh?
Well, I mean, it's,
It's kind of badass.
Yes, I am fine.
Guys, thank you.
Thank you for all these gifts.
Yeah, uh, gift shop had, like,
the most basic options. So...
Yeah.
Well, it's the thought
that counts.
Absolutely.
So... how are you feeling?
The show's right around
the corner. Tell me everything.
You guys ready?
- What, did I say something?
- Well...
...we might have had,
like, a little, tiny hiccup.
We had a catastrophic hiccup.
We lost our venue.
What?
-How? Wait. What happened?
-Well...
-...it's complicated.
-It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
And the venue's
actually booked now.
I begged my mom, but there was
nothing she could do.
So why do you try
to sabotage us?
I don't know.
At first, I thought
it was a funny joke,
but then I was standing
in the room full of people
who hated me.
Whatever. Here.
-The gift shop had
the most basic options.
-Right?
Mm. I'm sorry, guys.
All is lost then...
Nothing's going to be available
on such short notice.
I'm sorry. You did your best.
Or you could use my place.
-Are you sure?
-Am I sure?
-Yeah. Are you kidding?
-Oh, my God.
I told you Jack
was our ace in the hole.
Oh, we're back on, huh?
Pretty close.
We're on.
I'm going to go to school,
do a, a big e-mail blast,
uh, print some flyers.
I'm so proud of you.
I don't expect you to help. I--
Let's talk hors d'oeuvres.
The bridge club gals are
ready to do the cooking.
So, is this a good time?
One HD projector for milady.
- Thank you, Stanley.
You are a lifesaver.
Yeah. So I, I can come over
and help you set it up.
Oh, that's okay.
August is, like, a whiz
of this kind of stuff,
-so...
-All right.
Oh, and one more thing.
About the other night, I
just want to let you know that,
-you know, I'm going through
a lot of stuff--
-Let me stop you right there.
You have nothing to worry about.
I'm a reformed man.
You sure?
Crystal.
Clear.
-What?
-See you at the show tonight.
Okay, I wouldn't miss it
for a software convention.
Good luck!
Bend. Nice. Go round.
Very nice, Sadie. And reach.
Reach, reach, reach, reach...
Hey, all! Come out
to the art show tonight.
We've been working really hard,
and we're just dying to see you.
Right, August?
We are dying. Yes.
Every single one of you
should be proud.
We did it.
Your work is so beautiful.
I'm so proud of you,
and I don't care
what happens tonight.
If we sell one painting...
I just want you to be proud.
Just be proud, okay?
All right, let's mingle.
Well, look who got creative.
-Helen!
-Hi.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Hoping to raise enough money
to convince you to come back.
Oh, no, my dear.
I could never do this.
This is you.
You and your team.
Your passion.
Your purpose, Daisy.
I'm just an old crone.
Oh, stop!
Miss Bonneville!
- Hi! Hey!
-We have to show you our stuff.
-Oh, I'd love to see it.
-Thank you for coming.
-Well done to you.
Daisy, what a turnout!
I can't believe this. Look.
Those are the principals
from some of the Magnet Schools.
-Oh, that's amazing.
-You did that.
-Aw.
It's so, uh...
...poetic.
I choreographed it.
Oh, did you now?
Of course.
Yeah, you did.
-Mm.
-Hey, guys.
Oh, hey, Daisy.
We're having a great time.
This is awesome.
Cool.
- You looked so good.
- Oh, thank you.
He looks like trouble.
You want me to get rid of him?
Look at you.
Ouch. Yeah.
You saved us. Thank you.
Daisy, I gave you a key.
Hey, Miss Bea,
I think we should do it.
Yeah, like, right now.
You ready?
We're not done yet.
Bring it on.
Everybody, quiet down.
Thank you. Come this way.
I want to thank you all
for coming out for the inaugural
West High School Art gala
hosted by none other
than Jack Palmer.
The students' final piece
is called We're not done yet.
It was created by
the entire art class as a unit,
cobbled together
from things forgotten.
We hope you get it.
With your support, we would love
to add more creative minds.
But even without it,
well, we'll find a way.
So, uh, no pressure.
Wait, wait.
We need to thank our mentors.
Mr. Palmer, thank you
for letting us use your studio,
and of course, for
your knowledge behind the lens.
Ah. Give me a bump. Phew.
And a big thanks to Miss Eden
for your free-flowing spirit.
Aw!
Thank you.
But of course, of course,
-the biggest thanks of all
has to go to...
-Miss Bea.
Thank you for believing in us.
And never giving up on us.
We don't know what
we would've done without you.
Thanks, guys.
Come on.
Oh!
-Drive safe.
-Of course.
And no texting.
Hey, Jack, are we still on
for tomorrow?
Yeah. Four o'clock.
Bring that Pentax.
Yeah.
Aw, thanks so much
for coming, guys.
-It was fun, Miss Bea.
-Oh, good.
Yeah. Your new place is awesome.
Oh, thanks.
Bye.
Wow.
Stragglers, am I right?
Come on.
Bye, guys.
-Happy birthday!
-Bye.
-Do you want to sit?
-Oh, sure.
Yeah.
Careful.
Feeling okay? You need anything?
I'm good.
A little sore,
but I'm on the up and up.
Hmm.
Well, first birthday party
in the new house. Check.
- First glass of wine on the front steps.
-Check!
What else is on the docket?
I got a few little things.
Practice exam,
-certification.
-Wait.
Are you telling me that
you're not yet a legal teacher?
More art shows...
...probably a bunch of
teenage angst before summer.
So much to do.
So little time.
We have plenty of time.
But there is one thing
that can't wait.
Oh, yeah?
We've got to get on those weeds
in the back.
- No!
- Yes.
No. No way.
Can we just ask
your mom to do that?
No. She'll tell us
to get a new yard.
Ugh.
I miss the loft life.
Cheers to pulling weeds.
No.
How about...
...here is to...
...our new little normal.
So long as you're happy
with that, Daze.