Remember me.
I live within you
in absolute stillness
waiting.
Have you forgotten?
Have you placed me
outside of yourself?
Far beyond your reach?
I am here
within you.
Close as breath.
I always have been.
I always will be.
Find me.
You are me.
We have descended from realms
beyond our human memory.
Our birthright is to return.
The truth of who we are
lives deep within us
In absolute stillness
waiting for us to respond
to the calling
of a deeper memory.
The journey of awakening
to our own eternal adventure
begins
with the Birth
of Innocence.
There is only life
and life is forever.
An ever expanding,
dynamic continuum
always in a state of change.
Life is a force
imbued with love.
Its natural momentum is joy.
Moving through everything
everyone
everywhere
in both seen and unseen aspects
of all creation.
Nature moves in rhythm
with this force.
Alive with power.
Alive with change.
Alive in stillness.
Nature's power
is in its stillness.
Our power
is in our stillness.
In our stillness
we dream.
We form a vision of our desire.
We enact our will through focus.
Our own creative power
infusing our dream with life.
Nature reminds us
to create our dream
with passion and purpose.
To give ourselves
wholeheartedly
until our experience
of our dream
becomes our life.
We are free to change.
Free to experience
new unknowns
new dreams
new life.
Sowing our dreams like seeds,
we gain experience.
We harvest wisdom.
Moving in rhythm
with our own life force
we experience the potency
of cycles.
We experience our own joy.
When trusting our nature
to dream
to experience
to gain wisdom and move on
we are in harmony with life.
Our love for life grows greater
and greater
inspiring us
to become one with life.
To dream bold
and outrageous dreams.
We dissolve everything we are
everything we have known.
A death without dying.
A birth into a whole new being.
A genetic leap
into the vast unknown.
In choosing to make this dream
our reality
we ride the mystery
of our own deep stillness.
There is only life
and life is forever.
Our gateway to forever
lives deep within us
in absolute stillness
waiting.
Have we forgotten?
You do?
No, I don't, but she wanted
the tomatoes, so I was very
nice to trade
-Oh, alright--
-Thank you
'Cause I'm not doing
any of it.
-You were nice--
-You're not?-
No.
Lord of the Rings is so bad.
No it's not!
It is! It's so bad!
I've never seen it.
You have to see it!
Okay, the only thing I got
an A+ in was culinary arts.
You're gonna love it!
For as long as I can remember
we have allowed ourselves
to be planted in rows.
For as long as I can remember
we have allowed ourselves
to be buried in rows.
Have we forgotten how to live?
As our memory fades,
our deepest dreams
can become buried within us.
We begin looking
outside of ourself
for life
for inspiration
for love.
What was dreamed to be
a life of exploration
becomes a life of repetition.
We learn to comply
while we wonder
mostly in secret
what happened to our joy?
Greater realities surround us
but we can't see them.
We can't feel them.
We become closed to them.
We stop listening.
We grow arrogant
in our forgetfulness
insisting we know how to live.
Insisting that
what we know
is all there is to know.
Without great dreams
we cannot change.
Without change
we are out of rhythm
with our life.
At odds with our nature,
we grow tired and resentful.
Cut off from our innocence,
our inner life
becomes hardship,
and our outer life confirms it.
We develop a constant need
to be built up
to be stimulated.
I love you!
Thank you!
You're perfect!
To feed the many appetites
that make us feel alive.
But the rush of emotions
dies in a moment,
and then we just need more.
Our human life
becomes our life
without thought
of the greater life
that even now sustains us.
We may remember exactly
when we gave up
on our innocence.
When the world around us
overwhelmed our trust
that who we are is enough.
Seeding doubt
that our dream must not be real.
But where can we go
without that dream to guide us?
We try to find some way
to orient ourselves.
But no matter where we search
no matter what we do
we feel a deeper longing
that is rarely answered
that nothing outside us
can answer.
When do we go back in to listen?
When do we become still enough
to hear our own calling?
We can become so lost
that we forget
even what we have lost.
Our innocence
seems like another being
a childish fantasy
impossible to find.
To remember our dream
we may have to walk
back through a past
we have tried very hard to bury.
Separated from our own source
from our own love
we wither and die
while life waits
right inside us.
It can take a great pain
to wake us up
a death to what we thought
our life was all about.
In that emptiness
through that crack
from a darkness
we tried everything to avoid
our deeper memory
begins to stir.
I am always close.
Always waiting.
Always offering another chance
no matter what you have done
with every other chance.
I will not leave you
because
I am you.
This deeper memory
takes root
and begins to grow.
The more it grows
the more I trust it's power.
Quietly I realize
this power is me.
Reminders are everywhere
that there is so much
more to life
than what I have been living!
And now this unknown
is all I want to know.
This new life growing within me
is all I want to tend to.
We have given ourselves
this opportunity
to bring forth
everything we are
to love everything we are
to transform ourselves
into greater and greater
expressions of life.
We don't know how to do this.
Our Innocence does.
We don't believe it is possible.
Our Innocence knows it is.
We have that seed
within us
reaching up for light
down for rich soil
to create itself
to make it's dream known.
Look at our bodies:
Every finger matters in our grip
and in our touch.
Every cell has a purpose.
Every fluid carries something
we cannot live without.
Every organ beats or hums
in infinite complexity
giving us the
staggering opportunity
of life.
We are born remembering.
And this memory
is always with us.
In this Innocence
we embrace life
actively seeking out experiences
and living them richly
into wisdom.
Each bold step
makes the next step bolder.
Every adventure into the unknown
creates more trust
for grander adventures.
I am the creator of my life
through the power
of my own thought.
Through the potency
of my own dreams
my life takes shape and form.
I have created what my life is.
I am now creating
what it will become.
Our own
endless
ever-evolving creation
into the vast unknown.
The eternal womb of space
waiting
for new dreams
to be conceived
for new life to be created
for new realms
to be experienced.
Patiently waiting.
Waiting
for you
to remember.
Find me.
♪ Suspended on
♪ the edge of time ♪
♪ remembering
who we are. ♪
♪ A blue green planet
spins and turns ♪
♪ around a burning star. ♪
♪ Across the silent ♪
♪ galaxies ♪
♪ the universe ♪
♪ unfolds. ♪
♪ This great ship sails ♪
♪ the seas of space ♪
♪ toward the vast ♪
♪ unknown. ♪
♪ Companion travellers
all are we ♪
♪ whether stranger
foe or friend. ♪
♪ Evolving through
these births and deaths ♪
♪ a spiral without end. ♪
♪ Sharing joy and sorrow ♪
♪ our laughter and our fears. ♪
♪ We're learning
in this school ♪
♪ of life ♪
♪ together through the years. ♪
♪ The universe ♪
♪ within our hearts ♪
♪ embraces all that live. ♪
♪ True rest we find
and peace of mind ♪
♪ are all we have to give. ♪
♪ Our place is here ♪
♪ our time is now ♪
♪ sunrise to sunset. ♪
♪ The beauty of ♪
♪ these days we share ♪
♪ I never will ♪
♪ forget. ♪