[ HEAVY BREATHING ]
[ EXPLOSIONS; GUNFIRE ]
[ GASP ]
[ METALLIC SOUNDS OF
ZORDS FIGHTING ]
When two empires
declare war...
neither side is innocent.
You're still a traitor,
you worthless piece of...
We were children,
asked to fight
an intergalactic war against
an enemy we'd never met.
Let's stop pretending OUR side
stood on some moral high ground.
What do you want, Rocky?
Where's Tommy?
[ SIRENS BLARE ]
[ RAT SQUEAKS; BOTTLE CLANKS ]
[ AIRSHIP WOOSHING OVERHEAD ]
[ BEEPING SOUNDS; MECH FOOT STOMPING ]
[ HIGH-PITCHED SCANNING SOUND ]
Tommy Oliver is a ghost.
You'll never find him.
I don't even know where he...
[ FACE PUNCH; METAL CHAINS CLANK ]
Bullshit is an ugly color
on you.
I prefer pink.
If dying is what you choose
to do here today...
I would prefer you did it
with your dignity intact.
How soon after the truce did
you turn?
Did you even wait until
we were disbanded?
The second the Machine Empire
integrated their technology
into our society, I knew the freedom
we'd bled for was done.
So you stabbed us
in the back?
I followed the only rule worth
following in this fuck storm:
I made sure I was on
the winning side.
Which is why I'm sitting here
and you're chained to a chair.
Comfortable?
You were never really
one of us.
Thank you.
Who'd've thought that weaponizing
youth
and training them to kill could
have turned out so ugly
for so many of them?
We were a team.
We fought for each other.
You never understood that.
Let's talk about Jason.
What about him?
You were married to him,
weren't you?
For eight hours.
[ LOUD KNOCK ]
[ GUNFIRE ]
NOOOOOOOOOO!
D'you know why they did it?
Bulk: Got a little tired of being
made fun of by you cunt fucks.
[ SKULL LAUGHS ]
Bulk! Skull! You sold us out!
[ GUN BUTT THUD ]
Machine Empire
had better meth.
That was all it took.
You know what happens to a dog
that chases cars
and finally catches one?
[ LIGHTS BUZZ ]
It doesn't end well
for the dog.
Let's move on to Zack,
shall we?
Good kid. Fit.
Little hyperactive.
D'you know where he ended up?
About those Hip Hop
Kido tapes...
Zack: Hip Hop Kido! Let's kido.
And Abs! Abs!
Light 'em up.
Knee 'em up! Work it!
Count it! & punch! Work it!
Hip Hop Kido! Let's go!
[ PUNCHING ]
He knew it was bullshit,
but the public ate it up.
It wasn't about
the money for him. He's...
... addicted to the action.
That was his outlet.
And you think peddling
false hope to fat kids
was enough to scratch that itch
for him?
Did you know he joined
the Machine Empire?
Didn't even have to recruit him.
He was so hungry
for a battlefield,
he volunteered to help us sweep up
whatever resistance was left.
[ GLASS SMASHING; GUNS COCKING ]
If you hand over the general,
all your lives will be spared.
If you don't, well...
I know YOU.
You're that black man
with the exercise program.
Is this some kind of joke?
Damn.
And I know you motherfuckers
bootlegged my shit too.
You have a nice body!
Kill him!
Oh! Do you have any
last words?
It's morphin' time.
[ THUD ]
[ CRASH ]
[ GUNFIRE; COMBAT SOUNDS ]
[ KNIVE SLASHING SOUND ]
[ KNIFE COMBAT SOUNDS ]
Most people play the odds.
But then there are those rare
few who just don't feel alive
unless the odds are stacked
completely against them.
I knew you'd get me.
It's all good.
Get on with it.
It’s tough seeing your
friends murdered, one by one...
... especially by one
of your own.
What the fuck are you
talking about?
Think about it.
Rita made Tommy to fight against us.
And then he betrayed her, switched sides,
mommy tried to kill him, then he lost
his power, gained it back, lost it again,
only to see a fucking treaty
signed? I'm...
... I'm glad I'm not his shrink.
Say what you want
about the Machines:
at least they're consistent.
What does this have to do
with me?
Tommy's always been
hung up on you.
[ DOOR WOOSHING OPEN ]
Yesterday Tommy paid a visit
to Billy Cranston.
But don't worry, I think
we all know it's unlikely
you fucked him too.
Our alliance with the
Machine Empire
will bring a new level of synergy
within Cranston-Lockheed Martin.
We will be mass producing our
signature Blade Blaster weapons
with an initial order of 1.6
trillion euros
from the Soviet Europe.
Damn it, Billy.
What d'you do?
You're out of your mind!
Tommy didn't kill any of us.
He's a Ranger.
You just forgot what that means.
Why do you think they gave
these powers to kids? Hmmmmm?
Because we were the only ones
who could destroy Rita and her-
You are NOT that stupid!
For fuck's sake! Pull your shit
together and start thinking, for yourself.
For once in your life!
You're not a little girl any more.
Now where's Tommy?
Go fuck yourself.
[ MACHINE NOISES ]
[ CHAIR SCRAPING ]
You think you're defending
something worthwhile.
I get that.
But technology?
The Machines?
They always win.
I told you, I haven't seen
Tommy since-
[ SUDDEN YELP OF PAIN; CRACKING SOUNDS ]
One last warning.
Every move we make
leaves a footprint.
Trini's funeral.
While the government
was negotiating the treaty,
we were burying our own.
I saw him for a moment,
and then he was gone.
It's been years.
You're telling the truth.
The Machines are never wrong.
They told us exactly
what you'd know.
So, you lose.
Oh Kimmy: you really just
don't get it, do you?
We never needed you
as a witness.
You, my dear, are bait.
[ GUNFIRE; SWORD COMBAT SOUNDS ]
[ METALLIC SWORD UNFOLDING SOUND ]
[ SWORD CLANG ]
[ MACHINE NOISES; SWORD SCRAPING ]
[ SWORD COMBAT SOUNDS ]
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ HEAVY BREATHING ]
Who are you?
I'm Kimberly.
No. You're not.
I held Kimberly in my arms
when she died.
So I'm going to ask you
one more time.
WHO ARE YOU?!
[ CHAINS BREAKING ]
[ SKIN CRACKING ]
Kill.
Stab.
Drown.
Sleep.
Shoot.
Don't you remember me darling?
I'm the one who turned you a
Ranger in the first place.
I've killed them all
and now the world is ours.
[ SCREAM ]
Rita...
[ SCREAMS ]