- You the new girl?
- Yes. Hi.
- Okay, well, I've been
out front looking for you
for the past 15 minutes.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I, they told me to wait here.
- All right, come on.
I wanna get to the lanes
before they run outta half price
wings.
Supplies are in here.
We run low on anything,
you write it down on this
clipboard.
Got it?
Your shirt should be over there.
What'd you say your name was?
- Um, Karen.
- My ex-wife's name was Karen.
- I'm sorry.
Hey, Tina.
Is everything okay? How is she
feeling?
She threw it up again?
I was really hoping she'd
keep something down.
Um...
Maybe next time try
again with some crackers.
Uh, just try that and
yes, please clean it up.
Thank you again for staying with
her.
I've gotta go.
- Is that gonna be a problem?
- No, no. I'm sorry.
I've got a sick little one at
home.
My neighbor's with her and she
has kids
but she acts like she's
never seen a sick one before.
- The boss man doesn't take too
kindly
to personal business on his
dime,
so don't have that out anymore.
- Got it.
- Have you worked in a
place like this before?
- No, sir.
- You can see it's dirty.
Floors need to be swept each
night.
Bathrooms.
Clean 'em, mop 'em, refill
the soap, paper towels, TP.
Empty the trash from each
office.
Vacuum each office and hallway.
Close all the doors.
Make sure they're locked.
We had a break in at a plant
down the road the other night.
We don't want that here.
Why don't you go get these.
Also, no smoking inside.
- I don't smoke.
- You will if you stay here long
enough.
You married?
- Why?
- Just asking.
You said you had a kid and all.
- No, I'm not.
- This one's a little tricky.
You really gotta work it.
Oh, I hate this door.
- I think you got something on,
um-
- Ah, dammit.
- Wait, wait.
Don't, don't rub it in.
Hold on.
Give me your shirt.
I have an old injury.
Can you open this?
- What the hell?
Where did you learn that from?
- School. Good old family
and consumer sciences class.
- Sounds made up.
- Oh, it's real, all right.
- Don't think by knowing this
fancy stuff
you're gonna be getting my job
or nothin'.
- Don't we have the same job?
- No, I'm day shift.
- There you go.
- Not bad, Kathy.
- It's Karen.
Like your ex-wife.
- Yeah, right.
Well, I'm off.
Any last questions?
- Does anybody else work night
shift?
- Nope. Just you.
I, uh, hope your kid
gets to feeling better.
- Thank you.
- Well look at this shit.
- Mm-mm-mm.
Fresh meat.
- Nah, this is Danny's old lady.
- No shit?
- Or ex old lady, guess I should
say.
Ain't that right?
Whoa, careful. Don't
wanna burn yourself now.
You know she served him divorce
papers
right there at the construction
site.
In front of his foreman and
everybody.
- You don't know me.
- I know anyone gonna deny a man
from seeing his little
girl on her birthday
is a fuckin' bitch.
- Come on, man.
- You missed a spot.
- Shit.
Oh, it's nasty.
Hey, Tina.
- I know you said not to
call,
but your kid is crying and
I can't get her to stop.
- Is she okay?
- I don't know.
She's going on about her
dad's gone, you're gone.
I told her you're just at
work, but she won't listen.
You want me to say what
happened to her dad?
- No, no, don't say anything.
Just...
- What do I need to do?
- Okay, um, let me talk to her.
- Mom?
- Hey baby.
What's the matter? Are you okay?
- Where are you?
- I'm at work.
Remember I told you I
was going to be working
while you're asleep?
- No.
- Yes, you do.
That's why Miss Tina's there to
watch you.
- Are you coming back?
- Yes, of course I am.
I'll be there when you wake up.
I promise.
And then we'll make breakfast.
Okay?
- Eggs Benedict?
- No, maybe pancakes.
- Okay.
- Okay, baby.
I love you.
- Love you, too.
- Can you give the
phone back to Miss Tina?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- I'm sorry about that.
I think she'll be all right.
How's her fever?
- I dunno.
- Well, will you take her
temperature?
- Pretty sure it's gone.
She don't feel hot.
- Will you just take it with a
thermometer
and text me back and let me
know?
- Fine.
I'll do it in a minute
when things settle down.
- What things?
- Well, this dog out
here is barking like crazy.
Shut up dog!
Ugh.
Oh, and the land lady stopped
by.
Said you still owed for this
week.
- I know. I'm taking care of
that.
- I saw you got
a lot of bills here.
Are you gonna be able to pay me?
- Yes.
Now will you take her
temperature
and stop going through my mail?
- Fine.
- Hey, thank you again for
watching her.
I really do appreciate-
Hm.
- Hello?
- Delivery.
- Can you leave it by the door?
- I need a signature for it.
Sorry I'm running late.
The truck got a flat.
They put a rush on this, so
I figured it's important.
Machine part, I'm guessing.
Is Frank here?
- No.
- What about Wayne?
- Nope.
- Anyone besides you?
- No.
Uh, well, well, there's the
people in the back, but-
- Take care.
- Do I need to sign for this?
- No, you're good.
Hey.
- Oh, shit.
Fuck.
- Now find her.
- See
anything?
- No.
Check back here.
Guys, this way.
- Shit.
- Ow!
- Dammit!
- Here, here's here
phone.
- Fuck.
- Spread out.
Hey, go find every phone.
Start cuttin' the lines.
- Piece of shit.
Ugh, this fuckin' place.
- Hey, go
check on the breaker box.
I don't think it's the one down
here.
- Hey, I might
have something over here.
- You sure in
the clear?
Anybody check that closet right
there?
- The
longer you drag this out,
the more we're gonna
make you bleed, bitch.
- Fuckin'
bitch.
Don't go runnin' little piggy.
Your ass is mine now.
Fuckin' hell.
I see you.
You ain't gettin' away.
- Fuck.
- Bitch!
Come here, you slippery little
bitch.
Fuck!
You ain't gettin' away!
Come here!
Oh, shit!
- Piece of shit.
- Hey, hey, hey!
No, Eddie.
- Take the note.
- No Eddie, hey.
- Come on, go.
- What happened?
- Just leave.
He's fuckin' dead, man.
- Listen.
- Shit.
- Yeah, I
hear it.
- Over there.
Go, come on.
You're in a shit ton
of trouble now, bitch.
She's over here. I can smell
her.
Mm, I smell her, too.
Smells like trash.
Dirty, dirty trash.
Dirty...
Dirty girl.
Ain't no use hidin'.
Come on out.
Come out, dirty girl!
We know you're up here.
Come out, dirty girl.
Check that aisle over there.
I got this one.
Hey!
Get your ass back here.
She's over here.
She's running!
Don't let her get away!
- Yeah, I see her.
- She's getting
away, go!
Get her!
Hey, where'd she go?
- She's
hidin'.
Somewhere close.
- She can't get out.
The phone lines are cut and
the doors are chained shut.
Vic is keeping watch outside.
She's stuck in here.
Let's find her.
- Think.
Think.
- Hey.
- Give me those.
- Fuck.
- Hey Bobby, right here.
Right here.
- Hey sweetheart.
Come here!
Open the fuckin' door.
- Shit.
Shit.
- Fucker.
- Shit.
Oh, fuck.
- I
seen 'em come down this way.
Bi-itch!
Come out, come out, bitch!
- I
heard somethin' up here.
- Shit.
What the fuck is this?
- Hey, you find
anything?
What is that?
- Look at
this.
- Shit, that's
Bobby's iron.
- Is this
his blood?
- Check the
closets.
She's not fuckin' in here.
- Is she in
here?
- She's
close.
Maybe she doubled back around.
Anyone check the rough mill?
Bobby.
That fuck. Where the hell is he?
You think she got him?
That's a lot of fuckin' blood
over there.
Hey Vic, get down here.
Take the keys and go
check all the offices.
Thoroughly.
- I'm on it.
- Go head
down to the rough mill.
See if Bobby's still down there.
When I find this bitch,
I'm gon' slit her fuckin'
throat.
- It's too fucking long.
- Oh!
Come here!
- Got ya!
Oh, we gonna play now.
Get up!
We gonna play real nice.
That's right.
Open up your mouth. Open up.
- What? No.
No, no, no, no.
No.
- Karen!
Come here.
- Shit.
- Why'd you do this?
Danny. I know it's you.
Answer me.
You won't get Lily
- Too late.
Did you really think I
was gonna let you leave
and take my little girl from me?
Get used to it.
I'm gonna knock every single
tooth outta your fuckin' head.
This is what happens
when you try to pull
some bullshit like this.
You're not smart enough, Karen.
Look at me.
Look at me!
You're so fucking stupid.
Don't pick that up.
You pick it up and I will
break your fucking hand again.
Come here.
You never fucking listen.
- No.
- This is why
you are such a fuck up.
Give me the other hand.
- No.
- Karen, you gonna listen this
time?
Give it to me.
- Please, Danny stop.
No, please.
No, stop.
Danny, please, stop.
No.
Danny, please.
- You turned on me.
I gave you everything
and you turned on me.
- Mommy?
- Lily?
Mommy?
- Lily.
- Goddammit, I told
you to stay in the car.
- Lily!
- Mommy!
No.
No!
- Lily!
- Mommy!
No!
Let me out of here!
Mommy!
- Karen.
Stop acting like you're smart.
Get out here and I'll make it
quick,
like I did that stupid bitch
you left my little girl with.
Fuck.
Karen!
- Mommy!
Mom!
No!
Mommy!
- Fucking die already.
Fucking die.
- Take that mask off.
Take it off!
- Okay, please.
I'm sorry.
Please.
- Get used to it.
I'm gonna knock every one of
your teeth
outta your fuckin' head!
- Mommy!
- Lily.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
You're okay.
Everything is okay.