I'll take caller number seven right now.
Oh, man, this is caller seven!
- Huh?
- I'm caller seven, right?
You're caller number seven.
Who is this?
This is Butcher Duke!
Do I get to play for the home or what?
I mean, Kathy and I
have been dreaming about this
ever since we first saw 'em
drive by on the highway, you know?
Now, if you beat Creek Thompson
two out of three games,
you win a manufactured home.
You bet I do!
It's so funny 'cause people say
these are tornado magnets,
you know, these manufactured houses,
and I say, "No, they're not.
They're not tornado magnets."
It's not like tornado's like,
"Ooh, ooh, manufactured house."
You know, what I tell people
is, "Look, if God wants ya,
he's gonna take ya."
I think this is God's way of showing me.
You know, "This is it, Butch.
You can do it."
I tell ya, I mean, of course,
I'm human, I have some doubts.
Butcher had a chance to win at state
and he lost the first round.
I'm content where I am, I'm happy,
but I know if I can win this home,
man, it'll make things better.
Game end match, Mr. Thompson.
Not only did Butcher lose
a double-wide mobile home that day,
he also lost a big piece
of his warrior heart.
Some say he's never been the same since.
All right, guys, so why are we here?
- To have fun!
- Why is that?
Because we're not very good.
Not very good.
We had a tough year last year,
didn't we, Knox?
- Yeah.
- We didn't win a match.
But guess what.
That was okay with me.
I had a great time with you guys.
I feel closer to you.
I mean, really,
I'd call you my best friends
if that wasn't a little weird.
I've got goals for the team,
but I need to know what your goals are.
Okay, Faith, what do we got?
I really want to learn
a between-a-leg shot.
That's my favorite shot,
we're gonna work on that.
Kaylee, what do we got?
I want to be able to serve straight.
Yeah, I don't think
you got a serve in last year.
Knox, what do you got,
what's your goal this year?
To not cry.
- How about you, Jack?
- I want a girlfriend.
Me too.
So, we got a match on Friday,
and I decided to go to the east side
to pick up some new blood.
Make him feel welcome.
John.
Tell us a little bit about yourself, bud.
I want to get better at self-expression,
lyrical poetry, and dance, mainly.
Well, piggy-backing off of John,
I'm in anger management.
And you all know I needed it.
You know, I used to throw my racket.
Sorry about that, Knox.
I still can't drive or vote
or go roller skating.
But guess what, I can coach tennis.
And this year, we're gonna win a match,
and I think it starts Friday
at Ramsey, right?
- Yeah!
- Okay, who's gonna have
a forehand this year?
- That's right. Forehand.
- Forehand.
- Backhand.
- Volley.
- Lob.
And between-the-legs overhead spin shot.
Start again!
I hope you're enjoying
the Saturday afternoon movie,
Over the Top, with Sly Stallone,
but I'll be quick.
We have two bedrooms, three bedrooms,
four bedrooms, five bedrooms,
all the way up to two or three bedrooms.
But, listen, believe me today.
Come on down after the movie.
I want to serve you quality today!
- That was your dad.
- And he looked good.
We looked at the numbers,
okay, and a big reason
for your dad's success
was his commercial campaigns,
so we were thinking...
- Hire an actor.
- Why not do it with you?
It's not easy being the son
of an ex-tennis pro mobile home mogul,
but with his daddy
evading taxes in South Vietnam,
Delta's doing the best he can.
- Oh.
- You are the one
who's sitting in the executive chair, okay?
And you could really change this.
I'm flattered, ladies, I really am,
but, you know, I just...
You're young and exciting.
And think about it, with tiny homes,
our audience is young people anyway.
So what type of commercial are we thinking?
Oh, a good one.
I like that.
- Hey, Don?
- Yeah, boss.
Could you get us a camera?
We're shooting a commercial.
That sounds like a good idea.
Yeah, all right, I got to go.
I'll teach you later.
Bye, guys! See you tomorrow.
See you, Butch.
- What's up, Gordy?
- Hey, Butch.
Uh, where are we going?
- I need a protein shake.
- Protein shake.
Yeah, yeah, get in, let's go.
The tag, and here comes
the man formerly known
as Will Lockhart, now under the spell...
Oh, I'm hungry, Mom.
Well, there's things in the fridge.
Help yourself.
What?
Oh my gosh, Emily is getting married?
Who's Ellis?
Dadgummit, why didn't you tell me this?
I thought you and Emily were gonna talk.
You know we haven't talked in forever, Mom.
Gosh, look at this guy.
He kind of looks like me.
Oh, hey, did you finish
your side of the guest list
for... so we can start
sending out invitations?
Uh, yeah, I've got,
like, an idea in my head.
Um, I know I want to invite my Uncle Greg
and that side of the family
like my cousins.
Yeah, are they... they're driving in?
- Yeah, driving in.
- Oh, that's great.
I'm so glad they can make it.
I know.
And, then, obviously my paintball team.
Um, how many is that?
Um...
I think it's 20, about.
- Twenty? Twenty people?
- Can we maybe just invite,
like, half of the paintball team?
I guess we could invite
just, like, the Raptors,
- but I mean...
- Okay, who's on the Raptors?
Tyler, Matt, Ben, Reggie,
the one with the glass eye.
There's Jim, there's Chris, there's Danny.
And that's just the defense.
So the offense is Tim, Brad, Matt, Carter.
If I invite Carter, I have to invite Marcus
'cause he's, you know.
Felony Marcus?
- What?
- Felony Marcus?
Don't bring up the felony again.
It's always the felony with Marcus,
the felony this, the felony that.
They're my paintball team, babe!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to raise my voice.
I'm just so stressed out.
Babe, you don't need to be stressed.
- Why are you stressing?
- I can't help it.
There's a lot of expenditures
happening right now,
and I'm kind of balling on a budget,
and my couponing can only go so far.
And I don't mean to be mean,
but your family
is not really able to help out, and...
Gosh, is your dad even gonna be there?
Looks like Ellis is about to open
a can of daddy issues.
Can we just... can we just focus
on the logistical stuff right now?
Okay.
- So, catering...
- Got it covered.
Mom's got the gumbo
and all the broth premade,
so we just got to heat it up
on the day of the wedding.
Sorry, the broth?
Yeah, I thought we talked about this.
The broth from Thanksgiving?
I was kind of thinking
we could do something
a little nicer for the dinner.
Nicer than chicken broth, babe?
Oh, my arm is hurting.
I'm having a heart attack.
I don't know, guys.
I can't do this.
Let's just hire an actor.
Delta, look at me, look at Jennifer.
Look at me.
Say, "I'm Delta Thompson."
- I'm Delta Thompson.
- Say it again.
- I'm Delta Thompson?
- With force.
- I'm Delta Thompson.
- One more time!
I'm Delta Thompson!
Are you having a good day?
I know I am!
Are you tired of living
in the dump you're living in?
Well, not to fear
because we've got the solution for you!
That's right!
And by the way,
we have 0% APR financing,
and I know what that means!
We've got homes with one bathroom...
- Two bedrooms!
Oh, no!
It looks like it broke!
But guess what.
We want to give you homes today.
That's gonna be a thousand dollars.
- You said $15 an hour.
- Mm, thousand dollars.
I'm gonna need that right now.
Ladies, you know I'm not good with numbers.
It's an extra 15 for
the two wings you broke too.
You broke that.
I'm not God, I didn't create the wind.
All right, let's see your grunts.
Everybody's got to have a grunt.
Serena, John McEnroe, Connors, Borg,
Dominique Ravicii.
Okay, Djokovic, Murray.
- Should I name more?
- No.
Okay, all right, here we go.
Oh, that was awesome!
Let's go. Here we go, John.
Whoa, let's go, here we go, Jack.
Okay, doesn't mean
you have to hit the ball hard
'cause you didn't even touch the ball.
So, Kaylee, don't tell
the rest of the kids this,
but you're probably my favorite student.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
I said probably, not yet.
I haven't made up my mind, but...
- Okay.
- It's between you and Knox,
Faith, and Jack, so...
- Okay.
- Oh, look who's here.
That's your dad.
- Hey, Brad.
- How are you doing, Butch?
You got it.
Bye.
Man, I don't know, Gordy.
I've... I've thought about calling her,
I've thought about,
you know, going to her work,
try to catch her coming out.
I don't know where she lives now,
but maybe I could figure that out.
It's hard, man.
Whose house is this?
You know whose it is.
We're at your estranged daughter's house.
All right, here it goes.
Emily?
- Did you hear that?
- Emily?
Hello?
There you are.
- Dad.
- Gosh.
Hey. Butcher Duke.
Sir, Ellis Perkins.
It is so nice to meet you.
Hey, Emily.
- You look good.
- Thanks. You too.
Uh, what are you... what are you doing here?
Well, I heard my daughter
was getting married.
I thought I'd come by
and say congratulations.
- That's exciting.
- Yeah.
Thank you, it means a lot.
Things are... things are going well?
You still working at the hospital?
Yeah, yeah, I guess I've been working there
for about a year, so...
- It's going well?
- Yeah, I love it. It's great.
You still playing tennis?
Uh, no.
I didn't know you played tennis.
- She's good.
- Played in like middle school.
State runner-up.
Em, I just...
I just want to say, um,
I know I wasn't the best father,
but I'm different,
and I just want to let you know
that I care about you.
I just wanted to tell you that
and, I don't know, you're getting married
and I'd just, uh,
I'd just like to be
a part of it if I could.
- Okay.
- Is anybody
walking you down the aisle?
Uh, yeah, so I think
I'm probably just gonna
walk myself down the aisle.
Just keep it simple.
Okay.
Okay, well, um...
Well, gosh, it's good to meet you, Ellis.
The pleasure is mine, sir.
Truly.
And, Emily, I'll see you around, okay?
All right, bye, guys.
Bye.
Look, all I'm saying is,
I think it's pretty cool
that your dad came by.
I think so too. I think it was
really a big step for him,
but I am not there yet, so...
Okay.
I mean, what did he do
that was so terrible?
Um, I'll show you.
Golly! Emily!
- Dad!
- What?
Stop, please!
Your daughter is cheating.
Emily!
Stop!
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah.
Dad, you're embarrassing me.
Get a ride home!
Stop, you're embarrassing me.
What did you say?
Wow he... he knows how to throw a punch.
Mm.
Your kid's a cheater, man!
- Dad!
- What?
Stop, please!
Get a ride home.
Get a ride home!
Hey, that's my daughter.
Agh!
- Emily!
- Dad, stop.
What'd you say, mofo?
Golly! Emily!
Come on, dear.
We've been shooting like 60%
for free throws.
It's ridiculous.
Thirty or forty feet from the basket.
No way.
Watch this, if they score here,
I swear I'm gonna throw this remote.
- Momma, I'll throw it.
- Do not throw my remote.
I'll buy you a new one.
I don't even smoke, but I want to start.
Well, to cheer you up, look what I found
in the attic last night.
Oh my goodness.
Look at that.
- Little Butcher.
- Little me.
- Aww.
- Yeah, and...
- Tennis rackets.
- Yeah.
- What?
- And I need you to move out.
- I need you to move out.
Why?
You've been here ten years.
Yeah?
And because Jan is wanting a place to stay.
I can share a room with Jan, Mom.
Jan would not go for that.
You don't know that.
Well, how long are you gonna give me?
Nine days.
Nine days?
- Nine days?
- Nine days.
Sometimes life is hard, buddy.
Even your mom will punch you in the gut
every once in a while.
Jump over him, nice.
Oh, that'll do it.
- Hey!
- Hey, ladies. How's it going?
Hey, uh, we just thought we'd come
and talk a little bit,
talk a little bit about the day.
Okay, yeah.
How's the morning going?
We're out of money.
Okay. Uh, what do you mean?
The houses aren't selling.
Right, but, ladies, in English,
what do you mean?
So we need to sell more and get more money
or this business is over.
Listen to me.
My daddy always used to say,
"Don't ever sell the business.
Even if you have to fire
your best employees,
even if you have to fire
Jennifer and Kelly,
don't sell the business."
I mean, word for word, he said that?
He said, "Even if you have
to burn down the property
and claim insurance,
never sell the business."
We said, "Oh, we ran out of lights.
Oops, I knocked over a candle.
Oops, that candle happened to be
next to a trash can
full of gas."
- Okay, let's...
- We know you're stressed.
But I think I have an idea to save us.
Okay.
Here we go. Let's go, Knox.
Okay, little harder, little harder.
Okay, that was terrible.
One more.
- All right, Kaylee, come on.
- Mr. Duke?
- Come on.
- Uh, we're with
Village Homes Tiny Homes.
- Hey, how's it going?
- Creek Thompson's old business.
Yeah? What do you want?
We have a business proposition.
Okay, hold on a sec.
Hey, guys?
Why don't you guys go ahead
and do some push-ups
and sit-ups back there?
Drop down, give me 120.
- Butcher Duke.
- Jennifer Calloway.
Lovely to meet you.
Kelly Anderson, hi.
- What's going on?
- We want to invite you
to a big tennis rematch event,
this time against Delta Thompson.
And if you beat him,
you will win a tiny home.
Okay.
So...
Think about it.
- Think about it.
- What?
What do you mean?
Do I...
You're gonna call me or...
I'll call...
It's not every day you get a second chance
to play tennis for a tiny home.
What will Butcher do?
What the hell's a tiny home?
You've got to go for it.
What if I lose again?
So, you already lost.
No one can think of you any less.
Once you've hit rock bottom,
there's only one way: up.
Okay, that's my line.
All right, have you ever
had your heart ripped out
on the tennis court?
I was this close to winning
a double-wide mobile home,
and I lost and it hurt.
We lost every match last year.
We're still showing up, though.
I mean, you live with your mom, Butch.
You got to go for it, Butch.
So you guys really think I got a shot?
Yeah.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Like, seventyish percent.
- Fifty.
- Thirty-five.
- Yeah.
- Thirty-five, yeah.
Not as good as I wanted, but...
Here he comes, the challenger!
Out to win a manufactured home tonight:
Butcher Duke!
Go, Butcher!
Duke!
Challenging Butcher Duke to a tennis match
and the winner gets a tiny home, so...
- Babe, look, it's Delta.
- And will the match be
in one of the tiny homes?
Yeah, wasn't he, like, a grade above us?
- Yeah.
- June, I love you.
Uh, you're great, uh...
Didn't you date him?
- No, I dated you.
- Oh.
...the home that Butcher Duke
will be winning?
Babe, look, it's your dad.
Hold on!
- Hey!
- I'm sorry, sir,
this is a live...
This thing rolling?
I'll tell you something.
I'm Butcher Duke.
I lost a mobile home
opportunity 20 years ago.
Not this time.
It means something this time.
I lost my daughter.
I haven't talked to her in two years.
My wife's dead, she died in a mudslide.
Okay, I live with my mom.
I'm 45.
It's embarrassing.
I've been in anger management
for 18 months,
but I'm a different person.
So I'm here, and I'm here
to tell you, June,
I accept this challenge.
Yes!
- You look good today, June.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
This is gonna be a fun match
because you're gonna watch a young buck
just pounce on an, uh, older man, uh...
Oh, this is clearly getting
kind of emotional.
- It's all right.
- What'd you say?
Oh. Boys, we don't need
to bring this to a violent place.
- I'm gonna grab him...
- Pan in, pan in, pan in.
Good. All right.
Like I said, I've been
in anger management now
for 18 months.
I almost hit him.
I wanted to hit him, but that's...
Why aren't you more excited?
Your dad is on TV right now.
He's playing for a tiny home, babe.
That's no small thing.
I mean, it's a small house,
but it's no small thing.
- You think I can beat Delta?
- I do.
I've always thought you could do anything
you wanted to do.
You know that.
I just wish Kathy was here, you know?
- I miss her.
- I miss her, too.
I want to talk to Emily.
Oh, well.
Maybe winning a tiny home
will change everything.
Everything okay there, Butch?
Seem a little quiet.
Yeah, I'm just...
...just really missing
my wife today.
Hm, I didn't know you were married.
Oh, I'm not.
She died in a mudslide.
It's just hard, you know?
Yeah.
I mean, it could be worse, right?
She could've died in,
you know, volcanic molten lava,
you know, like my cousin Steve did.
Wait a second.
Where are we, Gordy?
You know where we are.
We're at your dead wife's grave.
How do you know where my wife is buried?
Go to her, Butch.
Hey, Butch?
It's not that one.
It's the one over there.
Yeah.
Ah!
Well, how'd you think I was hitting?
I mean, I think you're hitting pretty well.
You got a couple days left.
I'd keep working on your backhand.
- Yeah.
- Just keep drilling.
- Serve is okay, though, right?
- Yeah.
- I feel good about the serve.
- Looking good as ever.
- Yeah.
- Maybe better.
Ah, thanks, man. Yeah.
So, what's the latest with you and Emily?
- How are you guys?
- She's getting married, man.
- Wow.
- I didn't even know
she was engaged.
You know, apparently, he's some,
you know, state champion paintballer.
I guess that pays these days.
You know, people gamble online,
they can play paintball,
make mon... I don't get it,
know what I mean?
You know, I just... yeah.
Well, I don't... I don't mean
to be a big advice giver,
but just don't give up.
- Yeah.
- Don't give up.
I can't, man.
She's all I got.
Dang.
Ooh, okay, I already like this one.
Okay.
- It's pretty good.
- It's doughy.
Look at this one.
It's got a remote to it.
- Oh, it's like a hospital bed?
- Yeah.
Like, soft and firm.
Oh my gosh, I don't know
if I'm gonna be able
to get out of this.
Like, I legitimately... I don't know.
It's like putting my face
in, like, a lamb's belly.
Whoa, look at this giant one.
Can we get the huge one?
I feel like royalty.
I feel like I should have, like, jewels
just draped around me.
Yeah, this one is nice too 'cause, like,
when I'm mad at you, I can be on my side
and I don't have to touch you.
Look how many kids we can fit in this bed.
Oh my God, no, please.
- Whoa.
- Oh, man.
- That's it.
- You ready?
Yes.
Robobed.
Oh, let's wake up, the baby is crying.
Uh-oh, "Wah, Mom,
I need milk, Mom."
The pregnancy joke is funny
when I make it, not you.
Going back to bed.
I can't wait to live with you.
Me neither.
Hey, Jennifer,
thanks again for staying late.
I mean, that's what I'm here for.
How's the training going?
Oh, it's great, you know.
Uh, my forehand, great.
Backhand could use a little work.
And I'm gonna surprise him
on my serve, I'm telling ya.
That's good to hear.
- Thanks so much.
- Yeah, of course.
- Can I show you something?
- Yeah.
So, this is one of my favorites.
His name is Wilburforce.
They call him The Force because he... oh!
You see that?
Gets him at the hip, but guess what,
he's gonna get back up.
He's a little squatty, a little scrawny,
but that's what I like about him.
He's energized, he's ready.
Oh! Gets to jump over,
leaps over him.
Pulls back, he leaps over him.
Ah, oh, yeah.
Ooh!
Oh!
Oh, wow!
Hot dog.
I don't know about you,
but that gets me jazzed.
Yeah, I mean, I went to a WWE match...
- Whoa, professional?
- Yeah.
That's amazing.
Man, Jennifer, I just...
I can't believe I'm asking you this,
but if I can, after all this is over,
take you out to dinner
somewhere nice like Cheddar's?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah, I'd really like that.
Man, hot dog!
You did it, Delta, you asked her.
Yeah, I should probably get that.
- Yeah, I'll...
- All right.
See you, Jennifer.
- Have a good evening.
- Yeah, you too.
Oh, hey, uh, Village Homes.
Delta Thompson speaking.
Oh, tiny homes, no, no, no,
you can be normal sized
in a tiny home.
Up.
Toss above the head.
Okay? So let's take a look
at you guys.
Okay. The serve is the most
important part of the game.
Okay.
Okay, that's enough.
There you go.
Close, close.
Last year, you hit rock bottom.
Where do you go from here?
- Up.
- Up, that's it.
Okay, here we go.
What?
Oh, almost, Kaylee!
All right.
Good job on the serves.
All right, so as you guys know,
do you remember what Faith's goal was?
- Between the legs?
- Between-the-legs shot.
Okay, that's good.
Oh, that's close.
- Hm.
- Did it make it?
You think we should make you another goal?
- Yeah.
- John?
You want to show us
what you've been working on?
Um, so, yeah, I've been
working on some poetry,
so I thought I could
share it with you guys.
"Tennis racket, tennis racket,
I don't like you very much.
You think you're great,
but you're not great and stuff.
You make me feel like it's hard to hit you.
But, Trish, you know,
I could never quit you."
- Woo! Yeah.
- Woo.
Hey there, welcome to
Delta Thompson's virtual tour.
Delta, you got this.
Hey there, welcome to
Delta Thompson's virtual tour.
I'm your host, Delta Thompson.
Sure, sure, a tiny home
can most definitely fit
four dogs, abs... absolutely.
I don't know why you're doubting that.
This is our Colorado B-style house.
This thing is high.
Wow, it's long.
Holy moly, and it's a tiny home.
Are you kidding me?
Do you not know
what APR financing is?
You can see this thing
is full of ample space.
I'm talking square feet upon square feet
upon square feet.
You come on down here,
you come on down today,
I'll give you a tour myself.
Full-blown kitchen with a working sink,
running water.
Okay, it's not working right now.
That's a love seat
for when you got those couples.
Leopard blanket not included.
Even rich people can't afford homes
that withstand hurricanes, okay?
Full-on medicine cabinet.
That's right there... uh-oh, scary movie!
Scary movie! It's just me.
Scary movie.
Hey, ladies and gentlemen,
I just want you to subscribe
to my channel.
It's right here.
Yes, a mobile home is a...
Okay, okay, well, if you want
to call me that, then...
That was not very good.
Do you ever just have a tough day?
How do you get through that?
What's the worst...
...worst day
you've been through?
Oh, there's been a lot of them,
but you go home, you sleep it off,
and you come back recharged.
Yeah.
Don, what's it like to love someone
for so many years?
It's pretty good.
We want to serve you...
...quality homes...
...today!
Are you tired of people
saying you have a lazy eye?
He is so hot.
When I was a little hijo,
people used to make fun of my lazy oho.
So come on down to Abe's Eye Repair.
Get rid of that lazy eye
and get yourself...
Ooh, I bet he smells like olive oil.
Kind of not what I expected.
Wait.
I think this is it.
Yeah, definitely.
It's him.
Cut!
This is a cool place.
Wow, it's like a thrift shop,
but, like, professional.
I'm kind of in the middle
of something important.
- Can I help you?
- Kelly Anderson.
Jennifer Calloway.
Lovely to meet you.
Village Homes Tiny House.
Are you familiar with
the Village Homes Tiny House?
No idea.
Introducing Wilburforce.
A local hero
who happens to be the most famous
part-time minor league wrestler in town.
- Our boss...
- ...is a huge fan.
- Makes sense.
- And he's participating
in the biggest tennis match of the season.
And what we want you to do
is be the preshow entertainment.
And what does this "preshow"
entertainment entail?
Before the show, you'll be
entertaining the audience.
As in...
You will be wrestling
volunteers from the audience
for 30 seconds, just...
Bam, bam, bam!
We know a lot about wrestling.
Yeah, no, you don't, but...
Hm.
You know what?
I'll do it.
Nice doing business with you.
- Thank you, ladies.
- Our hotmail is on the card.
So, guys, I'm gonna teach you
the poach today.
Does anybody know what the poach is?
- No.
- No one?
- The egg.
- There's a poached egg.
Has anybody ever poached a whale
off the coast of Madagascar?
- No.
- Well, I have, okay?
Let's keep that between us.
Okay, John, you're gonna start.
This is the poach.
Boom!
Did you see that?
You guys think you can do that?
- Yeah.
- Okay, Friday,
when we play this match against Ramsey,
they're not gonna be expecting it.
Okay? Rackets up, get excited.
You're gonna want to aim right there.
See Knox's belly?
Just right in the center, okay?
Come on.
Yes! Yes.
When she becomes the cougar,
you become the leopard.
Right? Cougar, leopard.
Now go get it, go get it.
Whoa! What the...
- Did you see that angle?
- Yeah.
Oh my gosh! Right here.
All right, bring it in,
right here, bring it in.
Let's go, let's go.
Who... who are we gonna celebrate today?
- Me?
- Kaylee.
On three, "Kaylee."
One, two, three, Kaylee!
- Hi.
Is there anything in particular
you're looking for?
Well, primarily rackets and some balls
and maybe some snacks.
So, just like that, yeah.
Ooh, oats and honey.
Yeah, I'll take all these.
- What do these do?
- Uh, those go over the grip.
Yeah, I'll need five of these.
I'll take this.
Basket of balls, all right.
- Okay.
- And...
Cool, uh...
You know, I have a girlfriend.
- You do?
- Mm-hm.
- Well, good.
- Yeah.
Glad to hear that.
Do you, uh, do you have any advice for me?
Well, women really like to be listened to.
Do you have any other advice
besides listening?
'Cause it's hard for me
to do that sometimes.
Do you have a sense of humor?
- Women like sense of humor.
- Okay.
- What's your name?
- Wendy.
I'm Delta. Delta Thompson.
- Knock-knock.
- Who's there?
- Interrupting cow.
- Interrupting...
Moo!
- Hey!
- Hey! How's it going?
Oh.
- Nice to see you again.
- Good to see you.
Um, I thought maybe we could
just hit some balls.
- Yeah, that sounds good.
- And I got some snacks.
- Oh, awesome.
- Oats and honey,
and these are some baked fish.
- Thanks.
- Yeah. Let's head this way.
Let's... let's go.
Yeah, I hard-boiled an egg this morning.
Oh, wow, was that your first time?
No, I do that every morning.
Typically, I try and do
a soft boil or a medium boil.
I can never get the soft boil right.
- One.
- Two.
Sorry, that was a little high.
Three. Sugar!
- Okay.
- One.
Two.
- Three.
- Four.
Oh, we almost had five!
Hey, you did pretty good out there.
Thanks. You weren't
too bad, though.
Oh.
You might want to get a lesson, though.
It wouldn't hurt.
Yeah. Yeah, that's a good idea.
Knock knock.
Ellis, Emily, welcome.
Glad you're here.
Well, how'd you guys meet?
- Tell me how you met.
- Uh, was it freshman year
- of high school?
- Freshman year of high school,
I'd eaten some really old chicken fingers
- for breakfast, and...
- Yes.
But, we were in line getting food,
and he, instead of puking, like,
on his tray, he leaned over
and puked on mine.
Well, now that's
kind of romantic, a little,
- isn't it?
- Yeah.
- I think so.
- Kinda cute,
- puked on the first date.
- But...
I played it off pretty well, I thought.
Oh, good, well who's got the debt?
Who's got the debt here?
- Sorry, debt?
- Yeah,
every counseling situation I come in,
one of the two has debt,
so who is it?
- I don't have any debt.
- That's good.
- And I don't think you...
- But, what...?
Um, I was only talking about,
'cause I have some loans
I took out.
- Just the ones...
- Oh, like, you still have
- those loans?
- I mean, like,
you know, I have the credit
paid for my house,
and, like, car payments.
You're gonna have, like, some debt.
I mean, everyone has debt.
- No.
- Right, it's like a...
- It's a fairly com...
- Not everyone.
No, that's a fairly common thing.
- No.
- How much debt is it, Emily?
The number?
- A few thousand.
- A few thousand?
- 50,000.
- $50,000 in debt.
- Okay.
- Oh, God.
All right.
Well, why didn't you tell me
you had that much debt?
- 'Cause that...
- My dad never taught me
how to, like, manage finances,
so I don't know
- what you're expecting.
- Okay, this is something
we've got to work on, obviously.
We can work on it.
So, how do you guys feel about pets?
- Um.
- Do you want them?
Do you like them?
- You first, Ellis.
- Sure, uh,
I like dogs.
- Cats I'm allergic to...
- Yeah, okay.
...and I think they're
really cold and mean.
- Oh, okay.
- That's a little...
Oh, you like cats now, too?
Do you have cat debt?
Do... all the money
- that you pay for cats.
- Yeah, yeah, no, actually I do
have cat debt, because I had to get surgery
- for Toby when he had cancer.
- Oh, how'd that work out?
Toby's dead, babe.
Oh, my God.
I'm so glad you're here.
Okay, the wedding's coming up.
We've got details I'd like to hear about.
Bridesmaids, who's walking you
down the aisle?
Um.
Well, I, uh...
- I know who my bridesmaids are.
- Okay.
Who's walking you down the aisle, Emily?
Um, I mean, we were
talking about it earlier.
I think I'm probably just gonna
walk myself down the aisle.
Oh, that's so sad.
And you know Jennifer and I kinda have
a little thing going, right?
No, what thing, what kind of thing?
Well, we signed a thing,
we talked to Don, so he said...
No flirting with the coworkers
or customers that come in.
Look, it's just me and Jennifer, Val, okay?
I know you thought we had something,
but it's not there anymore.
I just don't wanna see you
get your heart broken again.
Well, you're the one that
broke my heart, Valerie.
Hey, hey there, Don.
- Yeah?
- You mind if I talk to you
- in your office for a second?
- Come on in.
I'm smitten, I'm a...
I'm a love bug, and I don't know
what to do, Don,
and I'm... I'm about to be squashed here.
What advice do you give?
Start slow, maybe ya ask her to lunch.
- Okay.
- Some place quiet,
and where you can build up a rapport.
Mhm, all right.
And Don, what is 0 APR?
Oh, look at that.
- Let's go, y'all.
- Faith, you wanna, uh...?
- You wanna break into groups?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- You gotta work.
- What is this?
- Kay, Butch, um, so,
we know that your match
is coming up pretty soon,
and we wanna help you,
because you've been helping us
for the last couple years now,
and we wanna train with you
- to help you get your home.
- You wanna train with me?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Go!
Oh, yeah, come on, you got it.
Come on, y'all.
Keep 'em up, don't touch the ground.
Ooh, John, you throwing up?
Yeah?
10, 9, 8...
- 3, 4...
- Ugh!
There ya go... 5...
Come on, other way, Faith, come on.
You got it.
Got it.
Come on, guys, come on!
Yeah, this is, uh... this is
one of my favorite models,
and it's actually
incredibly
huge for what we call a tiny home.
Hey, Ray, uh,
- we got any sales today?
- No.
- No?
All right.
Yes, uh, it's a walk-in closet,
really, if you walk in and...
- Oh, cool.
- Yeah, and I can close you in.
It's almost like a third bedroom,
if you want.
- Hey, Valerie, how's it going?
- Hey, good, how are you?
- Good, all right, see ya.
- Good.
I said it'd be a bit small for a bedroom.
Absolutely, it'd be a great bedroom.
We get any sales today?
No, not... not that I'm aware of.
Well, this is our...
this is our toilet, and...
- It says don't use it.
- Yeah, some local teenagers
come often in there to take dookies,
but we try to prevent that by...
- Oh.
- Yeah, see,
- so that was that smell.
- Yeah.
You... so you don't want a tiny house?
No, no, no, I... I have a really big house.
Delta? Mike Clark.
- Nice to meet you, sir.
- What do you got there?
It's a candy bar.
Winners don't eat candy.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go.
Delta, the most important thing
is consistency.
- Okay.
- Making the other guy
have to hit one more ball.
- What was that?
- I don't know,
you hit it harder.
Try to see the ball hit the strings, Delta.
Delta, you sure you're right handed?
All right, good job.
But, you wanna try to hit the ball.
- Oh, okay.
- Okay?
All right, let me show,
let me show you something.
Backstretch, toss, and then swing.
- Great.
- Like you're throwing a ball.
- Yeah.
- But, get that racket back there
like you're scratching your back.
I have a back scratcher, uh, back home
that's, uh... it's in the shape of a hand.
Oh, okay, well, good for you.
Why don't we use the racket
out here, though?
- Okay.
- That's it.
Nice, that's it.
- Great serve.
- There we go, I did it.
Maybe... maybe now we could go grab a beer.
No, let's just get this over with.
Okay.
Thank you so much, Mike.
Any last advice?
Yeah, well,
you're not very good.
You might wanna consider
changing it to a doubles match.
There's just like an air of death
over the apartment right now,
'cause I think Marcus's ferret
got in the walls and died,
and it smells so bad that I threw up
in my sleep last night,
I'm not even joking.
- Baby, that's not good.
- Is that normal?
- No.
- I just...
I just wanna live with you so bad.
I... I don't wanna live in
a smelly, haunted apartment anymore.
Okay, well we have like a week
until we get married,
so maybe we can make it.
Boys, woo!
- All right.
- Big paintball game today?
It's a scrimmage, but yeah, still big.
- All right, be good.
- Later!
Okay, listen, Jack, Kailey,
you guys are gonna start us off, okay?
Knox, Faith, you're gonna close it down.
- All right, we ready?
- Yeah.
Okay, one, two, three, go for it!
All right, let's go, Jack, Kailey, come on.
- Go, guys! Kailey!
- Let's go, let's go.
- Go!
- Yeah!
Come on, Jack, come on!
What was this?
That... I didn't teach you that.
Come on, Jack, you got this!
Woo!
Jack, yeah!
- Yeah!
- Yes, yes!
First point of the day.
Yeah, Kailey!
Hold on a second, guys.
Okay, doing what we worked on.
All right a little softer, yeah?
Okay, and just cross court over the net.
- A little higher.
- Woo, come on, Kail.
I just want you to relax.
Okay, listen.
Okay, I think you're
thinking about it too much.
- Why are we here?
- To have fun.
To have fun.
Proud of you, you're gonna get it.
Let's go, right here,
okay, here we go, Kailey.
- Come on.
- Come on, Kailey!
- You can do this!
- Yeah!
Way to go!
Whoa, yeah!
Awesome, you guys.
- Kailey, you did it!
- Yeah.
Yes!
I got ball.
Totes, yes!
Way to go!
It's the poach off the coast
of Madagascar, is what that is.
Boom, boom.
- It's all right.
- Keep your eye on the ball.
- Hey.
- Oh.
Come on, Knox, please, please, God.
Hey, whoa, Knox, no.
No, don't you get my court wet.
Don't.
Hey, bud, hey, just take a break,
take a break, you can come back,
come on, take a break.
Go, John, come on, John, fill in.
Hey, you're okay.
You almost got one in.
No crying, you didn't cry.
Who's got a ball?
We got destroyed today,
but you know what?
Somebody got a serve in for the first time.
Kailey.
Faith got a poach, how about that?
You just learned that this week.
Knox almost cried.
But, he didn't.
Jack, Kailey,
I think there's something there.
- Mm, mhm.
- Yeah?
You listen here, Jack.
You better guard her heart.
And I someone out there expressing himself.
John, how do you feel?
Feel like I had good, you know,
eye contact with the ball and all that,
but, um, I don't know,
I feel like I could've
expressed myself more.
Well, guess what?
It's never too late.
John, close this out.
- Can I get a beat, please?
- Come on.
- Call this one "The Pancake."
- Oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
This is our Colorado D unit,
it's one of my favorite units.
Oh, the Colorado, I like that.
Yeah, it's Colorado
because in Colorado they have
a lot of trees,
and this is completely made out
- a lot of wood.
- I like the...
I like the pine and the lighter floor
that kinda gives it
more of an open feeling.
- Sure, yeah.
- Now, is this Formica, or, um...?
Uh, I don't know who it's for.
But, I'm not sure,
I don't know who Mica is.
- And this bathroom?
- The teenagers often come in
and take dookies at night,
but we try and prevent that,
and we'll get you a clean one before.
Have they... but not in this one, right?
Like, they... teenagers don't...
You know, I actually can't even remember.
This, everything, the stain of wood,
the size, has everything we're looking for.
Good, but you don't want it?
No, I mean, we'll take it.
- We'll take this.
- Real... uh, really?
- Yeah.
- Yes, yes!
You can have it, it's yours.
- Yes, yes.
- Thank you.
Pleasure doing business.
- You... yeah.
- Hot dog.
Yes!
- Come on in, come on in.
- Yeah, okay, cool.
- Awesome.
- Yeah.
Man.
So, first just, like,
take a feel of the home, like,
kind of reach out, feel the air.
- Do you feel it?
- Yeah, real something.
This is good.
This is our farm basin sink.
You got two sides, no disposal,
but there is room.
- Full oven.
- Full oven
- for all of the cookies you...
- Oh, my God, it's got two racks.
Yeah, also, don't forget
to look at this microwave.
- Two racks!
- Make sure you remove
- the papers.
- Golly, Ma.
It's better than your microwave.
What is this... this the bathroom?
Yeah, come on in, follow me in.
This is awesome.
Wow.
This is great, ladies.
- What else you got?
- Well, we got the Dryclone.
Mom, these are like yours at home.
Yeah, guess Mom won't be
doing your laundry anymore.
Nah, she'll come over and help me.
- All this room.
- No way.
- Yes, if you have a baby.
- My gosh, Kelly.
Right here, you can store it right there.
It's kind of like a ladder, which adds a...
- Whoa!
- ...a key of... ow!
Ow, oh, uh, watch your head.
- Well?
- I'll take it.
- I'm gonna win this thing and...
- That's what we wanna hear.
I think I got a good shot at Delta.
Yeah, I mean, now that it's doubles,
like, I think it'll be even more fun
and more publicity
will come to the both of us.
- Did you say "doubles"?
- Yeah, you need to find a buddy.
It's kind of like, you see,
we're working better
- as a team.
- So, no... okay, whoa, whoa, whoa.
So, Delta and I are not playing?
- Oh, oh, no, no, no.
- Singles?
You will be playing,
just with two other people
also on the court at the same time.
So, I gotta find a partner by tomorrow?
- Delta's got one, so you should.
- Yes.
Dang it!
Um.
Uh, Jennifer let's show her
the linoleum options.
Crawl on over.
- Follow us.
- Just right down stairs.
I'll be down there in a minute, Mom.
God.
Gotta buy this home.
I'm content where I am, I'm happy,
but I know if I can win this home,
man, it'll make things better.
Look, just give me a minute, okay?
Delta changed the rules
from singles to doubles,
and I need a doubles partner,
so please, will you be my doubles partner?
- No.
- No?
Dad, I haven't played tennis
in like nine years.
Uh, like that matters.
Come on, you can pick it up.
Please, this is hard for me
to come here and ask.
Look, I'm sorry,
it's just not gonna happen.
But, I'm glad you're doing this,
but I can't, I'm sorry.
- You're serious?
- Yeah.
I'm serious.
- Good to see you, Ellis.
- Always a pleasure, sir.
- All right, take care.
- Yeah.
Looks like you're
my doubles partner, Gordy.
Yes.
Let's see how many
we can get in a row... one.
Count yours out.
I'm at zero, all right, one.
- Two.
- I got one.
- All right,
work on your back hand side, see this?
Doubles, we're gonna have
a lot of volleying tomorrow.
Five, six... I'm beating you.
- One.
- Seven.
That's it, that's it.
Hey, we may win a point.
All right, 10 in a row, come on, Gordy.
We can't leave till we get 10.
One, two,
three... good.
Four... play it.
Oh, well start again.
Okay, 10 in a row,
trying to be positive here.
- Here we go... one.
- Okay.
Oh, almost!
You know what, five in a row.
- Five in a row, okay.
- How about five in a row?
Here we go... one,
two.
- Sorry.
- Uh-uh.
- Hey, Gordy,
come here real quick.
You're not doing bad,
but I think it's important
you know something.
- What's that?
- Okay,
- you know I live with my mom.
- Uh-huh.
- She's kicking me out.
- Why?
I don't know, menopause probably.
So, if we don't win tomorrow,
I don't have a home.
I need you to step it up
on the game here, okay?
- You're all I got here.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Right?
- I can do it.
Here we go.
That's it.
Come on, buddy.
There you go, come on.
Come on, Gordy.
Come on, recover.
Recover, recover.
Recover, recover, recover.
Gordy, God, Gordy.
Let's pick 'em up.
Think we got a chance tomorrow, Gordy?
Yeah, we always have a chance, Butch.
Always got a chance.
I just love looking at old pictures.
This is one of your dad,
I think he was about 8 or 9,
- and look at all that hair.
- Oh, my God.
I know, gosh, he had more than me.
And here's another one, we did...
we never cut his hair.
- Yeah, well...
- We just let it grow.
He rocked the chili bowl.
Now, Ms. Ems, let's look at you.
- Look.
- Drill team.
- Love it.
- Oh, I miss being a cowgirl.
I loved watching you, I loved watching you.
Look at this one, look at this one.
- It's so beautiful, I love it.
- Oh, my gosh.
Where did you even get a dress
from, like, the 1890s?
Well, actually your dad picked that out
- and bought it for you.
- He's always had
really good taste, I guess.
And this is one I found
in the attic the other day.
I'd forgotten I even had it.
Oh, my gosh, with his tennis rackets.
Tennis rackets and tennis shoes.
Grandma, you set him up for this.
Oh, I love it.
I think Ellis looks like your dad.
- Oh, God.
- June Cooper, Channel 5 News.
We are here live
at the Caswell Tennis Center
for the game to beat all games.
The clash of the local titans.
Delta Thompson and Butcher Duke
are finally going to battle it out
for a 20 year grudge over tennis.
Do you think that Butcher is
prepared for it this go around?
I'm sure he's ready.
Who do you think is gonna
take away the big trophy today?
Delta.
- Mr. Wilbur Force.
- Yes?
Delta Thompson, big fan.
Here's my demo tape.
It's my wrestling portfolio,
got a couple of my moves on 'em.
I thought maybe you could watch it
and give me some pointers,
and that'd be really cool
- because then you would show me.
- I'll see what I can do, okay?
- Okay.
- Um, do you know what?
- Can you hold this for a second?
- Yeah, of course.
All right, hey,
I'll see ya out there, okay?
See you out there on the court.
Yes.
I am here interviewing with Slaton Ralls.
He is the chair referee at today's match.
All right, guys, tonight's a big night.
There's a tiny home on the line,
this is important.
This is not play around.
- Hey.
- Just came to wish you
- good luck.
- Thanks, I'm gonna need it.
Goodbye.
Yeah, Butcher, you're gonna win,
and I love you,
and you're kind of like a dad figure to me.
Please don't... please, please don't lose.
Um, how are you feeling?
Do you have any words
that you'd like to give
to your mentor and your coach?
Good luck.
How y'all doing tonight?
Before this amazing, life-changing match,
we have a little pre-show entertainment
- we'd like to introduce to you.
- Match is on, babe.
So, you know him,
- you love him.
- You love him.
Some of you who volunteer
might wrestle him.
It is... Wilbur Force!
Ugh, this guy gives me the heebie-jeebies.
You don't like Wilbur Force?
No, he looks like
he smells like mayonnaise.
We're looking for some volunt...
Volunteers.
Oh, say can you see,
by the dawn's
early light,
what so proudly...
- You ready, Gordy?
- Yep, just got the diarrhea.
Oh, say does that
star-spangled
banner yet wave...
- Babe, are you crying?
- Yeah.
O'er the land
of the free,
and the home
of the...
- Is it "brave"?
- Brave.
- Brave!
Thank you.
Come on.
Don't you hurt my baby!
He's got a pulse.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the event of the evening,
featuring the team of Delta Thompson
and Nobeck Ivandich.
Butcher Duke and Gordy.
The format for tonight's match
is best two out of three games
wins the match.
Remember, a tiny home
is on the line tonight.
Let's go!
Let's go, Butcher, let's go!
- 15, love.
- All right, Butch, let's go.
Come on, come on.
Come on, Delta!
That's not what we needed.
15, all.
Come on.
Yes!
Game one winner:
Delta Thompson.
Come on, Butchy!
Well, hello again.
It's been a while.
It sure don't look good
for Butch about now.
If he only had a better tennis partner.
A good friend.
A daughter with tennis experience
who needs to reconcile with her daddy.
Well, looky there.
- Oh, my gosh, you came.
- Well, I saw you on TV.
You're kinda getting killed out here.
Yeah, I could definitely use you.
Well, let's get you a tiny home.
Let's do it, come on.
Wait a minute.
Oh, come on, this isn't right.
You may not switch partners
in the middle of the match.
Yeah, and we watched tape
on him, we know how he plays.
Come on, man, it's my daughter.
Let her play.
Fine, but no funny business,
for real.
Let's go, baby, woo!
- Yes!
- 15, love.
That's my girl.
30, love.
- Here we go, wake up.
- Yeah.
Yes!
Game two winner:
Butcher Duke.
Listen, I know you don't speak English,
but come on, kill.
Kill.
Whoever wins this game wins the match.
Remember, a tiny home
is on the line tonight.
Love, 15.
Come on.
- Love, 30.
- You're doing good.
See.
You got this.
Love, 40.
I just want you know, whether we win
this match or not,
I'm just glad you're here.
Okay, everyone's staring,
let's just get back.
Okay, real quick,
one more thing, one more thing.
- What?
- I do need to win
- this home though, though.
- Okay, yeah, Dad,
the ref is, like, staring at us right now.
Okay, okay.
15, 40.
Let's go, Em.
- Yes!
- 30, 40.
Yes.
Me.
Yes!
No way!
- Oh yeah.
- Yes.
Oh, God.
Ah, it's all right, hey, it's all right.
Yes!
- Dang it!
- It looks like the next point
- will win, Butch?
- What'd you say?
I said, "It looks like
the next point will win, Butch."
I know how to keep score, turd burglar.
Dad, Dad, it's okay.
Do you breathing.
What are we gonna do?
It's the last point.
You remember the poach?
- Off the coast of Madagascar?
- Is there any other coast?
Oh, my God, let's do this.
Sudden death, final point.
Delta, go Delta!
Quiet, please, a tiny home is on the line.
I wanna win this home, it's obvious.
I wouldn't be training the way I am
if I didn't wanna win the home.
But, I need to know that
it's okay with the people I love
that, if I don't win it,
it's gonna be okay.
Yeah!
Who gives this young lady
today in holy matrimony
to this young man?
Her dead mother and I.
Well, things sure worked out for Butcher.
What a happy ending.
"But, what about Delta?"
you might be asking.
Hi, I'm Delta Thompson!
We have zero percent APR financing,
and I know what that means now!
We've got tiny homes
we're excited to show you!
And we wanna serve you quality today!
He lost the business.
But, he's pursuing his lifelong dream.
- Yeah!
Give 'em what the people want.
- Oh yeah.
- You give 'em what the...
Give 'em what the people want.
Hot dog, I love wrestling.
Well, I hope you enjoyed our story.
I sure did.
Who you been talking to, Gordy?
You know who I'm talking to, Butch.
No, no, I don't.