- Hm.
Oh.
Ah!
Come explore science
as we go above...
- Three, two, one, zero.
- And beyond!
Close your eyes.
Go ahead.
Most people think
it's just a black abyss.
But in fact,
the universe appears.
Look closely.
Do you see it?
It's faint,
but it's there
if you concentrate.
It's probably colorful
and shifting.
It's evolving and growing.
Do you see it?
What you're seeing
is entirely unique to you.
It's a kind of fingerprint,
your own personal universe.
Now...
Open your eyes.
- I said, can you open
your eyes for me, Cameron?
Hello?
Oh, my God.
It was unbelievable.
- Was he dead?
- The ambulance guy said
he had a chance.
- Paramedics.
- Yeah, I know
what they're called.
- Well, was anyone else hurt?
- What did you do
till they showed?
- No, but-but-well,
I just kind of sat there,
uh, with him.
I don't know.
I just-it was weird.
What?
- It's-it's a really
crazy story, Cam.
It's really crazy.
You don't believe me, do you?
- I do. I do.
It's just the part
about falling from the sky,
you know?
You sure it didn't hit
the curb and then flip over?
- Well, who was he?
- Yeah. Yeah, I am.
They didn't tell me, but he-
he looked like a younger,
better-looking version of me.
- Hm.
I bet my twin is a hot blonde
with big fake boobs.
- Oh, come on.
You're beautiful as is.
- Cam, you do know
that it sounds outlandish,
though, right?
- You're a man, right?
- Yeah. I understand, but it-
- So why is it that, like,
the standard of beauty for men
is, like, high heels
and a dress?
What is that about?
I mean, it doesn't make sense
to me.
Like, why-
- I'm just saying-
- What's wrong with, like,
a good pair of pants?
- I feel like
there's no reason
you can't give a rational
explanation for this.
- Because, like, at school
they make you either wear,
like, a skirt or pants
for your uniform-
- This is pressure.
Air pressure.
Air pressure makes
the wind blow
and allows us to breathe.
Without air pressure,
nothing could fly.
Now, look at this.
This airplane is flying.
Well, it was in rehearsal.
Air moving across the wings
is what scientists call lift.
Now, any fluid,
be it air or water,
flowing around an object
puts a force on that object.
Lift is the component
of this force
that is perpendicular
to the oncoming flow.
And it is
this perpendicular force
that causes airplanes...
- Your show's on way too late.
Why do they put a kids' show
on at midnight?
Midnight's a decent time slot.
Besides, Tony's got
some Saturday morning slot
opening up soon.
We'll be on
with the other kids' shows
before you know it.
- Didn't he say that
last year?
- You know, my dad
used to always say,
"There are two kinds of people
in the world, Cameron,
"astronomers and astronauts.
Some look at the stars,
others swim in them."
- Okay.
- Just be happy you're young.
You could still be
an astronaut.
- Yeah, but I don't
wanna be an astronaut.
You do.
- No, what I mean is,
you still have time
to do something fantastic.
- What do you want me
to say here, Cameron?
You're calling me Cameron now?
- Yeah.
It's your name, isn't it?
- Isn't it your bedtime?
I think it's your bedtime.
- Shh. Shh. Shh.
What'd I miss?
Come on.
- You missed the fact
of the day.
- No!
- Yes.
And that-
- That's my favorite part.
- Now you won't-
- What was it?
- You missed it.
The fact's gone.
- Ugh. Come on.
You don't get the fact.
- I talked to Larry.
He said the divorce papers
should be...
ready in a few weeks.
- Are we sure
we want to do this?
- We have to figure out
how we're gonna tell everyone.
- Forgot to brush my teeth.
- Hey, come on!
It's 7:15.
- Whoa.
- What?
- It's that guy.
That-that guy
from the car crash
that I saved or whatever,
He won a Copley.
He's an astronaut.
- What's a Coupler?
- Copley.
- It's British.
- It's a medal,
for science,
like the Nobel prize.
- Well,
except the Nobel is Swedish.
- Remember Bill Lang?
He won a Copley only
four years after graduating?
- God, who could forget
Willie Lang?
- Exactly. Ugh.
- Hang on.
Didn't you win a medal once?
- That was a Crawford.
- His father won the Copley.
- Okay, now I'm lost.
Actually, I don't care, so...
- All right. I'm off.
- God, this guy looks like me.
He totally does.
- I-I mean, like a little,
not that much, right?
- No, he does.
Okay. See you, Cam.
Does-does he look like me?
Not a lot though, right?
- Statistically speaking,
in a room with over 23 people,
there is more
than a 50% chance
that two people will have
the same birthday.
We've got 22 in here now,
but I think we've got
a pretty good shot.
So let's hear some birthdays,
starting in the back.
Mr. Cohen.
- September 8th.
- August 9th.
- November 7th.
- March 28th.
- December 10th.
- November 7th.
- April 4th.
- February 14th.
Valentine's Day.
- October 31st, Halloween.
- Ooh, October 31st.
Spooky.
Yes?
- Hi. Yeah.
I just got registered,
and they said to come here.
- Oh.
Welcome, welcome.
And what is your birthday,
good sir?
- October 31st.
- We have a match,
ladies and gentlemen.
Mm!
Isn't math cool?
A Halloween destiny
has been foretold.
Why don't you come on in,
have a seat
right in front of your match.
Now, probability statistics...
- There is a certain force
of attraction in our universe
pulling us together.
You,
me,
and the TV you're watching
are all pulling on each other.
This...
Is gravity.
The more mass
an object has on Earth,
the greater pull it has
from Earth.
We call this pull weight.
With all that weight
pulling down,
it's a wonder anything
or anyone has ever made it
off planet Earth
and into outer space.
You gotta go 600,000 feet up
to get there.
That's 20 times higher
than Mount Everest.
So how do you get there?
Rockets.
- That'll work.
It's a go for broadcast, Cam.
- You didn't watch
the whole thing.
- Ooh, I trust you didn't slip
any subliminal messages
in there.
Your shows are all
the same anyway, right?
- Um...
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
- Man, sorry about
the Saturday slot.
- The-the what?
- The Saturday morning slot.
I thought you guys
really deserved it.
- I've got the footage-
- Mm-hmm.
- And we're seeing
a few problems with it...
- Uh, thanks.
- Yeah.
- I tried to organize it,
but...
Tony, did you give
the Saturday morning slot
to another show?
- Cam, Cammy, come on in.
- Shonda said that-whoa.
- Kent Armstrong.
- But-I can't believe you're
even standing right now.
- Excuse me?
- The crash.
You crashed
your car yesterday.
- I'm afraid I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- I saw-I was-
- No, no, no.
Kent just moved to town.
You know him?
He's a famous-uh, uh-
wow, I'm sorry, it's just...
you two look a lot alike.
You know that?
- Not really.
- Relax, buddy.
It's a compliment.
- But-but I don't think we do,
not-not that much.
Can I talk to you, Tony,
for-in private?
- Be my guest.
Nice to meet you, uh, Samuel.
- See you in a second.
- What the hell is this?
You promised me
that Saturday slot
for, like, two years now.
- Okay.
Cameron, take a seat.
Look. I got some good news.
PBS called.
They are interested
in "Above and Beyond."
Network.
Scott from
the Columbus affiliate,
he sent them a VHS.
They loved it.
- Wh-really?
- "Above and Beyond"
is gonna take off.
I'm talking about lunch boxes,
key chains,
doodads, widgets,
the whole thing.
And you are gonna be
an amazing
creative consultant.
- What does that mean?
- They want a different host.
They want Kent.
He won a Copley.
Did you know that?
- Did you?
- I did. I did.
- That guy?
You're joking, right?
I mean, I-
he's, like-he's-he's, like-
he's like,
my antithesis or something.
- Like your nemesis?
- No.
- Your nemesis.
- No
- Cameron.
- Antithesis.
- You're still gonna get paid.
- He-
- Technically, WKFH
still owns 51%.
I'm sorry.
The decision is final.
- Well, I-I don't even
know what to say.
- Well, the other option,
you walk right now.
I mean, hell, Cam,
maybe this is good for you.
You go do
what you're destined for.
You're always talking
about NASA.
Send them an application.
- It's not that simple.
- All right.
Well, I got a meeting, so...
- Go around.
What?
Jesus.
- We're gonna need
two more dispatched.
- Copy that.
- Of course.
- Sir, I need you
to stand back.
- This is my house.
- I'm sorry.
- Cameron.
- Where have you been?
- What is this?
- You are not gonna believe
what happened.
- No, some old-ass Russian
rocket fell from outer space,
and it crashed
in our backyard.
- What?
- How are you?
- Right. Right.
I work at
the Air and Space Museum,
so if I could see it,
I might actually be able
to help
with the identification.
- Nobody's allowed back there.
- Do you understand
how rare it is
that a piece
of this thing would fall...
- You're the homeowner?
Mr. Edwin?
- Yeah.
- Well,
I'd say it'd be a while
before we see any progress.
No one knows
who should claim it
or why it even fell
in the first place.
There's a lot
of paperwork to do
in this kind of situation.
- Can I-can I see it?
- See what?
- The rocket that fell
in our backyard.
I'm a-I'm an astronomer.
- An astronaut?
- No, I'm an astronomer,
but this-
- Look, I'm afraid the house
is SOE, a site of evidence.
You can't see it and you can't
move back in either.
Government jurisdiction.
- So-
- We'll keep you posted.
I can't believe-
- You smell
like dog shit, Cameron.
- Hey.
Come in, come in.
- How are you doing, Lin?
- Hi, Cameron.
- Hi.
- You know, in Hawaii,
they would call this "'ohana,"
which translates to
"the connection
of all things."
Some milk?
- Thanks, Lin.
- Cam, I can tell you're not
taking this very well.
You don't look so good.
You should see a doctor,
or maybe a therapist.
- Thanks, Lin.
- Thanks for letting us
stay a while.
- Course. Course.
I mean, you couldn't stay
at that house.
- They wouldn't let us.
Okay.
- They're calling it
"Sputnik in suburbia."
In a one-in-a-million event,
a defunct Russian
ICBM rocket crashed
into the suburban neighborhood
of Fairview Heights
just outside
of Dayton, Ohio, today.
Neighbors in this sleepy
cul-de-sac tell us
they heard a large crash
around 7:00 p.m. this evening,
most thinking it was just
some kind of car accident,
and were shocked
to hear the truth.
Local police had no comment,
but the FAA is investigating
its origins.
- So come explore science
as we go above-
- Hey.
- Hi.
Uh, you just moved here,
right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, my dad works
for the military,
so we moved from Orlando
via Houston via...
list goes on.
We probably won't be here
that long, honestly, so...
- Oh, okay.
Uh, do you live this way?
I mean, for now, at least.
- Yeah.
- Cool.
- I mean, we've been staying
at a hotel until-
well, today's the day we move
into our new place, so-
- Oh, God, we just moved too.
- Oh.
- See, a Russian rocket
crashed into our backyard,
so we had to evacuate.
- That was you?
- Yeah.
Welcome to Fairview Heights,
the place where space junk
falls from the sky
and you have to move in with
your weird beach-loving aunt.
Every single towel
in her house is a beach towel.
Strange.
Uh, hey, um...
Sorry, I just wanna
be clear here.
I'm not, like,
flirting with you or anything.
- No problem.
- Like, you seem interesting.
I just, um...
You're just-like, you're not
my type, you know?
- Oh.
Uh, hey,
I got to run, actually.
Um...
I'll see you tomorrow?
- Yeah.
- Cool.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- So I heard a rocket crashed
in your backyard.
- Yeah.
- Can I see it?
- They...
Sure.
Come on.
- This isn't Russian.
I think it's American.
- Oh, yeah.
I think you're right.
- Is it Gemini, maybe?
The service module?
- Service module, yeah, but...
Apollo 10, I'd guess.
Can't be sure.
- Uh, sorry, do you know her?
- Huh.
Do I know you?
I guess not.
I don't know who she is.
- Wait a minute.
I recognize you.
You were the-you were the host
of the TV show
my dad just took over.
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry about that.
- No one ever
watched it anyway.
God, this is not how I thought
things would turn out.
I wanted to be an astronaut.
I wanted to do
something...fantastic.
- Hm.
Well,
I mean, you've got this pile
of rocket crap right here.
Why don't you just
build your own rocket?
It's not that simple.
- Eh, it might be.
Who knows?
Well, thanks for showing me.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Visitor.
- Cameron, hi.
Doc has me
on a steady regimen of crafts.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
You know what that is? Yeah?
- Uh...
- Moebius strip.
See, it only has one side.
A mathematical paradox.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- You know, I know
what a Mobius strip is.
Makes you think, right?
- It sure does.
- Yeah.
- Hey, so the craziest thing
happened yesterday.
- You know what that is?
- Uh...
What is it?
Tell me.
- A-
a Moebius-Moebius strip.
- Oh, it is?
- Yeah.
- What is-how many-
how many sides does it have?
Do you think
this is just chance,
all this happening right now?
The-the show
with the rocket crash.
My...I don't know,
doppelganger.
It's all pretty weird, right?
- What else would it be?
I don't know.
Um...
Some kind of like, uh...
Like a-
- Look.
You're a scientist,
and that is a chair
that you're sitting in,
and that's a stapler,
and this is a nursing home.
And I am a physician
for the elderly,
not a therapist, not a-
a psychic.
I don't know
what these things mean.
Sometimes, they just happen.
- What are you trying to say?
- I'm not telling you
to be rational.
- Okay.
So I should be irrational.
- No.
Absolutely not.
- But then what?
- I'm suggesting that perhaps
the universe in our heads
is more real
than reality itself.
- You got fired?
When?
How-how is that even possible?
It's our sh-your show.
- And you didn't even
come home
for dinner tonight, Cameron.
What were you doing?
- I was at the house.
- The house is condemned.
- Condemned?
It has tape around it.
The house is fine.
- Oh, okay.
- Linda.
- Erin.
Erin, you gotta see
this rocket.
It's not Russian.
It's American.
An Apollo service module.
- What?
- I think it's a sign.
- A sign?
- Yeah.
- No, Cameron,
the rocket is
government property,
and you're trespassing.
You can get
into real trouble here.
Are you listening to yourself?
You gotta figure out
what to do about the show.
- Are you listening
to yourself?
Remember when we used to talk
about doing
something fantastic?
Whatever happened to that?
- It's not that simple.
- Gotcha.
The Apollo rockets
weren't simple,
but in a way, they weren't
complicated either.
They operated in stages.
These first three stages
were just giant fuel tanks
that were discarded
as the rocket got
higher and higher
to shed payload
and to maximize efficiency
as the atmosphere thinned out.
Pretty brilliant, right?
Whoa.
- It is, Cam.
But to get to the moon,
the CS module had to detach
from these first three stages
and fire up its own engine.
This propelled the astronauts
almost a quarter
of a million miles-
ooh, watch out
for the asteroids-
and into the moon's orbit.
- Whoa.
That's a long way away.
- The view is so great
from out here, Cam.
Come see it.
- But how would I get there?
- So this is where you take
all your dates
to get murdered.
- Dude, I like girls.
Okay?
So this isn't a date.
You're just, like,
the only other normal person
in this town.
- This isn't bad and all.
Don't get me wrong.
I enjoy your company.
- Oh, how sweet of you.
- You're doing a new one?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
That's cheating.
- No, it's four!
- No, that doesn't exist.
- You said-I got it right!
It was four.
- It's pretty simple,
actually.
You just wanna cross-reference
the new item
with the museum database
to see if we've already
cataloged it or not.
- So since it's an engine,
we put it in which category?
- That would be propulsion.
Yep.
- Got it.
- Great.
Just tab through
and keep filling them in.
Let me know
if you have questions.
- You know,
I used to watch your show.
- Oh.
- They showed it
in class sometimes.
- Jeez.
That's embarrassing.
- Whatever happened to it?
- Oh, I haven't been involved
with it for years.
- Oh.
That's too bad.
- No, no, it's fine.
I had a lot of fun,
but we just weren't
really getting anywhere
with the show, so...
a lot of work
for a lot of dead ends.
How are you liking it here?
- I love it here.
This is, like, my dream job.
- Really?
- Totally.
- Wow.
This is your dream job?
- Of course, down the road,
I'd love to be at a national
museum or something,
but what about you?
- Um, studied
aerospace engineering
and mathematics
in grad school.
- I mean,
what did you wanna be
when you grew up?
- Um, you know, I don't think
I really ever chose one thing.
I just kind of wanted
to leave it open,
but I do remember
telling people
that I just wanted to do
something fantastic.
- That's amazing.
I love that.
- Well, it's...something.
- Hey, dude.
Uh, hi.
- Oh, is this your friend?
- Uh-huh.
- Well, it sure is a pleasure
to meet any friend of my son.
- Uh, yeah, you too.
I-I've heard so, um, little
about you, actually.
- Well, he is embarrassed
of me.
Uh, nice wheels, dude.
- Hey, nice pants.
- Uh, well, I mean,
dress code says
skirt or pants, so-
- No, I really mean it.
Some people are
too quick to judge.
Very progressive.
Feminism.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
For sure, man-no, I just-
I just don't do dresses-
- Okay.
Uh, bye, Dad.
- I-it was-
it was nice to meet you.
- Great to meet you.
See you after school.
- Yep.
- Why don't we ever go
to your house?
I mean,
your dad seems awesome.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- One of my photos
just got published
in "Metrobop Magazine."
- Nice.
- Was thinking you might want
to pose for me sometime.
- Yeah, sure.
- Cool.
- Dude, are you kidding me?
- What?
- "What?"
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe it's just because
she's the worst.
Dude, you can't be in one
of her stupid pictures.
- No, she's just insecure.
I'm sure she's nice
in there somewhere.
- Whose side are you on?
- Are you jealous?
- Jealous.
- Cameron,
I'm glad you're here.
As you've probably noticed,
the condition is declining.
Death has become
a very real possibility.
- Death?
- It happened on my birthday.
- What did?
- Does that mean
anything to you?
- To me?
- Yes.
No.
- Look, it's common
for anyone
at this later stage in life
to begin to examine
their past,
to look back
at their accomplishments
and scrutinize their regrets-
the big picture stuff.
Most of us have no issue
with this,
but for someone
with memory issues like this,
looking back is not so easy.
The brain is actually
clogging up
like plaque on teeth
without a brain toothbrush.
- So what do you
suggest we do?
- Antidepressants are
a temporary solution,
but frankly,
mental stimulation is key.
Now, the-the best way
to combat this kind of thing
is through sharing memories
with a loved one,
stories from the past.
It's all up here
in the mind.
You understand?
- Y-yeah.
- Good.
- You here
to give me a shower?
- No, the nurses give you
showers, not me.
- Well, then who are you?
- I'm Cameron.
You know me.
- Oh, Cameron.
Oh, of course.
Hello.
How are you?
- I'm good.
- Yeah.
- Good.
- How are you feeling?
- Oh, fine.
- Look, this is gonna
sound crazy,
but there was a rocket-
well, part of a rocket-
that fell in our backyard.
They thought it was Russian,
but it was-
- Yeah.
You told me this already.
- You remember that?
- Yeah.
Yeah, you-you told me this
the last time you visited.
- I know, but I didn't
think you'd remember.
- You know,
I used to fly rockets.
- Fly?
But you built rockets.
An engineer.
You didn't fly them.
- Well, not yet.
- Right.
Right, well-
I'm trying
to take this rocket,
build my own rocket.
I'm thinking maybe
you could tell me
what some of the pieces are.
You know, like,
do you know what this is?
- Yeah, it's the combine plate
for the intake mount.
- What about this one?
- That's the engine valve
for the nitrogen regulation.
Um...
- What-what would you say
if I...
took you home for a while?
You know where you are?
- Yeah, my room.
- That's right.
This is your old room.
- Uh-huh.
- You comfortable?
- Mm-hmm.
- Do you remember
some of this stuff?
- I recognize it.
- It's nice to have you here.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's been pretty exciting.
I've been busy.
- So you've done
a few episodes of the show?
- Two episodes.
They're still editing, but...
- That's amazing.
So when does the show air?
- Uh, tonight, Channel 34.
Uh, hopefully
you can all watch.
Uh, this is my son.
Say hello to everyone.
- Hi.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- This is Father Thomas.
- Welcome.
- Where were you?
- I'm sorry.
- Were you with that girl?
- No, sir.
I was working
on my application.
- So you've decided
on a branch, then.
- Air Force.
- Good, good.
Very respectable.
The next time you decide
to be late,
don't bother showing up
at all.
It's embarrassing.
- Hi.
- Oh, hey.
- How's it coming?
- Great.
See?
Got the LOX tank.
Fuel vent's a little burnt,
but still functional.
No idea how I'm gonna
get the thrust
to get this
off the ground, but...
well, do you got any ideas?
- Oh.
I don't actually know
that much about rockets,
but Dad would know.
- Yeah.
Uh, I-I'll get there.
It's just the slosh baffles.
And the heat diffuses somehow.
- You know,
you're a lot like him, my dad.
- Yeah.
I've heard.
I mean the good parts of him.
You're like the version of him
I wish he was.
- Oh.
Well, thanks.
- Yeah.
I mean...
I used to want to be him,
you know.
I used to dress like him
and act like him.
Well,
I never really knew my mom,
so I guess he was
the only real example I had.
So...
In any case, as I get older,
things are starting to-
well, it's complicated.
Yeah.
I know the feeling.
You wanna see the rocket?
- Right, so this was all part
of the airplane that came in.
- But this one's
a rocket engine.
- Yes, yes.
This one would be attached
to the service module.
So it's actually this guy
that propels the rocket
from Earth
all the way to the moon
and then back again
before it detaches
from the command module,
which is that little pod
with the astronauts in it
that splashed down
in the ocean.
- So this went to space?
- Not this one specifically,
'cause this was actually
a backup.
- So what happens
to the service module?
- Oh, those are normally
just cast off
until they burn up
in the atmosphere.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's kind of sad, isn't it?
I'll be right back.
- Holy.
You built this thing
in, like, a month?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
Is there gonna be enough room
for you in there?
- For what?
- Well, for you
to fit in there.
I mean,
it looks kind of small.
You're the one who's gonna be
in the rocket, right?
- Yeah.
- Are you excited?
- Yeah, uh, yes.
Of course I'm excited.
Thank you.
- Fantastic.
Now, they're gonna reach out
directly with the offer.
You have about two weeks
before she retires,
so you can
get things together here.
- Sure. Yeah.
- Okay.
I gotta go to work.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- So do you really think
this thing's gonna fly?
- Eventually. Eventually.
Testing it out today.
- What, really?
- Just a test of the boosters.
I gotta make sure
this thing doesn't blow up
when I turn it on.
This sucker is gonna prove
to the world
that I'm worth a damn.
Copley, here I come.
Hey, I'm about to do a test
of the booster.
You wanna check it out?
- Yeah.
- I'll grab your coat.
- Oh, okay.
- Okay.
Here we are.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen,
to a beautiful day
here in Fairview.
Not the most ideal conditions.
- No.
- But we are looking
at a simple test
of the boosters.
Hold that, my friend.
Here we go.
Ta-da!
- Whoa.
Oh.
All right.
Here we go.
♪ Duh, duh, duh,
duh, duh, duh ♪
Just a test to the booster,
but here we go.
Auxiliary power initiating.
Stand by.
- All right.
- Three, two, one.
- What?
- Wait-
Okay.
- What's going on?
- It's not working.
Oh, wow!
Uh, h-hold this.
- The universe is factual.
It's objective, study-able,
and concrete.
It has no emotions
and no feelings.
The universe is rational.
Chemistry.
Mathematics.
Biology.
Earth sciences.
Physics.
So come explore science
as we go "Above and Beyond."
What is an experiment?
An experiment
is a procedure carried out
to refute or validate
a hypothesis.
Experiments provide insight
into cause and effect
by demonstrating
what outcomes occur
when a particular factor
is manipulated.
- Cheers to that.
Thanks, Lin.
- It's just amazing.
They're finally seeing
your potential.
What's wrong?
I just-
I'm not sure
it's the right path for me.
You know, I think I was hoping
to transition into something
hands-on like the technicians
department or...
plus it's a two-hour commute
each way.
And I don't even know
where I'm gonna be living
once the divorce is finalized
in a couple months.
- But you said it yourself.
People wait their whole lives
for an opportunity like this.
- Yes.
Yes, I know.
I know.
- Are you worried
about Cameron?
- No.
I mean, I think he should know
before I commit-
- To be blunt,
he's really lost it.
He's been sleeping in your
condemned house for weeks.
It's not rational.
It'll be good for you
to get away from him.
Start fresh.
Anyways, I'm just-
I'm really happy for you.
You either take that job or...
go back
to the way things were.
Well, I think we need
another refill here.
Maybe some champagne...
Sneaking out?
- Nah, just going for a walk.
- Huh.
Usually, people use a door
for that kind of thing.
- I, uh, take it the test
didn't go so well, huh?
- Oh, it was a huge success.
Liquid oxygen froze
around the intake valve,
which built up pressure
until it popped
and sprayed everywhere.
Lit the garage on fire.
- Hm.
At Cornell,
I had published three articles
in the "Astrophysical Journal"
by the time I was 21.
Won the damn Crawford.
Now I'm stuck
building a DIY rocket
out of a hunk
of Apollo garbage
just to prove
I'm worth a damn.
I'm almost 50 years old.
Is that what I'm supposed
to be doing?
Jesus.
Einstein came up
with the Theory of Relativity
when he was 26.
You know what I'm gonna
be known for?
A failed children's
television show...
And a rocket
that didn't lift off.
It's kind of poetic, really.
Heed this warning:
do not grow old.
Huh.
- Hey, it's that woman again.
- Yeah.
I don't know
if she's following me or you.
- Entropy,
the gradual decaying of stuff.
Believe it or not, over time,
we're all headed
towards chaos.
The natural state
of the universe
is, in fact, chaos, not order.
- What are you doing awake?
- We can try to organize
our stuff and control it,
but in the end,
it will always find its way
back to chaos.
- Well, that sounds kind of
harsh, don't you think, Erin?
- Oh, it's just
maximum entropy, Cam.
It's science!
Good evening, madam.
- Shut up.
- Oh, hey.
- You good?
- Lookee what I got.
- What is this?
I mangled it a bit. Sorry.
"Darcy Penzone is having
a Halloween party."
That's stupid.
- Do you want to go with?
- No, definitely not.
Did she, like,
invite you or something?
- Are you jealous again?
- I mean, y-
kind of, yeah, I guess.
- Oh, I thought
I wasn't your type.
- No, I'm jealous
because she invited you
and not me.
- Huh.
Are you sure you're gay?
- What?
What-yeah.
Yes, I am.
I totally am.
- I mean, no judgment.
Just asking.
- I've never, uh-
I've never actually been
with a guy before, so that's-
yep, that's that.
- So...have you been
with a girl before?
- I made out with this girl
from Redding my freshman year.
Um, but it was like,
some older dudes dared us to
at this dumb
lacrosse party thing.
- Could be some fun.
- I mean,
what did you expect, though,
asking that question,
whether I wanted
to go to Darcy Penzone's
Halloween party?
- I figured it would be a no,
but of course I'm gonna ask.
- Wow, well,
that's very polite of you.
Um, but the answer
is still no.
- Mm-hmm.
- Why?
Because I hate her guts.
Like...
people wanna put you
in a box, you know,
like, a category and...
Like, I've tried
to do that too, but, um,
it just-
it just seems to make it
simpler for everyone else
and, like, way more
complicated for me.
And I try not to care
what they think, but I do.
I-I definitely do.
I just, um-
in the end, it's just easier
to go along with it all,
you know?
But I don't know if that's
how, like, I actually feel.
Like, I don't even know
if I have a preference.
Like, if that's even a thing.
I just, um...
still figuring it out
or whatever.
- Hm.
Well, I mean, I like to wear
girls' underwear sometimes.
- You do?
- Yeah.
So, see,
nothing is really that simple.
Plus, if it helps, I've never
been with anyone before.
So there's that.
- Really?
You?
I thought
you would've already.
- Why's that?
- Because.
Because you're...
cute.
- Wow.
- Shut up, dude.
- A bona fide compliment
from the bisexual in the room.
I mean,
you can't take it back.
- No, that was a-
- There's no take-backsies.
I guess you're right then.
It's just, uh-
it's not that simple,
is it, huh?
- Maybe it should be.
You know?
Simply put,
we don't fit in,
probably never will,
but that's okay.
It's all up here, right,
in the mind?
So-
- Cheers
to our abnormal future.
- Oh.
May it always be fantastic.
- Fantastic.
I like it.
No.
Nope. No.
There's no way
I'm spending my-
nay, our birthday,
what, at Darcy Penzone's
Halloween party?
No.
Because we...
should throw our own party.
A, um-
a fantastic party.
Well, go on.
- A more fantastic
Halloween party.
- Thanks.
- "Fantastic Halloween party"?
What does that even mean?
- It's, like,
totally over your head.
Don't worry.
- Are you going to this?
- Yeah.
I'm organizing it.
You should come.
I can't believe this.
Okay.
No one's gonna go
to your dykey party
because they're gonna
come to mine.
- Oh, I didn't know
that you were throwing
a dykey party too.
I'm sorry.
- You're just so funny.
- Thanks.
I thought it was funny.
- Well, it was worth a shot.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- What the hell happened
to our garage?
- It was, um...
- What is this, Cameron?
- I was building-
I was trying
to build a rocket.
- A rocket?
In the garage?
- Yeah.
But it clearly didn't work.
So-
- Cameron.
This is insane.
What are you
even talking about?
This-it's breaking the law.
- Since when did you care
about rules so much?
- Well, someone had to.
- Look, I'll fix it all back.
It's-
- Oh, really?
- Erin.
- I-I don't-
I just wanted to-
I came here to talk to you
about a job, Cameron.
I got a job offer
at the Wright-Patterson,
and I just wanted
to get your...
- Well, that's great.
- I don't know,
get your second opinion
or whatever.
I just wanted to talk to you.
But I can't
'cause I don't know
where you are.
- This is the second law
of thermodynamics,
and I bring this up
because I know
you might be thinking,
"Dr. Fuller,
this is a math class.
"Come on.
Why are we learning
about science?"
Well,
this law impacts statistics,
game theory,
systems, analytics,
and even parts of linguistics.
It is essential
for understanding
how things work
and even how people think.
But it's not as easy
to predict
as you might imagine.
All right, class.
Come on. Settle down.
- You really stepped
in there, huh?
- Yeah, well,
you probably would've
killed her if I didn't.
- That's a great point.
You okay?
- I don't even know
where to start.
What were you thinking?
- That those kids
were assholes.
I was sick of it.
- Look, maybe that wasn't
the best option.
- Yeah, sure.
- Sure?
This is going to be
on your permanent record,
and you have a 4.0.
For Christ's sakes,
you have your interview
with MIT next month.
Do you just wanna
ruin all of that?
I-I am trying to understand
what has gotten into you.
- You're blowing this
way out of proportion.
- Is it the new boy
that you've been dating?
- You don't even know him,
and no,
we're not-we're not dating.
- Okay, fine, not dating.
Is it the new boy
you have been sneaking out
at night to see?
- He-he's a real
good kid actually.
- Oh, is he?
Then I'm sure his father
is actually upset with him.
- God, this is bullshit.
- Don't use that language.
- No, I'll do whatever I want.
- I am not going to permit you
to hang out
with that boy anymore.
- They're just friends.
- You have no say
in this anymore, Cameron.
Really? When I leave,
do whatever you want.
- Leaving?
What the hell is that about?
- Apparently,
I'm the only one in this car
who's even remotely
rational anymore.
- Rational?
Is that what you've become?
That's what you call it,
is rational?
- That's enough.
- You're not rational.
- That is enough.
- How did you marry
this woman?
I mean, like, seriously,
all she ever does
is sit around and complain
like some old lady.
- Fuck you!
- So...
What happened?
- Nothing.
- Hm.
They don't send you home
for nothing.
- It was just a stupid fight.
- Is it the girl you've been
hanging out with?
- No, sir.
It's not her.
- Oh.
I don't want you hanging out
with that girl anymore.
Do you understand?
- Yes, sir.
- You're doing this
to yourself.
If I see you with that queer
one more time,
I'll kill you.
Let me try an experiment.
Say I take a rubber band
and I stretch it out
between my finger.
This creates
stored potential energy.
Now, really,
energy is the only thing
that can counteract...
The effects of entropy.
Now, let's take a look-
Thanks, buddy.
How you doing?
- I can't believe I said that.
Who does that?
What's happening, Cameron?
- Sometimes,
things just happen.
- It's not that simple.
- I think it might be,
actually.
- Want some?
- Yeah.
- So you're leaving?
- I got a job offer
at Wright-Patt.
- Wow.
Congratulations, yeah.
- I'm not gonna go.
- Why not?
- Because it's
someone else's dream.
- Um,
I'm-
I'm sorry about before.
- You have nothing
to be sorry for.
I'm the one
that needs to apologize.
I said something that
I so wish I could take back.
- I don't know what I'm doing.
- So what?
Who cares?
- Yeah.
- You are gonna be just fine.
You are intelligent
and so confident
and strong-willed
and one of the most
loyal people
on this Earth.
And yeah, there's gonna be
some ups and downs,
but I can tell you
that no matter
what you choose to do
or who you choose to be,
it'll be the right decision.
- Thanks.
Can I ask you something?
What did you wanna be
when you grew up?
What was your dream?
- Hey.
I, uh-
I nabbed it from the museum.
It's pretty cool, huh?
- What are you doing?
- Something fantastic.
Aw, Merry Christmas
to you too, Cam.
- Well,
it's not Christmas yet, Erin,
- Oh, but you were talking
about the north pole.
- It's Halloween.
- All right, well,
where's your costume then?
- Hey, I'm home.
- I think I'm pale
like a ghost.
Our planet is filled...
- Hello?
- With liquid molten metals.
- Ooh, spooky.
- It's my birthday, you know.
- Which turn our planet
into an enormous magnet.
But our planet
isn't the only thing
with a magnetic field.
Am I right, Erin?
- That's right, Cam.
The sun also has one.
And the sun's magnetic field
is much more powerful.
It can cause sunspots--
- Always leaving
this dang thing on.
- Television screen go fuzz-
- Hey, where is, everyone?
- Cameron is being
completely irrational.
And it seems
Erin has joined him.
- Well, you won't technically
have a display console,
but you know what?
Neither did John Glenn.
- John Glenn?
Never heard of him.
What are we gonna do
about propulsion?
- Oh, this thing
actually still had
a significant store
of liquid H2 in it.
- Sweet.
- Yeah.
I think it might be enough
to get you to the L point.
- It might be?
Well, that's a relief.
That is-it might be.
- Well, what are you gonna do?
Siphon gas out of the wagon?
It's gonna be fine.
- This is so crazy.
- Yeah.
- No, I agree with Cameron
on this one.
- Hi. Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday.
- Great.
Thanks.
Um, I'm decorating the house.
I'm having a Halloween party.
So obviously,
you're not invited.
Please don't come.
- Obviously.
Where's your witch costume?
- Um, yeah,
Darcy Penzone decided
to dress as a witch today too,
so now I am costume-less.
- Sorry.
What are you gonna do?
- I was gonna
raid your closet.
- Sure.
Yes, of course.
You could just go as yourself.
- No.
- She's like a bundle
of positivity.
What about over here?
- You made it.
- A dress?
- Oh, well, I mean, sort of.
It's my worst nightmare,
a housewife.
- Yeah. I mean, yeah,
you look horrific.
- Wow.
Thank you.
- I mean, fantastic.
- It's for you.
Come on, let's, uh,
find you a costume.
Party's about to start.
- You have an extra?
- Honey, where is everyone?
I-I thought the party
started at eight.
- Okay.
I think this is ready to go.
Come on.
Let's get it outside.
Cameron.
- Open your eyes.
- Cameron.
- Yeah.
- Are you sure
you wanna do this?
- The launch isn't
gonna happen, okay?
It's not gonna work.
It didn't work.
I can't launch a rocket
from our garage.
It's-
- Not that simple.
Why do you always
tell yourself that?
- I just wanted
to do something...
you know.
- Do you know what that is?
- I know
what a Moebius strip is.
- It only has one side.
Yeah.
It's a mathematical paradox.
- It's not that simple.
- Oh, it might be.
Who knows?
- It happened on my birthday.
- What did?
- Cameron.
You remember me?
- Does that mean
anything to you?
- Can I come to your
stupid party or whatever?
- Under one condition:
you take our photo.
- Whatever.
Fine.
Out here.
- It's all up here
in the mind.
You understand?
- I said, can you open
your eyes for me, Cameron?
You're looking good.
Do you know who I am?
Cameron.
- I might.
- Do you recognize
any of this stuff?
Here.
Do you know who this is?
That's you, Cameron.
Over 50 years ago.
And that's me.
Do you recognize this photo?
- Sam.
- Sam?
- Yeah.
- Sam isn't in this picture.
He was stillborn.
Remember?
- Swiss mathematician
Daniel Bernoulli...
We never knew
what he would look like.
- The brain is actually
clogging up
like plaque on teeth
without a brain toothbrush.
- I think I know
what's happening.
- I think you do too.
- I'm scared.
- I'm here.
I'll always be here.
I show you these things
every day.
How we met,
our life together.
This week's
scientific discovery is...
Rockets!
- Over there, there's-there's
somebody over there for you.
Do you know who I am?
Erin.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hi, Cam.
You've been here
a few weeks now.
Oh.
Your father's car.
Do you remember your father?
He tried to run you over
at our Halloween party.
Do you remember that?
Cameron?
- This is the end, isn't it?
- Don't worry. Don't worry.
The doctor's on his way.
- It's about to happen.
- What is?
- The launch.
The launch.
It's about to happen.
- No, there-
there was no rocket launch.
I told you that, remember?
- Time is running out, Erin.
We have to go.
Help me.
- I'm sorry.
- Help me.
I can't. I can't.
- With the rocket.
- Oh, Cameron.
- The rocket.
- The rocket-
The rocket is coming.
It's coming.
Come on! Cameron, hurry up.
The countdown has started.
Don't you worry, love.
I'll make sure
it's there for you.
- Thank you.
- Ma'am, I'm sorry.
You can't go with him.
- Oh, I'm going with him.
- Two seats?
- Yeah. I'm coming with you.
- But you don't have a suit.
- I'll be okay.
- Close your eyes.
- Go ahead.
Most people think
it's just a black abyss,
but in fact,
the universe appears.
- Look closely.
Do you see it?
- It's faint, but...
it's there if you concentrate.
- It's probably colorful
and shifting.
- It's evolving and growing.
Do you see it?
- What you're seeing
is entirely unique to you.
- It's a kind of fingerprint,
your own personal universe.
- I used to look up to you.
I used to act like you,
dress like you.
I wanted to be you.
- I know.
- Then why did you do it?
- You did this to yourself.
- That's not true.
Things are gonna be
different this time.
Now, open your eyes.