♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪
FOR A SECOND I DIDN'T THINK
YOU WERE GOING TO SHOW.
I ALWAYS TRY TO
KEEP MY APPOINTMENTS.
SO, WHAT'CHA GOT FOR ME?
OH BEAUTY. BEAUTY.
YOU LIKE, HUH?
I LIKE.
GOT A LITTLE BONUS FOR YOU.
ALL RIGHT! ALL RIGHT!
SURPRISE.
CHANCE!!
WORM, ASH.
DON'T YOU GUYS KNOW
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO PLAY WITH GUNS?
FUCK YOU IN THE NECK, CHANCE.
ALL RIGHT KIDS,
YOU KNOW THE DRILL.
YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT.YOU GIVE UP--
[GUNSHOTS]
♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪
[EXPLOSION]
♪ MUSIC ♪
SHIT!
[CHAIN RATTLE]
[BACKGROUND MUSIC]
[RUNNING FOOTSTEPS]
[DOOR BANG]
[BACKGROUND MUSIC]
READY?
HIT IT.
[THUD]
[BACKGROUND MUSIC]
[BEEPING]
[EXPLOSION]
[BACKGROUND MUSIC]
[ELEVATOR]
[CHEERING & APPLAUSE]
COP CHANCE,
I'D HAVE TO BE IN YOUR SHOES.
WORDS OUT ON THE STREET;
YOU BEEN A BAD BOY,
JON CHANCE.
I HEAR YOU
BLEW UP ANOTHER CASE.
YEAH, CAPTAIN'S
IN A REAL NASTY MOOD.
HEY CHANCE,
I HEAR THE CAPTAIN'S ABOUT
TO MAKE YOUR DAY.
I HEARD YOU MIGHT BE
REASSIGNED TO CROSSING GUARD
AT THE BURGER HOP.
MAKE MINE A DOUBLE CHEESE,
CHANCE. HOLD YOUR PICKLE.
GOOD LUCK HOTSHOT.
WAY TO GO CHANCE.
YO' MAMAS.
[CROWD WOO]
[LAUGHTER]
I DON'T GIVE A SHIT
ABOUT YOUR PERSONAL PROBLEMS!
SIR?
SIT DOWN.
I JUST WANT THAT GODDAMN
MANIAC OFF THAT ROOF.
HE'S GOT A GUN?
YOU'VE GOT A GUN!
HE USES HIS,
YOU USE YOURS.
GOT IT?
SIT DOWN.
I AM SITTING.
DON'T YOU EVER GET TIRED
OF THIS SHIT DETECTIVE?
DOING MY JOB?
THIS WAS NOT
YOUR GODDAMN JOB.
MY GOD JON. NO BACKUP,
THREE DEAD BODIES,
AN EXPLOSION CAUSING
$30, 000 IN DAMAGE
TO THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
NOT TO MENTION THE
MEDICAL EXPENSES OF A
MILD CONCUSSION TO A CITIZEN
FIVE BLOCKS AWAY?
JUST CUT TO THE CHASE CAPTAIN.
YOUR SUSPENDED...AGAIN.
PENDING THE DECISION
OF A REVIEW BOARD AND
THE IAD INVESTIGATION.
YOU MAY NOT BEAT THIS ONE JON,
YOU'VE MADE A LOT OF ENEMIES
WITH YOUR FREE-WHEELING STYLE,
AND SOME OF THOSE
ARE ON THAT BOARD.
HAVE A NICE DAY.
SHIT!
[PHONE RINGING]
HEY, CHANCE.
WHAT?
YOU KNOW TERRY KINGSLEY
DON'T YOU?
WHY?
SOMEBODY RIPPED HIM OFF
LAST NIGHT,
FOR A WHOLE BUNCH OF DIAMONDS.
SOMEBODY WANTS TO
DIE REAL BAD.
WHO'D BE THAT STUPID?
I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS HOPING MAYBE
YOU COULD TELL ME.
SORRY, I CAN'T HELP YOU RILEY.
I' M NOT A COP.
WHAT? AGAIN?
YEAH.
[LAUGHING]
OH JESUS!
[SPEAKING IN FILIPINO]
OKAY OKAY, SLOW DOWN.
GIVE IT TO ME IN ENGLISH.
ENGLISH, GO BACK
TO THE BEGINNING.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT WENT BLANK.
WHAT THE HELL'S
THE MATTER WITH YOU PEOPLE?
WHY CAN'T I GET
INTO MY OWN OFFICE?
YOU KNOW MISTER KINGSLEY,
YOU'RE A VERY
INTERESTING MAN.
A VARIETY OF BUSINESSES:
RESTAURANTS, FURNITURE,
PROSTITUTION, GUNRUNNING,
DRUGS.
DID I LEAVE ANYTHING OUT?
THOSE WERE ARRESTS,
NOT CONVICTIONS.
BRIBING A JUROR
GOES A LONG WAY.
YOU KNOW RILEY,
I'M THE VICTIM HERE,
SO DON'T BUST MY BALLS.
NOW I HAD A MILLION SIX,
IN LEGALLY PURCHASED,
REGISTERED CUT DIAMONDS
IN THAT SAFE,
AND I WANT THEM BACK.
IF YOU CAN'T DO IT YOUR WAY,
I'M GOING TO DO IT MINE.
I ASSURE YOU MISTER KINGSLEY,
THE LAPD WILL DO EVERYTHING
IN ITS POWER TO SEE THAT
YOU GET YOUR PROPERTY BACK.
[PHONE RINGING]
♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE BABE.
COME ON SWEETHEART,
WE'RE ALREADY LATE.
I'M COMING.
HONEY, WE'RE GONNA BE LATE.
LISTEN, IF YOU'RE GOING
TO STOP BY THE OFFICE
ON THE WAY BACK,
I'M GOING TO TAKE MY CAR, OKAY?
OKAY?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
LET'S GO BABY.
♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪
JON LOUROY CHANCE,
DID WE DO IT WITH THAT
DAMN THING UNDER THE PILLOW?
YEAH, BUT YOU DIDN'T KNOW IT.
YEAH, WELL,
I HAD OTHER THINGS ON MY MIND.
WHY DON'T YOU GET YOURSELF
SOME SLEEP AND I'LL TALK
TO YOU LATER, HUH?
AND WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO A VERY IMPORTANT MEETING,
AND NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
WELL, EXCUSE ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S WORSE,
BEING IN LOVE WITH A COP
OR BEING MARRIED TO A COP.
YOU MAY NEVER KNOW.
OH YEAH?
YEAH.
SO, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT TIME YOU'LL BE BACK?
EVENTUALLY.
YEAH, RIGHT.
GOOD JOB GOD.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
OKAY PEOPLE,
LET'S GET STARTED.
LET'S GET A MEETING GOING HERE.
LET'S ROCK AND ROLL.
MY NAME IS ANN AND
I AM A RECOVERING ALCOHOLIC.
HI ANN.
HI.
ANY OTHER ALCOHOLICS
PRESENT TODAY?
WELCOME.
YOU ARE IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
IT IS A CUSTOM IN THIS MEETING
AS IT IS IN MOST MEETINGS
TO CELEBRATE 365 DAYS
OF CONTINUOUS SOBRIETY.
WE DO HAVE ONE BIRTHDAY TODAY
AND THAT IS FOR ZACH.
ZACH, COME ON UP.
[APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU.
MY NAME IS ZACH AND
I'M A RECOVERING ALCOHOLIC.
HI, ZACH!
HI.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
I'M NOT TOO GOOD
ON GIVING SPEECHES..
I DON'T DESERVE THIS...
I REALLY DON'T.
I THINK WE ALL DO.
GOD ONLY KNOWS I'VE BEEN
BATTLING THAT BOTTLE
LONG ENOUGH.
I LOST MY WIFE OVER IT,
I LOST MY JOB,
AND I THINK MORE THAN ANYTHING,
I LOST MY SELF-RESPECT.
I COULDN'T HAVE DONE IT
WITHOUT YOUR SUPPORT.
I COULDN'T HAVE LASTED A DAY.
I MEAN THAT.
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST SIT DOWN
BEFORE I START
MUMBLING UP HERE.
BUT I WANT TO THANK YOU FOR
YOUR SUPPORT AND YOUR HELP,
AND I THINK THAT YOU SHOULD
CONGRATULATE YOURSELVES.
THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
THANKS A LOT.
WAY TO GO ZACH.
ALL RIGHT SPORT.
YOU HANG IN THERE,
HUH?
OKAY.
SEE YOU LATER.
CONGRATULATIONS BUDDY PAL.
HOW YOU DOING JON?
HOW'D YOU FIND OUT ABOUT THIS?
OH YOU KNOW,
A LITTLE DETECTIVE WORK.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY COP
AROUND HERE TODAY.
HOW'S IT GOING MONA?
HI JON.
THANKS FOR COMING.
YOU KNOW,
YOU MUST BE REAL PROUD OF HIM.
OH, I AM. VERY.
HEY YOU KNOW,
MAYBE IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO
CAME BACK TO THE FORCE.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NOW HE QUIT DRINKING AND
HE'S THROUGH BEING A COP.
AND WHAT ABOUT YOU MISTER
"I'LL BE SINGLE UNTIL
THE DAY I DIE" CHANCE?
YOU GOT A STEADY GIRL YET?
WELL...
WHY DON'T YOU COME OVER FOR
DINNER NEXT FRIDAY NIGHT
AND I'LL INVITE SHELLY,
OUR NEXT DOOR NEIGHBOR.
WOULD YOU QUIT
BEING MATCHMAKER?
SHE IS YOUR KIND OF
RIGHT THOUGH JON.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL LEAVE YOU ALONE FOR NOW.
BUT JUST FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
LISTEN,
YOU GONNA BE OKAY GOING HOME?
OF COURSE I WILL.
YOU CALL ME LATER?
YOU GOT IT.
BE CAREFUL.
BYE.
BYE BYE.
SEE YOU LATER MONA.
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD BUDDY.
MONA.
LOOKS LIKE YOU GOT YOURSELF
A REAL GOOD LADY
THERE BUDDY PAL.
SHE'S A GOOD LADY.
SHE'S BEEN GOOD FOR ME.
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD JONNY.
DON'T CALL ME JONNY.
YOU ON THE DEPARTMENT
THIS WEEK?
NO.
I HAD ANOTHER DISAGREEMENT
ABOUT POLICY...AGAIN.
WHO'D YOU KILL THIS TIME?
THESE THREE LOW-LIVES
TRIED TO TAKE ME OUT.
DEFENDING YOURSELF?
NO BACK UP.
PROBABLY TURNED THE PLACE
INTO WORLD WAR III, DIDN'T YOU?
YEAH.
[LAUGHTER]
LIKE THE OLD DAYS.
GOOD OLD TIMES MAN. TELL ME,
WHAT'VE YOU BEEN DOING SINCE
YOU LEFT THE DEPARTMENT?
GOT IN THE CAR BUSINESS.
REALLY.
I DON'T LIKE IT TOO MUCH
BUT THE PAY AIN'T BAD.
IT'S A JOB.
YEAH.
I'M REALLY PROUD OF YOU MAN.
YOU BEAT IT.
I KNEW YOU COULD.
IT'S NOT EASY.
BUT...YOU DID IT.
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD JONNY.
YOU TOO MAN.
AND QUIT CALLING ME JONNY.
[LAUGHING]
ZACH,
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR
FIRST YEAR BUDDY.
WAY TO GO!
YEAH, THANKS ALVIN.
NOW, WHAT ABOUT MY MONEY,
HUH?
COME ON MAN,
WHAT ABOUT THE JOB?
I THOUGHT THIS WAS ABOUT A JOB.
IT IS, BUT FIRST
MY MONEY ZACH.
COME ON, A HUNDRED BUCKS.
LET'S GO.
YOU MAKE ME SICK ALVIN.
THIS IS ALL I GOT.
TAKE THE REST
OUT OF MY NEXT CHECK.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU ZACH.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU.
I MEAN, I'M SITTING THERE
WITH THREE QUEENS UP
AND YOU'RE BLUFFING WITH SHIT?
COME ON. WHEN WILL YOU LEARN,
HUH?
WHAT ABOUT THE JOB?
YEAH.
IT'S THIS RED BARRACUDA HERE
OUT ON WHEATON ROAD, ALRIGHT?
HERE'S THE LICENSE.
DO ME A FAVOR ZACH,
TRY NOT TO FUCK THIS UP, HUH?
YEAH, DO ME A FAVOR.
BUY YOURSELF A SET OF LIFTS.
♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪
YEAH, UH-HUH. YEAH. YEAH.
HE JUST CAME IN.
GREAT. OKAY, LATER.
SO WHERE'D YOU PUT IT?
UNDER THE SPARE,
JUST LIKE HE SAID.
YOU THINK IT'S SAFE?
YEAH, SURE.
NO SWEAT.
YOUR DEAL.
ALRIGHT.
♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪
OKAY, TRY NOT TO FUCK THIS UP.
B-I-N-G-O...BINGO.
[CAR ENGINE]
WHAT THE--
[GUNSHOT]
ALVIN! ALVIN!
[GUNSHOTS]
SHIT!
THOSE SON OF BITCHES
HAD GUNS OUT THERE AND
THEY WERE SHOOTING ME!
HOW DARE YOU SEND ME OUT TO
PICK UP A CAR WHERE
THERE'S GUNS GODDAMMIT?
LISTEN, I COULD HAVE
GOT SHOT DOWN,
THERE GODDAMMIT!
YOU HEAR ME?
I REPO CARS
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
YOU DON'T PAY ME ENOUGH
GODDAMN MONEY
TO DUCK BULLETS.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
NOW, I WANT YOU
TO CUT ME A CHECK.
RIGHT NOW.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
JUST AS SOON AS YOU BRING ME
THE CAR ZACH, THAT I WANT.
WHAT IN THE HELL DOES THAT
LOOK LIKE OUT THERE?
HEY EINSTEIN, LISTEN.
CHECK IT OUT.
THERE'S NO WINDSHIELD,
THERE'S NO BACK WINDOW,
THE SEATS ARE ALL SHOT
TO SHIT ZACH.
SO WHAT?
LOOK, BEETLE BRAIN.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO
GIVE ME DICK FOR THAT CAR
AT THE DEALERS.
WHEN DO I GET MY MONEY?
ZACH, BABE,
YOU KNOW THE ROUTINE.
I GOT TO TAKE THE CAR
OVER TO K&K AUTO BODY.
I GOT TO GET IT REPAIRED.
THEN I GOT TO TAKE IT
OVER TO THE DEALER,
THEN THEY'RE GONNA
CUT ME A CHECK.
THEN I GO OVER TO THE BANK.
I MAKE SURE THE CHECK'S GOOD.
THEN I COME BACK
AND I CUT YOU A CHECK.
AND THEN YOU GOT YOUR MONEY.
HEY ZACH, IT'S OUT OF
MY FUCKING HANDS!
YOU KNOW THE ROUTINE.
YOU'RE A PIECE OF WORK.
I'VE LEARNED TO
INVEST MY MONEY.
I BOUGHT THIS HARLEY-DAVIDSON
FROM SOME GUY NAMED MIKE JONES.
IT'S A CLASSIC.
AND WOMAN?
OH SO MANY WOMAN.
I TELL THEM LIES ABOUT ME
BEING ON THE RESERVATION.
BEING SOMEBODY BIG.
I TELL THEM MY NAME IS
BIG CHIEF IRON DICK.
OH YEAH,
THAT'S MY LOVE NAME.
LOVE NAME.
YOU SEE DUDE,
A WOMAN IS LIKE THE MOTORCYCLE.
YOU MUST LEARN TO RIDE HER.
THEN YOU SIT INTO THE SADDLE.
THEN YOU MUST LEARN TO
THROTTLE HER NICE AND EASY.
REV HER HARD AND FAST.
WHUHH!
AND THEN OFF INTO THE SUNSET.
IT WORKS EVERY TIME CHANCE.
SANDRA'S MAKING BURGERS.
BOTH YOU AND YOUR FRIEND
CAN COME OVER.
THAT'S IF YOU'RE HUNGRY.
MY FRIEND?
YEAH, CHIEF IRON DICK.
[LAUGHTER]
[DOG BARKING]
THIS CITY LIFE,
I'M BEGINNING TO LIKE IT.
ONCE YOU KNOW YOUR WAY,
IT ALL FALLS TOGETHER,
LIKE A KID'S PUZZLE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
OKAY CHANCE,
ALL DAY I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO MAKE YOU HAPPY.
I SMILE, YOU'RE SAD.
YOU GOT SOME HEAVY THINGS
ON YOUR MIND.
WHAT'S UP?
LIFE.
LIFE?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
DON'T MIND ME BEAR.
I'M JUST TRIPPING
WITHOUT MY LUGGAGE.
I GOT SUSPENDED MAN. AGAIN.
SOUNDS PRETTY SERIOUS.
COULD BE. I'LL LIVE.
I'M PRETTY TOUGH GUY
WHEN I HAVE TO BE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
ANYTHING I CAN DO TO HELP YOU?
SURE. BE MY FRIEND.
I MIGHT NEED ONE.
ALWAYS.
I GOTTA GO NOW.
LATER ALLIGATOR.
SANDRA.
LATER BEAR.
HEY,
DON'T BE A STRANGER, OKAY?
♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪
HEY ALVIN, HOW'RE YOU DOING?
FUCK YOU RAY.
LISTEN, I NEED THIS CAR FIXED.
PRONTO MAN.
NOT TONIGHT MAN. TOO LATE.
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING.
FUCK YOU RAY.
WAIT UP MAN,
I'LL GIVE YOU A RIDE HOME.
DETECTIVE RILEY.
YEAH.
WE GOT A PROBLEM.
AND UH,
WHAT'S THAT?
THE BARRACUDA WAS RIPPED OFF.
I'M SORRY, COULD YOU, UH,
COULD YOU REPEAT THAT PLEASE?
SAID SOME GODDAMN FAT CLOWN
RIPPED OFF THE BARRACUDA.
I SEE. I'LL LOOK INTO IT.
THANK YOU FOR CALLING.
OH BOY IS HE PISSED.
[PHONE RINGING]
YOU'RE ON.
JONNY, IT'S ZACH.
HEY ZACH, WHAT'S UP?
HEY, CAN YOU DO ME
A FAVOR PAL?
I NEED YOU TO
DROP ME OFF MY CAR.
I LEFT IT OUT AT A JOB.
SURE.
I GOT NOTHING ELSE HAPPENING
AROUND HERE RIGHT NOW.
YOU DON'T?
MONA?
YES ZACH.
HONEY,
CAN YOU DROP ME OFF
AT THE OFFICE?
SURE.
I'LL BE AT THE
END OF ELLIS WAY.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE THAT'S AT?
SANDRA, SANDRA,
I'VE GOT TO HELP A FRIEND.
OH NO YOU DON'T!
I'VE GOT BETTER THINGS
FOR YOU TO DO.
I MIGHT BE LATE.
OKAY.
THANKS A LOT JONNY. BYE.
♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪
SO TELL ME NOW,
WHY DID YOU LEAVE YOUR CAR?
REMEMBER THE OTHER DAY
WHEN I TOLD YOU
I WAS IN THE AUTO BUSINESS?
YEAH.
WELL, I'M A REPO MAN.
I POPPED ONE THE OTHER DAY
AND THESE GUYS
STARTED SHOOTING AT ME.
SHOOTING.
THAT'S WHY I ASKED YOU
TO TAKE ME BACK IN CASE
THEY SAW ME.
AND JUST WHAT THE HELL DO
YOU THINK I COULD DO ABOUT IT?
YOU'RE THE BEST BACKUP MAN
A GUY COULD WANT.
I TURNED IN MY GUN, REMEMBER?
COME ON JONNY,
YOU NEVER TURN IN
ALL YOUR GUNS.
DON'T CALL ME JONNY.
♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪
THANKS FOR BRINGING ME UP JON.
IT'S NO PROBLEM.
YOU WANT ME TO
WAIT AROUND HERE?
NO, I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
YEAH?
I DON'T SEE ANYBODY AROUND.
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
I MEAN, WHAT IF THESE SHOOTERS
WHAT IF THEY SHOW BACK UP?
I'M OKAY. YOU GO AHEAD.
YEAH?
YEAH. THANKS BUDDY PAL.
OKAY PAL, WHERE IS IT?
WHERE'S WHAT?
MY CAR MAN!
WHERE'S MY FUCKING CAR!
LOOK SPORT, ALL I DO IS REPO.
WELL, YOU REPOED
THE WRONG ONE.
NOW, WHERE THE FUCK IS IT?
UP YOUR ASS.
NOW KINDLY DROP THE GUN
BEFORE I MAKE A MESS
OUT OF YOUR HEAD.
YEAH?
WHAT IF I KILL THIS ASSHOLE
RIGHT NOW?
THEN THERE WILL BE
TWO DEAD BODIES FOR
THE CORONER TO DEAL WITH.
MAKE YOUR CHOICE.
NOW. NEXT TIME,
MAKE YOUR PAYMENTS ON TIME.
HAVE A NICE DAY.
THIS AIN'T OVER MAN,
NOT BY A LONG SHOT.
SON OF A BITCH.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
[GUNSHOT]
GO! LET'S GO!
GODDAMMIT GO!
SHIT!
NOW WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS ALL ABOUT?
HEY LOOK GODDAMMIT!
I TOLD YOU ALL I DID
WAS REPO A CAR.
A GODDAMN ROLLING WITH THAT.
YEAH? WELL,
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT THAT
CAR THAT'S WORTH
KILLING PEOPLE FOR.
WHERE'S THE CAR?
ALVIN TOOK IT OVER TO K&K
AUTO BODY TO HAVE THE GODDAMN
BULLET HOLES TAKEN OUT OF IT.
I WANT TO SEE THAT CAR NOW!
WELL, GO OVER TO ALAMEDA
AND TAKE A LOOK AT IT.
YEAH RIGHT.
DON'T FORGET TO CALL ME
WHEN YOU GET THERE.
HEY.
CAN I HELP YOU?
YEAH. I'M A FRIEND
OF ZACHERY CHAMBERLAIN'S,
FROM THE FORCE.
JON CHANCE.
YOU A COP?
NO, NOT THIS WEEK. HIS BOSS,
HE BROUGHT IN AN OLD CAR HERE?
WHERE IS THAT?
'CUDA. IT'S IN THE BACK.
HAVEN'T STARTED ON THAT YET.
DO YOU MIND IF I
HAVE A LOOK AT IT?
SURE. COME ON,
I'LL GIVE YOU A HAND.
WELL, HERE SHE IS.
THAT'S MY BABY.
WELL, SOMEBODY SURE
SHOT THIS TO SHIT.
YEAH, YOU KNOW IT.
WELL, YOU CAN'T JUDGE
A CAR BY ITS PAINT JOB.
YEAH.
DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
THERE AIN'T NOTHING THERE.
YOU SEE ANYTHING?
NOPE.
WELL, AIN'T NOTHING
BACK THERE.
I DON'T GET IT.
THERE'S NOTHING IN THIS CAR
WORTH KILLING FOR.
SOMEBODY IS DEAD?
NOT YET.
BUT I HAVE A HABIT OF BEING
AROUND DEAD BODIES.
I GOTTA GET BACK TO WORK.
♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪
YOU ALVIN FINCKLE?
YEAH, WHO'S ASKING?
RILEY, LAPD.
YOU RECENTLY REPO
A 1968 BARRACUDA,
LICENSE NUMBER UOF171?
BARRACUDA. YEAH,
WE GOT THE BARRACUDA.
YOU KNOW WHERE IT IS?
IT'S OVER AT K&K AUTO BODY
ON ALAMEDA.
GOT SOME MINOR DAMAGE TO IT.
GOOD.
WE'RE GOING TO SEND
A COUPLE OF PEOPLE OVER FOR IT.
CALL THE DEALER,
TELL HIM WE'RE IMPOUNDING.
HEY DICK TRACY,
HOW ABOUT MY RECOVERY FEE, HUH?
WE'LL SEND YOU A RECEIPT.
WHAT THE HELL ARE
YOU DOING HERE RILEY?
THAT'S NONE OF
YOUR BUSINESS CHANCE,
YOU'RE ON SUSPENSION.
NOW, WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
THAT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
I'M ASKING OFFICIALLY.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M TRYING TO FIND OUT ABOUT
THE CAR THAT ZACH REPOED.
NOW YOU SEE?
WE DO HAVE SOMETHING IN COMMON.
THAT CAR IS WANTED
IN CONNECTION WITH
THE KINGSLEY ROBBERY.
YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THAT?
NO.
THEN WHY THE INTEREST
IN THE CAR?
LOOK,
THE PEOPLE THAT ZACH TOOK
THE CAR FROM TRIED TO KILL HIM
WHEN HE GRABBED IT.
NOW, MAYBE THAT'S YOUR THIEVES.
UH-HUH, NO. NO,
I THINK WE SHOULD...I THINK
WE SHOULD TAKE A TRIP
DOWNTOWN AND TALK ABOUT THIS.
BULLSHIT!
OKAY, LET'S MAKE IT OFFICIAL.
YOU ARE UNDER ARREST
FOR SUSPICION OF GRAND LARCENY.
YOU'RE GOING TO RESIST, I HOPE?
NO, BUT I AIN'T GONNA FORGET.
YEAH. PUT YOUR HANDS BEHIND
YOUR BACK CHANCE.
YOU KNOW THE ROUTINE.
COME ON.
COME ON. COME ON.
HEY JONNY! JONNY,
I'LL GET YOU OUT OF THIS.
YOU KNOW CHANCE,
YOU AND YOUR PARTNER
CHAMBERLAIN ARE
IN A LOT OF TROUBLE.
NOW, IF YOU TALK TO ME...
I JUS MIGHT BE ABLE
TO SAVE YOUR LIFE.
GET TO THE GODDAMN POINT.
THE CAR THAT CHAMBERLAIN
POPPED IS WANTED IN
CONNECTION WITH THE
KINGSLEY DIAMOND ROBBERY.
NOW, THE ONLY TWO PEOPLE
THAT SEEMED TO BE INTERESTED
IN THAT ARE YOU
AND CHAMBERLAIN.
WHAT ABOUT THE GUY
HE TOOK IT FROM?
THE CAR WAS STOLEN
THE NIGHT OF THE THEFT.
HOW CONVENIENT.
RIGHT NOW,
MY TWO BEST SUSPECTS
ARE YOU TWO.
THAT'S HORSESHIT
AND YOU KNOW IT.
NO, IT FITS.
LOOK, YOU'RE ON SUSPENSION,
YOU MIGHT LOSE YOUR BADGE.
CHAMBERLAIN?
HE GETS BUSTED OUT
FOR DRINKING.
NOW YOU USED TO BE PARTNERS,
SO...YOU STEAL THE CAR,
YOU POP THE DIAMONDS.
YOU STASH THE DIAMONDS
IN THE CAR.
YOU REPO THE CAR BACK
ALL LEGAL LIKE AND
TAKE OUT THE DIAMONDS,
ZIP, BAM, BOOM,
LIKE THAT, YOU'RE OFF TO RIO.
JONNY, I LOVE IT.
WHERE ARE THE DIAMONDS JON?
RILEY,
DO YOU HAVE TO PRACTICE
OR DOES STUPIDITY
JUST RUN IN YOUR FAMILY?
[PHONE RINGING]
RILEY.
THANK YOU.
BURKE, BOOK HIM.
FOR WHAT?
YOUR LITTLE ESCAPADE
OUT ON WHEATON ROAD.
SEEMS THAT MISTER BOWEN
WANTS TO PRESS A FEW CHARGES.
TRESPASSING, ATTEMPTED ASSAULT,
ASSAULT, ASSAULT WITH A DEADLY
WEAPON, GRAND THEFT AUTO,
AND SUSPICION OF GRAND LARCENY.
DID I LEAVE ANYTHING OUT?
YEAH. ASSAULTING AN ASSHOLE.
MR. KINGSLEY,
THAT COP RILEY JUST CALLED.
HE THINKS HE'S GOT THE GUY
WHO RIPPED OFF YOUR DIAMONDS.
AND WHO IS IT?
HE ARRESTED A COP
BY THE NAME OF CHANCE.
CHANCE?
DID THEY FIND THE STONES?
NO SIR.
THEY JUST--
I DON'T CARE WHAT THEY DID!
I WANT THE STONES.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND? GOOD.
NOW...CALL THIS RILEY
AND YOU TELL HIM THAT
I WANT MY STONES BACK.
AND I REALLY DON'T CARE
HOW HE GETS THEM.
CHANCE WON'T TELL
THEM ANYTHING.
WELL THEN, WE'RE GOING TO
GIVE DETECTIVE RILEY SOME HELP.
MILO, GO BAIL OUT CHANCE
AND BRING HIM HERE.
WHAT IF HE DOESN'T WANNA COME?
PERSUADE HIM.
ZACH, ZACH LISTEN.
I'M TELLING YOU MAN,
YOUR COP FRIEND,
HE CAN STEW IN HIS OWN JUICE
FOR ALL I CARE.
I'M NOT YOUR BROTHER'S KEEPER.
LISTEN ALVIN,
I'M ASKING YOU
FOR A LITTLE HELP.
MY FRIEND'S IN TROUBLE,
THAT'S ALL.
YEAH?
YEAH.
SO WHAT?
SO WHAT?!
LISTEN,
YOU AND YOUR COP FRIEND,
YOU COST ME THAT RECOVERY
FEE ON THAT BARRACUDA.
AND NOW YOU WANT ME
TO GO AND BAIL HIM OUT?
IN TWO WORDS ZACH, FUCK YOU!
HOW ABOUT FUCK YOU!
I'VE HAD IT WITH YOUR SMART
MOUTH AND YOUR BULLSHIT,
YOU LITTLE SON OF A BITCH!
YOU'RE GONNA GIMME THAT MONEY
FOR HIS BAIL RIGHT NOW.
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
OR I'LL RIP YOUR
GODDAMN LUNGS OUT.
YEAH. SURE ZACH.
I DIDN'T KNOW HE MEANT
SO MUCH TO YOU.
THANKS ALVIN.
HEY, DON'T I KNOW YOU?
I DON'T THINK SO.
YEAH, I DO.
YOU'RE NAME IS CHANCE.
YOU'RE A FUCKING COP.
YOU BUSTED A BUDDY OF MINE
A WHILE BACK, BOBBY.
YEAH. HEY FELLAS,
WE GOT A FUCKING COP
IN OUR CELL.
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS
TO A COP IN JAIL, CHANCE?
YEAH,
I WOULD IMAGINE
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
ANYBODY ELSE?
GETTING TO KNOW YOUR
CELLMATES CHANCE?
YEAH.
WE WERE JUST DISCUSSING
OVERCROWDING IN OUR
JAIL SYSTEM.
THAT'S NICE.
YOU'RE OUTTA HERE.
BAIL'S BEEN POSTED.
BY WHO?
I DON'T KNOW. LET'S GO.
YO!
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
WE'RE HERE FOR THE BARRACUDA.
DETECTIVE RILEY SENT US.
YOU GUYS ARE WORKING
KIND OF LATE TONIGHT, HUH?
YEAH, YEAH.
WE'RE WORKING OVERTIME.
KEYS ARE IN IT.
BE KIND OF CAREFUL
WITH IT, HUH?
YEAH, DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL BE REAL CAREFUL.
I CAME TO BAIL CHANCE OUT.
HE WAS JUST BAILED OUT.
HE WAS JUST BAILED OUT?
WHAT? IS THERE AN ECHO
IN HERE OR SOMETHING?
LET'S GO. MOVE IT.
YEAH.
THEY'RE NOT HERE! DAMMIT!
SOMEBODY HAS OUR DIAMONDS.
HERE HE IS MR. KINGSLEY.
AH, DETECTIVE.
NO, IT'S MISTER CHANCE
THESE DAYS ISN'T IT?
PLEASE, HAVE A SEAT.
I'LL STAND.
SIT DOWN CHANCE.
YOU TELL SUPERFLY TO
STOP POINTING THAT GUN AT ME
BEFORE I MAKE HIM EAT IT.
..BARREL FIRST.
SUPERFLY. A MAN WITH A
SENSE OF HUMOR, AND BRAVADO
IN THE FACE OF ADVERSITY.
I DO SO ADMIRE THAT.
CAN I INTEREST YOU IN A...
EVENING WITH ONE OF
MY LOVELY LADIES?
NO CHARGE.
I GOT A BETTER OFFER...
AT HOME.
WHERE ARE MY DIAMONDS?
I DON'T KNOW.
AND I'M SICK AND TIRED
OF HEARING ABOUT THEM.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
DETECTIVE RILEY TELLS ME.
RILEY COULDN'T FIND
HIS BUTT WITH BOTH HANDS.
HE FOUND YOU.
I DON'T HAVE YOUR DIAMONDS.
BUT IT SEEMS TO ME
SOMEBODY AROUND HERE
IS BEING PLAYED FOR A SUCKER.
GIMME THE GUN. THAT'S NICE,
THAT'S A GOOD BOY.
NOW ON THE FLOOR.
SORRY TO BREAK UP
THE PARTY GENTLEMEN.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME
WE GO CHANCE.
IF YOU INSIST.
WE'RE NOT THROUGH CHANCE,
COUNT ON IT.
I'M TREMBLING KINGSLEY.
I SUGGEST YOU TALK TO RILEY
ABOUT YOUR MERCHANDISE.
HE SEEMS TO KNOW MORE
ABOUT IT THAN ANYBODY ELSE.
INCLUDING YOU.
ARE YOU EVER GONNA GROW UP?
NEVER.
RED, MILO...FOLLOW THEM
AND KILL THEM.
IT'LL BE MY PLEASURE.
WHAT ABOUT THE DIAMONDS?
CHANCE MAY BE RIGHT,
IT SEEMS RILEY KNOWS MORE
ABOUT THIS CASE THAN
HE IS TELLING US.
WE'LL DEAL WITH HIM LATER.
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU MEAN
THE DIAMONDS AREN'T THERE?
WE LOOKED,
THE DIAMONDS AREN'T THERE.
GET BACK TO THE BODY SHOP.
WHERE ARE THEY?
I DON'T KNOW MAN.
CHANCE, THAT COP, HE WAS HERE.
HE LOOKED AT THE CAR.
ALVIN DID TOO, I DON'T KNOW.
YEAH,
THEY DIDN'T FIND ANYTHING
BECAUSE YOU DID.
NO, I SWEAR TO GOD.
I HADN'T EVEN STARTED ON THE
THING WHEN THEY GOT HERE.
HE DON'T KNOW
WHERE THEY ARE.
YOU BETTER NOT BE LYING PAL.
BECAUSE IF WE
FIND OUT YOU ARE--
YEAH? WELL,
SOMEBODY TOOK THE STONES
OUT OF THAT CAR.
AND UNTIL WE FIND THEM,
THEY'RE GONNA ALL
ASSUME IT'S US.
HEY GUYS, YOU TAKE
$2 MILLION WORTH OF DIAMONDS
AND YOU HIDE THEM IN A CAR?
ISN'T THAT PRETTY
FUCKING STUPID?
MAYBE NOT.
ZACH, LET'S ASSUME...RILEY.
HE RIPPED OFF THE DIAMONDS.
THE GUY THAT OWNS THE CAR,
HE'S IN ON IT. OKAY?
NOW RILEY GETS ASSIGNED TO
THE CASE AND THEN HE PULLS
THE CAR IN AS EVIDENCE.
HE PULLS THE DIAMONDS
AND THEN HE BUST
THE ACCOMPLICES. NOW,
IT'S THE PERFECT DOUBLE CROSS.
EXCEPT...EXCEPT RIGHT NOW
THE DIAMONDS, THEY'RE GONE,
AND KINGSLEY IS GETTING
PISSED AND PRETTY SOON,
JUST 'CAUSE HE'S IN THE MOOD,
HE'S GOING TO START
KILLING PEOPLE.
[GUNSHOT]
JESUS CHRIST,
A LITTLE BIT SOONER
THAN EXPECTED, HUH?
I SAW SOME MUZZLE FLASHES
OVER ON THE ROOF.
WHERE? WHERE?
2:00.
[GUNSHOTS]
COME ON,
LET'S GET THE
HELL OUT OF HERE.
[SIREN WAILING]
[HELICOPTER]
YOU KNOW CHANCE,
YOU AND YOUR PARTNER HERE
ARE IN SHIT
UP TO YOUR EYEBALLS,
AND THE TIDE'S COMING IN.
MR. BOWEN,
DO YOU KNOW WHO I AM?
T-T-TERRY KINGSLEY.
AND YOU OWN A RED BARRACUDA,
AM I RIGHT?
WHY?
WHERE ARE MY DIAMONDS?
I, UM, I...
YES?
I...I DON'T KNOW. I SWEAR.
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S THE WRONG ANSWER.
ISN'T IT MILO?
IN THE KNEE.
NOW WHERE ARE MY DIAMONDS?
WE PUT THEM IN THE CAR
AND AFTER IT WAS REPOED
IT JUST DISAPPEARED.
WE DON'T KNOW
WHERE THEY'RE AT.
MILO, TAKE HIM BACK
WHERE YOU FOUND HIM.
MILO, COME ON. NO.
YO TOMMY! HEY TOMMY,
I GOT THE BEERS.
TOMMY? YO, TOMMY!
WHERE THE FUCK IS HE?
TOMMY! HEY NATURE BOY,
I GOT THE BEERS.
TOMMY. OH, JESUS.
HE KNOWS, HE KNOWS.
[GUNSHOT]
JONNY?
WHAT?
LISTEN PAL,
I'M REALLY SORRY
FOR GETTING YOU IN THE MIDDLE
OF ALL THIS CRAP.
YEAH,
YEAH, I KNOW ZACH. I KNOW.
WHY'D YOU LIE TO ME MAN?
WHY'D YOU LIE TO ME?
I THOUGHT YOU WAS ALL THROUGH
WITH ALL THAT DRINKING STUFF.
I'M REALLY SORRY
FOR LYING TO YOU, I REALLY AM.
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
WRONG WITH ME SOMETIMES.
I...I GET SCARED...CONFUSED.
MAN I...
GOD ONLY KNOWS I'M TRYING.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR LADY?
MONA? HOW DO YOU THINK
SHE'S GONNA FEEL? I MEAN,
HOW DO YOU THINK SHE'S GONNA
FEEL AFTER ALL THIS TIME?
STICKING IT OUT WITH YOU TO
FIND OUT YOUR STILL A DRUNK.
GODDAMMIT MAN!
I AM NOT A DRUNK.
I'M NOT A DRUNK. I'M NOT.
CHANCE, YOU'RE OUT OF HERE.
BY WHO?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE YOU'VE GOT
A FAIRY GODMOTHER.
WHAT ABOUT ZACH?
HE STAYS. LET'S GO.
SEE YOU LATER PAL.
WHO THE HELL DO YOU
THINK YOU ARE CHANCE?
YOU THINK YOU CAN
GO AROUND THIS CITY DOING
WHATEVER YOU FEEL LIKE
WHEN YOU FEEL LIKE IT?
YOU'RE A POLICE OFFICER
FOR CHRISTSAKE!
A PUBLIC SERVANT.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
UPHOLD THE LAW.
YOUR JOB IS TO FIND TROUBLE,
NOT MAKE IT!
[ECHO]
10 YEARS ON THE FORCE
NEVER SHOT A FIRE.
FIRE.
I'M SORRY, I WAS TIRED.
YOUR'E A POLICE OFFICER
10 YEARS ON THE FORCE
YOUR JOB IS TO FIND TROUBLE,
NOT MAKE IT.
YOU NEVER SHOT ANYONE.
FIRE,
FIRE.
NOT MAKE IT!
NOW I HAVE PUT MY GODDAMN
CAREER ON THE LINE FOR YOU
CHANCE,
BECAUSE I'VE HAD YOU TURNED
OVER TO MY CUSTODY.
DO NOT FUCK UP!
YOU'RE A DAMN GOOD COP
CHANCE,
BUT YOU HAVE A COMPLETE
DISREGARD FOR PROCEDURE.
YOU'RE STILL ON SUSPENSION
FOR CHRISTSAKE.
WHAT IS IT CHANCE, HUH?
WHAT'S EATING AT YOU?
DO ME A FAVOR, HUH?
DON'T TURN INTO ONE OF THESE
BURNED OUT BADGE CARRIERS.
LAW ENFORCEMENT IS NOT
SOMETHING YOU USE
ONLY WHEN IT SUITS YOU.
CAPTAIN.
SHUT UP!
I'M THE ONE GIVING THE
LECTURE HERE.
I WANT YOU TO GO HOME AND
STAY THERE UNTIL IT'S TIME
FOR YOUR ARRAIGNMENT.
AND THAT'S AN ORDER MISTER.
HERE. IT'S NOT THE GUN
THAT KILLED ALVIN FINKLE.
KEEP IT AT HOME.
CAPTAIN?
YEAH, WHAT?
YOU WANT A TIE,
OR CUFF-LINKS FOR CHRISTMAS?
SON OF A BITCH.
[DOG BARKING]
[DOOR SHUTS]
[PHONE RINGING]
YOU'RE ON.
JONNY.
ZACH...KINGSLEY?
HE'S GOT US GOOD BUDDY PAL.
I HAVE YOUR EX-PARTNER AND
YOU'RE PRETTY
LITTLE GIRLFRIEND.
DO WE UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER
MISTER CHANCE?
UNDERSTOOD.
I WANT MY DIAMONDS!
I TOLD YOU,
I DON'T HAVE THEM.
MR. BOWEN TOLD ME
BEFORE HE DIED,
HE HID THEM IN HIS CAR.
YOU HAVE TWO HOURS TO GET
THEM HERE BEFORE
EVERYBODY DIES.
THE PIECES ARE IN PLACE,
IT'S YOUR MOVE.
[DIAL TONE]
[PHONE RINGING]
BEAR'S DEN.
IT'S CHANCE.
HEY CHANCE,
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
I NEED YOUR HELP.
COME PREPARED.
I'M ON MY WAY.
♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪
[MOTOR REVVING]
READY?
I'M READY.
SO YOU THINK MAYBE
THE DIAMONDS ARE
STILL IN THE CAR?
I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE.
BUT WE DON'T HAVE
A LOT OF TIME.
RAYMOND. COME ON.
[ENGINE ROARING]
WHAT THE FUCK
DO YOU GUYS WANT?
THE DIAMONDS.
FORGET IT.
IF YOU DON'T TELL ME WHAT
YOU KNOW,
SOMEBODY IS GOING TO DIE.
AND I MIGHT IF I DO.
ONE IS POSSIBLE,
THE OTHER IS CERTAIN.
MAKE YOUR CHOICE...NOW.
♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪
THIS IS THE STORY
OF THREE LITTLE PIGS.
ONE OF THEM STOLE SOMETHING
FROM THE BIG BAD WOLF AND
THAT UPSET THE BIG BAD WOLF
VERY MUCH.
[WIND BLOWING]
CUT THE BULLSHIT KINGSLEY.
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU WANT?
I WANT MY DIAMONDS!
I WEARY OF THIS WHO TOOK
WHAT CAR AND WHEN BUSINESS.
IF I DON'T GET THEM BACK,
I'LL TAKE GREAT
PERSONAL SATISFACTION
IN KILLING ALL OF YOU.
NOW, LET'S PLAY A LITTLE GAME.
IT'S CALLED "LIVE OR DIE".
IT'S VERY SIMPLE.
I ASK YOU A QUESTION AND YOU
GIVE ME AN ANSWER.
IF IT'S THE RIGHT ANSWER,
YOU LIVE.
IF IT'S THE WRONG ANSWER,
YOU DIE.
DO YOU HAVE MY DIAMONDS?
RILEY PUT US UP TO IT.
SHUT UP!
SHUT THE FUCK UP
YOU STUPID CUNT!
SHUT UP!
SHUT THE FUCK UP!
DO YOU HAVE MY DIAMONDS?
NO.
I DON'T HAVE YOUR DIAMONDS.
THAT'S RIGHT, YOU DON'T.
BUT IT'S THE WRONG ANSWER.
[GUNSHOT]
MY DIAMONDS.
YOU'RE A LITTLE LATE CHANCE.
FIRST THEY REACH ME,
THEN YOU GET THE REST.
RILEY TOO.
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNFIRE]
I THINK WE OUGHT TO GET
THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
LIKE THE GOOD OLD DAYS,
HUH JON?
CALL ME JONNY.
♪ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ♪