It's okay.
Relax.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'm just gonna learn about you
for a little while.
Is that okay?
I'm gonna name you Kerolien
after my friend at school.
She's really nice.
But she farts in class sometimes
and pretends like she didn't.
So, please don't do that,
'cause you're sharing this jar now,
and the others won't like you
if you smell. Okay?
Hi there.
I'm not from around here,
but I was hoping to make some new friends.
Can I talk to you for a little bit?
I-I don't talk to strangers.
Of course you don't.
You shouldn't. You're smart.
But I'm here to be your friend,
so, hopefully,
we won't be strangers for too long.
What's your name?
Wenling.
- But everyone calls me Wen.
- Well, it's nice to meet you, Wen.
My name's Leonard.
I see you're catching grasshoppers.
Can I help you?
Um, I guess so.
I loved catching grasshoppers
when I was your age.
- Oh, you're really good.
- Thanks, Wen.
Can you pass me the jar there,
please?
Wait.
Let the ones inside calm down a bit.
We don't want them to panic.
There you go.
Are you just a natural,
or did someone teach you
how to catch grasshoppers?
Daddy Eric taught me.
I'm studying them.
I'm gonna take care of animals
when I grow up.
You call your dad by his first name?
It's so they know who I'm talking to.
There's Daddy Eric and Daddy Andrew.
All the other kids at school
only have one dad.
All the Disney Channel shows
only have one dad, too.
Well, does that bother you?
No.
Except when my guidance counselor
keeps saying
how it's so great that I have two dads.
For some reason, it makes me feel like
she's saying the opposite.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
How old are you, Wen?
I'll be eight in six days.
Well, happy almost-birthday.
In fact, it just so happens
that I have something for you.
I saw it, and I thought it was pretty,
so I decided to keep it.
So, consider it
an early birthday present.
And if you don't like it,
we can play a game with it instead.
What kind of game?
We'll take turns pulling petals off
and asking questions,
and by the time we're done,
we'll know each other better.
Be better friends.
M'kay.
What's your favorite movie?
Kiki's Delivery Service.
I haven't seen that.
I'll check it out.
Okay, your turn.
Why are you here?
Leonard?
Why am I here?
Well, I suppose I'm here
to make friends with you and your dads.
Maybe catch some more grasshoppers.
How'd you get
that tiny little scar on your lip?
I'm so sorry, Wen.
I shouldn't have asked that.
It's too personal, even for this game.
It's okay.
My lip was broken when I was born.
My dads said it took a lot of doctors
to fix it.
Well, I don't have a scar like you,
but if you could look inside,
you'd see that my heart is broken.
Why is it broken?
Because of what I have to do today.
What do you have to do?
Are they your friends?
You're my friend, Wen.
No matter what happens,
I want you to remember that.
The others who are coming
are more like people I work with.
You see, the four of us
have a very important job to do.
In fact, it might be
the most important job
in the history of the world.
This isn't about you, Wen.
Or your dads.
Okay?
You haven't done anything wrong,
but I'm afraid the three of you
are gonna have to make
some tough decisions.
Terrible decisions.
And I wish with all my broken heart
that you didn't have to.
Wen!
Your dads won't want to let us in.
You have to tell them they must.
Otherwise, we're gonna have to find
our own way in. Do you understand?
Wen, tell me you understand!
♪ Oh, love is always… ♪
- This isn't bad.
- The cheese is good.
See? Factual proof. There she is.
You didn't need to check on her.
You have to come inside right now.
There's strangers
and they want to come in,
- and they're scary!
- Whoa, whoa. Slow down.
- Hurry, now!
- Okay, okay, I'm coming.
- We're coming inside.
- God, okay.
- Come on!
- Honey, what's happening?
- Tell me what's so…
- Relax, relax. Okay. It's okay.
- It's okay.
- Wen, what's up?
Wen, Wen, it's okay.
Listen, sweetie. What happened?
What scared you?
There... there were four of them.
The big one, his name's Leonard.
He... he says we have to help them.
He says they have the most important job
in the history of the world.
Jehovah's Witnesses?
Great.
They have these weapons.
Hello in there.
My name is Leonard,
and I'm here with some associates of mine.
Can you open the door, please?
This guy is frigging huge.
What do we do?
I don't know, um…
Tell them to go away nicely?
Hi. Uh, hello, Leonard. We...
Is that Daddy Andrew or Daddy Eric?
I met
your delightful daughter Wen already.
She's so thoughtful and kind.
You two should be very proud.
This is Eric.
Is there something
we can help you with?
There is.
Why don't you open the door?
It'll be easier if we speak face-to-face.
Tell them to go away.
Please make them go away.
Wen, please.
Uh, we weren't expecting visitors.
I don't want to sound rude,
but we'd like to be left alone.
I understand.
And I'm sorry to intrude
on your vacation,
especially in such
a beautiful place as this.
Make them go away!
Wen.
You should know
that this isn't easy for us, either.
None of us
have been to this lake before.
And the four of us, we never thought
we'd be here talking to you nice people.
Who else is out there with you?
I'm here with Sabrina,
Adriane and Redmond.
And the four of us are here
because we're trying to save
a whole bunch of people.
- Eric, come here. Come here.
- But we need your help to do that.
We can't do anything without you,
and speaking through a door
is making a difficult conversation
near impossible.
What?
There's a woman carrying something
that looks like a pick with a chain
and a mallet head at the end.
I'm calling the police now.
This can't be right.
There's no dial tone.
What?
I checked it when we got here.
Is the battery dead?
The battery's not dead.
It's not dialing.
Like I said, we need to talk.
We don't have a choice.
Yeah, well, we don't have a choice,
either! We're calling the cops!
Hey, um, we know you can't do that.
None of our phones
get service out here, either.
And sorry, we had to cut the phone line.
Wen. Wen. Wen.
Wen, give me the phone.
We don't mean to rush you,
but we're a little pressed for time.
Please open the door
so we can have a real conversation.
- If you want to talk, then why do you…
- Wen, Wen.
- …have those scary weapons with you?
- Wen. Wen.
They're not weapons, Wen.
They're tools.
Just open the goddamn door!
- We're coming in either way.
- The hell you are! I have a gun!
You brought it here?
Yes and no. It's in
the safe in the back of the truck.
He's lying.
Show us what you're packing,
Daddy Andrew!
We all like show-and-tell.
You'll see it when I'm pointing it
at your head, you piece of crap!
What's wrong with you?
You're not helping.
- You're upsetting him.
- What?
I'm sorry.
Redmond is as anxious
and passionate as we all are.
I'm giving you one last chance
to open the door.
They're breaking in!
Andrew, couch!
Good job, Wen. Keep going.
Push it.
Okay.
Daddy Andrew!
I got you, baby.
They're in the basement.
One is in the back,
one is downstairs.
Let's make a run for it to the car.
I've got the keys.
It doesn't have to be like this.
Get Wen out of here.
Eric!
Let me help him.
- Wait…
- Don't touch him!
I'm a nurse! He's hurt!
Stop! Stop.
Eric.
Daddy Eric.
Please get up.
We have to go, Daddy.
Eric, wake up.
Wake up, Eric!
Shh. Shh, you'll be okay.
Andrew, that's enough.
♪ To illustrate ♪
♪ My last remark ♪
♪ Jonah in the whale, Noah in the ark ♪
♪ Tell me, what did they do… ♪
I like your fridge.
Thanks, Mom.
♪ Man, they said we got to ♪
♪ Accentuate the positive ♪
♪ And eliminate the negative ♪
♪ And hang on to that affirmative ♪
♪ But don't mess, don't mess with… ♪
They drove for seven hours
and stayed 45 minutes.
I'm sorry.
What do you expect?
That's my mom asking how it's going.
Well, you can tell her you were wrong.
Andrew.
Always together.
Hi.
Thanks, Custard.
This is a very important cupcake order.
Let me see if this helps.
Is that better?
Try not to move.
Almost done.
I have to finish
this special order before tomorrow.
It needs to be purr-fect.
Can you turn that down?
We did when you asked before,
but I'll do it again.
Is Eric cleaned up?
He's cleaned up, yeah,
but severely concussed.
Hey, Eric.
You feeling any better?
I'm… I'm so sorry.
I've never watched this show
before, but... but I like it.
The characters, they...
They seem curious and good.
I get the sense that it
explores or teaches empathy
and tolerance,
and that's just lovely.
Empathy and tolerance?
Is that what you're here to talk about
now that you have the queers tied up?
Andrew, I assure you
that we're not here
with hate or prejudice
in our hearts. Not at all.
We don't have one homophobic bone
in our bodies.
I don't hate anybody.
I do have conflicted feelings
about this door.
You have to believe that.
But we had no idea
you were a single-sex couple
until we got here.
That one was a surprise.
Well, I guess if you promise,
then I have to believe you.
I mean, we're normal people
just like you.
- We have no choice.
- There's always a choice!
He's right about that.
Our choices make our destiny.
I almost got that tattooed.
Okay, you're right, Andrew.
There's always a choice.
So we choose to be here.
Can everyone
come in here, please?
It's almost time.
Time for what?
You don't need us tied up.
You said you were here to talk,
so we'll talk.
Hi, Eric, Wen…
…and Andrew.
My name is Sabrina.
I live in Southern California.
I live in a town
you've probably never heard of.
I have been a post-op nurse
for almost five years.
I used most of my savings
to come out to Pennsylvania,
to come here to talk with you guys.
I have a little half sister back home,
and, Wen, you kind of remind me of her.
Well, I think you... you guys
already know my name is Leonard.
And I'm good at catching grasshoppers,
right, Wen?
I'm from Chicago.
I'm a second grade teacher,
and I run the after-school program.
I'm also a bartender. I…
Okay. Me?
Am I next?
Hi there.
I'm Redmond,
and I like long walks on the beach
- and I like beer.
- Hey.
We already discussed this.
They deserve to know who we are.
We wasted time
for this guy to wake up.
You know, this get-to-know-you stuff
doesn't matter at all.
Doesn't change what we have to do
or what they have to do.
When you say stuff like that,
you sound how you sound, okay?
You just scare them.
You make it less likely
that they'll believe us or cooperate.
Okay. Okay, my turn it is.
I live in Medford, Massachusetts.
I work for the gas company,
making sure houses
and apartments don't blow up.
I'm single, if you can believe that.
I've done some time,
as they say.
Did a lot of, uh…
questionable stuff
when I was young and stupid.
But I'm much better now.
And my father used to beat the shit
out of me, like Andrew just did.
Wish I could go back in time,
give the kid-me this thing.
May I speak now?
I hope I don't sound confusing.
Hold on. Hold on a second.
Wh…
We get that you guys
are a part of some group,
and it sounds like...
It sounds like you want to…
fix things. To help.
Eric, you don't have to try to talk...
No, no, I'm okay.
I want to say this.
If you're try...
Trying to recruit us,
I mean, why else bother
introducing yourselves to us, right?
If you're trying to change us
or make us different,
all of this…
this isn't the way.
Can someone put the curtain
on the backdoor?
What's wrong with Eric?
When you have a concussion,
you're extremely sensitive to light.
There's nothing we can do
about that now.
He's only gonna get better
if he rests in a darkened room
or if we make it dark in here.
We shouldn't move him
until we make our proposal.
He might need to be
in a darkened room for days,
- not just a few hours.
- You're not separating me
from Andrew and Wen.
I'll see what I can do
with the curtains.
So, whatever.
I'm, um, I'm Adriane.
Yeah, I-I've been a lot of things,
but... but right now,
or, um, before I got up here,
I-I was a line cook
at a Mexican restaurant
in... in Dupont Circle, DC.
I love to feed people.
It feels like it's more than food to me.
Um…
God, what else? Uh…
Oh! I have, um, I have two cats.
And you'd love them, Wen.
Their names are Riff and Raff.
Do you like cats, Wen?
You don't have to answer her, sweetie.
Sorry, Wen.
Maybe I'll put it back on later, okay?
Forget the curtains.
It's time.
The four of us are here
to prevent the apocalypse.
We... and when I say "we,"
I mean everyone in this cabin...
Can stop it from happening,
but only with your help.
Ultimately,
whether the world ends or not
is completely up to you three.
You are having a psychological break
of some kind.
Your family must choose to willingly
sacrifice one of the three of you
in order to prevent the apocalypse.
After you make what I know
is an impossible decision,
you must then kill the one you choose.
If you fail to choose,
or if you fail to follow through
with the sacrifice,
the world will end.
You three will live…
but the rest of humanity,
seven billion plus…
will perish.
They're lunatics.
And you will all live long enough
to witness the horror
of the end of everything.
And you will be left to wander
the devastated planet alone.
Permanently and cosmically… alone.
Leonard.
We haven't done anything wrong.
I agree with you. You haven't.
You haven't done anything wrong
to deserve this burden.
You're just the family chosen
to decide for us in this time.
Look, we're not here to hurt you.
If we wanted to hurt you,
we would've used duct tape
- instead of ropes.
- You stop.
You have to understand that we cannot
and will not choose
who has to be sacrificed for you.
And just as importantly,
we cannot act for you.
And you cannot kill yourselves.
We're not choosing anyone.
We're not sacrificing anyone.
Not now, not ever.
Even if it means the death
of everyone else in the world?
Yes.
Even if I believe the world was at stake,
which I don't, that's what it means.
I would watch the world die
a hundred times over
- before having to...
- Christ.
Waste of time.
They're never gonna
choose to do this.
And I don't blame them.
- Who would ever choose...
- Shut up, Redmond.
You just vomit
everything you think.
Oh, God, we are so screwed.
Okay,
you need to listen to this part too.
I've been shown exactly what will happen
if you choose not to make a sacrifice.
We've all been shown.
We couldn't stop drawing
the visions we saw.
I actually thought
something was wrong with me,
but the visions were so strong,
so specific and so, so real.
Sabrina, Adriane and Redmond,
they had the visions too.
So, that led us to each other and…
and that led us here to this exact cabin.
We have no idea why we were picked.
First, the cities will drown.
The oceans will swell
and rise up into a great fist
and pound all the buildings
and people into the sand,
and drag everything out to sea.
There is
something wrong with you,
with all of you, if you believe this.
Then a terrible plague will descend
and people will writhe with fever
and mucus will fill their lungs.
This is psychotic!
It's delusional.
Did you try to get help?
Let us go and we'll get you help.
The skies will fall and crash to the earth
like pieces of glass.
And God's fingers will scorch the earth,
and an everlasting darkness
will descend over humanity.
You need help!
This is going to happen.
And we've been shown
that only your sacrifice can stop it.
Shown by who?
By what?
Are you gonna answer that?
You sound like every fake doomsdayer
on every corner of every city.
Come on, talk to us.
Dreams can have
many different meanings.
Our part in your visions
is kind of vague.
Almost like you didn't know
who would be here.
Like it was random.
It doesn't make sense.
For every "no" you give us,
we will unleash a plague
for the sins of humanity.
Will you make a choice?
Wait, stop.
- You don't need to do this.
- You don't need those things.
You said you couldn't hurt us.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Don't touch her.
Don't touch her! Get off her! Get off her!
Get off of her!
Wen, Wen.
Run, Wen. Wen.
I can't.
Run.
Please, God, just let us go.
Fuck.
I'm scared.
Keep looking at me, okay?
Don't you fucking look away from me.
A part of humanity has been judged.
Whatever it is
you're convinced of, it isn't real.
- You don't have to do this.
- This isn't real.
It's not gonna... No!
You can pray if you want.
I won't make comment.
Mr. and Mrs. Brooks?
Yes. My wife couldn't be here today.
This is her brother.
Now tell me this isn't a miracle.
Hi. Hi, Daddy.
Hi, Wen.
Hey.
Oh!
Adriane, can you help me out here?
- Adriane.
- Hey, yeah.
What?
Help me take Redmond outside.
We'll cover him with a blanket.
Wen, I'm sorry, but I'm gonna have to
change the channel for a little bit, okay?
Go fuck yourself, Mister Rogers.
I want you to try a piece of this.
I want to see whether the air fryer oven
- makes it just as crispy…
- Please watch the TV.
- It should be on soon.
- I'm not even gonna kid you.
I really just want this.
Do you hear that gorgeous crispy crunch?
Doesn't get much better than that.
Mmm!
And it tastes amazing.
Amazing fried chicken
and a lot less guilt.
We continue with our coverage
of the earthquake
centered in the Aleutian Islands,
which struck more than four hours ago.
The US National Tsunami Warning Center
has issued a cautionary advisory
to British Columbia, Canada,
and more than a thousand miles of coast
along the American Pacific Northwest,
including the cities
of Seattle and Portland.
The Pacific Tsunami Warning Center
issued its strongest warning
to the islands of Hawaii.
Is this what we're supposed to see?
…high schools, malls
and colleges's campuses…
I explained to you what would happen
as a result of you not choosing.
A plague will be released
by Redmond's death.
You have to listen to me. I remember,
but this doesn't mean anything.
- It doesn't mean...
- No! Just watch!
I know I shouldn't yell.
I know you're afraid of me, of us.
Just… please watch.
…points to a sizable wave
of 15 to 20 feet in height
headed south
towards the Hawaiian Islands.
We do have information
that the tsunami has made landfall.
Now, as you can tell from our live feed,
this resort on Kauai
has already been evacuated.
Our early warning detection systems
gave plenty of time to evacuate the coasts
and low-laying areas
at the affected Hawaiian Islands.
No injuries or fatalities
have been reported.
Please let Eric and Wen go at least.
Eric has a concussion.
…sending aid to a few reportedly capsized…
I'll stay.
And we can talk about doomsday
or the apocalypse
or mass traumatic events
of the 21st century all you want.
- I don't understand, this isn't the...
- Sabrina, just keep watching.
Until we see what was shown to us.
A second massive earthquake
has struck in the Pacific,
registering 8.6 on the Richter scale.
The epicenter is only 70 miles
off the coast of Oregon
in what's called
the Cascadia Subduction Zone.
That's an area scientists have long feared
would produce a catastrophic earthquake.
Unbelievable.
There it is.
We did this.
It's really fucking happening.
- …triggered this second quake now…
- Oh, Jesus, God.
…five minutes,
and given the proximity of the epicenter,
people on the coast are gonna
have mere minutes to try to find shelter.
A tsunami triggered by a quake
of this magnitude
and proximity to the shoreline
will be massive.
I-I mean, 50-foot-high bluffs
along the coast are not gonna be safe.
And we've just gotten word
the tsunami has indeed
hit the Oregon shoreline,
and we have footage
shot minutes ago from Cannon Beach.
Holy crap, this is what I saw.
The same jutting rocks.
Me too.
Wen,
go to your room
till I tell you to come out.
She didn't need to see this.
Tomorrow morning,
you can make the difficult,
selfless choice of sacrifice
and save the world…
or you can choose once again
to let the clock move another minute
closer to permanent midnight.
For the rest of today and tonight,
we'll tend to your needs within reason.
But otherwise,
we'll leave you be to reflect
and talk it over.
- We told you.
- You have to believe us.
It doesn't matter if we believe your
craziness. The answer is still the same.
Everyone in the world can die,
as far as we're concerned.
Am I right, Eric?
Eric?
You okay?
I'm okay.
I just need a moment.
I have a little surprise
- queued up for you.
- Ooh, a surprise!
- What's that gonna be?
- Are you ready?
- Yeah!
- Oh!
- Are we gonna sing along?
- Yes, of course.
I don't know.
♪ Girl, to be with you
Is my favorite thing ♪
♪ Ba dum, ba dum ♪
♪ I can't wait till I see you again ♪
Here we go. Ready?
♪ I want to put on ♪
♪ My, my, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
- ♪ Hey ♪
- ♪ Just to boogie with you ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I want to put on ♪
♪ My, my, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
♪ Just to boogie with you ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ I want do it till the sun comes up… ♪
It's gorgeous.
Except for the... the main road
being further away than we thought,
I'm officially impressed.
Okay.
- Hey, Wen, come get your bag.
- Wen?
Wen, come on.
Wen, come check out the view.
It's better than the website.
How many grasshoppers did you catch?
Just one so far.
Her name's Liv.
Ooh, you see any bears yet?
Andrew, don't start.
If we joke about it,
she won't take it seriously.
We won't leave the garbage out,
we'll be fine.
Wen, show Daddy Eric
your scary bear face.
Wen, run from... Run!
Hey, Wenling, sweetie, not too close.
That dock might have rusty nails.
Eric, come on with your rusty nails.
We got so lucky with this place.
Whoo!
Get in!
Come on, Wen!
- Come on!
- Oh!
Whoo!
Whoa!
- Here I come!
- Eric, come!
He's coming in!
Oh, come on.
Hold on, one second, one second.
Coming right at you.
- Here I come.
- Yes, yes, yes!
- Oh, it's a cold spot!
- Look at you swimming!
Just applying a little pressure.
Told you I'm a nurse.
You may not be on board
with all the "end of the world" stuff yet,
but at least trust me on that.
None of us wanted it to go this way.
We need you
in a clear state of mind.
You've got a big decision to make.
You think I'm some kind of
religious freak, right?
I would too.
Truth is, I haven't even been to church
since my grandma forced me to go
when I was little.
I always thought religious stuff
was so tired and boring,
from another time,
when people were scared of shadows.
Then the visions started.
I didn't believe it
at first, either.
But you will.
When I was a kid,
my dad used to say to me,
"Trust in something
more than you."
It's sort of become my mantra
these past few days.
I said it when I saw the visions.
I said it when I built my weapon
exactly the way it was shown to me.
I said it over and over
as I passed every freeway exit
on my way here.
I said it when I walked out
onto the boardwalk and I saw the others.
We were all wearing the same colors
we saw in our visions.
That's when I knew I wasn't alone.
And all of this…
…is real.
And I'm saying it to you now, Eric,
you need to trust something more than you.
You may not want to believe it,
but we're all on the same side.
I'm on my family's side.
Eric?
You really okay?
My head's still ringing,
but my vision is clearer.
You know that first earthquake happened
a whole four hours ago, right?
Before they showed up here.
Leonard's checked his watch
a thousand times.
They've been timing all of this.
I know.
I just don't want you to…
I don't want you to be spooked
or anything.
- You think I believe them?
- No.
No, it's just…
With your head and all, I want
to make sure you're thinking straight.
Without them trying to manipulate us.
They take you alone in there
and try and talk to you.
I don't believe them.
I'm trying to keep it together.
This isn't gonna work.
They're never gonna believe us, man.
We have to believe in
what we're doing, what our goal is here.
Did you see
Redmond's fucking face?
It was just crazy.
Say whatever it is
you have to say to them.
Convince them.
Wen!
No!
I'm afraid the rule is
that no one's allowed to leave.
Were you trying to escape, Wen?
Leave her alone.
I told her to do it.
You're just scared, Wen.
We all are.
You'll ask us to choose again.
Don't listen to them, Wen.
We were targeted.
We've always been targeted. We...
Andrew!
I knew I recognized him.
Redmond…
is the guy from the bar.
What?
Are you sure?
What guy from the bar?
Andrew was attacked by a man
at a bar in Boston many years ago.
The man went to jail for a short while.
But his name was O'Bannon.
It's him.
He's gained weight
and his beard's different, but it's him.
His name was Redmond.
We don't know dick about him,
Leonard.
We all met him for the first time
on that boardwalk.
Stop the bullshit!
This is all some kind of sick scam
to get us to hurt each other.
That's not true.
We don't know why each of us is here.
It's a coincidence
the man who attacked me
and had me in years of therapy
is one of your group?
Go get his wallet.
I'll show you his name isn't Redmond.
No, we're not doing that.
Why?
Because it doesn't matter
what his name is.
Okay? We all had the visions.
This has to be exact.
Everything has to be right.
Didn't he tell us about this cabin
on the message board first?
- And then we all had visions of the cabin?
- I don't know. It...
No, we had the visions first.
Message board?
Look, we're not doubting
why we're here.
Go to sleep.
The sun will rise,
maybe for the last time for all of us.
The premise of your scam is flawed.
I'm a human rights attorney,
Leonard.
How about I show you photos of kids
who have been tortured and killed,
lying in piles?
You want to make a case
for humanity to go on, you're gonna lose.
This is a picture
of some of the kids I coach.
This year,
the boys had a record of 3-8.
The girls, 5-6.
So, we're not very good.
If you could hear them laugh,
you'd understand why I'm here.
Maybe you'd sleep better
if you could see each other easier.
♪ I got some troubles
But they won't last ♪
♪ I'm gonna… ♪
You like it?
Come to the restaurant,
I can make you all kinds
of breakfast burritos.
♪ 'Cause I'm in shoo-shoo… ♪
They say if you can make an egg great,
you can do anything.
Eric.
My hands are a little looser.
I just need to get
to the trunk of the car.
♪ Never had a friend or wanted one ♪
♪ So I just lay back
And laugh at the sun… ♪
You're very polite.
♪ Shoo-shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo-shoo... ♪
You're a good person.
- Okay.
- Listen.
You guys met on some kind
of message board, right?
You're having a shared delusion.
That's a uniquely
21st-century health crisis.
It is real.
You're in an echo chamber.
You know that, right?
You got online,
and you found random people
who had random visions
and you took that as evidence.
Remember the guy who shot up three people
in an Army base in Louisiana?
He was part of an online group like yours.
They posted videos
about how the shadow government
was stalking them
and using mind control weapons
in an attempt to destroy their lives.
We found each other online
because we said we had the same visions.
Remember what
you did at Thanksgiving?
And then we decided
to meet on the boardwalk.
You're gonna do that if I nod.
Okay, let's continue.
You have the opportunity to choose.
I don't mean to rush you,
but we're gonna ask
for your decisions very fast now.
I'm gonna be straight up.
I'm the next one to go.
I'm counting on you, man.
You're, like, my last hope here.
Adriane,
you can walk out of here right now.
Just walk out and see,
nothing will happen.
None of this can stop
until you make a choice.
Don't you get that already?
You think I want to be here?
I'm just some fucking cook.
I didn't tell you at first,
but I have a son.
I didn't want to speak his name,
but here I am,
begging you to do what has to be done
because if you don't, my son is gonna die.
Over the last few days,
I've had to watch him die
over and over and over again.
I've watched my little boy burned alive
as I held him in my arms.
Everything was burning.
I can't get the sound of his screams
out of my head,
even right now, so…
…as a mother, believe me when
I tell you that this is really happening.
And it's up to you.
What exactly did you guys see?
Stop talking to him.
He doesn't believe you.
None of us believe you.
Let your time run out.
We're not gonna do
what you want us to do.
His name is Charlie.
He likes pancakes.
Very well.
Close your eyes and cover your ears.
You don't have to do this.
You guys are delusional.
You are part of a suicide cult.
Can't you see that?
Stop! Please stop this!
A part of humanity has been judged.
I'll move her into the other room
so they don't have to see her.
Hundreds of thousands of people
are going to die now.
We've unleashed a second plague.
Bullshit.
Sabrina, put on the TV, please.
There have also been new
developments with the novel X-Nine virus,
which is proving particularly fatal
to children.
The X-Nine virus is highly transmittable
amongst children age ten and under.
These outbreaks seem to be originating
in three distinct pockets of the world:
Cape Town, Suffolk, England,
and outside Nashville in Tennessee.
Lockdowns in these areas
have already begun
as numbers rise along with fear
for the safety of those infected.
Numerous public schools
have been suspended
with some being converted
into makeshift quarantine facilities.
While there is hope
that the virus will be contained
- to the geographical pockets in question…
- I think I saw something, Andrew.
…these communities
are trapped in lockdown.
What?
What are you saying?
I think I saw a person.
Or a figure.
Turn the TV off.
Where'd you see a figure?
In the light behind you.
In the reflection in the mirror.
When you were standing
behind Redmond.
Right before you struck him.
Eric, look at me.
You have a severe concussion.
She even told you
you would be extremely sensitive to light.
We're under extreme stress here.
I need you to listen
to the words I'm saying.
Breathe in for a second, okay?
I've been reading about these X-Nine cases
for months already. You know that.
It isn't a fucking plague.
It's a news report.
They all knew about it
before they showed up here
and knowingly made it
a part of their narrative.
And this guy has been checking his watch
all morning, just like yesterday.
- Come on, Andrew.
- All four of you have watches.
What, you just showed up here
like that? No.
You knew you were coming out
to this particular cabin
where cell reception wouldn't exist.
Did you see the banner
at the bottom of the screen?
It isn't live. It's preprogramming.
It's a TV show.
Leonard, Sabrina, all of them knew
this X-Nine show would be on
- and at what time.
- Andrew, this virus
- is gonna spread everywhere.
- If you...
It's a fucking preprogrammed show!
They knew this virus show
would be on at this time,
just like they knew the Alaskan earthquake
and the tsunami warning
had already happened
before they showed up here.
I'm clearheaded now.
Always together.
You don't talk to him from now on.
You talk to me.
I want to watch Paddington and Chloe now!
I want to watch Paddington and Chloe!
Wen.
I want to watch a cartoon now!
Wen, okay, we're gonna count down
from five together, and we're not
- gonna yell anymore, okay?
- I want to watch it now!
Wen. Five…
- I want to watch Paddington and Chloe now!
- …four…
- Okay, let's try this again.
- I want to watch a cartoon!
Wen, take a deep breath.
And five…
- four…
- I want to watch Paddington and Chloe now!
Wen. Three…
- Get away from my family, fucking losers!
- Eric! Eric!
Eric! Eric! Please stop. Please.
- Stop! That's my dad.
- Everyone needs you.
No! No, I don't believe you!
- Eric, please. Please stop…
- No. No, no. Back away from me.
Don't you look at me.
Don't you look at my daughter!
You don't understand what you're doing!
- I don't fucking believe you! No!
- Please!
No! No, I don't believe a word you say!
Fuck you!
Andrew.
I hit you in the knee
just so you wouldn't run away.
This is triage,
like in an emergency room.
We have to make the decision
to save the most lives.
We have to help each other.
Open up! Andrew, listen to me!
Andrew.
Come on.
Please! Come out!
Stay away from me.
Stay away from me! I will kill you!
Stay away from me!
Please stop!
Leave whatever you're going for,
get out of the car and come inside!
I don't want to have to hurt you!
Come back inside!
Now!
We don't have time for this! Please!
Andrew, trust me!
Now, you listen to me,
you crazy fucking bitch.
You drop that thing
and back the fuck up.
Okay. Okay.
- Back the fuck up!
- Okay!
Keep going!
Okay, okay.
Move!
Breathe.
Stop. Stop!
Fuck. Fuck.
Stay back!
I believe you were chosen because your
family's love for each other is so pure.
I know you've been through a lot,
and people haven't been fair to you.
Drop the weapon
and move away from Eric,
or I'll show you I was chosen
to put a bullet in your head.
Drop it now, Leonard,
or I'll kill you!
You're dooming us all, Andrew.
You're dooming your husband.
You're dooming your daughter...
I'm done with you!
I'm not listening
to another goddamn word you say!
It's time for the next sacrifice.
Are you willing to make a choice?
You're crazy.
I'm taking my family
and I'm leaving.
Andrew!
You have a temper.
Not in a scary way, just…
It's there.
You're uptight.
You can…
suck the life out of any situation.
Hey, we said you have to qualify things.
I'm sorry. You...
You suck the life out of some situations.
I'll accept that.
It's not a bad list.
I think most parents
would have a worse list than that.
I can't believe
we're actually gonna do this.
I have never,
for one second of my life,
ever doubted loving you.
The kid'll be washed in that every day.
How is it you can say stuff like that
out of nowhere?
You guys keep it down?
Were we being loud?
I'm trying to have a drink
with my friends.
Oh, we were being too loud?
Is that what it is?
Get your drunk ass back to your seat.
Fuck you.
♪ And the Southern Central Freight ♪
♪ Got to keep on pushin', mama ♪
You shouldn't provoke them.
I wasn't provoking...
Oh, my God! What the fuck?
What the fuck?
Andrew, are you okay?
Oh, my God! What the fuck?
Somebody call an ambulance!
Andrew! Andrew, look at me.
Andrew, look at me. Are you okay?
Open your eyes. Open your eyes.
Can you hear me?
Andrew!
All right,
so what you got here is an HK P30.
German engineered, very light,
very easy to handle.
Um, pretty much good for any scenario.
Carry, home protection.
Screw 'em, right?
I'll take it.
No, Leonard.
Are you willing to make a sacrifice?
No more, you bastard.
A part of humanity has been judged.
The four of us
can't make this decision.
It's got to be your choice.
Shut your mouth.
Keep an eye on Leonard.
Yell if he does anything.
It's O'Bannon.
They were here to torture us.
We don't know why we were chosen.
Don't say another word
of your horseshit!
None of this is real,
and you were targeting us!
I always look for motive, Leonard.
How about a crazy bigot
meets a bartender from a bar somewhere,
and they find a woman from a small town
who has extreme religious beliefs.
That's not true.
Then they come across a young woman
who can be persuaded of anything.
I didn't believe for a second
that Adriane had a kid, Leonard!
Now, I'm not a murderer like you guys,
so I'm gonna lock you in that bathroom.
They slashed our tires,
but they must've come
in a truck or a vehicle.
We need to get to that vehicle.
You're wrong about all of us.
Now get in that bathroom, Leonard.
And make no mistake,
I will fucking kill you if I have to.
We need
something to tie the doorknob to.
The lamp.
Here.
Okay. Come on. Come on.
He broke the window.
He got out.
He's gonna come get us!
He's gonna get to the car before us.
He could be outside and hurt us.
We have to make sure he's in the bathroom.
Leonard?
If I open this door and I see you,
I will shoot you.
Leonard!
Get off me!
Fuck.
- I thought you wouldn't kill us.
- I won't.
But I will shoot you in the leg
to keep you from leaving this cabin.
Turn on the TV
if you want to be convinced.
You'll see that everything I said
was gonna happen has happened.
- No one's gonna do what you say...
- More terrifying images
as we see yet another passenger aircraft…
- …plummet to the ground.
- -Eric, what are you doing?
- Why did you turn it on?
- Local and international governments
are investigating whether there's
any correlation between the crashes.
We have yet to receive death tolls or
receive any statements from the airlines.
You said it wasn't real.
"The skies will fall and crash
to the earth like pieces of glass."
"And God's fingers will scorch the earth,
and an everlasting darkness
will descend over humanity."
We now have confirmation
of as many as 700 airplanes
having crashed without warning,
without issuing distress calls,
amid fears and increasing speculation
there may have been
a coordinated cyberattack…
That terrorist stuff
has nothing to do with this.
- I've heard this before.
- TSA has yet to issue a statement.
Airports around the globe
are canceling flights.
- It is hard...
- Excuse me.
It is hard to describe
the images that we are seeing.
They fill us with disquietude and horror.
We are witnessing a collective tragedy
unfathomable only moments before.
We are getting word of more airline...
How the fuck did you know
what she was gonna say?
Is this some closed-circuit TV?
Did you guys pump this in?
Maybe the truth is…
…that the end was happening
long before we got to this cabin.
And what we're seeing now
isn't the fireworks.
It's just the final flickering sparks.
I don't know what's going on here,
but where are the keys
to the truck you guys came in?
Andrew.
I'm taking my family,
and we're leaving.
Do you really think that
everything that happened today…
everything we've seen…
Do you really think it's all
just a coincidence?
Yes.
I think it's all a coincidence.
Some horrible, unexplainable coincidence.
Or it has to be a trick.
I have to believe that!
You already don't believe that.
I know when someone's lying.
Eric…
let's go.
Let's get out of here and never come back.
Don't listen to Leonard anymore.
Can everyone come out
onto the back deck now?
I'd like to do this last part outside.
What are you doing with that,
Leonard?
When I'm gone, you'll only
have minutes to stop everything.
After that, it'll be too late.
Will all the children die?
Wen, I want you to take your music
and your headphones
and go to that tree house
that we climbed in.
Put your music on
until one of us comes to get you.
Do what Daddy says, okay?
I love you, chicken.
I love you too.
Go. Go.
Nothing can happen
to the three of us.
You'll be okay.
The worst thing about the visions
was the screaming.
I could hear everyone screaming.
And I knew when the visions ended,
the screaming was just gonna go on and on.
You know what I loved most
about teaching kids?
They believe everything you say.
So you have to be careful.
Say only what you know,
what you know to be true.
It's a big responsibility.
Maybe one of the kids I taught
will do something great for the world.
What do you think?
Please…
my new friends, Eric, Andrew…
will you make a choice and save the world?
All of humanity has been judged.
We still have a few minutes, he said.
Eric.
There was something in the light.
A figure.
And I feel it now.
I believe you.
Let's the three of us leave.
Maybe this is the way it's always been.
Maybe families have been deciding this
all through time.
Let's just walk the earth, then.
The three of us.
What kind of life is that for Wen?
Andrew, this wasn't a home invasion.
They didn't target us.
They came here to spend time with us…
for us to get to know them.
They remind us of all aspects of humanity.
Redmond, malice.
Adriane, nurturing.
Sabrina, healing.
Leonard, guidance.
They're the Four Horsemen
of the Apocalypse.
I believe we had to see them die.
We had to feel their loss.
Why us?
We're nothing special.
Because I know what I felt
when we saw Wen in that orphanage
and we were together for the first time.
It's our decision.
It's our fucking decision?
We're supposed to give up our love
for them?
It's a sacrifice, Andrew.
That we would be willing to give up
something so beautiful to us
- for everyone else.
- They're not worth it!
They hate us, Eric.
They hate that we exist.
They're just scared. Like all of us.
They're monsters.
They destroy everything.
They hurt each other.
You're not just a prosecutor.
You know there's something to defend.
That's where your anger comes from,
Andrew.
Kill me.
No, sweetheart.
We're running out of time.
Maybe I saw a figure,
maybe I just made it up,
but it's giving me peace.
My mind is set in its truth.
I won't be scared.
You gotta do it now.
We're out of time. All of us.
I don't believe in them, Eric.
I do.
Do it while I'm thinking
the most beautiful thought
so that I can have that feeling
in my heart
to take me right to wherever it is
I'm going.
It's almost time. I can feel it.
Kill me, Eric, please.
Please. Please.
I'm thinking about our daughter
in the future.
When she's living her life
exactly as she wanted to.
She's got her own practice.
You're there with her.
You guys are locking up her office
because you guys are going to dinner.
She is everything we always hoped for.
She's still got her crazy laugh.
She still asks everybody questions
about everything.
She found someone who loves her
and who she loves just as much.
Just like her dads.
Eric.
Did Daddy Eric save everyone?
Did we stop it in time?
There's a diner over there.
The only thing we could
do was climb out of the upstairs window
onto the roof…
…but water kept climbing higher
and higher.
No one could hear us.
Standing on the roof
with my daughters, my girls,
I thought it was the end.
And two of my girls, they can't...
They can't swim.
And the water just stopped rising.
Switch to the other one.
The last of the planes in Australia
and Russia have landed safely.
Families are rushing to airports,
searching for their loved ones.
Amidst this chaos are emotional scenes…
We were rolling the bodies out into
the parking lot because there wasn't room.
This past hour is the first time
in many, many hours
that we haven't had a death in the ICU.
Actually, we're coming up
on our second hour here of no deaths.
I know.
I love you so much.
Everything's gonna be okay.
The sudden lightning strikes that set fire
to many areas have not returned.
Though several fires have yet
to be extinguished
and the damage to regions
both rural and urban across Great Britain
is extensive
and remains to be determined,
the worst conflagrations have,
as of this moment…
♪ Girl, to be with you... ♪
♪ I want to put on
My, my, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
♪ Just to boogie with you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I want to put on
My, my, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
♪ Just to boogie... ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I want to put on
My, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
♪ Just to boogie with you ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Boogie down, boogie down ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ I want to put on
My, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
♪ Just to boogie with you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I want to put on
My, my, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
♪ Just to boogie with you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I want to put on… ♪