- [phone rings]
- [sighs]
[Dr. Yates] You disappeared
on me. We had an appointment.
The mountains called.
[Dr. Yates] Sadie, it's normal
to be affected by what happened.
Death, anyone's, can
fill us with urgency.
This is not about what happened.
I didn't really know her,
but... [inhales sharply]
[stammers, sighs] She
was the same as me.
Same age, same job.
The one time I was in her house,
it was the same as mine. [chuckles]
Nice, but cold.
Empty, except for one sad houseplant,
which is more than I have.
She died alone.
[Dr. Yates] Sadie, stay present.
No big moves, no big changes.
So don't marry the
rafting guide I just met?
[chuckles] Maybe start
with a houseplant.
I'd probably eat it.
My cold, empty house has
a cold, empty fridge.
I'm gonna stop for groceries.
- [Dr. Yates] Let's check in tomorrow.
- Yeah.
["Feel It Still" playing]
No pesticides, more nutrients.
It just tastes better, you know.
Out of 20.
Sorry, guys.
[phone chimes]
Five, six, seven.
Have a good one.
[coworker] You know you're gonna
need to buy stock in those trackers.
You'd lose your butt if
it wasn't attached to you.
Well, you lost your hair,
and that was attached.
I walked into that one.
Hey, Cole. Are you okay?
Yeah, heard you got
dumped. Tough break, man.
- Edna.
- I gossip when I'm bored.
- For your information, it was mutual.
- Mmm.
That's what everyone says
after getting dumped.
- That's true.
- Hmm.
Maybe try being a little
less needy, you know?
Girls don't really like that.
I'm not needy.
We just grew apart. [sighs]
And I really just don't
wanna talk about it.
You wanna go get high?
I got a edible in the truck.
No, thanks.
Okay. Well, watch my booth.
I'm gonna go get high.
Enjoy.
- [dog owner] Come on. Here.
- [customer] Uh, just that one.
- [customer 2] Just this one.
- [customer 3] I'll take one too.
Salmon. Halibut. It's all fresh.
[song continues]
[Cole] Can I help you?
Uh, yes, thank you.
I'm gonna get that one.
Begonia. Nice choice.
- Is that what it is?
- Yeah.
It is pretty.
Yeah.
Don't let any pets eat the leaves.
They can be slightly toxic.
[chuckles] Pretty
and slightly toxic.
What is it with
me and roommates?
Didn't realize you roomed
with all of my exes.
[chuckles]
[chuckling] Mmm.
How much watering does it need?
Uh, every other day or so.
Begonias need a little bit of love.
Uh... [sighs]
I... [stutters] I'm actually
gone a lot for work.
Okay.
Okay, got it. Um, less love.
- [chuckles]
- Um, what about a snake plant?
They only need watering
every two weeks.
Sometimes I'm gone longer,
like a month or two.
Okay. Mmm.
Sorry, then why do you want
a plant if you're never home?
I'm not never home. I just...
How about if you find me
something a little less needy?
Right. Um, why not just
get a plastic plant?
That's sad.
Well, not as sad
as killing a plant.
And some of the new ones,
they look totally real.
No amount of neglect
will kill them.
Neglect?
You know what, I'm...
I'm gonna get this one.
- Yep.
- Thank you.
Sorry, I... I can't
sell you this plant.
I can't sell it to you
in good conscience.
Good conscience? What are you,
the patron saint of plants?
I just don't feel comfortable
selling a plant to someone
that can be so indifferent
- towards a living thing.
- Indifferent?
Is this how you speak
to all your customers?
'Cause if you do, I'm shocked
that you sell anything at all.
No, as a matter of fact,
this isn't even my stall.
I just don't wanna
be an accomplice...
You're refusing to sell me a
plant that you don't even own?
- That's right.
- [Edna] Hey, Cole.
- What's going on?
- Hi.
- Are these your plants?
- Yes.
Awesome. 'Cause Farmer Clown
here won't sell me one.
- [chuckles] Farmer Clown. That's funny.
- The plant is $10, honey.
Edna, sh...
All right, you know what? Hey,
want a plant? Here. Cactus.
Requires the bare minimum
love a human can give,
- so you'll totally kill it.
- [Edna sighs]
You should fire him.
- She's just gonna...
- Have a good one.
RIP, little guy.
- Can you believe that?
- No.
I thought for sure you two
were gonna exchange numbers.
- What?
- Yes.
I thought, under all that stupid
fighting, you were flirting.
- Wait, we were flirting?
- Are you kidding me?
Are you high? [chuckles] The
sexual tension was off the charts.
Edna, watch my stall.
- Hey, hey, hey, sorr... [stammers]
- [car horn honks]
- [Cole] Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
- Shit.
Hi. Hi. Yep...
[sighs] ...it's me.
Sorry. Just, uh...
- Are you here to rescue the plant?
- [chuckles]
No. No, I'm not. That's funny.
Um, no, I was just...
Well, I was just wondering
if you wanted to, um,
you know, go out sometime.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I...
I mean, I know we
were kind of...
- arguing back there...
- Mm-hmm.
But I thought that, uh,
underneath it, there was, uh...
um... something.
Something?
- Yeah.
- [scoffs]
I'm wrong, aren't I?
Well, this is
embarrassing. Um...
- Sorry, sorry. I misread it.
- Hmm.
[car horn honks]
I can use a coffee.
A coffee? You want to
get a... Yeah. Like, now?
[chuckles] Yes, now.
[chuckles] Get in.
Yeah, well... Yeah.
[chuckles] Yeah.
[grunts]
- I'm Cole, by the way.
- Mm-hmm. Seat belt.
Yep, yep, yep. [grunts] Sorry.
[sighs] I'll just hang on.
[chuckles] Okay.
["Love Is Everywhere
(Beware)" playing]
[Sadie] I like the canal.
It reminds me of Amsterdam.
[Cole] So, art
curators travel a lot?
Oh, yeah. All over
the world. [slurps]
I love it.
Just jumping on a
plane, moment's notice,
and then, you know, stepping
out into a new place.
Wow.
Oh, gosh, don't tell me
you're one of those big,
tough guys who's afraid
to leave the country.
Okay, first of all, thank you
for calling me big and tough.
Let's keep that going. And
I travel. I travel a lot.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I think the trips
that you plan the least
are the ones that
give you the most.
I agree.
[Cole] Lincoln got shot just across the
street, and he died right next door.
Sounds like you're a
big fan of Lincoln.
Well, history in general.
I majored in agriculture,
but I minored in history.
- That's my real passion.
- Huh.
You know, I'm writing a book.
- You are?
- Yeah.
History of farming?
No, it's about the rise and
fall of different empires
and the critical role
that agriculture...
Yeah, it's about farming.
[laughs] So how's it going?
[inhales sharply] Well...
[sighs] ...it's on pause for now.
My dad got hurt a few years ago, so I
came back to help him with the farm.
So not a lot of
time for writing.
Hmm. I'm sorry.
Oh, it's okay. I'll finish it.
[Cole] You've never seen The
Exorcist? It's a classic.
It's one of the scariest movies ever
made, and they filmed it right here.
I don't know. I don't
get scared by movies.
Yeah, because you haven't
seen The Exorcist.
No, 'cause you can
choose not being scared.
Okay. Little bet.
Race me to the top.
And if I beat you, you gotta
tell me what scares you.
- I love this.
- All right. I like the confidence.
Hang on, wait, wait, wait,
wait. Let me just... Hang on.
Oh, come on. Put
all that in here.
Are you gonna carry all my
stuff? Okay. Wait, wait, wait.
- [inhales sharply]
- You looking for pity?
[sighs] That's exactly
what I'm looking for.
Oh, my friend.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
And go!
["Like Sugar" playing]
[panting]
- [groans]
- [sighs]
[breathing heavily]
You know, I'm guessing
you work out. [pants]
Are you okay? [pants]
- Oh, yeah. [panting]
- [laughing]
Oh, my God. I love Monet.
[Cole] So you can just
choose not to be scared, huh?
When I was six,
my mom and I fled our country...
on a raft.
Oh, my God. That
must have been...
Worse than you can imagine.
The sun, the waves, sharks,
people screaming, crying.
I was terrified. Everyone was.
They wanted to go back, but...
[scoffs] ...my mom was so strong.
She kept us all
going for five days,
until we made it. [chuckles]
And I still remember how they
looked at her on the beach.
I just, you know,
wanted to be like her,
strong and brave.
So that's the day I decided I was
never going to be afraid ever again.
And I'm not.
I believe you.
But it is very cute that you're scared
of this movie with the little girl.
- Oh, my God. This is my own fault.
- That's... What's the name again?
- It's The Exorcist.
- I have to watch it now.
One of the scariest movies of all time.
You're gonna have nightmares for a month.
- Wow. [chuckles]
- Just watch.
This has just been incredible.
It was great. [sighs]
And not to be too forward,
but if you ever felt like
getting a drink sometime...
How about now?
Okay.
I know a great place.
[cheering]
[singing indistinctly,
vocalizing]
[Sadie laughs]
[Sadie] Hey! Whoo!
Thank you.
You are amazing.
How do you make that look cool?
That's rockaoke.
No dignity here.
And next up, we have Cole
Turner, turnin' up the heat
- with "20th Century Boy."
- What happened?
- No, no, no, no, no, n... No, no.
- I might have put your name down.
- Come on, Cole.
- Sadie. Sadie.
Sadie, I get nervous
singing in the shower.
- Just give it a go.
- I'm not a performer.
- Cole! Cole! Cole!
- Cole Turner.
- Where is Cole Turner?
- Please.
I can't.
He's not gonna do it.
Just call someone else.
[singer] Give me the mic.
Thank you.
[Cole] Now, you're out there,
seeing the world, traveling,
meeting interesting
people. It's quite a life.
Lately, I'm not so sure.
Someone I... I know
just died. A coworker.
[sighs] It got me thinking.
You know, there are all these
things you want in life...
[inhales deeply] and it's so
hard to find someone who...
If only people could be
more like your cactus.
Not needing watering
all the time?
Right. Exactly.
- Just living their own lives.
- Yeah.
Not needing someone else,
like, nourishing them.
That makes sense.
["Sound & Color" playing]
Morning.
- What?
- [chuckles] Nothing.
[chuckles, groans]
Good... Good night then.
I mean, good morning.
This was quite a date.
You mean a day?
Right. Yeah, that's...
Officially. That's a first.
Yeah, me too.
Well, goodbye.
Goodbye.
[breathes deeply]
Well, uh, I look
forward to our next day.
[chuckles] Bye.
[sighs] Bye.
[exhales deeply]
["Pretty Please" playing]
[groans]
Be a cactus.
No big moves. No big moves.
[both chuckle]
[Sadie chuckles]
[Sadie laughs]
Wow.
First farmer?
[chuckles]
Yeah.
You know that power you
felt? That's from the land.
[both laugh]
Hey, Coleslaw.
[Cole] Hey, Dad.
Thanks for closing up the
stand for me last night.
Not a problem. Edna gave
me a hand. She was high.
Look who's finally home.
God, take it easy, Mom.
He just got back from
having sex with a stranger,
not fighting the Germans.
Okay, now, come on.
Spill the beans.
Well... [sighs] her name
is Sadie, and she is...
She's incredible. I mean, I
know this sounds a little crazy,
but... [chuckles] I think
she might be the one.
Oh, really? Well, that's fast.
Well, I can't wait to meet her.
Did you tell her you
wrestled in high school?
- No.
- [scoffs] What is this?
You took a selfie in bed
while she was asleep?
Dude, that's weird.
That's what serial killers do
before they kill their victims
and harvest their eyelids.
I was happy. I wanted
to preserve the moment.
- [stammers] He is doing it again.
- Doing what?
It's just... Cole,
you can get a bit...
Smothering, needy, pathetic,
- desperate, delusional.
- What?
Yeah, stuff like this. The stupid
gifts, the constant texting.
I mean, that's why things
never worked out with Fiona.
Fiona was a bitch.
You're a hopeless romantic,
just like your mom.
Tell her you wrestled
in high school.
Look, I'm not needy,
and I'm not smothering.
And for your information, I've
sent Sadie one text today. One.
Three. And some light emoji
stuff, but that doesn't count.
Emoji stuff counts.
[exhales sharply] He is
gonna blow it. Mark my words.
- I'm not gonna bl... [sighs]
- [door closes]
She really is great.
You'll see.
["Last Night" playing]
Hey. Head in the game, Coleslaw.
Come on. A lot of honey to harvest.
You need some slack?
We're good. Hang on. Just
gotta hook it in. One sec.
[phone ringing]
Should I get it? I can get it.
It's right here. So easy for me.
Hello?
[sighs]
Good news.
Mortgage refinancing rates
have never been lower.
[animals bleating]
Any word?
[grunts]
Maybe your phone's broken.
Yeah, maybe you should
do a hard reset.
[sighs] There's nothing
wrong with my phone.
Oh, no, no, no, I
meant with your life.
You know, grow a pair, move
out of your parents' house.
Guesthouse.
Well, I'm sure there's
a logical reason for it.
There is.
He came off way too
strong, so she ghosted him.
Ghosted?
Yeah. It's when someone
breaks off all contact.
For example, let's just say a
young lady makes a horrible,
horrible mistake one night,
and then the guy just keeps
on texting her with emojis,
over and over.
She did not ghost me, okay?
- Mmm. She did.
- You wanna pick this up?
- [breathes heavily]
- No.
Hey, pal, you're huffing and puffing.
Why don't you take a hit off your scuba?
Come on, hey. Let's go.
Oh, my God. [breathes deeply]
[chuckles] Sorry. You did the
leave-behind with your inhaler?
Come on. Isn't your
asthma sad enough already?
It wasn't a leave-behind.
I forgot it in her purse.
And it has one of those, uh, tiles on
it. Those tracking things that I use.
All right. Drumroll, please.
The woman of my dreams is in...
[signal pings]
- London.
- England?
- Oh, London, the Lady in the Mist.
- No one calls it that.
- The Gray Lady.
- No, that's New York Times.
- Are ya sure?
- Yes.
She does travel a lot for work.
Well, there you go.
That makes sense.
She probably got called away last minute
on this job and had to rush over there.
You know, international
calling plans and whatnot.
I bet she hasn't
even seen your texts.
Yeah, yeah, that
makes sense. Okay.
- Exactly.
- Okay, so this is fine?
- Absolutely.
- Yeah.
Cole, you should go over there.
- What?
- Yeah, show up and surprise her.
It'd be a romantic gesture, something
we can tell our grandchildren.
Mom, you can't be serious.
Cole, going to London? No.
Why not? This is a
perfect opportunity
to get out there and
grab life by the horns.
She's gonna think you're psycho.
Or she'll think that
I'm the kind of guy
that's willing to jump on a
plane at a moment's notice.
Wait, but you're not that kind of
guy. You do not travel anywhere.
- You haven't even left the country.
- That's not true.
He was conceived in Ontario.
Cole, you can do this.
Yeah, but what about the
farm? There's so much to do.
- I can't just leave you here.
- Coleslaw, don't worry about the farm.
- [Mom] Yeah.
- By the horns. Come on.
Yeah, go to her.
Oh, you know what I have?
You remember that spring break
where I was supposed to go to Spain
and I gave up my seat
and I got a voucher?
That is my point exactly, Cole.
You missed spring break
to get a stupid voucher,
which you never used.
I mean, that is the
type of guy you are.
Not today.
- Oh, you still have... [laughs]
- Oh, I've got goose bumps.
Oh, thanks for the warning.
I'm going to London.
So it's not like a weird stalker thing.
It's just a grand romantic gesture.
Yeah, that is amazing, mate. I
mean, I admire your confidence.
5,000 miles to surprise a
girl who you've only met once.
I mean, that is the
epitome of romance, mate.
Yeah, exactly. See, you get it.
Especially if she's the
one who ghosted you.
I was... Wait, what? No,
no, she didn't ghost me.
She just doesn't have an
international calling plan.
Oh, right.
An international art curator, doesn't
have an overseas calling plan.
That's very unusual.
[stammers] Talking
of romantic gestures,
what's that you got
in the back then, hey?
- Is it a little cactus, is it?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, this is a little
inside joke between us.
Little cactus. I'm sure she'll
split her sides laughing.
Right, we are nearly
here. Tower Bridge.
That'll be 137 quid, please.
- That's kind of a lot, isn't it?
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's outrageous.
You never get a cab from the
airport to the center of London.
It'll cost you a small fortune,
mate. Yeah. Toodle-pip.
[crowd chattering]
[bar employee] Take care,
now. Thanks very much.
Have a good evening.
Have a good night.
[signal pings]
[signal pinging]
[grunts]
[henchman] Let me tell you how this
will be. One for you, 19 for me.
'Cause I'm the taxman.
Listen to me.
I can't believe I'm quoting
"The Taxman" to you.
So lame. I really am
turning into my dad.
It's true what they say.
When you meet a celebrity,
your IQ drops 50 points.
- Where am I?
- It's just... You're a living legend.
Stopping our shipment in Turkey,
the assassination in Berlin
and now this thing with
Elena and the passcode.
The boss talks about you all the time.
You've become an obsession for him.
"The Taxman killed Elena.
The Taxman has the passcode.
Oh, how I want to find
and murder the Taxman."
And now here you are.
No, no, I'm... I'm not
a taxman. I'm a farmer.
I came to London to surprise a girl,
and these guys, they jumped me.
Textbook evasion.
Frankly, a little disappointing,
but the performance?
Sublime.
It's like you truly
believe what you're saying.
Because I'm telling the truth.
You have the wrong guy.
My name is Cole Turner.
My passport's right over there
in the bag, in the front flap.
Sublime. It truly is an
honor to torture you today.
Whoa. Okay, just...
just wait. Wait.
Normally, I begin
with the punching.
Wait a minute. [groaning]
You see, it causes
me a little pain too.
- I'm all about sharing the experience.
- [panting]
My therapist says
that I'm an empath,
which means that I'm deeply
attuned to others' feelings.
But alas, the boss is in a
real tizzy about the passcode.
[panting]
Are you familiar with the
Schmidt sting pain index?
Wait, the what? Wait a minute.
It's a rating system for the pain caused
by the bites and stings of insects.
From the simple ouch
of the western honeybee
to the spray-and-pray of the
Latin American bullet ant
that you can see primed and
ready in that box on the table.
Spray-and-pray is short
for "spray in your pants
and pray for the merciful
release of death."
Excuse me, sir,
will you just grab that
bag for me quickly?
I promise, this is just
a big misunderstanding...
Normally, we like to start
slow and build our way up.
But you are special,
so we begin with
the murder hornet.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Unless, of course, you want
to reveal the passcode.
I don't know any passcode! I'm
telling you, you have the wrong guy.
My name is Cole Turner.
Just look at the passport.
It's right there in the bag.
That's just great. This
is going to be fun.
For me, not for you.
[pants] Holy shit. Holy
shit. Wait, wait... [blows]
Oh, God. Oh, shit!
Oh, shit! [screams]
- [gunfire]
- [grunts]
[grunting]
- You.
- [exhales sharply]
Can you walk?
- What?
- [sighs] Can you walk, Cole?
[breathes heavily] Sadie.
[grunts]
Head down, mouth closed. Follow
me before anyone sounds the alarm.
[alarm blaring]
- Know how to use a gun?
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah. But...
Shoot anyone who's not me.
Stay on my six. Let's go.
[exhales sharply]
Sadie. Geez. [grunts]
Sadie, what the hell is going
on? Who are these people?
Bad guys.
They set a trap for one of our
agents, and you fell into it.
Agents. Art agents?
- [guard] Over here.
- Down!
- [shouts, groans]
- [gunfire]
Not an art agent. Got it.
[grunts] Sorry, there's a lot going
on. Plus those guys drugged me.
- [shouts] Who are you?
- [pants]
CIA. At least, until they
find out about this fiasco.
Keep moving.
My God, you're a spy!
Do you actually know
where you're going?
- [grunting]
- [gunfire]
Get down!
- [grunts]
- Behind you!
[guards grunting]
- [pants]
- [inhales sharply] You hurt? [panting]
No, it's... it's the most
amazing thing I've e...
[pants] I'm so confused. They
kept asking me about the Taxman.
- They asked you about the Taxman?
- No, they think I am a Taxman.
They think you're the Taxman?
That the Taxman would actually
fall for that lazy trap?
- They caught the Taxman, and it's you?
- [exhales sharply]
- [gunfire]
- [guards grunting]
- You're the Taxman!
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
[guard 2] All right.
Check down here.
- Freeze!
- [shouts, grunts]
- [shouts]
- [grunting]
[grunting]
- [groans]
- [grunts]
- Shoot him! [shouts]
- [strains]
- Hey, hey!
- Shoot him!
- Just, uh, stick 'em up.
- [groaning]
[groans]
- [panting]
- You said you could shoot!
At tin cans, not people.
[groans] Sorry,
sorry, sorry. [sighs]
[guard 3] Here.
- [guard 4] There! Go!
- [gunfire]
[groans]
- Move! Move!
- Where they at?
Art curator, my ass.
I thought you were different
too. Sweet, fun, low-maintenance.
I can't believe I was gonna
call you when I got back.
Cover me.
Cole.
[panting]
[Sadie sighs]
Were you really gonna
call me when you got back?
[pants] Yes, until you texted
me 11 times in two days.
- Seven. Emoji stuff doesn't count.
- Yes, it does.
Emoji stuff counts. Move.
[panting]
- Come on.
- [grunts] Where the hell are we?
[panting] Jump! Cole, come on!
[grunting, coughing]
- I swallowed a rock. [coughing]
- Keep going!
[Sadie grunting]
[both panting]
[gunfire]
Cover me.
[bus horn honks]
Stop!
Get off the bus.
[passengers clamoring]
[exhales sharply]
- [exhales deeply] Come on!
- [horn honks]
- You're never gonna make it through.
- We're not going that way.
["My Sharona" playing]
[bells tinkle]
Do you know what you're doing?
Have you done this before?
I'm gonna let you think yes.
[Sadie grunts]
[screaming]
I cannot believe you got me kidnapped
and tortured all after one date.
You're the one who
flew to London.
[horn honking]
- Holy shit!
- [driver shouting]
- [Sadie] You are unbelievable!
- [Cole] What?
You stalkered your way
across the ocean to find me.
That is not cactus behavior!
[gunfire]
Don't use stalker as a verb.
And it was a romantic gesture!
[grunts]
I checked your records.
You've never even
left the country.
You checked my records?
Who's stalkering now?
[tires squeal]
[grunting]
[panting]
[strains]
[grunting]
[pants]
[groans]
[chuckles]
[strains, grunts]
[grunts]
Sadie!
[Cole straining]
[gunman grunts]
[both grunting]
Look out!
[screams]
- [groans]
- [chokes]
- Choke him out.
- They usually tap.
He's not going to tap.
Just choke him out.
- [grunts]
- [Sadie grunts, groans]
[Cole grunting]
[straining]
[groans]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[straining]
[screams]
- [Cole grunts]
- [screams]
[groans, screams]
[both grunting]
- [grunts]
- [screams]
- [groans, grunts]
- [grunts]
Cole! Are you comfortable?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
[explosion]
[bus creaking]
[engine sputters, stalls]
[breathes heavily]
Is that what I think it is?
- It was meant to be a joke. [sighs]
- [sighs]
It was a lot funnier before
I used it to kill a man.
Hey.
Time to walk.
Great khans,
they used to cross these lands.
Brutal killers.
It was said if you
wanted to find one,
you had to step over the dead.
The Taxman has a face. No matches
in the intelligence databases.
They must be running
him off the books.
[leader] Mmm. Clever.
I've got blood on my hands.
It's the blood of bad men.
We did what we had to.
Is that what you tell yourself?
You're a liar.
I'm not the liar here.
I told you things I've
never told anyone.
It was all true.
Not all of it!
[Sadie sighs]
Okay, one lie about my job.
I really ate it
up too, didn't I?
Especially that sob story
about your coworker that died.
That is low.
That was actually true.
Her name was Elena.
And she really died?
I may have killed her.
What?
She was an enemy agent.
She worked for these guys.
You said she was a coworker.
She was. In a loose sense.
See, this is what
I'm talking about.
- It's just lies and lies and more lies.
- It's not lies and more lies.
It's the sub-lie of
the first original lie.
- You're unbelievable.
- Hey.
Fine, I lied about my job.
But you lied about who you are.
Well, excuse me for
fudging a few details
to try and impress the most
amazing woman I've ever met.
Ugh, please.
Who apparently kills coworkers.
Oh, my God! She killed
innocent people, Cole!
Do you know what?
I am done with you.
Head down, shut your
mouth and follow my lead.
The sooner I get rid of you, the
sooner I get back to the mission.
Fine. You know what?
I just want to get away from you
and out of here as fast as possible.
You should.
'Cause I've tangled with these
guys before, and they are ruthless.
And now they think you're me, so
they're looking for you, Taxman.
I'll speak with Utami.
Buy us some time.
[chuckles]
And the passcode?
Looks like Borislov
was too slow.
As usual.
But I finally know what
the Taxman looks like,
so I'll find him.
[person straining]
What is this?
[boss] He doesn't know anything.
We cannot afford
this kind of failure.
The game we play,
it's like no other.
If we succeed,
we have wealth, power.
And if we fail, we die.
And that is only if
we're lucky. [chuckles]
No, please.
- Please... Please help me. [crying]
- No more mistakes.
No. [screams]
[groaning]
Get that photo to every bounty
hunter on the continent.
One million dollars. Alive.
He is our only
access to that code.
Anyone kills the Taxman, that
bounty moves onto their head.
[crowd chattering]
Be right back.
[chattering]
[camel grunting]
[horn honking]
Just like your farmers' market.
Come on.
Where are you taking me?
Back to your farm,
unless you screw this up.
Stay close.
Be cool.
[dance music playing]
[speaks Urdu]
[sighs]
- How you doing?
- [slide rack clicks]
What? Friendly isn't cool?
Well, well... [chuckling]
well, Sadie sunflower.
- Marco.
- Look at you.
[Sadie] Mmm.
Who's your friend?
- I'm, uh...
- He's a civilian I just recovered.
Ah.
You look ravenous, mate.
Let me put something inside you.
Come on. Mmm.
[friend exclaims, speaks Urdu]
Sit down, sit down.
Come on, sit down.
Aye. The scrap out at the caves.
I should have known that was you.
It was the same people
that stole Aztec.
- What's Aztec?
- A biochemical weapon.
Very nasty. Deadly enough to
wipe out the Eastern Seaboard.
That's classified.
They're going to sell it.
Thank you for filling me in.
And they're using those caves
with highly paid protection.
There's only one man
that can pull this off.
Leveque. Disgraced
French intelligence.
Played in this sandbox for
most of the war... [sighs]
and then he went into business for
himself. Arms deals, assassinations.
If he's your target, be
careful. He's a dangerous man.
Anyway, mate, best
chaat in town.
- Enjoy it.
- [Cole] Hmm.
This is yours, sunflower. Extra
spicy. Just how you like it.
[clears throat]
So, are you two, um,
you know, a couple?
- Yeah.
- No.
- [friend] Yes. Yeah.
- [Sadie] No.
- It was like five months.
- A long time.
You know, we had a lot in
common. You know, work. Not work.
Hey, Mahmoud. [laughs]
Got it. Subtle.
[Sadie chuckles] It's not that.
It's just that sometimes it's easier
to date someone in the same profession.
Always.
Although I wouldn't
call what we did dating.
Oh, please. Can we focus?
Well, that's
charming. Very cool.
- Okay.
- Very cool.
I need to find Aztec.
And I need your guys to get
Cole back safely to America.
- Who is he really?
- Nobody.
He's a mistake.
I... You're the mistake.
She said she was an art curator.
- [laughs] Wait a second.
- [mouthing] Oh, my God.
You said... What?
Is he your boyfriend? [laughs]
He's very funny.
Oh, you poor bastard.
You thought you met a hottie,
right? Not a Mata Hari.
But, hey, at least the no
pants dance was worth it.
- Oh, God.
- No, it wasn't.
Oh, come on. It wa...
Oh, come on. It
was. It was for me.
And I lost a hand.
Lost it.
- Wait. You lo...
- Yeah, gone. It's fake.
- Touch it.
- That's because of Sadie?
- Yeah. You can touch it.
- No. I... I'm... I'm okay. How?
When Sadie and I were together,
we took a little romantic
getaway to Myanmar.
Uh, no. It was a mission.
There were many positions.
Don't know if you remember,
but anyway. Things went south.
I got captured, and, uh,
Sadie took right off.
Turns out that's exactly what
the secret police did to me.
- Oh, my God.
- [Marco] Yeah, don't worry about it, man.
You got two hands,
right, but only one life.
You know what I miss
most, mate? Guess.
- Yeah.
- [Marco] I used to do that all the time.
Can't do it anymore, can I?
Sorry. You left your boyfriend
to get his hand cut off.
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- Nothing.
I'd have done the
same. Mission over man.
Right, sunflower?
Surrounded by lunatics.
Wait a minute.
Did you come back to
save me or get Aztec?
Ooh.
You were a secondary objective.
- Oh, my God.
- High-priority secondary, I'm sure.
And look at you now,
brother. Thriving.
Every word you're saying
is making it worse.
- Every word. I know you're trying. Just...
- Marco.
- This guy.
- Hey.
Are you gonna take
him back home or not?
Oh.
Please say yes.
I'd really hate it if one of my limbs
comes between Sadie and a clean exit.
Sure. Sadie survivors have to
look after each other, right?
[Sadie] Thank you.
Honestly, thank you so much.
You're welcome, babe. Kiss?
No.
Goodbye, Cole.
I'm glad that you survived.
Um, I just wanna be very clear.
Do not ever contact me again.
- Okay?
- With pleasure.
- I've already forgotten your name.
- [laughs]
Which I'm sure by the
way is fake anyway, so...
[scoffs]
- Unbelievable.
- Tell me about it.
She went for a normie, but
that's just lying to herself.
- Yeah.
- Anyway, cheer up, mate.
Stop staring at her. Stop
crying. You're safe now. Come on.
We got a cheeky
bottle-o in the back.
On the piss, you and me
get drunk, get smashed.
Alcohol in your mouth.
This is my town. Nothing happens here
that I don't see coming a mile away.
- [gunshot]
- [people clamoring]
Everything but that I guess.
Walk. Both of you.
- Sorry about Marco.
- Stop talking before you get us killed.
[bounty hunter] Don't
worry. They want him alive.
I don't know what your deal is, but
I'm sure they'll pay for you too.
- Oh, they definitely will.
- Cole, shut up. Just...
- I'm trying to keep you alive.
- [scoffs]
Would you rather I say
they wouldn't pay for you?
This is so cute. Get a room.
If it means anything,
he's not the Taxman.
Yeah, and I'm not
the Grandson of Sam.
Huh? Like the Son of Sam, the
serial killer, but next gen.
I'm the best bounty
hunter alive.
- [grunts]
- Ooh.
[gunshots]
- [people clamoring]
Second best.
That was very impressive.
- Shall we?
- Yep, yep. Yep.
You disappointed me,
Taxman. That was too easy.
Now your lady friend's
gonna die 'cause of you.
That's funny. Usually
the other way around.
It was you who
followed me to Europe.
Lured by your lying.
God, you two need to get a room.
We did. That's what
got us into this mess.
Okay, get in the car.
Lady drives. Taxman,
you're riding middle.
Scooch, scooch.
Well, Taxman it up.
Don't use Taxman as a verb.
You mind telling us who you are?
- They call me the Leopard.
- [groans]
- [neck cracks]
- [gasps] Oh!
Oh, my God.
[bounty hunter 3]
Called him the Leopard.
But even leopards
get killed by lions,
hyenas, lightning.
[breathing heavily]
Get him out.
[straining]
And drive.
[door closes]
[Cole] And who are you?
God. The Bounty Hunter.
Wow. You guys have really
good names in your world.
It's like the WWE, but scarier.
One twist of this ring will send
50,000 volts through your sorry ass.
- Make you wish you were dead. [chuckles]
- Too late.
This is great.
Thank you for this.
- Huh?
- No, I was just thinking how happy I am
to have an electrified hockey
puck stuck to my neck with what,
- 50,000 volts ready to go into...
- [Sadie] I can't take this.
- Volts into my...
- You really need to shut up.
- Wow.
- [Cole sighs]
You two should get a room.
[God] You know what? Stop.
Pull over here.
My car is better.
Look, I don't mean to
shake your confidence, God,
but the last two
guys didn't make it.
My confidence doesn't shake.
I spent years conditioning
myself to attuning my sense...
[people screaming, clamoring]
[groans]
Got you, suckers. [grunts]
[groaning]
[grunting]
If you're collecting the bounty,
where are they taking delivery?
[groans]
Listen, I'll stash
you someplace safe.
If I don't come back for
you, an extraction team will.
So you're really gonna raid a plane
full of armed goons by yourself?
I have to find Aztec.
It's my only play.
Wow. [sighs]
Well, for what it's worth,
I'm sorry about Marco.
Ugh. God. Seriously?
You know, I'm trying to connect
about a person that just died.
Someone you knew well.
Are you capable of that, or
is that only on first dates?
The rest of the time, it's just
chemical weapons and passcodes
and bullets and death.
Wait, what passcodes? W-What
do you mean about passcodes?
The bug guy in the cave kept
asking me about passcodes.
- [brakes screeching]
- Jesus!
- He thinks I have the passcode?
- Yeah.
And you're telling me this now?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was slightly drugged
and kidnapped at the time.
Unbelievable.
Also, in case you
forgot, I'm a farmer.
I'm not a super spy.
Why didn't you just ask me what the
torturer was torturing me about?
You are unbelievable!
- What? What?
- [breathes deeply]
What are the passcodes?
The least you could do is tell
me what I almost died for.
Aztec is inside a high-security case
that cannot be opened without a passcode.
Elena figured out
the DNA encryption.
What do you mean,
DNA encryption?
The passcode is the entire genetic
sequence of a living organism.
- Insanely long and unique.
- Wow.
I got to Elena before she
could upload it to Leveque.
So they think you
have the passcode?
But I don't because
she destroyed it.
But if Leveque is trying
to get it from me,
that means he doesn't
have it either.
Which means he can't hand the
weapon over to his buyers.
- Which means...
- He still has Aztec.
Which means change of plans.
Do you trust me?
Is that a fucking joke?
Thank you for your honesty.
[grunts]
[boss scatting]
[muffled] You're a f...
I cannot believe...
[boss] 'Cause I'm the taxman
- [boss grunts]
- [Cole grunts, groans]
Yeah, I'm the taxman
- Get it?
- The song? Very funny.
You left an impressive trail of
blood bringing us our friend.
- Well done.
- Thanks.
But I don't get
paid in compliments.
Hmm.
[boss] You'll get your
money, bounty hunter.
So you're the Taxman.
CIA's golden boy.
[chuckles] Your pseudonym has
generated as much fun as you have.
But I know you.
I know you because I was you.
Disposable.
Except one day, I found myself
bleeding out in a ditch
on the edge of Kabul.
Mmm.
There was trash everywhere.
And then suddenly,
I got clarity.
I had given them everything
and sacrificed everything.
It is a waste of life.
And what are we? Hmm?
Instruments.
Expendable.
We deserve better.
[muffled shouting]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
Tell me the passcode
and walk away.
If you don't...
well, we both know
how that will go.
I will get what I want...
and you will die anyway.
- [breathing heavily]
- For nothing.
I swear to God, I don't
know what the passcode is.
I'm not even the
Taxman. [grunts]
- [Cole coughing]
- Shut up.
[Sadie sighs] Can we
get back to business?
Is that my money?
Your payment will be wired soon.
Rumor has it you stole
a weapon you can't use,
so you're overextended.
And now you want me to
work on what? Credit?
No, no.
Cash.
And until I get it, he
doesn't leave my sight.
Or we just kill you.
[Cole grunts]
And make your boss the
guy who offers big paydays
and kills anyone who delivers?
Let me guess.
This is the idiot who
lost him to begin with.
You'll get your
cash when you land.
She called you an idiot.
Yeah.
To your face.
Kill her when you touch down.
Get that passcode.
I expect that to be open
next time I see you.
You're not coming?
If anything should go wrong
when you open that case...
[imitates explosion]
everyone on board dies.
No pressure.
Yes, sir.
We're looking for
a genetic sequence.
Do you know what
"genetic" means?
[shouts, groans]
That's a cactus.
Thirsty?
- [softly] Be smart.
- [softly] Sociopath.
I'm not a sociopath.
You know who says that
a lot? Sociopaths.
I have dated some crazies in my
day, but you are certifiable.
This is bigger than you and me.
- [sighs]
- And my plan worked.
Better than I imagined.
Oh, really?
Did you imagine I'd make
it out of this alive?
We found Aztec.
[sighs]
As soon as we land, we'll
take these guys down.
We'll be safe.
The world will be
safe. Everybody wins.
[Cole grunts]
What's all this?
What's...
all this?
Hmm?
I would expect more discretion
from the Taxman.
So would I.
[boss] So what are you really?
Hired help?
Or just the girlfriend?
Oh, believe me, she's
not girlfriend material.
You know, I don't care.
[smacks lips] You
die either way.
Hey, hey, hey. Wait, wait. Wait.
Who's the idiot now? Hmm?
I have the passcode.
[chuckles] Bullshit.
He doesn't have it.
I do.
Oh, really?
So we can kill him.
Hey! Wait. Okay. Wait.
The passcode. Now!
Sure. It's in my pocket.
[boss] We're good.
Really?
Open it.
[boss sighs]
- [electronic zapping]
- [groaning]
Shit!
[Sadie, henchmen grunting]
I can't believe you took a picture
of me while I was sleeping!
Not of you, of us!
I knew you were a creep!
[all grunting]
[pants] I'm not a creep!
- You know who says that a lot? Creeps!
- [henchman grunts]
[Sadie screams]
[all grunting, groaning]
[groans]
[grunting, groaning continues]
[screams]
[Sadie groans]
[grunting, groaning continues]
[Cole grunts]
[panting]
- [groans]
- Whoa. Let me see.
- Let me see. Let me see.
- [groans]
Oh, my God.
Take the case and go.
[breathing heavily]
- There is a parachute. [breathing heavily]
- What about you?
Mission over man.
No. No. I gotta stop this bleeding
first. You're losing a lot of blood.
- Just go, Cole.
- I gotta find...
- Cole, go! Go!
- Sadie, I'm telling you right...
[Sadie breathes heavily]
Get out of here.
Hey!
[exhales deeply]
[Cole panting]
[boss] Get out of
the way, you idiot.
- [pants, exhales heavily]
- What are you doing?
I have no idea.
[wind whistling]
[Sadie groaning]
Sadie?
- [Sadie grunts]
- Oh!
- [Sadie grunting]
- [Cole] God. [groans]
[Sadie breathing deeply]
[Cole grunts]
I told you to go.
[Cole groans]
I did.
I just took you with me.
How long was I out?
A while. [sighs]
[Sadie] Looks like you got
creative with the parachute.
I had a lot of nervous energy.
[Sadie sighs]
[sighs]
You got it.
Yeah. Yeah.
- You got Aztec.
- Yeah.
[breathing heavily]
- Wait. Take it easy.
- I mean, do you have a...
You lost a lot of blood.
[breathes deeply]
It was really gross.
I'm sorry. I... I... I
don't know what to say.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[inhales deeply]
[dance music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
[cell phone ringing]
Pardon me. Excuse
me. [clears throat]
Pardon. [clears throat]
Hello?
[boss] Leveque, things
didn't go as planned.
The girl sprung the Taxman.
How many times can
you lose one man? Hmm?
Listen carefully.
If we do not deliver an
operational weapon in 48 hours,
our buyers will kill us all.
Now, you find the Taxman,
or they will not have the chance
because I will kill you myself.
[henchman] Boss. We have a
sighting of the parachute.
Good.
[device beeps]
[device chimes, beeping]
[Cole] You know, I think,
depending on your strength,
we should consider maybe
hiking out of here tomorrow.
- Depending on your strength.
- [chuckles]
[Sadie chuckles]
You have to tell me. What
is this gunk? [laughs]
It's periwinkle and gavilana.
I found it up the beach, smashed
it up and put it in there
to stop the bleeding
and fight the infection.
- How did you know how to do that?
- I read about it.
Throughout history, every culture has
their own knowledge of the crops they grow
for food or clothing, medicine.
I just don't get why you
never left the country.
- Here we go.
- What? I'm serious.
You're clearly
interested in the world.
I wanted to travel. I really did. I
thought I was gonna after I graduated.
You know, research the book.
Then my dad got hurt...
just went home.
He never recovered?
No, he did. He's good now.
But you know, he's getting old.
And you know, we got to keep
production high to compete,
and business is changing.
Anyway...
They need me there.
Do they?
What about you? Your
mom must be proud.
Daughter's a CIA agent. Right?
I'd like to think she'd be.
My mom died when
I was very young.
- [groans] God, I'm sorry. I didn't know.
- It's okay.
I promise it's... It
happened so long ago.
You know, and then after she died
I... I found the... the army.
You know, somewhere where
I could put my focus.
And then the agency,
they gave me purpose.
Our struggles make us
stronger. [chuckles] Right?
Any other family?
In my line of work,
it's better being alone.
Is it?
For what it's worth, I think that
any parent would be very proud...
of you.
[Sadie] You know what?
I just can't believe that that little
shit is still in one piece. [chuckles]
[chuckles] Maybe you can keep
a cactus alive after all.
Maybe.
I'm sorry about the selfie.
I'm sorry about the gag.
Call it even?
Deal.
[vehicles approaching]
Run!
Get me the Taxman alive, kill
the girl, and I'll get Aztec.
[gunfire]
[henchman] Move! Move!
[boss] There she is.
[henchmen shouting]
- [henchman grunts]
- [mechanical whirring]
[pants]
[marine 1] Attention. This
is the United States Marines.
Safety your weapons and
drop them on the ground.
[groans]
[boss grunts]
[grunts]
[Sadie pants]
Damn it.
[mechanical whirring]
[twig snaps]
[all grunting, groaning]
- [neck cracks]
- [thudding]
- [Sadie panting]
- Where's the case? [pants]
Agent Rhodes. It's
time to go home.
We're fine. Thanks.
Let's go.
- That's not too tight on you now, is it?
- [Cole] No.
Okay. Just wanna make sure.
- Mmm. Yeah, that's good.
- [door closes]
[Sadie] A polygraph, Jackson?
Are you really this desperate
to jump ahead of me?
I'm just doing my job, Rhodes.
No, if you were doing your job,
you'd be out there looking for Aztec.
If you had done yours, we
never would have lost it.
Well, it wasn't her fault. She
was just trying to save me.
Of course.
The boyfriend, accidentally
along for the ride.
Didn't it ever occur to you that
he could be a foreign asset,
trying to compromise
your mission?
Oh, yeah. Six-foot honeypot sent to kiss
and nibble the secrets right out of you.
Patti, just watch
the machine, please.
Right. Sorry.
We both know you checked him out.
He's a civilian, and he's clean.
[machine beeps]
[Jackson] Some civilian.
Because you chose his life over
thousands, if Aztec is ever deployed.
I let my emotions
cloud my judgment.
[smacks lips] Wait a minute.
Are you saying you think it
was a mistake to save my life?
- Yes.
- [gasps]
[erratic scraping, beep]
[sighs]
That's great.
Cole, I'm sorry, but they're right.
One life compared to thousands.
Yeah, no, I get it. Mission
over man justifies everything.
Marco's hand, using me
as bait at the airstrip.
- I get it.
- You used him as bait?
- Yes.
- No.
- Well...
- [mixed electronic tones]
Marco was right about you. You
should date someone just like him.
Completely cut off from
emotional connection
- and not afraid to lose a limb.
- What?
You know what? Marco was
right, but not about that.
We only have one life, and
you are too afraid to live it.
Says the one-handed dead guy.
- What's happening?
- [shushes]
Cole, you went to your
parents' house to help them.
But I don't think
they need you anymore.
I think they're just an
excuse to avoid life.
Look who's talking.
Your job, the duty, the sacrifice,
that's your excuse to keep people out.
I think you're afraid
to get close to people.
'Cause if you do,
you might lose them.
- Just like you lost your mother.
- Hey!
You don't talk about her!
[sighs]
And I'm not afraid of anything.
- You two need to get a room.
- [Sadie] Ugh.
- Oh, my God.
- Patti,
he's not even hooked
up to the machine.
I'm sorry. But, you guys, the sexual
tension in the room is just...
The boss wants to see you.
So much for starting
with a houseplant.
[Jackson] I know she
pulled you into this...
but...
you're still in deep shit.
You're facing prosecution.
For what? Visiting
a girl in London?
Why are you protecting her?
I know this looks
bad. I can fix it.
We can still get Leveque.
You were always my
favorite, Sadie.
But you going rogue,
there's nothing I can do.
What do you mean?
- She didn't lose Aztec, did she?
- [chuckles]
No, no, no, no, no.
She's working an angle.
- No. No.
- Looking to cash in.
Sadie would never do that.
[Dr. Yates] You let Aztec get
into the hands of a known threat.
You're suspended, pending
a full investigation,
but you know how
these things go.
You'll be lucky to have a
job at all when it's done.
[Sadie exhales sharply]
Look at what she does.
And this is just
the last six months.
She's a liar and a killer, Cole.
Is that someone you
want to protect?
Hmm?
Take home to Mom?
Oh, my God.
[Dr. Yates] What am I
looking at? A houseplant?
Well, it's not a houseplant.
That's an amaranth. A crop.
[electronic beeping]
Farmed in the Americas for
thousands of years, mostly for food,
but often used in
rituals by the Aztecs.
Oh, my God. The plant wasn't hers. She
took it from Horvath, the scientist.
He was obsessed with the
Aztecs' use of human sacrifice.
The genetic sequence of that
amaranth is the passcode.
[clicks tongue] I'll be damned.
I want that plant retrieved
from Elena's apartment now.
You know, we can use this to lure
in Leveque. We get a message to him.
"The Taxman is ready
to sell the passcode."
He'll never go for it.
Unless we bait the hook.
The passcode is divided
into four segments.
Send Leveque the first.
What? Give him part of
the key? That's insane.
Exactly. The agency
would never allow it.
So if the Taxman is doing it, that means
he went rogue and the offer is real.
Leveque is desperate.
He'll bite.
That means we're
gonna need the Taxman.
Me? [chuckles] No, no, no way.
It's only for appearances.
He won't even get near you.
Well, then what do you need me for?
Use a dummy. Put Jackson in a disguise.
That's a great idea.
Mr. Turner, I know you don't want to
do this, but I also know that you will.
As long as Leveque thinks you're
the Taxman, you're in danger.
Well, then put me in protective custody.
Hide me just until you find the guy.
What about your family?
- What about my family?
- Guys like Leveque, they never stop.
The only way to guarantee
your family's safety
is to take him off the board.
[Cole sighs]
No, no, no.
Hey, Cole. Cole,
it's too dangerous.
They're using you.
Well, that's funny because he just
said the same thing about you.
Remind me, which one of you
can't stop risking my life?
I know you're angry,
but this is a mistake.
Protecting the people you
love is never a mistake.
Maybe one day you'll care enough
about someone to understand that.
Rhodes.
[Sadie sighs]
Come on, you have
to let me run this.
I know more about Leveque's
operation than anyone.
Go home, Sadie. And stay there.
[Sadie exhales sharply]
[beeping]
[boss] What do you think?
What do I think? I
think it is a trap.
[classical music playing]
Test it.
[electronic tone]
It's genuine.
Maybe it's not a trap.
Or maybe it is just a very good one.
Either way, what choice do we have?
[henchman] Boss.
Mr. Utami. Pleasure
to see you again.
Funny. When you accepted
my first payment,
you neglected to mention that
you didn't have the passcode.
We will have it soon. Aztec
will be yours as promised.
[clears throat]
Mine, I believe.
You're meeting the Taxman?
- Uh...
- We'll go together.
If he has the passcode, we conclude our
business. If he doesn't, I kill you.
Uh, Mr. Utami, one condition.
Whatever happens,
the Taxman dies.
So be it.
[Jackson] Turner, get in
there and make it look good.
You'll be in and
out in 20 minutes.
[radio static]
Stop messing with your collar. Sounds
like a goddamn thunderstorm in here.
Sorry, I hate suits.
[exhales heavily]
- How many guys do you have?
- Including me? Three.
Three? What do you... What do you
mean? Three... Three guys total?
You have three guys total? You
can't do this with three guys.
The CIA can't operate on US
soil. We had to travel light.
Travel light? What are you,
backpacking through Europe?
You're the CIA. What does
that even mean? Travel light?
[Jackson] Calm down. Leveque's
men just need to see you in there.
We'll arrest him as
soon as he shows.
You got to play the part.
You're not a farmer anymore. Remember?
You're the Taxman. Now, get in there.
- [elevator bell dings]
- [exhales heavily]
Hi, welcome in.
[Cole] Table for Mr. Taxman.
Yes, right this way.
[diners chattering]
[all] Cheers!
[Jackson] Everything will be fine.
We've got it all under control,
and the bad guys will
never get near you.
Three guys. [sighs]
[electronic beeps]
They're here.
[Jackson] We got eyes on the
target. He has the weapon.
Let's get ready to move.
[CIA agents grunting]
[gunfire, clatter
via listening device]
Jackson. What was that?
[transmission static]
- [Jackson] Cole.
- What?
Get out of there.
Go now? Okay. Okay. Okay.
Does this mean we lose Leveque?
Jackson, what happens to my
family if you lose Leveque?
[transmission static]
[breathing deeply]
I'm staying.
She's coming.
I know it.
[chattering]
[sighs]
Well, well, well, what a romantic
spot for our first official date.
Mmm.
[Leveque] Uh...
I brought a little something
special for us to open up.
Mmm?
And, uh, some chaperone.
Hope you don't mind.
I apologize. Yours
are no longer with us.
It is more intimate
this way, no?
Are you all right, Taxman?
I hate to think something
might ruin our night.
- Thank you.
- For what?
For helping me
with my chaperones.
Saves me the hassle of
having to kill them myself.
It was my pleasure.
But somehow I don't believe you.
Well, I don't care
what you believe.
My intention is to walk out of
here a very rich man and disappear.
Oh, the great Taxman
betraying his country.
[clicks tongue] No.
Why would you do that?
What you said to me about
wasting my life. Made me think.
Let's not delay this
new beginning. Hmm?
The passcode.
Money first.
And... my price doubled.
Negotiations are over.
Well, um, negotiations
are never over anytime.
You know, it... [chuckles]
actually reminds me of this one
time I was, um... [clears throat]
I was selling missiles
to a arms dealer,
and, uh, he was haggling
and haggling, wouldn't stop.
Finally, he, uh... he bought
the missiles and, um...
And he comes back an hour
later, and he says, uh,
"I paid too much for these missiles.
I want a better price," you know.
And I said, "That's not how this
works. You can't haggle now."
He says, "I want a full refund. I
don't even want the missiles anymore."
I said to him, "Look, I can't...
I can't take these missiles back.
- You've had them for an hour."
- Enough!
- The passcode now!
- [Leveque] Hmm.
Or you both die.
[Leveque] Hmm.
He gets very upset.
Do you have the passcode, hmm?
Do you have the passcode or not?
'Cause it is going to be very
painful for both of us if you do not.
- Hmm? My friend?
- [breathing heavily]
["Taxman" playing]
I'm sorry I'm late.
Glad you could make it.
Well, what can I say? You
might be growing on me.
What is this?
An opportunity for me to
check out all the players.
Mr. Utami, since you're the one
with the money, I'll address you.
The price of the passcode is
exactly half of Leveque's fee.
Wire it to this account
after that case opens.
You are the Taxman.
Here to collect.
[whispers indistinctly]
In that case, then who are you?
My boyfriend.
Damn straight.
If you have the passcode,
I accept your terms.
- Mr. Utami...
- Open it.
You have the passcode?
I still have friends
at the agency.
Wait a minute. You
can't open that.
When the people you love are in
danger, you do whatever it takes.
[electronic tone]
- [beeps]
- [air lock pressure releases]
- [Utami sighs]
- [Leveque] Voil.
Aztec, as promised.
Thank you very much.
[cell phone chimes]
[whirring, dinging]
It's a pleasure doing
business with you.
[Leveque] Yes,
thank you very much.
However, my business is not
yet finished, but you are.
What makes you think I will let
you two out of here alive? Hmm?
The ten-million-dollar bounty
I put on your head might help.
I don't know how many
bounty hunters are here...
[cell phones chiming]
[Sadie] but they
definitely know about you.
Know what's funny?
Like you, I didn't actually
have the money until just now,
but the bounty hunters
didn't need to know that.
They just needed to
know where you were.
Okay, Leveque. You're
worth a lot of money.
- I'll take that from you.
- Gun!
- [bounty hunter 2] Nobody move!
- [diners screaming, clamoring]
You are so dead, my friend.
Tell your guys not to
do anything stupid.
[screaming, clamoring continues]
And what is the plan, huh?
Now what are you going to do?
Do nothing. You're
coming with me.
How can I do nothing
and come with you?
You idiot, how are you
going to get out of here?
I'll give you 20 million to shoot
this one. To kill her right now. Hmm?
[sighing] Are you ready?
Ready for what? No, I'm not.
I'm definitely not. What...
["Uptown Funk" playing]
[groans]
[grunts]
You flush them forward. I will
cut around. Get the vial. Now! Go!
- [grunts]
- [groans]
Stairs.
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[both grunting, groaning]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[breathes heavily]
- [Sadie grunts]
- Where you going?
[grunts]
[mechanical whirring]
[grunting]
[mechanical creaking]
- Sadie?
- [gasps]
Whoa, I'm an ally.
- Jonas?
- I have missed you so much.
Listen, it was never
gonna work out between us.
No, no, no, no. Of course it wasn't.
I was losing too many body parts.
That's not sustainable. But if
you look on the bright side,
I still have 20 vision.
- [gunfire]
- [groans]
Jonas, I'm in the middle
of something here.
I know. Look, losing
the eye sucked.
But I'll tell you, getting
this thing blown off,
that was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
Seriously, it changed my whole life.
I'm a good, solid, active listener now.
- [henchman shouts]
- [groans] That's the other ear.
I didn't need the ear. You
keep going. You do what you do.
[both grunting, groaning]
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
All right, yes. That
looked cool, but cheating.
[sighs] You're not the
Taxman. Who the hell are you?
What she said.
[pants] I'm the boyfriend.
[gears grinding]
[groans]
No!
You need to get me out.
No, you stay here.
- [gunshot]
- [groans]
[both grunting, groaning]
[Cole shouts]
[alarm blaring]
[both grunting, groaning]
- [panting]
- [Leveque] Give me the weapon.
[grunting, groaning continues]
Damn it.
Come on, Taxman.
Give me my weapon.
- [Cole grunts]
- [boss screaming]
[gears grinding]
[both grunting, straining]
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
- [Sadie groans]
- Squandering all this talent.
- You and I could've had so much working...
- There's nothing you have that I want.
[grunting]
What is it that you want, huh? You
want a boyfriend? So pedestrian.
He does not know you. He
does not see the real you.
[both grunting]
[Sadie] Cole?
Cole! [grunts]
[straining, grunting]
[groans]
- Get me over there!
- [straining]
[Cole grunts]
[Leveque screaming]
[breathing heavily]
[both grunting, panting]
You look amazing in that dress.
And you should wear more suits.
- [Dad] He almost died in a refrigerator.
- But I did not do that. That was his.
- In a refrigerator, for how long?
- Was it you?
- Why would I put a cat in a fridge?
- What are you talking about?
- You didn't put him in.
- I think it's pretty clear.
- You didn't notice him when you closed it.
- Oh, not the cat story.
- [laughs] He did it.
- Yeah, the cat story again.
So, Europe by rail.
That sounds so romantic.
You want to write a book,
you got to do research.
What's Sadie supposed to
do in all these places
while you're reading musty
old scrolls about farming?
Don't worry about me. I have a whole
list of clients I need to hunt down.
Mmm. I'm sure you're
gonna get them all, dear.
I know I will.
- Yeah, she will.
- [Mom chuckles]
Art curating is so much more
exciting than I imagined.
- Oh, yeah. Mm-hmm.
- Yeah. God, like, I want to be you.
I mean, except the part where
you're sleeping with my brother.
- [Mom laughs] Ah.
- What?
- [Mom, Sadie chuckling]
- Just, please.
- So...
- [Dad] We're at the dinner table.
You guys promise to take care of
this little guy while we're gone?
Yes, I love succulents.
- How hard is it to keep a cactus alive?
- Sometimes harder than you think.
- But worth it.
- Very much.
Aw. [chuckles]
I mean, we're talking
about a cactus. Right?
You water it once a month.
- Or are we talking... Okay. It's subtext.
- [Mom] Okay.
- That's right.
- There's a...
- There's a hidden meaning.
- Yep. There's... And then...
- Levels.
- [Dad] Okay, that's great.
- Your mother and I have a...
- Oh, there's no "mother and I" story.
- It's not about a cactus.
- [Mom] No, it is not.
- It involves wrestling.
- [all laughing]
Did he ever tell you that
he wrestled in high school?
Keep drinking your wine.
[stammers] Okay.
[engine revs]
- Hey, babe, I'm sorry I'm late.
- [whistles] Nice car.
Are you sure the CIA didn't let
you keep Utami's money after all?
Ha, you wish. I'm
borrowing this.
How was your meeting
with Professor Kirkland?
- Really good.
- Yeah?
He gave me some
amazing research.
- [groaning]
- [Sadie] This is Raul.
He's an arms dealer,
but business stays in the car.
Hmm?
[clicks tongue]
Date night. [sighs]
[muffled shouting]
Us time.
["Love Again" playing]