Whoo
Come on
Who's the man
with the master plan?
Who's the man?
Who's the man
with the master plan?
Who's the man?
I used to kick it
with the thugs
Pushin' drugs
in the park
Makin' every mark
That was out
after dark
Stick 'em
for their loot
Cut 'em up,
then I'd dash
And when
I had to shoot
I'd nutted up
for the cash
Ran down the block
with my .45 Glock
Capped off a round,
everybody hit the ground
The next thing I heard
was a siren
Couldn't turn around,
money grip kept firin'
Runnin' for the ride,
I can't go inside
I'd rather that I died,
I got too much pride
I guess it's just something
that you can't understand
My gun's in my hand,
tell me who's the man?
Who's the man
with the master plan?
Who's the man?
Who's the man
with the master plan?
Who's the man?
Who's the man
with the master plan?
Who's the man?
Who's the man
with the master plan?
Who's the man?
I used to sell yayo
back in the day-o
Ran with the gang,
had all my homie's slang
Grams to the quarters,
I'm takin' all the orders
Makin' all the runs
Rakin' in the funds
I always got my gun,
it's that old 6-shooter
I'm the king
of the neighborhood
Crazy white peckerwood
People thinkin'
Danny lost his mind
It must have been
from all the wine, man
And all the hard times
Like chillin' in the park
in the dark with the crew
I'm always gettin' high,
I saw my man die
Now I got the work
and the dough
25 grand and
the 5 keys of blow
I got to relocate
and start all over
But watch it blow up
like a supernova
I keep my game in tight
and follow my plan
My gun's in my hand,
so tell me who's the man?
Who's the man
with the master plan?
10, 20, 30, 40,
50, 60, 70, 80, 90...
1...2...
Morning, Brenda.
Wanna get in?
Sorry, I got
man business.
Whoo!
Brenda's got man business.
Look at her, man.
Yo, check it out.
Check it out.
Yo, Brenda,
what's up, baby?
Damn!
That
was House of Pain
with ''Who's the Man?''
here on the Kid
Capri music show.
It's 55 degrees
and sunny
in New York City...
and it's time to
open up the airwaves...
and let the
audience take over.
Our first caller's
from Flatbush, Brooklyn!
You're on the air!
This is Rosanna Rodriguez...
Rivera Ramirez
Hernandez de la Cruz...
and I wanna give a shout out
to Tito the 40-Ounce King...
and Jose in Riker's lsland.
Don't worry--I'm keeping
that coochie warm, baby!
Damn.
I bet that coochie's warm.
Yo, this is
Deep Jack Jones...
from Patterson,
New Jersey...
and I want to give
a shout out...
to my girl Judy...
my son Elijah,
my brother K-Love...
my sister Wanda,
my dog Ziggy...
and my cat Muffy--
Hey, hey, hey, slow down.
We only have so much time.
You understand, my brother?
Let's get to the next caller.
You're on the air.
Kid, this is
Juanita from Strong lsland.
I wanna give a shout out
to my man Miguel...
who hasn't come
home in 2 nights.
Fuck you, Miguel!
You hear me, motherfucker?
Chill! Chill!
The F.C.C. is gonna
shut me down.
You understand
what l'm saying?
Yo, check this out.
This is the Kid Capri
radio show.
We want y'all
to sit back, relax...
and feel the vibe
of New York City.
I'm out,
but I'll be back...
so chill out.
What do you think about
those condos, Albert?
I don't know why they building
them condos in Harlem, Nick.
It don't make no sense.
Black man can't live
in no condo.
I hear you.
Want some talcum powder
for your neck?
I love that talcum powder.
A condo's a good investment.
What you talking
about investments?
Give me
that $20 you owe me.
What $20?
Look, Gerald, everybody's
doing that B-boy thing.
Look like someone took
a chainsaw to their head.
Let me hook you up,
give you something new...
something fresh!
Yo, fuck
good and fresh, man.
Just hook my shit up
the regular way: fade.
Fade, fade, fade.
That's all everybody want.
Fine, it's your head.
Back the fuck up
off me, man.
Why you touching me
like that for?
You know you like it.
You be my way soon.
Yo, whatever you say.
Save that shit.
That's right.
Whatever I say is right.
I'll ride you like...
one of them go-go
dancers on ''Soul Train.''
Lickin' her toes
all in my mouth.
Working myself up
toward her thighs.
Kissing ever so gently
around her gut.
Then I started
kissin' on her titties.
Then, you know
she's got a big mouth.
She says, um--she says...
''What you gonna do
with my lips?''
''I says, I'm gonna put
some crazy glue on you...
if you don't
shut the fuck up.''
You need to stop talking
all that shit, G.
Hey! Nigger dude...
I'm not talking no shit.
What you laughin' at, Ray,
with your ugly ass?
Look like you bit a brick.
He's right.
You through.
What's up, everybody?
Hey, how you doing?
Good, man.
What's up, man?
What's up, Roscoe?
What up? What up?
Come on.
Get in the chair, man.
Come on, Roscoe,
get in the chair, man.
Yeah, Roscoe, get in
the chair, man.
Keep your dick fingers
off them clippers, man.
Look what you did to my shit
the last time I was in here.
That's in!
That's the new Hammer!
Fuck, Hammer, man.
My shit is like
George Fucking Jefferson, man.
My shit is backed up
like traffic, man.
Man, if he
don't want his cut...
can I get mine cut now?
You next!
Always next.
Motherfucker,
please!
Roscoe,
get in the chair!
It's got to be
an improvement.
Got to!
Yo, I'll kick
both your asses.
And we're
moving on up
Movin' up--
- Weezy--
- We--
Hello, fellas.
Hey, Nick.
Hey, Frankie.
Who's playing today?
I am!
Holy Mother of Mary.
Let's, uh,
just get going here, huh?
Give me my
8-2-1, Frank.
Give me 7-5-4.
1-8-4, and if
I don't make my rent,
I'm giving your number
to my landlord.
A little snippy there,
Mushmouth.
I really--I don't know
about your whole attitude.
Get your hands...
- Hey, Big Nick.
- Hey.
How long's the wait, man?
No wait at the end, Boogie.
...for letting me
touch his hair.
You the one that fucked
his hair up the last time.
Man, I wouldn't let them
2 brothers cut my taxes.
I think I'll wait.
Half price.
Half price, Roscoe.
Hey, Nick,
you playing today?
Uh, 4-6-2.
I feel lucky, Frankie.
Great. You love 4-6-2.
Hey, Nick, you really
know Sugar Ray Leonard?
Yup. I cut his hair
right in this chair.
Wow. You know,
I grew up with him
on 109th and Amsterdam
in the same building.
He grew up in Maryland,
Frankie.
A tremendous fighter.
Hey, Nick, why let
that white boy in here?
You just mad because
he makes more money than you do.
Damn squirrel makes
more than he does.
A crippled squirrel.
Uh-oh, Mushmouth Rockefeller,
come on, and sit down here.
Can I get a cut?
No wait down at the end.
- My man.
- What's up?
Hey, get that there
on the other side!
Adrian! Adrian!
All right, homes,
you're the victim...
of another Doctor Dré
and Ed Lover masterpiece.
Yo, man, what'd you do
to my hair, man?
And that'll be
17.50 plus tip.
Yo, man, what did you do
to my hair?
Damn!
You better put your head
in a bag, man.
I wouldn't let them brothers
cut my grass.
Shut up, K.K.
See, this is...
that new Wesley Snipes
''New Jack City, Part 6'' shit.
Man, Wesley Snipes
after the money ran out!
Oh, Wesley was here yesterday.
I gave him his last cut.
When was Wesley Snipes
in this chair, man?
When your ass was
at White Castle.
Now be quiet.
Come on. Why you gotta be
bullshitting everybody, man?
What did you do
to my hair, man?
Now, you gotta hold
your head at the angle.
Man, see, women are gonna think
you're a big Wesley Snipes.
Go, Wesley, go Wesley
Go, go, go Wesley
It's your birthday
Ed Lover, you a liar!
Yo, Brenda.
Shut up, Dré!
You been telling people
you're sleeping with me?!
But, Brenda,
I ain't--
Don't ''But, Brenda'' me.
You ain't nothing
but a virgin anyway.
Who?! Me?!
Ed lover?!
I ain't no virgin.
I ain't!
Oh!
- Damn!
Ooh!
Fuck Tyson.
- Mmm!
Fuck him.
So her panties
around my neck, right?
Around your neck?
Yeah, yeah, so she said to me,
''Ed, baby...
I want you to take
your hand''...
I bet she did.
''And put it right here...
'''cause you know
the way I like it...
when you put your hand
right there.''
Why are you lying to me?
Shut your lying mouth
and sweep, boy.
Oh, come on, Nick.
How come we always gotta sweep
up after everybody, man?
Yeah, Nick. We've been
here for over a year.
Ed, Dré, you know
I love you like sons, right?
- Yeah.
We've gone through a whole
lot together, haven't we?
True. We've been
through a whole lot.
For the last 6 months,
all I've been getting...
is complaints
about your haircuts.
I ask you to straighten up.
You haven't done it.
You 2 are the worst
barbers in Harlem.
What you trying
to say, Nick?
I have to let you go.
Fired? Come on, Nick.
Come on, Nick.
Ain't nothing happening.
Nothing happening.
I'm serious.
You boys have got to find
careers for yourselves.
I was just reading
in the paper today...
the police force
is hiring brothers.
- The police?!
Uh-uh, Nick. Uh-uh.
Ain't trying
to be the man.
Dré, you trying
to be the man?
I am not trying
to be the man.
See that, Nick?
Dré don't want
to be the man.
I don't want
Nobody here wants
to be the man, Nick.
Give me one reason.
- Rodney King!
It's a job, boys.
It's too violent, Nick.
Man, we not doing that.
You're always watching
karate movies.
Man, those Bruce Lee movies
are B.S., man...
but when you the man...
people really shoot at you.
That's right.
Anyway,
we got another career.
What is it this week?
We're gonna be
nightclub promoters, man.
That'll be real risky
for you boys.
See, me and my man--we
live right on the edge, man.
I'll tell you what.
If you take the test,
you can stay here...
till you find out
the results.
If you don't...
I'll fire both
your asses right now.
What's wrong with you?!
I saw a rat, Nick.
What's up with that?
What you laughing at?
How can you be scared
of a little rat...
you big wuss?
Hey, Nick, I can't believe...
he pissed in his pants
over a little rat.
You're a wuss, man.
Knock it off, both of you!
If you don't take the test,
you won't get paid no more!
That's it!
Yo, man, come on.
Get back.
Come on, man, you
bad-haired motherfucker.
Go to the end
of the line, baby.
One line. One line.
Come on, man,
stop holding back.
Brother, chill out, man.
Yo, there ain't
no guest list.
So stop talking that.
There ain't no guest list.
Hey, ho
You drew a picture
of my morning
But you couldn't
make my day
I'm rockin'
and you're yawning
But you never
look my way
I'm lickin'
down you, darlin'
In every single way
Your funny flow
is foreign
And a green card's
on the way
This ain't got to do
with shampoo
But watch your
head and shoulders
Brother older bold enough
to fold ya, yo, I told ya
A raid afraid of what I made
plus played a funky fit
So save ya flips plus tricks
For that music
and the monkey bit
Thank you.
Dré needs you upstairs
right now.
It's an emergency.
Sweatin' his balls off.
All right.
Here go the money, Frankie.
Yo, George,
I'll be right back.
Frankie, it's $10.
No skimming.
I know. $10.
It's $15.
$20. $20.
- I'm sorry. $20.
- $20.
20-damn-dollars.
Get your ass on in there.
What you looking at,
old scarecrow?
Who you calling
a scarecrow?
40 for you.
Hey, ho
You heard a lot about
a brother gaining mo' ground
Being low down,
I do the showdown
With any little ho round
I wanna know
who you're believing
Through your funny reasons
Even when I'm sleeping
you think I'm cheatin'
You said I know you're
Mr. O.P.P. Man
Yo, P.P. Man,
won't only see me, man
You should've known that
when we hit in the stack
That I was with it a bit,
not to consider the rep
I did your partner
cause she's hot as a baker
Cause I'm naughty by nature
Not cause I hate ya
You put your heart in a part
of a part that spreads apart
Even though I forgave ya
when you had a spark
Yo, man,
I'm telling y'all...
y'all got that look.
I could make y'all
the dopest rappers.
Hype, my man here
got crazy contacts.
Motherfucker, please.
Listen,
y'all, cockstrong.
When I finish with y'all,
y'all gonna be hotter
than Public Enemy...
E.P.M.D., and Vanilla Ice!
And Vanilla Ice.
Motherfucker, please.
Tell 'em.
Ho
Hey, ho
Hip-hop hip-hip-hop
hip-hip-hop hooray
There's many hungry
hip-hoppers
One reason
hip-hop's hip top today
Swerve what ya heard
cause I ain't bailing hay
Ain't choppin' no crops
but still growin' every day
Here's a thunder sound
from the wonders found
From the underground
town down the hill
Feel how illtown
drown smiles to frowns
Snatchin' crowns from clowns
Beat downs are found
Don't know me,
don't come around
Tippy tippy pause,
tippy tippy pause
Sometimes creepin' up
I eat em up
Your style is older
than Lou Rawls
Peace to this one
and that one and them
That's when I shout out
and I didn't miss one friend
Yo, man, Naughty By Nature
is ripping shit, man.
How we doing?
Yo, we cleared
about 2,000 so far, man.
- We way up.
- Aah!
That's 3 months' rent,
homeboy.
Yo, man, Nick
must have been crazy...
to make us take
that police test.
I'm telling you something,
man...
Nick's gonna be
frickin' surprised...
when he find out we ain't taking
nobody's police test.
You understand
what I'm saying?
And every hood, G
That's right,
my fight is ill
Peace goes to L.O.N.S.
and Quest
Nice and Smooth
and Cypress Hill
I live and die
for hip hop
This is hip hop of today
I give props to hip hop,
so hip hop hooray
Ho
Hey, ho
Hey, ho, hey
Everybody get the fuck
down on the floor!
Everybody
on the motherfucking floor!
Next person that moves is
dead in this motherfucker.
All right!
Give it up!
Give up all your shit!
Damn it!
This ain't no joke.
Don't fuck with me!
Give it here!
Put it in
the fucking bag!
Give it up!
Take it off!
Bring it over!
Give me the money, man.
Yo, give me--
yo, give me the money, man!
Real man don't need a gun.
Sucker.
Give me the fucking wallet.
Why don't you
get out of my face?
Damn.
Put your fucking head down.
What you looking at?!
Name?
Date of birth?
Social security number?!
Why they gotta know all that?
It's what you gotta do
on most job applications.
But I don't want
the damn job.
You got any other
bright ideas?
We're about to be evicted.
Why are you holding on
to this piece of property...
like it's your wife?
I got my stake here, Lionel,
don't you understand that?
Sell it, man.
It's just a barber shop.
You're being offered
a fortune.
You got junkies and
dealers in this block.
Later, man.
See you, Nick.
Bye to you, Lionel.
Good night, K.K.
Get home safe, son.
Lionel, look at the pictures
on my wall here.
Muhammad Ali, Marvin Gaye,
Adam Clayton Powell.
I cut Adam Clayton Powell's
hair in this chair.
I was so nervous,
I almost cut the man.
Just look
outside the window.
You got pipeheads
and crack dealers...
right out there.
The kids can't play
in the street anymore.
Didn't used to be
like that, Nicky.
We've got to get all this
bad shit outta here.
L.D., how we gonna get the bad
shit out with me selling?
We've got to stay here,
brother.
The people have got to take
responsibility for this mess...
not the government...
and not some outside
real estate developer...
like the one
you're working for. Here.
Demetrius is not
the problem, Nicholas.
He's just a white boy
with a lot of money...
and if he wants
to invest up here...
I say let's get a taste.
Every man's free to make his
own choices, right, L.D.?
Don't forget
who you are, brother.
Don't forget who you are.
Ed, Dré, lock up.
All right, Nick.
See you later, Lionel.
Good night.
No show.
Give me all.
Get it, yo.
Get yours, yo.
Love it, Rashid.
I'm telling you...
don't let me catch you
on this block again.
Yo, man, put that gun down,
man. What's up with you?
Cool out, man.
I know this old fool.
You gonna be sorry you ever
pulled a gun on me, old man.
I remember when your mother
would bring you...
to my shop for haircuts.
Now you're out here
selling stuff to your people.
You got Billy and Rashid
out here with you.
You know what
you need to do, man?
You need to get that gun
the fuck out my face...
because you ain't
fittin' to use it, man.
Take Dracula with you.
Yeah, fuck all you
motherfuckers.
Fuck you old ass bastards, man.
Yadda, yadda.
Yadda, yadda, yadda.
Yeah, next time we'll
rip you a new asshole...
you stupid son of a bitch.
They're breakin'
my heart, man.
These kids are
breakin' my heart.
I know. Put your gun away now.
Put your gun away.
Yeah, it's all right.
Let's get out of here.
Let me buy you a drink, man.
Yo, man, you eat
some of my chips?
Why you always
think about food, man?
I don't always think
about food.
I think about
other things.
That's all you worried about.
You don't think
about nothing else.
I think about
some other stuff.
What?
Girls, man: Tall ones,
short ones, big ones--
Please, Dré. Please.
Ed Lover, what's up, man?
How you doing?
Yo, Jose, what's up, man?
I'm just coolin', man.
- Word.
- Who's that?
That's my man,
Jose Gomez, man.
We stole a car together
when we was 15.
I ain't seen him since.
Hey, yo, Jose,
this is my man Dré.
Yo, what's up, Dré?
How you doing, man?
Word up, man.
Yeah, Jose, say hi to
your sister for me, man.
Yeah, don't even try that.
I am John Boothby.
I'm the proctor.
The what?!
What's a proctor?
This is the standard
police exam.
Please answer
all the questions...
to the best
of your abilities,
and don't forget to use
your number 2 pencils.
Begin.
- Yo, man.
- What's up?
How you finish
the test so fast?
I spelled ''abbacadaba''
all the way down.
You did what?
I spelled ''abbacadaba''
all the way down.
My man! Yo, I did the same
exact thing, man.
No way we passing that test.
Definitely not.
Look, man, you were
not with Lorraine, man.
I'm telling you.
Last night at my house...
on the couch, man.
I don't believe you.
- Me and lorraine.
- No.
She's all over me, man.
I'm telling you.
Yo, I heard y'all
2 wanted to be the man.
What's up with that?
Nah, man,
we flunked that test.
Ain't nothing happening.
So why you wanna
be the man, anyway?
Why? What do you
2 knuckleheads wanna be?
What you think?
Rappers.
Rappers?!
You 2 can't even
dress yourselves.
Yeah, suckers!
A bunch of wise-apples, man.
You want apples?
3 for $1.00.
I also got grapes!
Special on tomatoes.
Hey! Where you going?!
Now, look, Lionel.
I hired you to acquire
certain properties in Harlem.
I must say I'm very
chagrined...
that your friend Nick...
who owns a very important part
of that Godforsaken block...
has refused to sell to me.
I can't make any moves
until I acquire his property.
I've done everything
I possibly--
No, you haven't!
You must take care of this.
We had a deal.
And if you renege on it...
I'll give your markers
back as a gift...
to the guys that you
owe that money to.
Now, that would be
very unfortunate.
Joey, what happened here?
Building burnt down
this afternoon...
and of course the fire
department was late...
just like they was
last week up the block.
Ain't nobody looking out
for us out here, man.
Damn!
Nick, where we gonna live?
Where we gonna go, man?
What's the landlord doing
about this?
That Demetrius ain't nothin'.
That motherfucker
don't give a Goddamn...
about what happens to
none of us around here.
He owns this building?
He owns most
of the neighborhood.
These people gonna stay
in the church tonight.
I'll--I'll let you in.
Come on.
Bring your children with me.
We're going with Nick, man.
Come on,
let's go with Nick.
Fuck Demetrius.
Let's get out of here, man.
Later for this fire department.
Look at Jed Clampett.
The man shoots
at a possum...
and strikes oil.
How come that shit
don't happen to us?
This ain't Hollywood, man.
This is Homeywood.
I want to be
Jed Clampett.
What for?
He's got a phat house
in Beverly Hills!
With his granny.
He's got more money
than Bill Cosby.
You ever see Jed Clampett
with a woman?
He's got a swimming pool.
You can't swim.
Elly May is fly.
You right.
But they're related,
and if you Jed Clampett...
you got that fool Jethro
living with you.
Man, l'd kick
his monkey ass out.
But you can't do
none of that...
'cause you
here with me, Dré.
And you ain't never
gonna get rich...
and you ain't moving
to Beverly Hills.
Is anything ever
gonna happen to us?
Someday, my brother.
That's it?
Life ain't
no TV show, Dré.
Look at that fool
Jethro, man!
I hate that motherfucker!
Throw his ass out, Jed!
Get him out!
We are not going
to the police academy...
are we?
Ain't no way
that's gonna happen, man.
No way, no how.
You are police officers now!
Being a police officer
is about one thing!
Who knows what that is?!
Harassing
black people.
It's about order!
We are the people
who have to maintain order!
Order in our own lives,
and order on the job!
That means you can't go
into a fried chicken joint...
and eat the Goddamn
party plate anymore!
Is that clear?!
- Why not?
- What?!
He said why not?
And if my man likes
fried chicken, he can--
I don't like
your attitude, boy!
Boy is a white
racist word.
Shut the fuck up, pig!
I know how
you got in here...
and I'm gonna
be watching you!
Did you see him
wrinkle my shirt, man?
Yeah, he fucked up
your shirt.
Did you see him wrinkle
my shirt, man?
What's wrong with
old Mr. Clean?
Black Kojak trying
to be better than Baretta.
Freeze!
Oh!
Every once in a while,
there are civilian losses.
Try to avoid it.
Next!
Ready...
What the hell?!
Get out of here!
Next!
Ready...
Ooh!
Get--get out of here!
You are gonna last about
2 minutes on the street!
Next!
No, no, no, y'all!
You're gonna blow
your johnsons off.
Do it police style!
That's uptown style.
Gimme some.
Get back in line!
Ow!
Captain...
they screwed up every drill,
every exercise...
and they have no respect
for police regulations.
You know, when I was
in Vietnam with Nick...
he was just like you 2.
He had no time
for regulations...
but he was a helluva lot
smarter than you 2 clowns...
and he could get away with it.
You were in 'Nam with Nick?
You don't think
you got in here...
by the merit system, do you?
Now get your act together
and do what Griles says.
Now get the hell
out of here.
- Yes, sir.
Take it easy on them,
Sergeant.
They're all right.
Yes, sir.
Amen!
I know God heard us today!
- Mm-hmm.
One of our community
leaders...
has asked to speak
to you today.
Is it all right?
Yes!
Let's have an amen
for our brother...
Deacon Nick Crawford.
Amen!
Thank you very much.
Thank you, brother.
We in the Harlem community...
are faced with the threat
of creeping gentrification.
Oh, that's a fancy word.
It means that people move
to your block...
and make it nice.
They make it so nice...
you can't afford
to live there...
unless you a judge,
or something like that.
Now, we have got to let
the people behind this...
know what time it is.
We have got to gain control
of our neighborhood.
We need to support
our own businesses.
We need to own
our own homes.
We need to take Harlem back!
Now, I'm gonna
lead a demonstration...
to stop these condos...
and I want to see
all y'all there!
Give us back our
neighborhood!
Don't go on,
the strip is good...
Give us back
our neighborhood!
Don't go on,
the strip is good...
To protest
the gentrification of Harlem...
by outside developers.
Our own Ralph McDaniels
was on-site...
to interview the organizer
of the march Nick Crawford.
Do you really think
you'll be able...
to stop Demetrius?
The man has got
to be stopped.
He's turning people
from their homes.
The people in Harlem
have got to stop...
the colonization
of their neighborhood.
We have to give ownership
back to these people.
You can't keep 'em
down on the plantation.
They got to rise up.
He says he's building condos.
I don't see
no building going on.
Oh, no, Dré!
Look, man!
Nick's on TV!
The big problem in Harlem
is Demetrius.
Crawford is a local merchant...
who has owned
a barber shop...
You call us, boss?
I need to talk to you
about a problem I'm having.
I'm telling you,
Redd Foxx is alive.
Man, you crazy!
Redd Foxx ain't alive!
No, he's not dead.
He faked his own death...
so the I.R.S. wouldn't
come looking for him.
Oh, God.
Him and Sammy Davis...
are hiding out
together out in Las Vegas.
Redd Foxx dead!
Yo, man.
I want my initials
on the side of my head.
Oh, no. See,
where you been, son?
That was last year.
Why don't you let me
style you, baby?
Make you look like Peabo.
- Oh, shit!
- What the hell?
What up?
Wait. Wait.
Hold up, guys.
Now--now this
is fucked up!
Oh, lookee here.
Lookee here.
My boys are cops.
Well, all right.
Wait. Hold up, man.
You mean to tell me...
they gave y'all guns?
Say, who in the fuck...
believe you 2
niggers cops, man?
Look at you--looking
like before and after.
I swear to God.
I wish you would
try to arrest me.
You'd be wearing 3 shoes.
2 on your feet,
and one in your ass.
Back off, man.
I know y'all brothers
ain't doing no real work.
I bet y'all writin'
parking tickets.
Y'all need to represent...
comin' here with
that bullshit, man!
Hold it!
We're here to fight
the forces of evil...
to make the streets safe...
for you people to walk on.
So don't fuck with us.
Y'all are police!
It's wonderful!
Come on.
Come on, man!
What? I love
a man in uniform.
You're looking mighty fly...
in that uniform,
Officer Dré.
Looking mighty fly yourself,
Officer Lover.
Man, this is
a trip, Dré.
I never thought
we could be cops.
You know we're going
to have to do...
a lot of explaining
in the street.
Yo!
Isn't that Jawaan's jeep?
Yeah, that's
his jeep, man.
I'm going
to pull him over...
so I can get
my $10 he owes me.
I don't understand, man.
What's going on, man?
I'm just here
chillin' like.
You see us
with our people...
me and my mens-like.
What's going on?
Why's we being prohibited?
Jawaan.
Oh, shit!
Ed Lover. You the man?
That's right, Jawaan.
I'm the man.
Who's the man?
Ed Lover's the man? Damn!
Yo, Jawaan!
Doctor Dré?!
You the man, too?
Oh, that shit
is fucked up, kid!
Fucked up!
OK, OK. Listen up.
Listen up. Quiet!
Put the magazines away, now!
You guys are
not selling enough...
of these
raffle tickets, OK?
Somebody's gonna win
this trip to the Poconos.
Get on the stick
with this, all right?
OK.
Number one:
- Barnes.
- Here.
I want you to go up
to 153rd Street.
Keep the gang members
away from the old ladies...
all right?
Got it.
- Day!
- Here.
I want you to go up
to St. Peter's.
Get the crackheads out of
the bake sale, all right?
And get that hair
out of your face.
Thank you.
All right. Uh...
Uh... Louver?
Lever?
Lover, Sergeant.
Lover.
And, uh...
Dree?
Dru?
Dra?
That's Dré, Sergeant.
Dré...
Doctor...Dré.
Yes, sir.
Everybody else dismissed.
Dree, Larva,
up here, now.
Lover.
Yes, sir?
Have a doughnut.
Thank you, Sarge.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Doc.
Doctor...Dré.
Let me ask you something.
You got a stethoscope?
No. Do you, uh--
do you work in a hospital?
- No.
- Do you have any patients?
No, no, no.
Did your mother
give that name by birth?
No.
You just decided
to become a doctor?
Yeah. OK. Uh...
Can I borrow
your billy club, please?
Thank you.
Ahem.
Ahem!
Mother--
Thank you.
You know, my, uh, brother...
went to school for 8 years
and took out $350,000...
in federally financed
student loans...
that he's paying back
at an interest rate of 18%.
So he should be done
paying that about...
I don't know--when he's
about 75 years old...
just so he can
call himself Dr. Cooper!
Excuse me, Sarge...
mind if I have
a doughnut?
No...
you may not have
a doughnut, OK?
You will never have
a doughnut again, ever.
another doughnut, OK?
Lover can have as many
doughnuts as he wants.
He can have
a dozen doughnuts.
He can have 2 dozen doughnuts.
He can strap a fag bag
full of doughnuts...
around his waist
when he goes to work.
He can have a giant doughnut
on the top of the squad car, OK?
But you will never
have another doughnut.
You can't even say
the word ''doughnut.''
Do you understand?
The word ''doughnut''...
is no longer
in your vocabulary, OK?
If you meet
a guy named Don...
you call him by
his last name from now on.
That's the way it works.
No bagels. No life savers.
Nothing round
with a hole in it! Nothing!
Now...here's the situation.
You guys are the good guys...
and you chase and arrest
the bad guys.
What a surprise, huh?
It's a good system.
It works.
And here's your assignment:
all of Harlem, OK?
From Lennox Ave.
to the river.
And I want all crime
and all drugs...
stamped out
by 6:00 tonight, OK?
You got that, Doc?
Dismissed...
Larva.
Larva?
What kind of doughnuts
they got over there, man?
Oh, a whole lot.
A wide assortment.
Jelly?
Jelly, eclair, crullers.
Think I can get some?
The long ones
with the cream.
Those, too.
Jesus.
This is a piece of junk.
I can't believe
they give us...
this big hunk
of scrapola, man.
At least we got a car.
What you complaining about?
I think the sergeant
dissed you, man.
I don't know.
I think the sergeant
kind of likes me.
No, I'm telling you.
He dissed you.
Come on.
Let's go see Bubba.
Yo, man. Remember that old
TV show ''Mod Squad?''
That was some
dope shit, man.
Oh, hell, yeah.
Clarence Williams III
was Mack Daddy!
You know, that big
Afro-wearin' brother--
you know he was goin'
with Peggy Lipton, right?
The white girl?
The same white girl that
got married to Quincy Jones.
She's into that
black culture shit...
or some shit like that.
You know what I'm saying?
Get up against the wall!
Oh, man!
Man, why the cops
always hassling us?
Now, drop your pants
around your ankles...
and sing me a tribute
to your favorite black woman.
They want to see
our butts or something?
Sing!
Super fine
She's got it going on
Something's going wrong
Super fine
Well, boys.
You guys sing real good.
Hey, my man, what's up?
Shut up.
Yo, Bubba, man.
Can you do some magic
to this car?
Yeah...
I always wanted
to soup up a police car.
Word up.
I'm telling you, man.
When I get that
police car...
I'm going to turn it
into a lovemobie.
I want fur pillows,
reclining seats--
Damn! I forgot
to tell Bubba about the VCR.
Are you Ed Lover?
The one and only, baby.
Ow.
That's for my sister Lorena...
you ain't bonin'.
Lover, come here and
check this out, man.
She just knocked
the shit out of me.
You didn't see that?
Forget that, man. Come over here
and check this out, man.
I don't know nobody
named Lorena.
Oh, OK.
They've been drilling
down here for about 6 months.
Man, it don't look like
they're building...
any condominiums over here.
Let's go see what
they are building.
Yo. Pull the stake
and bring it in the corner.
Excuse me.
The far corner.
What are you guys doing?
Just taking
soil samples.
Soil samples?
What for?
Standard procedure, Officer.
We check the soil before
we start construction.
So it's OK if we borrow
one of your soil samples?
Uh, I don't think
that's possible.
Why not?
There's enough dirt
around here for everybody.
This is private property.
Well, how about
if we just borrow...
some of your
private property?
I don't think
Mr. Demetrius...
would like that very much.
You tell Mr. Demetrius
to kiss my ass.
Come on. We got to go talk
to Nick. Come on. Let's go.
Private property.
Soil sample.
Precious Lord
Take my hand
Lead me on
Let me stand
I am tired
And I am weak
But I am worn
Oh
Through the storm
and the night
Oh
Lead me
Lead me on
to the light
Take my hand
Oh, precious Lord
And oh
We love you
Brother Nick,
we love you
We'll always love you
And that precious Lord
Oh oh
Oh, that precious Lord
We just need you,
need you, need you
Need you,
n-n-n-need you
Oh, precious Lord
Appreciate that, man.
I'm sorry.
Thanks a lot
for coming.
You're welcome.
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
Hey.
Hey, what's happening, man?
You guys remember
my niece Teesha.
She was in Europe
for the past few years.
That's definitely
home's loss.
Thank you.
Teesha.
Would y'all excuse me
for a second?
I'm sorry to hear
about Nick.
- Sure.
- I'll be back.
Can I have a word
with you guys?
- What's up?
- In private.
I talked with Nick's
lawyer this morning.
You guys have been
named in the will.
He left you
the barber shop.
- The barber shop?
- Damn.
And I know some people
that'll pay you...
a lot of money
for that property.
See, I don't care
about money right now, man.
I just want to find out
who killed Nick.
Maybe it was
the same people...
that's been
setting these fires.
You have any other
ideas, Lionel?
He had a nasty exchange...
with that
crack dealer Chauncey.
Thanks, Lionel.
- Thanks Lionel.
- See you later.
Come on, Dré.
Damn! Chauncey!
- Bubba.
- Yo, B.
How's the ride?
It freaks.
Let's get him.
Whoever burned
this barber shop down...
knew exactly
what they were doing.
It's going to cost
a fortune...
to put this place
back on its feet, man.
Yeah. Money we ain't got
right now, partner.
Money we ain't
never gonna have.
Shit.
Hey, yo, Dré,
check this out, man.
What you got
there, man?
This look
familiar to you?
Nick never owned
a gun like this.
This ain't Nick's gun.
Let's bring it to Fuji.
Fuji!
Can you do a test
on this thing?
Test on what?
- Test on gun.
- Gun kill Nick?
- Do a test.
- On the gun.
- When you want?
- Today is good.
- Today?
- On the gun.
On the gun?
No need.
Gun German.
Cannot be traced.
An untraceable German gun?
- Later, Fuj.
- Hai.
Hai.
Eh, Doctor Dré, Ed Lover...
what a pain in the ass.
Say, brother...
say, brother...
you need to get off
that stuff, man.
That's stunting your growth.
Damn, Dré,
if you're the man...
I've definitely been
on the crack pipe too--whoa!
Man, Chauncey's not here.
Wait a minute.
Baby, you should
be up outta here.
Yeah. Don't be...
Baby, I got money.
You buggin'.
Excuse me.
What's up...Chauncey?
Name's Nighttrain,
all right, nigger?
Your name is Chauncey?
Vanessa, shut the fuck up.
What is this, man?
Halloween or some shit?
Your eyes do not
deceive you, brother.
Say, man, you
know anything...
about Nick's murder, man?
I know something about it.
I know homeboy got smoked...
but I ain't got
shit to do with it.
I ain't got no
beef with him, man.
Yo, man!
What's up, huh?
Mmm-mmm.
Oh, shit!
Who's going to pay for
my fucking booze, pig?
Mind yours!
Where'd you get the piece
from, Chauncey?!
My name is Nighttrain, fool!
Yo, man!
Where'd you get
the gun from, man!
It fell off a fucking
truck, all right?
Come on, man!
What's up here?
Ooh...
Oh, OK. Uh-huh.
Now I got you on
gun charges and drug charges.
You tell me a story.
Look, man...
you need to just cool
the fuck out on me, man.
You need to be talking
to Lorenzo Martin--
315 West 137 Street--
but I ain't no
motherfucking snitch.
You ain't heard that
from me, man.
What you lookin' at?
Anybody want
to go for a swim?
Y'all folks
have a nice day.
Let's go, Dré.
Later, Chauncey.
Nighttrain.
Nighttrain, man!
Nighttrain!
You...
don't even try.
It don't look like
Lorenzo lives there.
I think Chauncey played
us like a B-side, man.
I told you he was frontin'.
You didn't say
nothing, Dré.
Ed, look, man, you don't
listen to nobody, man.
All you do is lie about all
the women that you ain't got.
Please, man, OK?
Central, this is car 2899.
l need an address
on a Chauncey Jackson...
A.K.A.: Nighttrain. Over.
Yeah, I think this
is Chauncey's house.
Gotta be, man.
It's gotta be.
Knock on the door.
Open the door, Chauncey.
It's Ed and Dré. Knock again.
Chauncey,
we going to count to 3...
then I'm going
to kick in the door...
then we're going
to kick in your ass.
One...
Ready?
Yaaahhhhh!
Damn, Dré.
Somebody talked to that
motherfucker already.
Could have cut
himself shaving.
Shit. He's dead
as a motherfucker, man.
What were you 2
guys doing here?
We thought he knew something
about the Nick Crawford murder.
So you were functioning
as detectives?
No, not really.
Look, we each
got our own...
responsibilities
on the force, fellas.
Who's your sergeant?
Sergeant Cooper.
Look, guys, you let
the real detectives...
handle this, all right?
Y'all guys just
get out of here.
Beat it!
Big Laurel and Hardy
look-alikes...
wannabe detectives.
Now what are
we going to do?
Get the results
of the dirt...
we took to the lab.
You gave him
the dirt, right?
You were supposed
to give him the dirt.
No, no, no, man.
You were supposed to give him
the dirt. Trust me.
Damn it, Dré!
I never had
the dirt, OK?
Those guys look like
Run D.M.C.
Oh, that's good.
Come on, baby.
There. That's it.
That's it.
Fuji!
Fuji, my man.
Gun untraceable.
Yeah, Fuji, we know.
We want you to check out
that soil sample...
and let us know
what's in it.
Drugs in soil?
- You tell us.
- Tell you what?
- Something in soil.
- What in soil?
You tell us.
Need police geologist.
Who's the geologist?
I call Bernstein.
- Go call Bernstein.
- Hai.
Good morning, men.
Good morning, Captain.
Sergeant Cooper tells me...
that you two have been
playing detective.
Yes, sir.
We're investigating--
Excuse me.
You're patrolmen.
And l want you
to understand...
in no uncertain terms...
that you are not
to investigate...
Nick Crawford's murder
or anyone else's.
Is that clear?
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah.
Somebody new is being
put on the case today.
I think he's a friend
of yours.
Come in, Detective.
- Griles?!
- Detective?
Got promoted.
Now Griles is going
to head the case...
and I don't want
you 2 near it.
Capisce?
- Yes, sir.
Ok, good. Dismissed.
Yo, Griles.
Griles.
Lorenzo Martin, man,
this guy, man...
he's selling this type
of gun, man.
Hey, look!
I don't want your help...
and I don't need your help.
Now you 2 dickheads...
are lucky you're
even on the force!
Now you stay
away from me...
and away from this case!
Hey, look!
This is no
''Police Academy'' bullshit...
you can just clown
your way through!
Now you stay
away from me...
and away from this case!
You got it?!
Fuckin' dickheads!
Why it be all that, man?
Dickheads.
We're doing
the best we can.
Isaac Hayes lookalike.
All right, people,
quiet down.
Quiet down.
Pipe down.
They got George back.
They got pitching.
They got the whole--
Hertzog!
What the fuck?
Why is it every time
I start a meeting...
everybody else shuts up...
you keep talking?
Shut the fuck up.
Yes, sir.
Thank you. OK...
the first order of business...
Barnes and Day,
37 collars this week.
Not bad.
Well, look who came
to join the party.
Doctor Dree and his partner
Mr. Lurver.
What'd you guys get?
You got 2 collars this week.
Pretty sure they're
the ones on your shirts.
I'm sorry. My mistake.
My mistake. Uh...
I forgot the dead guy
you apprehended...
on your day off.
Tell you what.
Everybody dismissed...
except for...guess who.
Doctor Dré.
Let's go.
Sergeant Cooper?
What is it, Lover?
May I have a doughnut?
You can have as many
doughnuts as you want.
Thanks, Sarge.
Hi.
Don't even
think about it.
I'm glad you dropped by.
Little change
in precinct policy.
As of today,
I will be known as
President Cooper.
I'm not going
to get paid or anything.
I'm not going to debate or go
on the ''Larry King Live'' show.
No--I'm just going
to be President Cooper.
As a matter of fact...
Monday, Wednesday, Friday,
I'll be President Cooper...
and Tuesday and Thursday,
I think I'll be...
King Cooper!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
And you know why?
Because I...
feel like it!
I just want to be a king,
and now l've decided...
I'm going to call myself king--
so I'm a king!
I'm a king.
King Cooper. That's me.
King Cooper...
we want to be assigned to...
the Nick Crawford murder case.
That's right. We got a--
We felt like--
But--
I got a better idea.
Tony Como.
- Tony ''Clams''?
- Mm-hmm.
- The wise guy?
- That's right.
He's supposed to be
testifying...
as a government witness in
a case over in Brooklyn...
but his gall bladder
acted up, so now...
there's apparently
a hit out on him.
We got a 24-hour
surveillance thing going on...
and you guys
are going to go over...
and relieve
the 2 officers on duty...
and take over for
the next 24 hours, OK?
But King Cooper,
we just feel that--
See you later,
King Cooper.
By the way, uh, Lover.
Yeah?
How's that doughnut?
Mmm. It's good.
And there's
a whole big box...
of chocolate doughnuts
sitting over on that table.
Hey, Clams, where are
the ashtrays around here?
What do you think this is,
a hotel?
This is a hospital.
I'm sick over here.
Relax. Your gall bladder's...
going to explode,
for Christ's sake.
Do me a favor.
Get rid of that cigarette.
There. You happy?
Hey! That's my water,
for Christ's sakes!
What did you want me to do?
Stick it up
in your ass?
You know, you're driving me
fucking crazy.
You're supposed to be
over here taking care of me.
Hey, I'm not your
fucking nursemaid.
Hi, Tony.
We're your replacements.
I'm Officer Dré.
This is Officer Lover.
We're here to protect you.
What's this?
Abbott and Costello?
You mean Amos and Andy,
don't you?
Who sent these
moulies in here?
How the fuck do l know?
I don't work here.
We'll be right outside.
Vito, do me a favor, huh?
Get rid of these guys.
Yo, Dré, man,
what's a moulie?
You're supposed
to be taking care of me.
I think it's
an uncomplimentary...
description
of a brother.
Who the fuck are you?
Damn, man. This day
is not going well at all.
I'm out.
I'll call.
Where'd that third
ace come from?
I palmed it.
Bad, man.
That's bad.
Hello?
Dré, what's up?
Bellevue?
All right.
Fellas, Frankie's
outta here.
I gotta go bail out
my homies.
Yo, why you always hang
with those pigs, man?
Steve, I told you, when
I was the only white kid...
growing up on
114th street...
them 2 are the only ones
that ever had my back.
What the fuck are you
talking about, man?
You grew up on 120th street.
That's not the point,
Billy, really.
It's about friendship--
men with other men,
playing cards.
Man, we got things to do.
We can't stand around all day
guarding this racist
piece of shit.
One more word
from the pasta king here...
I'm deflating all his tires.
I can't stand it.
Nuh-huh-huh.
Fuckin' day, man.
Fellas, sorry I'm late.
It was that 2 train.
The power went out.
In the dark, somebody
starting touching my balls!
The lights come on, I look
at this guy in a silk shirt--
Frankie, Frankie.
We got Tony Como in the room.
Tony Clams?
I love that guy!
Good, 'cause
you're guarding him.
Tell him you're a cop.
We gotta go out for a while.
It's about Nick. Cool?
Cool, yeah. Can I borrow
your hat to look legit?
Thanks, Frankie.
Gotta be realistic, fellas.
Hi, how are ya?
Detective O'Hearn.
From the 2-3.
Tony. Tony, how are ya?
Who are you?
Detective O'Hearn
from the 2-3.
Oh, good.
A white cop.
Hello, officers.
Hi. Is Mr. Demetrius available?
I'm sorry.
He's in a conference.
Well, tell him
the police are here.
This one is gonna
be real popular.
They'll be in the next
issue of ''Vogue.''
Teesha?
Ed, Dré, what are
y'all doing here?
You know each other?
Yeah.
From the same neighborhood.
Well, what can l do
to help you gentlemen?
You seem pretty interested
in Harlem, Mr. Demetrius.
Well, it's a great
neighborhood...
and I believe
it's coming back.
Did you know
a Nick Crawford?
He was that
unfortunate barber...
who was killed
by the drug dealers.
I understand he was
a model citizen.
So this is a map
of Harlem, huh?
All these buildings
on this block...
are coded red.
Except for one
the barbershop is in.
Why is that?
Here, let me show you.
All the red ones
are the ones that I own.
I'm developing
those properties...
into condominiums.
Well, what's that drillin'...
you doing uptown?
My engineers are collecting
geological samples.
It's what one does
when one builds.
How come you ain't done
no building in Harlem?
All that drillin',
no building.
Don't make sense to me!
Because it takes time to get
the necessary information.
One spends a lot of money
to put up a building.
If the preliminary steps
aren't handled carefully...
you can imagine
the results.
Would you care for
some coffee or tea?
You buying up
all the property...
around the barber shop.
Nick is leading
demonstrations...
to try to stop you.
Somebody tries to buy
the property...
but he won't sell.
Bang! He's dead.
Dré, you smell
something?
I smell bullshit.
I knew it!
I knew it smelled like
bullshit in here!
If you're implying...
that I had anything
to do with that murder...
I can assure you...
I do not do business
like that.
Now, if there's
anything else l can do...
to help you gentlemen...
No. Thanks for your time.
You know, I cannot believe
you 2 just did that--
Save the drama for your mama.
I ain't tryin' to hear.
What's up with you
and Demetrius?
We are business partners.
My uncle introduced us.
Lionel?
Yes, Lionel. He's backing
my design company.
And by the way, we're having
our first fashion show...
in a couple of days.
I would appreciate it
if y'all did not show up.
Cool. But I'm telling
you, he's dirty.
What do you think
he's doing?
I don't know, but whatever
it is, it ain't cool.
I'm a pretty good
judge of character...
and if I thought
the man was dirty,
I wouldn't be doin'
business with him.
Frank. It's Ed.
Everything cool?
No. He's gettin' to be
a royal pain in the balls...
for one thing.
Yo, Frankie, man.
Yo, gimme 4 on 615.
Sure. Can you get me
some of those catheters?
All right. Thanks.
It's impossible. I can't!
Hey, Detective.
I can for a couple of hours.
I didn't--no, I can.
Yes.
OK. 2 hours.
Good-bye.
You know what?
Maybe Teesha was right, man.
Why would Demetrius
have Nick killed?
I know she's fine, Dré...
but don't let your johnson
run your life, all right?
Who else got a motive?
What the--
Do you guys know what
happened today at 4:36?
Do you have any idea what
No, you don't.
Let me tell ya.
Tony Clams got shot.
He got fuckin' shot!
Only by the Grace of God
is he still alive!
You guys were supposed to
watch him!
You fucked me!
You might as well kiss me,
'cause you're fucking me!
Where were you guys?
Where the--
Is that jelly...
that I smell?
Bavarian cream?
Bagels?
Gimme the club.
You guys are
on foot patrol...
for the rest of your lives!
Do you understand that?
Foot patrol.
Capital ''f,''
small ''o'', small ''o''...
little tiny ''t.''
Did you ever see
a little tiny ''t''?
It's like
a little curlicue--
little--
Tell me...
that...you're...not...
touching my fucking badge!
He lost it.
The sergeant lost it.
Let's get outta here.
Yeah. I went to that Michael
Bolton concert last night.
Oh! He's such
an accomplished performer.
I was really impressed.
014 to 183
Amsterdam right away.
That's us.
Let's hit it. Let's go.
Whoa! Whoa!
What is that?
Stop it!
I can't!
Go, go, go, go!
Yo, man, I don't understand.
You guys fucked up!
You oughta be cops...
like Leon Spinks shoulda
won a beauty contest...
and that nigger ugly!
Now, Leon's a good brother.
Now, Biz Markie--
that's a ugly motherfucker!
Bullshit. Yo, yo,
I--I need a refill.
Who's comin' back
with me to the store?
Oh, man!
Why the fuck you keep
drinkin' that shit, man?
Your insides'll be fucked up
like your ugly-ass face.
I just--
Forty, you're so
messed up all the time...
you don't remember
nothin' no way!
That's fucked up--
Shut the fuck up, man.
Sound like you have
a dick in your mouth, man.
You don't make
no Goddamn sense.
Hey, fair ladies.
Hey.
What up, light skin?
Hey, I'm sorry
about Tony Clams.
Where the fuck were you?
Yolanda showed up.
What do you mean,
Yolanda showed up?
We oughta kick your ass,
Frankie.
You almost got us busted
off the force!
Hey, I did you guys
a favor...
and they tried to arrest me!
It's unbelievable.
I was in the smoking lounge
5 minutes.
Some wise guy comes in and--
boo-yah--pops Tony Clams...
and it's my fault?
I don't wanna hear
that shit, Frankie.
You supposed to be
my friend, man.
And you supposed to be guardin'
that racist piece of shit...
and you doin' the wild thing
with Yolanda.
Lorenzo!
Get that motherfucker!
Come on!
Hurry up, man!
He knows who killed Nick!
Come on!
There he goes!
Y'all go that way!
Get that motherfucker!
Don't move.
You fucked up, Ed Lover...
Tryin' to be the man.
Fuck you, Lorenzo.
Say good-bye,
Mr. Man.
So, Lorenzo,
you're in the gun business?
Naw, man,
I'm retired, man.
Where'd you get the gun?
I don't remember.
Think I should let Frankie
refresh your fucking memory?
Yo, what about my rights?
You got the rights to get your
ass thrown in the East River...
if you don't start
answerin' my questions!
All right. All right.
I don't know the guy.
All I know is he's bringing
them in from Germany.
Can I go now?
You ain't goin' nowhere!
Does anybody
have any cab fare?
Yo, man, did you
have to take a cab, man?
Man, I got there, didn't I?
After Frankie
saved my ass, man.
Me and you are
supposed to be--
Look at Flavor, man!
Yo, Dré, get me
outta here, man.
I can't do nothin'
for you, man!
Hey, Griles, what's up
with the case, man?
We're makin' progress.
When you gonna go talk
to Demetrius, man?
What's he gotta
do with it?
He know what's goin' on.
Oh, yeah?
Tell me, Sherlock.
What be goin' on?
We don't know exactly--
Yeah, yeah. Great.
I'll go arrest him.
Beat it!
Hey, Griles...
I want you to keep
your eye on those 2.
Yes, sir.
Oh, yes...
uh, maybe once more...
how's...it look?
I have no idea
what you're doing.
Perfect!
Fuji!
Ed, Dré...
this is Bernstein.
- Hi, Bernstein.
- Hey.
Where'd you guys
get this sample?
Uptown.
Guys were drilling.
Have any idea what they
might be lookin' for?
- This is peat.
- Who's Pete?!
Peat's a substance.
Found in bogs.
- Found in swamps.
- What else?
We have leaves.
Like from a tree?
Yes. From trees.
- That it?
- No, not it.
The layer above the peat,
the leaves...
is made up of sand.
Sand from the beach?
Precisely.
Peat, leaves, sand?
There's a geological profile
the drillers look for...
when they're
trying to find oil.
Oil. Like what
Jed Clampett got?
You trying to tell me
there's oil in Harlem?
Possibly.
Demetrius
is lookin' for oil!
It's very unlikely.
I mean, they never found oil
around here before.
That's why he smoked Nick.
- Hai!
Hello.
- Ed.
- What's up, Dré?
Man, what makes
a beautiful girl like that...
wanna go out with a short,
slimy sauerkraut-suckin'...
short and slimy
motherfucker like that?
I'm-a go ask.
Hold it. Aren't we supposed
to lay back a little bit?
I'm gonna throw him
off his game, man.
Looks like we got
company, y'all.
Oh, man! It's Griles!
Yo, Fab, you got
any ideas, man?
Plenty, baby.
I got you covered like
a rug on this one.
Watch this.
Come back, Daddy.
Baby, I'll be back.
Ooh, Daddy,
you're home!
You lookin' good
tonight, girl.
Mm. How you been?
Everything's cool.
Looky here, baby...
you see that kid in that car
back over there?
Yeah, I see him.
I want you to go
over there...
and I want you
to rock his world.
- You hear me?
- Yes, Daddy.
I want you to
make him scream.
Anything for you,
Daddy.
Yeah. Handle it, girl.
You look pretty hungry
back there, baby.
Why don't you call me...
when you're ready for
dessert, big boy? Rrr!
That's what
I'm talkin' about!
What's he got
that I don't got?
I'm-a go ask.
Hold that.
You got soda all on my jacket.
I got half a burger
and soda on my jacket.
Why am I gonna do that?
I'm suspending you 2
from the force...
effective immediately.
But, Captain, we got
a suspect and a motive...
in the Nick Crawford
murder case.
We think
there might be...
oil in the hood,
Captain.
Oil?
That's why Demetrius is
buying up all the property.
You see, Nick Crawford
was sitting...
on the last piece of
property on the block.
And that's why
Demetrius had him killed.
So, wait a minute.
What you're telling me...
is that one of the most
successful...
real estate developers
in this city...
is digging for oil
in Harlem?
- Yeah!
Listen to me.
There is oil
in Saudi Arabia...
not Harlem.
There is oil in Venezuela.
There is no oil
on 125th Street!
Am I clear?
But, Captain, if you--
You're lucky
that Mr. Demetrius...
is not pressing charges.
Now, clean out your lockers
and get out of here!
Hey, Mel, I need
some more tape.
Sue, we gotta
get those--
Is Teesha around?
Uh, yeah,
she's in the back.
Thanks a lot.
Hey, Mel, that tape!
Ok. You got it?
- Yeah.
- All right, good.
Yeah, these
shoes are much...
much better.
Does it have to
be so tight?
Yes, it does.
Child, for the money
you getting paid...
we can strangle you.
OK. We'll loosen it
after the show, Kelly.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, yo, Teesha.
Can we speak to you
for a minute, please?
Come on, y'all, I can't
talk to y'all right now.
I've got work
to do here.
My first show in New York
is tonight.
It's kind of important.
All right. Dana, come here.
Something's wrong in here.
Could you--
I don't know what it is.
Just fix it, please.
Outfit is really fly.
It's a new fabric.
Imported, thank you.
Now look, y'all, we all
from the same neighborhood...
and I really want to
help y'all out.
Don't get me wrong.
But this is my shit happening
here tonight, OK?
And I'm not gonna let y'all
mess this up for me.
Check this out.
We're not here
to mess nothing up.
We're here to find...
a little bit more
about Mr. Demetrius.
Well, what do you want
to know about him?
He's my financial backer...
and he imports this
new fiber for me.
From Germany?
How'd you know that?
Where's the warehouse?
In Brooklyn. Why?
Don't worry about it.
We got it.
Whatever. I got work to do.
I'll see y'all later.
Save that drama though.
Word up.
Ed Lover.
What's up, Sherise?
There she is, baby.
Baby, y'all look so good.
What the hell you doing...
telling people
I'm sleeping with you?
- Sherise--
- Un-uh! Un-uh!
Yo, I'm telling you,
Ed Lover...
don't fuck with me!
Ow! Sherise? Sherise!
I didn't--
3 times this week.
Third one.
She smacked me right
in my fucking band-aid, too.
Come on.
I swear to God, man.
How you gonna smack a man
with a band-aid on?
Man, I hope
we ain't down here...
wasting our time, man.
Man, I feel we're
getting real close now.
We're gonna find
something down here...
and nail him on it.
I hope so, man.
Yo, man, yo, Teesha likes me.
What?!
What Teesha want...
with somebody
like you, man?
She likes me.
Why does every girl
in the world...
gotta like you, man?
They don't have to.
They just do, man.
So you're bugging.
No, no, you bugging.
You bugging.
Yo, I'm not bugging, man.
You're bugging.
Man, it's dark in here.
That because
it's nighttime, man.
Stop wasting time.
Come on.
Yo, what's the number
we're looking for?
3 and 4.
Ok. There's 3,
there's 4.
It's over here.
Bingo.
God, please.
Let's get to work.
There ain't nothing
in these crates...
except this damn fabric.
Keep looking, man.
You'll find something.
There's gotta be
something in here.
Damn. Thing's tight.
Crazy.
I can't believe this.
How do you get this open?
Damn, the thing's
locked up tight, too.
Wait a minute. Look
what we got here.
Mm. Smart enough
to put Teesha's name...
all over the crates, too.
We're gonna
nail his ass.
We got him, kid.
Got him.
Drop it!
Call the boss.
Aw, come on, fellas.
You know the bad
guys are gonna lose.
That's word up.
Just like in
''The Magnificent Seven.''
Yep. I like that movie.
Or Bill Cosby
and Sidney Poitier...
in ''Uptown Saturday Night.''
I like that.
Shut up!
Demetrius.
Yeah, boss.
Yeah, we got 'em.
No. That won't be
a problem.
Can I place a call--
Shut up!
Say good night, boys.
Don't do it!
You guys all right?
Yeah.
What took you
so damn long?
Proper police procedure.
Griles.
What are you guys
doing here?
Demetrius
is smuggling guns.
This warehouse
is full of them.
You got a search warrant?
Griles, we ain't
cops no more.
Who gives a damn
about a search warrant?
Can we please go pick up
Mr. Demetrius?
These shoes
are killing me.
Go ahead, Kelly.
Just keep complaining.
You'll be modeling
post office uniforms...
I'm telling you.
Get up there!
All you do is complain.
What's happening, baby?
Didn't I see you...
on the cover
of ''Essence Magazine?''
Oh, shit. I know you ain't
trying to dis me...
with that bright-ass orange
carpet on your head.
Fuck you! Shit!
Hey, yeah.
Hey! What's
happening, baby?
Didn't I see you...
on the cover
of ''Essence Magazine?''
What have you been
telling people...
about my business
affairs, Lionel?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Don't bother
prevaricating.
Those 2 moronic police
officer friends of yours...
have gotten in my way
for the last time.
They've finally been
taken care of.
And you can be
taken care of, too.
Don't threaten me,
Demetrius.
I don't have to
threaten you, Lionel.
Sashay, sashay, sashay!
Yo, Lamar.
Oh, Doctor Dré, Ed Lover,
how y'all doing?
Lamar, where's
Demetrius at?
Oh, he's over there
in a fabulous suit.
6 buttons, buttery
leather shoes--
All right,
thanks, Lamar.
All right, y'all. Bye.
Demetrius,
where you going?
I'm sorry.
Something came up.
I have to go.
Oh, you can't leave now!
The show is great,
but I have to go.
Come on, Demetrius,
don't go!
Freeze!
You're under arrest.
Your chief is gonna be
awfully upset...
when he hears
how I've been treated.
First, he's gonna hear
about those guns...
you running through
Teesha's warehouse.
And then we're gonna
pin Nick's murder...
- to your ass.
- That's absurd.
If there's any guns
in Ms. Braxton's warehouse...
I know nothing about it.
And as far
as Nick Crawford goes...
I never murdered anyone.
If you didn't,
then who did?
You ever read the bible?
The book of ''Daniel'' says,
''Every man's sword shall be
against his brother.''
Man, what the hell
are you talking about?
Hello, yes. This is
Lionel Douglas.
I want to book
a flight for Jamaica.
Yes, tonight, yes, yes.
You already have my credit
card number there.
Yes.
Come on, come on, come on.
Lionel Douglas.
Right, that's it, yes.
OK, that's tonight, right?
OK. I'll be there.
Thank you.
Why'd you go to work
for Demetrius, Lionel?
What are you doing
in my house?!
We had a talk
with him tonight.
I smoothed over...
some uptown feathers
for the man.
There's nothing
wrong with that.
What's in Jamaica, man?
Vacation.
Kind of a spur of
the moment thing, huh?
Yes, Ed.
What else were you
doing for Demetrius?
I told you.
Nothing else?
What's your point, Ed?
This is my point.
We found a warehouse
full of guns...
out in Brooklyn, and maybe
you know about that.
And maybe you know
who killed Nick.
I don't know anything
about warehouse guns...
or who put
that bullet in Nick.
Bullet?
Everybody thinks Nick
was killed in an explosion.
The police didn't say
nothing about no bullet.
How'd you know
he got shot, Lionel?
Where you there?
Why'd you kill Nick, man?
I tried to save Nick.
I said, ''Nicky...
sell the property.''
But he wouldn't listen.
What was I supposed to do?
That shit don't make
no difference, man.
Nick loved you.
You killed
your best friend...
you sorry motherfucker!
Just shut up!
Demetrius was setting me up.
He was gonna ruin me...
and I couldn't
let that happen.
I'm on my way now...
to take care
of Mr. Demetrius.
But now, I have to...
take care of you first, Ed.
I am sorry, Ed.
Not as sorry as I am.
You all right, man?
Yeah,
I'm straight, man.
Son of a--
Well, boys...
Demetrius and Lionel
are behind bars.
I still don't know why
anyone would want to kill Nick.
There's a lot of sick people
in this world.
The important thing
is that you guys were right.
How'd you like
to rejoin the department?
No, I don't think so.
Not even if I made you...
the youngest detectives
on the force?
- Nope.
- No, I don't think so.
We're not cut out
for police work, man.
Nah, too violent.
Well, what are you guys
gonna do?
I mean, it's not like
you found oil.
You guys need jobs.
We'll think of something.
You know us.
Yo, check this out.
I'm going to the store...
to get us some more
40 ouncers...
so we can all celebrate.
Forty...
Go grab a beam, man.
Hey, George, help Mickey
with that beam, man.
All right.
Yo, Dré.
Check this out, man.
I miss Nick, man.
So do I, man.
Oh. Oh, y'all just got
men working in here.
Where's all the women at?
What's up, Teesha?
How y'all doin'?
Sorry how everything
turned out.
Yeah, well, you know,
life goes on.
Hey, we could
always use another barber.
No, got a job.
Thank you.
Dré, where the hell you
get that cannon from, man?
I hate rats, man.
Yo, what's that black stuff?
I worked for 3 hours
for this shit.
I'm telling you, this
new Spike Lee joint...
they're ''Crooklyn,'' man.
Ed told me
this is the new Arsenio.
- Arsenio who?
- Arsenio Hall.
Nah, Dré told me
this is Arsenio Hall cut.
It's the ''New Jack City,
Part 7.''
See, I know Wesley.
He wouldn't go out like that.
This original
Shabba Ranks?
I got your Shabba Ranks,
Buster.
See you later. Yo, Dré,
I thought once
we struck oil, man...
we wouldn't have
to work here no more.
I know, man.
I thought...
things were gonna
get better...
being rich
and wealthy now--
We'd be
laying on beaches...
with girls
with little bikinis.
Know what I'm saying?
Third time in 2 days...
you cut my hair, man.
I can't help it.
We ain't got no customers.
They got all the damn customers.
Look at 'em.
Yeah, Dré and his
Fat Albert ass.
Man, like he stink!
- Mmm!
And the world's
coming to an end.
- Mm-hmm!
Hey, guys, can I get a cut?
Whoo
Come on
Who's the man
with the master plan?
Who's the man?
Who's the man
with the master plan?
Hey, how you guys been?
Just great, Sarge.
Can you hold your head
to the side, Sarge?
That looks great, Sarge.
You know, if you
had a pony tail...
everything would be
just right.
Oh, is that right?
Ow, ow!
What are you doing?
Nothing. Don't worry
about it, Sarge.
I got this.
We professionals. Remember?
I'll take that.
Ouch! Ow.
Move your head
to the left, Sarge.
What's that thing for?
Don't worry about that.
These won't hurt at all.
Professionals.
We're professionals.
Put your head down, please.
Down.
This is what we did before
we were police offices.
Couldn't you use
the mirrors? Ow, ow.
Oh, we will be using
mirrors before it's done.
How's things down
at the precinct, Sarge?
Good.
Ok. Down there.
Could you hold your head
down to the side, please, sir?
You know, you really are
bashful...
I'm not paying for this.
Could you just kind of
turn your head this way!
Ow!
I used to kick it
with the thugs
Pushin' drugs
in the park
Makin' every mark
That was out
after dark
Stick 'em
for their loot
Cut 'em up,
then l'd dash
And when
I had to shoot
I'd nutted up
for the cash
Ran down the block
with my .45 Glock
Capped off a round,
everybody hit the ground
The next thing I heard
was a siren
Couldn't turn around,
money grip kept firin'
Runnin' for the ride,
I can't go inside
I'd rather that I died,
I got too much pride
I guess it's just something
that you can't understand
My gun's in my hand,
tell me who's the man?
Who's the man
with the master plan?
Who's the man?
Who's the man
with the master plan?
Who's the man?
Who's the man
with the master plan?
Who's the man?
Who's the man
with the master plan?
Who's the man?
Mic check, here I go again,
check me out
Bust the flavor
Hey
You know my clout,
rough and rugged
Funk's the contact
I hit you with
To make your head split,
trip, and do a backflip
I swing it hard-core,
like an orangutan
I bring it wicked,
and freak the funk slang
Like, goddamn
Yeah, dude,
gnarly, fuckin'-a
I don't Play-Doh,
my nickname ain't Clay
Hittin' switches
Off and on, off and on,
it's on
Hittin' switches
Off and on, off and on,
it's on
What's the law?
Pimp or die
To my niggas uptown,
gotta pimp or die
To my niggas downtown,
To my niggas crosstown,
gotta pimp or die
To my niggas round town,
I just jump in my cab
Drive up the ave
Talkin' on my cellular,
huh, I'm too cool to laugh
I'm the man,
that's how I get down
I follow through,
knock the boots
And then I got
the stiff change
Ease up,
what's that all about?
Why you wanna try
to play 3rd Eye out?
Ease up,
what's that all about?
Why you wanna try
to play 3rd Eye out?
Somebody said my shit
ain't hip
What's up with that?
Somebody said
my shit ain't phat
Do you believe that?
Somebody said
my shit ain't hip
What's up with that?
Somebody said
my shit ain't phat
Well, that's OK,
that's OK, you know me
I been on some bad shit,
checkin' who oughta pay
Step quick,
3rd Eye's protected, G
Don't even sleep,
my gangsta ghetto party
Enclosed by the cops
So go ahead with that,
you're dead with that
Trouble's coming,
ease up when I freeze up
Into mes,
I'll be makin' Gs
I'm a bad boy,
I'm makin' a move, boy
I paid my dues, boy,
I was doin' bigs
While y'all
was still kids at school
Ease up,
what's that all about?
Why you wanna try
to play 3rd Eye out?
Ease up,
what's that all about?
Why you wanna try
to play 3rd eye out?
Hey, baby
Ho
She, she
Do you wanna pump?
Do you wanna pump with me?
Show me with your body
If you don't wanna
get sexy, babe
If you don't
wanna get nasty
Maybe we can compromise
And both get
a little bit freaky
Slide
Right over here
And let me rub that body
Maybe you would
like it, girl
It might get you
in the mood, gee, yeah
Let's go through
the motions, baby
Every night
and every day
Let's go through
the motions, baby
Yeah-eah-eah-eah-eah
Let's go through
the motions, baby
Gee-ee-ee
Jodeci, sing
It won't be long
We can go home
If you wanna go home
I say it won't,
I'll say it again
It won't be long
If you wanna moan
'Cause you look
so sexy, baby
You really turn me on
Oh oh oh
Loving you
I'm so glad to have you
Hey, yeah
And I'm so glad
to have you
Hey, cutie,
if it's your style
Come stay with me
a while
And hypnotize me
with your sexy ways
And, baby,
it is no surprise
How you've come
into my life
And changed
my way of thinking
I believe in love
this time
And I'm lovin' you, baby
In your arms
I want to be
Ooh, this time,
I realize
That I want you
here with me
And I'm lovin' you, baby
And you're all I want,
so stay
I have never had a lover
love this way
I, I, I, I
Ooh, boy
In your arms
I want to be
Ooh, this time
I realize
That I want you
here with me
And I'm lovin' you, baby
And you're all I want,
so stay
I have never had a lover
love this way
I, I, I, I
Come and stay with me,
where you ought to be
You will see
how true love can be
If you stay with me,
I will make you happy
I want you
Come and stay with me,
and I will love...