[MUSIC PLAYING]
[RAPPING] They say we three
fourths man, and the rest of us
is a beast.
That's why they want us in the
cage, but you know how it go.
Yo.
Lock my body, can't trap my
mind.
Easily explain why we adapt to
crime.
So if I could rewind the hands
of times,
I'd go back and change this
messed up life of mine.
Lock my body, can't trap my
mind.
Easily explain why we adapt to
crime.
So if I could rewind the hands
of times.
I'd go back and change this
messed up life of mine.
First thing's first.
You're better off dead in the
first place.
Life was crazy before I caught
my first case.
Take it back to my first
birthday.
A bad fort when I was in first
grade.
[GUNSHOTS]
[THUNDER]
What's up, little man?
You missed my party.
Well, nigga.
I paid for your party.
You want to hold it?
Come here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Now, it's not a toy.
It's heavy.
Yeah.
Hold it like that.
See, now you can kill a nigga.
Darius!
Put that down right now and go
to your room.
What's wrong with you?
I don't want our son playing
with your guns.
I ain't having my son grow up
to be no punk.
Where were you tonight, James,
huh?
Who'd you kill on your son's
birthday?
I was handling my business,
baby.
I don't watch your criminal ass
around my boy.
You going to teach our son how
to be a man?
You're not. I guess I have to.
CREEPER: OK, five card draw.
Bury the first car. You in?
No, man.
I play dominoes.
CREEPER: Best five card takes
the whole pot.
[COUGHING]
CREEPER: Discard.
How many you want?
ANIMAL: Where you going dressed
like that?
Out.
No, you ain't going out, just
stop now.
Yes, I am.
I haven't been out with my girls
in over a month.
And you're watching the boy.
Should be easy.
He's asleep.
Clean up after yourselves.
I don't know how you put up
with that shit.
Man, that's my baby's mama.
Y'all ain't even married.
Fuck both y'all.
DOUBLE T: Look, while we warring
with these niggas,
man, I need your head in the
game.
Look, don't worry about where
my head's at, nigga.
- You gotta stay in the game. -
Look, yo.
Fuck the game.
You think I give a fuck about
them niggas?
No.
Them niggas can set it off
whenever they ready.
See that's the difference--
CREEPER: All right.
No, no. Fuck that.
That's the difference between
you and me.
You niggas get hard before you
kill a nigga.
I get hard after.
All right, man.
Whatever.
Give me a card.
CREEPER: What you got?
Wait, wait, wait wait.
What about all them other cards
in your hand?
You smell that?
[SNIFFS]
Smell that?
Smell that. - What
DOUBLE T: What the fuck are
you--
What you smell?
Death.
That shit smell like death.
[SNIFFS]
DOUBLE T: Come on, man.
You high.
Oh, shit.
Aw, shit.
Guess who's high?
Oh, man.
That's death.
That ain't death.
That's you, you nigga, and your
funky ass.
God, forgive me.
Come on.
Get back up in your seat, man.
ANIMAL: No, mama.
Uh-uh.
No, I don't want to go, mama.
I don't like it over there.
Come back up here, baby.
Mama, don't leave.
Don't leave, mama.
Please?
Please, mama.
Don't leave me, mama.
Mama, don't leave me.
Please, mama.
Don't leave me.
Please?
Please, mama.
Mama, don't leave me, please.
Mama, don't leave me.
Please, mama.
Mama!
Don't-- don't leave me, mama.
Don't.
[POLICE RADIO]
[DOG WHIMPERING]
Let's go.
Get the boy.
Move it.
Go, go, go.
Back room.
James Allen, you're under arrest
for attempted murder--
Oh, my god. James!
COP: --and armed robbery of the
Liberty Street liquor store.
Anything you say can and will be
used
against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an
attorney.
If you cannot afford one, the
court will appoint one for you.
Let's go. Come on, man.
That's it. REECY: See.
This is that shit I'm talking
about, James.
I didn't rob no liquor store,
son.
COP: Keep walking.
Keep walking.
Get that gun off my baby.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's go.
Watch your head.
[GAVEL POUNDING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[BUZZER]
GUARD: Stand in line, formation.
Let's go.
[GRUNTS]
This way, ladies.
Lucky it wasn't you.
I know where I be, bitch.
GUARD: All right, ladies.
Come on.
Follow me.
Hey, hey.
Single-file.
KASSADA: Whoa, whoa. What are
you doing?
Come on, come on.
You're giving them too much
mashed potatoes.
All right? Here.
Like this, like this. All right?
Come on.
It comes out of my pocket, all
right?
Go ahead.
Keep an eye on those guys.
Hey.
What are you doing with that?
What's in there, huh?
Where are you going with this?
Huh?
This goes in my locker.
Don't ever make this mistake
again.
You know much this is?
What's the matter with you?
Keep an eye on these guys.
Chicas, vamos.
Show them how I like it.
Go ahead.
What's this?
I think we got something.
Listen, put those two, put them
in a cage together.
[CLANGING]
GUARD: Rec time.
INMATE: This shit's going down.
Straight ahead.
ANIMAL: Rec time, huh?
[CELL DOOR OPENING]
[GROWLING]
[SCREAMING]
Fuck.
Get up!
Aw, shit.
ANIMAL: Breathe.
[LAUGHING]
[SCREAMING]
Mom, I got to talk.
Listen, mama.
It's almost a year now.
You know Danny Harris?
That nice man that owns that
hardware
store down on Maxus Avenue?
Mm-hm.
He wants me to move to Atlanta
with him
to start a new business.
I'm gonna help him run it.
Mama?
I need this.
Mama, this is a chance for me to
start all over again.
Oh, and Danny, he's a good man.
He's willing to take Darius.
What about James?
James is in jail.
James ain't getting out no time
soon, is he mama?
And you and me both know when
James does get out,
James is going right back in
them streets.
There's always hope.
Mama, Danny.
Danny is hope.
This is a chance for my baby to
get
a shot at a real decent kind of
life, not this.
What about the house?
Mama.
I'm leaving it.
It's yours.
Reecy--
I'm cooking dinner tomorrow
night for Danny.
Why don't you come on by and
meet him?
I suppose, 'cause that boy sure
needs a daddy.
Look at him.
Oh, my god.
Darius.
You stop that.
Stop it.
Darius, stop it. Stop it.
Stop.
D?
Darius?
A way to a man's heart.
D?
Darius?
Baby?
You are about to work on my
nerves.
Here.
Here, here, here.
Darius, where's the shirt I
picked out for you?
OK.
All right.
This is going to be great.
Mr. Danny is a good man, but
you're my main man.
[GUNSHOT]
THUG: 5-0, Little Bill!
Come on, nigga. Let's roll!
Let's go! Come on!
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[KETTLE WHISTLING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm gonna get them mother
fuckers!
[MUSIC - CHRIS THOMAS KING,
"DOWN"]
[SINGING] When you're up and
flying high,
you see all the little people as
you go flying by.
But when you come down and
looking up, and nobody gives--
[SOBBING]
LATREESE [VOICEOVER]: Dear
James,
it's hard to imagine that so
very many years have passed.
We're all getting older.
Your son is a man now and he's
as strong willed as you were.
I know you don't want him
visiting you up there
and I understand that, and so I
just do the best
I can and pray for Darius.
He worries me no end.
Here's a recent picture.
He so reminds me of his mama.
I also found your dominoes and
Reecy's Bible.
I hope you'll read it.
And I pray for you every day.
You stay safe.
Mama Latreese.
Yo, ma.
What's up with the lights?
The electricity's off.
I can't pay the bill until I get
my next check.
Close the door.
Why didn't you say something to
me?
When am I supposed to tell you
anything?
You ain't never here.
Here.
Ma.
I got something.
This will pay the bills.
There you go.
Darius, where did you get this?
What difference does it make?
I don't want you doing nothing
illegal.
You know what?
You can pay the bills, you can
sit here in the fucking dark.
I really don't care.
You're turning into your
father.
Yeah, well that nigga can't pay
the bills, can he?
I can.
I'm not going to lose another
one to them streets, Darius.
Get the fuck out of here.
I'm not going to lose another
one, Darius.
Don't you walk away from me.
Darius!
You can't be getting your money
this way!
Darius!
[CRYING]
Oh, Lord.
Help me.
Oh, help me, Lord.
You.
You don't want nothing to do
with me, man.
Is that a loss?
Let's go.
Yeah? What you want?
It's not what I want.
It's what you want.
ANIMAL: I don't want nothing.
KASSADA: Don't be stupid.
You've got people on the
outside.
So?
I got a job opening.
One of my boys is getting
paroled.
I need a guy like yourself, you
know,
to straighten some people out.
You know, you're the muscle.
You do what you do.
What do my people get?
KASSADA: $2,000 a month, plus I
could arrange
a conjugal visit for yourself.
Huh, how's that?
Conjugal visits mean, you know,
a nigga gets some pussy,
then I'm your nigga.
KASSADA: That's right.
You're my nigga.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING]
DARIUS: Thanks. DELIVERY MAN:
Thank you.
Merry Christmas, man.
LATREESE: What's that?
I don't know.
I think it's from Pops, though.
Oh.
You send him something?
I send that nigga something
every month.
I wish I could see him though.
LATREESE: Well, he don't want
you nowhere near that prison.
That's the problem.
But you could try being here
when he calls.
Well I can't be sitting there
waiting all day.
I got business to take care of.
[GUNSHOT]
[MUSIC - "O HOLY NIGHT"]
[SINGING] A thrill of hope the
weary soul rejoices.
For yonder breaks a new and
glorious--
[GUNSHOTS]
Wow.
Ma gave that to me.
LATREESE: Oh.
I was like three.
I was right out there in that
tree.
Well, OK.
Let's put this one right up here
in the front.
Your little toy soldier.
I can't believe you remember
this little guy.
Yeah.
[SINGING] --divine.
O night.
[SHUFFLING DOMINOES]
INMATE: Hey, it's Berwell! Yo,
man.
Hey hey!
Hey.
Watch out.
What's going on over there?
That's Berwell,, late '60s
revolutionary.
They put him on death row.
People were protesting in the
streets.
Shit.
He was on the row?
Yeah. He was on the row.
CREEPER: Animal.
ANIMAL [ON PHONE]: Yo.
You must be bigger than a truck
by now.
ANIMAL [ON PHONE]: Yeah.
I'm making it, man.
How's Darius?
He's got his action going so
good,
they calling him Little Animal
now.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go check in back. [MUSIC
PLAYING]
[RAPPING] If by chance I should
die, raise my casket up.
I know the Lord will take me,
and won't pass me up.
Gangster, I'm a hustler, a
robber.
Keeping in my waist trained
pants a revolver.
Make shots quick in memory of my
partners.
Beat to the streets in memory of
my father.
See, this how a gangster walk.
Yeah, that's how a gangster
talk.
And these lyrics right here,
these is gangster thoughts.
They're from the worst part of
New York.
And it's us.
We make New York City hot.
You know me.
And for the feds and the
snitches, I can really walk.
I'm gonna make y'all see a 450
pop.
Yeah.
Now you witnesses get to see how
big the business is.
[GUNSHOT]
Shit, man.
Shit.
[RAPPING] When we jump out, walk
right passed the kids.
And the bouncers at the door
make passages,
and the bitches in the corner be
messages.
'Cause these niggas, in they
head, they square they too shy.
They can smell a real nigga.
Motherfucker, we gangster--
Need somebody making moves.
Dice took over everything.
Dope, gambling, hoes.
Damn near ran us off the
streets.
Hey.
I'm sending you that present,
like you asked.
This is the real thing.
This ain't no show pony.
Got a name?
CREEPER [ON PHONE]: Ramona.
Thanks, man.
Ramona.
[CHUCKLING]
Damn, baby.
What's up, Ramona.
What's up, James?
[GIGGLING]
Go easy on me.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Yo, man.
I need the remote.
Here.
You have half an hour.
Yeah, that dating show.
NARRATOR ON TV: In the absence
of going home with a man
last night, Steps found herself
something else to grab hold of.
[LAUGHING]
Is that the best you can do?
Yeah.
What's wrong with this?
Well just keep it down, OK?
No.
Fuck you, nigga.
You go back to your cell if you
want to read.
GIRL [ON TV]: It just feels
good, all over.
And after a while, your whole
body will
go numb, like on a long ride.
Fuck me?
What?
Man, I said turn that shit
down.
Whatever, man.
Old mother fucker.
Yeah.
You've got to live to get old,
brother.
What's your story anyway, man?
They say you was a
revolutionary.
Still am.
Yo, nigga, please.
That civil rights shit is over
and we lost.
No, you lost, brother.
ANIMAL: Yo, nigga.
Peep this.
I'm locked up in here and you
locked up in here.
[SIGHS]
What's your name, man?
ANIMAL: Call me Animal.
Real name, man.
James.
Why?
Maybe I like to get to know who
I talk to.
We ain't talking, nigga. You
reading.
I'm watching this dating show.
Look at the ass on that bitch.
[BUZZER]
BERWELL: Here.
Read that.
And you ain't no animal, James.
Don't let them turn you into
one, man.
Who the fuck is Malcolm X?
Let me see that.
Make sure everything's right.
You see that new miga?
That's the one who did your
girl, man.
ANIMAL: What the fuck?
Get the fuck up, nigga.
I need to deal with that new
nigga.
Who?
He's talking about Little Bill.
What's your beef with him?
He killed my baby's mama.
I can't sanction it.
He's protected.
Besides, it would disrupt
certain businesses that I have.
Business with who?
Never mind business with who.
The nigga works for me, all
right?
It'd be very destructive.
I can't do it.
That nigga killed my people.
Don't give me the kill my
people bullshit.
You killed his, mother fucker.
Come on.
There's nothing but mother
fucking killers in this resort.
All right, all right.
So that's how it is, right?
That's how it is.
Fuck, man!
[GUNSHOT]
[BUZZER]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
What's up?
You all right?
Let me see a hamburger.
What's up, man?
What's up, D?
Mama L!
LATREESE: Hey, baby.
How you doing?
DOUBLE T: You need some help,
mama?
No, baby. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I'm going to get some of this
diet chicken down here.
See, I'm losing some weight.
LATREESE: Baby, you need every
diet thing you can find.
You're looking good though!
Thanks, mama.
DARIUS: Don't be lying to him.
What?
You look like a burnt
marshmallow.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Kassada.
Yeah?
ANIMAL: Kassada, we need to
talk, man.
I got no time right now.
You better make some time.
You know, you see, Animal,
that's your problem.
You've got no self-control.
What do you want?
ANIMAL: Been in the hole over
four months.
Yeah?
ANIMAL: I need to make some
money.
I was gonna talk to you about
that.
You see, I'm having a little bit
of a cash flow problem.
So what's that got to do with
me?
My people need to get paid. -
Yeah?
Well fuck your people. Fuck your
problems.
All right?
That's enough.
You had to fuck with Little
Bill, huh?
You wouldn't listen to me.
You need money, nigga?
You go to the dice.
Your fucking pay day is over.
Get the fuck out of here.
[CHOKING]
[TRAIN HORN]
ANIMAL: What you looking at,
nigga?
I'm looking at a Negro that
just got his ass kicked.
Yeah.
Ha ha ha.
There's going to be payback.
Yeah, well I got your story
from Kassada.
Fuck Kassada.
BERWELL: Yeah, fuck Kassada,
man.
All that killing and silly-ass
shit.
That's putting yourself in
Willie Lynch's trick bag, man.
Little white boy, little Negro
boy, Willie Lynch trick.
I ain't now fucking Negro.
I'm a nigga.
You hear me?
I'm a mother fucking nigga.
I'm gonna fuck Kassada up.
And who the fuck is Willie
Lynch?
BERWELL: Read the book, James.
[BUZZER]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[SCRAPING]
KASSADA: Straighten him out
right away.
ANIMAL: So what's going on man?
What's happening, James?
You and Kassada are all cozy
and shit.
What's he waiting for?
Your ghost.
What?
You got a pass on one
condition.
You're shut out.
No protection from the Mexicans.
No protection from the white
boys.
You're on your own, James.
You don't exist.
I'm a ghost?
Says who?
Says me to Kassada.
Who asked you to do that, man?
Tell me about your father,
James.
You don't know, do you?
Well tell me about your son.
Or have you been in here so
long,
you don't know that either?
Who the fuck are you, man?
Stay out of my fucking business.
What? What?
You want to beat up on me like
my daddy?
Go ahead.
Willie made you, James.
If you don't know that, you
don't know nothing.
Are you man enough to clean up
after yourself?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
BERWELL [VOICEOVER]: Tell me
about your father, James.
[RAPPING] Sometimes your boys
ain't your boys, right?
Tell me about your son.
[RAPPING] Sometimes your boys
ain't your boys, right?
Sometimes your boys ain't your
boys, right?
Wilson!
Richardson!
Allen!
Yo.
Carl?
ANIMAL: Berwell, don't you get
any real mail?
From who?
Your people.
Nope.
I gave that up a long time ago.
My son, he hooks me up every
month.
Come on, James.
Come on, man.
Damn.
You got kids, man?
Nope.
So tell me, on the real, what
you in here for?
Did you read that book I gave
you?
I'm reading it, man.
You know he was a pimp?
I like that part.
Mm-hm.
Love.
But, you know, what you in here
for?
[SIGHS]
They convicted me of murder.
Oh.
Oh, they convicted you of it.
Oh, you're trying to say you
innocent like all
the rest of us?
No, I killed people.
In Vietnam, the enemy at home.
I'm here, James, because the
government
did not care for my politics.
We scared a lot of people with
the stuff
that we're running down, man.
What kind of stuff are you
running down?
Liberation.
Liberation?
Mm-hm.
Too bad your revolution ain't
jump off.
Oh, it jumped off, but it got
sold out to drugs and money.
Yeah. See?
Yeah, see.
Now that's what I'm talking
about.
My nigga-- I mean Negro.
Yeah, OK.
ANIMAL: See that's what I'm
talking about.
Now, it's good fighting for the
cause and all that,
but look where it got you.
Yeah, but if we didn't do what
we did,
you wouldn't have any choices,
James.
Ain't everybody got them
choices.
BERWELL: Oh, yes they do.
Some of them just got tricked.
By Willie? BERWELL: Yeah,
that's right.
By Willie, man.
You've got to smarten up, James.
You know, stupid is a choice
too.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[RAPPING] Sometimes your boys
ain't your boys, right?
OK.
Listen up.
Sometimes your boys ain't your
boys, right?
Yeah, nigga. That's true.
For reasons like that, there's
things you do.
When he talk, you listen up, for
real,
because I know my niggas that
would chill, kill, and steal.
Those new cats playing video
games, casing your spot.
Get high.
Take your money, get your
stomach in knots.
Niggas that talk too much, most
likely cowards.
Type to watch you get stabbed
up, then send you some flowers.
Tell your family they was right
by your side.
But there's no evidence, no
battle scars--
ANIMAL: Yo, Berwell.
BERWELL: Yeah?
I finished.
How was it?
Man, it was all right.
Just all right?
Can I tell you something, man?
Yeah.
It's the first book I ever
read.
You know, that's why it took me
so long.
I appreciate you telling me
that, James.
ANIMAL: I read Malcolm.
Now, who's Willie?
All right, I'm gonna tell you
about Willie.
The first thing I want to do is
put this chair over here
close to you.
He was a slave owner in the West
Indies.
So?
BERWELL: So I got these papers,
and I call
them the Willie Lynch papers.
It's powerful stuff, man.
The term lynching, they got it
from his name.
Say he was a master of keeping
slaves in line,
so American slave owners asked
him to share his secret.
In Virginia, 300 years ago, he
gave this speech.
He says, I have a foolproof
method
for controlling your slaves.
I use fear, distrust, and envy
for control purposes.
He says, distrust is stronger
than trust,
and envy is stronger than
adulation,
respect, or admiration.
You must pitch the old black
male
against a young black male, and
the young black male
against the old black male.
You must use the female against
the male,
and you must use the male
against the female.
You must use a dark skinned
slave
against a light skinned slave.
It is necessary that your slaves
love,
respect, and trust only us.
Says, the black slave, after
receiving this indoctrination,
shall carry on for hundreds of
years, maybe thousands.
That's just some of it, James.
I'm gonna give this to you, and
I'm gonna let you read it.
Wait, wait, man.
This is real?
Don't matter if it's real,
James.
It matters if it's true.
You are a part of his
indoctrination.
It goes from generation to
generation, from father to son.
ANIMAL: Yeah, but that shit
ain't right.
You know, what the fuck am I
supposed to do now?
Ain't no body never spent no
time with me, man.
Nobody teach me nothing, man,
just the streets.
You have an opportunity to
change your life.
And when you change your life,
you
will affect many other lives.
James, you have an opportunity.
I can't change.
BERWELL: You have an
opportunity, my brother.
No, my son.
It's not complicated.
You got to care about people,
man.
I care about you, James.
I get it.
[CRYING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
James Allen.
I'm Paul Wilson of the district
attorney's office.
You were convicted of attempted
murder and armed robbery.
ANIMAL: I told y'all I ain't do
that.
Yes, well we're inclined to
believe you.
Several of the officers involved
in your conviction
were recently charged with
tampering with evidence.
In short, Mr. Allen, you may be
released in some months
rather than some years.
This will bring you up to speed.
If you have any questions, the
warden
has been instructed to allow you
the use
of the phone to call my office.
Congratulations.
Guard.
Guard?
Yo, what's happening?
Berwell, can I come in, man?
Hey, James.
Good to see you, man.
ANIMAL: Hey, brother.
I got some great news.
Peep that.
Great news.
Uh-oh.
Wow.
Congratulations, big guy.
Yo, man.
BERWELL: That's really nice.
I'm happy for you.
ANIMAL: Looks like I'm gonna get
out of here, man.
I'm gonna be going back to my
same hood.
BERWELL: Come on, man.
You worried about that?
ANIMAL: Yo, on the real, the
only place I ever
been in my life is the hood and
jail,
and there ain't that much
difference.
OK, so is Willie Lynch thing.
I go back in the same
environment.
BERWELL: Yeah, but you got it in
your soul, man.
Just take what you got in your
soul.
Yeah, right.
That fear is natural.
ANIMAL: I don't know if I can,
uh--
INMATE: Yo, Animal. You owe
Kassada.
BERWELL: Hold up, hold up.
You can't come in here.
INMATE: Berwell, this has got
nothing to do with you.
BERWELL: Kassada and I made a
deal, man.
INMATE: Kassada's changing the
rules.
Fuck Kassada.
Let me get there!
[GROANS]
Mother fuckers!
Medic!
James.
Break the chain, James.
Break the chain.
[GROANING]
[SCRAPING]
BERWELL [VOICEOVER]: You see
these papers?
These are the Willie Lynch
papers.
In Virginia, 300 years ago, he
gave this speech.
I'm gonna give this to you, and
I'm gonna let you read it.
My method is simple.
You must pitch the old black
male
against the young black male,
and the young black male
against the old black male.
You must use a dark skinned
slave
against a light skinned slight.
Use fear, distrust, and envy for
control purposes.
This indoctrination shall carry
on for hundreds of years.
You have an opportunity to
change your life.
Freeze.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[RAPPING] You keep on calling me
back.
You keep on calling me.
The streets keep on calling me
back.
There ain't no problem with that
though.
Rap's another means of cash
flow.
That's where I started my
hustle.
Pockets full of dollars,
waistline.
You taught me to keep it moving.
That makes it harder to touch
you.
That's why I stay loving you.
You calling me back.
I stay loving you.
Oh, man. I'm scared.
Nah, not you.
They still got bars up
everywhere, huh?
CREEPER: Yeah.
Shit ain't changed.
Maybe you changed.
ANIMAL: Creep, you know that
girl you hooked me up with?
Ramona?
She straight.
CREEPER: Yeah. I done knew that.
I've got something else to tell
you.
Yeah?
ANIMAL: Yeah.
It's really important.
Got a little James running
around.
CREEPER: Shit.
Just between you and me.
You ready?
Let's go.
[LAUGHING]
Yeah! [CHEERING]
How you been, son?
Damn, man.
I'm doing great.
It's so good to have you back
home.
I missed you, man.
All my life, man.
Yeah, we lost.
Yeah, man.
We've got a lot of catching up
to do.
Yeah, man.
Mama.
Oh, man.
Oh.
Praise God you're home.
Oh, let me look at you.
Come on. I know you hungry.
Come on and get supper.
Oh yeah.
Little man, damn.
You got bigger, man.
Yo, bro.
What's up, man?
Damn.
I heard you spitting it, man.
Spit something, but spit it in
Spanish.
FRIEND: All right.
[RAPPING IN SPANISH]
Yo.
Welcome home, James.
And a nigga like me like that,
it's [RAPPING IN SPANISH]
Let's get this party started,
y'all!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINGING IN SPANISH]
James.
This is another chance for you,
son.
You gonna take it?
Yeah, mama.
I'm gonna take it.
It's good to have you home,
son.
It's good being home.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
DARIUS: Hey, pop.
Hey.
You miss her?
I don't know.
Sometimes I do, I guess.
Man, she was real good people.
I'm sorry, D, neither one of us
was able to look after you.
Hey, I'm cool.
I turned out all right.
You're sure?
Yeah, man.
LATREESE: James!
Aunt Mabel's on the phone.
[MUMBLES]
There you go.
Thanks.
Hey, Auntie.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Time to get a little air, huh?
Yeah.
Want a hit?
No, man.
I've got to see my PO in the
morning.
Yeah, I got something for that.
No thanks.
Talk to Darius?
Not really.
My nigga.
Now you home, we're gonna get
this shit rocking.
So what is your first move,
man?
My first move is I got to get a
job.
[COUGHS]
Nigga, what?
Yeah, a job.
That's blasphemy.
Look, how much you need, man?
It ain't about the money.
I got to show my PO that I'm
working.
When you go see him?
ANIMAL: Tomorrow.
I'm gonna just chill for a
while.
All right?
Can I use your car?
Ah.
[LAUGHING]
Yeah.
You keep those.
DOUBLE T: It's a new world out
here, man.
King size.
[CAR CRANKING]
Where my pops headed to?
Where my pops go?
Ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
[LAUGHING]
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
You cooking? - Yeah.
Good morning, son.
You want some?
No.
I got my breakfast.
Saved it from last night.
Where's grandma?
You know, she's probably over
at the church.
So what you doing today?
I've got to go see my PO.
DARIUS: What time?
11:30.
Well shit.
I'll take you over there.
ANIMAL: It's cool.
Creeper got me.
What time he picking you up,
soon?
About 11:00.
Well shit.
If you want, man, you and I can
go get you hooked
up a little bit, you know?
Get some new gear on you.
Cool.
Here.
Here try this.
[FLAMING]
Ooh.
You can tell I ain't been around
a kitchen in too long.
You definitely ain't Chef
Boyardee.
[LAUGHING]
ANIMAL: Thanks for the gear,
son, and the phone.
Yeah.
It's my gift.
I've been blessed, you know,
handling my little business.
But you know, if you want,
there's a lot more out there.
What?
Well, my man Jeff over at Grim
Reaper Records,
he says he's always in the
market
for somebody with your talents.
Do what?
Security.
Stuff like that.
[CAMERA SHUTTER]
ANIMAL: Yeah?
Yeah.
Is Mr. Belzer here?
RECEPTIONIST: Yeah.
Can you sit down, please?
Move your chair over please.
Kevin Belzer.
I'll be your parole officer for
the time being.
What do you mean, the time
being?
Well it looks like you've been
in the system for a while.
I'm transferring next month.
Let's see.
You come with quite a
reputation, Mr. Allen.
You need a job.
The sooner, the better.
You got anything lined up?
Nothing yet.
A couple of leads.
I need to see a pay stub by the
end of the month.
Now, I know there's a tendency
for new releases
to track down their old crew,
you know, just
to hang around with the guys.
I understand that.
But let me warn you, if you're
involved
in any type of illegal activity,
and I mean anything,
you got two strikes already.
One more, and you're long gone.
You're doing life. Understood,
Animal?
The name is James.
I left Animal inside.
Good.
Under the terms of your parole,
you're
subject to random searches,
either by myself
or any of my assigns.
Understand?
Yes.
Good, because drug tests are
also random and weekly.
Fill this up.
CUSTOMER: I'm here to see-- -
Hey.
Hold up, man.
I don't know this nigga.
FRIEND: Oh, he cool.
He cool.
[MUSIC FROM CAR OUTSIDE]
Yo, D. Yo, yo. Come here.
Come here. Check this out.
Come on.
Ain't that Dice right there?
That's Dice right there, man.
They run through early.
What you gonna do about this,
man?
True what I hear about Darius?
Darius is into it thick, thick
as we were, maybe thicker.
He got a crew?
Oh, he's built one hell of a
crew.
What about the OGs?
We are the OGs.
Everybody else is either dead or
in jail.
Darius, he can handle his
business.
Like I handled mine.
What happened to you in there?
You got that look about you,
man, like none of this matters
no more.
The hood never changes.
After all these years, man.
I don't know why I just can't
give this shit up.
Why can't we just give it up,
Creep?
Don't tell Darius about this.
Excuse me.
WORKER: You looking for a job?
James, garbage. - Yeah.
One minute.
See y'all tomorrow.
Man.
[CAR HORN HONKING]
Yo, man.
Give me a turkey sandwich.
Get your own damn turkey
sandwich.
Hop in. Take a ride.
No, man.
I've been here since 5:00 AM.
I'm tired.
I want to get home.
40 minutes, man.
I got a surprise for you.
Yeah.
Hurry up.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
What's up, brother?
- What's up Double T? - You all
right?
- Yeah. - Hey.
Why don't y'all come on out
here?
CREEPER: The sexy Shae, and miss
curious Kris,
and the delectable Veneda.
DOUBLE T: So what you think?
Of what?
About our little set up here,
man.
We plan on taking this
worldwide.
Major events, Super Bowl,
All-Star Weekend, Vegas, baby.
Yo, nigga.
Please, man.
Y'all ain't no kind of pimps.
We got this thing worked out,
but we
need a little muscle to help
kind of smooth things out.
You know?
Got to make the girls feel
safer.
You down?
Man, I got a job.
I got to show my PO a legit pay
stub every two weeks.
Come on, man.
We're talking about making some
real money, man.
I'll take care of that parole
shit.
We need you.
Can't do it.
I got to get back home, OK?
You going to give me a lift or
what?
I got to go to the east side
later.
Man, you might as well move on
up to the east side
if it's all like that. - Yo.
I'll peep you later.
DOUBLE T: All right, man.
It's like that, huh?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
LATREESE: You seen your father?
I've got us dinner in the oven.
Did you take him to his parole
officer?
DARIUS: No, one of his partners
took him a couple days ago.
Well he got him there on time,
right?
He just got out.
Why don't you just lay off him a
little bit?
Yo, grandma, why are you always
trying
to play my father like he's some
type of loser or something?
Because your father wasted his
whole life.
He was either running the
streets or sitting in jail.
Now he's too old to go forward,
too old to go back.
He's got this one chance to turn
himself around.
The next time he goes to prison,
he ain't coming out.
And you heading down that same
road.
Your mama tried to change things
when--
now just look at you.
DARIUS: Big papa.
Who's your papa?
What's up, D?
Hey.
Grandma, she-- she left you some
dinner
in the oven if you're hungry.
No, man.
I'm too tired to eat.
DARIUS: Yeah.
I feel you. Hey.
You got a minute?
Maybe I can holler at you about
something?
Sure.
You know them cats from dice,
right?
ANIMAL: Yeah.
Well they've been over there
selling wolf tickets
in the park, you know, like they
trying to take this shit
to a whole other level.
You know what I mean?
Ain't nobody tougher than me.
Bingo.
Tough got me in jail almost
half my life, most of yours.
- Yeah. - Tough ain't shit, son.
It's about being smart.
You got to be smart.
See, that's what I'm talking
about.
What I'm thinking is if you and
Creeper and Double T,
if y'all link in with my boys,
man--
No, no no.
--this shit would be bananas,
pops.
No, D. That ain't smart.
That's tough, and tough will get
you killed for nothing.
Smart is about making a choice.
OK.
You lost me right there.
Peep this.
I can whip up on any white man,
but who's got the money?
Who's got the power? - Yeah.
Who put your ass in jail?
I put my black ass in jail.
Yeah.
It's called the Willie Lynch
Syndrome.
Willie Lynch was a slave owner
300 years ago.
He wrote some letters that said
niggas gonna kill niggas.
OK.
I didn't trust you over there
because you a dice, you a crip,
you a blood. You east side.
You west side. You light
skinned.
I'm dark skinned.
Divide and conquer.
Fuck.
This shit sound like some
jailhouse preacher
shit right here. - No.
This ain't no Bible bullshit.
DARIUS: Yes, that is, man.
No, that's the truth.
No.
The truth is the streets, man.
The truth is what you taught me.
In all reality, you ain't even
been in the streets
in like 20 years.
And if you don't get your shit
tight,
if you don't get your shit
right,
man, you're gonna be dead in
these streets, man.
Yeah.
You're going to tell me about
dying?
Nigga, I-- everybody I talk to,
man, they got mad respect
for you but they say one thing.
You ain't never been good for
nothing but killing niggas.
And now you saying you ain't
even good at that shit no more.
I've been waiting for my father
to show
up for 20 goddamn years, and you
the fuck showed up.
All due respect, man, it sounds
like a whole lot of shit
you talking.
[DOOR CLOSING]
Morning, pop. - Yeah.
Good morning, son.
Hey, about all that stuff I was
mouthing off with last night,
you know, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
We cool.
You know, I've been thinking
that--
I don't know how you feel about
it and all,
but if grandma been riding you
the way she's been riding me,
maybe you and I should just get
our own little spot.
You know?
What about Grandma?
I think she'd be cool.
It's not like we ain't gonna see
her no more.
We just ain't going to be living
here.
Yeah, but you know when I was
locked down,
she gave a lot of time to you.
I can't leave her here alone.
I owe her.
It just seems liked everybody
else come first.
You know?
I'm sorry you feel that way.
And you're right.
Let me just get my bearings
straight, then we need to talk.
It's cool, but I got time now.
The Willie Lynch letter.
Hey.
Good morning, mama.
LATREESE: Morning, baby.
Made you some coffee.
- You did? - Mm-hm.
Good. ANIMAL: Two sugars?
That's right.
You remembered.
Hey. What's up, baby?
RAMONA: What's up, baby?
How's he doing?
Better.
How you doing?
My beautiful queen.
You hungry?
ANIMAL: No.
What?
Darius.
You still haven't told him
about us?
You got to let him know that
this is his home too now.
Sweetie, it's not that easy.
I'm trying to connect with him.
I'm trying to find a way to be
his father,
and I think I lost him.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Pop?
Hey, pop.
Nigga don't ever come home now.
What are you doing, man?
I'm working.
How did you find me?
You know I got eyes all over
the neighborhood.
Where you been, man?
You ain't even been home.
Well, a man needs a little
loving, son.
Yeah, but you know, you being
all
over here working like this,
man,
you got me looking real bad.
You actually slopping chicken
and the whole nine.
Yeah.
If I do anything crooked, my PO
will be up my ass.
Yeah, see, but nobody talking
about you
doing nothing crooked.
I told you about my boy, Jeff.
He got a straight up job for
you, man.
Security doing a little music
video. $200 straight up.
$200?
Yeah, man.
Cash.
What time you get off?
About 5:00.
OK.
I'll be here to pick you up,
man.
$200?
$200 cash.
Bring some chicken home though.
That's funny.
Damn.
This is strange, man.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
WORKER [ON RADIO]: I need a 20
on Spyda.
Yeah.
He's in his trailer.
Yo, pops.
Hey.
What's up, son?
Did I hook you up or what?
Yeah.
You hooked me up, thanks.
Man.
You know I got you a little
something too.
See, you doing the security
thing,
you need you a little back up.
No.
That's OK.
I don't need this.
You've got it like that, huh?
I can be smart or tough.
I'm gonna be smart.
WORKER [ON RADIO]: Spyda on set
in 10 minutes.
All right.
I'll be one minute.
Talk to you later.
Stop!
No!
No.
Stop!
Stop.
ANIMAL: What's going on?
Nothing, mother fucker.
Step off.
ANIMAL: She said no.
SPYDA: And I said step off.
Matter of fact, take this Benji,
go run
and tell Jeff you did your job.
Put your dress on.
Man, she ain't putting nothing
on but a rubber on my dick.
Now get the fuck out of here
before you make the news.
Go ahead.
Maybe you'd be doing me a favor.
Nigga, you crazy. You know
what?
Get the fuck out of here.
Take this sorry-ass hoe with
you.
Come on.
Go ahead.
[CRYING]
ANIMAL: Take her to her trailer.
Pop, you can't let no nigga
just put a gun in your face
like that.
D, I got two strikes against
me.
Now I'm going to kill this fool
for disrespecting me
and go to prison for life?
Look, pop.
I know you're trying to change
and all that,
but you're still in the mother
fucking streets
and there's rules to this shit.
Let it go.
Yeah.
Just walk away from your
manhood.
Yo, Spyda.
Come in.
What you getting coked up,
nigga?
I'm trying to get right with
that, man.
DARIUS: Yeah, I saw that.
Fucking hip hop cop.
DARIUS: I wish you would have
pulled that shit on me, nigga.
[GUNSHOT]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Yo.
What up, man?
Dude.
I got to change clothes.
What happened?
You'll never believe this shit.
Your boy, Spyda, happened, man.
I'm sitting there and Spyda come
out of his trailer
demonstrating, real raw.
You know what I mean?
And I'm waiting, man.
I'm sitting there waiting for my
pops to say
something or do something.
The nigga stood there like a
little bitch.
I tried to offer him my piece
earlier.
Mother fucker wouldn't even take
it, man.
He been acting strange.
Your dad's got a lot going on,
man.
Yeah, well shit.
He ain't got me going on.
I'm supposed to be his mother
fucking son.
That nigga don't even fucking
come home, you know?
Fuck. Look.
Got me all emotional like a
little bitch or something.
I need to find that mother
fucker, man.
I'll get this shit back to you,
all right?
Forget I talked about it.
Yo, man.
Close the door.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
DOUBLE T: Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh.
Oh.
Hey. What up, D?
Hey.
Where my pops at?
Well he ain't here.
Man, tell the little nigga
where his pops is, man.
You're fucking up my dance.
He'll tell you when he's ready.
Shit, Creeper.
If you know where he at, man, I
can't put this
shit off no more.
DOUBLE T: Man, tell him where
his pops is, man.
He's on the east side, D.
Ain't you got a big mouth?
Where on the east side?
ANIMAL: He still got a fever?
A little, but it's breaking
though.
You look kind of tired.
You coming down with something?
No, I'm fine.
If we could get out of here,
baby, and go someplace else,
would you?
Go where?
I don't know, just someplace
else.
Can we do that?
I mean with your parole and
everything?
I think so, just as long as we
stay in the state.
Why you want to leave?
Because I, uh--
I can't figure out a way to make
it right with Darius and me.
Look, baby.
You ain't never going to get
past
that if you don't stay and try.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Can't keep running.
Who is it?
DARIUS: Is Anim-- is James Allen
there?
What are you doing here?
Who is this?
Ramona, Darius.
Darius, Ramona.
Nice to finally meet you.
What's up with you, man?
Can we talk in private?
I'm going to go check on James
Jr.
I'll give you two some privacy.
We'll talk outside.
Let's talk over here.
You killed Spyda, didn't you?
You killed another black man, D.
He had a girl in his trailer
who saw him point a gun at me.
Now when that gets out to 5-0,
5-0 is
going to come looking for me.
I'm on probation.
I've got two strikes against me,
and you bring this shit
to my home around my son.
Is that smart or tough, D?
What the fuck is up with you?
You used to be a legend, man.
You used to be Animal.
I used to be a slave.
All I did was kill people who
looked like me.
You know why the hood will never
change?
Because anyone who can change
the hood, we kill them.
Me and niggas like you, we kill
them.
My generation did it, and your
generation did it.
It's that Willie Lynch shit.
And now we got to build.
We got to come together and we
got to build.
We got to build?
ANIMAL: Build.
Nigga, it look like you
building
pretty fine on your own.
Got a nice little bitch and a
nice little apartment.
You got a little nigga--
Don't fucking disrespect me.
You got a little nigga up in
the house.
Nigga, what the fuck about me?
ANIMAL: I know I fucked up my
life,
but you still have a chance, D.
You're young,
and your baby brother has a
chance.
I don't even know that nigga,
man.
And you ain't had no problem
bringing
all this shit around me when I
was growing up.
But now-- oh, I'm sorry.
Now you mister good man.
You're mister good dad.
What do you want?
Huh?
That's the past, D. What do you
want from me?
Fuck you, man.
I don't want shit from you.
Because when I needed you,
nigga, you weren't there.
Nigga, I've been on my own since
I was 12 years old.
And now after all that shit, you
ain't got no love for me?
I ain't got no fucking love for
you.
And you know why I ain't got no
love for you?
Because I don't know how to
love.
Because I ain't got no love for
myself.
Now I'm trying to raise your
little baby brother.
You keep this shit away from
him.
You ain't got no love for me?
This is all I've got to give to
you.
I ain't got no love for you
either.
[GUNSHOT]
Shit.
ANIMAL: It's OK, D. It's all
right.
Pop. I'm sorry, Pop.
You should've talked to me,
nigga.
That's all I got to give you.
Look, pop.
We're gonna just--
ANIMAL: It's OK.
This shit ain't OK.
Nigga, it ain't OK.
ANIMAL: OK.
Come on.
It's OK.
DARIUS: I just want to talk to
you, nigga.
I just want--
Run, D. You just run.
[CRYING]
Come on, run.
Run.
[SIREN IN THE DISTANCE]
[COUGHING]
[THUNDER]
[SOBBING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINGING] Motherless children
have a hard time.
And I'm confused, whoa, in my
bones.
And passion flows like a river
of fire.
And when I'm down, when I'm
down, I feel I'm finally alone.
You are there to take me higher.
Take me higher.
Now, mama.
I need you.
Oh, Lord.
Now I need you.
DARIUS: Ramona!
Ramona!
Ramona.
Sorry I was late. - Oh, no.
That's OK.
Thanks so much for doing this.
OK?
Yeah.
No problem.
I think I've really got a shot
at this job.
Well hit it.
I got it. RAMONA: OK.
What's up, man?
Wait.
What?
Some kids at his school,
they've
been talking about how bad his
father was
and he's been asking a lot of
questions.
Can you talk to him please?
I'll talk to him.
Thanks.
OK, baby.
Bye.
Hey, kill them over there, all
right?
DARIUS: I will.
Hey, come on.
Take a walk with me.
You know your father loved you a
lot with all his heart?
He did the best he could, you
know,
to be the best type of man he
could with what he had.
And when he died, he wanted
nothing more than for you
to have a better life than him.
He actually had these letters, a
story
about a man named Willie Lynch,
who was a slave owner,
you know?
And he set up this entire way of
dealing with people,
of how to run black people--
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINGING] All the youngsters
around the world
who may be feeling what I feel.
Like there's no way out.
But if you just believe, then
you're not alone.
Walking down the streets on the
avenue.
It's been a long, cold winter
and I'm feeling blue.
In my belly there's a hunger for
something more than holes
in my shoes. More than holes in
my shoes.
Everybody's in a hurry to get to
nowhere.
A young child is crying.
Her mother don't care.
No milk in the bottle, but she
gets welfare for food.
Welfare for food.
The world keep turning but the
fire's burning out.
I guess I'll take another trip
down to the rock house.
The only place I go where
everybody knows my name.
They know my name.
You know I feel so high when I'm
in bliss.
I would sell my soul for just
one more hit.
I'll do anything to escape this
pain.
Oh yeah.
[MUSIC - WYCLEF JEAN,
"PRESIDENT"]
[SINGING] Election time's
coming.
Who you gonna vote for?
Yeah.
If I was president, I'd get
elected on Friday, assassinated
on Saturday, buried on Sunday.
They go back to work on Monday.
If I was president.
If I was president, yeah.
Instead of spending billions on
the war,
I can use that money so I can
feed the poor.
'Cause I know some so poor, when
it rains,
that's when the shower.
Screaming, fight the power.
That's when the vulture
devoured.
If I was president, I'd get
elected on Friday, assassinated
on Saturday, buried on Sunday.
They go back to work on Monday.
If I was president.
Yeah.
I know some soldiers that sleep,
but they can't dream.
Wake up with screams, sounds of
M-16s.
So take this medal of honor for
your bravery.
I wish you the best, kid.
You and your family.
If I was president, I'd get
elected on Friday, assassinated
on Saturday, buried on Sunday.
They go back to work on Monday.
If I was president.
But the radio won't play this.
They call it rebel music.
How can you refuse it, children
of Moses?
Tell the children the truth, the
truth.
It's not all that bling.
That's diamonds.
Tell them the truth, the truth.
Most of y'all wear cubic
zirconium.
Tell them the truth, the truth.
Yeah.
Your soul is worth more than
diamonds and gold.
If I was president, all blacks
will have
reparation, no segregation.
Feed the nation 'til there's no
famine.
Muslims, Jews, Christians would
all hold hands.
Every week on the beach, party
by the sane.
Word up.
Take trips on Air Force One.
No need to bring the homeless
with no sneaks
to Air Force One.
Better schools in the hood,
better teachers
for the classes.
Making money, paying no taxes.
Find the best scientists.
Tell them, come up with the
answer.
I want the cure for AIDS and
cancer.
But I gotta watch my back.
Snipers on the hill with the
steel.