♪ ...FOREVER
YOU AND ME ♪
♪ THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
FOR ME TO SHOW YOU ♪
♪ OH, YOU KNOW
ALL THERE IS TO KNOW ♪
♪ NOW IT'S YOU AND ME ♪
♪ THAT'S THE WAY IT'S GONNA BE ♪
♪ AND PRETTY SOON
YOU'LL SEE... ♪
LOOK, A PUPPY...
♪ ...THAT FOREVER YOU'RE MINE ♪
♪ IT'S YOU AND ME... ♪
HEY.
♪ ...THERE IS NO OTHER WAY... ♪
THANK YOU.
♪ ...AND WE'RE
STARTING HERE TODAY... ♪
GUYS, WE GO IT!
HE'S BOOKING OUR TOUR!
♪ ...IT'S JUST YOU AND ME ♪
TOURING, HERE WE COME!
♪ THAT'S THE WAY
IT'S GONNA BE... ♪
'KAY, BYE.
I'LL BE BACK SOON.
I'LL MISS YOU.
♪ ...THAT FOREVER YOU'RE MINE ♪
♪ FOREVER ♪
♪ IT'S YOU AND ME... ♪
BYE.
♪ ...THERE IS NO OTHER WAY ♪
♪ AND WE'RE
STARTING HERE TODAY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE TODAY
IT'S JUST YOU AND ME... ♪
♪ OOH, IT'S JUST YOU AND ME ♪
♪ IT'S JUST YOU AND ME... ♪
GOOD MORNING, SWEETIE.
GOOD MORNING, MOM.
EIGHT-FOOT PALMS?
NINE FOOT.
COFFEE?
TRIPLE ESPRESSO.
GOOD MORNING, FREDDY.
HEY, OLIVIA.
CAN WE GET THIS PLACE
CURB-PERFECT BY 5:00?
4:59, GUARANTEED.
THANK YOU.
YOU ARE GONNA BE GREAT AT THIS.
GIVE IT SIX MONTHS,
AND YOU'LL BE THE NEW ME.
THIS IS NOT
WHAT I HAD IN MIND
WHEN I SAID I WANTED
TO FIND MYSELF.
WELL, WE'LL SEE.
DON'T SAY IT--
"ALL THE WORLD'S--
"--A STAGING."
SO, ARE YOU GETTING EXCITED
ABOUT THIS WEEKEND?
WHY? WHAT'S
THIS WEEKEND?
JUST KIDDING.
YES, I CAN'T WAIT.
THERE'S A SLIGHT GLITCH
WITH THE MUSIC,
BUT I'M ON IT.
WE DON'T NEED MUSIC.
IT'S YOUR WEDDING.
SECOND WEDDING.
EVEN A SECOND WEDDING
SHOULD BE MEMORABLE.
AND TELL ME YOU AT LEAST
TRIED ON THE DRESS.
I WILL.
YOU ARE THE WORST BRIDE EVER.
AND YOU ARE THE BEST DAUGHTER.
OH, LET ME JUST...
THOSE GO BYE-BYE.
OKAY...
THE GNOME, IT GOES.
-BRUCE.
-GOOD MORNING.
GOOD MORNING.
OLIVIA PERSHING.
AND THIS IS
MY ASSOCIATE,
GRACE.
WE ARE HERE TO STAGE
YOUR HOME FOR THE OPEN HOUSE.
I KNOW JOSH SAID
THIS WAS NECESSARY,
BUT IT JUST FEELS...
-INTRUSIVE?
-A LITTLE.
A LOT.
I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND.
THE THING IS,
A BUYER WANTS TO KNOW
WHAT A HOME
COULD LOOK LIKE,
NOT WHAT IT DOES LOOK LIKE.
MEMORIES ARE WONDERFUL, BUT...
THEY'RE YOURS.
ALL RIGHT, GO TO IT.
I'LL BE AT MY OFFICE.
OKAY.
DON'T WORRY,
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING.
THANK YOU.
MM-HMM.
OKAY...
THAT GOES.
LAMP CAN STAY.
CURTAINS GO.
QUOTES FROM
"THE WIZARD OF OZ"?
BRINGS TO MIND TORNADOS,
WITCHES,
AND DEPRESSED FARMLANDS.
ALL OF THESE
KNICKKNACKS CAN GO.
AW, "WORLD'S GREATEST DAD."
THAT'S SWEET.
YEAH, SWEET,
BUT GUILT-INDUCING.
DO WE WANT TO
TAKE THE CHANCE
THAT AN ALL-CASH BUYER
MISSED HIS KID'S SCHOOL PLAY
OR FIRST PITCH?
IT'S WAY TOO CROWDED IN HERE.
LET'S LOSE EVERYTHING,
MAKE IT MORE SIMPLE.
OH!
PURPLE.
HAVE THAT PAINTED
RESALE-WHITE BY NOON.
HI!
WELCOME TO WILLOW LAKE INN.
♪ I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT SOMETHING ♪
♪ NEVER KNEW JUST WHAT IT WAS ♪
♪ TILL I MET YOU, BABY ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN DREAMING
'BOUT SOMEONE ♪
♪ NEVER COULD QUITE
PLACE THE FACE ♪
♪ TILL I LAID MY EYES ON YOU ♪
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
REALLY?
PLAYING FOR
THE DUCKS AGAIN?
WELL, I GOTTA KEEP
MY FAN BASE HAPPY.
YOU GOTTA KEEP
THE GUESTS HAPPY, TOO.
NO, THE INTERNET'S OUT AGAIN?
GARBAGE DISPOSAL.
THIS PLACE IS FALLING APART.
IT'S RUSTIC AND CHARMING.
LIKE YOU.
YEAH.
COME ON, LUCKY.
HERE WE GO. COME ON!
WE'VE GOT ANOTHER WEDDING BOOKED
THIS WEEKEND.
AS LONG AS
IT'S NOT YOURS.
DAD...
I JUST DON'T THINK
THAT MADSEN KID
IS GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU.
YOU DON'T THINK ANYONE'S
GOOD ENOUGH FOR ME.
ANYWAY, WE BROKE UP.
OH, HONEY, I'M SORRY.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
WHEN I GO OFF TO COLLEGE?
PROBABLY RENT AN APARTMENT
NEAR YOUR CAMPUS.
HONEY, I KNOW IT'S JUST
BEEN THE TWO OF US
FOR A WHILE NOW,
BUT YOU'VE GOT THIS
BEAUTIFUL LIFE TO LIVE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
BUT YOU'LL BE
ALL ALONE HERE,
FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE MOM DIED.
I'LL BE FINE.
I'VE GOT MY GUITAR,
I'VE GOT MY DOG,
AND I'VE GOT
A LOT OF STRANGERS
WHO LIKE TO TIE THE KNOT
IN MY BACKYARD.
I'LL HAVE THE PAPERWORK
SENT OVER FIRST THING.
MAKE YOU SURE YOU GET
SOME SUSHI ON THE WAY OUT...
GET BACK TO ME
ON THAT CONDO, BROTHER.
DID YOU FINISH
ALL THE SUSHI AGAIN?
SORRY, HONEY.
IT'S SO GOOD.
HOW MANY OFFERS?
THREE. ALL ABOVE-ASK.
THAT'S FANTASTIC.
PLUS TWO NEW CLIENTS
FROM THE OPEN HOUSE.
OH, HONEY, THAT'S WONDERFUL.
CHEERS.
TO US.
CAN YOU STAGE THE HOPE STREET
COLONIAL TOMORROW?
NO, TOMORROW'S THURSDAY.
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL
ABOUT GOING UP ALONE,
AND THEN I COULD
MEET YOU THERE
FRIDAY NIGHT?
YEAH, OR YOU COULD SHOW
THE HOLLAND ESTATE
FRIDAY NIGHT,
AND JUST COME UP
SATURDAY MORNING.
THAT'S AN EVEN
BETTER IDEA.
PERFECT.
OKAY, SO,
REHEARSAL DINNER IS AT 7:00.
UH-HUH...
AND I'M THINKING
AROUND NOON?
THAT WAY, YOU CAN SHOW
THE COLONIAL ON YOUR WAY IN.
THAT'S WHY I LOVE YOU.
THAT'S WHY YOU LOVE ME?
AMONG OTHER THINGS.
YEAH.
WHY DON'T WE GO
TO THE JUSTICE OF THE PEACE
RIGHT NOW,
AND GET THIS OVER WITH?
BECAUSE MY DAUGHTER
THINKS WE ARE UNROMANTIC.
WE'RE NOT UNROMANTIC, ARE WE?
NO, LOOK AT US.
CHAMPAGNE, SUSHI.
OPEN HOUSE.
THERE'S THE MAN
OF THE HOUR.
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
GREAT NEWS, BRUCE.
MULTIPLE OFFERS.
I DON'T CARE,
I'M NOT SELLING.
OLIVIA, THE PLACE
IS AMAZING.
I'VE FALLEN BACK
IN LOVE WITH IT AGAIN.
I'M STAYING,
AND I'M BUYING
THE FURNITURE, TOO.
REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED
THE LAST TIME
YOU TRIED TO FIX THAT.
I'M TRYING NOT TO.
WELL, I'VE COME
A LONG WAY, HAVEN'T I?
FROM A SPOTLIGHT
ON THE STAGE
TO A FLASHLIGHT
UNDER THE SINK.
WEDDING CAKE.
TELL ME WHAT YOU THINK.
THEY'RE PROBABLY ALL GOOD.
MM. GOOD, YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW, SHOULDN'T
THE BRIDE BE DECIDING THIS?
I LIKE THE LEMON.
I JUST HEARD FROM
THE BRIDE'S DAUGHTER.
DON'T TELL ME
THEY CANCELED.
NO, THEIR BAND DID.
OH. WELL, CALL LYNN.
-OUT OF TOWN.
-WHAT ABOUT THE JENSONS?
I ALREADY TRIED.
WELL, I'M SURE
SOMEONE'S AROUND.
SOMEONE IS.
NO.
THERE'S NO TIME
TO GET ANYONE ELSE.
PLEASE?
IT'LL BE GOOD FOR YOU
TO PLAY AGAIN.
-I PLAY ALL THE TIME.
-TO THE DUCKS.
THEY GET MY MUSIC.
I ALREADY SAID YOU'D DO IT.
-JULIE!
-IT'S SETTLED THEN.
THANKS, DAD.
MICK!
ARE YOU IN HERE?
NOWHERE TO HIDE
NOW, PAL.
BE RIGHT OUT!
GO WITH THE LEMON.
HEY.
HI.
DID WE HAVE A GOLF
GAME I FORGOT ABOUT?
WELL, IF YOU COULD TAKE
THE AFTERNOON OFF, WE DO.
OH, I'D LOVE TO,
BUT I'M SWAMPED HERE.
JULIE CAN HANDLE THINGS
FOR A FEW HOURS.
RIGHT?
YEAH, IT'S FINE, DAD.
WELL, THE THING IS,
I JUST FOUND OUT
WE HAVE A WEDDING
COMING IN THIS WEEKEND--
FINE.
BUT TOMORROW NIGHT, DINNER.
AND I AM NOT TAKING NO
FOR AN ANSWER.
TOODLES.
SOUNDS LIKE A DATE.
SHE'S VERY FRIENDLY.
SHE LIKES YOU.
YEAH, I'M IRRESISTIBLE.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
RE-ENTER THE DATING POOL
SOMETIME.
BE READY SOON, GRACE!
HI!
MOM...
ARE YOU DRIVING UP WITH US?
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
JOHNNY HAS A GOLF TOURNAMENT.
WE'RE DRIVING UP TOMORROW.
WHO...
WHO'S JOHNNY?
OH, MY PLUS ONE.
YOU ARE GOING TO
LOVE HIM.
HE'S THE EXACT OPPOSITE
OF MY LAST PLUS ONE.
OH.
CAN'T WAIT TO MEET HIM.
AND I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW RELIEVED I AM
THAT YOU DO NOT HAVE TO
BE ALONE ANYMORE.
OH, MOM, I'M NOT ALONE.
I HAVE GRACE, AND I HAVE WORK.
THAT IS NOT THE SAME
AS HAVING A HUSBAND.
I SHOULD KNOW, I'VE HAD A FEW.
AND WHAT IS THIS I HEAR
ABOUT YOU ORDERING
YOUR WEDDING DRESS ONLINE?
YOU COULD HAVE BORROWED
ONE FROM ME.
I'M NOT SURE WEARING
A WEDDING DRESS
FROM A FAILED MARRIAGE
IS A GOOD IDEA.
JUST BECAUSE THEY ENDED
DOES NOT MEAN THEY FAILED.
OH, THERE SHE IS.
GRAM!
I DIDN'T EXPECT
TO SEE YOU
UNTIL TOMORROW.
JUST DROPPING OFF GIFTS
FOR MY TWO GIRLS.
OLIVIA...
THANK YOU, MOM.
NOW, GRACE,
I KNOW THAT YOU PREFER
THE NATURAL LOOK,
BUT YOUR MOTHER WILL ATTEST
TO THE POWER OF MAKEUP.
YOU SHOULD TRY
THE WRINKLE CREAM, HONEY.
IT'S NOT EVERY DAY
SOMEONE LIKE JOSH
COMES ALONG.
A DEMAIN.
DID SHE JUST CRITICIZE US,
OR COMPLIMENT US?
I THINK BOTH.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU AND JOSH
TOOK FOUR DAYS OFF?
I'M PRETTY SURE... NEVER.
THAT'S HORRIBLE.
ACTUALLY, I THINK THIS
IS THE FIRST WEEKEND
WITHOUT AN OPEN HOUSE.
WELL, WE ARE LEAVING
THE CITY BEHIND NOW,
SO YOU TWO
CAN'T DO ANY BUSINESS.
I LIKE YOUR
THINKING, HONEY.
REMEMBER THAT
WHEN I TELL YOU HOW MANY PEOPLE
ARE ON THE GUEST LIST.
48.
48?
GRACE, THIS WAS SUPPOSED
TO JUST BE A FEW FRIENDS.
I KNOW,
I GOT CARRIED AWAY.
WHY AM I
NOT SURPRISED?
SOME OF THEM
ARE COMING UP
ON SATURDAY...
OKAY, WAIT, SATURDAY?
BUT MOST OF THEM
ARE DRIVING UP ON SUNDAY
FOR THE CEREMONY.
AND THE DINNER,
AND THE MUSIC,
AND THE LANTERN
LIGHTING OVER THE LAKE.
ARE YOU MAD?
NO. NO.
OF COURSE, I'M NOT MAD.
THAT SOUNDS BEAUTIFUL.
HI!
WELCOME TO WILLOW LAKE.
I'M JULIE TURNER.
GRACE PERSHING.
WE SPOKE ON THE PHONE,
LIKE, 15 TIMES.
16.
NICE SHOES.
THIS IS MY MOM,
A.K.A. THE WORST
BRIDE EVER.
OH...
HI. I'M OLIVIA.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
NICE TO MEET
YOU, TOO.
WOW, YOUR PLACE
IS REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
THANK YOU.
I MIGHT SUGGEST
YOU MOVE THIS PLANTER
OVER TO THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE PORTICO--
-MOM...
-SORRY.
IT'S PERFECT THE WAY IT IS.
WEDDING JITTERS?
WORKAHOLIC.
HMM.
I PROMISE
THE NEXT FEW DAYS
WILL BE AMAZING.
SHALL I SHOW YOU AROUND,
OR SHOULD WE WAIT
FOR THE GROOM?
OH, NO, NO, IT'S JUST US.
HE'LL BE HERE ON SATURDAY.
HOPEFULLY.
HE'S THE WORST GROOM EVER.
THE PERFECT
COUPLE, THEN.
WHO'S THIS?
THAT'S LUCKY.
LUCKY?
HE DOESN'T USUALLY TAKE
TO STRANGERS LIKE THAT.
GOLDEN RETRIEVERS AND I
GO WAY BACK.
WE'VE HAD THREE.
US TOO.
SORRY, GIRLS,
I'LL GRAB THIS REAL QUICK.
BRUCE, HI.
COME ON,
I'LL SIGN YOU IN.
I LOVE THOSE.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD
BECAUSE I'M
YOUR WEDDING PHOTOGRAPHER.
YOU TOOK THOSE?
THEY'RE AMAZING.
THANKS.
THIS PLACE IS BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S EVEN BETTER
THAN I'D HOPED.
WE CAN HAVE THE CEREMONY
EITHER INSIDE OR OUT.
OUTSIDE.
DEFINITELY.
SHOULD WE WAIT FOR
YOUR MOM TO WEIGH IN?
SHE WON'T CARE.
YOU'RE SURE?
POSITIVE.
SHE'D GET MARRIED
IN THE CAR IF SHE COULD.
THAT COULD WORK.
WE DO HAVE A TRUCK.
ONCE WE GET
YOU SIGNED IN,
I'LL SHOW YOU THE GROUNDS,
AND THE PERFECT OUTDOOR SPOT,
UNLESS YOU WANT TO SEE
THE TRUCK.
WE'LL KEEP THAT
AS A BACKUP PLAN.
I'LL MAKE SURE IT'S WASHED.
YOU REMIND ME OF SOMEONE.
WHO'S THAT?
ME.
LET'S JUST GO
WITH THE SECTIONAL.
WE CAN CHANGE OUT THE PILLOWS.
A POP OF PINK WOULD BE GREAT--
YES, THANK YOU.
OOH! OH!
YOU OKAY?
I'M SO SORRY.
NO, NO, MY FAULT--
MICK?
LIVVY?
YOU LOOK...
OLDER?
BEAUTIFUL.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
I'M GETTING MARRIED.
YOU'RE THE
PERSHING-JOHNSON WEDDING?
YEAH.
HOW DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT?
YOU CHANGED YOUR NAME?
PERSHING WAS MY FIRST HUSBAND.
HOW MANY HUSBANDS
HAVE YOU HAD?
WHY ARE YOU STANDING HERE
WITH ALL THE TOWELS?
I LIVE HERE.
WHAT?
I OWN THE PLACE.
YEAH, IT GETS WORSE.
I'M YOUR WEDDING SINGER.
UH, MOM?
OKAY, I'M DYING.
DAD?
I CAN'T FEEL MY LEGS.
WHAT'S WRONG?
-NOTHING.
-EVERYTHING.
IT WAS A MILLION YEARS AGO,
BEFORE YOUR FATHER.
BEFORE YOUR MOM.
WE WERE--
---REALLY YOUNG.
---AND STUPID.
--HE GOT A RECORD DEAL,
AND HE WENT OFF TOURING,
--I CAME BACK, AND SHE WAS
ALREADY WITH SOMEONE ELSE.
HE WAS MY FIRST LOVE.
SHE BROKE MY HEART.
HOW DID I NOT KNOW ABOUT THIS?
I GUESS I JUST NEVER
WANTED TO THINK ABOUT HIM.
--EVER AGAIN.
EVER.
I'LL CANCEL.
WE CAN DO
THE JUSTICE OF THE PEACE THING
LIKE YOU WANTED.
YOU WANTED TO GIVE ME
A MEMORABLE WEEKEND,
AND IT WILL BE THAT.
BESIDES, HONEY, WE HAVE
48 PEOPLE COMING THIS SUNDAY.
57.
I LIED.
MAYBE SHE'LL CANCEL.
YOU'D BETTER HOPE NOT.
WE SPENT THEIR DEPOSIT
ON DORM FEES.
ALL OF IT?
HI. THIS IS JOSH JOHNSON.
PLEASE LEAVE A MESSAGE
AT THE TONE.
JOSH, HEY, IT'S ME.
OKAY, SO, THIS IS KIND OF WEIRD.
WELL, ACTUALLY, IT'S KIND OF
FUNNY...
OR NOT.
UM, JUST GIVE ME A CALL.
I LOVE YOU.
FOR YOU.
OH.
THANK YOU.
WELL, THEY'RE NOT FROM ME.
THEY'RE FROM A....
"JOSH JOHNSON.
NUMBER TWO REAL ESTATE AGENT
IN LONG ISLAND"
GOOD-LOOKING GUY.
A LITTLE
OFF YOUR TYPE.
MY TYPE HAS CHANGED.
LOOK, CLEARLY, THIS IS AWKWARD,
SO IF YOU'D LIKE TO CANCEL,
I UNDERSTAND.
I DO.
BUT I CAN'T, I DON'T WANT TO
DISAPPOINT MY DAUGHTER.
BESIDES, I BARELY REMEMBER
THE DAY YOU LEFT ME
STANDING ON THE SIDEWALK.
SO THAT'S HOW
IT'S GONNA BE, HUH?
THAT'S HOW IT WAS.
WELL, I BEG TO DIFFER.
YOU STILL ALLERGIC TO ROSES?
NO, I'M NOT.
MAYBE YOU'RE ALLERGIC TO ME.
MOM!
WAIT UNTIL YOU SEE
THE HONEYMOON CABIN!
AW, LET ME PUT THESE
IN YOUR ROOM.
THANK YOU.
PUT THEM BY THE WINDOW,
SHE'S ALLERGIC.
DON'T YOU JUST LOVE IT?
THE RIVER ROCK FIREPLACE?
THE VIEW TO THE LAKE?
HONEY, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
MY DAD PUT A LOT OF
TIME INTO THIS ONE.
YOUR DAD DID THIS?
YEAH, HE REBUILT
THE ENTIRE PLACE.
IT TOOK HIS MIND OFF THINGS
WHEN MY MOM DIED.
OH.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO BRING THAT UP.
NO, NO, NO, I'M GLAD YOU DID.
I'VE KNOWN YOUR DAD
FOR A LONG TIME.
I FEEL AWFUL.
IT'S BEEN FIVE YEARS NOW.
HE'S KIND OF SHUT DOWN
SINCE THEN.
WHICH IS WHY
I WAS SO GLAD
HE AGREED TO SING
AT YOUR WEDDING.
HE REALLY DOESN'T
PLAY MUCH ANYMORE.
UNLESS YOU WANT ME
TO GET SOMEONE ELSE--
-NO.
-YOU'RE SURE?
ABSOLUTELY.
I MEAN, WHERE ELSE
ARE WE GOING TO FIND A POP STAR
IN VERMONT
THAT'S AVAILABLE ON SUNDAY
FROM 2:00 TO 4:00?
WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T LET HIM HEAR YOU SAY
"POP STAR".
HE HATES THAT.
OKAY, YEAH, I REMEMBER.
I'LL LET YOU GET SETTLED IN.
GRACE, I'LL SHOW YOU YOURS.
IT'S JUST ALONG THE PATH.
LEAD THE WAY.
THANK YOU.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
I HAVE TO THROW
A WEDDING FOR HER?
AND SING!
WHILE SHE MARRIES
THE NUMBER TWO REAL ESTATE
AGENT IN LONG ISLAND?
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
UNLESS YOU STILL HAVE
FEELINGS FOR HER.
FEELINGS?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HER.
SHE'S A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT PERSON.
HOW DOES SHE LOOK?
THAT GOOD, HUH?
POP STAR...
STAGER...
LUCKY, NO!
SORRY.
THAT'S OKAY.
HE LOOKS
SO MUCH LIKE ROWDY.
RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, I RESCUED HIM,
AND I THINK IT TURNS OUT
HE ACTUALLY RESCUED ME.
YOU REMEMBER
HOW WE FOUND ROWDY?
YEAH.
WASN'T HE EATING PIZZA
BEHIND THE DORM?
THE DOG LOVED HIS PIZZA.
HE DID.
UM...
JULIE TOLD ME ABOUT HER MOM.
I'M SO SORRY.
OH, THAT'S NICE OF YOU,
THANK YOU.
YEAH, UM...
IT TOOK ME A WHILE TO ADJUST.
I THINK I'M STILL ADJUSTING.
YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT YOU
AND YOUR HUSBAND?
HUSBAND NUMBER ONE?
OH, THAT DIDN'T TAKE
MUCH ADJUSTING.
HE LEFT AFTER GRACE WAS BORN.
I'M SORRY.
IT ALL WORKED OUT.
WELL, YOU SURE PICKED
A BEAUTIFUL PLACE
TO SETTLE DOWN.
OH. YEAH.
IT WAS MY WIFE'S HOMETOWN.
FIGURED IT'D BE A GOOD PLACE
TO RAISE A KID.
JULIE'S A GREAT GIRL.
SO IS GRACE.
YEAH.
I GUESS WE DID PRETTY GOOD THEN.
WELL, I'D BETTER
GET BACK TO MY... STUFF.
OH, SURE.
SEE YA.
YEAH.
OH, UM...
HOW'S YOUR MOTHER?
STILL HATES YOU.
SO, THE GROOM.
WILL HE WANT
TO GO OVER THE MENU?
NO, HE AND MY MOM
HAVE THE SAME TASTE.
THEY'RE EXACTLY ALIKE.
THAT MAKES IT EASY.
I GUESS IT DOES.
HEY, GIRLS.
-HELLO.
-HI.
IT'S NICE THAT YOU GUYS
ARE SO CLOSE.
ACTUALLY WE'RE
WORKING TOGETHER,
TEMPORARILY.
SHE'S "GROOMING" ME.
MOTHER AND DAUGHTER
STAGERS.
YIKES.
SHE WANTS ME TO BE
JUST LIKE HER.
YIKES AGAIN.
NO KIDDING.
DO YOU HAVE ANY
BROTHERS OR SISTERS?
ONLY CHILD.
ME TOO.
YOU'VE DONE A GREAT JOB,
ORGANIZING THIS WEDDING.
I SURE HOPE SO.
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ANYTHING HERE.
WE'RE GONNA MAKE THIS
THE PERFECT WEDDING,
ESPECIALLY SINCE
IT MIGHT BE...
MIGHT BE WHAT?
NOTHING.
I DON'T KNOW WHY
I'M TALKING SO MUCH.
BECAUSE OUR PARENTS
ARE EXES?
AND WE HAVE
THE SAME SHOES.
HE'S SELLING
THE PLACE.
HE DOESN'T THINK
I KNOW,
BUT HE LEFT THE INFO
ON THE OFFICE COMPUTER.
HE'S NOT EXACTLY
A TECHIE.
HE SAID YOU LOOKED
GREAT, BUT WOW.
-DUKE!
-HI!
AW, IT'S SO GOOD
TO SEE YOU.
WHO IS OUR BOY GONNA GET
TO DO THE COOKING, HUH?
YOU STILL, UH,
COOKING FRIED CHEESE STICKS
WITH PEANUT BUTTER?
YOU KIDDING?
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE GETTING
FOR YOUR REHEARSAL DINNER.
AND I'M GONNA
BACK HIM UP ON DRUMS
ON YOUR WEDDING SONG, TOO.
♪ BA-DUM-BUM... ♪
OH, YOU HAVEN'T MISSED A BEAT.
OR LOST A POUND.
-YOU LOOK GREAT.
-THANK YOU.
DO YOU REMEMBER THAT CLUB
THAT WE PLAYED,
THE ONE NEAR THE RIVER?
IT WAS MORE OF
AN INDUSTRIAL RUN-OFF.
WELL, YEAH,
AND WE HAD
THE THREE AUDIENCE MEMBERS...
YEAH, IT WAS THE BARTENDER,
THE WAITER AND THE DISHWASHER.
THAT'S RIGHT, YEAH.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT THAT
THE SONG YOU WROTE FOR THAT ONE
WAS, UH... IT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
YEAH.
OH.
ARE YOU STILL WRITING?
UH, YEAH,
I MEAN, WELL, POST-ITS.
AND WEDDING VOWS.
CONGRATULATIONS ON THAT,
BY THE WAY.
AW, THANK YOU.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU
LIVED HERE?
ALL MY LIFE.
IT'S PROBABLY
FOR THE BEST.
HE NEEDS A FRESH START,
AND THERE'S TOO MANY
MEMORIES HERE.
IT SOUNDS LIKE
GOOD MEMORIES.
YEAH.
HE GAVE UP A LOT
TO RAISE ME.
HE SOUNDS LIKE
A GREAT DAD.
HE REALLY IS.
YOU'RE LUCKY.
NOT EVERYONE HAS
ONE OF THOSE.
HE WON'T SAY IT,
BUT HE'S DREADING THE DAY
I LEAVE FOR COLLEGE.
MY MOM WENT THROUGH
THAT PHASE.
AND SHE SURVIVED?
THEY ALL DO.
AND HE'LL MAKE
YOUR ROOM REALLY NICE
WHEN YOU COME HOME
FOR HOLIDAYS,
SO YOU WON'T
WANT TO LEAVE.
THAT DOESN'T
SOUND SO BAD.
HE'LL PROBABLY BUY
HIMSELF A FEW THINGS,
CLOTHES,
MAYBE A NEW CAR.
OKAY...
AND THEN THERE'S
THE HOBBIES.
YOU KNOW, THE THINGS
THEY THOUGHT
THEY ALWAYS WANTED TO DO
BUT REALLY DIDN'T?
LIKE WHAT?
IN MY MOM'S CASE,
IT WAS WEAVING.
FOLLOWED BY
SYNCHRONIZED SWIMMING.
SYNCHRONIZED SWIMMING?
IT'S AN OLYMPIC EVENT.
OH, AND
THE MANDARIN LESSONS.
YOUR MOM
CAN SPEAK MANDARIN?
"NI HAO.
NI CHIFAN LE MA."
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
"HELLO, HAVE YOU EATEN?"
WHICH IS PRETTY MUCH
WHAT SHE ASKS ME
IN ENGLISH
FIVE TIMES A DAY.
THANK YOU.
'KAY. TALK
TO YOU SOON.
JOSH, HI!
SO, GUESS WHAT I JUST HEARD?
DID GRACE CALL YOU?
HONEY, I... I WANTED
TO TELL YOU MYSELF.
IT'S REALLY NO BIG DEAL--
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
IT'S A HUGE DEAL.
PROPERTIES LIKE THAT
NEVER COME ON THE MARKET.
WAIT, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
THE LISTING WENT UP YESTERDAY.
"FOR SALE BY OWNER.
NO BROKER."
APPARENTLY, THE OWNER
IS SOME SINGER
WHO WAS FAMOUS IN THE '70s?
IT WAS THE '80s.
IS THERE ANY WAY THAT YOU COULD
PUT IN A GOOD WORD FOR ME
BEFORE I GET UP THERE?
ACTUALLY, NO, I CAN'T.
IT WOULD BE A LITTLE WEIRD,
BECAUSE AS IT TURNS OUT,
HE'S MY COLLEGE BOYFRIEND.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I KNOW, IT'S TOTALLY AWKWARD.
AWKWARD?
IT'S GREAT.
UNLESS HE HATES YOU
FOR BREAKING UP WITH HIM.
NO.
IF I GET THIS LISTING,
IT COULD OPEN UP
THE HIGH-END VERMONT MARKET.
THIS COULD BE BIG FOR US.
I... I DIDN'T THINK ABOUT THAT.
WELL, THAT'S NOT LIKE YOU.
HONEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
COMING UP BEFORE SATURDAY?
WHY, WHAT'S WRONG?
I DON'T KNOW,
I JUST MISS YOU.
AW...
I MISS YOU, TOO--
OH, HANG ON,
I GOT ANOTHER CALL.
I GOTTA TAKE THIS ONE.
JULIE SAID THIS IS
BEST FOOD IN TOWN.
GREAT.
I AM STARVING.
HI THERE, HANDSOME.
YOU CLEANED UP
REAL GOOD.
DID YOU TRY ON THE DRESS YET?
MM.
I WILL.
I PROMISE.
WEDDING VOWS?
ALMOST.
MOM...
I STARTED.
OKAY.
LET'S HEAR WHAT YOU HAVE.
TELL ME YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
READ FROM YOUR PHONE
AT THE CEREMONY.
"JOSH...
"WHEN I STAGED YOUR OPEN HOUSE
THREE YEARS AGO,
"I HAD NO IDEA
WE'D END UP HERE.
"REAL ESTATE
IS A SMART INVESTMENT,
AND SO IS OUR RELATIONSHIP."
WHAT? IS THAT BAD?
AWFUL.
ALL RIGHT, HOW'S THIS?
"JOSH,
YOU MOVE HOUSES,
AND YOU MOVE ME."
WHAT WAS THAT?
HER WEDDING VOWS.
I'M STILL WORKING ON THEM.
DO YOU HAVE A TABLE
IN ANOTHER PART OF
THE RESTAURANT?
SORRY, MICK.
IT'S AN HOUR WAIT.
HOW ABOUT ONE
NEAR THE KITCHEN?
OR MAYBE IN THE KITCHEN?
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
UH, NO.
SO...
YOU TWO
KNOW EACH OTHER?
YES, WELL, WE USED TO.
CAMILLE,
THIS IS LIVVY PHILLIPS.
OR, UH, I'M SORRY,
PERSHING...
SLASH-HYPHEN-
JOHNSON-TO BE?
HI.
-I'M OLIVIA.
-NICE TO MEET YOU.
YEAH, NICE TO
MEET YOU, TOO.
THIS IS MY DAUGHTER, GRACE.
-HI.
OLIVIA'S GETTING MARRIED
ON SUNDAY.
OH, CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU.
SHE'S MARRYING THE NUMBER TWO
REAL ESTATE AGENT
IN LONG ISLAND.
OH.
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS AGAIN.
THANK YOU.
SO, WHAT WERE WE TALKING ABOUT?
OH, UM, I THINK
YOU WERE TELLING ME
HOW THIS IS YOUR FIRST
ACTUAL DATE IN AGES.
I THOUGHT WE WERE
TALKING ABOUT HOW WE MET.
AT THE P.T.A. MEETING?
RIGHT.
MOM...
OH, I'M SORRY, HONEY.
WHAT WERE WE TALKING ABOUT?
WEDDING VOWS.
RIGHT. ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
I KNOW IT'S
NONE OF MY BUSINESS,
BUT HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
THE SONG WE WROTE
IN CENTRAL PARK?
I REALLY DON'T RECALL.
-YOU WROTE A SONG?
-SEVERAL.
JUST SOME WORDS,
THAT'S IT.
I THINK WE USED TO
CALL THEM LYRICS.
HOW AM I JUST HEARING
ABOUT THIS NOW?
BECAUSE IT WAS
A MILLION YEARS AGO,
AND I BARELY REMEMBER.
WHAT WAS THE SONG?
WHAT WAS IT...
"WHERE DREAMS COME HOME."
REALLY?
NOW, WHERE HAVE I
HEARD THAT BEFORE?
OH, MY.
DO WE HAVE A COPYRIGHT
INFRINGEMENT HERE?
OKAY...
FINE.
I'LL CHANGE IT.
OH, NO.
NO, DON'T.
IT'S CATCHY.
I'M STARVING...
OH...
OH!
IT'S BAD LUCK
TO SEE THE DRESS
BEFORE THE WEDDING,
RIGHT?
YOU'RE NOT THE GROOM.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR GRACE,
SHE'S WITH JULIE.
THEY WENT
TO GET FLOWERS.
OH.
YOU FINISH
THOSE VOWS YET?
BECAUSE I HAVE A WHOLE DRAWER
OF UNUSED LYRICS.
OLD UNUSED LYRICS.
OH, IT'S SO HARD TO TURN DOWN,
BUT I'M GOING TO HAVE TO SAY NO.
YOUR LOSS.
HEY, HOW WAS YOUR DATE?
YOU SHOULD KNOW,
YOU WERE PRACTICALLY
ON IT WITH ME.
WELL, IN THAT CASE,
I'D SAY YOU'RE A BIT RUSTY.
I'M NOT RUSTY!
I GUESS SEEING THE DRESS
BEFORE THE WEDDING
IS BAD LUCK.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S MY FAULT,
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE
LEFT THE ROOM.
TAKE IT OFF,
I'LL GET IT CLEANED.
I WOULD
IF I COULD GET OUT OF IT.
I'M PRETTY SURE
CLEANING IS NOT AN OPTION.
IT'S JUST RIGHT HERE.
DO YOU GET ALONG
WITH JOSH?
YEAH.
JOSH IS COOL.
REALLY.
YOU TRYING TO
CONVINCE ME OR YOU?
NO, HE'S A GREAT GUY,
AND MY MOM SEEMS HAPPY.
MOSTLY.
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M JUST NOT SURE I'VE EVER
SEEN THEM ACTUALLY KISS.
I MEAN, ON THE LIPS.
THAT PASSION,
LIKE IN THE MOVIES.
BUT MAYBE THAT'S JUST
WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN PEOPLE GET OLDER.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR DAD?
HAS HE BEEN SEEING ANYONE ELSE?
NO.
I TRY, BUT...
HE DOESN'T PLAY WELL
WITH OTHERS.
MY DAD'S A GREAT GUY,
HE JUST NEEDS A LITTLE--
A LITTLE EXCITEMENT?
EXACTLY.
MY MOM'S THE OPPOSITE.
SHE COULD USE A LITTLE...
SMALL-TOWN-I-NESS?
THERE'S GOT TO BE MORE TO LIFE
THAN JUST WORK, RIGHT?
THERE BETTER BE.
OH!
OH, I'M SORRY.
I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO GET THAT FIXED.
LOOK-- I'M SORRY.
IT'S FINE.
IF I STAY HERE
LONG ENOUGH,
I MIGHT NEED
A WHOLE NEW WARDROBE.
WELL, THAT WOULDN'T
NECESSARILY BE A BAD THING.
I'M JUST SAYING,
I GUESS I'M USED TO SEEING YOU
IN JEANS AND STUFF.
YOU'RE NOT USED
TO SEEING ME AT ALL.
THAT'S TRUE.
HI, JANEY!
MICK, HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD, GOOD.
WE NEED A DRESS.
YOU'RE GETTING MARRIED?
YOU TOLD ME YOU WERE
NEVER GETTING MARRIED AGAIN.
OH....
I'M GETTING MARRIED.
HE'S STILL
ON THE MARKET.
GREAT.
RIGHT THIS WAY.
LOOKS A LITTLE MERMAID-Y.
NO.
THAT'S THE ONE.
REALLY?
DEFINITELY.
OKAY.
WE'LL TAKE THIS ONE.
THERE'S NO "WE".
THANK YOU,
BUT YOU ARE NOT
BUYING MY WEDDING DRESS.
I RUINED THE FIRST ONE.
RING THIS UP.
NO, ACTUALLY, HERE.
PLEASE TAKE MINE.
I APPRECIATE THE OFFER,
BUT I DON'T WANT TO BE
THINKING ABOUT YOU
EVERY TIME I WEAR THIS DRESS.
WELL, HOW MANY TIMES ARE YOU
PLANNING ON WEARING IT?
ONCE.
WELL, AT LEAST LET ME BUY YOU
A CUP OF COFFEE.
SO, YOU'RE A CHEF
AND A DRUMMER?
WELL, I USED TO BE.
YOU QUIT
THE MUSIC BIZ LIKE MICK?
NO, NO, I USED TO BE A CHEF.
I'M STILL A DRUMMER.
RECENT CUTBACKS
AROUND HERE
DON'T REALLY ALLOW ME
TO DO MY BEST WORK, THOUGH.
I DIDN'T SEE THAT
IN THE BROCHURE.
OH, DON'T WORRY,
MICK'S ORDERED
ALL THE TOP-SHELF STUFF
FOR THE WEDDING.
YOU PLAY WITH HIM
BACK IN THE DAY?
YEAH.
YEAH, I WAS THE HEARTBEAT
OF THAT BAND.
WHY DID HE LEAVE?
I THINK HE THOUGHT
HE WAS CHASING A DREAM,
AND HE JUST DIDN'T REALIZE
HE'D LEFT THE REAL THING BEHIND.
WHY DIDN'T MY MOM GO WITH HIM?
THEY WERE A TEAM.
YOU'D HAVE TO ASK
YOUR MOM THAT.
THEY WERE REALLY
THAT GOOD TOGETHER?
THEY WERE A PERFECT HARMONY,
THEY WERE LIKE ONE VOICE.
IT WAS PURE MAGIC.
I WISH I COULD'VE HEARD THEM.
WHAT DID THEY WRITE ABOUT?
I'VE GOT SOMETHING I THINK
YOU MIGHT WANNA HAVE A LOOK AT.
THIS IS EVERY LYRIC
THAT YOUR MOM
AND MICK WROTE.
"I FOUND WARMTH
IN YOUR EMBRACE,
"COMFORT
IN YOUR HEART,
AND HOME
IN YOUR EYES."
WOW.
YEAH... YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S MICK'S HANDWRITING.
THIS ONE.
YEAH, THAT'S YOUR MOM.
"LOVING YOU
IS LIKE BREATHING
"I CAN'T STOP
"BUT WHEN I DO
"I WANT TO HAVE
MY LAST BREATH SPENT
SHARING A KISS WITH YOU"
IT'S A LITTLE UNSETTLING,
'CAUSE IT'S MY MOM,
BUT WOW.
THEY WERE INTENSE.
INTENSE IS AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
I JUST CAN'T WRAP
MY HEAD AROUND THIS.
MAYBE PEOPLE GET OLDER, AND...
AND CHANGE.
OR SOMETIMES,
THEY JUST NEED TO BE REMINDED
OF THEIR BEST WORK.
YOU MIND IF I TAKE THESE?
THEY'RE ALL YOURS.
THANKS.
YOU KNOW, WE USUALLY
DON'T GET DAUGHTERS
PLANNING THEIR
MOTHERS' WEDDINGS.
OH, YEAH,
GRACE JUST REALLY
WANTS IT TO BE SPECIAL.
DON'T YOU?
YEAH, I...
HONESTLY, I WOULD HAVE
BEEN FINE
WITH A CEREMONY
IN THE COURTHOUSE,
BUT GRACE IS 20
AND STARRY-EYED.
WELL, YOU WERE 20
YEAH, IT'S WEIRD.
OUR KIDS ARE THE SAME AGE
WE WERE WHEN WE MET.
TO BE HONEST,
I'M FREAKING OUT
THAT JULIE'S GOING
AWAY TO COLLEGE.
YEAH, WHEN GRACE
MOVED OUT,
I REDID HER ROOM
FOUR TIMES IN ONE WEEK.
AND I SLEPT
IN HER CHILDHOOD BED,
UNDER A POSTER
OF THE BACKSTREET BOYS.
OKAY, I'M NOT
DOING THAT.
IT'S FUNNY
HOW TIME FLIES.
I STARTED DRINKING
HERBAL TEA
AND POMEGRANATE JUICE.
HMM, ANTIOXIDANTS.
OMEGA 3'S, GLUTEN?
OH, "GLUTEN,"
I HATE THAT WORD.
HOW ABOUT THIS,
"V.I.B.B.A."
"VERMONT INN
BED & BREAKFAST
ASSOCIATION."
I'M THE TREASURER.
OH. I.P.S.A.
HOME AND PROPERTY
ASSOCIATION,
THIRD V.P.
HMM, M.S.G.U.,
MAPLE SYRUP
GROWERS UNITED.
AND YOU ALREADY
KNOW ABOUT THE P.T.A.
GIRLS WILDERNESS
GROUP LEADER,
NEW YORK BOARD
CO-OP DIRECTOR,
RULES COMMITTEE,
AND NEIGHBORHOOD WATCH.
HEY, I CANNED
MY OWN JAM LAST YEAR.
OH, EXCUSE ME.
JOSH!
HEY, SWEETIE.
HI.
HOW'S IT GOING UP THERE?
OH, IT'S GOOD.
NOT THAT GOOD.
REGULAR GOOD.
DID YOU GET A CHANCE
TO TALK TO HIM YET?
WE TALKED.
UM...
LISTEN, HONEY, I'M NOT
FEELING THAT COMFORTABLE
BRINGING IT UP
IN THIS SITUATION.
IS THAT HIM?
UH...YEAH.
PUT HIM ON.
I'LL ASK HIM.
OKAY.
JOSH...
UH, HEY, JOSH.
CONGRATULATIONS.
WELL, THANKS.
I HEARD YOUR PLACE
IS FANTASTIC.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE IT.
WELL, IT'S HERE WAITING.
SO OLIVIA TELLS ME
THAT YOU TWO HAVE A HISTORY.
ANCIENT HISTORY.
I BELIEVE IN BEING UPFRONT ABOUT
THINGS, DON'T YOU?
UH... SURE.
SO I'M JUST GOING TO COME
RIGHT OUT AND SAY IT.
OKAY.
I CAN GET YOU WAY ABOVE
ASKING PRICE.
WHAT?
I KNOW THAT'S A BIG STATEMENT.
BUT IF YOU GIVE ME
THE LISTING, I'LL GUARANTEE IT.
THE LISTING...
OH, RIGHT, RIGHT.
UM...
YOU SAID
ABOVE ASKING?
WAY ABOVE.
WELL... SURE, WHY NOT?
THIS IS GOING TO BE GREAT.
I GOTTA JUMP ON THIS CALL.
TELL OLIVIA I LOVE HER.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
UH...
I LOVE YOU.
HE LOVES YOU.
BRACE YOURSELF.
I'M BRACED.
WHAT'S SHE GOT
TO CRITICIZE?
SHE'LL FIND SOMETHING.
HI, MOM.
HI, GALS.
AND YOU MUST
BE JOHNNY.
JOHNNY, THIS IS
MY DAUGHTER, OLIVIA,
THE BRIDE-TO-BE.
AND THIS IS GRACE,
MY GRANDDAUGHTER,
WHO WILL ALSO
BE A BRIDE ONE DAY.
NOT ANYTIME SOON, THOUGH.
WELL, YOU NEVER KNOW.
MOM, ONE WEDDING
AT A TIME.
I'VE HEARD SO MUCH
ABOUT YOU GIRLS.
WHATEVER SHE SAID,
IT ISN'T TRUE.
HOW WAS
YOUR DRIVE UP?
OH, YOU KNOW,
UNEVENTFUL.
FARMS, TREES.
TREES, FARMS...
AND NORA,
WHO SPOKE NON-STOP.
HEY!
EXCUSE ME, LADIES.
I'M GONNA HAVE
A LOOK AT THIS LAKE.
AND MAYBE EVEN
JUMP IN.
YOU DO THAT.
MM...
MOM...
I LIKE HIM.
ME TOO.
YEAH, I THINK
HE MIGHT BE A KEEPER.
LET'S SEE THIS PLACE.
OH.
NICE...
VERY NICE.
ISN'T IT?
WOW.
I ASSUME YOU'VE PICKED OUT
ALL YOUR PLACE SETTINGS,
AND FLOWERS, AND CAKE?
PLACE SETTINGS, SILVER.
FLOWERS, LILIES.
CAKE, LEMON.
LEMON.
WHO CHOSE THAT?
I DID.
HONEY, NO ONE HAS LEMON
AT A WEDDING.
MOM...
I LIKE IT.
LEMONS ARE SOUR.
IS THAT HOW YOU WANT
TO START YOUR MARRIAGE?
IT'S A CAKE, MOM.
IT'S NOT LIFE.
WELCOME.
MOM, YOU REMEMBER
MICK TURNER.
YES, OF COURSE, I DO.
WAIT, YOU DIDN'T
INVITE HIM TO YOUR WEDDING?
HE OWNS THE INN.
YOU LOOK GREAT, MRS. PHILLIPS.
IT'S MS. WINTERS, ACTUALLY.
OH, CONGRATULATIONS,
YOU REMARRIED.
TWICE AND COUNTING.
ONE KEEPS
DOING SOMETHING
UNTIL THEY
GET IT RIGHT.
I SEE.
AND OBVIOUSLY,
YOU'VE GIVEN UP THE MUSIC.
MICK IS OUR WEDDING SINGER.
OH...
THAT MUST BE SUCH
A COMEDOWN FOR YOU.
NOT REALLY.
I'M GOING TO
MAKE SURE
YOUR LUGGAGE
GETS TO YOUR ROOM.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
MOM...
YOU COULD BE A LITTLE NICER.
I NEVER LIKED THAT BOY.
HE'S HARDLY A BOY.
HE'S JUST LIKE
YOUR FATHER WAS,
RUNNING AFTER...
SOME DREAM.
MOM, IT WAS
A LONG TIME AGO.
HE BROKE YOUR HEART.
A MOTHER NEVER GETS OVER THAT.
I GOT OVER IT.
WELL, WE'LL SEE
HOW YOU FEEL
WHEN SOME BOY WITH A GUITAR
BREAKS GRACE'S HEART.
NORA...
COME ON,
LET'S GO FOR A WALK.
OH. OKAY.
A LONG WALK.
THANK YOU.
DID YOU SWIM?
NO, NO.
WHAT'S THAT?
OH, IT'S JUST SOME JUNK MAIL.
DAD...
I KNOW YOU'RE
SELLING THE PLACE.
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
I WAS GOING TO TELL YOU.
I WAS JUST WAITING
FOR THE RIGHT TIME.
IT'S OKAY.
I'M FINE WITH IT.
YOU ARE?
THE PLACE IS TOO BIG,
AND IT'S TOO MUCH WORK.
I JUST KEEP THINKING ABOUT...
ALL OUR MEMORIES HERE.
WE'LL MAKE NEW ONES.
YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY?
I'M SURE.
OH, YOUR STUDENTS ARE HERE.
THEY'RE SETTING UP
IN THE GARAGE.
I THINK WE'LL GO
A CAPPELLA TODAY.
THAT'S NOT
LIKE YOU.
YOU DON'T KNOW OLIVIA'S MOTHER.
SHE DOESN'T LIKE MUSIC?
SHE DOESN'T
LIKE MY MUSIC.
LET'S START WITH
"LONELY NIGHT," OKAY?
WE'LL JUST DO
THE CHORUS IN UNISON.
ON ONE,
TWO, THREE...
AND...
♪ LOOKIN' AT
ANOTHER LONELY NIGHT... ♪
NICE.
♪ LOOKIN' AT
ANOTHER LONELY NIGHT... ♪
ALL RIGHT, READY TO
PUT IN THOSE ANSWERS?
SO, GROUP ONE, GROUP TWO,
REMEMBER YOUR PARTS.
FOCUS ON PITCH
AND TIMING,
OKAY?
WE'LL DO THE CHORUS
IN UNISON,
THEN WE'LL ADD THE ANSWERS.
HERE WE GO.
TWO, THREE, AND...
♪ LOOKIN' AT
ANOTHER LONELY NIGHT ♪
NICE. HERE WE GO.
♪ YOU KNOW I'M LOOKIN'... ♪
♪ LOOKIN'... ♪
♪ ...LOOKIN AT
ANOTHER LONELY NIGHT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I'M... ♪
♪ LOOKIN' AT
ANOTHER LONELY NIGHT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I'M... ♪
♪ LOOKIN' AT
ANOTHER LONELY NIGHT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW
I'M LOOKING AT ANOTHER... ♪
♪ ...LONELY NIGHT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I'M... ♪
♪ LOOKING AT ANOTHER ♪
♪ LONELY NIGHT... ♪
I HAD NO IDEA
SHE COULD SING.
CLEARLY, SHE CAN.
AND SHE'S GOOD.
♪ LOOKIN'... ♪
♪ LOOKIN' AT
ANOTHER LONELY NIGHT ♪
♪ LOOKIN' AT A LONELY NIGHT... ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I'M... ♪
THEY LOOK SO...
GOOD TOGETHER.
HE HAS PICTURES
OF YOUR MOM.
I FOUND THEM
A LONG TIME AGO,
BUT I NEVER KNEW WHO
THEY WERE UNTIL NOW.
WHY DO YOU THINK
THEY NEVER TALKED
ABOUT EACH OTHER?
MAYBE THE MEMORIES
WERE TOO PAINFUL.
OR TOO GOOD.
AND NOW HE GETS
TO LOSE HER AGAIN.
AND VICE VERSA.
♪ ANOTHER LONELY NIGHT... ♪
JOSH...
HI.
THAT WAS... AMAZING.
YOU CAME EARLY.
I MISSED YOU.
THIS IS
STILL YOU, RIGHT?
YEAH, THAT WAS THE OLD ME.
YOU KNOW,
A ONE-TIME PERFORMANCE.
I HAD NO IDEA.
ME EITHER.
YOU MADE IT.
AND A DAY EARLY.
SURPRISES ALL THE WAY
AROUND HERE.
OH, UM, JOSH,
THIS IS JULIE...
IT'S SO NICE TO MEET YOU.
LIKEWISE.
AND, UM, MICK.
-WELCOME.
-THANK YOU.
SO YOU'RE "THE ONE
THAT GOT AWAY".
YEAH.
YOUR PLACE IS
INCREDIBLE, MAN.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
THE REST OF IT.
OH, THANK YOU.
IT WON'T LAST
THE WEEKEND.
I MAY NOT EITHER.
HARD COPIES.
SIGNATURE PAGES
ARE MARKED.
GREAT.
RIGHT.
WELL, I'LL... GIVE YOU GUYS
SOME PRIVACY.
HEY, GUYS, THAT'S A WRAP
FOR TODAY, OKAY?
WE'LL PICK IT UP HERE
NEXT WEEK.
GREAT JOB.
FOR PUTTING UP WITH ME.
THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL, HONEY,
BUT YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
YES. I DID.
I SHOULD HAVE
BEEN HERE YESTERDAY.
WELL, YOU'RE HERE NOW.
HEY.
IS THAT HIM?
YEAH.
HE LOOKS...
LIKE A DECENT GUY?
IF I DIDN'T
KNOW BETTER,
I WOULD THINK
THAT YOU WERE--
DON'T SAY "JEALOUS."
I WAS GOING TO SAY
"HAVING FEELINGS
FOR HER AGAIN."
DON'T SAY THAT
EITHER!
BUYERS LOVE
CELEBRITY PROPERTIES.
I THINK WE SHOULD PLAY UP
THE POP STAR ANGLE.
DO WE REALLY
HAVE TO DO THAT?
WELL, I ONCE SOLD A HOUSE
FOR DOUBLE THE COMPS,
JUST BECAUSE
A REAL HOUSEWIFE,
WHO SHALL
REMAIN NAMELESS,
USED TO LIVE THERE.
WOW...
WHAT A ROOM.
OH, THANK YOU.
I RESTORED IT TO
ITS ORIGINAL STATE.
I'D SAY WE STAGE IT,
AND WE'RE GOOD TO GO.
YOU KNOW, I ACTUALLY LIKE IT
THE WAY IT IS.
IT HAS CHARACTER.
IT FEELS RIGHT.
FOR A COUNTRY INN.
IT IS A COUNTRY INN.
NOW.
NOT THAT YOUR PLACE
ISN'T AMAZING,
BECAUSE IT IS.
BUT THE WALL STREETERS
AND THE TECHIES
REALLY GO FOR
THOSE CLEAN MODERN LINES,
AND THAT IS OUR TARGET MARKET.
DON'T WORRY,
OLIVIA IS THE BEST.
LUCKY, COME ON,
GET OUT OF HERE.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
GO ON, COME ON, COME ON.
UH, SORRY,
JOSH ISN'T REALLY
A DOG PERSON.
I WAS ATTACKED
AT AN OPEN HOUSE
BY A POODLE.
A TOY POODLE.
I THINK I HAVE IT
FIGURED OUT.
SHOULD I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT EXACTLY?
THAT WHOLE SOMETHING OLD,
SOMETHING NEW--
SOMETHING BORROWED--
SOMETHING BLUE.
HERE'S THE OLD.
WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S ONE OF
MY GRANDMOTHER'S VEILS.
SHE KNEW MY MOM
WOULDN'T WEAR IT,
BUT THOUGHT MAYBE WE COULD
SNEAK IT IN SOMEHOW.
SHE'S CRAFTY.
SO AM I,
AND DEVIOUS.
SO, WHAT'S THE "NEW"?
I BOUGHT HER AN ANKLET.
I'LL GIVE IT TO HER
THE DAY OF THE WEDDING.
THEN YOU JUST NEED
SOMETHING BORROWED.
GOT IT.
SHOULD I ASK?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD READ.
"YOU AND ME
"ON AN OPEN ROAD
"THE STARS ALIGN
AND THEY GUIDE US ON
"BUT WHEREVER WE GO
WE ARE HOME."
I LOVE IT,
WHERE'S IT FROM?
MY MOM WROTE IT.
SHE'S REALLY GOOD.
LIKE MY DAD.
SHE WROTE IT FOR YOUR DAD.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
AND THERE'S MORE.
HOW MUCH MORE?
AN ENTIRE BOX FULL.
DUKE SHOWED ME.
DON'T TELL HIM
I TOLD YOU.
I HAD NO CLUE.
BUT IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
YOU'VE SEEN
HOW THEY'VE BEEN ACTING.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S AS LONG AGO AS WE THINK.
AND SO YOU'RE PUTTING THIS
IN HER BOUQUET BECAUSE?
I'M CRAFTY.
AND DEVIOUS.
I KNOW YOU SEE IT.
RIGHT?
I DO.
SO, WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
WE WAIT.
AND HOPE
NATURE TAKES ITS COURSE.
WOW.
IT IS BEAUTIFUL
OUT HERE, ISN'T IT?
INCREDIBLE.
I WONDER WHAT
THE LAKEFRONT FOOTAGE IS?
JUST KIDDING.
NO REAL ESTATE TALK.
MAYBE GRACE WAS RIGHT.
ABOUT WHAT?
WE'RE UNROMANTIC.
WE'RE NOT UNROMANTIC.
I MEAN, LOOK AT WHERE WE ARE.
AND WE'RE GETTING
MARRIED IN, UM...
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED
IN 46 HOURS AND 20 MINUTES.
YOU SET A REMINDER
FOR OUR WEDDING?
DIDN'T WANT TO MISS IT.
HEY...
THIS IS US.
YEAH.
I WONDER HOW FAR
THIS PATH GOES?
LET'S FIND OUT.
OH, HANG ON.
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S NOTHING.
I KNOW THAT LOOK.
LOCAL BROKERS.
AND?
WITH A TON
OF CLIENT ACCESS.
BUT IT CAN WAIT.
COME ON,
I'LL RACE YOU AROUND THE LAKE.
HEY...
GO AHEAD, GO MEET 'EM.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH.
I MEAN, THE LAKE'S GOING TO
BE HERE WHEN YOU GET BACK,
AND SO WILL I.
WHY DON'T YOU COME WITH ME?
THEN WE CAN GRAB A BITE
IN TOWN AFTER.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT,
I THINK I'D RATHER
JUST STAY HERE.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH.
LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
I'LL BE GONE,
LIKE, AN HOUR.
TWO, TOPS.
NO BIKING AND TEXTING.
I KNEW IT.
YOU OWE ME FIVE BUCKS.
SO, WHAT'S THE PLAN
AFTER YOU SELL THIS PLACE?
YOU'RE GOING TO OPEN
YOUR RESTAURANT.
AND WHAT, YOU'LL BE
MY MAITRE D'?
MAYBE.
SO, YOU HAVEN'T REALLY
THOUGHT THIS THOUGH A LOT,
HAVE YOU?
JUST PLAYING IT BY EAR.
LIKE IN THE OLD DAYS.
WHEN YOU USED TO
TAKE CHANCES.
I'M JUST SAYING,
YOU USED TO GO AFTER
THE THINGS YOU WANTED.
OH!
OH.
I THINK I LIKE THIS ONE.
HEY, MOM,
YOU'RE ON SPEAKER PHONE.
HI, HONEY, UM...
I'M ON THE LAKE PATH,
AND MY CHAIN SLIPPED OFF.
I'M NOT REALLY SURE
HOW TO FIX IT,
SO I'M GOING TO BE JUST
A LITTLE LATE GETTING BACK.
I'LL SEND SOMEONE.
NO, NO, NO, DON'T BE SILLY,
I CAN WALK.
WE GOT THIS.
HOW FAR DO YOU
THINK SHE GOT?
FAR ENOUGH.
DAD, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING RIGHT NOW?
HEY.
OH, HEY.
SORRY.
NO, IT HAPPENS
ALL THE TIME.
WELL, THANK YOU.
WELL, YOU CAN JUST
CONSIDER THIS
PART OF
THE CONCIERGE SERVICE.
THANKS.
OH, YEAH.
CHAINS ARE TRICKY.
YEAH.
OF ALL THE PLACES FOR YOU
TO PEDAL INTO,
YOU HAD TO PEDAL INTO MINE, HUH?
YEAH.
WELL, WE'LL ALWAYS HAVE
THAT THIRD-FLOOR DORM.
-YEAH.
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
AS LONG AS
YOU'RE OUT HERE,
THERE'S A PLACE
A LITTLE FURTHER ALONG
THAT'S PRETTY SPECIAL,
IF YOU'D LIKE TO SEE IT.
SURE.
WHY NOT?
FOLLOW ME.
WOW.
TOLD YOU
IT WAS SPECIAL.
IT IS BEAUTIFUL.
YEAH.
I THINK THIS IS
OFFICIALLY MY FAVORITE PLACE.
MINE TOO.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
I'M SAYING GOODBYE,
AND YOU'RE SAYING "I DO."
NOW, THAT
COULD BE A SONG.
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT
TO LET GO OF ALL THIS?
I'M NOT SURE ABOUT
A LOT OF THINGS, LIVVY.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
THE INN, RIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW, ARE WE?
I'M NOT FALLING FOR THIS AGAIN.
FALLING FOR WHAT?
FOR YOU.
WELL, I REMEMBER YOU WERE
PRETTY HAPPY WITH ME ONCE.
I REMEMBER THE TAIL-LIGHTS
OF YOUR VAN
AS YOU DROVE AWAY.
OH, COME ON, I HAD A TOUR.
YOU PROMISED
YOU'D COME BACK FOR ME.
I DID.
OH, SORRY FOR NOT WAITING
TWO DECADES.
TWO DECADES?
IT WAS SIX MONTHS AT THE MOST.
AND YOU WERE ALREADY
WITH SOMEONE ELSE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU DIDN'T COME BACK FOR ME.
YEAH, I DID.
I WENT TO YOUR DORM.
YOUR ROOMMATE SAID
THAT YOU'D MET SOMEONE.
MY ROOMMATE?
MY-- WHY WOULD YOU
BELIEVE HER?
WELL, WHY WOULDN'T I?
BECAUSE SHE HAD A CRUSH ON YOU,
AND SHE WAS
A PATHOLOGICAL LIAR,
AND IF YOU HADN'T
GIVEN UP SO EASY,
YOU WOULD HAVE FOUND OUT
THAT I WAS HEARTBROKEN.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY TO THIS. I...
NOTHING.
I'M GOING BACK.
I CAN'T WAIT FOR THIS WEDDING
TO BE OVER.
WHAT DOES IT NEED?
NOTHING.
IT'S PERFECT.
WELL, THANK YOU,
BUT THAT'S NOT VERY HELPFUL.
EVERYTHING YOU'RE PREPARING
IS AMAZING.
IT CAN ALWAYS BE BETTER.
TRY THE SAUCE
THAT GOES WITH THIS.
AND?
ARE YOU GOING TO BE MAD
IF I SAY "AMAZING?"
-YEAH.
-THEN NO COMMENT.
YOU ARE LIKE YOUR MOM,
VERY SWEET.
TRY IT AGAIN.
IT'S BETTER, RIGHT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WHAT'S YOUR SECRET?
DON'T EVER SETTLE.
LIFE'S TOO SHORT, GRACE.
WE'RE STILL TALKING
FOOD, YEAH?
YOU DON'T THINK SHE SHOULD
MARRY JOSH EITHER, DO YOU?
WHAT I THINK...
IS THAT IT CAN ALWAYS BE BETTER.
MM.
MM-HMM.
HEY...
OH, HI.
I'M SORRY,
I KNOW THIS WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE
A WEEKEND WITHOUT
AN OPEN HOUSE.
OH, HONEY, WHAT'S A WEEKEND
WITHOUT AN OPEN HOUSE?
AFTER THE WEDDING,
WE'LL TAKE SOME TIME OFF.
YOU MEAN A HONEYMOON?
NOT THAT MUCH TIME.
YES, A HONEYMOON.
NO CELL PHONES,
OR SINGLE-FAMILY DWELLINGS?
DONE.
I HAVE TO HEAD INTO TOWN
AND PICK UP THE SIGNS.
YOU GOT THIS?
OH, I GOT THIS.
SEE YOU SOON.
OKAY.
-MORNING, GRACE.
-GOOD MORNING, JOSH.
REHEARSAL DINNER
TONIGHT.
GOT IT.
DON'T GO TOO FAR!
WOULDN'T
DREAM OF IT!
WORST GROOM EVER.
SO, WHERE'S HE OFF TO?
OH, IT'S OKAY.
OPEN HOUSE.
HE'LL BE BACK.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK,
AREA RUG, YES OR NO?
I LIKE THE RUG.
YEAH, I DO, TOO.
I MEAN, IT DOESN'T
SAY "WALL STREET,"
BUT... IT STAYS.
GUILT-INDUCING?
LET'S LEAVE THIS
THE WAY IT IS.
YOU KNOW, UM...
MAYBE A LITTLE
SENTIMENTALITY IS GOOD.
BUYERS CAN SEE
THAT PEOPLE WERE HAPPY HERE.
I HAVE TO SAY,
I LIKE WHAT YOU'VE
DONE WITH THE PLACE.
I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING.
EXACTLY.
GOOD MORNING, MICK.
MORNING, LADIES.
MORNING.
YOU DON'T...
NEED ANYTHING FROM ME, RIGHT?
NO.
NOT A THING.
YOU READY?
YEAH.
OKAY, UH...
WHERE WERE WE?
AS I RECALL,
WE WERE LEAVING EVERYTHING
EXACTLY AS IT WAS.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
MOM...
ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANT TO GET MARRIED?
WHAT?
IT'S JUST...
YOU'RE DIFFERENT AROUND HIM.
HIM?
WELL, IF I AM,
IT'S JUST BECAUSE HE BRINGS OUT
THE WORST IN ME.
OR THE BEST.
HONEY, I'M JUST
TRYING TO GET THROUGH
AN AWKWARD SITUATION.
IT WOULDN'T BE AWKWARD
IF YOU DIDN'T HAVE FEELINGS.
NOW, THAT--
THAT IS RIDICULOUS.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
MY WEDDING PLANNER.
I'M ALSO YOUR DAUGHTER.
AH!
WE SHOULD JOIN
THE WEEKEND TOURNAMENT
AT THE CLUB.
YEAH, MAYBE...
YOU SEEM DISTRACTED.
I'M HAVING
A LITTLE TROUBLE
MOVING ON, I GUESS.
FROM THE INN, OR HER?
THE INN.
WELL, SHE'S GETTING MARRIED
TOMORROW, RIGHT?
YEAH.
OKAY, WELL THEN,
PROBLEM SOLVED.
YOU'LL NEVER HAVE
TO SEE HER AGAIN.
OUT OF SIGHT,
OUT OF MIND.
YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU SELL THE INN,
WE SHOULD DO
SOMETHING SPECIAL.
LIKE A WEEKEND AWAY SOMEWHERE?
A WEEKEND?
OR A WEEK.
I MEAN, WHEN IS THE LAST TIME
YOU JUST WENT TRAVELING AROUND?
A LONG TIME AGO,
AND IT WAS ON A TOUR BUS.
WELL, I'M THINKING MORE...
HOTEL, AIRPLANE,
SANDY BEACH.
THIS COULD BE A SWEET
CORPORATE RETREAT.
IF WE GUT IT, YEAH.
EXACTLY WHAT
I WAS THINKING.
WAIT TILL YOU SEE
THE OUTSIDE.
800 FEET
OF PRIMETIME LAKEFRONT.
I'VE NEVER BEEN
TO AN OPEN HOUSE.
I'VE BEEN TO TOO MANY.
LOOKS LIKE
A BIG TURNOUT.
AT LEAST
HALF OF THEM ARE HERE
JUST TO SEE THE PLACE,
AND MAYBE GRAB
SOME FREE FOOD.
IT'S THE OTHER HALF
I'M WORRIED ABOUT.
IT'S WEIRD
THINKING ABOUT THIS PLACE
BELONGING TO SOMEONE ELSE.
OR A CORPORATION.
THERE'S ALWAYS A CHANCE
IT WON'T SELL,
ALTHOUGH WITH
A PROPERTY LIKE THIS...
HOW GOOD A SALESMAN IS JOSH?
HE SOLD MY MOM ON MARRIAGE,
SO I'D SAY GOOD.
I'D BETTER START
GETTING USED TO THE IDEA.
THE THING IS,
I'VE SEEN A LOT OF PEOPLE MOVE,
AND IT'S HARD.
BUT YOUR DAD
WILL BE OKAY.
AND YOU WILL, TOO.
YOU HAVE EACH OTHER.
THANKS, GRACE.
COME ON,
LET'S GRAB SOME SUSHI.
REHEARSAL DINNER?
"OPEN HOUSE SUSHI."
YOU SEE ALL THOSE
PEOPLE OUT THERE?
TRYING NOT TO.
YEAH, ME TOO.
I REMEMBER
WHEN I BOUGHT THIS PLACE.
THERE WAS NO SUSHI,
JUST AN OLD HOUSE
AND A RUSTY DOCK.
AND AN EVEN
RUSTIER DRUMMER
WHO MADE GRILLED CHEESE
ON AN IRON.
WHY'D YOU TAKE THAT
OFF THE MENU?
I THOUGHT IT WAS
A HOUSE FAVORITE?
MORE LIKE A DUCK FAVORITE.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO?
ABOUT WHAT?
SORRY ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
OUT ON THE BIKE TRAIL.
NAH, IT'S ALL RIGHT,
IT'S MY FAULT.
I DON'T KNOW
WHY I GOT SO UPSET.
PEOPLE GET NERVOUS
AROUND WEDDINGS.
YEAH.
I SEE IT ALL THE TIME.
DID YOU REALLY
COME BACK FOR ME?
YEAH, I DID.
THERE HE IS...
POP STAR IN THE FLESH.
WHOA-HO, HUGE FAN!
CAN I GET
A SELFIE?
SURE.
MY MOTHER
PLAYED YOU NON-STOP
WHEN I WAS
GROWING UP.
YOUR MOM, HUH?
AND MY GRANDMOTHER.
OH, YES...
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN BIG
WITH THE GRANDMOTHERS.
I CANNOT WAIT TO TELL THEM
WHOSE PROPERTY WE'RE BUYING.
I THINK I JUST
HEARD AN OFFER.
COME ON,
LET'S SHOW THEM WHERE
WE'RE GONNA TIE THE KNOT.
RIGHT UP HERE, GUYS.
SWEETIE?
WHAT'S THAT
YOU'RE READING THERE?
I WANTED TO DO
A TOAST AT THE WEDDING,
AND I NEEDED
SOME INSPIRATION.
BUT I'M NEVER GOING TO
BE ABLE TO WRITE
ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
THEY REALLY
LOVED EACH OTHER,
DIDN'T THEY, GRANDMA?
OH, IT WAS
SO LONG AGO,
THEY WERE WET
BEHIND THE EARS,
PUPPY LOVE.
IT WAS MORE THAN THAT.
MAYBE.
DEFINITELY.
EVEN BEFORE MICK LEFT,
YOU DIDN'T LIKE HIM.
WHY?
AS A MOTHER, UM,
YOU WANT THE BEST FOR YOUR KIDS.
SO, IF YOU SEE HEARTACHE COMING,
YOU DO EVERYTHING YOU CAN
TO JUMP IN AND DEFLECT IT.
READING THESE,
I'M GUESSING
SHE GOT HIT ANYWAY.
WHATEVER HAPPENED IN THE PAST
IS PASSED,
AND IT LOOKS LIKE EVERYTHING'S
TURNED OUT ALL RIGHT.
I MEAN, SHE'S GOT JOSH NOW.
BUT WHAT IF HE'S NOT
THE RIGHT ONE?
AND WHAT IF HE IS?
TELL YOU WHAT...
WHY DON'T YOU LET ME
MAKE THE TOAST, HMM?
IF YOU THINK OF SOMETHING,
YOU CAN ADD ON.
IT'S JUST ONE LESS THING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
FOLKS...
I'VE GOT A CHOIR GROUP
IN AN HOUR.
WHERE'S OUR GROOM?
HE'S...
HE'S ON A CALL.
HE WON'T BE LONG.
PERHAPS WE COULD USE
A STAND-IN UNTIL HE GETS HERE?
OH, YES,
JOHNNY WILL DO IT.
GO ON.
I KINDA MADE A VOW
NEVER TO WALK DOWN
ANOTHER AISLE, SO...
AND I'M JUST HEARING
ABOUT THIS NOW?
MICK, YOU DO IT.
UNFORTUNATELY
I'M A LITTLE BUSY.
DAD, GET UP THERE.
THE REVEREND HAS TO LEAVE.
COME ON.
AND... MUSIC.
WE ARE GATHERED TOGETHER
TO UNITE A COUPLE IN LOVE.
OBVIOUSLY,
THE BRIDE AND GROOM
WILL BE STANDING
A LITTLE CLOSER.
CLOSER.
THAT'S GOOD,
THAT'S GOOD.
I BELIEVE
YOU'VE WRITTEN YOUR OWN VOWS.
UH, ACTUALLY, I HAVEN'T
QUITE FINISHED MINE.
YOU REALLY HAVEN'T FINISHED?
NO.
SORRY, IT'S JUST,
YOU USED TO WRITE
ENTIRE SONGS FASTER.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
THOSE WORDS WERE MEANINGLESS.
OH, OUCH.
DOES THE STAND-IN
HAVE TO TALK?
PERHAPS WE'RE GETTING
A LITTLE OFF TRACK.
I BELIEVE WE HAVE A SONG?
YEAH, THAT'S ME AGAIN.
WE'LL SKIP OVER THAT.
RINGS?
THE GROOM
HAS THE RINGS.
AND THEN, OF COURSE,
DOES ANYONE OBJECT
TO THIS UNION...
JUST STRETCHING,
THAT'S ALL.
SIT DOWN.
MOVING ALONG,
I'LL PRONOUNCE YOU
MAN AND WIFE,
AND YOU MAY KISS THE BRIDE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WELL, YOU DON'T
WANT TO ARGUE
WITH A MAN OF GOD, DO YOU?
SORRY,
EVERYONE!
YOU MUST BE
THE GROOM.
I APOLOGIZE FOR
THE DELAY, REVEREND,
BUT I HAVE
SOME GREAT NEWS.
TWO OFFERS.
BOTH OVER ASK.
ALL CASH, 30-DAY ESCROW.
30 DAYS?
WELL, I COULD PUSH
FOR 15 DAYS IF YOU WANT.
NO, I WAS THINKING OF PUSHING
IN THE OTHER DIRECTION.
IF YOU LET THEM
SLEEP ON IT,
THEY MIGHT NOT SLEEP IN IT.
AND WITH THE PROFIT
THAT YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE,
I'M GOING TO FIND YOU
THE PLACE OF YOUR DREAMS.
BUT THIS WAS
THE PLACE OF MY DREAMS.
THERE ARE ALWAYS
BIGGER DREAMS.
CONGRATULATIONS.
WELL, I GUESS CONGRATULATIONS
IS IN ORDER FOR BOTH OF US.
OKAY, YOU TWO.
MAYBE A BRIDE AND GROOM KISS?
OH, YES.
SURE. GOOD IDEA.
GREAT.
OH, HANG ON, MY PHONE.
SORRY, I FORGOT
TO SHUT OFF MY PHONE.
YEAH, I'LL TURN IT OFF.
GOOD, ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
WOW, THAT'S WHAT I CALL
A REHEARSAL DINNER.
LET'S EAT!
OH, HEY, MICK.
I'LL HAVE THOSE PAPERS
DRAWN UP AFTER THE WEDDING.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
OUR BEING HERE WAS FATE.
MAYBE.
IT'S LOOKING LIKE OURS
WILL BE THE LAST WEDDING HERE.
TO MARRIAGES AND MORTGAGES.
AND YOU'RE GONNA BE
PAYING FOR BOTH OF THEM
FOR THE REST
OF YOUR LIFE.
I'D LIKE TO MAKE A TOAST.
OLIVIA...
I KNOW I'VE BEEN
CRITICAL OF YOU.
AND A LOT OF PEOPLE
IN THIS ROOM.
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT
TOGETHER, SWEETHEART.
MOM, WHERE ARE YOU
GOING WITH THIS?
I'M APOLOGIZING.
I'VE BEEN MARRIED A FEW TIMES,
AS A LOT OF YOU KNOW,
BUT THAT WAS BECAUSE
I DIDN'T WAIT FOR THE RIGHT ONE.
YOU ARE A WONDERFUL,
BEAUTIFUL,
SMART WOMAN,
OLIVIA,
AND I'M
SO PROUD OF YOU.
AND IN THE END,
YOU ALWAYS DO THE RIGHT THING.
HEAR, HEAR.
TO OLIVIA.
THANK YOU, MOM.
I KNOW YOU GUYS WANTED
TO DO THIS AT THE COURTHOUSE,
BUT I'M REALLY HAPPY
THAT WE'RE ALL
HERE TOGETHER
IN THIS AMAZING PLACE,
EVEN IF YOU DID MANAGE
TO SQUEEZE IN AN OPEN HOUSE.
MOM, YOU
ALWAYS TOLD ME
TO FOLLOW MY HEART.
TO FOLLOWING YOURS.
THANK YOU, HONEY.
I KNOW
I'M NOT PART OF THE FAMILY,
BUT I FEEL LIKE
I AM TONIGHT.
WE'VE HAD A LOT OF
WEDDINGS HERE,
BUT THIS ONE IS SPECIAL
FOR A LOT OF REASONS.
I WISH YOU BOTH THE VERY BEST.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU.
DAD, YOU SHOULD
MAKE A TOAST.
ME? NO!
DAD...
MICK, PLEASE.
IT WOULD MEAN A LOT
TO ALL OF US.
UM...
WELL, AS PART OF OLIVIA'S PAST,
IT'S...
IT'S AN HONOR
TO MEET HER FUTURE.
JOSH, YOU'RE A LUCKY MAN.
WHEN I THINK OF
THE TWO OF YOU TOGETHER...
...I FEEL SICK.
BECAUSE YOU NEVER THINK,
AT 19,
YOU'RE GOING TO MEET
THE LOVE OF YOUR LIFE.
I SHOULD HAVE
FOUGHT FOR YOU THEN, LIVVY,
BUT I MESSED UP,
AND I CAN'T STAND TO WATCH YOU
SLIP AWAY AGAIN.
WE BELONG TOGETHER.
DON'T MARRY HIM!
THAT'S ENOUGH.
I'M SORRY.
BUT I LOVE HER.
I ALWAYS HAVE--
JOSH!
IT'S ALL RIGHT, HONEY.
HE PROBABLY SHOULD HAVE
HIT ME HARDER.
I WAS WRONG
ABOUT YOU, MICK.
I'M SO SORRY.
HERE YOU GO, SWEETHEART.
THANKS.
I JUST CAME
TO SAY GOODBYE.
HOW'S YOUR DAD?
HE'LL BOUNCE BACK.
ALWAYS DOES.
I'M SURE THE DUCKS
WILL HELP HIM THROUGH IT.
HOW'S YOUR MOM?
SHE'LL SURVIVE.
WE'RE JUST HEADING OUT,
I'M GUESSING A WEDDING
WOULD BE A HARD SELL
AT THIS POINT.
I'D IT'S ON HOLD AT LEAST.
MOST LIKELY A VENUE CHANGE
IF ANYTHING.
UNDERSTANDABLE.
I WISH THINGS
ENDED DIFFERENTLY.
ME TOO.
GROUP HUG.
YOU HAVE MY EMAIL
AND MY NUMBER.
FRIEND ME.
I'M SO SORRY, MOM.
I JUST WANTED THINGS
TO BE ROMANTIC FOR YOU.
I KNOW, HONEY.
IT'S OKAY.
IT WAS AWFUL.
YOU KNOW, HONEY...
IT WASN'T.
I'VE BEEN THINKING A LOT
THE PAST FEW DAYS,
AND, YOU KNOW, I'VE REALIZED
THAT I'VE BEEN STAGING MY LIFE,
AND NOT LIVING IT.
AND I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO STAGE YOURS, TOO.
YOU DON'T NEED
TO BE THE NEW ME.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF I WANT TO BE THAT PERSON.
GO FIND YOURSELF,
SWEETHEART.
WHO KNOWS, MAYBE YOU'LL EVEN
WANT TO BE A WEDDING PLANNER.
AFTER THIS WEEKEND?
I DOUBT IT.
COME HERE.
I LOVE YOU.
WELL...
IT'S STILL OFFICIALLY
MY WEDDING DAY, AND...
I HAVE NOTHING TO DO.
DINNER AND A SAPPY MOVIE?
I WOULD LOVE TO.
IT'S JOSH.
HEY.
LEMON CAKE?
WHY NOT?
YOU OKAY?
I'M HANGING IN THERE.
I'M PROUD OF YOU, DAD.
I RUINED A WEDDING,
AND I LOST THE GIRL.
YOU TOOK A RISK.
AND FAILED EPICALLY.
NOT IN MY EYES.
YOU KNOW, MY COLLEGE
ISN'T THAT FAR AWAY.
YOU CAN VISIT ME ANYTIME.
AND YOU CAN
VISIT HOME ANYTIME.
THANKSGIVING
AT YOUR NEW PLACE?
THANKSGIVING HERE.
I'M NOT SELLING.
REALLY?
WHERE AM I GOING TO FIND
A PLACE ANY BETTER THAN THIS?
I LOVE YOU.
YOU'RE THE WORLD'S
GREATEST DAD.
AND I'VE GOT A TROPHY
TO PROVE IT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'VE BEEN BETTER.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
I GUESS IT'S SAFE TO SAY
THAT WE'RE NOT GOING
TO THE JUSTICE OF THE PEACE
ANYTIME SOON.
PROBABLY NOT.
UNLESS YOU HAVE A LISTING
NEAR THE COURTHOUSE?
IS THERE ONE?
WE ARE GOOD TOGETHER, OLIVIA.
WE ARE.
AT WORK.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS ENOUGH.
SO DID I.
BUT IT'S NOT,
FOR EITHER OF US.
HEY, YOU TWO.
SO...
I GUESS CONGRATULATIONS
ARE IN ORDER?
NO, THAT...
RECENTLY
FELL OUT OF ESCROW.
OH, I'M SORRY
TO HEAR THAT.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
WELL, THE REASON
I CALLED YOU BOTH
IS THAT I'VE DECIDED
TO LIST AFTER ALL.
REALLY?
I MEAN, THE PLACE IS AMAZING,
AND OLIVIA,
IT'S NEVER LOOKED BETTER,
BUT...
IT JUST DOESN'T
FEEL LIKE ME ANYMORE.
I THINK I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
BRUCE, I HAVE
A GREAT LISTING
THAT JUST CAME ON THE MARKET.
KILLER VIEWS,
3,200 SQUARE FEET.
WHEN YOU SEE IT,
YOU'RE GONNA FORGET
THAT YOU LIVED ANYWHERE ELSE.
AND HE'S BACK.
...IT'S GONNA BE FANTASTIC.
HEY!
DRINK UP.
WE GOT A GIG.
DON'T TELL ME YOU BOOKED
ANOTHER WEDDING?
NO, A CLUB.
TWO NIGHTS.
AND BEFORE YOU SAY NO,
THINK OF ALL THE PERKS.
POOR PAY,
POOR HOURS,
ALL WE CAN DRINK.
I'M IN.
YEAH.
IT'S BEEN A LONG
TIME, BUDDY.
MOM, YOU READY?
COMING!
YOU LOOK AMAZING.
THANK YOU.
AND BY THE WAY,
WE'RE NOT GOING TO DINNER,
OR A MOVIE.
WE'RE NOT?
NOPE. COME ON.
YOU MADE IT!
WE DID.
OLIVIA, YOU LOOK...
LIKE HER OLD SELF.
"OLD?"
NEW "OLD."
COME ON,
I SAVED YOU SOME SEATS UP FRONT.
WEDDING'S OFF.
GIG'S ON.
♪ IT'S YOU AND ME ♪
♪ THERE IS NO OTHER WAY ♪
♪ AND WE'RE
STARTING HERE TODAY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE TODAY ♪
♪ IT'S JUST YOU AND ME ♪
♪ I FEEL YOU DEEP IN MY HEART ♪
♪ OOH... ♪
♪ OH, IT BREAKS
WHEN WE'RE APART ♪
♪ AND THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
FOR ME TO SHOW YOU ♪
♪ OOH, YOU KNOW
ALL THERE IS TO KNOW ♪
♪ NOW IT'S YOU AND ME ♪
♪ THAT'S THE WAY
IT'S GONNA BE ♪
♪ AND PRETTY SOON
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ THAT FOREVER YOU'RE MINE ♪
♪ IT'S YOU AND ME ♪
♪ THERE IS NO OTHER WAY ♪
♪ AND WE'RE
STARTING HERE TODAY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE TODAY ♪
♪ IT'S JUST AND ME... ♪
♪ OOH, IT'S JUST YOU AND ME ♪
♪ IT'S JUST YOU AND ME ♪