Josh, can you please just, um,
- look at the storyboard here?
- Uh-huh.
Me and my storyboard artists
worked on these panels
for, uh, about six years here.
I don't want to
toot my own horn,
but, uh, there's been
a lot of anticipation
from the whole team
about this project,
so I just, uh...
I'm very excited to get started.
Okay.
What's that?
No, I think it's--
You're perfect
right there.
-I'm Izzy.
-And my name is Diana.
And we're making a movie.
And it's called The Seed.
The Seed is an intimate
neo-noir
reflecting on both the overt
and subvert oppression of women.
Is there another way
to say neo-noir?
No?
I just--
as a-- as a, you know...
It's like a neo-noir.
Not everyone knows
what neo-noir is.
Well, like,
then we don't need their money.
Okay.
It's about the things
that limit us.
The possibilities in the future
through plant life.
The Seed is a film about the...
Uh, apocalyptic? Fuck.
This gorgeous woman sitting
next to me, Diana Irvine,
is our lead actress.
I-- I actually do think
it's important
to show vulnerability, Izzy,
I think it's important to--
when you're asking for money
to, like, endear yourself.
It's okay, just be human.
Our fundraising goal
is 600 tho--
That's always the thing
on crowdfunding stuff.
It's like, "Okay, why this--"
you know, "Why this project?"
Like, what about it
is so special?
Like, why our film, you know?
Yeah.
Are you gonna donate?
Yeah. Deep need. Yes.
And you feel it.
Oh, Iz. Oh, Iz.
Oh, no, you're actually upset?
Oh, I thought
you were acting for a second.
I was like, "That's good."
Our fundraising goal
is $600,000.
Any amount helps.
Howdy.
We're making a movie! Yeah!
-Hey!
-Hey, Iz. Hey.
- Road trip. So fun.
- Hey, Josh.
- What's with the camera?
- Hey.
My brother's gonna do
behind the scenes stuff for us.
It's gonna be great
for marketing.
Okay.
So he's gonna
follow us in his car?
No, he's gonna, um...
he's coming with us
'cause you got
a big old car here.
I didn't know that
so I just gotta, um--
He's got these,
um, camera cases too,
so just, uh...
Uh-huh.
You still live
with your parents?
Yeah.
-Yeah.
-Dude.
You said you were gonna look
into the COVID protocols?
Yeah,
so that binder back there,
that's the whole--
that's all of it.
Oh, I thought
these were your lines.
No, no,
so that's the protocols
for the state and the city,
um, that we're gonna be in.
And then also
just my suggestions
for basic protocol on set.
This whole-- this whole--
this whole thing is--
- Mm-hmm?
- Did you read the whole thing?
- I compiled it.
- You wrote it?
Well, I compiled it.
But I think
we're fine in the car.
I think I'm gonna take mine off
because it's just,
like, you know.
It's just too much in the car.
It is a long drive, I guess.
It's three days.
It's three days, Diana,
I mean, come on.
- I'll skim it.
- No, don't skim it.
I mean, you know, you got
plenty of time to read it.
You can actually read it,
but we're okay
because we're-- you know,
we're effectively--
a-- a family.
There's also a section in there
about intimacy
and physical intimacy.
No touching, no hugging,
definitely no kissing.
We can't have any, like,
on set romances
or any like, hooking up
or anything like that.
You hear that Josh?
No hooking up.
- I think that's a good rule.
- Okay.
I think
that's an important rule.
I think well done
for making that rule.
Uh, I think, yeah,
obviously no hooking up.
I mean, that's the best way
to get sick
for lots of different reasons.
Right, Diana?
You know some-- you know
a couple things about that.
- Don't put that in.
- What? Izzy.
How much longer?
Today? Like, six hours.
Thanks for driving.
Thanks so much for asking me.
I think it's really important
that I, in fact--
yeah, I think this is--
this is why you're here to--
so that I can share
all of my, you know, thoughts.
Making this film...
you know, it's just...
I've always dreamt
of making a film.
Have you directed
a film before?
I have observed from afar
many, uh,
very powerful directors
and from that,
I have gleaned
excellent techniques
and I will bring that
to this production
and I'm very excited about it.
Okay, not all--
You can stop now.
Oh, I am starving.
-This looks so good. Great.
-Yeah.
Did you just-- did you just
use the public bathroom?
Number two, so...
I...
I washed
my hands already, Diana.
Yeah, no, just,
you know, for safety.
Yeah, but the episode
should be airing soon.
I hope that,
you know, when I see Matt,
he'll tell me
if it was good or not
because I haven't
heard anything.
Did they like your
suggestions about the character?
Yeah, the director was,
like, all for it.
At first, a little resistant,
but then was just really
into me taking ownership.
And the wig
that you brought,
did they end up using that?
No, no, they didn't.
When that comes out
and then when this comes out.
- Yeah.
- Together it's gonna be so good.
I really want my reps also
to just, like,
see me in a new light
and I think that-
They didn't drop you?
I thought they dropped you?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They just said
that we should, you know,
have a talk when I get back.
- To part ways?
- Um, no, no, no, no, no.
I mean that's, you know,
I mean,
I might decide that I want that.
- But I think they just---
- Right.
They just want to touch base.
Got it, got it.
You know, they-- I need
to tell them where I'm at
and they need to know
how I feel.
Yeah, totally.
There's gonna be
an enormous amount of momentum
for you after this, I think.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, I can't wait.
- I need that.
- Yeah.
- I need that momentum.
- See the sign.
- Yeah.
Really, just a sign
that it's gonna keep going.
Yeah.
Um, so you were supposed
to have gotten off
about eight miles ago.
Exit 75.
And let me try to find
the name of the road.
It's called "Exit 75."
I just feel like we're going
in circles a little bit.
Well, we'll go
in a circle for this...
- Okay.
- ...but we're not--
we're going in a pretty
straight line otherwise.
Josh, thank God
that you are here.
This is absolutely terrifying.
-Oh, shit!
-What? What?
I forgot to bring my toothpaste.
I'll just...
I'll just use some water.
Dude,
you can use my toothpaste.
- Really?
- Yeah, it's okay.
It wasn't
in the protocols though.
It's okay.
Did you brush your teeth yet?
You have to brush
your teeth tonight, Josh.
He has this thing
about brushing his teeth.
- It's gross.
- Mm-hmm.
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
-What?
Ew, I don't know,
there's something on the floor,
there's something there.
Gotta wipe it.
Do you have
any more of those wipes?
- It's like tar.
- Tar?
Did you tell her
that we're here?
- Did, like--
- No, I texted her.
Okay.
She didn't text me back.
I think she does.
She didn't text you back?
Well, like, I don't--
Does she know
we're coming today?
Oh, my God,
this is so beautiful.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God,
it's beautiful.
Do you think
we can eat that corn
or is it like, uh--
like, uh, ornamental corn?
- Wait, what is that?
- What?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God,
that is beautiful.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, wow. Wow.
Di, there's a tree,
what the fuck?
- I'm sorry.
- Jesus.
- Hi, Izzy.
- Hi!
- How you doing?
- I'm good. How are you?
What a beautiful farm you have.
This work for you?
Yeah, I think it'll work.
Diana was telling me
how incredible you looked
on the horse
when you were driving in.
- Oh, my God. Thank you.
- Oh, yeah.
Well, I used to ride
so I just-- I miss it, you know?
-You used to ride?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
-What kind of riding?
-What did you do?
Um, like, a mix
of little-- a little English
and, um, uh,
the-- the-- the-- you know.
Yeah, cool.
-That's awesome.
-Yeah.
-There is a guy here.
-Yeah?
He's been looking for you.
-Wait, does he have a poof?
-He does.
He keeps asking about the WiFi.
Dude, you gotta wear
your mask.
I'm six feet, bro!
Oh, there he is. Hi, Matt!
-Hi.
-What's up?
He's my producer.
- He's amazing. Um...
- Okay.
- He grows on you.
- All good.
- I'll let you settle in.
- Amazing.
Well, yeah, you guys
should definitely hang out.
-I think you'll really--
-Yeah.
We will.
It'll-- we'll-- I'll see ya.
Why did you just say that?
It's so awkward, Izzy.
I want you to be friends.
Yeah, but, like...
The Seed
is set in a barn,
which is why
we're in Kentucky here.
I really wanted
to combine rural America
with a sort of dystopian view,
sort of superimpose that
on-- on it.
Luckily, I have family friends
who own a barn here in Kentucky.
This image here, I think
really encapsulates the film,
you know, somewhat surrealist,
somewhat noir.
We had to, um...
scale back a little bit
on, um-- on these ideas just,
uh, for budgetary concerns,
so disregard
all of the, um, protective gear,
but, um, that was
the original intent.
I love this, Josh.
Little movement.
Most of my character work
starts with-- with costume
and-- and within the costuming,
starts with the feet.
My feet touch the earth.
It's how I stay grounded.
So I need to look down
and go, "That's Delta."
You know, from here up,
I'm Diana
and from here down, Delta.
So it's a--
it's a big part of my process.
Acting.
Are shoes as important to you?
Yeah. Yeah.
- I think it's important...
- Okay.
...for a character...
to get into character.
To get in some shoes.
- It's a-- wardrobe.
- Mm-hmm.
Are those good pants
for horseback riding?
-Are there horses in this?
-No.
If you put a horse in this,
I can ride it.
I just didn't do
the world-building for that,
um, when I did my research.
Um, I didn't think about horses.
Okay, that's fine.
But we could ask Izzy.
I-- um, I can-- I can prep that,
I can prep that.
Then I am gonna...
put my pants on.
Great!
- So...
Gotta take these pants off
to get these pants on.
Yeah,
totally, absolutely.
Uh, I'm gonna go talk to Izzy
about the horses.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, yeah.
Well, it's a survival film.
So, um, if there-- if it--
if we're still in that range,
then we're good.
Okay.
Yeah, for sure. Okay, bye.
Um, well, I...
I-- I think
everything has gluten in it, Di.
-Okay, that's-- that's fine.
-I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, no worries.
I just-- I just won't to eat.
- Okay, so--
- Hey!
-Oh, Geoff, hi.
-Hey, I made it.
You made it?
You're-- Geoff, you're late.
Yeah, I had to take care
of something.
What's with all these cameras?
- Matt, this is Jeff.
- Hey, 'sup, man?
This is our DP,
Alec has won a lot of awards.
We're super lucky to have him
and let me introduce you
to our co-- your co-stars,
um, Diana and, um, Devon,
this is Geoff.
-Hey, ladies.
-Hey.
Ma'am.
While I have you all here,
I've just got some, uh, forms
for you to sign.
- Here you go.
- Safety first.
- At all times.
Just some
standard contracts, you know,
release forms, yadda, yadda,
yadda, boring, boring, boring.
Yeah, you can just sign
at the bottom.
That's right, you can skip
three through, uh, seven.
It's just right there.
This is just to release
production from responsibility
if something goes down...
which of course it won't
'cause we've got Izzy in charge.
Am I right? Sound good?
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey.
Try to distract them
when they're looking at it.
If they read the whole thing,
they might have more questions.
- Oh, what kind of questions?
- Here we go.
Why does it say
that "the production
is not responsible
if any of us
catches any kind of--"
If you get sick,
we can't actually tell
where it came from, right?
So you don't know
that it came from here.
You know what I mean? We can't--
I don't know, I mean,
like, if all of us got sick,
I think it'd be pretty obvious.
- Hey-- hey, Matt?
- Yes, ma'am.
I'm just wondering why that part
is handwritten on the back?
Sure, that was,
uh, that's-- that's--
that's a little touch from me.
Bottom line is
if you don't fill out
these forms tonight,
we can't film tomorrow.
So just sign at the bottom.
- Hey, guys?
- Thank you, brother.
Who, um, wants some wine?
No, no,
we're working tomorrow, so.
Oh, yeah, totally.
- Um, I'll have some.
- Okay, cool.
I got it,
the initials work.
Bless you.
Just sign at the bottom
and, uh-- and, uh,
I'll date it for you
if you want me to.
Yep, thank you, brother.
Um, are we doing
the read through
tonight or tomorrow morning?
Oh,
we actually have enough time
for either a read through
or load in,
so a real Sophie's choice.
You didn't schedule time
for a load in, what the--
I can squeeze one in,
but then we've got
to pull up the call time
by two and a half hours.
- Matt, she'd have to do the--
- No she doesn't.
All right, y'all,
so what we're gonna do
is we're gonna pull
the call time up tomorrow
by about two and a half hours
to make room for the load in.
That's about 4:30 a.m.,
not too bad, not too bad at all.
That's fine,
I've done that before.
Easy pe--
Oh, and hey,
not gonna print new call sheets.
Why waste paper, yeah?
So just do the math.
Subtract about 150 minutes
from whatever it is now
and that's your call time, 4:30.
Gotta save those trees.
Right, Diana?
I was actually wondering, Matt,
um, how the episode
is coming together,
how the edit is,
and when is it gonna--
The episode. Our episode.
-Yeah, I'm dying to know.
-Oh, my gosh.
Also, it was so fun
working with you
and I'm glad
we get to do it again.
Oh, me too.
I'm really glad
we get to do it again
because that episode
has changed a lot.
Okay, cool.
I'm excited to see it.
I'll mark my calendar.
When is it coming out?
It's coming out next month
and it's not gonna look
anything like you remember.
Primarily from
your character's perspective.
Cool, can I still get
the footage for my reel?
You can't get
the footage anymore,
contractually and legally,
because, uh...
You know what?
Take a deep breath in.
Exhale.
One more time. Deep breath in.
You're not in it anymore.
We re-casted.
Exhale.
Let that part out
of your system.
-Matt, sorry.
-We had to recast the part.
You did everything right.
We were just looking at it
and thought maybe somebody else.
- Wait, sorry, I'm-- I'm lost--
- Don't be sorry.
No, no, Di. Don't be sorry.
Because now
we've got The Seed,  huh?
Let's leave the past
in the past.
It's not even smart
to talk about it.
You recast me?
We did recast you,
but that was then, this is now,
and now you're first
on the call sheet, babe.
And I think this is redemption.
Hold that thought.
Hey, Geoff. Geoff, Geoff, Geoff.
It's actually- whoa,
we've gotta distribute these.
Protocol, you know what I mean?
Want some wine?
- Yeah, I do.
- Got it.
I would actually
love some wine, too.
- Yeah? Okay.
- Yeah.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
- Oh, I'm so good.
- All right.
I just-- I just changed my mind.
Really happy to be here.
Thank you so much.
And hey, I hate
that we had to do it like this,
but I know you can handle it.
-You know what?
-Yeah?
We'll just-- you'll get me
on the next one, right?
I will get you on that--
you know, I got you on this one.
-How about that?
-Can I get some more wine?
Or actually something stronger.
Do we have any--
Is that normal for, like--
to do, like, the whole roll
and get cut?
Um, it does happen
to some people.
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
And you know-- you know people
make-- make-- make choices,
I mean, editing-- a movie
is made three times, right?
When it's-- when it's written,
when it's shot,
and when it's edited,
so, um, there's a lot of...
there's a lot of changes
that happened.
I'm just gonna-- um,
I'm gonna run to the bathroom.
- And then I'll be back.
- Okay.
Can you not? Just don't--
- What is happening?
- Just don't talk to her, okay?
She's-- it's-- it's-- it's
just happened a lot, okay?
So please just
don't say anything.
Are these guys gonna be filming
the whole time?
Um...
yeah.
Izzy, this is so weird.
I'm gonna need you
to blur my face out
of all of this stuff.
- I'm gonna go to sleep.
- Sorry.
Yeah, I'm gonna see
how Diana is.
Okay.
Is this your first movie, too?
Yeah.
-Yeah.
-Cool.
Yep.
It's gonna be great.
- Good night.
- Night.
Hey, Josh.
Do you know where I'm staying?
Uh...
Good morning.
Guess what day it is today?
It's the first day of my movie!
And I'm just, um...
I'm just really happy.
I'm really happy.
I have been on sets
for ten years...
as the assistant
to somebody else
and guess-- guess what?
Not anymore!
This time, it's my set...
and I'm not an assistant.
It's so good.
I'm so happy.
If I can do it, so can you.
Keep going.
-Oh, hey, Geoff.
-Hey, morning.
-Hi.
-Yeah.
Hey, um, is my boom guy
here yet?
Oh, yeah, buddy, we cut him.
You-- you what?
We cut him.
Motherf--
Dude.
What's your job?
Don't you have some,
like, acting exercises to do?
- No.
- That's really too bad.
How high's that go up?
Hey, um,
have a sound pack for you.
So are you comfortable
with this?
- Yeah, that's fine.
- Down here.
Okay.
Hey, Diana.
-You look bad.
-Okay.
Hey, Matt, sorry,
do you have an Ibuprofen?
Nah, Ibuprofen? No.
Wait, you're not sick, are you?
-No, no, I just have a headache.
-Okay, are you sure?
Because we're all getting tested
again tomorrow.
-Yeah, I promise I'm fine.
-Okay.
Um, Josh, do you-- no.
Did you drink too much?
Nice costume, man.
It's just
my regular clothes, man.
Hey, Izzy,
why does this guy have a beeper?
Um, I don't know, he's just,
like, a nostalgic kind of guy.
Hey, Izzy, how do you
and Geoff know each other?
Uh, just--
uh, I don't know,
like, out and about.
- Ew.
- Out and about.
Rehearsal, everybody!
Okay, so tell me
about your limp.
You push your hip forward
and then you roll with it.
Okay, two more times.
Delta Ray.
It's empty.
You don't know
what's in that.
I do now.
High levels of nitrogen,
little phosphorus.
Potassium carbonate.
Someone tried
to burn something here.
Maybe a body.
Okay, sorry.
I'm so sorry, guys.
I'm so sorry. Um...
Okay, while we're holding,
are we gonna be going in
any tighter or?
Because I'm saving
a lot for the--
Yeah, no, we'll go tighter.
Just-- just-- just a moment.
We'll-- We'll-- Diana. We'll...
Go check it out.
Yeah, I'll definitely go
check it out.
Okay.
Like, now.
Oh, like, right now, right now.
Got it.
- Hi!
- Hey, can I help you?
- Hey.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
-I'm here for a set visit.
-Oh, okay.
Uh, normally when you come
to see somebody on set,
you're coming
to watch them film,
so you wouldn't drive up
slamming on your horn.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
That's exactly what I did.
That's exactly what you did.
-Matt, this is Felipe.
-Uh, Felipe? Felipe.
- Felipe!
- Hi.
-Hey.
-I'm so sorry.
- All right.
- It's okay.
Oh, my God.
Hi, Felipe. You're here!
-You're doing it.
-I'm doing it.
Um, how are you?
- How was the drive?
- It was wonderful.
I saw a bird that I think
was pretty much the same bird
just followed me half the ride.
I met a girl in Wichita.
-Wichi-- Wichi-- Wichita.
-Wichita.
Her name was Chastity
and, uh, I spent the night
just, like, holding her
while she cried
and it was transcendent.
So you with the, um, stranger
on the way--
With Chastity.
Wow, okay,
so, um, just by the way,
so we can't hook up
with anybody here.
Diana's--
It's Diana's rules, so.
Just for s-- you know, safety.
-Okay.
-Oh, hi, guys.
This is Felipe.
He's our financier.
He's, you know,
big man on campus.
He's the reason
that we're all here.
So, I think, like,
let's give him
a really big round of applause.
- Yay, Felipe!
- Stop!
- So fun.
- Stop it.
Stop it, you guys.
Stop, stop.
All right,
should we keep going?
- Let's do it.
- Yeah, come on guys.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Come on. Geoff.
- We'll talk.
- Great.
Let's make a movie!
Hi!
Thanks for so much,
like, for all of this.
Oh, my God, it's my pleasure.
I'm so excited.
Everyone--
Actually, can I get a headset?
-Oh, Stefan.
-Oh, yeah, sure.
Can we get a headset for Felipe?
No? No more headsets?
-Um...
Yeah, that's fine.
Oh, my God. Thank you.
-Yeah, sure.
-Okay. That's really sweet.
That's, like, amazing 'cause
you already know the script.
Okay. And action.
What y'all doing on my land?
Actually, just so I'm not,
like, get in the way again,
can I sit?
'Cause I've been driving and
my legs are, like, killing me.
I just don't want
to complain again about it--
You want to sit
because you've been driving?
Yeah, that's fine.
I'm so sorry,
of course, take a seat.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
- Um, yeah, no problem.
- That's better.
Why does it just keep...
- Hey.
You're on my target.
Um-- oh! Oh, oh, wow.
- Sorry.
- It's all right.
Wow. This is...
that's cool.
-You wanna try?
-No, no, no.
Why not?
Come on.
-Left forearm.
-Okay.
Yep.
-Grab it right below my hand.
-Okay.
Nope. Below. Yeah. Nice.
- Okay. Two fingers.
- Mm-hmm.
Just gonna pull it
right back onto the string.
-Into here. Okay.
-Yep, that's nice.
-Okay, you can go.
-Oh, my gosh.
I want you
to square your hips up.
-Okay.
-Okay. This arm straight out.
- Mm-hmm.
- Great.
Now pull this one back.
You're gonna anchor your thumb
to the corner of your mouth.
-Yeah? When you're ready.
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay. Yep.
-Okay.
Gotta keep it square.
-Yep. Good.
Nice. Yep. Straight.
Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
It's really scary.
-It's okay.
-I'm so sorry.
-No, you're doing well.
-Okay, I just feel--
Good. That's good. You got it.
-I'm just nervous.
-Don't be.
Okay.
There you go. Yep. Way back.
-Arms straight. Eyes forward.
-Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Slightly down. Good.
When you're ready.
Keep your eyes forward.
-Yes. Sorry.
-Just release the two fingers.
-Wow!
-That was actually really good.
I've never done that before!
Well, you did a really good job.
-Thank you.
-You're so welcome.
-Wanna do it again?
-No, no, no, no, no, no.
-No?
-No. You take that.
-Okay.
-But I'm really grateful.
You're so welcome.
And now it's a new--
new skill of mine.
As a thespian I can tell people
I've-- I've done it
before at least.
Cool, well,
I'll leave you to it.
I don't wanna--
I don't wanna im-- impede.
- All right.
- I'll see you.
Ooh, I need to make sure
you understand your job.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, so what happens?
Before 11, girls get in free,
dude, you can't charge them.
Chicks in free, dicks pay.
Yeah, chicks free, dicks--
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you get it.
Make it a rhyme.
Okay, it's not a club.
No, it's a lounge.
That's right.
Dude, I'm on a movie set, bro.
Put Mom on the phone.
Put Mom on the phone, dude.
Our supplements
simultaneously allow you
to lose weight,
have more energy,
sleep more soundly,
and increase sex drive.
So, make that initial investment
of $250 today
and live the life
you've always dreamed of.
Better believe you deserve it.
Better Believe Supplements
is the key
to the door to the world.
Dinner's good?
Yeah, no,
we should-- we should--
Yeah, it's really yummy.
Who made it?
- I think it's really yummy.
- Yeah, it's delicious.
Soul food, that's that supper.
-I'm just gonna go eat outside.
-No, Di, Di, Di.
We're a pod,
so we're actually all safe.
- Yeah, we're a pod.
- This is good. We're safe.
Out of all the pods I'm in,
I trust this pod the most.
Are you-- are you
in more than one pod?
- What does that mean?
- Yeah.
Well, it's like a pod of pods.
I don't think that's-- I don't
think that's how it works.
That's not
how it works at all.
-CDC.
-Okay. Okay, sure. You're right.
I think it's okay, Di.
It's-- we just, like,
cleaned-washed
our hands and stuff.
Do you want me
to get you some more food?
-No, no, I got plenty.
-Okay.
So I've been meaning to ask you,
is this your first feature?
I did
a TV movie last-- last spring,
but this is the first time
I'm a lead,
- so...
- Amazing.
This is my first time, so,
I mean, give me some pointers.
Yeah, 'cause you've done
a lot of theater and stuff?
I mean,
it's not really theater per se.
-It's more like dinner theater.
-Um, hey, guys.
Um, in the, uh, spirit
of community and sharing,
we're actually
all gonna, um, share
the cost of food for production.
- Is that a joke?
- Yeah.
I mean, I thought Felipe was
bankrolling this whole thing.
I'm getting a phone call.
Bonjour. Oui.
- Uh...
- Okay, listen.
Honestly, we have
a tight budget, all right?
- So, uh--
- What budget?
-You're not paying us.
-Yeah, they are.
They're paying you?
-What?
-Oh, great. Okay.
I see that
we've reached a consensus.
Beautiful.
Um, so production will be
covering the cost of food
and thank you so much
for all speaking your truth.
It's very helpful
for me, so great.
When she says from now on,
does that mean
we have to pay for this one?
'Cause it's tasted way better
when it was free.
How are we actually
going to cover that?
Um...
Felipe, you know, has donated
so much already, so, uh...
Uh, well, you know,
um, my unemployment check
I think will clear
at the end of this week
and then I can
probably cover half of it
and then you could maybe cover
the other half maybe?
I, uh...
Oh, um, okay, no, that's okay.
No, it's my project
and I will shoulder,
um, the costs.
You sure?
'Cause I don't wanna be a dick.
Yeah, no, it's my choice
and it's my voice.
I love that rhyme.
Josh,
you're filming this too?
Unpaid work.
Grab a chicken wing.
Yeah, there's more
that's here for you guys.
Hi. Hello. Yes, yes.
Um, my name is Is-- Isabel,
Isabel Shill,
S-H-I-L-L.
Yes, that's right.
Hi, Candace.
Yes, so nice to-- uh, hello.
I was wondering, um,
uh, if there's any way for me
to increase my credit card limit
on my Visa?
Um, uh, it's already-- okay.
No. Okay. Um, that's fine.
That's fine.
How about...
um...
how about on my dad's card?
What the fuck?
Okay. Focus, focus.
Okay. Focus.
Big Geoff to Little Geoff,
real talk right here.
That picket fence. The family.
That ship sailed.
We didn't make it.
Uh-huh.
It doesn't have to be
like before.
Right, yeah. You're an actor.
You got this.
It's like that thing Jack says.
Lie to yourself first,
double down,
the world falls into place.
Don't screw this up.
Good morning, camera.
- Good morning, Geoff.
- Oh, hey.
- Did you sleep okay?
- No.
Do you want me
to move that?
No.
That's
a safety hazard, Alec.
- Geoff.
- Geoff, please.
What are you doing, man?
- Morning!
- Hi, Diana!
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey, good morning.
Izzy, can you
clear frame please?
Did you-- did you
just touch my prop?
What? No, no.
I would never.
Uh, yeah, sure. Whatever.
I-- okay,
guys, guys,
I think the communication
is breaking down
a little bit here.
-Please don't touch the camera.
-Just checking the frame.
Geoff, get-- Jesus!
- Josh... Six feet!
- Okay, dude!
Sorry, Jesus. Stop.
Like a fucking zoo.
-Geoff, get away from me.
-When do we rehearse?
Hey, Geoff, clear frame.
This is all frame. Thank you.
Are you kidding me?
Get out of my space.
The genetics are malleable.
Jesus.
You know,
she's-- she's asexual, you know?
Ugh, what?
Seriously?
- I'm not.
- Huh?
Josh!
- Get outta here.
- Why?
- That's weird. Stop.
- You're weird.
- Can I help you?
- Y-- yes.
Hi. Yes.
I would like to report
a work violation in Kentucky.
Not LA. No.
I've brought it up several times
and production doesn't seem
interested
in following the regulations
that, as far as I know,
state and local governments
have issued.
No, I have a list.
What? Oh, sorry, what?
My membership number?
Um, uh, I thought I could make
an anonymous complaint?
That's what it said
on the website at least.
Right. Right, I--
There aren't any
SAG performers on this shoot.
Well, that was
such a funny joke.
No, it's not.
I am not in SAG
but I am SAG eligible.
Yeah. Oh. Sure.
I-- mm-hmm.
Well-- well-- well, thank you.
Thank you for all
that you do for--
Hello?
Um, I'm just...
Morning.
So, here, um, I'm really,
really excited about this.
This is the miracle plant here.
It came to me in a dream
and it has the ability
to inseminate women.
Um, and that is
how it saves the world.
Yeah, it kind of kept appearing
in my unconscious mind,
um, over and over
and over again.
Hey, now. I was just looking.
Looked like you were touching.
- Is this it?
- Maybe.
-How do I know it's even real?
-That's none of your business.
If this is gonna
save our species,
I think it falls
under the purview
of something I'd like to know.
This is it.
- How's it work?
- Don't.
It's genetics are malleable.
What does that mean?
It's double helix
adapts to different species.
Um, this is a moment
of discovery for Russ,
you know,
as well as the audience.
- Yeah.
- And I just want to make sure
that we're all clear
on the scientific language.
The thing
that's amazing about it
is that it's actually
all really possible.
- It is?
- Yeah.
In theory. Uh, let's shoot.
Oh, okay, um, it's-- no.
It's not possible,
just so you know.
It's not a thing.
I made
some breakthroughs with plants,
cross pollinations that,
in other circumstances,
would never hybridize.
Then with rats.
I had some success
with the jellyfish.
I was on the verge of seeing
if it could fertilize
a human egg.
That's when the ash came.
-The ash.
But we've been on the run
for about a week now.
It needs some consistent
photosynthetic opportunity
in order
to maintain the stability
of its genetic structure.
Yeah, sure.
Male sperm
would no longer be necessary.
It's fine with me.
But how would you even go about
fertilizing a human egg then?
Experiments are ongoing.
- Diana.
- Oh, hey.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- How are you doing?
- Good, good.
- I'm just working.
- Cool.
I just have my script analysis
happening right now.
What I'm doing
right now, actually,
is I am working
on my animal exercises.
Delta Ray is a scientist,
she's very smart.
She is-- she is grounded
and-- um, and wise
and so for her,
I've chosen a salamander.
You know, really what that means
is that I observe salamanders
in the wild
or watch YouTube videos
and I just sort of
go deep on their behavior.
- Yeah.
- Neat.
And, you know,
the person who really--
really taught me this,
um, is my acting teacher,
Rudolph Eichner.
He teaches the Eichner technique
and I've been studying with Rudy
for about ten years now,
so, um, you know,
if it wasn't for him, I...
I wouldn't be in this place.
Geoff, for example,
Geoff is a badger, you know?
He's got that energy to him.
Because of Rudy,
I can identify quickly,
um, what people's animals are.
He-- he's not cheap,
but-- uh,
but he is worth every penny
and, you know,
if I have to skimp,
um, and pay,
like, cheaper rent--
I-- I've moved,
I have moved before
because all I wanna do
is-- is afford that class.
If you bring people
into the class,
you get a discount.
So-- um, so I have
a lot of friends in that class.
Yeah.
Anyways, I-- I think
I should get back to studying
because we have an early call
and I am behind.
Terrible.
-Hey.
-Hello.
So word on the street
is you were the voice
of in
the Explorer.
-That's the word on the street?
-Oh, no, sorry.
-Uh, Izzy told me.
-Izzy told you that?
Sorry, sorry,
should she not have?
No, I'm just kidding.
Yeah, that was totally me.
Uh, I-- I was.
Cool. That's amazing.
I've been trying to get
into voice over
if you have any tips.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
There's, like, one golden rule.
-One.
-There's one rule. Okay?
And it's that the microphone
can hear
your facial expressions.
Say this line with a frown.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Um, uh,
"This food is unacceptable."
This food is unacceptable.
Okay, now say it
with, like, a big smile.
This food is unacceptable.
Big frown. Bigger. Bigger.
Frown with your cheeks.
Frown with your cheeks more.
And now say,
"This food looks terrible."
This food looks terrible.
And now, like, a big smile
and feel the difference.
Feel the difference.
Smile with your ears,
like-- like, all--
like, lift it all up,
lift it all up,
and then say,
"This food is terrible."
This food is terrible.
Do you feel the difference?
- Oh, my God.
- Right?
It's, like, opposite.
'Cause you're changing
your tool.
Oh, yeah.
First the ash, now acid rain.
We're done for.
- You're not leaving, are you?
- Diana?
-Sorry. Diana.
-Yeah?
I--
You know, Diana, okay, babe,
I need you to--
have you ever heard the phrase
-"Use your diaphragm"?
-Yes.
Okay, I need you to, like,
take your diaphragm,
wring it out,
and when you say your lines,
like, squeeze
the tension back in,
and say the lines
through your nose
as opposed to just like,
keeping them in your mouth.
-Okay, Okay.
-Okay?
- It feels trapped.
-Let it-- let it out.
-Okay.
- You know?
- Okay. Thank you.
-Yes. Yes.
-Okay, cool, cool.
Is that-- is that okay, Izzy?
I-- I think that maybe,
um, that we should do that
-at the end of the take.
-Good, yeah.
Me giving notes and stuff?
Yeah, I think it would be good
if we did that at-- at the end.
- Yeah.
- We're rolling right now.
Yeah, yeah, that's a good--
that's a good point.
That's a good point,
that's smart.
Maybe you could come and...
- Moment.
- ...sit down again.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you have any notes for me?
Oh, no, no, no.
Devon, you're, like,
you blow everyone away.
You're the best actor here.
All good.
Okay, all right, cool.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Awesome, awesome, so...
I just, um--
What's going on?
- Yeah, hmm.
- I think that maybe, um--
I think that maybe,
we should go again.
We're going again.
Is anybody listening to me?
-Sorry.
And action!
Hot nurse. Hot nurse.
So, that means quiet, everybody.
It's not easy being the leader.
I think I could have maybe
done a little bit
of a better job
communicating with my team.
I need to rally,
and get people back on board.
I'm gonna pull it together.
Everything is great.
People are feeling
so good on set,
really believing
in the material.
I'm not worried.
I'm not worried at all.
Hey, Iz?
Yeah?
In my pants?
I don't understand why I would.
Well, it's about
the genetic structure
- of the leaves.
- No, I get it.
- You know, it's like--
- Can you just-- can you--
But did you put this one
in your pants already?
Um...
how-- how much
do you want me to enjoy this?
Um, well, um...
I think it's--
I think it's an erotic scene.
-You know?
-Sure.
-I don't...
-Right.
- ...do this, and so I--
- Right, right, okay, so--
Like, I just need
a little bit of direction here.
-Breathing is always good.
-Like, teeth...
-bared?
-Mmm.
-Teeth is never...
-I don't know, I just sometime--
-...really that great.
-Okay.
-No teeth.
-Um, maybe, like...
-play, like, cup on that area.
-Okay, yeah, yeah.
Devon, you feeling good?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Okay, from the top.
So that's
your first mark.
Okay.
Did you get all this stuff?
Did you see
the smiley face cake?
Oh, it's fantastic,
and by the way,
thank you so much
for supporting this project.
It's a really exciting film
to be a part of.
Oh, no.
All right, sweet or savory?
Bagel?
-Hey, your tummy talking to you?
-I'm good, man.
You should try one of these,
try one of these,
try one of these.
If you want more,
I'll have more.
I'll have more of this.
I'm not trying to be dense,
but I'm-- I'm totally confused.
- So this plant makes babies?
- Mm-mm, mm-mm.
It allows people to make babies.
Okay, but so when
it makes babies, are they, like,
cute, soft babies
or do they have,
like, hard bark skin?
I didn't prep that, Devon.
You guys, I'm pretty sure
Izzy googled all of this.
Because I was thinking
we could just, you know,
change our lines ourselves
into something
that maybe made sense.
It's all gibberish anyway.
It's come to my attention...
that people in this cast,
um, want to change their lines.
They want to rewrite the script.
They want to go back,
and change things
even though
we're already behind,
because I'm not a machine,
and I can't come up with ideas,
like, constantly.
If they didn't like it
then they
shouldn't have signed on
is how I feel, but maybe...
maybe I'm not built...
for this.
So Geoff, when you put
your hands like this,
it blocks the shot.
Okay, so what-- what--
what would Russ do
with his hands in the scene?
Put them in your pockets.
-Okay, I'll try that.
-Okay.
It's, like,
not usually this bad.
-Um, so--
-Hmm, it's a lot of takes.
So let's just go again,
and action!
Geoff, it took me eight years
to write this,
and I would have specifically
written "gun..."
- if a gun was supposed--
- I just thought maybe,
like, if there's
-like, marauders and--
-Please, let's--
let's start again.
- Sabroso.
- Oh, it's "sabroso."
- Sabroso,
-it's not what I said?
-Sabroso.
- Sabroso.
- Listen to him. Yes.
- Like I said.
Not like you said it.
- Okay, sorry.
- Sabroso.
Sabroso.
- Sabroso, sabroso, sabr--
- Like that.
-Do it more like that.
-It's okay, you got it.
No, it's okay.
Why is he giving my actor notes?
-I have no idea.
-Why is he giving my actor--
-I'll talk to him.
-I thought you talked to him.
I talked to him already.
I'll talk to him again.
I thought he retained it.
I thought-- I didn't know.
I told him not to and he did.
-Why aren't you doing your job?
-I'm so sorry.
-I'm trying to do my job, but--
-I just think that I need--
No, Iz, Iz, I'm sorry.
Izzy, I'm sorry.
I think that I need...
-10 minutes.
-No, no, Izzy,
we don't have 10.
We're already
a whole day behind.
Are you-- did you get--
-Just--
-Izzy.
This is really hard.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Is this stupid?
Where's Izzy?
Uh, she's taking--
taking a fi-- taking a break.
She's just looking at--
she's looking at something else,
-checking out something out.
-Must be nice.
Why are they so bad?
Why are you still filming me?
- You told me to!
- Stop it!
Okay.
Jeez.
You're not leaving, are you?
No, okay.
Hey.
How'd you find me here?
-Beeper.
-Oh, yeah, right.
You gotta move
more product, Geoff.
Listen, I have been
talking it up to everybody
-in this cast and crew...
-Uh-huh.
...but nobody's biting, Jack.
Don't call me by my name.
What did I say?
- Trevor.
- Show me.
Ah...
-You see--
-Open it.
I'll do better.
Oh, my God.
We were counting on you.
We let you into the family.
We're committed to you.
If you are not committed to us,
maybe we need to recali...
-No. No.
-...btate.
They're fucking filming?
- Yeah, it's a movie.
- Oh, my God!
It's a movie set.
Fucking kill you.
- Ow! Ow!
- Oh, are you scared?
I'm scared of your failure.
I just need
to pull this new guy in,
just a little bit,
this guy Felipe?
You saw him,
long hair, kinda cute.
I haven't pulled
the trigger yet, but--
- Ow, ow, ow, ow!
- Stand still.
- No, no.
- God, you're hard to hit.
I think
I can sell them on...
...four...
...twelve units.
I think I can sell them
on 12 units
probably by the end of--
By the end of the--
by the end of the week.
Um, you know what we say.
Supplements make--
- Better actors.
- Better Believe.
Oh, I do.
I know you do.
You need to sell product.
-Okay.
-Okay?
- I'm on it.
- All right then.
Better Believe.
- Good job.
- Thanks.
Better believe.
This is, um...
This is really hard,
and I think that...
I just need somebody to, like...
touch me?
That's it.
Hey, Devon?
Do you-- do you get itchy?
- What?
- Well, you know,
like, my bug bites
are really itchy,
but I know
that, like, asexuals experience,
like, sensation differently.
So I was curious if, like, um...
like, you're affected
by, like, bugs?
Um...
Stefan, your room
is way better than mine.
Do you taste
the hints of pineapple?
Not over these nuts.
How long is this gonna take?
This is ridiculous.
Where are you?
Fuck's sake.
Izzy-- hey, what do you think
about Izzy?
Well...
she's got that attitude.
-Yeah, she's tall.
-Yeah.
I didn't think
she would be that tall.
she'd run that fast.
In a good way.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
And those bangs?
-Those bangs?
-Mm-hmm.
What would he be--
and what
would he be fertilizing exactly?
The double helix breaks down
exactly three minutes
after it's been plucked anyways.
Double helix breaks down
exactly three minutes
after it's been plucked anyways.
Well, yes, well,
the genetics are malleable.
And what would he be
fertilizing exactly?
Oh, Jesus, there--
Broom.
If I was a broom,
where would I be?
I bet Devon has a broom,
I just--
- Oh, my-- oh, my God!
- Oh, my God!
Uh, Josh!
Uh, oh, my God, um, sorry.
- Sorry.
- Gross!
- Get out!
- Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, pop it open for me?
What happened? What happened?
You should see the other guy.
Why, what happened
to the other guy?
Oh.
- Morning, Felipe.
- Good morning.
- Oh, my God, fun straws.
- Thank you.
-What do you have here?
-Hey, hey, hey, hey.
-Good morning.
-Hey, everyone in there?
Uh, yeah, everyone except Diana.
Diana's late?
Yeah, by like,
five or ten minutes.
No.
Something's off.
Diana!
- Diana!
- Okay, there she is.
- Diana-- oh, my God!
- She's there.
- There she is.
- Diana!
She's fine.
Okay, so we found her.
- Izzy! Come on.
- Diana!
- Izzy!
- Diana.
- There you are.
- Let's go, Diana,
let's go!
Hi! Hi!
Welcome back.
Welcome home, let's go!
There you are, hi.
- I'm fine.
- Diana.
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- She's not dead.
- Shocking.
- Why? What's wrong?
- Listen, I just--
- Um, you had
- something to say, right?
- I just wanted to--
It didn't really mean anything.
That's not what you-- okay.
You can go to work now.
What I did wasn't
the right thing to do.
And I want-- you know, you--
I won't do it again.
I won't, but I just, um--
do you still
want to be in the movie?
Yeah, Izzy, I'm in the movie.
I signed a contract.
When I commit to something,
I commit,
and I don't break
my promises, so...
don't worry about me.
I just wanted
to make a good movie.
It's been a really long time
since I've been with anybody.
I'm an idiot, and I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, okay?
I just want to apologize
to everybody
involved in this shoot.
I crossed a line
that was very clearly
drawn in the sand by me,
and, um,
the-- the local government.
This whole project
is to build community
for the greater good,
for the herd--
- We get it.
- As a unit--
-Yes, okay, great.
-Yeah.
My behavior was just to--
was totally unacceptable.
To rectify that,
this morning, I went
to get a test at 6:00 a.m.
I will have the results
in the next couple of days,
and if I have your consent,
it would be my honor to continue
to tell this story
- with you all.
- Love that.
Tell the story.
Everybody cool? Yeah?
Okay, Matt, I just don't want
to rush anybody, okay?
So let's all just take a moment.
Yeah, um, it's--
it's cool with me.
Oh, yeah, shocker.
Okay, we're all gonna die
one way or another, so...
Speak for yourself, Dev.
What
does that even mean?
Great, so it sounds
like we're all agreed, right?
-Let's go.
-Um, uh, Di,
I'm-- I'm sorry.
I didn't-- I didn't hear you.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm-- it's fine. Whatever.
Whatever,
I'll take it. Cool!
Let's get the shot!
- No, no.
- Great.
-Thank you everybody.
-Damnit, Matt,
for the millionth time
I can't shoot if I don't know
what I'm shooting!
You got these in here, right?
We'll--
we'll figure it out, Alec,
don't worry.
You're doing great.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, that's--
that's really nice.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, I--
Maybe not touch me here.
Thank you.
We'll just-- we'll do that--
we'll do that later...
-Yeah, uh--
-...um...
...potentially. Okay.
Okay.
Okay. Yeah.
Yes.
Yes. Yes. Do this.
I think this helps?
Yeah,
it really opens you up,
- just a little more forward.
- Okay.
Oh.
Geoff,
how did you and Izzy meet?
At a gas station
and, uh, she was having
some trouble pumping her gas,
so I helped her
pump it.
-Yo, Matt.
-Yeah, man?
Apparently Izzy's been
helping Geoff pump his gas.
- Out and about.
- Yeah.
-Iz, I'm ready.
-Everybody on your marks please.
Thank you.
-That actually does help.
-Anytime.
Are we ready?
Yeah, yeah, ev--
Guys-- guys,
on your first marks.
I wouldn't make
heads or tails of it anyway.
I guess that's true.
But it tells a bad story, huh?
How could you tell?
I just know things, sometimes.
I wish I could say the same.
But you're the smartest woman--
smartest person we got.
I'm scared.
About what?
Our species.
No, something more.
What?
You tell me.
I really need this to work...
but experiments
don't always pan out,
but I need this to succeed.
We need you to succeed.
It's a lot of pressure.
Do you want to hug?
A hug?
It's sure been a while.
Yeah.
Let's try.
What is happening?
Um,
uh, yeah, let's cut.
- Okay, I think what I--
- I'm so sorry, Diana.
That's okay.
Just-- can you just step back?
Are you okay? Is your--
- Yeah, no, I'm fine.
- Okay.
What I would love
for you to do is,
um, you know,
it's, like, human and intimate.
- Right?
- Mm-hmm.
-Right?
-Yeah, yeah.
I mean...
it-- the script says
"Spread your wings like a bird."
Arms like a bird's wing.
Um, that was poetic.
We're hugging,
though you don't need to squat.
-You can just stand up.
-But she's shorter than me.
So we're hugging like a normal--
normal-- normal people.
Embrace her like somebody
that you love, yeah?
Wait, now, I already love her?
Just hug her
like we just did, normally.
I mean, I respect the script,
but I'll try.
And action!
-I'm sorry.
-Cut!
I can't take this.
I can't, honestly.
Can I-- can I-- can I try
something please?
-Please.
-Yeah?
Um, Geoff.
So good, I'm gonna have you...
take a big step to the left.
Two more steps. Keep going.
Just keep-- keep going until--
There's a light
over here.
Okay. Amazing.
Um, Diana,
just go with me, okay?
One more step over here.
- Won't just be the shot?
- I think it's okay.
-I think-- I think--
-I think it looks great.
- Yeah?
- You sure, Izzy?
I think it's really good.
I think we should shoot.
- Okay.
- And action!
Stefan, clear the shot.
What are the numbers
telling you?
It's not good.
-Was it me?
-No, no.
Pruning it
actually encourages growth.
You know, I thought
you were angry with me.
I was.
Do you forgive me?
Uh, um...
I, uh...
oh. Ah, uh...
this isn't in the script, is it?
Just go with it?
Uh, yeah,
I think give it a shot.
Okay, um...
Are you scared?
A little.
Um,
and cut!
Okay. And cut.
Di, how did you feel about that?
Yeah, I-- I think the work was--
was good in that one.
Okay, great, um, Devon?
Yeah.
That was fine.
Am I-- am I not
in this scene anymore?
I just really don't want,
uh, the point of the film
to be about female sexuality.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm,
I think it works.
It's just, like, the climactic
moment of the movie.
Yeah, and that felt
pretty climactic to me.
-Yeah...
-I mean...
Aren't you--
I mean, aren't-- aren't you...
- What?
- You know, an asexual?
Oh, Jesus.
It's called acting.
Right, yeah.
Okay, I was gonna
practice a little bit more,
but okay,
I guess we can do it now.
I need a second, okay?
Okay, I'm ready.
This was a really
beautiful experience.
I'm so grateful
for the community
that we built in this film.
Everybody came together
in unison,
and together,
we told a really beautiful story
about the world,
and I think
that, uh, we succeeded.
And gratitude
is really the main--
Oh, shooting was fantastic.
I mean, specifically for me.
I think it's because,
thematically, this film hits
on so many things
that are really important to me,
like, in particular,
plant-based healing.
- You really ought to try one.
- What's in it?
Look,
just take one first,
'cause I want to see
how it makes you feel.
Felipe just had one.
He's doing great.
Oh, baby. Hold me.
Hold me with your branches.
Photosynthesize me,
make me green.
Give me your sap.
No, I'm good.
Your loss, man.
Did-- didn't you
just take one of those?
Did I?
- Yes.
- Shit.
So the film, um,
do you think
it's going anywhere?
Do you think
Izzy has a future with it or...
Whoa, the-- the future.
What is your future?
What is my future?
We don't know
the nature of things.
We just know that...
she has a thing.
You know, it's--
it's not everybody's thing,
but it's her thing,
and she's good at that thing.
And so, I think she will be
known for that,
and, uh, that's...
You're gonna edit this, right?
When do you think
that thing's gonna burn out?
The sun?
I think we've got some time.
Cool.
Hey, so are you happy
with the footage?
Yeah? Am I happy?
That's an excellent question.
Is anybody happy?
Hey, Devon, are you happy?
What?
Well, just get that thing
out of my face, okay?
All right,
I'll-- I'll try you later.
Yeah, uh, Izzy's
a fucking genius,
uh, her ideas are killer,
and working with her
has been dope.
Is that what you need?
You didn't--
you didn't sign the waiver.
Hey, Devon,
can-- uh, can I
interview you next, actually?
If you can find me.
- So cool.
- Who does that?
- I don't know.
Um...
- oh, I-- I--
- Go ahead.
You know, I found
parts of myself I didn't--
I knew were there,
but I didn't--
I didn't really--
I didn't really know
like that, you know?
So-- sorry, I'm just--
- Okay, so we're-- I'm done?
- We're good. We got it.
Okay, cool, I'm just gonna--
I gotta go, um--
I gotta-- I lost my cell phone,
so I'm just gonna--
I'm gonna go find it,
and, uh, I'll see you later.
- All right. Cool.
- Thanks so much.
Great-- great
-working with you, Di.
-Yeah.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
God,
where is my cell phone?
It's-- I don't see it. So weird.
Good, I--
I'm-- I'm really scared
she's not gonna come.
No, it's okay.
Does the back of my head
look okay?
I really like this shirt.
It looks good, right?
Oh, my God. Oh, God.
Are you okay?
Okay. I can do this.
We can do this.
Josh.
You're gonna
be there with me, right?
You can be proud of yourself.
Okay, okay, okay.
All right, all right, all right,
we at the movies, y'all.
Who's all in--
Okay, first place.
What's up, daddy?
Hey, good to see.
We're at the movies, y'all,
this is the premiere.
Premiere night,
so you know your boy
had to drip out,
but, uh, where's everybody at?
Let's get in the chat.
Who's all in the chat?
Come on, pour in.
Who's on the chat?
Oh, it's Devon, y'all!
Everybody drop some love
for Devon in the comments.
Some hearts. Devon, what's up?
Let's say hi to everybody.
Matt, there's, like,
two people here.
Oh, my God,
there are people here.
Hi, hi, hi!
- Oh, God. Hi, hi.
- That's the director
Hey, y'all this is
the director, Izzy, right here.
-Hi!
-Izzy, we're live.
-My hair.
-Yeah.
-We're live?
-We're live right now.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, you're getting
everybody, right? Okay, good.
- Hi, Devon.
- Hey.
-Hi.
-How are you?
It's so good to see you. Hi.
Hi.
You came all the way out here.
-Thank you.
-Well, you bought me a flight.
-Hi.
-Hey, did you get my text?
Which one?
Listen, I don't--
-Sorry--
-Good to see you.
-Sorry. Oh, my-- hi!
-Hi.
Geoff, are you--
are you okay?
I'm just kicking the vitamins.
I'm fine, thanks to Felipe.
-Oh.
-Yeah, yeah.
I bought his supply
and we're weaning him off.
Hey, real quick, do you always
dress like a cowboy?
Baby, say hi.
Say hi to the world.
-Hey, hey. I'm Geoff.
-I know who you--
Hey, Alec.
- Hi!
- Hi.
Oh, my God, Diana.
-Hi. Hi.
-Hey, everyone.
- Hi. So good to see you.
- Hi.
-Hi.
-What's up?
Um...
I'm so excited
everyone's here.
I'm so happy you're--
I'm-- I'm so happy you're here.
Totally. Congratulations.
Thank you, I-- I didn't know
you were gonna come.
Yeah, of course.
- Hey, Devon, how's it going?
- Hey.
-Good. How are you?
-I'm so happy to see you.
I didn't-- I didn't know
that you were gonna come in.
-Where are you, uh--
-I'm just gonna give
a little speech, guys.
Nothing crazy,
I just wanted to say
that, um, I'm so happy
that you're here.
It's wonderful to see
all of your beautiful faces.
We did
really strong work together
that I'm very proud of,
and I just really wanted
you all to know that.
I'll stop talking.
Um, but yay!
Good speech, Izzy!
Good speech.
-That was great.
-Thanks.
-You smell really good.
-Oh, thanks.
It's kind of,
like, off the 101
-on, uh--
-That's really close--
The movie's starting now.
What did you do with it?
I continued the experiment.
Are you scared?
A little.
Hey, congrats, Iz.
Oh, thanks.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, you worked hard.
Um...
do you wanna go get a drink?
Yeah.
Like, now?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Okay, uh, just follow me.
Okay.
And-- and sort of, like,
why are, you know-- why--
The mound
is where you came from,
-you were both there together.
-That's my line,
-that my line.
-She's part of the AX,
which used to be ANTIFA.
-Also my line.
-She comes to save you,
-because you live on the mound--
-No, I got--
That's where you had your lab,
but that-- there was
an apocalypse,
-a second apocalypse.
-Yeah.
It's fictional, guys.
It's science fiction.
This party sucks.
See y'all later.
Bye, Matt.
Why did you stop me?
He can talk to Izzy for us.
Absolutely not.
He is a dumb, dumb person.
I actually loved that,
I didn't wanna--
I wasn't gonna break that.
He is a dumb, dumb person.
It's not funny. It's not funny.
He's a dumb, dumb person.
She can't do it.
There she goes.
Izzy.
Wait, where did Izzy go?
Is she crying?
I think she's crying.
Oh, God.
- Like, I could--
- Did somebody call me?
I think we need
Geoff's voice.
No, hang on.
I'm just trying to--
I'm confused,
is somebody calling me
- or were you acting?
- I was acting.
-No, she was acting.
-I thought it was serious.