I have a confession to make.
I'm not the person
you think I am.
I murdered my brother.
♪ ♪
You'll be back.
(laughs) John.
(both sigh)
Have fun in camp?
No.
Well, you look good.
Well-fed.
You need to wash your hair.
Listen, this guy inside
told me about this land deal
-in Boca Raton.
-Boca Raton?
-You know, Florida.
-Uh-huh.
It's sweet.
It's a huge return.
-Yeah, what's the angle?
-No, no, no angle.
It's an investment.
It's legit.
Legit?
Yeah, get us
out of this dump, man.
We'll live on a beach.
Forget about it.
I got a job all ready to go.
It's for a million.
Sounds dangerous.
This is huge, John.
Harry and I roped in these two
stock exchange trader losers.
They're desperate.
But we need you
to set it up today.
-Harry? Are you kidding me?
-Harry's okay.
Harry talks.
ROME:
Not anymore.
What's the matter with you?
Hey, you want to make an omelet,
you got to break some eggs.
I'm not doing it.
I'm not doing
any more time for you.
Man.
Camp really got to you,
huh, John?
Rome, it's not camp,
it's prison.
And now you're out,
so what's the big deal?
You came to pick me up from jail
with a body in the trunk.
Yes, I did.
Now get in the car.
What do you got,
maybe 50 bucks in your pocket?
What's it gonna get you?
A bus ticket to Florida?
And once you get there,
what kind of job
you gonna get with
your record, huh?
And what are you offering?
I'm offering you
a half a million dollars.
It's a lot of Ben Franklins.
John, you want to go legit?
It's gonna take
a couple of bucks.
Now get in the car.
One more. That's it.
ROME:
Here's the bait, 50 Gs.
Where'd you get this?
Somonoff.
You went to the Russian mob?
It's a loan for a week.
Hey, we all set?
Yeah.
Good. Now let's grab some lunch.
I'll make you a spinach soufflé.
It's good to have you back, kid.
(engine starts)
♪ ♪
♪ Lord God Almighty,
let me tell the news ♪
♪ My head got wet
in midnight dew ♪
♪ Great God, I been down
on my bended knees ♪
♪ Talking to a man
from Galilee ♪
♪ Michael spoke
and he sound so sweet ♪
♪ I thought I heard
the shuffle of angels' feet ♪
♪ He put one hand
upon my head ♪
♪ Great God Almighty,
let me tell you what he said ♪
♪ Go tell that lonesome liar ♪
♪ Go tell that midnight rider ♪
♪ Tell the gamblin',
the ramblin' backslider ♪
♪ Tell them God Almighty
gonna cut 'em down ♪
♪ You might run on
for a long time ♪
♪ Run on, duckin' and dodgin' ♪
♪ Run on, children,
for a long time ♪
♪ Let me tell you, God Almighty
gonna cut you down ♪
♪ You might throw your rock,
hide your hand ♪
♪ Work in the dark
with your fellow man ♪
♪ Sure as God made you
rich and poor ♪
♪ You're gonna reap
just what you sow ♪
♪ You might run on
for a long time ♪
♪ Run on, duckin' and dodgin' ♪
♪ Run on, children,
for a long time ♪
♪ Let me tell you, God Almighty
gonna cut you down ♪
♪ You might ♪
♪ Run ♪
♪ I did the right thing ♪
♪ Run... ♪
It's getting cold.
Yeah, that's because
it's, uh, it's gonna rain.
-It's not gonna rain.
-It's gonna rain.
It's not gonna rain.
This-this is
what I'm talking about.
You're just, you're just--
you're rude.
I can't agree with you
all the time.
What's the matter with you?
Oh, thank you.
I'm telling you.
Don't shake your head.
You do this all the time.
-Can I get a bag of chips?
-Yeah, sure.
Get away.
♪ Go tell that lonesome liar ♪
♪ Go tell that
midnight rider... ♪
Great.
You know, what?
Can I get a ten for ten ones?
Sure, I can always do singles.
Get out.
The matter with you?
Hey, stupid.
There's a ten in here.
Oh, so what is that, 19 then?
Here's one more.
You just give me a 20.
Ow.
Thanks. Take it easy, guys.
♪ You might run on
for a long time... ♪
(laughing)
What? What?
You just got screwed
out of ten dollars, beanbag.
-Hey!
-Hey.
♪ You might run on
for a long time ♪
♪ Run on, duckin' and dodgin' ♪
♪ Run on, children,
for a long time ♪
♪ Let me tell you, God Almighty
gonna cut you down ♪
♪ You might run on
for a long time ♪
♪ Run on, duckin' and dodgin' ♪
♪ Run on, children,
for a long time ♪
♪ Let me tell you, God Almighty
gonna cut you down ♪
♪ You might run on
for a long time. ♪
Sounds to me like you guys
are in a lot of trouble here.
So can you help us, then?
Counterfeiting's
a federal crime.
People go to jail for that.
(conversing in Japanese)
(laughs):
Oh, I get it. I get it.
Okay, so it's-it's like
with hookers, right?
So we got to say it.
Right.
We want to pay you
one million dollars
for 20 million
in counterfeit currency.
Oh, yeah,
and we need it by Friday.
Okay.
Now let me hear him say it.
H-He's Japanese.
I got that.
He doesn't speak English.
Okay.
One of these stacks is $25,000
in official U.S. currency.
The other was printed by
my partner this morning.
(laughs) Unbelievable.
-(speaks Japanese)
-Yeah.
So how quickly can we do this?
-(shouts)
-We do it as soon as
I'm sure about Mr. Roboto here.
-(shouts in Japanese)
-Talk to me in English.
Let me hear you say
you're a cop.
-Ho-Ho-Ho-Hold on!
-Come on, show me your badge!
Look, he's not a cop, I swear.
You, shut up.
You, talk to me in English
or you lose your head.
You want to put me in jail?
(shouting in Japanese)
English! You understand me?!
English!
Look, he's not a cop.
You got to believe me, man.
I mean, I'm his accountant.
He's an embezzler, a tax evader.
(both speaking Japanese)
(jet engine whooshing)
-He's a coke addict, man!
-English!
(shouts)
♪ Take me out to the ballpark ♪
♪ Take me out to the game ♪
♪ Buy me some peanuts ♪
♪ Cracker Jack. ♪
Okay.
We're okay.
I'm sorry.
I just had to be sure.
(knife clatters)
We're cool.
Tell him we're cool!
(speaking Japanese)
(panting)
Now let's do this.
-ROME (over phone): Is it done?
-JOHN: Yeah.
-Where are you?
-I'm at the park by the statue.
-Rome, I got a bad feeling
about this.
-Why? What happened?
Nothing, I just--
I got a bad feeling.
What are you talking about?
This is Rome.
I always take care of you.
-Yeah.
-(siren wails in distance)
-I know.
-Don't move.
I'll be there in five minutes.
♪ ♪
(phone dialing)
Hi. Steve Bergen, please.
Hey, Steve.
Uh, My name is John Moray.
A friend of mine
gave me your number,
said that you had some kind of a
real estate opportunity set up?
Yeah, Boca Raton.
What would it take
for me to get in on that?
Yeah? Well, how about 50,000?
Uh, I'm not in Florida
right now.
Can't I just wire you
the deposit?
Okay, well,
hold me a spot, then.
All right,
I-I'll be there on Wednesday.
Okay, Tuesday. Great.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
SUNNY:
John!
-(quietly): Sunny.
-Hey.
Not now.
When did you get out?
Go away.
-Hey, are you gonna go
to that party tonight?
-No.
Perfect. Here we go.
Like my new coat?
Don't I look like a flapper?
Yeah. Love it.
Where are we going?
Sunny, what did
I just say to you?
I'll catch up with you later.
Come on, let me in.
No, I'm not letting you in.
-(car door opens)
-It was open.
This is nice-ish.
There's no smoking in my car.
Sunny...
What's in here?
-Whose money is that?
-(ignition sputtering)
Who do you think?
SUNNY:
Are you crazy?
-John, he'll kill you.
-Come on.
Come on.
-Come on!
-John, you have
to give that money back.
Sunny, shut up!
(engine whirs)
(tires screech)
Hello.
(laughs)
Busted.
What are you so happy about, TJ?
Your girlfriend
drop the charges?
Yo, why don't you
say something else, punk?
I'll tell you what.
I'll just get out
-and we'll talk about it.
-(thudding)
Hey! Yo, watch the car,
white boy!
-Yo! Hey, hey!
-Sorry, man, I
can't seem to get out of here.
(tires screech)
Go.
Yo, what's wrong with you, man?
That's goldenrod 27.
They don't make
that color no more, man. Hmm?
-Go away, TJ.
-Yeah, go make me a taco.
Are you kidding me,
with this guy?
Rome, I waited at the park
for, like, a half an hour.
(panting)
The whole thing's set up.
Tuesday at 3:00,
I meet him outside the hotel,
and I bring him
by the warehouse.
Be like candy from a baby,
just like you said.
Mm-hmm.
And here's your money.
Safe and sound.
Rome...
-Come on.
-You want me dead?
What are you doing?
You want me dead?
Rome...
Be a man.
-Do it yourself.
-Come on.
Hey, you were gonna
take that money,
and let the Russians
finish me off.
I raised you.
I saved your life.
At least have the decency to put
the bullet in me yourself.
Come on, here. Do it.
Finish me off.
Eh, you're pathetic.
I'll do the job, Rome.
No, you won't.
I can't trust you anymore.
But I'll tell you
what you will do.
You're gonna pay Somonoff back
his interest,
and you're gonna make up
for that easy million
that you just cost me.
You're not working
with me now, kid.
You're working for me.
Back on the streets.
You're gonna work this off if
it takes the rest of your life.
Or the rest of yours.
(gun clicks)
(clicking)
(chuckles)
Oops.
Or you can go to jail.
Because now I have the gun
that you used to kill Harry,
with your fingerprints
all over it.
(sniffs)
Okay, well, you win.
Let me just ask you one thing.
-(grunts)
- ♪ Lift me up ♪
♪ From your shallows ♪
♪ I am stumbled ♪
♪ In a lonely grave ♪
-(groans)
-♪ Lift me up ♪
♪ From your shallows ♪
♪ I am destined to ♪
♪ Live ashamed ♪
♪ I've been sold out ♪
♪ By my best friend ♪
♪ I've been knocked down ♪
♪ And thrown away ♪
♪ I've been sold out ♪
♪ And mistreated ♪
♪ I've ignited a dying flame ♪
♪ I'm a sinner ♪
♪ A believer ♪
♪ I'm a cynic in a ♪
♪ Blinding rage ♪
♪ A beginner ♪
-(exhales)
-♪ In the middle ♪
(tires screeching)
(horn blaring)
(grunts)
(panting)
(quietly):
No. No.
(distorted chatter)
(tires screeching)
You okay?
Hey, what are you doing?
(tires screeching)
-That's my car!
-Go!
♪ ♪
(tires screeching)
(grunting)
(dialing)
Yeah, I need an address for, um,
I think it's Lawndale,
for Jeremiah Davis.
It's upstate somewhere.
Yeah. Wait.
Go ahead.
Yo, he's dying.
We got him.
(engine grinding)
Aw, man!
I'd like to spend some more time
this morning
taking an even closer look
at the first chapter of Matthew.
When examined
carefully, this passage
gives us a greater comprehension
of the genealogy of Christ.
For example, there were
14 generations from David
to the deportation to Babylon,
then 14 more generations
till the time of Christ.
-(snoring)
-That's 28 generations
-from David...
-(police radio chatter)
My bad. My bad.
I'm-I'm sorry.
Um, keep going, keep going.
That's 28 generations
from David to Jesus,
yet we say Jesus was
the son of David.
So we need to look more closely
at those 28 generations.
(snores)
SAM: It definitely shows
that you know the Bible.
It's just... very long.
-It's as long as it should be.
-I know. I know.
It's just a lot of detail
to take in all at once.
Sam, that's the whole point.
The detail is what makes
the passage so relevant.
It's not the passage.
It's just-- if you could
deliver it with a little...
-The sermon sucked, brother.
-(Sam sighs)
Very constructive, thanks.
Come on, J, wake me up, man.
Move me.
That's what you up there for.
I wouldn't have to
wake you up if you'd stop
taking double shifts
all the time.
Come on, don't do that.
This ain't about me.
Look, I was sleeping
because you were boring.
Oh, all right, all right.
Why bother asking my opinion
if you don't want to hear
what I've got to say?
I didn't ask your opinion.
I didn't.
Look... I think you're gonna be
a great preacher.
Once you get out of that head
of yours and let God move you.
You're the vehicle
He uses to touch people.
Trust Him.
Get out of the way.
Stop being so Jeremiah
about everything.
-Amen.
-Okay?
(sighs) O-Okay. Okay.
-I'm out. I'm out.
-(Sam chuckles)
I'm out of my head.
I'm headed back to the station.
I'll see you later, Sam.
Bye, Tex.
Mm.
Hey, can I borrow
your house keys?
-Sorry, I lost mine again.
-I'll catch you at home.
Thanks.
I was thinking
that we could talk...
One-one second.
(sighs)
♪ We're gonna make you move
on the dance floor ♪
-(turns up volume)
-♪ We're gonna
make you groove ♪
♪ On the dance floor ♪
♪ Gonna keep it live,
gonna make it hot ♪
-(turns down volume)
-♪ Gonna make you work ♪
♪ Gonna rock the spot,
we're gonna make you move ♪
-(turns up volume)
-♪ On the dance floor ♪
♪ We're gonna make you groove ♪
♪ On the dance floor,
gonna keep it live ♪
♪ Gonna make it hot,
gonna make you work ♪
♪ Gonna rock the spot,
we're gonna make you move... ♪
-Okay, okay, okay.
-(music stops)
Oh. I didn't know you were here.
I thought we were gonna
talk about this tomorrow.
I want to talk
about it tonight.
Okay. We'll talk
♪ ♪
(engine starts)
SAM:
It's an amazing campus.
Right in the center
of the art community.
I'd get my own studio.
I only teach
two classes a week,
and-and the rest of the time
is just for me to paint.
♪ Turn Your eyes
from on this way ♪
♪ I have proved to live
a dastardly day ♪
♪ I hid my face from... ♪
Don't you dare.
Marry me.
♪ Sing of Your glory... ♪
What are you doing?
I know it's a little
ahead of schedule,
but I'm trying
to be spontaneous.
What do you say?
♪ Shine, show me grace ♪
♪ A little more
than I can give ♪
than I deserve ♪
♪ Unearth this holiness
I can't earn ♪
♪ It's a little more
than I can give ♪
♪ A little more
than I deserve... ♪
Sam... I love you.
I want to marry you.
This is the worst thing
that you've ever done.
I thought you wanted this.
♪ Set me free still ♪
♪ What I do
I don't want to do... ♪
Do you... have any idea
how cheated I feel?
I don't understand.
You've been saying for years
you want to get married.
I-I thought this would
fix everything.
This isn't about
marriage, Jeremiah.
This is about Chicago
not fitting into your plans.
Whoa, wait a minute.
There are plans.
And the only reason
you're even considering Chicago
is because
I haven't proposed yet.
No, I'm considering it
because it's something
that I have always wanted to do.
But this just
came out of nowhere, Sam.
I'm about to be ordained.
Well, just because
you didn't plan for it
doesn't mean that
I shouldn't do it.
Everything I have worked for
leads up to this month,
and now you want me
to put it all on hold
and run off to Chicago?
I'm not asking you to go.
If you would have talked to me
about this at least once,
you would have known that.
So you're gonna go alone?
Yes.
Well, I don't see
how that's gonna work,
because that pushes back
being able
to buy a house
by at least 18 months.
(whispers):
I'm gonna scream.
♪ Oh, it's a... ♪
When did you get like this?
-Sam, come on, all right?
-No, it-it just...
-Just-- no, no, calm down.
-No, you just...
poisoned everything,
Jeremiah, all at once.
Chicago,
the proposal, everything.
So you're saying no?
♪ Yeah, yeah... ♪
I...
I'm not saying anything.
I'm gonna try to forget
that this even happened.
You got to be kidding me.
You're going for your 7:00 run?
What?
Sounds to me like
we're done here.
♪ ♪
(engine sputtering)
Yo, that's the car.
That's the car!
Okay.
(panting)
Hey, brother. Surprise.
You got 50 grand I can borrow?
Hello?
(tires screech)
-Nice try.
-What?
Ooh. (laughs)
(tires screech)
Unbelievable.
♪ ♪
Hello?
Look at me.
I'm a world traveler.
So, I got a bachelor's degree
and a master's degree.
But where do I keep my money?
Figures.
♪ ♪
No way. Jackpot.
-(knocking on door)
-TEX: Hello?
Come on, man, open up.
The door's locked.
(knocking)
Open up!
-(knocking)
-I know you in there.
-I saw you in the window!
-You got to be kidding me.
Stop screwing around.
You got my keys, remember?
Open the door, J.
J!
Freeze!
(panting) Whoa.
Whoa, I live here.
This is my place.
(exhales)
Jeremiah.
-Yeah.
-What are you doing, man?
I've been pounding
on the door for five minutes.
Hey, you busted out a window.
Sorry. You gave me
a heart attack, man.
I thought you were breaking in.
What? I knock on the door
and you jump out the window?
What's the matter with you, man?
I wasn't expecting you.
That's the stupidest thing
I've ever heard.
Yeah, I just-- I freaked out.
Yeah, well... good thing
you, uh, saved the candlesticks.
You in for the night?
No, I told you.
Picked up a shift.
Just grabbing a sandwich.
Brought your keys. (sniffs)
Well, can I get mine back?
-Um...
-You lost mine, too.
-I'll look around.
-Yeah.
Where's Sam? Thought you were
hanging out tonight?
Yeah. He couldn't make it.
-Who couldn't make it?
-Sam.
Samantha. Your girlfriend.
Yeah, she couldn't make it.
You sure you didn't hit your
head diving out that window?
(laughs)
Sam's here.
(door closes)
-(knocking on door)
-Hold on.
-(knocking)
-Come in.
Sam.
I need an answer.
Okay.
If I decide to go--
which I might--
are you gonna be able
to fit that into your plan?
Because if you can,
we need to talk about it,
and if you can't,
we need to talk about that.
I don't want to talk.
Great.
Sam, I know you're upset,
and I'm sorry...
but it's not gonna
do either of us any good
to make a decision
in this state.
I think we should just clear our
heads for a few days, you know?
Step back a little.
You look weird.
Yeah?
You look great.
Let me take you out
tomorrow night.
We'll have fun.
(sighs) Tomorrow?
You can't tomorrow. It's Sunday.
You have your study group.
Mm, doesn't matter.
I'll cancel it.
I just want to spend
some time with you.
Then we'll deal with this,
I promise.
Come on.
We'll paint the town red.
(laughs)
"Paint the town red"?
Just say yes.
O-Okay.
Two days.
Good. I'll walk you out.
Where's your brother?
(panting) What?
My brother's dead.
I'm onto you, Jeremiah Davis.
No scorpion.
(engine starts)
Finally.
(door opens, closes)
Hola.
-Great.
-I win.
That's the difference
between you and me, TJ.
You think we're in competition.
I just think you're an idiot.
And I think
it's gonna be a holiday
watching Rome bust you up.
Hmm, I don't think
I ever realized till now
just how ugly you are.
Look at that. I got your gun.
Like, two seconds ago,
you was all tough,
and you was, like,
swinging around,
and now, look, here I am,
I'm holding it.
You suck at this, TJ.
I can't believe
you're not dead yet.
-My brother's alive?
-Temporarily.
That's impossible.
(sighs)
How do you fit into this?
-Does Rome know I'm here?
-I'm not saying nothing, man.
(gasps) Nah, nah.
He, uh, he found
your brother's address,
-so he sent me here to check.
-So nobody else knows I'm here?
Okay.
(sighs)
Now, where is my money?
-I-I don't know.
-(door opens, closes)
I don't know anything.
No luck, boss. He slipped town.
Here's what you're gonna do.
You're gonna go back
and you're gonna tell Rome
that you looked around
but you didn't find me.
You give me some of the 50 Gs
and I'll do it.
TJ, the guy who can
keep his hands on the gun
makes the rules.
Think about it this way.
If I go now,
I'm out of your life for good
and Rome never needs
to hear how you paid
for your little
yellow pickup truck.
It's not a pickup,
it's an El Camino.
And how did you
pay for it again?
That's right.
You ripped off Rome.
I've been meaning
to tell him about that.
So unless you want
to start taking the bus
with two broken ankles,
I suggest you go tell Rome
I slipped town.
What do you mean, slipped town?
I mean he slipped town,
like, he's gone.
Good, good, good, good,
good, good, good, good.
He slipped town
with my 50,000.
(grunts)
(groans)
(panting)
Yo, this is messed up.
It's your brother.
Don't you understand
Rome will kill him?
What my brother gets,
he deserves.
Now, get off my yard.
Fingerprints on this gun
will put your brother away
for the rest of his life.
Now, I can either
give it to the police,
or I can chuck it in the river.
It's your choice.
I know what you did on
the bridge that night, preacher.
Must be a real shock to find out
your brother's still alive,
but I'm gonna give you a chance
to make things right.
Now... now, you could
either stay and do this
or you can get up and walk out
and abandon him again.
But you decide right now.
What do I have to do?
There, see, it is true.
All roads lead to Rome.
(scissors cutting)
♪ ♪
J! Hey, what are you doing, man?
Get up.
We got to leave in ten minutes,
man. Rise and shine.
Leave for what?
ALL:
♪ A... ♪
♪ ...men. ♪
(quiet coughing)
You'll be very pleased to hear
that, for this morning's sermon,
-I will not be speaking.
-(congregation laughs)
Instead, a certain very busy
deacon who we all know
will be giving
his first official sermon
entitled
"The Genealogy of Christ."
Jeremiah?
-Good luck.
-(congregation murmuring)
Go on up there. Go on.
(murmuring stops)
WOMAN 1:
Is he okay?
WOMAN 2:
Oh, he'll be fine.
Shh, shh, shh.
Um...
The, uh...
genealo... (clears throat)
genealogy of...
Christ.
(man clears throat)
I was gonna talk about that,
but instead,
let's just talk about...
-money.
-(congregation murmurs)
Look around you.
We all got a lot of money.
MAN:
We do?
Can I get an amen?
(man coughing quietly)
But not everyone
is as fortunate as we are.
I mean, there are people
out there right now
who need money,
and I believe...
...I believe it is a sin
for us to turn our backs
on them.
I'm-I'm talking about
good people here.
I'm talking about good people
who may not have
a lot of choices
'cause they're living
on the streets,
and it is hard to see
the Almighty
when your stomach is empty.
-Amen?
-MAN: Amen.
Thank you.
Now, my brother and I,
we were raised on the streets.
We used to play
in burned-out buildings.
I was fortunate enough
to get out,
but my brother wasn't so lucky.
J's got a brother?
Doesn't like to talk about it.
And there are other kids
out there right now
who will fall
into the same cycle
-of crime and violence.
-(congregation murmuring)
These kids are falling
through the cracks.
Even now, as we sit here,
they have no food, no money,
and, worst of all,
they have no hope.
We got to do
something about this.
We got to do something
about this right now.
We need to put our money
where our mouths are.
So I suggest that
this morning's collection
go towards starting
an outreach program
for the welfare
of juvenile offenders.
What do you say? Huh?
Don't you think
that God would like that?
-Can I hear an amen?
-CONGREGATION: Amen.
Thank you.
Can I hear another amen?
-ALL: Amen!
-Amen!
Glory be to the God Almighty!
Hallelujah!
Hallelujah! I feel the spirit
of God coming on through me.
Praise you, Jesus!
Praise you, Jesus! Hallelujah!
Hallelujah!
I volunteer to serve
as treasurer.
(excited shouting)
♪ Hallelujah. ♪
(timer ticking)
I don't get it.
Pay attention.
I just gave you a 20.
Add that to your ten.
Now you're up ten.
-Yeah, but you're just giving...
-What is wrong with you?
This is simple. I don't have
time for you not to get this.
What does this have to do
with counterfeiting?
Basics.
You expect me to let you
pull a million-dollar job
when you can't even scam a guy
for ten bucks?
Watch your step, darling.
Woo, woo, woo. Watch, watch.
Hey, look what I found
at John's place, boss.
-Any money?
-No, no money.
Don't touch me.
(mocking):
"Don't touch me." (chuckles)
I think she likes you, TJ.
(Rome chuckles)
John. John! Stop it!
Are you sure you don't know
about my money?
What are you gonna do?
What am I gonna do?
(chopping rapidly)
(laughs)
Rome, who's that girl in there?
-Answer my question.
-I told you.
I don't know anything about it.
♪ ♪
Rome, I don't know anything.
(sniffs)
Well... if you're sure.
Come on, Rome.
-(timer buzzes)
-Oh, Sunny.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
How much you need?
Rome, I'll get you the money.
(chuckles)
Have you got $50,000?
-In the bank.
-Well!
Weren't you the lucky one?
Found yourself
a well-fixed family, huh?
-Something like that.
-Mm-hmm, good.
Good, good, good.
Tomorrow, we'll go by the bank
and we'll find out.
In the meantime, let's eat.
What'd you do to the bowls?
I was looking for your keys.
There's glass
all over the kitchen, J.
Yeah, I didn't find them.
Look at this.
4,800 bucks.
With the money from
the old folks' home
and the potluck dinner,
I should be able
to double that by Tuesday.
Juvenile offenders, huh?
-Where'd you get that from?
-Well, what can I say?
I was inspired.
Sounded more like a sales pitch
than a sermon, if you ask me.
All I'm saying is that
when kids get in trouble,
we should figure out
something to do with them
besides throwing them in jail.
I totally disagree.
I think those kids need jail.
Punishment that
matches your crime.
You really love
being a cop, don't you?
-Just lock them all up.
-What are you talking about?
I'm not trying to hurt kids.
I'm trying to save them.
Look, if I hadn't have
done that time,
I wouldn't be here today,
I guarantee it.
I was robbing people, J.
Now, you may not know
anything about it,
but it-it takes
something out of you.
Stealing what someone else
worked hard for.
It was killing me.
But Jesus... saved my life.
By letting me go to jail,
He gave me a second chance.
I guess I just don't believe
in throwing people away.
You're not hearing me, J.
You don't think
there's any situation
where a kid should
just get a break
instead of getting locked up?
No. Not if he committed a crime.
Whatever.
-J, what's going on with you?
-Nothing.
-You all right?
-I'm fine.
-Come on, J, just talk to me.
-I'm fine. Back off.
EMERIL LAGASSE:
And to kick it up maybe
a notch or two,
I got a jalapeño pepper.
-(TV audience exclaiming)
-Ah, yeah, yeah.
Put that right in there to...
-JEREMIAH: I have a question.
-Yeah?
Why don't you just counterfeit
the money yourself?
I'm not a counterfeiter.
Then I'm confused again.
Okay, listen to me.
A good con
is like a gourmet meal.
Starts with the menu.
The rope-- that's you--
shows the marks-- that's them--
two stacks of money.
Tells them one's real
and one's phony.
The beauty is
they're both real.
Now they're hungry.
They think we are the greatest
counterfeiters in the world.
John already did that,
but then he bailed.
So pay attention.
Here's where you come in.
We use your money
to spread out over blank paper.
Then we pile it up.
Now 50,000 becomes 20 million.
Tuesday at 3:00,
you pick up the marks
at the Imperial Hotel.
Be polite.
Then you bring them
back here to me.
♪ ♪
And then you'll introduce me
as the master counterfeiter.
Mr. Takashi
is a big fan of your work.
Well, let's get down
to business.
(chuckles)
Here's the appetizer.
See, this is the first trick.
It's the only full stack
in the pile.
Choose the wrong one,
and you're the loser.
Now he believes
every stack in this pile
is just like the one
in his hand,
unless we screw it up.
So do not screw it up.
Well, it looks like we each
have some counting to do,
so if Mr. Takashi
would be so kind.
Oh, yeah-yeah-yeah,
right, right.
(speaking Japanese)
Love that sound.
This is the main course.
This way, gentlemen.
From here on out,
it's blocking.
It's all about separating
them from their cash.
You get between them and
their case and you stay there.
You know what it takes
to get a guy to walk away
from a million dollars?
20 million dollars.
Remember, the secret
to serving a really good meal
is to give them something
they do not expect.
Stop!
There's too much money in here.
What, are you
going behind my back?
Don't worry about it.
Are you marking another price
for yourself?
-We have an arrangement.
-Forget it. Deal's off.
No, this is my deal.
It's my money.
I don't need you anymore,
old man.
And that's... when you shoot me.
-And I don't mean one shot.
-(clicking)
You empty that thing into me.
(TJ laughs)
ROME: Look at them. They're not
thinking about money anymore.
They're thinking about bullets.
(siren wailing)
Now, they got a choice.
They can either go
for their money and get shot...
-Police! Freeze!
-...stay and get caught...
-Kneel down!
-...or cut their losses
-and run for it.
-(speaking Japanese)
You stay where you are.
(shouting in Japanese)
They're gone. (laughs)
Let me feel it.
I want to feel it.
-Whoo! Ooh, it's heavy.
-(both laugh)
-He did it!
-(laughs)
-That guy was like... (whoops)
-(whoops)
(laughs)
ROME:
And that's the dessert.
-I don't know.
-Don't know what?
Well, this may surprise you,
but in seminary,
they don't teach about
guns and handcuffs.
Trust me, kid,
I'll show you everything.
-You'll do fine.
-(sighs)
Have some faith in yourself.
-Sunny.
-(taps plate)
Eat your dinner.
Okay, now let me hear it again.
Julie?
Please give money
to help inner-city kids.
Okay, good.
Now, all of you, show me
your saddest faces.
Come on! Sadder!
This is important.
Okay, good.
Now, hit the streets.
Take no prisoners.
Not bad, except for the drop.
Now, remember, keep it natural.
Don't favor that side.
No one should know
you're gonna pull a gun.
But it's slipping.
Then do it again,
and again a million times.
You know, I could really
make you into something.
Let me ask you something,
preacher.
You think people got free will?
I believe people
have the freedom
to make their own decisions.
But God has a plan, right?
Absolutely. He has a plan
for everyone's life.
-Even yours, Rome.
-Mm-hmm.
All right, keep that going.
So this crime
you're about to commit--
that's part of God's plan
for your life?
No, you're making me do this.
Oh, so you're saying
I have power over God.
That's not what I'm saying.
You're twisting my words.
I'm saying I'm doing this
to help my brother,
and that's a good thing.
Well, you can't just
ignore the bad thing.
I mean, you're stealing
from people here.
I'm pretty sure that's a sin.
If you'd just give me the gun
with the fingerprints on it,
I wouldn't have to do this.
You don't have to do this.
I mean, if you're so certain
that God has this good plan...
Are you trying
to talk me out of this?
Nope, never.
I'm just trying to figure out
what you're doing here.
You seem to think it's right
to steal from the innocent
just so your criminal brother
doesn't get the justice
he deserves.
Yes. He's my brother.
So what you're saying is
it is better
to take care
of things yourself...
even if it means
going against God.
-No.
-'Cause God's got
-this big plan, right?
-Yes.
And was it God's plan that
I saved your brother's life?
What?
That I dragged him from
the river and took him in?
Was it God's idea... for you
to leave him there to die?
No, I don't, I don't know!
You don't know?
You don't know what's right,
and you don't know what's wrong.
So why are you here?
I'm here to save
my brother, that's it.
Exactly.
You're here to save
your brother's life,
so you can just forget
everything else.
Come on, do it again.
Do it again.
11,415 bucks.
Thanks, God.
Yeah, I was talking
to Steve Bergen
about a $50,000 investment
for the Boca Raton deal.
I wanted to find out if I could
get in on that for just ten.
All right,
can you page him, then?
-Sure.
-(knocking on door)
Yeah-- Hey, have him
ask for Jeremiah.
(door opens, closes)
Wow.
(chuckles)
You ready for dinner?
Yeah. Sure.
Fugazi's or the Lampliter?
Let's try something different.
You decide.
Really?
Yeah. Anything you want.
My treat.
Okay. (chuckles)
Should-should I get dressed up?
Yeah.
♪ I'm gonna dance ♪
♪ Oh, oh, I'm gonna dance ♪
♪ I'm gonna dance, baby... ♪
You sure it's not too loud?
Nah, it's great.
-Oops!
-You hungry?
Oh, I'm starving.
-I'll get us some food.
-(laughs)
♪ And fly so high ♪
♪ So high ♪
(lively chatter)
♪ Don't be afraid ♪
♪ To get on the floor
and move... ♪
-Excuse me. Hi.
Ooh.
(chuckles)
-I'm Jeremiah Davis.
-Oh.
Can I offer you
a veggie burger with no cheese,
no pickles, no onions
and light on the mayo?
Mmm. What are you having?
Well, um, chili dog
with jalapeños.
Actually, that sounds better.
(chuckles)
(laughs):
Oh.
Mmm.
♪ You have a song ♪
♪ That is playing to... ♪
-So... what's your name?
-(chuckles)
(laughs)
You're in a fun mood tonight.
No... really.
What's your name?
♪ You have a dream ♪
♪ That the world
wants you to share... ♪
I'm Samantha Evans.
It's nice to meet you.
Let me ask you something.
Okay. What?
If you could live anywhere,
where would it be?
That is a stupid question.
-Hey, I want to know.
-Why?
'Cause I've been answering
your questions all night.
Scotland.
Scotland, really?
Why Scotland?
That's where
my real dad is from.
I always wanted to go there.
I didn't know that.
Find a quiet little town
close to the water.
Raise some kids.
Maybe open up a pub.
Stay up late nights
talking to friends.
What?
What's wrong?
I just...
I had so much fun tonight.
♪ ♪
This really needed to happen.
I love you. So much.
♪ I think about it
all the time ♪
♪ Don't know what to say ♪
♪ When the room is cold
and empty ♪
♪ And you look at me
that way... ♪
JOHN:
Hey, Steve, uh...
this is John Moray again.
I'm gonna have to pass
on that land deal for now.
Something unexpected came up.
It's personal.
Thanks.
♪ I broke the rules ♪
♪ One time
when I was young... ♪
You okay?
Yeah.
Wonder where John is.
He's probably on
a plane somewhere.
What's his last name now?
-Moray.
-Really?
Yeah, why?
What does that mean?
It's a town in Scotland
where our father was born.
John Moray.
Why hasn't he ever contacted me?
He hates you.
What happened with you two?
We spent most of our childhood
in this awful halfway house.
We used to sneak out
in the middle of the nights.
There was this little
empty space under the stairwell
where we'd get a flashlight,
and we'd stay there for hours,
telling each other stories
about getting out into the world
and what we wanted to do.
John always wanted
to be a magician.
(chuckles)
When we were 14,
we got moved to this
really bad neighborhood.
And this gang of kids
were chasing us.
And, uh,
and we're trying to hide
under this old metal bridge.
But they got John, and they
were beating him up pretty bad.
YOUNG JOHN (distant):
Jeremiah!
JEREMIAH:
And he kept...
he kept calling my name,
-Jeremiah!
-and I didn't do anything.
I just stayed down, watching.
And they struggled, and he fell
off the side of the bridge
and he broke right
through the ice.
And I just stood there.
Why didn't you help him?
(voice breaking):
I don't know.
I was so scared.
I didn't even tell anyone.
By the time the police
started looking,
they said it was too late.
And this is his life now.
♪ ♪
♪ Living the good life ♪
♪ Not a care in the world ♪
♪ Feeling the sunshine ♪
MAN:
Good morning.
♪ Such a good, good life ♪
Morning.
♪ Yeah, living
the good life... ♪
♪ If you want it,
come and get it, what? ♪
♪ If you feel like I feel it,
won't you spit it? ♪
♪ What? If you can do it
how I do it, homie, quit it ♪
♪ Quit it, the changeover,
taking over... ♪
So, let's go empty out your
bank account, white boy.
Hey, you think you can
say a blessing
over my little nephew?
His dad won't let my
sister get him baptized.
-Sure
-Cool.
Yo, check this out, man.
My cousin Carlos?
He's a priest,
just like you, right?
But even he wouldn't give
$50,000 to some skanky chick
he didn't even know.
I'm doing this for my brother.
What did you say?
I said I'm doing
this for my brother.
Yeah, well, your brother
wouldn't do it for you.
-You don't know that.
-Oh, I don't know that?
I don't know that he's ripping
off all your friends right now?
♪ And it might not be for you,
but it's worth it to see... ♪
-That he's playing around with
your girlfriend?
-You're lying.
Look, I hate to break it to you,
but John ain't no saint,
all right?
And he ain't worth saving,
if you ask me.
How far is the bank?
Yo, why are you so nervous for?
You better have that money, man.
Rome will put you
in the ground otherwise.
Do you understand me,
preacher man?
♪ Come and get now ♪
♪ If you want it,
come and get it... ♪
TJ: Yo, let me ask you
something. If you're a priest,
how come you get to have a
girlfriend? What's up with that?
I'm Episcopal, not Catholic.
What is that?
♪ If you want it,
come and get it, what? ♪
♪ If you feel it
like I feel it,
won't you spit it? What... ♪
(whistles)
Yo, Jolita!
Yo, Jolita, what's up, man?
Oh, you don't remember me?
What up, baby? Where you going?
Right, so here's a question,
right? Dig, I already got
a girlfriend, right?
So is it a sin if, like,
I-I...
Oh, man. Oh, man,
you got to be kidding me.
Oh, man. No way!
♪ On Gospel-Gangsterz,
with a Z dot com... ♪
JEREMIAH: What do you mean,
you can't advance
me the money?
It's an express card.
I thought this thing
had no limit?!
MAN (over phone):
Sir, even if you had
a PIN number,
the maximum cash advance
for this account is $1,500.
But I need 50,000.
It's an emergency.
Look, if I don't get this
money, someone could die here.
Sounds to me like you should
be talking to the police.
I can't. The police will
just make it worse.
If you'd like, we could
send you an application
for a PIN number.
John.
Yeah, I-I need an address.
♪ ♪
♪ When all around has fallen ♪
♪ Your castle has been burned ♪
♪ You used to be a king here ♪
Hello?
John?
♪ Now no one knows your name ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ When tomorrow ♪
♪ Has been stolen ♪
♪ And you can't lift
your head... ♪
(whispers):
Come on, John.
Where did you put the money?
♪ And summer
feels like winter ♪
♪ Your heart is full of stone ♪
♪ Though all your hopes
have fallen ♪
♪ Your skin is now
your only armor ♪
♪ Oh, wear your scars ♪
♪ Like medals ♪
♪ Defender of the faith ♪
♪ Oh, come ♪
♪ Come ♪
♪ Lay your weary head ♪
♪ Be still, my friend ♪
♪ Come ♪
♪ Rise ♪
♪ I'll place my sword ♪
♪ Upon your shoulder ♪
♪ Come ♪
I hate you.
♪ Rise with me. ♪
TJ:
Rome, it's not my fault.
I was watching him
the whole time.
-ROME: Then where is he?
-Well, give me my wheels back,
-and I'll go find him.
-Too late.
ROME: We're gonna have
to make this work
for 12 grand.
-Can't believe you sold my car.
-Shut up, TJ.
-That was my El Camino.
-How many stacks you got?
-There's not enough here, Rome.
-Make it work.
Sunny, hold the gun straight.
I don't want to hold the gun.
We have one day!
(radio beeps)
I had these made for you.
I'm sorry I've been
a little weird lately.
(sighs)
You still paying
for that window.
You know that, right?
(laughs softly)
Man, these things
are nice in front.
-What does this do?
-(radio crackling)
Stop touching.
Let me ask you something.
How come you never told me
you had a brother?
You didn't know that?
How would I?
I don't know.
I don't know why
I didn't tell you.
I guess it's just hard
for me to talk about.
I should've told you.
TEX: You're not at all
worried about him?
No, I'm not.
I think it's great.
We've been going through
a lot of stuff recently,
and he's had
a real breakthrough.
I haven't seen him
like this in years.
(exhales) I don't know.
-I don't like it.
-Well, I do like it.
So do me a favor
and stay out of it, please.
See, you don't live with him.
I'm telling you,
something is up.
Oh, would you just get out
of here and go catch a bad guy?
But wait, wait, wait.
What do you know
about his brother?
Just that he died.
-His brother's dead?
-Yeah.
He died when they were 14.
They were twins.
That's why it's so difficult
for him.
That's what I'm saying.
He has a twin brother, and he's
never talked to me about it?
He'll talk to you about it
when he wants
to talk to you about it.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a date.
(exhales)
♪ My love is a storm... ♪
SAM: Dinner will be ready
in about a half an hour.
Smells great.
♪ I fear that she'll never be ♪
♪ Back in my arms ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ How she held me tight ♪
♪ And I just might... ♪
Here you go.
(exhales):
Yeah.
-To us.
-Mm.
♪ When the rain comes down ♪
♪ The clouds will roll... ♪
I can't get over you lately.
♪ Lord, and the wind
will blow ♪
♪ You are my undertow ♪
Can I kiss you?
♪ Caught in a riptide ♪
(quietly):
Yeah.
♪ And I am currently ♪
♪ In love with you ♪
♪ My love is an ocean ♪
♪ She glides like a seagull ♪
♪ She is the potion ♪
(exhales):
I love you.
♪ That makes me emotional ♪
♪ She is a song... ♪
Why?
(chuckles)
What do you mean, why?
I-I want to know... why.
Okay.
"Why?" Let's see.
"Why?"
Oh.
Well, I love your hands.
And I love your beautiful,
beautiful, hazel eyes.
And I love your chest.
And I love how strong you are.
And I love that you're
going to become a preacher.
I love how smart you are,
and how hard you worked to get
the things that you want.
And I love
that you're going to be leading
your own church one day,
Father Jeremiah Davis...
(grunts)
You're gonna spill my wine.
What?
Jeremiah, what's wrong?
Why can't anyone see that
Jeremiah Davis is not a saint?
What are you talking about?
You are the most honest,
genuine man
that I have ever met.
Why do you think
I'm still with you?
You're pathetic.
What?
(panting)
You want to know
what goes on
in this honest, genuine man?
I don't want to be a preacher.
I don't want to marry you.
And this whole Chicago thing?
Are you kidding me?
Thinking you can
make it as a painter.
Your work sucks.
You live in a dream world.
Why are you saying this?
'Cause I don't love you,
Samantha.
How many years
do you have to be strung along
before you get it?
(crying softly)
♪ You are my undertow ♪
Jeremiah.
♪ Caught in a riptide ♪
Jeremiah's dead.
♪ And I am currently ♪
-(door closes)
-♪ In love with you. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You're falling down... ♪
(glass shatters)
DAN:
Jeremiah, calm down.
Relax, relax.
Now, is there's something wrong?
I have a confession to make.
I'm not the person
you think I am.
I murdered my brother.
I sat and I watched
as he was beaten up
and thrown into a river.
I could have saved him,
but I didn't...
I didn't, I didn't do anything.
I can't be a priest.
Jeremiah, we've
been through this.
God has forgiven you.
He's forgiven you.
What?
But it was my fault.
I am a murderer.
Son, I've seen you down
on your knees.
And God has heard you
and he has forgiven you.
You must accept that
and move on.
So, that's it?
I'm just...
...forgiven?
Son, look at me.
God loves you.
He loves you.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
Hey, how are you?
I'm great. Uh, can I help you?
Yeah, uh,
what's the cheapest
thing you got?
-Potato chips.
-I'll take some.
Eighty-five.
(clears throat)
I got a bunch of ones here.
Can I get a ten?
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What, are you kidding?
-What do you think, I'm stupid?
-(grunts)
You okay, kid?
(grunts)
Hey! Come on, man.
-What's the matter with you?
-Get off me!
(groaning)
(phone ringing)
(answering machine beeps)
SAM (over machine):
Hi, it's Sam.
Leave me a message, or else.
JEREMIAH (over machine):
Sam, are you there?
(sighs) I wish you were there.
I'm screwing everything up.
I just...
I just wanted
to hear your voice.
Sam, listen to me. I have to
tell you something impor...
(answering machine beeps)
Sam? Sam?
♪ ♪
Excuse me, could you
hand me that two-inch brush
over there next to those cans?
Thank you.
What do you think of this shade?
You think Jesus would like it?
I-I-I don't know.
Well, it is His house after all.
You know... (clears throat)
you look like a wise man
who lost all his frankincense,
or maybe his myrrh. (laughs)
You have no idea.
You know, I knew
this guy from Honduras.
He used to ride around
on this mule.
-Do you have $50,000 I can have?
-Whoa, that's a chunk.
No offense, but if you don't,
I don't think you can help me.
Money problems,
I know about those.
It's more than just money.
This buddy of mine,
he had money problems,
then he got both
of his legs blown off.
After that, his money problems
looked pretty good.
-You don't get it.
-Oh, I bet I do.
No, no, you don't.
All right, painter man,
just shut up.
Last night,
I almost beat
a total stranger to death,
and I have no idea why.
I'm supposed to be
ordained a priest
in less than a month.
My brother hates me,
my girlfriend won't marry me
because she knows
that I am a total fraud,
and the only way
that I can fix it all
is to rip off these guys
that I-I don't know
using money I don't have.
Could you hand me
that round brush?
All right, I'll get it myself.
(sighs)
You know what I think?
I think you should just...
-...give up.
-What?
Give up.
You can't handle this
whole thing by yourself.
But I know someone who can.
You know what that's all about?
You know why He did that?
He did that so we could
all be forgiven.
I told you,
I'm about to be ordained.
I know all of this.
Ain't enough to know it.
You got to accept it.
-I have.
-No, you haven't.
Accepting it means
letting go of those things
for which you need forgiveness.
You're carrying all those
things around with you still.
You got your brother,
you got your girlfriend,
you got your money,
you're a phony,
and you're feeling
pretty bad about all that.
No, son, you are carrying
a lot of baggage.
Well, I can't just
ignore my problems.
Well, you can't just ignore God
until you get things
all fixed up.
He don't want that.
You see, the great thing
about God,
unlike my ex-wife,
you don't have to be perfect
for Him to accept you.
And that's when Jesus
comes into the equation.
Listen, you are standing
on the doorstep
of the Hotel Forgiveness,
but they don't allow
baggage inside.
You got to leave that with
the doorman-- that's Jesus--
and He's happy to take 'em.
Well, thanks,
but I got to go.
You let go of those bags,
you hear?
Let 'em go.
(door closes)
♪ ♪
Tex!
(tires screech)
Where's my money?
Where's my money?!
Tex, I need that money.
What's this?
Hello?
When'd you take up smoking?
I don't smoke.
-How about the tattoo?
-So what? I got a tattoo.
Guess where I found these?
In your key bowl, the first
place Jeremiah would've looked.
So what are you getting at?
Remember when we went
to Holland two summers ago?
-Sure.
-No.
-We've never been to Holland.
-(sighs)
I did some research, John.
They dredged that river,
but they never found your body.
-Hands behind your head.
-All right, all right, you win.
What'd you do
with Jeremiah, huh?
I didn't do anything with him.
(grunting)
-Your turn. On your knees.
-(grunts)
-Where's your backup?
-My right boot.
-Where's my money?
-Where's Jeremiah?
-Where's my money?!
-I gave it back. It's gone.
You gave it back?
John, the best decision
you can make right now
is to put the gun down
and tell me where Jeremiah is.
-Shut up.
-What's wrong with you?
He's your brother, man.
You've got to help him.
Why? He wouldn't help me.
You're wrong.
You don't know Jeremiah.
You're his best friend
and you never even heard of me.
He's no brother.
John, you really should think
about what you're doing.
Shut up! Shut up!
-Lord, please be with John.
-Tex.
Guide his hand and...
-(gun cocks)
-Tex.
...don't let him
make this mistake.
-I'm warning you.
-Calm his heart.
Tex!
And let him know this minute,
Lord, that You love him.
(echoing):
Shut up!
(phone ringing)
Yeah?!
Yes, Mr. Somonoff.
No, everything's good.
Right on schedule.
-No problem.
-My El Camino, man.
-You want it tomorrow?
-That car was a classic.
Don't worry.
But we agreed on 20%.
No, no, you're right.
That's very reasonable.
Yes. Yes.
Yes, sir. And thanks again
for the loan.
Mm-hmm. Thank you.
We don't pull this off,
I am dead,
but I'm gonna kill
the both of you first.
I swear to God I will.
Are you kidding me?
Well, I'm sorry.
I was trying to get your money.
Give me that.
Lot of ones.
Okay, let's do this.
-So the deal's still good?
-You pull it off, it is.
You give me John's gun back
when this is over.
-When it's over.
-But you let Sunny go now.
No. That's not part of the deal.
Sunny stays to make sure
you come back.
Fine. Good luck
with your situation.
Sunny, if you're gonna meet
Mr. Takashi at 3:00,
you better leave now.
Wait.
You're just as bad
as your brother.
You're right.
Okay, you know the drill.
Grip it tight.
They're only blanks,
but they got a lot of kick.
And remember, aim for the chest.
Hey, go on, get out of here.
You be careful in there.
Yeah.
Thanks, Sunny.
Hey.
Take care, preacher.
(phone ringing)
-Hello?
-JEREMIAH: Sam?
-Oh, thank God.
-I don't want to talk to you.
I'm leaving for Chicago.
Sam? Sam?
Come on.
(line ringing)
-John?
-Jeremiah?
Why didn't you find me?
Like you care.
John, I'm trying to save you,
give you a way out of this.
No thanks, Father.
I already tried your life,
and I didn't like it.
♪ ♪
What'd you do to Sam?
What'd you do to her?!
(grunting)
What are you doing
in my clothes?
John, let me do this, please.
Stay out of it.
That money is mine.
You're gonna screw it up!
(panting)
(thumping)
Man.
♪ ♪
Welcome.
Rome, this is
Peter, Mr. Takashi.
Mr. Takashi's a big
fan of your work.
Thank you.
Can I offer you gentlemen
something to eat?
-An appetizer?
-No.
Well, let's get
down to business.
(groans)
(engine starts)
(tires screeching)
I believe we both have
some counting to do,
so if Mr. Takashi
would be so kind.
(speaking Japanese)
Oh, come on,
you got to be kidding me.
What's the problem?
Cuffs, they won't open.
Here, let me try.
Gentlemen.
Stop!
Nice try, John.
You back for seconds?
Yeah, I'm starting to
like ripping you off.
I knew it.
Don't look at me like that.
Like I owe you something.
You sad old man.
I never asked you for anything.
Get away from my money.
Go to hell.
You first.
Wait, wait!
Peter, give me the gun
before you hurt yourself.
-Okay.
-(siren approaching)
Freeze!
(shouting in Japanese)
Was that supposed to happen?
(shouting continues)
PETER:
Oh! The door's locked.
-(Takashi crying out)
-This way!
How do we get out of here?!
Rome?
(groans)
Wrong gun, John.
-Drop it.
-(sets gun on floor)
Slow.
Hate to eat and run,
boys, but...
...too hip, got to go.
TJ?
No, not me, man.
I'm out of here.
(Rome groaning)
TJ?
We had a deal.
Give me the gun.
-Deal's off.
-What deal?
Give me the gun.
I mean it.
Gun doesn't matter.
I don't have anything on John.
You're lying.
I made it up.
John didn't kill anybody.
As soon as your safe,
you'll turn him in.
Now, where is it?
(chuckling)
I won't let you
take him away again.
New deal.
Give me the gun or die.
Jeremiah, stop.
Who's he kidding?
He can't do it.
Neither of you can.
You don't have to
do this for me.
It's not your responsibility.
My life is not your fault.
I've got to do this.
Come on.
Let's just get out of here.
We'll go together.
Jeremiah, look at me.
Give it up.
Let it go.
It's okay.
(faintly):
Let it go.
♪ ♪
(sirens approaching)
Police! Freeze!
Don't anyone move.
-Stay down. Keep your hands up.
-Oh.
Put your hands up. Step away.
I think I'm really hurt.
Hands up! Against the wall.
(siren winding down)
(indistinct
police radio chatter)
JOHN: I wouldn't worry
about jail, Rome.
Just like camp.
(emergency workers chattering)
(wheezes)
(engine starts)
Goodbye, Rome.
You shot him?
Yes.
Think about this
very carefully, J.
I can't give you any
special treatment.
Forget it, Jeremiah.
I'm taking this.
No, with your record,
you'll go away for 25 years.
-I'll be out in six months.
-J...
Tex.
He spent too much of his life
paying for things
that aren't his fault.
I stole your car.
I shot Rome.
-Let me do this.
-He deserves to go away.
Maybe that's what he deserves,
but it's not what he needs.
Well, what about
your ordination?
What about Sam?
I'll just have to wait and see.
TEX: Looks like one of those
situations where a kid's
gonna get a break
instead of going to jail.
But until he gets out,
you're staying with me;
you've got a lot to learn.
Hey, Sarge.
Must be what this is all about.
Hmm, maybe not.
(chuckles)
(laughs):
Oh, geez.
What? How did you...
It's what I do.
You can't keep this.
Oh, come on. I mean...
I mean it.
Tex.
♪ ♪
-(sighs)
-You be careful out here, kid.
You know I worry about you.
And I don't want to see you
back in here again.
-All right, Lou.
-All right.
Hey, convict.
Hey.
-Hey, brother.
-(laughing)
Whew! Like to say I missed you,
but it's like
you weren't even gone.
Think your time in jail
really straightened him out.
What am I gonna do?
I live with a cop.
Hey, your brother's got a point.
(laughs)
Took him to church yesterday.
He didn't steal nothing.
Good for you.
I'm pretty sure we're not
gonna have room for this.
♪ ♪
♪ Empty hours ♪
♪ Pass my eyes ♪
♪ The floor ♪
Hi.
♪ My checkered bed ♪
♪ There you stand ♪
♪ Like nature's child ♪
♪ Unfettered by
my wandering hand ♪
(sighs):
Oh.
♪ The night creeps on... ♪
You look great.
Aw.
Sam, I'm... sorry.
I've been so stupid for so long.
I love you.
-♪ Will you be here tonight? ♪
-(sighs)
♪ Hello, you know... ♪
I love you, too.
What are your plans now?
I don't really have any.
(both chuckle)
-Really?
-Yeah.
I'm just-just gonna
see where God takes me.
Mm.
Is there any chance that
God will take you to Chicago?
♪ My heart will beat in time ♪
I hope so.
♪ Hello, you know ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
-♪ Goodbye ♪
-(engine starts)
♪ Hey there ♪
♪ How's it been, my dear? ♪
♪ You sure do look all right ♪
♪ Hello, you know ♪
-♪ Goodbye ♪
-(siren blaring)
♪ Well, hello ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ Goodbye. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You must be the seed ♪
♪ Descend into the earth ♪
♪ Searching for the union ♪
♪ Of death and then rebirth ♪
♪ But I need love ♪
♪ It is patience,
it is kindness ♪
♪ I need love ♪
♪ It is rain
after the dryness ♪
♪ I need love ♪
♪ Sister Wisdom, help me see ♪
♪ It's the one thing
that I need ♪
♪ The only thing that I need ♪
♪ The harvester is near ♪
♪ His blade is on your skin ♪
♪ To plant a new beginning ♪
♪ Well,
then let the cut begin ♪
♪ But I need love ♪
♪ It is patience,
it is kindness ♪
♪ I need love ♪
♪ It is rain
after the dryness ♪
♪ I need love ♪
♪ Sister Wisdom, help me see ♪
♪ It's the one thing
that I need ♪
♪ The only thing that I need. ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ ♪
♪ If you walked ♪
♪ Down this alley ♪
♪ And turned the corner ♪
♪ You'd be home ♪
♪ And if you choose ♪
♪ That path along the way ♪
♪ You may fall ♪
♪ Be forced to crawl ♪
♪ And then stand tall ♪
♪ 'Cause we all break down ♪
♪ When we finally meet ♪
♪ The light of town ♪
♪ On the mercy streets ♪
♪ Even the ones ♪
♪ Closest to you ♪
♪ Thought you had gone ♪
♪ Away ♪
♪ But you're back at last ♪
♪ And you almost forgot ♪
♪ To forget ♪
♪ The past ♪
♪ And we all break down ♪
♪ When we finally meet ♪
♪ The light of town ♪
♪ On the mercy streets ♪
♪ Yes, we all break down ♪
♪ When we finally meet ♪
♪ The light of town ♪
♪ On the mercy streets ♪
♪ Yes, we all break down ♪
♪ When we finally meet ♪
♪ The lights ♪
♪ The lights of town ♪
♪ On the mercy streets ♪
♪ Yes, we all break down ♪
♪ When we finally meet. ♪