- Bit early for you, isn't it?
- Yeah.
I wanted to see
what it felt like to be you.
And?
It's overrated.
You'll get used to it.
How about I just live
vicariously through you
instead?
Hmm?
Listen, I need you to give
Karl at STB Capital
a call on your way in.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
I woke up
to an email from him.
I think he's got
buyer's remorse.
He likes the returns.
Yeah, but still,
I think something spooked him.
I need you to do your thing.
I'll talk to him.
He'll be fine.
Good. You're a credit
to capitalism.
Say hello to Heather for me.
Not a good idea.
You're an asshole.
Morning.
Anders says hello.
Going somewhere?
I...
I'm meeting Christina
this morning.
Uh-huh?
After that, I thought
I'd pick up the kids
and maybe move
to the Moon.
Oh.
Matt!
I'm sorry, honey.
It-it's work.
Right.
I'm meeting Christina.
You said you'd
take them today.
Oh, God. I really need
to make this call.
I can't have them
playing in the back,
making noise
while I'm on the call...
- Matt, I need to see her.
- ...with an important client.
Can't you see her this weekend?
I asked you
to help out just one day.
Okay, okay. Fine.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Mm-mm.
Heather...
Congratulations.
This actually helps...
- Where's your brother?
- On his phone.
Tell him to come down.
We're leaving now.
Zach, we're leaving!
- So, um,
I think you'll be...
I was
watching that.
Go and get
your brother. Now.
Ugh! Zach!
Ay-ay-ay-ay-ay.
What now?
Nothing. It's fine.
Hey.
Get them to school
on time, okay?
Yeah... Lov-love you.
- Hey, we're leaving.
- Hey, get out!
- Let me come in!
Just get out!
- I told you last time...
- Oh, for the love of God.
- Get out! Get out! Get out!
- Zach!
- Hey, get out!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey!
What's happening here?
- He slammed the door on me.
- You don't come in here!
Don't speak
to your sister like that.
Then don't let her
in my room, Matt.
Hey, I am your father.
I'm not Matt.
- Why is she crying?
- 'Cause she knows
you'll fall for it.
- He's gonna skip school
with her.
- Shut up, Em!
I don't have time
for this.
Go and get
your things ready.
Dad, he broke my finger!
Go!
We'll be down in a sec.
Okay.
If this is gonna be
one of your talks, I don't
have time for it if it is.
Zach, what is this?
Can I just go now, Dad?
- You're skipping school?
- Why would I skip school?
You have
a girlfriend, yeah?
Do you even care
if I do?
If you're skipping school,
yeah, I care.
Get in the car.
We're going! Now!
- Where's your brother?
- I don't know.
He was walking.
Oh, jeez.
Careful, careful.
What is that?
For practice.
I have a match today.
Well, don't bounce it,
honey. I need to focus.
Are you coming?
Uh...
Um, I can't.
You don't even know
when it is.
Work is busy.
Next one, I promise.
Zach, get in.
Zach.
Can you just listen
for once?
I can hear you.
Zach, get in the car.
- Or what?
- Get in the car right now!
Zach, get in the car
this second!
Please!
Please. Come on.
Thank you.
I think I can see my bone.
- Shut up.
- Hey.
Call Unger.
- Hello?
- Karl, it's Matt.
How's Katherine?
Telling me not to waste
any more of our children's
inheritance.
I heard.
When did you get
so sensitive?
When my stock dropped
17% overnight.
See it
as an opportunity.
I see it as a trend.
Not in the right direction.
I want out.
What have I always
told you?
"Predicting the rain
doesn't count."
"Building the Ark does."
I thought that was
Warren Buffett.
So listen to him, then.
Turbulence is inevitable.
When everyone runs
from the fire,
you run to it.
Karl, you're investing in me.
That's the deal.
Maybe you've lost
your touch.
Hey, how long
have we known each other?
- Eighteen years.
Do you remember what you said
to me the first time we met?
That was
a long time ago.
Well, I remember.
You told me you were tired
of playing it safe.
That you wanted
to be someone else.
Like I said,
that was a long time ago.
The man you are now,
I know you.
You don't run
from a challenge.
You take it on.
You take on the uncertainty,
the risks,
so you can give Katherine
everything she's ever
dreamed of.
You provide.
Just look in the mirror
and ask,
how you've provided
everything. How?
Where you've come from
to get where we are?
You've climbed up
that ladder.
You can't let go.
I know you, Karl.
We're the same.
You walk away from me
and you're walking back
to that old life.
And at our age,
you don't come back
from that.
Karl, are you looking
in that mirror?
Hmm?
All right. I'm in.
Is this why Anders
likes you so much?
You make people feel good
about losing three million
euros in 24 hours?
You'll have to ask him, pal.
Did you win, Daddy?
Yeah.
How?
Eh, it's complicated.
It's like I caught a fish.
You use a nice big fat worm
and you dangle a hook and--
You lie.
It's pretty easy.
Someone important?
- Her name's Mila.
- Shut up.
I wasn't talking
to you, Zach.
Well, you are right now.
Hey, that's enough.
- Are you gonna answer that?
- What?
Are you gonna answer that?
It's not mine.
- Is it Mom's?
- No.
Emily?
It's not mine.
Hello?
Hello, Matt.
Hello. Yes. Who's this?
I like your car.
Sorry, who is this?
You keep asking
the same question.
Do you think
you'll get an answer?
- Sylvain?
- Not Sylvain.
Just me. And you.
I'm hanging up now.
I wouldn't do that.
I said I like
your nice leather seats.
But I wouldn't really want
to be in that seat right now.
All right, that's enough.
You hang up on me,
they'll be picking your guts
out of the trees
from here to Austria.
Do I have
your attention?
Matt Turner,
there is a bomb
under your seat.
You armed it
the second you sat down.
If you--
Who was that?
Um, no one.
No one, honey.
Dad?
- Dad? Dad, stop!
- Dad!
Are you crazy?
You just missed the turn.
Right here.
You sure
this isn't Mom's?
Pretty sure.
Where are we?
Um...
Just, uh,
checking the car, sweetie.
Your brand-freaking-new
100,000-euro car's
breaking down?
- Great. I'll walk.
- Wait.
Wait.
What is it?
Dad, what's wrong?
Dad, who is that?
- Dad.
- Huh?
No one.
Hang up on me again
and I detonate.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Drive.
Don't stop driving.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
I didn't hear you.
Yes, I'm driving.
Good. Now that I have
your attention,
listen very carefully.
The device is connected
to a pressure plate.
If you get out of your seat,
the bomb will detonate.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
There is a secondary trigger,
a remote switch
that I am holding as we speak.
If you try to call the police,
if you try to get help...
...I will detonate.
I'm watching you.
If you go somewhere
I don't like,
I will detonate.
Do you understand
everything I have said to you?
Yes. What do you want?
Don't worry.
We'll get to that.
Look, I have
my children in the car.
That's interesting.
- Let me get them out
and you and I can...
- No.
Remember the first rule.
The pressure plates, Matt.
Wouldn't want
to change the pressure.
Keep it nice and heavy.
You do exactly what I say,
when I say it,
maybe you'll get out of this
in one piece.
And so will they.
Think of this day
as a profound
life experience.
Did I-- did I do
something to you?
If I did, I'm sorry,
just... just tell me.
You sound so... guilty.
What have you done, Matt?
Whatever it is, I'm sorry.
- Dad?
- I'm not convinced.
Dad, you're going
the wrong way.
Zach, please.
Jesus.
Don't you turn around.
I'm watching you.
Look.
Drive.
Don't stop driving.
Do exactly what I say.
I said I'm watching.
Why does he keep going
the wrong way?
Take your kids' phones.
Th-their phones?
What am I supposed to say?
Say whatever you want.
And my phone?
Keep it.
You're going to need it.
- I don't think my children
are gonna like--
- Now!
Zach.
Zach!
What?
The kids' phones,
I want them out of the car.
Give me your phone.
- Em, you too.
- What?
Now!
- Are you psycho? Why?
- Yeah. Why?
I have no patience, Matt.
I'm your father.
I said give me your phones.
Why? What did I do?
You almost took my finger off.
Zach!
Throw the phones out
- or kiss your kids goodbye.
- Now!
- Zach!
- What the hell, Dad?
I told you
to get their phones.
I'm counting now.
I hear you.
Ten, nine...
...eight, seven...
...six,
- five...
- I hear you.
...four, three...
- Hang on, kids!
- ...two...
- What was that?
- Dad!
Oh, my God. You just hit
Zach's girlfriend!
Hey, what is wrong with you?
You could've killed me!
I told you they were
skipping school.
- What are you doing?
- Accidents happen, Matt.
- I'm... I'm getting out.
- No!
- Zach!
- Now drive.
No, no, no, no.
- I'm leaving.
- Stay in your seats!
What the hell's wrong
with you?
Zach...
Are you out of your mind?
- Are you crazy?
You just hit her!
- Dad, stop it!
What are you doing?
Give me your phone, Zach.
- What are you doing?
- Give me your phone! Now!
No! Stop the car!
There's a bomb in this car!
There's a bomb in this car.
If any of us get out,
the car blows up.
If you don't get rid
of your phone,
the car blows up.
A bomb?
Now.
- Get rid of them.
- Give me your phone.
Thank you.
Number one dad.
Your kids really listen,
don't they?
I did what you asked.
Good. Now drive
to this location.
Where are we going?
Why does he
want to hurt us?
I don't know, sweetie.
Dad, what did you do?
Answer that.
- I don't know
what you're saying.
- Sylvain!
- Sylvain, who is that?
- Wait, hold this. Matt?
I'm freaking out
here. Okay?
There's a guy that called
and said that there's a bomb
underneath the car.
And if we get help,
it'll blow up.
Stop! Just stop doing that!
No! I don't understand.
Matt,
he said we're gonna die
because of you.
No. Hey! Stop! Stop!
- What else did he say?
- Wait, you know him?
Just stop!
Would you stop doing that?
Please, please.
Sylvain, steady on.
What else did he say?
I don't know. Stop.
He said to wait for you
until you arrived.
That's it.
So there you are.
No! No, don't touch that.
Don't touch that. Stop it.
Just stop it for one second.
Please, I don't know
what you're saying.
Can you please be quiet
for one second?
Matt, please?
I'm freaking out here, man.
I know you are. Me too.
But it's important
that you stay calm.
It's easy for you to say,
"stay calm". There's a bomb
underneath the car!
Listen to me.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
He called me too.
Which means
we're in this together.
We're in what together?
Sylvain...
Okay, well,
what did you do to him?
I didn't do anything.
I need you to focus.
Did he say anything else?
No, no, no.
I don't want to die.
Matt, I have a family.
No. What are you doing?
He said no phones.
Give me the fucking phone.
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
- I don't want to die, Matt.
- You're not going to die.
You just need
to stay calm and think.
I am going to die
if you don't...
Don't make
promises you can't keep.
Sylvain, there's a police
officer walking towards you
right now.
- Help! Help!
- Shh! Don't say another word!
- Help! No!
- No! No! Stop!
Calm down now.
Just be calm.
Just be quiet.
No! No!
No!
Zach, Em, are you okay?
Answer me. Answer me.
Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
Zach, Emily, are you hurt?
I'm good. I'm okay.
Check her.
Check she's okay.
- She's good. She's good.
- I'm good.
She should've listened.
You didn't have to do that!
- She broke the rules.
- Rules?
You just killed three people.
They weren't the first.
But they can be the last.
That's entirely up to you.
Why did you want me
to see that?
So you won't have any doubts
about my sincerity.
Then take it out on me.
Just let my children go.
- Who was that?
- Someone from work.
Is that what
this is all about?
I told you,
I don't know.
I'm... I'm sorry, Zach.
it's okay.
Just tell me
what it is you want.
I'm sure I can get it.
I'm s-I'm sorry. I'm sorry
for whatever happened to you.
I'm sorry.
I want you
to call Heather.
What? Why?
You have a safety box
at the AIG bank
in Tiergarten.
Heather is going
to retrieve it.
This is about money?
You can get someone else.
She doesn't deserve
to be mixed up in this.
- What's going on?
- Not now, Zach.
You don't have the luxury
of time to debate me.
Call Heather.
And put her on speaker.
This is Heather. I'm not here.
So say something nice.
Heather, it's me.
Call me back immediately.
It's urgent.
She's not answering.
You're an industrious man.
Get ahold of her.
And quickly.
Call Christina.
Hello?
Christina, it's Matt.
I need to speak to Heather.
Heather?
Have you tried her phone?
She's not answering.
I know she's with you,
and I need to speak to her.
- She's not with me.
- Where is she?
I need to get
ahold of her right now.
- Matt...
- Tell me where she is.
It's a matter
of life and death.
What's happened?
Christina, I don't have
time to explain.
I need to speak
to my wife right now.
She's at a divorce attorney.
You haven't been there
for her, Matt.
What does that mean?
- Which one?
- It's in Lichtenberg.
I don't know.
Webber something.
Matt... you didn't--
You have
two minutes to find her.
Then you know what happens.
I found her.
No.
Webber and Babel.
Um, I need to speak
to Heather Turner, please.
I'm sorry. There's
no Heather Turner here.
This is Matt Turner speaking.
I'm her husband.
This is an emergency.
I need to speak to her now.
Well, I'm sorry, I...
Our children are in trouble.
One moment, please.
Are the kids okay?
They're fine.
I had to get you on the phone.
Listen to me.
Something's happened.
I need you to stay calm.
You're scaring me, Matt.
Just listen, please.
There's a man... there's...
There's a man
who's put a bomb in the car.
What?
We have to do
everything he says.
What are you talking about?
Heather, please.
Just listen
to what I tell you.
Emily?
Sweetheart, are you okay?
Heather, she's fine.
They're both fine.
- Is Zach okay?
- Yes. Yes, he's fine.
- Have you called the police?
- No. No, we can't.
Then I'm calling them.
Heather, please.
Just listen
to what I have to tell you.
If you call the police,
he will...
He...
Do you understand?
No. I don't
understand, Matt.
What you're saying
doesn't make any sense.
Who is he?
I don't know.
Right now, we just
have to do what he says.
And everything will be
fi-fine. Okay.
Oh, my God, Matt. What?
I need you to go
to the AIG bank
in Tiergarten.
There's a safety
deposit box in my name.
What?
When you get there,
they will ask to speak to me.
You call me, okay?
Then what?
I don't know.
Heather, I'm...
Look, if...
If I wasn't
enough for you, I'm...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's gonna be okay, Dad.
You bet.
Yeah.
There's
that number-one dad again.
You better find
somewhere to lay low
until she's at your big bank.
Remember, Matt.
I'm watching you.
Don't do anything stupid.
I'm waiting.
Hello? I'm waiting.
Hello?
We've just begun
our investigation.
Any speculation at this time
is just that, speculation.
Can you at least say
whether you're looking
for one suspect
or multiple suspects?
Everything's
on the table.
Because of the protests,
will you shut down the city?
No, not at this time.
Thank you. Danke.
You worked with him too.
The first guy.
That's your company.
It is. Yeah.
Dad, what did you do?
Nothing.
Stop lying.
This guy is trying to kill us
because of something you did.
- Look.
- I didn't do anything.
Nothing to deserve this.
Are you and Mom
getting a divorce?
What?
No.
See? You lie.
It's what you do every day.
To Mom. To them. To us.
- No. I promise.
- You promise what?
You made me get in this car.
You made me.
I promise I will get you out.
Both of you.
Zach.
Listen to me. I promise.
Okay.
- She's calling.
- Pick up.
Tell her you'll meet her
outside the bank.
She hands you the money
and then leaves.
No conversation. Nothing.
I'm here at the bank.
They want to speak to you.
Good. Put them on.
- Mr. Turner?
- Yes.
I understand your wife
would like to access
your safe deposit box
on your behalf?
That's correct.
- The password is "Siena."
- Thank you, sir.
What's in the box, Matt?
My passport,
uh, some personal items
and 50,000 euros.
Heather, just call me
when you get out.
I'll be waiting
for you outside.
Put the money
in the passenger seat
- and walk away.
- I...
- I'm serious.
- Okay.
And Heather...
listen to me.
The kids are going to be okay.
I promise you.
What's Siena?
It's where I met
your mom, sweetie.
Are we gonna see Mom?
Yes, love.
But you won't be able to talk
to her right now. Okay?
Matt, I'm coming out.
Look down the street.
Do you see us?
Uh...
Yes.
Mom. Mom.
I've got it.
Change of plan.
There's a man in a blue suit
sitting alone on a bench.
Tell her to go to him
and give him the bag.
That's not what you said.
I give the instructions.
She does that
and she walks free?
You give me your word?
Of course.
Heather.
There's a man sitting
on a bench in the square.
He's wearing a blue suit.
Do you see him?
Yes.
Give him the money.
Then walk away.
What about you
and the kids?
We'll be fine.
Just... just do it, please.
Okay.
It's all...
it's all there.
Excuse me?
The money,
it's all there.
What...
what money?
What? What? What?
No.
- Dad, why are they
doing that? Dad, help her!
- No, no. No!
Wait. Wait.
Drive!
I didn't call them, I swear.
Please believe me.
I called them.
- Why?
- There is no why.
You didn't want me
to see Sylvain die.
You wanted me
to be seen there.
My car. Me.
Trust me, Matt,
you're not as smart
as you think you are,
or your escape plan
would involve
more than a safety
deposit box
at a local bank.
- What escape plan?
- Take your money and run.
Your investors' money.
Dubai.
Dubai?
The little slush fund
that you and Anders have,
safe and tucked away
in the desert.
208 million euros
emergency collateral.
What is this?
Hey, I asked you a question.
I think we should
talk to your boss.
Anders? Why?
If you can't help me,
maybe he can.
I don't think this is a--
This is no time
to start playing games, Matt.
He's already
waiting for you. Drive.
Hey, asshole.
Can you hear me?
Zach, look at this photo.
Am I seeing it right?
Does that look
like a phone to you?
Yeah, I think so.
Good. Good.
- A phone.
- Is that good?
Yeah. It might be.
Great. More phones.
- Dad?
- Yes, baby?
You called him an asshole.
Good.
- Shit. Dad?
- Yeah?
You're on TV.
Hello? Hello?
- Heather.
- Mr. Turner,
this is Angela Brickmann
with Europol.
Europol?
I'm with your wife.
I've got to say, we're all
very concerned about you.
I'm not responsible
for all this.
That's good to hear.
I believe you.
Do not patronize me.
I'm telling you,
I'm innocent.
If that's the case,
letting your children go
would be a great way
to demonstrate that.
- I can't.
- And why is that?
This isn't
what it looks like.
Tell me what it looks like.
There's a bomb in my car.
- Like the others?
- Yes.
Matt, you can
let your children go.
It's not me.
You have to believe me.
There's a man--
Who called you, your wife says
that's what you told her.
It's not my job
to believe you,
Mr. Turner.
It's my job to stop
people from dying,
and to get
your children out safely.
I have to trust you.
God damn it,
listen to me.
I'm listening.
Can you stop cell phones
from working?
Now, why would I do that
if I could? We wouldn't
be able to talk.
Because the bomb appears
to have cell phone failsafe.
A pressure plate
and cell phone, okay?
- And?
- Then he can't detonate it.
- Who is he?
- Listen to me.
Shut off the phones!
I want to help you, Matt,
but I can't do that.
- Emergency services, police...
- Matt?
- ... you aren't the only man...
- Answer me.
You hung up?
- What if they could've
helped us?
- Ten,
- nine, eight...
- I'm here.
I'm here.
What do you want?
You think I'm stupid?
Taking your time?
You better drive faster.
Two minutes.
The police come to help us
and he finds out,
you know what he'll do.
- Will he kill us?
- Oh, God.
No, honey.
No. I'm... just...
I can't risk you.
You understand?
I won't risk you.
I can help us.
- We're here.
- Patience, Matt.
Put him on speaker.
Call Anders.
Matt...
Why are you doing this?
Anders.
What have I ever done to you?
Nothing, nothing. Listen...
What kind of fucking psycho
does this to his own
best friend?
And you brought your kids!
Anders, it's gonna be
okay. Just...
just look at me.
- Hey. Hey.
- Jesus.
Matt, why?
I don't have time for this.
Tell him to authorize
liquidating
your collateral account.
That isn't my money.
I didn't steal it.
It's the clients'.
If you're punishing me,
you should know that.
Matt, just...
tell me what you want.
If I did something
to piss you off, I'm sorry.
- Okay?
- Did you hear me?
Tell him to authorize.
Matt.
I said I'm sorry, Matt.
Anders, listen.
I need you to authorize
liquidating the emergency
collateral account.
The Dubai fund. All of it.
Jesus Christ.
That's what this is about?
You did this for money?
Tell him if he doesn't,
you'll kill him.
You killed them for money?
Tell him to do it,
or I kill you
and your kids.
Anders...
do it.
Authorize liquidation,
or I will...
Now.
Authorize liquidation
or I will...
kill you.
I will kill you.
Okay.
Okay. I'm doing
what you want,
all right?
I'm calling, Matt.
Just... hold on.
Do it.
Once he authorizes,
you'll do the same
and you'll transfer me
the money.
It's that simple.
As soon as he does it,
you'll let him go. Yes?
Are you listening?
He's doing what you want.
Okay, okay. It's done.
Matt, I said
it's all done, okay?
He did what you wanted.
It's over.
Once I confirm
the authorization,
you get it all.
All the money you want.
208 million euros.
You'll let us all go, yes?
Just tell me
where you want the money.
I'll authorize,
I'll send it.
Dad, it's over?
Open the glove box.
What?
Oh, Jesus.
You see what's inside?
Take it.
Shoot him.
Dad?
What...
I'm not doing this.
His life or yours.
Matt!
I did what you wanted!
Dad.
Ten, nine, eight...
- Dad, don't.
- May God forgive me.
Matt, let me go.
Dad, what are you doing?
...seven...
...six...
- Shit!
- Dad, don't do this.
- ...five...
- Please!
- Dad, don't.
- ...four...
Dad, don't do this, okay?
He's your friend.
- Matt, let me get out.
- Dad, he's your friend.
- Don't do this!
- ...three...
God... God forgive me.
- Please. God forgive me.
- Matt! Let me go!
- ...two...
- Dad! Dad,
he's your friend!
What are you doing?
Dad, don't!
- Shoot him. Now.
- I can't.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Emily? Em, are you okay?
Emily?
Em! Em!
Oh, shit.
Shit! Shit! Shit!
It's her leg.
Dad, it's her leg.
- Here. Here.
- It's bleeding.
Oh, God.
Here, here, here.
Use this.
Tie it, tie it.
What?
Her leg. Tie it.
Tie it above the wound.
- Dad, I'm okay.
- Tie it tight.
- It has to be tight.
- Okay.
Zach, I'm okay.
- Em.
- Dad, I'm okay.
- Em, baby. Look at me.
- I'm okay.
- Tight! Tight!
- Are you ready?
I'm sorry.
Hang on, baby.
- Hang on, baby. Okay, okay.
- I'm okay.
- I'm fine.
- Hang on, baby.
We're gonna get you
some help.
I'm fine.
You're a murderer now, Matt.
Make the phone call, Matt.
Your half of the liquidation
authorization.
Son of a bitch.
I will kill you.
Really?
Well, Matt,
that'll make four people
that you've killed today.
No. Just the one.
Dad.
- Make the call. Now.
- Fuck you.
It's gonna be okay.
I promise.
- Em, look at me.
It's gonna be okay.
- Hold on, Em. Okay?
- Make the call or you die.
- No.
You hurt my daughter,
you scumbag.
You want that money?
You need me.
I meet you face to face.
When I'm ready.
First, I help my child.
- Then you get your money.
- I'm in control here.
No, you're not.
Em. Em, hold on,
okay? Hold on.
You do what I say or...
...or I will kill you...
Come on.
Come on. God damn it.
Shit.
Em, Em.
Stay awake, sweetie.
It's almost over.
I'm tired.
I know you are, baby,
but you have to try.
You have to try it.
Please, please.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
It's my family.
It's Mom.
What are they waiting for?
They think I'm the bomber.
Then tell them you're not.
Tell them about the guy
on the phone.
I'll try.
Try? I'll tell them.
Hey! Help us!
My sister!
My Dad didn't do it!
Zach, no one else
has heard this guy.
Turn off your engine!
My daughter needs help!
She's bleeding!
Hilfe! Help!
Anyone!
It's not there.
It's under our seats.
It's under our seats!
We have no time.
This is going to take
way too long.
No, we haven't got
the time for this.
Please.
Everyone okay?
My daughter's hurt.
She's lost a lot of blood.
We need help. Now.
How you doing,
sweetheart?
Good girl.
We have EMTs right here.
We'll get her seen to
real soon.
Then bring them in now.
You've got
everybody's attention, Matt.
A lot of people here
are worried about you.
Especially Heather.
She just wants
to see her family again,
and I want
to make sure she does.
I'm here to help you.
I just need to know
you're not gonna,
you know,
do something crazy.
I mean, you go, I go.
- And I have a family too.
- Hey...
My Dad didn't do
any of this, okay?
There's this psycho
on the phone
- talking into his ear.
- Zach...
You see all that?
I have a lot going on here.
I'm just gonna
talk to your dad here
for a minute, okay?
I promise
I'll talk to you too.
Zach, it's okay.
I... I didn't do this.
I wouldn't.
Matt. Can I call you Matt,
Mr. Turner?
Call me whatever you want.
Just get us out of this car.
Your children
can get out right now
if that's all right, Matt.
The car will explode.
I see. If they get out,
the car explodes.
Under our seats,
there are pressure triggers.
Well, our friends here
are looking into that,
aren't they?
You turned off the phones,
yeah?
We've jammed cell signal
for five blocks.
You should be honored.
They haven't interrupted
the telephone service
in Berlin since 1945.
Nice to unplug for a minute.
You say that he
called you on that?
Do you know who he is?
If I knew that,
I would tell you.
Just get them out.
Look at my daughter, please.
Okay.
They think
the doors are clear.
We'd like to open them.
So, three colleagues
from your company
die in one day,
but not you.
I didn't do this.
I didn't set off
those bombs.
Okay. Understood.
It's gonna be okay, okay?
But why would
someone do this to you?
- I'll have a look
under your seat now.
- Why you, Matt?
To punish you?
- Money.
- You can get money robbing a bank...
...or working
a fancy job like yours.
Not this kind of money.
What kind of money?
Trust, Matt.
I need trust.
You've had a lot of losses
for your clients,
but you still have
a nice car.
Do I?
Well, I guess
you've had a tough day.
A tough week?
A tough year?
How much did your clients
lose this year?
We all lost this year.
Well, I know that you
and your recent colleagues
lost a lot of money
for your trusting clients
who invested in your fund,
yet you kept
making promises.
Promises
that profits would appear.
Maybe he's an angry client.
"An angry client." Mm.
What kind of money
did you say he wanted?
Just hurry up, please.
What kind of money?
208 million euros.
All Nanite Capital accounts
have been frozen.
So, how does he plan
to access this money?
The account's based
in Dubai.
It's outside
your jurisdiction.
Who knows
about this account?
Partners in the firm.
How many are still alive?
Just me.
It's clear
back here. No device.
No pressure plates
in the back.
He said it was
under our seats.
What are you waiting for?
We're getting your children
out now, but...
Please, hurry.
But the bomb under your seat
is hardwired
to the seat sensors.
Even if we take out
the car battery,
shut down the car's CPI,
you get up, it will
still trigger the bomb.
Grab my shoulder.
There you go, Em.
Em, go. It's okay.
Baby, it's okay.
It's okay, baby.
It's okay. I love you.
Dad.
Dad, I'm not gonna
leave you.
- Uh, I'll be fine.
- If you stay, I stay.
- Go with your sister.
- Dad...
You just tell that girlfriend
of yours, um, Mila,
I hope I can still meet her.
Yeah?
- I hope so too.
- Yeah.
I made a promise
I'd get you out.
I love you, Zach.
Go on.
Love you too.
I'm gonna fix this.
Good boy.
Mom.
- I'm okay.
- Oh, sweetie.
Can it be deactivated?
We're still working on it.
Can I talk to my wife?
You will.
When we get you out.
I need to talk
to her. Please.
Okay.
- Ma'am?
- Oh. Oh.
Thank you.
Matt?
Honey...
Are you okay?
Uh, I've had better days.
I didn't do this.
I want you to know that.
Matt, just do whatever
the police say.
Just listen to them
and they'll get you out,
okay?
You have to do as they say.
Matt?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about everything.
I-I should've
been there for you.
For all of you.
Don't say that.
I love you, baby.
I always have.
Just come home.
- We'll be okay.
- I will.
- Okay.
- Come on.
You're all here
focused on me.
And he is still out there.
He's the one
that did this to me.
You don't have
to worry about that.
We'll find him.
You don't believe me.
What I believe right now
is irrelevant.
I can find him.
Matt, you go into custody.
We'll work through this.
We'll walk through
every possibility.
You have my word on that.
No.
He set me up
and you all bought it.
Right now, we're trying
to get you out of this car.
That is my only objective.
You have your objective,
and I have mine.
If you can't find him,
I will.
Matt...
Tell them to stand down.
Matt, if you leave,
I cannot protect you.
I want to be clear
about that.
Matt! Matt!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
No!
You hearing this?
You want your money.
I want my life back.
Transfer the money. Now!
Face to face.
Or you get nothing.
I could end this right now.
So, what's it gonna be?
End it!
End it! End it!
I choose the address.
Not you.
Hello, Matt.
I just need to press send
and we both go up,
along with a lot
of innocent people.
Now drive.
I said drive.
Where?
How about someplace
a little more quiet?
Surprise.
I told you, Matt.
You're not as smart
as you think.
Jesus Christ.
Well,
not quite water into wine,
but I did just manage
to turn a few bodies
into 208 million euros.
I...
I watched you die
in that explosion.
Misdirection is at the heart
of all great magic tricks.
I just needed
a little distraction.
Thankfully,
German trains run on time.
You know, that last blast
had a little more kick
than I expected.
But with all that money...
I'll just get myself
a new face.
You did this all for money?
Survival.
Prison's no place
for a man with my taste.
I gave you
18 years of my life,
you son of a bitch!
This was all inevitable, Matt.
Don't take it personally.
Inevitable?
If Cinderella's slipper
fit so perfectly,
then why did it fall off?
Huh?
Anders, what happened to you?
You know the business
we're in, Matt.
It's kill or be killed.
Your words.
Don't go thinking
you're different than me.
You're the murderer,
not me.
You really think so?
Are you sure about that?
Anders, authorize liquidation,
or I will...
Authorize liquidation,
kill you.
Okay. Okay.
I'm doing what you want,
all right?
I'm calling, Matt.
Just... hold on.
Do it.
Anders, I will kill you.
All sounds
pretty convincing to me.
The bombs, the money.
It all points to you.
You know what was
the easiest thing?
Setting up the bombs.
You know
there's a bomb-making service
on the dark web?
If you pay them a premium,
they'll even install it
in the car.
I'm five steps ahead
of everyone, Matt.
Make no mistake.
Now, if you'd be so kind
and complete the transaction.
Transfer the money, Matt.
The minute you try to withdraw
one cent of that money,
they'll know you're alive.
It's in a crypto account.
Untraceable. Impregnable.
You really think
I haven't thought
of every single
possible permutation?
When your kids
got in the car this morning,
do you think I panicked?
The one day that you decide
to be a good daddy
and drive your kids
to school? No.
I adapted. I overcame.
Just like I did
when Pils Kroger
was going to pull the rug
out from under us.
He was going to destroy us.
I wasn't gonna
let that happen.
He found out
you were siphoning money
from the offshore account.
The FCA doesn't look kindly
on embezzlement.
He...
he did nothing to you.
And what did you do
when you found out? Hmm?
You did nothing.
- You looked the other way.
- I didn't know
what you were doing.
Don't be naive!
It's always been about
the bottom line for us.
Bullshit! Everything I did
was above board.
You really do think
you're different, don't you?
At least I accept who I am.
You just lie to yourself
every day.
You just let it
eat away at you
until your own family
doesn't recognize you.
I'm not surprised
Heather wants to leave you.
I'm just surprised
it took this long to do it.
Now stop wasting time.
Call the bank!
I said call the bank.
This is your last chance.
I said call them.
Call them!
There's one thing
you didn't think of, Anders.
What a man will do
when he's got nothing to lose.
Pull over, Matt.
Stop!
- Stop!
- No, no.
- I said stop!
- No.
Pull over
or I'll kill us both!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Heather.
Pull over!
Come here. Come here.
The city
woke up to an explosion
- in Tiergarten this morning.
- By the time it was over...
...a total
of four bombs rocked the city
in as many hours.
Initially thought to be
a terrorist...
...the elaborate
money heist
involved Nanite Capital's
CEO Anders Muller.
The money was to be
transferred through crypto
accounts to avoid detection.
Now a new
development regarding
all the demonstrations...
Nanite Capital
executive Matt Turner...
...working
in conjunction with Europol,
were quick to respond.