[slow somber music]
[gulls squawking]
- [woman screaming] - [dramatic music]
- [ominous music] - [bell ringing]
[music continues]
- [Sally screaming] - [fast-paced music]
[bear growling]
[rats squeaking]
[Sally screaming]
[music continues]
[door slamming]
[horn honking]
[crashing]
I'm okay.
I'm okay. I'm awake.
Okay.
I'm awake and I'm alive.
I'm alive, awake.
I'm in my father's car.
I'm dead, he's gonna kill me.
[ominous music]
[car engine sputtering]
[water splashing]
Oh my god, a fallen cloud!
- [Sally screaming] - [fast-paced music]
[car engine sputtering]
[Sally screaming]
[music continues]
[screaming]
[upbeat eerie music]
[Stacy] There's nothing out there.
[Jim] Where's the bedrooms?
[Stacy] It's wild and it's lively.
It's wild and it's lively.
[Jim] l don't see anything, it's probably nothing.
Jesus, you scared me, scared--scared me.
[punk] Hey, dude!
[Mike] Nothing to worry about, right?
Right? Ri--right?
[Stacy] He's driving me crazy.
[David] ooh, l think l stepped on something.
[Janet] Like what, what, what, what?
[punk] Hey, dude!
[Jim] Catch those aliens for us.
[Stacy] Green eyes.
[Mike] You're gonna be eaten.
[Doreen] l don't like it here.
[punk] Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
[boy] Uh-oh.
[Mike] Did you see it?
Did you see it?
[Mike] Need a shave, you son of a [Censored]!
[Mike] Well that was a stupid thing to do!
[slow suspenseful music]
[boy] Uh-oh.
[ominous music]
[teacher] This was one of my favorite stories when l was your age.
So what'd you think of it?
l know you may not have gotten through all 11 pages,
after all l only gave you a week to read it.
Anybody get up to page four?
John? Darlene?
[faint snoring]
Here's a question I'm sure you can answer.
How long till Spring Break?
[students] 38 seconds!
That's good, you should all major in math,
but your assignment for this vacation is--
Listen up!
A 3,000 word composition on what you did this vacation.
Everyone hear that?
Repeat!
[students] A 3,000 word composition!
Topic?
[students] Vacation!
- [bell ringing] - [upbeat music]
- Dismissed. - [students cheering]
[upbeat music]
[indistinct singing]
Now let me get this straight.
It's a house in the woods,
with four bedrooms, a pond,
and nobody else for miles around?
- Sounds great! - Yeah, too great.
Does it have other things like water,
heat, electricity?
It has everything!
Come on, I've been there tons of times.
How about bathrooms? I've always been very fond of bathrooms.
- [speaks indistinctly] - How's the wildlife?
It's wild and it's lively. What do you want?
Great, let's get packed and get out of here. David.
- Yeah? - [Jim] Coming?
l don't think so.
- Here we go again. - No really, I'd like to.
- No you wouldn't. - Yes, l would, it's just that,
well, l promised Janet here we'd do a little work over the break.
All right, work over at the house.
No, you don't understand. Her parents are really conservative
and l just don't think it'd be a good idea.
Janet, would you like to come up?
Does she understand anything I'm saying?
Oh yes, l study English for a long time before l left Brazil.
[Jim] Great, would you like to come along to the house?
I'd love it. Am l invited?
No, we're playing with your head?
- [Janet] What? - [Stacy] Of course you're invited, Janet.
Nick, will you tell Mike to stop teasing her?
Great. David, she's coming, you?
Well, don't think it's gonna be a little crowded?
Not if you're on top.
What did he say?
Nothing, absolutely nothing.
Are you sure?
[upbeat music]
♪ Ooh a smooth operator
♪ A real red letter
♪ And a shoe fall down the street ♪
Whose are these?
These are the ugliest things I've ever seen in my life.
Okay.
I'm dying here, how much longer?
[Nick] About another six miles.
That's six too many.
Where's the food, honey pie?
Baby face.
Sugar tits.
Doreen.
[Doreen] Yes, darling dork.
Sweetie scum.
Needle dick.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Why sorry? l think that's cute.
David, why don't you say things like that to me?
[Mike] Stop the small talk, we got something interesting ahead.
Slow down.
[ominous music]
[man] l mean there's no body.
No proof the girl's dead.
[man 2] l mean, you saw that car,
what the hell hit that, an animal?
[man] A damn strong animal if it was.
She drives off the road and then gets attacked by something.
One hell of a night.
[indistinct radio chattering]
[man] Hey, l found some blood up there,
to the right.
Well, this was a fun vacation, Nick. Too bad we have to go home now.
Come on, you're not gonna let a little thing like that scare you, are you?
Yeah, wanna bet? Can we please go home?
Look, take the wheel rotate it--
Forget it, man, we've gone this far, we're going all the way.
You don't understand, we just went through a warning.
Don't forget, l have rented out every single
horror film on videotape, and what we just went through
was called a warning stage.
Come on, none of us girls are scared.
Are you?
What s this, peer pressure? ls that what we're talking about now?
Really, Mike, it's logically stupid for you to be worried by this.
"Logically stupid"?
ls that what you said? Logically stupid?
ls this the person representing brilliance on our trip?
Come on, let's go, let's go, let's go!
[Mike] Oh, here's mistake number one.
[eerie music]
[Nick] We're here.
[Jim] No [Censored].
Name a horror film. Any horror film.
l can think of about 10 right now.
What are you talking about?
This place is beautiful.
Oh yeah, wait till nightfall.
Well, l don't care what you think.
l just don't want to still be in this car at nightfall.
Now are we gonna stay in this car?
Because if we are, I'm about to fart.
[siren blaring]
You got alarm in this place? What good would that do?
We're talking my parents here.
l had nothing to do with this.
l was just 10-year-old kid coming up here on weekends.
Wow, this place is great.
[Nick] You like t?
Like it? This place s perfect.
Where's the bedrooms?
Upstairs.
[Mike[ You're just gonna act like nothing's happened?
Do you realize if an insane madman came around here
hunting for flesh that nobody could help us?
I'm talking emptiness here.
What about the phones?
l mean, we do have phones here, remember?
Oh yeah, l remember that.
Hello, help, someone!
There's a killer after us! Please come quick!
Oh, two-hour drive?
Yes we'll be here. l don't know how many pieces we' be in,
but we--we'll be here.
Don't you think that you are creating most of this in your head?
A girl drove off the road in a storm.
It happens every day.
[Mike] You know, Janet, you're right.
I'm jumping to conclusions and overreacting.
I'm just letting all the horror films I've ever watched get to me.
l should overcome my fears right now.
Why don't l take a nice stroll down that dirt path
into the woods late tonight all by myself
and then afterwards l can go skinny dipping in the pond,
and while I'm at it,
l can wave bright white flags around so everybody can see me.
Come on, David, he's hopeless.
Oh no, no, that's good.
Leave me alone out here, nothing to worry about, right?
[bush rustles]
That was probably just the wind blowing through the trees.
No, maybe, just maybe, it's something else.
l should investigate.
Fat chance.
Ow!
[ominous music]
[loud punk rock music]
[Censored] A.
This way.
[all laughing]
All right, it's skinny dipping time!
[kids cheering]
Hey, you think there's any snakes around here?
God, l hope so.
Molly's just right in there!
[girls cheering]
[fast rock music]
Nick.
Friends of yours?
[Nick] Hey! Hey, you guys!
Hello?
Hello!
Hey, dude!
What the hell are you doing?
What's it look like? We're skinny dipping!
l can see that.
We could all see that, but what are you doing here?
[speaks indistinctly]
We're here to make this summer rock!
[group cheering]
But what are you doing at my house?
House?
Isn't this the camp by the lake?
No, this is the house by the pond.
Oh, [Censored].
A house by the pond!
I'm sorry, man, we thought this was the camp by the lake!
We'll get out of here in a few minutes.
l told you to go left.
Nick, you ever heard of the words foreshadowing?
It's one word, Mike.
Oh good, thank you. I'll remember that when I'm getting my face ripped off.
Look, don't you know what just happened?
Those kids were born to be murder victims
and just paid us a visit.
Don't you realize the significance of that?
[ominous music]
[suspenseful music]
[funky music]
♪ You want it all
- ♪ You're free - ♪ You're free
♪ You're free
♪ And you'll be what you want to ♪
♪ Be what you want to
♪ Be what you want to be
♪ You're having such a good time ♪
♪ Living in your own life
♪ You're gonna feel just fine tonight ♪
♪ You're having such a good time ♪
♪ Living in your own life
♪ You're gonna feel just fine tonight ♪
♪ You're having such a good time ♪
We need water to boil.
Nick, you said the water pressure would be fine.
Well, I'm sure it's fine if you shower with Doreen.
Only Doreen would take a shower before dinner.
You said it.
Dinner time?
[Nick] Just about.
Looks like we need more wood for the fire.
Are the doors locked?
No, the doors are unlocked.
Good, at least we're playing it safe.
Do they at least creak a little bit for some warning when they open?
Nick, we need more wood for the fire.
[Nick] Yeah all right, I'll get to it in a second.
Nick, Nick.
You're going out there? Are you crazy?
Look, Nick, we've been friends for 10 years now.
If you go out there, you're... you're gonna be eaten.
Eaten?
Or decapitated or mangled.
Look, don't you realize where we are?
The Twilight Zone ?
Yeah, now that you mention it.
Look, Nick, I'm just trying to explain.
We're in the perfect situation--
Mike, look, l have watched just as many of those films,
only l can tell the difference between make-believe and reality.
Now come on, l don't mind your imagination,
but it's the others who are starting to get annoyed.
[Stacy] Nick l need some help in here.
Yeah, all right, I'll be with you in a second.
Look, do me a favor, go get some wood by the shed.
- It's getting dark. - l know that.
It's near the woods.
Yeah, l know that too.
Oh, you know everything, huh?
Well what's that?
[Nick] That's an Indian sweat lodge.
ls that an Indian sweat lodge over there?
Accord ng to Indian legend, those were used
by the Indian men to increase their sexual potency.
- That's great. - Mind if l go check that out?
Enjoy.
Nick.
[suspenseful music]
Jesus!
Doreen.
Jesus, you scared me.
Mm, how about a quick one?
No, it's dinner time.
Jimmy.
[Jim] Did l say no?
What the hell was going through my mind?
Okay. Yeah. I love you. Okay.
- [zipper whirs] - [Jim whispering indistinctly]
[light music]
Okay, before we start,
l would like to propose a toast to Nick
for making this vacation possible.
- I'll drink to that. - Love you, Nick.
And also, seriously,
l would like to propose a toast to Doreen.
For being so great in bed.
- [laughter] - Hear, hear!
- [cheering] - [Mike] Hear, hear!
Guys, let's eat.
- [indistinct chattering] - [laughter]
So Nick, did you get the wood for the fire?
No, Mike and l got into a little discussion.
- I'll get it after dinner. - A discussion?
About oh, horror films perhaps?
[Mike] No, about what has the potential of becoming
a horror film unless we do something about it quickly.
There is something out there. Don't listen to me though.
Go right ahead.
There's nothing out there.
Famous last words.
What about the girl who drove off the highway?
What about her?
She drove off the road and got knocked
semi-unconscious and wandered off
through the woods in a daze.
And her car?
Like they said, some animal.
Yeah, right, an animal.
Like a bunny rabbit, or raccoon, or an anteater.
No, l bet you up some giant grizzly bear devoured her
and then bashed in her car.
- Are there bears around here? - No, there are not.
No seriously!
What if one escaped from a zoo or a circus?
[everyone laughing]
What's so funny?
l could just see this great big bear
out on the front lawn with a little red hat and booties doing flips and headstands.
We maybe it's not trained.
[Jim] Well then l guess it falls down a lot whenever it tries to do a headstand.
[everyone laughing]
[Nick] You're right.
[ominous music]
All right, so, what do you think happened?
I'm still going back and forth.
It could be an ax murderer and an alien from outer space.
You're serious.
You really think there's something out there
waiting to kill us?
[loud clanking]
No, now it may be inside.
That came from the kitchen.
What if there is a bear?
[Nick] There isn't any bears!
- I'm gonna go check it out. - I'll go with ya.
Yeah, I'll stay here with the girls.
No thanks, I'll join you.
[Janet and David] Wait for us.
Wait a second, this is stupid. We're not a gonna go look.
What if it is a bear?
[Nick] It isn't a bear!
Look, see, no bear!
A pan fell off the counter.
That's where the rest of the chicken was.
[everyone] Ew.
What is all this green stuff all over the pan?
l thought that chicken tasted kind of funny.
Yeah, no more dinner for me.
I'll pass on seconds, really, thank you.
Thanks a lot, Nick.
Well, l didn't mean anything.
Look, it's there.
[Mike] Okay, so the chicken went away.
Now, are we going to assume it just threw up
some green slime and walked away,
or are we going to do the intelligent thing
and bolt and lock the windows and doors?
Mike's right, we should lock the place up.
What if it is a bear?
Ugh!
l got to get out of here.
Stace, you wanna go for a walk?
No, thanks. l have to clean up my green chicken.
What, you're mad at me now?
Just do your own cooking from now on.
So, are we having a good time?
- [Doreen] Mm-hm. - What next?
[Jim and Doreen giggling]
Would you like to go walk outside with me, David?
l think it's getting a little dark out.
You're right, it's very dark out.
It's getting really dark, you better not go.
It's not safe. It's not safe.
I'm sure you can get a flashlight.
Nope, no flashlights. Look, you don't have one, l don't have one,
they don't have one. There's none in the house.
- I'm sorry it's just-- - I brought my pen flashlight.
That makes sense.
You're actually going.
You're actually going outside.
We've had warnings, murder attempts,
and you're going out for a walk in the woods.
l don't actually call a disappearing raw chicken a murder attempt.
- Well, l do. - l heard that.
So, what about you two?
How about a nice dip in the pond?
[loud clanking]
I'm sorry, all right?
I'm sorry, l didn't mean it.
It's not that, it's your friend, Mike.
- He's driving me crazy. - Shh.
He's going to ruin the whole vacation.
No, he's not, he's gonna help keep it from getting boring.
Come on, he's a really nice guy once you get to know him.
l don't want to get to know him.
l fee sorry for those who know him.
Nick, he has no life.
He likes to watch horror films, all right?
He is a horror film.
A walking, talking horror film.
You never know, one might come in handy.
[David] Can you believe Mike?
l mean, talk about overreacting over nothing.
Forget him.
l want to tell story l recently heard.
It's supposed to be a horror story or something like that.
Well, we got the right location for it.
[ominous music]
[Janet] It's not intelligent.
l didn't think it would be, but go ahead.
Okay, there were these two--two teenagers
out on a date, they drove into the woods to make out.
You mean intercourse.
Right.
They park by the road
and they packed a blanket,
they laid it out in an open field.
They start to get undressed
until they noticed that something was watching them.
They were too preoccupied?
[Janet] Right.
They just started to notice this.
And it start to approach them.
They were rolling around in the grass
and this thing got closer and closer.
Wait a second.
You mean to tell me that these two idiots
wouldn't notice a monster if it was right on top of them?
l told you it wasn't a realistic story.
So suddenly the girl open her eyes.
Oh, she'd been in too much [indistinct], right?
Whatever.
[dramatic music]
[screaming] Are you all right?
Damn fallen branch.
Where did the flashlight go?
Behind those bushes.
Oh wait, l think l see it. No, that's not it.
l think l see t.
So how does this story end?
Oh, it kills them.
l got it!
Ooh, l think l stepped on something.
Like what?
- [both screaming] - [fast-paced music]
[monster screeching]
[thuds]
Mike, l don't want to get rough.
We're going for a swim.
Why don't you put a sign on your chest that says, "victim"?
Come on, use your brains for a second.
David and Janet haven't made it back yet.
They've been gone 10 minutes
and they can take care of themselves.
Oh sure, I'd call a penlight enough protection against anything.
Okay then, after our swim we'll go look for them.
- Good? - Fine, you're gonna make one major [Censored] up,
why not go all the way?
Hey Doreen, what about the bear?
- That's right, Jim, what if there's a-- - [Jim] Shut up, Mike!
There--there are no big animals out there, Doreen.
And we're going for a swim.
Big animals hate the water.
- Not sharks. - Are there sharks? Sharks?
- Goodbye, Mike! - Did somebody say sharks?
- Nick. - Don't say anything, would you?
l just got her calmed down.
Now we're gonna go to bed, all right? Goodnight.
- But, Nick-- - Goodnight.
Guard the house, ol' buddy.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I'm al alone.
I'm all alone.
Holy [Censored].
[fast-paced music]
[indistinct singing]
[hammer tapping]
[Jim and Doreen giggling]
Jimmy.
You know l don't have my swimsuit on.
We'll get there.
[Jim laughing]
I'm not going in if it's cold.
I'm not!
[Jim] It's not cold! [laughs]
Oh, [Censored]!
- [laughing] - How is it?
How is it really?
Hurry up, it's good.
- Come on in. - ls it cold?
- Come on! - [Doreen screaming]
Can't believe I'm doing this.
[slow romantic music]
You just going to lie there and watch?
Just enjoying the view.
Yeah, you and everybody else.
Start your own strip show.
This ain't a solo number.
[Nick] All right.
[thuds]
[Stacy] Oh, you're so sexy Nick.
Hey, l meant to do this.
Thought it might be a nice change
if we would start on the floor and then
work our way up to the bed.
Yeah, well I'm not fond of back problems,
so I'll be on the bed whenever you're ready.
[Stacy giggling]
[ominous music]
[Jim] Come on in!
- [Doreen shrieks] - [Jim laughing]
"Not cols"? "Not cold"? What are you, crazy?
You're so exaggerative.
We'll stick together and get warm.
Okay.
Stop shivering.
[ominous music]
- [metal clanking] - What was that!
[Jim] What was what?
- Come on! - What was it?
l don't see anything, it was probably nothing.
Just a raccoon, forget about t.
Maybe you should go and check and see.
I'm naked in the pool trying to keep warm.
I'm not going looking for fuzzy little animals!
Well, what if it's not a fuzzy animal?
Oh, you bet your ass I'm not going out there.
[Doreen] But Jim, Jim, what if it's a--
Don't stay bear, okay?
No bear.
- All right. - I'm sorry l ever brought up the subject.
l don't like it here. It's cold.
It's dark.
It's wet.
Yes, wet.
Besides,
wouldn't you rather be in front of a nice, roaring fire drying off?
l suppose a place where we're warmer wouldn't hurt.
[Doreen] No, in fact, it would help a lot.
♪ The queen was so right
♪ But the king was too shy
♪ And you were my noble princess ♪
♪ See, l was your guest
♪ From far away
♪ Afraid to be wakened
♪ l came through the clouds
♪ Flying over the meadows
♪ Feeling so free
Well, I'm not gonna have to worry about getting any sleep tonight.
[loud clanking]
[Jim] Well, it's a good thing the back door was open
or we'd have been stuck out there all night.
Looks like everybody went to bed.
That's right.
The fire's all ours.
[ominous music]
[doorknob clanking]
[slow romantic music]
♪ Oh
♪ I'm happy in my dreamland
[ominous music]
[squelching]
[triumphant music]
[bed creaking]
[Doreen moaning]
[Doreen] Hurry.
[Jim] l can't get my shoes.
My buckle is stuck.
[Doreen] Jimmy. Jimmy, it's okay.
Here, let me try.
[Jim] l can't get the [Censored]... My zipper's stuck.
l can't get my zipper.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa.
[Doreen moaning]
[Jim] l got it.
[monster growling]
[Doreen screaming]
[dramatic music]
[Mike screaming]
[Jim coughing]
What the [Censored] are you doing?
Did you see it? Did you see it?
l see you.
You're determined to ruin this evening for me aren't you?
You think you're funny coming down here
looking like one of those insane killers?
No, it's for protection!
Protection?
I'll show you protection!
[Jim screaming]
[objects clattering]
Are you all right?
Oh, [Censored].
[both grunting, yelling]
[both screaming]
Did you hear something?
[Jim and Mike screaming]
[Jim laughing]
[Jim screaming]
[Mike] Are you all right?
[Mike grunts]
[Jim screaming]
[loud thudding]
Now l know l heard something.
[Jim] I'll kill you, you son of a [Censored]!
[both grunting]
Jim, no, there was this disgusting, weird, slimy thing!
Yeah, that's you!
[Jim yelling]
What the hell's going on here?
[Jim groaning]
This asshole comes down here
looking like Friday the 13th trying to scare us!
- There was this thing! - What thing, Mike?
[dramatic music]
- [Doreen screaming] - [thudding]
Doreen? Doreen!
- What's in there? - That's the basement.
You're going down in a dark basement alone?
[Jim] [Censored], the light's out.
Doreen. Doreen.
Can you move? ls anything broken?
[Doreen] I don't think so.
Oh, my head.
I don't think you broke your head.
How'd you fall?
Something pulled me.
[Mike] Ah-ha, l told you!
It's an alien from outer space.
Shut the [Censored] up, Mike.
Let's get her upstairs, okay?
[whispers] Just take it easy.
Where do you think you're going?
[Stacy] I'm looking for another light down here.
Oh good, if you see the creature, give him my best.
Look, just because you've got some unbalanced
mental problems, that's no reason to make us all suffer.
We came here to have a good time
and you're putting us through hell.
Now, for the last time, there are no crazy aliens or killers around.
They're not down here, outside,
upstairs in the bedrooms, the bathrooms, or the kitchen!
[cat yowling, hissing]
Here's your alien, Mike.
A nice, scared, little pussy cat.
What beautiful green eyes.
l thought l saw something green eyes.
Well, that's it then.
You must have tripped over the cat.
Where did it come from?
There's nothing up here but ceiling.
l love how these animals just fall out of nowhere right into your hands.
And what do they do, just hang up there by claws
and wait for people to pass by?
Oh, Mike, l almost forgot.
[Mike grunting] Wouldn't wanna forget that.
[Jim laughs]
Goodnight, Mike, catch those aliens for us.
[laughs]
[Nick] Wait, wait, wait.
You can't lock him down there all night.
[Jim] Why not? Let him come to his senses.
Maybe he'll realize there aren't any monsters
and we can enjoy the rest of this vacation.
Yeah, he deserves a small punishment.
We'll let him out in the morning.
One night down there is not gonna kill him.
All right, come on, let's just get Doreen up to bed.
l got you.
[Jim] Goodnight, Mike!
What, are they kidding?
Hey, hey!
You can't leave me down here!
Hey!
[object clattering]
Oh, [Censored].
[monster screeching]
[fast-paced music]
Active imagination, huh?
Very active.
Okay, deep [Censored]. Deep shit.
Slightly better than a flashlight.
[gasps]
[monster screeches]
[fast suspenseful music]
[grunting]
[monster screeching]
[glass shattering]
[slow pleasant music]
Good morning!
What's for breakfast?
Whatever you want,
as long as you can make it.
- How's Doreen? - Her head still hurts.
Let her rest a day.
Hey, hey.
[Jim] That's good.
- Oh my god! - What?
Green eggs?
[Jim laughing]
[groans] Great.
- Hi, Jim. - Hi, Nick.
- What happened to you? - It was on the rake.
It looks like some of that green stuff that was on the chicken last night.
[Stacy] All right, you guys,
just keep it up and see what happens.
I'm not getting any water now.
No water, what about my shower?
l don't know. l guess I'll have to go look at the pipes in the base--
Oh, [Censored].
We forgot about Mike in the basement.
We did?
What the hell happened down here?
Mike!
He must have gotten out.
How? The door was still locked.
[Jim] There's a broken window over there.
Oh, where'd he go?
Well, wait a minute,
has anybody seen David or Janet since last night?
Look, their bed wasn't even slept n.
Now what is going on here?
- What if Mike-- - That's it, that explains it.
What?
Revenge.
Mike's revenge.
Come on, we lock him up,
so he destroys the pipes
and starts his little game.
And pretends to disappear,
gets David and Janet to join along,
and now we're supposed to be all scared and worried
until they jump out and say, "Boo."
All right, if that's the way they're gonna play it then--
- We ignore them. - Yeah, right.
Except now l have drive into town and get those pipes fixed.
And I'm not paying for this.
Okay, and it's gonna take me a while.
l gotta drive into town to find the plumber my parents use.
God dammit! You know, this could take me all day!
Hopefully when l get back,
Mike's wonderful little game will be over
and we can finally get on with the rest of this vacation.
I'll see you later.
Yeah, right.
Well, no shower.
Looks like it's time for a swim.
Good idea, I'll get my suit and join you.
♪ Chime one at a time
♪ And then the second you chime ♪
♪ Comin' right down the line
♪ Oh, babe, you gotta believe it ♪
- [indistinct singing] - [window whirring]
[ominous music]
[Jim] Can you believe Mike?
l mean, he just won't quit.
l mean, first the monsters and then the disappearances.
l mean, what does he think we are?
A bunch of morons?
I'm sure you'll be okay in a couple hours.
- [Doreen screaming] - [fast-paced music]
[whooshing]
[monster growling]
[music continues]
[monster screeching]
[glass shattering]
[monster growling]
[music continues]
- You're alive! - Oh, you're quick!
Nice bikini. Believe me now?
What s it?
Oh, what is it?
Well, looks like what we've got there
is a big, green, slimy thing with very large teeth. Good description?
- How many are left? - How many what?
Our friends. The people we came up here with, remember them?
David and Janet haven't come back yet.
l scratched them off long ago. What about Doreen and Jim?
That thing was with them, but I'm not sure if they're dead.
Oh, not sure. Well, there are a couple of clues.
Were their bodies in more than one piece?
Any big holes through them?
Those are usually sure indications--
- [snapping] - [dramatic music]
[monster screeching]
I've got you, you ugly [Censored]!
We've gotta get out of here!
[Mike] Back to the house!
[monster screeching]
- Where? - Some place it doesn't know.
My room.
[music continues]
What about Jim and Doreen?
Well, where are they?
[ominous music]
Napping?
Doreen.
[Doreen screaming] What happened?
What happened?!
She's fine, thanks a lot.
Take her to my room.
- [ominous music] - [monster growling]
[groaning] Oh, god.
[ominous music]
[fast-paced music]
- [monster screeching] - [Stacy screaming]
[Stacy] Doreen! [screams]
Oh, that's disgusting.
[girls screaming]
[monster screeching]
[Doreen screams]
That won't work, it's gonna smash through.
It can chew the lock right off.
Oh, yeah?
[suspenseful music]
[monster screeching]
That ought to stop him for now, nobody likes a mouth full of shaving cream.
- Are you two all right? - What the hell is going on?
What is that thing?
What is it? Well, take your pick.
Mutant baby, an alien that's been in the snow
for 2,000 years, a genetic monster created by
some crazy scientists.
What difference does t make?
We either have to find a way out of here or figure out how to kill it.
What is he talking about?
Where's Jim?
Jim's in the other room melting right now.
- ls he dead? - Yes, melting is another indication of death, I'm sure.
What is going on?
Where did that thing come from?
l really don't think its historical background
is that important right now. We have to get out of here,
but I'll tell you from experience,
it's a most a ways impossible to leave.
What do you mean almost always?
ln all the movies.
For crying out loud, will you stop it?
Look, we are talking about reality here, not make-believe.
Well, let me tell you something, that creature out there is not reality!
[Stacy] So you're saying we're in a movie.
It's a distinct possibility.
What has happened to Jim?
His skin's turning into Silly Putty.
That thing pumped tons of that green chicken slime into him.
[Stacy] You know, what is that stuff?
It was on the chicken pan.
l found some on the pond this morning,
Nick found some on the rake outside now.
But it's not all over the house.
Eating.
That's it, it must have been after you
and Jim in the pond last night.
That stuff has got to be part of its digestive system.
Well, you know, people have saliva to break down food,
this thing must have green slime.
So it must have been getting Jim ready for...lunch.
- Oh, god. - [Mike] Making his insides juicier.
Shut up, shut up!
You're disgusting!
Well, we have to figure this thing out if we're gonna kill it!
And the next question is why didn't it slime you two?
[birds chirp ng]
What are you talk ng about?
Well, when it attacked me, l noticed some of the slime.
It pumped Jim with it.
But when it attacked you and pulled you into the basement last night, no slime.
It just had both of you in the hall a minute ago, no slime.
So maybe it wants you for something else.
Like what?
Reproduction.
Oh, no, that's sick.
Actually, it did seem like it was trying--
What are we talk ng about here?
Those things that pop out of your stomach
when you least expect it?
Yes, yes, that's it! You've seen some of these too!
But that means there could be more than one by now.
The girl who drove off the road two days ago.
Oh hell, there could have been an army of Girl Scouts on a nature walk.
There might be hundreds of them.
Where's Janet? What has happened to Janet?
Janet, where's Janet?
[Janet] Help!
Somebody help me!
Help me!
We've got to warn her! Why won't this open?
Because l nailed it shut yesterday.
Well then get something! Smash it!
All right, fine, look out.
[glass shattering]
Are you try ng to kill me?
Janet, get away from the house!
There's something here!
l can't!
l can't walk!
Janet, get up!
We've got to get to her before that thing does.
That thing may have already gotten to her.
We don't know that. We've got to help her!
We don't know anything about that creature
except it, like everyone else,
hates a mouth full of shaving cream!
Then grab the bottle and let's go.
We don't have any chance in this condition!
- I'm going. - Me too!
Great, this thing's gonna have itself an orgy.
- l don't see it. - l don't see it.
- It's okay. - It's okay.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
What creature?
David's dead.
[Doreen] Don't worry, Janet, we've got you.
[Janet crying]
Now where are you going? We have to get her upstairs!
[dramatic music]
- What the--? - [ominous music]
[glass shattering]
[groans]
Doreen, Doreen snap out of it!
[growling]
[Janet screaming]
[screaming, growling continue]
[music continues]
[Stacy screaming]
[Mike] Need a shave, you son of a [Censored]?
[monster screeching]
[ominous music]
[indistinct], huh?
[suspenseful music]
[glass shattering]
[somber music]
Well l guess that'll teach her not to start with you again.
Punishment seems a little strict, but what do l know?
l had to!
It was controlling her!
It shot green rays from its eyes and l looked away!
l guess Doreen didn't.
Okay, so if you look into its eyes
during a green ray, it can control your mind
when it wants to.
Oh wonderful, this thing hasn't missed a trick.
Controls minds, eats people, reproduces.
The car.
We can leave in the car!
[mouthing words]
Where's the car?
Nick took it to town to get the plumber.
Well, that was a stupid thing to do!
[laughs] Plumber!
Sure, gotta get those pipes fixed!
l mean, we're just dying around here.
[sighs] All right, think.
It went up to the roof,
we go to the basement.
Come on, get some flashlights.
l tell ya, if this thing came out on Halloween it'd have a hell of a time.
Oh god.
The floor feels like mud.
That's because it is mud.
Dirt and water make mud.
You learn something new every day, don't you?
The door doesn't lock from this side.
Well, that makes sense.
Why would somebody want to lock themselves in a basement?
All right, don't start.
All right, get some hammer and nails,
l gotta lock it from the other side
and come back in through the window.
You're going out there?
No, I'm gonna mentally will everything to happen.
What a stupid question!
You always ask the stupidest questions!
[door locking]
[ominous music]
[fast-paced music]
[rat squeaking]
[ominous music]
[Stacy screaming]
ls someone paying you to stand in front
of an open window or is that your own idea?
Hey, there's some razor blades in the corner you can play with next.
Would you like to do that?
- Look, Mike-- - Let's get this window boarded up first, hmm, please?
- Give me that one. - [Stacy] That one doesn't fit.
That one don't fit either.
- How 'bout this one? - The short one.
Oh, that's nice. Give me a nail.
Ouch, [Censored]! Ow!
Never mind.
- [Stacy] So, uh-- - Give me another one.
You know what keeps coming to mind?
Invasion of the Body Snatchers.
- Yeah? - Yeah, well, l mean, mind control,
birth cycle, high-pitched scream.
So, how did they kill 'em in that one?
- They didn't. - Great.
[somber music]
Are we just gonna stay down here all night?
l mean, shouldn't we think of a plan?
A plan, what a wonderful idea. What'd you have in mind?
l don't know. Look, you're the expert in this field.
Well, the problem is we don't know too much about this thing.
It doesn't react to water
and shaving cream is on its 10 best dishes list.
Well,
um, what about fire?
Maybe we could burn t.
Fire would be hard to come by down here.
But we could kill it with a gun or a big ax.
- Would that work? - Why not?
It's just a slimy, green, fleshy thing.
Seems to get hurt pretty easily.
ln fact, I'm not sure if it's that intelligent.
It smacked itself headfirst into the wall
last night after l got out.
It hit itself in the face with a hammer.
Tell you the truth, l think that thing's pretty stupid.
Wait a second, maybe that's it.
Well, if we can confuse that thing enough
that it beats the crap out of itself,
then we can get close enough to it with an ax or something.
Yeah.
[car approaching]
[horn honking]
Never mind, let's get out of here!
We locked ourselves in here!
We did, didn't we?
All right, let's get the planks off.
Hey Mike, the plumber's gonna be here in 10 minutes!
And guess who's paying for it!
What the hell is he talking about?
Oh, he thinks you broke the pipes and-- [gasps]
Wait!
He doesn't know about the creature!
He's gonna walk right into the thing!
- [Censored]! - We've got to stop him!
What the [Censored]?
He's in the house!
Was that comment really necessary?
That is it, guys!
Come on, the game is over!
You cannot come in here and destroy my house!
Janet.
- [fast-paced music] - [monster growling]
[monster growling]
[cat meowing]
[monster screeching]
[triumphant music]
Wait! We gotta get Nick!
- Well, where the hell did he go? - [Nick grunts]
Oh.
- Come on! - What the hell?
[Mike] No questions, time to leave!
[suspenseful music]
- What about the others? - Dead.
Look, just remember three rules.
Don't ever look into its eyes, beware of the green slime,
and whatever you do, don't ever...
try to kiss it.
[Censored], get us out of here!
[tires screeching]
Would you like me to drive?
- [loud banging] - [all screaming]
[Stacy] Get us out of here!
[dramatic music]
[Mike] Look away, don't look at its eyes!
House. House, house, house, house!
[monster screeching]
Bench, bench, bench, bench, bench, bench!
[Censored]!
[lasers shooting]
[monster screeching]
Pond, pond, pond, pond, pond, pond!
[loud splashing]
[ominous music]
[Mike] Okay, everybody out.
Nick, you didn't get your license, did you?
What the hell is going on here? You [Censored] crazy?
- [dramatic music] - [monster screeching]
[Nick] Holy [Censored]!
What now?
Back to the house!
[fast-paced music]
All right, we have to confuse it. Stacy, my coat.
What are you doing?
This is not a question and answer period, Nick, it's time to do.
Now we need all the mirrors in this house,
lightbulbs, and more flashlights.
Well come on, let's go!
[determined music]
What's this pile of goop on the floor?
I'll tell you later, just come down here.
[music continues]
Hey, l don't have a flashlight.
Stacy, give him yours.
It doesn't work.
It does now.
[suspenseful music]
Okay, places.
[monster crunching]
[ominous music]
[determined music]
- [glass shattering] - [monster screeching]
[ominous music]
[monster hissing]
- [glass shattering] - [monster growling]
[glass shattering]
[monster growling]
[suspenseful music]
[monster screeching]
[whispering] Where is it?
- [dramatic music] - [Stacy screaming]
[monster screeching]
[oven exploding]
[screaming] Get it off! Get it off! Get it off!
Oh, my god!
Get it off!
[Stacy screams]
[monster screeching]
She looked into its eyes!
What?
[Nick grunt ng]
Nick, will you help me here for a second?!
Will you help me for a sec?!
Oh god, l can't, she's crushing my balls!
- [monster screeching] - [indistinct shouting]
[monster exploding]
[triumphant music]
[somber music]
[electricity crackling]
[Mike] What the hell are you doing?
One more broken thing's not gonna make any difference.
- [glass shattering] - [alarm blaring]
What is that?
You guys remember that alarm system?
- Yeah. - It's hooked up directly to the police station.
They'll be here in about 30 minutes.
You mean all we had to do all this time
was set off that goddamn alarm
and police with real weapons would have been
all over this place in a half an hour?
You son of a [Censored].
Stop! Stop, wait!
l need help, please.
Thank god, please help me.
[Nick] Well sure, hop on in.
[Sally] Thanks.
Thank you.
- Thank you, thank you. - [Mike] What happened?
God, l had a car accident.
Next thing l know, I'm laying in the woods somewhere.
God, l must have been wandering around the woods for a day.
Um, how do you feel?
Um, a little dizzy and my stomach is hurting me.
Oh [Censored], her stomach hurts, Nick.
Mike, look, we don't know.
We have no proof.
Oh, proof, huh?
So, um...
Sally, Sally Foster.
So Sally...
Yeah.
Had any kinky sex lately?
What are you talking about?
What's wrong with everybody?
Your eyes are green!
Yes, l know, they've been that way since l was baby.
Why, don't you like green?
[upbeat music]
♪ So
♪ So and so
♪ The morning comes after
- ♪ So and so - ♪ The moon hits the sack
- ♪ So and so - ♪ The brink of disaster
♪ Sleeps
- ♪ So and so - ♪ It walks in the daylight
♪ So and so
♪ It lights up the dark ♪
- ♪ So and so - ♪ We all get to play so
♪ Deep
♪ So what
♪ What does it matter
♪ What can it mean
♪ So what
♪ It's all so so so
♪ So we dream, dream, dream
♪ Dream of
♪ So and so
- ♪ So and so - ♪ The dream keeps a-coming
- ♪ So and so - ♪ The kind of face you like ♪
- ♪ So and so - ♪ The spectral is another
♪ Hand
- ♪ So and so - ♪ The lover makes an entrance ♪
♪ So and so
♪ She sent those in my void
- ♪ So and so - ♪ She rots in the other
♪ Side
♪ So what
♪ What does it matter
♪ What can it mean
♪ So what
♪ It's all so so so
♪ So we dream, dream, dream, dream ♪
♪ So
♪ l said so what
♪ What does it matter ♪
♪ So what
♪ What can it mean
♪ So what ♪
♪ It's all so so so
♪ So we dream, dream, dream, dream, oh ♪
♪ So and so
♪ So what
♪ So and so ♪
♪ So and so
♪ So what
♪ So so so what
♪ So and so
♪ So what
♪ So so so what
♪ So and so
♪ So what
[funky music]