[watch ticking]
[ticking continues]
[ticking intensifies]
["Ruler Of My Heart" playing]
[shopkeeper bell jingles]
- Morning.
[exhales sharply]
[clicking tongue]
- Looking for something?
- [person blows raspberries] Yeah.
A hardcover
of Their Eyes Were Watching God.
Hardcover? Yeah. I think we have one.
[sighs]
- Thanks.
- [chuckles]
You know, uh, I actually haven't read
much Hurston. [stammers]
Yeah, she's great.
Um, it's actually a gift for my professor.
Oh, okay. You're a student.
Mm-hmm. Getting my PhD.
- Oh. Wow. [chuckles]
- [laughs]
- Columbia? NYU?
- NYU.
Nice. What's your, um... [smacks lips]
What's your thesis topic?
- [music plays on radio]
- "Redefining Radicalism:
The Rise of Black Feminism
in American Literature."
Oh, wow. [chuckling]
- [laughing]
- That's a mouthful.
- How's that going?
- Slowly. Very slowly.
Oh, yeah?
- [radio host] Irma Thomas…
- Well, I'm impressed.
…"Ruler of my Heart" on WNYC.
[shopkeeper] Um, that'll be 15 even.
- …New York public radio.
- Thank you.
- I'm John Schaefer…
- [cash register beeping]
…and if the soul queen of New Orleans
couldn't lighten the mood,
maybe Duke Ellington will.
Here's his classic version
of "In a Sentimental Mood,"
featuring John Coltrane.
Um, there's actually this
little Japanese restaurant on Mott Street.
Uh…
If you're not doing anything later,
dinner's on me.
[laughs] Sorry.
[laughs] Um…
No. That's... [stammers]
- You probably have a boyfriend.
- No, I don't. I'm… [stutters] …I'm single.
I'm-I'm single,
and I kinda like being single.
Oh, yeah. No, I-I-I totally get that.
[chuckles]
- [beeping]
- Uh, your card's not going through.
I must've maxed it out again.
- Let me see if I have enough cash.
- [chuckles] It's fine. It's fine.
You know what?
Actually just, um, take the book.
No, I couldn't.
- What if someone else came in looking...
- They can order it online. [chuckles]
Or whatever. I-It's fine.
You can come back and pay for it later.
- Thank you. I... [chuckles]
- Yeah.
- I promise I'll be back with the money.
[inhales sharply] Thank you.
- Bye.
- See ya.
[shopkeeper bell jingles]
You probably have a boyfriend.
[sniffs] Idiot.
"Probably have a boyfriend."
- Hi. Remember me?
- Hey.
Yeah. [chuckles]
Uh, got your money.
Oh, you didn't have to do that today.
I didn't wanna leave you hanging.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm. [inhales deeply]
- [shopkeeper] Uh…
- Just keep the change.
- Okay. Thanks.
- [chuckles]
Okay. Uh, well. See ya.
- All right. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Have a good one.
- You too.
- Hey. [chuckles]
- Hello. [chuckles]
So, remember this morning
when you asked me out to dinner?
- Oh, yeah. I-I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
- Oh! No, no, no.
I... I actually wanted to say yes.
[chuckles] I was standing there
thinking how nice it would be
if this guy asked me out,
and right as I thought it, you did.
And I...
I don't know. I panicked.
You panicked?
I panicked. [chuckles]
I'm Sandra.
Tom.
Nice to meet you, Tom.
Nice to meet you.
- So, Mott Street?
- Yeah. If that... Yeah.
- Okay. Yeah. Okay.
- This way.
Uh…
- You... After you. Yeah.
- All right. [chuckles]
- [laughs]
- I... I have my bag.
No, I do too. It's getting kind of cold.
[speaks indistinctly]
- That...
- Sorry… [indistinct]
- Backpack buddies.
- Buddies. [laughs]
[Tom] Yeah, and, like,
what have I gotten myself into?
You know?
Like, a short story is one thing.
- A novel, that's, like, 300 pages and...
- I know. And sometimes more.
Exactly. And, you know, here they are
offering me real money, you know?
I have to deliver something.
- So, what'd you do?
- I-I had a year-long panic attack, and I…
- [chuckles]
- …I wrote this book that was terrible.
Come on. [laughs]
I'm sure it wasn't that bad.
No, no, it was bad. It was... It was awful.
They wouldn't publish it.
Ouch.
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
No, it's fine. I... You know,
at least I got to keep the advance.
Do you still write?
No. Not really.
You know, all-all this happened
around the time that my mom died, and...
I don't know, I-I...
Things got dark for me,
and I kinda just gave up.
My parents died when I was a kid.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Must've been tough.
Anyway, um, yeah.
I started managing the bookstore.
That kinda pulled me out
of my depression, or whatever.
And… [inhales deeply]
…yeah, it takes up most of my time.
Must be nice being surrounded
by books all day.
- It's the best.
- [laughs]
After my parents passed,
my brother and I hopped
from one foster family to the next.
One point,
we were staying with this couple
that had this great collection of novels.
And one night, I started reading
Jane Eyre, and-and here was this character
that was, sort of, going through
everything I was going through.
And I didn't want it to end.
I finished it, went back to page one
and started reading it all over again.
Just loved books ever since.
Jane Eyre, huh?
Jane Eyre.
Can I show you something?
[shopkeeper bell jingles]
[Sandra giggles]
Oh. [chuckles]
Oh, my God.
- Is this a first edition?
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
Is this real?
This is real.
How can I be sure?
["I Won't Let You Down" playing]
[laughs]
I mean, some of these professors
are so obnoxious.
Actually used the phrase
"the vaginization of German literature."
- The what?
- I mean, I'm pretty sure
- "vaginization" isn't even a real word.
- [laughs]
[Tom] Where'd you learn how to cook?
[Sandra] I spent my junior year
in Florence.
[Tom, in Italian] Do you speak Italian?
[Sandra] I used to speak it well,
- now it's a bit rusty, unfortunately.
- [Tom, in English] Hello!
- [Sandra] Hello!
- [Tom, in Italian] Did you like Italy?
[laughs]
[Sandra] I have great memories.
[Tom, in English] This is amazing!
[Sandra, in Italian] But, I had
this boyfriend who was a real jerk.
- [bites]
- [laughs]
And what about you?
Where did you learn to speak Italian?
My mom was from Italy.
- And I watch a lot of Fellini movies.
- [Sandra] Oh, I love Fellini.
[laughs]
Have you ever had your heart broken?
[Tom] Uh… [chuckles] …yeah, once or twice.
I really like you.
Okay.
I really like you too.
- [person] Just hear me out.
- [Sandra] No, just... No, I can't.
- [person] I need your help.
- I'm not doing this.
- What do you mean you're not doing this?
- [Sandra] I can't.
[person] It's me and you.
It's me and you against the world,
- do you remember that?
- Can you please just go?
- It's me and you against the world.
- Jason, I need you to stop.
Please, I need you. Don't walk out
on me. You are the last thing that I have
- on this earth. You are the last person...
- Jason!
- [Jason yelps, bangs on door] Sandra!
- Jason, please don't.
[Jason banging on door] Sandra!
- Just go. Just go.
- Please.
[Jason] Please open the door.
Sandra, Sandra, open the door.
Fuck! Fuck!
Fucking bitch.
[Jason descending stairs]
- [Tom] Are you okay?
- [inhales sharply, breathing shakily]
Who was that?
It's my brother. He needs money.
[breathing shakily]
Jason wasn't so lucky.
Some of the homes he was put in were…
a nightmare.
It's not your fault.
[sighs]
I know, but he's the only family I got.
[inhales sharply]
"All happy families are alike."
- [sighs] And all that.
- [chuckles]
No matter how many times
he screws me over, I can't not help him.
He's my brother. I love him.
[people] ♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Tom ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- Yay. Okay, you gotta blow. Blow here.
- [guests laughing]
- [applause]
- [guest 1] You gotta blow harder. Come on.
[guest 2] Harder. Come on.
Yes! Yes! Yes! We got it. We got it.
[guest 3] So, how long have you known Tom?
Just a few weeks.
- Seems like so much longer.
- Yeah, I know. It's been kind of intense.
She's like a sexy librarian or something.
[chuckles]
- She's... She's literally your dream girl.
- I know. She's just incredible.
- Where did you go to undergrad?
- Uh, Vassar.
Oh, my God. [laughs] So did I.
You know, I thought you looked familiar.
When did you graduate?
Class of '14.
Class of '16.
Did you hang out at the Mug a lot?
Uh, honestly, I spent most of my time
at the library. [laughs]
But don't tell Tom. I'm trying to maintain
the illusion I'm not a total nerd.
[friend]
Glad to see that you're doing okay.
You were in a bad place there, so…
I was just a little depressed.
Uh…
Okay. It got bad but, you know, it's like,
who hasn't been borderline suicidal
at some point in their life?
It's not funny.
Not supposed to joke about that stuff.
- Come on. Come on.
- [laughs] Okay, you're right.
But, um… [smacks lips] …I'm good now.
You know, like, I'm great, actually.
It was pretty great. Um, yeah,
we actually met in the bookstore.
[laughs]
Hi.
How come we always come back to my place?
What do you mean?
I wanna see where you live. [chuckles]
It's, uh...
It's kind of uncomfortable there.
Well, my place
isn't exactly the Four Seasons. [chuckles]
No, it's not that. It's, um,
I live with my dad
and his new wife, and, uh…
My dad and I don't really get along.
Um…
he thinks I'm a disappointment.
"All happy families are alike."
And all that, right?
Anyways, uh, he's really sick, so…
Sorry he's sick.
It's okay.
But you're not a disappointment.
[chuckles]
[door buzzing]
[knocks on door]
Sandra?
Hey.
Are you okay?
You're not, um...
You're not returning my texts.
I'm sorry.
My brother's in trouble.
He owes them money,
so they cracked three of his ribs,
broke his cheekbone.
Said if he didn't pay up,
they'd come back and finish the job.
How much does he owe them?
Paying them back is not an option.
- So, what is an option?
- I give him money, and he runs.
Okay. So, say he runs,
and they can't find him.
Who do you think
they're gonna come looking for to collect?
Me? No, they don't even know I exist.
- Are you sure?
- [sighs] I'm not sure of anything.
- You have to pay them off.
- I told you that's not possible.
- How much do they want?
- $350,000.
And they want it in four days,
so short of robbing a bank,
that's just not gonna happen.
I can give you the money.
- What?
- It's in the bank.
I can just go make a withdrawal.
You wouldn't have to…
[inhales sharply] …rob it.
I-I don't understand.
[stammers] You live at home.
- You... You work in a bookstore.
- No, I own a bookstore.
How do you think I manage to keep it open?
All that place does is lose money.
You're saying you have that money
just sitting in a bank?
Yeah. More. Yeah. My father has money.
Why is this
the first time I'm hearing about this?
Why does that matter?
Maybe I didn't want you to know.
Well, honestly, it's kinda fucked up
- that you didn't say anything.
- Are you kidding me?
- I'm telling you that I can help you.
- I can't take your money.
- Why not?
- Because it's $350,000. That's why.
I appreciate the offer. I really do.
But let's face it,
we're practically strangers.
First of all, it's not my money,
it's my father's money.
And it's not like he earned it
in some noble way.
He has a hedge fund. [chuckles]
And second of all,
fuck you for saying we're strangers.
You are the best thing
that's ever happened to me.
[Sandra] I'm going to pay you back,
no matter how long it takes.
[Tom] That's okay. I wish
you'd let me come with you though.
[Sandra] I told you I don't want you
anywhere near these people.
- It's all there.
- Got it.
I'll be fine. What are you doing tonight?
[chuckles]
I'm... I was hoping to hang out
with this pretty girl that I know.
[chuckles] Well, there's this great
little Japanese restaurant on Mott Street.
If you're not doing anything,
dinner's on me.
Hey.
[Tom] I love you.
I'm so sorry about all this.
[inhales deeply] All right.
[breathes deeply]
[pants]
Sandra? [breathing heavily]
Sandra, are you okay?
Sandra! Sandra!
Sandra!
["Just A Lonely Christmas" playing]
Shit. [breathing shakily]
How's Christmas Day? It's not that bad.
[indistinct]
Hey, you Larusso?
[Larusso] Over here.
- You're pretty late, Sandy.
- I'm sorry.
There's no cabs.
It's fucking Christmas Eve.
Where's Carl?
Mr. Knutson's wife is sick.
I'll be taking over for him.
Carl usually...
Mr. Knutson usually has us meet
in his office.
Yeah, I thought we'd meet somewhere
a little less formal given the holiday.
But if you'd rather go to my office,
we can do that.
No, it's fine.
Great. Have a seat.
- So, where were you tonight?
- Nowhere.
[scoffs] Just with a friend.
Girl I work with.
- A girl you work with at Starbucks?
- Yeah.
Caroline.
I can give you her number if you want.
That won't be necessary.
- Did you do any drugs tonight, Sandy?
- No.
Did you engage in any behavior
that would violate your parole?
Nope. No.
How is that job? You doing good?
Yeah. It's fine.
Yeah. Starbucks is great.
There's lots of opportunity there.
[chuckles] Yeah, I love it.
Yeah.
The thing is, Sandy,
I went to your job and they told me
you haven't been there in a month.
Uh, yeah. I ca... I can explain. Um…
- I got into a fight with the manager…
- Yeah.
…'cause he's a real...
He's a real fucking perv, okay?
And I've been looking
for another job, so...
Having a job is
a part of your parole agreement.
- Do you understand?
- Uh-huh, yeah.
So, you getting fired is strike one.
So, let me ask you a question.
If I give you a drug test right now,
how would that go?
- Negative.
- Negative? Are you sure?
Because if I gotta go to my car
and take the trouble to get a test,
and it comes back positive,
I'm gonna be very goddamn upset.
So, tell me how would that go?
- I smoked some weed the other night.
- That is strike two.
I can bring you in right now.
Your list of priors,
- you aren't going anywhere anytime soon.
- I know, I know, I know.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- [Larusso] You're sorry?
Give me one reason not to bring you in.
[Sandra inhales sharply]
I'll give you money.
And that is attempted bribery.
Strike three.
Congratulations, Sandy,
that's the whole fucking ball game.
- So stand up and turn around now.
- I... Okay. No, no. Come on.
- Look, I can give you a lot of money.
- What is a lot of money?
Whatever you wanted.
Look, I know where to get it,
and you know I ain't lying to you,
Miss Larusso,
- because you're my parole officer and...
- What are you doing?
[chiming]
[laughs] What do you mean?
Nothing. What the fuck?
- Are you recording me?
- No! No, stop. Look...
Are you trying to entrap me?
- No, it ain't like that.
- What the fuck are you thinking?
- No, no, no. Look...
- Do you think I'm an asshole?
I do. I think you're an asshole.
Sir, I'm a parole officer
and this young lady is my parolee…
- Yeah.
- …and none of this is your concern.
You're shaking her down.
I've watched you do it
to parolees all night.
What do you want?
How about I pay you to walk away?
How much?
How much do I have?
[inhales deeply]
Um…
[inhales deeply] Let's see.
Um, that's twen...
45, 46, 47.
That's ten, 20, 40, 60, 80, 100.
Oh, shit.
Two hundred. Three hundred, 400.
- That's $447.
- Mmm.
You're looking at this?
Okay.
- That's a Rolex Submariner.
- Yeah, I know what a Rolex is.
You must be drunk.
[laughing] Yeah, maybe I am.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Have a good night.
[door opens]
Don't you fucking move.
Wait up.
Let's talk.
I've got a wife and I got two kids,
and I'm just trying to provide.
And this one has it coming
because she is a fuckup.
- Eat shit.
- Keep it up, Sandy. Keep it up.
How much is this gonna cost?
- Five grand.
- Good night.
No, no, no. No, no, no.
I just saw your car
and you are walking around here,
sporting an $8,500 watch,
that you were just gonna give me.
[patron] I only have $447.
- [Larusso] I'll take the watch.
- That's 8,500. Like you said.
Hmm. Eighty-five hundred, new? Correct?
What is it used? Maybe seven?
[patron] Maybe.
[Larusso] So, give me the watch
and I'll give you the change.
[inhales deeply, sighs]
[Larusso] Thanks.
[sighs] Happy holidays, motherfucker.
[door closes]
- [train chugging]
- [car alarm beeps]
It wasn't real?
Get in.
I gotta give you your cut.
- My cut?
- Your money.
Thousand dollars.
Got a knife on me.
[patron] Great.
Come on, it's freezing out.
[door opens]
[sighs] Have a seat.
You can take your jacket off.
Don't try any shit.
- [patron] Now take off your shoes.
- Fuck you.
I need to trust you.
I'm not a junkie.
Roll up your sleeves.
[scoffs]
You can sleep there. Or you can leave.
And what happens if I stay?
You work for me.
[door closes]
- [door opens]
- [breathing shakily]
[siren wailing in distance]
- [patron] Morning.
- [footsteps approaching]
What's your favorite movie?
What's my favorite movie?
- Yeah, what's your favorite movie?
- [chuckles]
Titanic.
[patron chuckles]
That's a classic.
- You like that movie?
- Of course.
[chuckles] DiCaprio was so young in it.
Honestly, he's never been better.
I liked him in The Departed.
He's okay, but Titanic,
that's the movie that made him.
And Kate Winslet was so beautiful.
And the end.
I'll still never get over that. [sighs]
[grunts]
Can't believe you like Titanic.
I don't. I've never seen it.
- You've never seen Titanic?
- No.
I don't watch movies.
They're a waste of time.
But I gave you the impression that I did,
and that's what we're gonna do with you.
We're gonna give people the impression
that you're somebody that you're not.
And when I'm done with you,
it's gonna be 100% convincing.
We're gonna teach you
a little about everything.
So that you can lie about anything.
Read those cover to cover.
You fucking kidding me?
What did you do
with that $1,000 that I gave you?
In my jacket. Why?
From now on, each time you curse,
I get a hundred.
Fuck that! That's my money.
Now I get 200. You still got 800 left.
Read those.
What's your name?
It's Max.
Merry Christmas, Max.
Merry Christmas, Sandra.
Sandy.
Everybody calls me Sandy.
Not anymore.
[door closes]
[sighs deeply]
[helicopter whirring]
[siren wailing]
[banging on door] Max!
Let me in. I promise
I won't do it anymore. Please!
[breathing shakily]
[bangs on door]
Max!
Please, please, please! [sobs]
[breathing shakily]
- [door opens]
- [gasps]
[sighs]
[breathing shakily]
I need you clean. You understand?
I gotta trust you.
[grunts, pants]
[sniffs, sobs]
[Max] Anna Karenina.
[Sandra] "All happy families are alike,
but each unhappy family
is unhappy in its own..."
"But each unhappy family
is unhappy in its own way."
- I was gonna say that.
- The Great Gatsby.
"Don't ever tell anyone anything,
or you'll miss them forever."
Catcher in the Rye.
"In my younger and more vulnerable years
my father gave me
some advice that I have been…"
- [Max] Where'd you go to school?
- [Sandra] Vassar College.
What's your thesis about?
"Redefining Radicalism: The Rise of…
Black Feminism in American Literature."
What's your favorite book?
Their Eyes Were Watching God,
Zora Neale Hurston.
When'd you graduate?
Class of '16.
- "It was the best of times..."
- "It was the worst of times."
- "Call me..."
- "Ishmael."
- [Max] Where'd you study?
- [Sandra] Vassar College.
- [Max] From when to when?
- 2012 to 2016.
I lived in a dorm, Jewett, for two years,
then moved off campus.
Didn't have much of a social life.
Spent all my time in the library.
- [Sandra] Am I the first?
- [Max] First what?
[Sandra] First girl you've done this with?
[Max] Yes.
Why did you pick me?
- I saw something in you.
- [Sandra] My brother's coming into town.
Every time I see him though,
he always asks for money.
- Do you give him money?
- Sometimes. He's all I've got.
You know, I'm from Seattle originally.
I've got a mom there.
- She's crazy, but she's all right.
- What did you major in?
- Hmm?
- At Vassar. What did you major in?
English.
Just trying to make some conversation.
Tell you about my mom.
What? You don't have a mom?
No, I have a mom.
I fucking hate her.
When did you go to Vassar?
2012 to 2016.
- [Max] You were there the whole time?
- [Sandra] No. Spent a year abroad.
- [Max] Where?
- [Sandra] Florence, Italy.
[Max] So you speak Italian?
[in Italian]
And what did you think of Italy?
I've got great memories.
But, I had this boyfriend
who was a real jerk.
I'm taking you out.
Where?
You like martinis?
I like martinis.
Good.
[people in restaurant chattering]
[soft piano music playing]
[Max] Cheers.
[Sandra] Cheers.
[inhales sharply]
So, what exactly are we doing here?
We're celebrating.
What exactly are we celebrating?
My birthday.
It's your birthday?
[chuckles]
You've been doing really well.
Better than I expected.
Thank you.
You ready for a test run?
- Test run?
- See that guy at the bar?
Yeah. What about him?
Get him to take you back to his room.
[soft piano music continues]
Are you serious?
Got 40 minutes.
And here we were having such a nice time.
[inhales sharply]
- What can I get for you, miss?
- Vodka martini, please.
How do you do?
[sniffs] I'm good. Hi.
[inhales deeply] Thank you.
Can I buy you a drink?
I hate drinking alone.
Yeah. Yeah. Sure.
I'm Sandra.
- I'm William.
- [chuckles] Nice to meet you, William.
It's nice to meet you too.
[Sandra] I have a confession.
[William] Oh, yeah. What's that?
[Sandra] Noticed you at the bar.
[inhales sharply]
I have a thing for older men. [sighs]
[William] Wow. You got a thing, huh?
- A bad thing. [chuckles]
- [William chuckles]
What's the matter?
Daddy didn't love you enough?
[chuckles] Daddy wasn't around much.
You're married, aren't you?
Yeah,
that's what the ring on my finger says.
[whispers] I wanted to fuck you
since the second you walked in tonight.
I'm going to tell you
what I'm gonna do to you, all night…
- [knocking on door]
- [kisses]
- What's that?
- Mmm. Just ignore it.
- It's just turndown service.
- [chuckles]
[knocking continues]
- [groans] Um…
- Hold on one second. Don't move.
- Yeah. [chuckles]
Fucking bitch.
Don't you think I fucking knew it?
I knew you were fucking him.
- What are you doing here, huh?
- I'm calling the front desk.
- I love you. Do you understand that?
- Jason!
- Relax!
- Shut up!
- Jason, calm down!
- Are you fucking him?
Are you fucking my girl?
Did you fuck my fucking girl?
- I'll fucking kill you!
- He didn't...
Fucking God! Jesus Christ!
- You fucking bitch!
- Jason, listen to me.
- Hey!
- Fuck!
- Jason, it is over.
- Get the fuck out of here!
- I'm calling security.
- No, okay. Sit down.
- Calm down.
- No, no. No, no, no. Look, he's harmless.
- [sobbing]
- Do you want me to call security?
No, no. I'm s... [inhales sharply]
He's just an old boy...
He's an old boyfriend. I'm-I'm...
He's just hurt. He's completely harmless.
- Are you gonna be okay in here?
- I'm fine. Yeah.
- I-I promise, just... Completely.
- Are you sure?
Can you just give us a few minutes?
- Uh, sure. Sure.
- Yeah. I'll... I'll...
Just-Just go down back to the bar…
You're a fucking liar! [sobs]
…and I'll meet you in half an hour.
- Okay? Yeah.
- Okay, fine.
- You sure you're gonna be okay?
- [sighs] Completely.
- Goddamn it. Fine.
- He's calming down.
- Yeah. I'm so sorry. Yeah. Got it. Okay.
- Just... Keep it down, okay?
[chuckles, breathes heavily]
Fuck. [squeals]
Well done.
You figured it out.
You're a natural. Right?
You were quick, you stayed cool.
You improvised. That's what we do.
What the fuck?
Shit.
I'm surprised
people still walk around with cash.
[Max] Ah, and of course. [chuckles]
Diamond earrings for the poor wife
who sits at home and waits for her husband
while he preys on young women.
I wouldn't say he was preying on me.
We sort of set him up.
Don't do that.
- What?
- Don't feel sorry for him.
You can't cheat an honest man, right?
That's why we never feel sorry
for the mark.
They look good on you.
What are you doing?
Happy birthday, Max.
["Slippery People" playing]
[music stops]
[singer] ♪ …against the wall ♪
- ♪ Like the drip, drip, drip ♪
- [concierge] Thank you.
♪ Of the raindrops ♪
♪ When the summer shower is through ♪
[server] Enjoy the evening, sir.
♪ A voice within me keeps repeating ♪
♪ You, you, you ♪
♪ Night and day ♪
♪ You are the one ♪
♪ Only you beneath the moon ♪
♪ And under the sun… ♪
Max. You made it.
Richard, I want you to meet my son, Max.
- Hi, Mom.
- Hi.
- [chuckles]
- [Max] You look great.
- Heard so much about you.
[sighs] I wish I could say the same.
Well, maybe if you returned a text
or actually picked up the phone
and called your mother
every once in a while. [chuckles]
I'm very busy, Mom. I'm sorry.
[mother, Richard chuckle]
Your mother tells me
you were in St. Barts.
- Yeah, I was.
- Yeah. I had some fun times there myself.
- Uh, back in the '70s.
- [laughs]
- You're old.
- [mother] Max.
That's, um... I'm...
Come... Come with me, I wanna talk.
- Come on. Come on with me. Yeah.
- Really?
I'm so sorry.
Come. Come on.
Let's go.
Excuse me, sir.
- Hi.
- No, stop that. Come on.
- You look great.
- Hey. What is the matter with you?
- What?
- You are so rude.
- [Max] What do you know about this guy?
- Honey, he's a public figure.
Anything you wanna know,
you can just Google him.
[scoffs]
You can't be alone for two minutes.
You throw yourself
into these relationships.
This is different.
[stutters] It really is.
Sure it is.
Go easy on that, please.
I think you've had enough.
Stop being my mom, Mom.
Wh... Sweetheart, what is it?
What's going on?
I thought you were gonna bring
your girlfriend tonight.
Where is she?
Seeing somebody else.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I never liked her.
I think she was a bad influence.
Can I stay here for a little while?
[sighs]
Okay. Um...
Uh… [sighs] …Are you using?
[jazz band continues]
No, I'm not using drugs.
I haven't done drugs in a year.
It's just that I-I can't
go through that again,
- and that can't happen here.
- Mom, I'm clean.
My God. What the fuck is...
What do you want?
You want me to prove it to you?
A fucking piss test?
- Is that what you want? Huh?
- Stop. What? What are you doing?
- Here. I'll do it right now! Okay?
- No! No, don't. Stop! Stop!
- You can see for yourself!
- Don't do that. Stop it right now!
[Max urinating]
Prove it to you.
[singing continues in distance]
- [breathes heavily]
- Go ahead.
- Test it.
- Please don't do this to me.
Test it!
Please. Please. Please.
Please, don't do this to me.
[sighs]
- [sobbing]
- Mom, I'm sorry.
- [sighs] I'm sorry, Mom.
- [cries]
Why do you do this?
Why do you do this to me? [sobbing]
[sighs] I'm really sorry.
Just... I still need a place to stay, okay?
Please?
You can stay.
Just not for very long, okay?
Thank you. I love you.
- [cries, exhales deeply]
- [kisses] Thank you.
[sniffs, exhales deeply]
You enjoy the show?
I'm so... I'm so sorry. [sobbing]
I'm... I'm so... I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
[sobbing]
[mother] He spent the last year
putting together a company
to charter boats in the Bahamas,
but then the hurricane wiped that out,
which is too bad because he was so happy.
- He was doing so well...
- [Richard] Madeline. Uh, how does he live?
Well, his father left him some money,
and, um... Mmm…
I help him out from time to time.
Of course you do.
I was so young when he was born, you know?
And then his father died,
and I'm suddenly a widow,
and I didn't always know
how to be a mother.
[Richard] It's up to him to do better.
He-He's an adult.
[Madeline]
No, he isn't. And that's my fault.
He's always been my little Max.
And he can't swim without me. [chuckles]
Morning, Mom.
Hi, sweetheart. How'd you sleep?
Great. Room's got an amazing view.
Good.
Um... Well, I, um...
I actually have an appointment downtown,
but I was thinking, um, if you were free
that maybe we could have lunch together.
Um, at one o'clock. Via Carota?
- Sounds great.
- Okay. Perfect.
- See you later. [kisses]
- [kisses]
Bye, honey.
Richard?
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I took a Klonopin,
and I had a lot of drinks.
[inhales sharply] Max, we're gonna be
in each other's lives
for the foreseeable future.
Let's make the best of it, shall we?
You know,
your mother and I are attending, uh,
a benefit tonight
for the Richard Hobbes Foundation.
[stutters] My late wife founded it.
We make all sorts
of charitable contributions.
Uh, did you want me to make a donation?
Because, honestly,
I'm a little light right now.
[chuckles]
No. No, I figured you might wanna join us.
There's a gonna be a...
A few very hip musical acts.
They tell me they're quite relevant.
There's gonna be
a lot of young people your age.
Lot of young women.
Thank you, but I think
I should just stay in and rest.
Yeah. Fair enough.
[crunching, chewing]
Well, you were terrible.
You treated him like a waiter. [laughs]
I still have no idea who he is.
No, he's... he's on that TV show.
He plays a spy. He's very famous.
All night, all I could think about
was being alone with you.
You're alone with me now.
I don't care about actors.
You should know that.
[breathes heavily]
I just want you all to myself.
[elevator dings]
- [officer] Sir, calm down.
- [Max] I asked you to identify…
- Sir, the police are here.
- [shouting indistinctly]
- Police? Hey! What's going on here?
- Fuck does that even fucking mean?
- Sir, excuse me. I'm, uh, NYPD.
- [sighs] Oh, my G...
Detective Collins.
Does this young man live here?
- Well, he's staying here.
- I don't fucking live here.
- What did you do?
- Nothing. I didn't do anything.
He solicited drugs
from an undercover officer.
You came up to me
and tried to sell me fucking cocaine.
- And you said yes.
- Don't put words in my mouth.
- Detective, how bad is this?
- It's not looking good.
[stutters] He has a few offenses.
We ran his name,
and he's looking at doing some time.
- Oh, my God. Max.
- Wha... What happens now?
- I'll take him downtown...
- Fuck that, dude. I'm outta here.
Get your fucking hands off of me!
Richard!
Richard, please. Stop him. Stop him!
Calm down!
- Fuck!
- Detective, can we talk about this?
- [Max sighs] Fuck.
- Now?
- [grunts]
- [Madeline stammers]
I make large donations
to the NYPD every year.
Yes, sir, I'm aware of that.
That's the reason for the courtesy call.
It's why I'm here.
I know the commissioner.
Marty is a good friend.
- I can put in a good word for you.
- Richard, you don't have to do that.
[Richard]
My word carries weight in this city.
That can cut both ways.
I really appreciate what you've done,
coming here.
Uh, I don't know, sir.
[Richard] I'm gonna pay you for your time.
I c... I can't do that.
No, I'm... I'm sorry.
Take the fucking money, Detective.
[breathes deeply]
- Stop. He's not a cop.
- What?
- Ma'am, ex...
- Shut up.
This is... This is what Max does.
He plays these… [inhales deeply]
…these little confidence games.
That's what this is, isn't it? This is...
This is one of your games, right?
- I can assure you that I'm...
- You get out.
Get out or I really will call the police.
I mean it. Get out of here.
[chuckles] Tipsy, I mean, I think...
- Dude, fuck.
- You better... You better go.
- Do you think this is funny?
- Why'd you fucking break?
Do you think this is funny?
Come on, man.
- You okay?
- Get out of here. Get out of here.
- Oh, okay.
- Sorry. I'm sorry.
- I'll call you later. Thank you.
- All right, dude.
- [chuckles] Hope I catch you later, bro.
- [Max laughing]
[Madeline] Oh, my God.
[Max] Mom, listen.
I gave you everything, you know.
You... You had every advantage.
You... You didn't...
You didn't want for anything,
and this is what you do to me?
- You humiliate me in front of him?
- It's just a little...
I want you to leave.
I don't want you here anymore.
[Richard] All that work for $1,000.
Let me give you a piece of advice, Max.
If you're gonna steal, steal a lot.
[sighs]
[knocking]
["In The Night" playing]
[door closes]
I'm sorry I hit you.
[Max sighs] Forget it.
No, I took it too far.
Let me see.
Is it too early for a drink?
[Max]
I don't like the way you look at him.
[Madeline] Oh, come on.
You like him a little bit.
Of course I like him. He's a billionaire.
That's not what I'm talking about.
[Madeline chuckles]
Look, I feel really good about this.
We're very close.
He wants to meet with you
at his office at one o'clock.
Mmm.
[sighs]
Well, maybe I don't wanna do this anymore.
- Why not? Don't be jealous.
- [song ends]
You know I don't like old men.
[chuckles]
[Madeline] You know what I like.
Okay.
[inhales deeply, sighs] No.
Tell me what I like.
- You like me.
- Mm-hmm.
I like you.
Why do I like you?
Because I get you what you want.
So, get me what I want.
[Max breathes heavily]
Get me what I want.
Okay.
[buckle clinks]
Max, thanks for coming.
Hey. Are you okay?
Oh, yeah, it's just maintenance.
Here, follow me.
I wanted to apologize about last night.
It was inappropriate.
[chuckles]
That's a hell of an understatement.
You know,
when your mother first told me about you,
she said that you were well-educated,
smart, clever.
I thought, you know, I'm always
on the lookout for a young man like that.
- [Max] Are you offering me a job here?
- No. I doubt if you'd want one.
What are you doing here?
Did you schedule a meeting?
No. I didn't know that I needed one.
[Richard] What is it, Tom?
[inhales deeply] I'm back.
Yeah, I can see that. So, what is it?
Just wanted to say hi,
see how you're feeling…
- [Richard] Now is not a good time.
- All right, cool. See you around, Dad.
Tom.
Come on, in here.
That was my son.
I always assumed
he would inherit all this.
Then his mother died
and he didn't take it well.
He doesn't have the fortitude
to work here. He's weak.
- [Max] Hmm.
- [Richard sighs]
When he turned 21,
I offered him anything he wanted.
You know what my son asked for?
I don't know, Richard.
A signed copy of Charlotte Brontë's
Jane Eyre. [chuckles]
Now he wants to open a bookstore.
Not exactly a sound investment.
No. But I'm gonna give it to him anyway.
You know why, Max?
Because we only get one life.
And I will not be my son's jailer
for his brief time on earth.
I want you to be honest with yourself,
Max.
If I were to hire you to work for me,
how do you think it would end?
Not well.
I agree.
Still, I want to offer you a job.
I'm thinking $60,000 a month.
Sixty grand a month? For what?
To go out and find opportunity.
Make a mark for yourself.
You want me gone.
You cause your mother anguish, Max.
And I will not have it.
So, what am I then? A bad investment?
I didn't get where I am
making bad investments.
Is that what I'm worth, Richard?
Sixty thousand dollars a month?
I'm offering you an opportunity.
I want a year's salary up-front.
That can be arranged.
I'll just transfer the money in...
[chuckles] Transfer the money?
No. What? So I can pay taxes?
Hire an accountant? No.
I want cash up-front.
Get me the cash
and you get my mom all to yourself.
I'll be gone. You won't even hear from me.
Not even a fucking postcard.
Wait here.
[bill counter whirring]
["Dirty Laundry" playing]
- [Max] We did it.
- [chuckles] We did it, baby.
[howls] Where the fuck is my money?
[all cheering, laughing]
Y'all look good.
- [Tipsy] Let's go.
- [Madeline] Whoo!
- Yeah! [speaks indistinctly]
- [Max] Let's do it.
Here we go.
[Tipsy] We got the big Gs, buddy.
- [music ends]
- Yo, wait, l-l-l-look.
- There is this new guy named Goldie.
- Mm-hmm.
- He from, like, LA.
- Yeah.
He started out working as a stuntman
before he was grifting,
or whatever the fuck we doing.
He started working as a stuntman. Crazy.
He comes highly recommended
and he's looking for a score.
And I need y'all.
- [smacks lips] Tipsy…
- Oh.
["Time Moves Slow" playing]
- We're out.
- [chuckles]
Oh, come on, man.
What you... What, y'all retiring?
- No. No, no, no. No.
- That's it?
What y'all gonna do?
Do the whole... Come on.
Uh, w... No, we're taking...
- We're just gonna take a vacation.
- We're... We're... Yeah.
- Taking a vacation.
- Okay. Well, y'all let me know
- whenever y'all get back. Okay?
- Okay.
Y'all gonna wanna meet him.
- Big shit, all right?
- Mm-hmm.
Hey.
[laughs] You're bullshitting me.
Where my money at?
- [laughing]
- [laughs] Come on.
- What?
- [chuckles]
- That's it. [laughs] Tipsy, that's it.
- [grunts] No.
Um, we had expenses…
- We handled some expenses.
- …that we didn't account for.
Yeah, okay, but this... No. No, no.
Thi... This isn't what we agreed on, man.
- I know, but things change. [laughs]
- Yeah. [chuckles]
This is becoming a habit with y'all two.
I'm starting to feel like I'm the mark.
- [laughs] Now we're laughing about it.
- No. Come on, man. No.
- No, no, no.
- Uh-uh.
Absolutely not.
[sighs]
It was a beautiful con though, right?
You can thank Madeline...
Madeline for that. [laughs]
[laughs] Stop it. Stop it.
Thank you, Madeline.
You're welcome, Tipsy. You're welcome.
- Thank you, Tipsy.
- Yeah. Thank you for everything, man.
- I'll ca... I'll call you.
- Yeah. For sure.
- [Tipsy] Y'all stay warm, all right?
- Bye.
[door opens, closes]
- Three quarters of a million.
- Not bad.
[both click tongues]
Now what?
I'm gonna go home. I'm gonna get my stuff.
And, um, I'm gonna tell him
that I have a sick aunt in Jersey.
And I'm out first thing in the morning.
[chuckles]
You love me?
Unfortunately.
[phone rings]
[line ringing]
- [phone rings]
- [sighs]
Hey.
[Madeline] Hey. So…
I have some good news and some bad news.
The good news is the money is all yours.
Okay. What's the bad news?
Uh, the bad news is you were right.
[Max] Right about what?
The old man loves me.
- [laughs]
- He wants to marry me, so I'm staying.
What are you talking about?
[Madeline] Maybe I don't wanna
sit around in a bar all day
pulling short cons
for the rest of my life.
[Max] You can't be serious.
Sooner or later the old man
is gonna ask questions.
[Madeline]
No. No, he won't. He's too invested.
He's got too much on his mind.
You know, his health and his business.
And that... that emotional wreck of a son.
[chuckles] But I'm the good thing, right?
- [laughs]
- [Madeline] I'm the good thing he's got.
Yeah.
I know you. You stay, you'll slip.
No, I won't. I'm too good.
And if they're not looking for you,
they don't see you.
[Max] Are you really doing this?
Um… Yeah.
I don't wanna play the mom anymore.
It's boring.
[knocking]
[officer] Max Burnett, it's the police.
We have an outstanding warrant
for your arrest. Open the door.
I don't believe you. Who's at the door?
Tipsy?
Oh, you better go. [chuckles]
You're bluffing.
Yeah, well, then call my bluff
and open the door.
[knocking]
[officer] Open the door.
So, you used me?
- [knocking]
- [officer] Max Burnett.
[knocking continues]
- Fuck.
- [officer] Open the door.
[breathing deeply]
["King Arthur:
Act 3 'What Power Art Thou"' playing]
[breathing shakily]
[sniffles, exhales sharply]
[breathes heavily]
[people at funeral chattering]
[attendee whispers] I'm so sorry.
[lawyer] I'm gonna need a minute
of your time to go over Richard's will.
There are documents
that are time-sensitive.
And also, I think it's best
we do it right away, for Tom's sake.
- Okay.
[lawyer] Richard dictated this last draft
of the will to me personally,
and then he signed it.
And because he was at the height
of his sickness,
I feel it's my obligation to assure you
that he was cogent and of sound mind
when he did so.
Richard left the bulk of his estate
to Madeline.
That's ridiculous, this… [stammers]
It should be Tom's.
Richard was very clear.
After the past incident with Tom…
- I had $350,000 stolen from me.
- He had major misgivings…
- And I had a nervous breakdown.
- …leaving Tom both the business
and the estate.
You'll be taken care of through a trust.
It's generous.
And it will allow you
to hold on to your bookstore.
Tom will also
retain control of the charity,
the Richard Hobbes Foundation.
As for everything else,
property, assets, shares, stocks,
the remaining 9.2 billion…
It will all go to Madeline.
[Tom] Well, at least
he trusted me with the Foundation.
[lawyer] He did, Tom.
You're chairman of the board.
And Madeline has been named trustee.
I'm a trustee?
[lawyer] It's only a formality.
A piece of insurance in the event
Tom is unable to fulfill his duties
- and Madeline will...
- [Tom] Will take over. Yeah, I get it.
[lawyer] He trusted you
with control of the Foundation.
I can tell you that
with complete sincerity.
- He thought the world of you.
- [Tom] Yeah, okay.
No offense, but my father's last wishes
tell me exactly what he thought of me.
[sighs, stammers] David, I'd like to
be alone with Tom for a minute,
- if that's okay.
- [David] Of course. Of course.
Um, thank you. Thank you.
I am so sorry.
- Don't be. It's not your fault.
- No, I just...
I want you to know that I'm your partner.
And that I'm here for you.
I'm here for whatever you need.
You don't have to go through this alone.
Thank you for saying that.
You can stay with me
for as long as you like.
You don't have to move out anytime soon.
But I'm gonna have to sell this apartment
because I can't do it.
I can't... I can't stay here alone.
I just can't.
I can't manage it.
- I don't know why I brought this up.
- Okay.
I shouldn't... I shouldn't...
- No, I get it.
- I shouldn't have brought it up right now.
- We can discuss it some other time.
- [sighs]
- I think it's just a lot.
- It's okay. It's okay.
It's a lot for both of us
to handle right now.
[exhales sharply]
[sighs]
["Count Your Blessings" playing]
[chuckling]
- Thank you, Patrick.
- You're welcome, Miss Hobbes.
- Good morning, Charlie.
- How are you, Miss Hobbes?
[song continues]
[both speaking indistinctly]
I'm gonna check on the room.
I'll be right back.
Thank you so much.
[speaks indistinctly] …Mrs. Hobbes.
Oh, wow. Ooh.
[speaking indistinctly]
This is so pretty.
May I see the other tray?
[employee] Yes, of course.
[speaks indistinctly, kisses]
[speaks indistinctly, kisses, chuckles]
[speaks indistinctly]
[whispering] I have to tell you something.
I think I saw… [whispers indistinctly]
[song ends]
[elevator dings]
[person] Please, come this way.
Tom is expecting you.
He's gonna be bored out of his mind.
Come talk to me in 20 years.
I'll be dealing with the exact same thing.
You know what I'm saying?
Oh, Mrs. Hobbes. Good morning.
I'm Pat Braddock.
We met briefly
at your husband's memorial service.
Yes, of course. How do you do?
[Braddock] I'm good. Thank you.
These are my associates,
Mr. McCabe, Mr. Mosely.
We're here to see Tom.
We're doing a bit of business for him.
What kind of business?
- [door opens]
- [Tom] Pat, hey.
- [Braddock] Oh.
- It's okay, Madeline.
- Braddock is an old family friend.
- Hi, Tom.
Good to see you. He did work for my father
whenever he had anything sensitive
he needed taken care of.
[Tom] Actually, Madeline, uh,
I want you to see this.
Tom enlisted our help to find
the young woman who committed the theft.
After running her picture
through the system,
we landed on this woman.
We think this is her.
- That's her.
- [Braddock] All right.
So her name is Sandra Carmichael.
She was born in Seattle. Rough childhood.
Talked to the mother, but she
hasn't spoken to her in several years.
Okay, she, uh,
drops out of high school at 16,
starts racking up a number of offenses.
Shoplifting, possession, assault.
But then she develops a habit,
and she crisscrosses the country
until she makes her way to Queens,
where she's arrested again for possession.
She gets paroled
and that's where the trail runs cold.
[Madeline] Okay, so that's it.
She's a drug addict.
[Braddock] Well, frankly,
it raises some questions.
- What kind of questions?
- Yeah, like what?
[Braddock] What she pulled
required a great deal of sophistication.
I don't see how this woman did it alone.
I think we're looking
for more than one person.
- [Braddock] We'll keep you posted.
- Thank you. I really appreciate this.
- [Braddock] We're gonna get 'em.
- Okay. No… [stammers] …I trust you.
- We'll talk to you soon, all right?
- Okay. Yeah.
[elevator dings]
[Madeline] Hi!
Hi!
- I didn't know you could cook.
- Not bad for a trophy wife, huh?
[chuckles] I mean, your dad told me
what you said about me.
- Sorry. I didn't know you then.
- Oh, I don't care.
- It was more about him.
- I honestly... I really don't care.
You hungry?
Uh, yeah. I could eat.
Let me just put my stuff down.
[Madeline] Did you have any luck
finding that girl?
Uh, not yet. Uh, Braddock had a lead
down in Miami but it was a bust.
[sighs] Honey, you know,
what these people did to you was awful
and confusing and unfair.
But I don't think that finding her
is gonna make you feel any better.
I disagree.
Yeah, well...
Okay. Hang on, I... I have
something I wanna show you. [chuckles]
So, I, um… [humming]
…started looking for apartments for you.
These are all downtown near the bookstore,
so it wouldn't be much of a commute.
- What is this?
- Well, I told you.
I'm gonna have to sell this apartment,
so I want you to find a place.
I know, but I don't need you
to do this for me.
But I want to, sweetheart.
- I wanna help you with this.
- I get that. I'm just saying that
- I can find my own apartment. Thank you.
- [chuckles] Why are you getting upset?
- I'm not.
- No, you are.
- No, I'm not. I'm just...
- You totally are getting upset.
- You can't come here and do this…
- No, but I want to.
- …and expect me not to react.
- I wanna be a part of this.
- It's not your problem. You're not my mom!
- No, you're right. I'm not.
'Cause if I were, I'd tell you
to grow the fuck up.
People get their hearts broken every day.
It happens to everybody, okay?
All the time.
But most kids aren't entitled enough
to hire men to find the girl who did it.
She stole money from me.
That's not why you're doing it.
You want to see her again.
Right?
You can lie to yourself,
but you can't lie to me.
[sniffs]
I'm sorry. That was harsh. [chuckles]
- You think I'm a loser.
- No, I don't.
- Yeah, you do.
- No, I don't think that you're a loser.
I think that…
I think that you're human.
I think we're all human.
We're just doing the best we can.
I'll have Braddock call it off.
Good for you, sweetheart.
I know it's hard.
[realtor] This apartment is unlisted.
You're the first people to see it.
- Oh, that's exciting.
- [phone rings]
- This is a great neighborhood.
- Hello?
- There are lots of young people here.
- Yeah?
Well, Tom has a bookstore
- on Thompson Street…
- Yeah. Okay.
- …so this may be absolutely perfect.
- Bring her to the apartment. Yeah.
- Honey, what... what's going on?
- Okay. Thanks.
Um, they found her.
I... I... I thought you told them
to stop looking for her?
Well, I did... I did. Uh, but they had
one last lead and they found her. Um…
- [stammers] Where is she?
- They're bringing her to the apartment.
I just wanna talk to her. I have to go.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. We're gonna have to
do this another time. Thank you so much.
- We've got her in the guest room.
- [Tom] Okay.
She was living in the Lincoln Motel
off the Cross Bronx Expressway.
And she has a serious heroin addiction.
She's fallen since you've seen her, Tom.
All right? Hold on. Just wait a second.
We gave her a sedative to calm her down,
but she's gonna be experiencing
some pretty heavy withdrawal so...
- Can I go in and talk to her?
- I'm gonna go with you.
No. I'm okay.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Did she say anything else?
You have any more insight?
Not yet.
[door closes]
You all right, sweetheart?
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm okay.
It's weird.
It's like, it's her, but it's not her.
[Braddock] Did she tell you anything?
[breathes shakily] Yeah, you were right.
She wasn't working alone. There was...
There's this guy who was her accomplice.
He taught her everything and trained her.
He planned the whole thing.
She said that he has
some sort of connection to... to us.
What kind of connection?
She said that he knew all about me.
She said that it seemed personal.
Did she describe him?
- Did she say what he looked like at all?
- No, but he cheated her too.
He left her with nothing.
I told her she could stay here…
- Oh, no, no, no, no. She can't stay here.
- …and, um…
- She's sick…
- No.
- …and she needs a place to detox…
- …and she regrets what she did.
- She's a junkie, you can't trust her.
- She's gonna do anything to get money.
- I agree.
- Very easy for me to do.
- No. She's staying here.
I'll take care of her.
I'll bring doctors or nurses, or whatever.
- But I wanna do this.
- Mr. Braddock, this isn't safe.
- I need your help with this.
- Well, I...
Look, I can put men outside her room.
She'll essentially be under lock and key.
That's not what I'm worried about.
But, come on.
I mean, are you ready
for when she sobers up
- and you have to see the real her?
- I'm dying to see the real her.
Okay. If she's gonna stay here,
then I need to talk to her.
- No, wait. She needs to rest.
- No, I should.
Sandra?
Hi, I'm Madeline.
I was married to Tom's father.
I'm his stepmother.
Suck my dick, you lying bitch.
[chuckles]
[Sandra] Yeah, I know who you are,
Madeline.
Max told me the whole score.
[sniffs]
That you set the cops on him,
but then had to beg him to come back.
How there was an old man who was dying
and was gonna leave behind a fortune,
and all we needed to do was…
nudge aside the son
so that his very full of shit widow
could inherit it all.
So, what do you want?
[Sandra] I wanna confess.
Confess to it all
and get this off my chest.
[inhales sharply]
Do me a favor and get Tom. Tom?
- How much?
- [chuckles]
I don't want your money, bitch.
You don't?
Max and I were supposed to meet
at Penn Station.
I waited there for three days.
Because I was so fucking stupid,
I thought something had happened to him.
[inhales deeply] Can you believe that?
He left me.
[smacks lips, inhales deeply]
Then what can I do for you?
I want Max.
I wanna see Max.
I wanna look into his face,
and I want him to see what he did to me.
- I wanna see Max.
- [chuckles]
Honey, I don't know where he is.
Well, you better find out.
[breathes shakily]
Or I will tell everyone in the next room
who you really fucking are.
She can stay.
[voice mail speaker] Your call
has been forwarded
to an automated voice message system.
When you are finished recording,
you may hang up
or press one for more options.
[beeps]
So, I have a problem.
They found your girl getting high
off the Cross Bronx Expressway.
And now she's in my apartment
pining after you.
You really did a number on her,
didn't you?
You d... You didn't have to go that hard.
I mean, what the fuck did you tell her?
Call me.
[Sandra speaks indistinctly]
Where is he? Where is he?
[sobbing, moaning]
[housekeeper speaking Spanish]
[Sandra crying]
[screaming] Did you find him?
- [door closes]
- Did you find him? [sobbing]
[voice mail speaker]
When you are finished recording,
you may hang up
or press one for more options.
[beeps]
[Madeline] Max. Uh, hey, it's me again.
Um, can you give me a call?
[Sandra crying, moaning]
[Sandra] Max told me the whole score.
And I know who you are.
[Madeline] Please call me back.
I need you.
[Sandra] I want Max.
I wanna see Max. I wanna see Max.
[Madeline] Just please call me back.
Come on, Max. Please.
[Sandra] Or I will tell everyone
in the next room
who you really fucking are.
[phone dings]
[Max] Listen, I came back like you asked.
I gave Tom a nervous breakdown.
I got my money. Now I'm out.
[stammers] Uh, yeah, but I, um...
[clicks tongue]
It's just that I, um…
I think…
I want you back.
[Max] You want me back?
Yeah.
[Max] You want me back to fix this.
Fuck, yes. [sighs, sniffs]
- [Sandra] Put that down...
- [Tom] Yeah, I know that's right.
- [Sandra] Okay. And then I'm gonna...
- [Tom] You're winning…
[Sandra chuckles]
…so I don't understand
why you have so many questions.
Are you cheating me? You hustling me?
Hi. How's our young patient doing?
- I'm doing a lot better. Thanks.
- Yeah, last night was rough,
- but I think we're over the hump.
- Mmm, that's a relief.
You look a lot better.
I was gonna take a walk.
Do you want to join me?
Uh, no. Uh, you know,
she's still not 100%.
I think the fresh air might do her good.
- Uh, I don't know about that.
- No. [stammers]
- A walk would be perfect.
- Oh, good. Brought you a sweater.
That was fast. Where was he?
You can ask him yourself.
We have a deal, right?
Once you see him, you get out of my life.
- I don't want anything from you.
- Good.
How can you do what you do?
Practice.
[elevator bell dings]
[elevator door opens]
Where are we going?
This is good.
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
You left me!
You li... I waited for days!
You fucking left me!
How could you?
You threw me aside
like I was fucking trash!
[panting]
Oh, my God. Please. You done?
You got taken. That's what we do.
So now, the question is,
how do we make this right by you?
I want him to apologize.
Well, he can't. Because he's not sorry.
[breathes shakily] Did you feel anything
for me? [breathes deeply]
I felt nothing.
What the fuck is this?
Shit.
What did I tell you?
She's used these two to swipe
your inheritance right out from under you.
What? You have nothing to say?
The inheritance belongs to Tom.
And you're gonna give it back to him.
It's his money.
[Madeline] If it was Tom's money,
he would have his money.
But it's my money.
And you know what I'm gonna do
with my money?
I'm gonna take a billion dollars
and aim it in your direction.
Your three-bedroom in Scarsdale
or Lloyd Harbor, or whatever the fuck.
It's gone. Your Benz. Gone.
Your kids' college fund.
[chuckling] By the time I'm done with you,
it's all gone.
[Tom] 'Cause it's
all about the money for you, right?
That's all any of you care about
is the money.
Right, Sandra?
Hey! Say something! Answer me!
- Whoa! Hey, hey. Tom. Tom. No.
- [Madeline] Hey! Hey, hey.
You've been fucking with me
since we first met.
- Tom…
- Put the gun down. Put it down.
You took everything. [breathes heavily]
- [Sandra] I'm sorry.
- You're a fucking liar. Don't say...
[Madeline] Tom, put it down. Come on.
Put the gun down.
- [Max] Put the gun down. Tom.
- Put the gun down.
I meant what I said, Tom.
I meant what I said.
[Sandra breathing shakily]
[Tom breathing shakily]
[groans] You're right. You're right.
It's not you.
- Tom, no! What are you doing?
- Hey. No. No, no, no, no. Tom, no.
You did this. You ruined us.
Look at me. Look what you did to me.
Look what you did to my dad!
I took care of your father.
I kept him alive.
- Bullshit!
- Tom, please don't do this.
Just sh-shut up.
Tom, put it do... Put the gun down, okay?
Please, just put it down. Put it down.
- [grunts]
- [gun fires]
[Madeline screams]
[Sandra] Tom, no.
[Braddock] No!
- [Madeline] Stay back.
- Put the gun down.
St... Stay back.
- Put the gun down, Madeline.
- You wanna kill me, Madeline?
- Get back. Tom, no.
- You wanna shoot me? Just do it!
- [Max] Hey! Tom.
- Just do it.
[Madeline gasps]
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- [Sandra] What? What h...
Tom?
- [breathing heavily, crying]
- [Braddock] Come on. Stay with me.
Tom.
[Max] What the fuck?
[Braddock] Oh, my God.
You killed him.
[stammers] I didn't. He... He...
He shot himself. You saw it.
- Call the police.
- [person] I'm on it.
- [Madeline] No!
- He killed himself.
I'm sorry, what? Who the fuck are you?
Shut the fuck up. You're a part of this.
- I need to report a shooting.
- I didn't do it. I... I...
- I didn't kill him. [stammers]
- Yes, there's been a shooting.
A-A young man's been shot in the chest.
I'm not sure.
This... This kid is dead. This is a...
This is... This is a tragedy.
- But I... [stammers] I... I didn't...
- No, she didn't. He killed himself.
I can make amends. I can...
- I can make amends.
- I'm sorry, what?
I'll give the money back.
- I'll give it to the Foundation.
- What are you talking about?
- You're just gonna give it up?
- Yes.
I don't want to go to jail
for something I didn't do!
No. They're coming. The police are coming.
[Madeline] You leave us to the police
and that money's not going anywhere.
- Just think of what it can do.
- Oh, you. [breathes deeply]
They'll give the money back!
Please! Please! I beg you, please!
I don't wanna go to jail!
What a fucking mess.
[line ringing]
[assistant] Madeline Hobbes on line one.
She says it's urgent.
Excuse me a minute. [sighs]
Madeline… Hello?
Is everything all right?
[Madeline]
I wanna transfer my inheritance…
to the Richard Hobbes Foundation.
[David] It was Richard's wish that you
receive the inheritance, Madeline.
It's yours.
But I want it to go to the Foundation.
[stammers] And I want it done today.
I need you to do this, David.
I need you to do this as soon as possible.
[David] Madeline, what is this?
Are you under duress?
No.
[David] You can tell me
if something has happened. I can help.
[Braddock] Next flight out is
to Oklahoma City.
We have 40 minutes. Keep moving.
[David] Madeline?
Have you spoken to Tom about this?
You're my lawyer, right?
[David] Yes. Of course.
[Madeline] Then I want you to
do what I say and transfer the money.
All of it.
[David] We'll prepare the papers.
[Braddock] Make it look like a robbery.
[engine starts]
[people chattering]
[grunts]
You seem very calm
for someone who lost a lot of money.
Well, I'm a professional.
You gave away billions of dollars.
- Is that what I did?
- Did you?
I don't know. Did I?
I mean, I gave the money
to the Foundation.
The head of the Foundation is Tom.
Or should I say, was. [sighs]
- [Max] Tom is dead.
- [Madeline] Mm-hmm.
And so, the money
is controlled by the trustee.
And guess who that is?
You're still talking about money.
Yes. Yes, we are.
[Sandra] Tom is dead.
We killed him. [breathes shakily]
We killed him.
- Keep it together.
- I'm gonna be sick.
[Madeline groans] We gotta get rid of her.
We can't. She's a witness.
She knows too much.
What is it? Did she get to you?
[chuckles] No.
It's okay. I mean, it happens.
She didn't get to me.
[smacks lips] I mean, you can do
what you want.
[chuckles] I don't care.
- She didn't get to me.
- Good.
[flight attendant]
Would you like some water?
Thanks.
- [Madeline] This isn't blood.
- What?
Look. It comes out too easily.
- This isn't blood.
- Let me see.
If it's not blood, then what is it?
Uh, you tell me.
What do you mean?
Are you behind this?
- Behind what?
- You got me to give away the money.
- [chuckling] No, I did no such thing.
- No, Tom's alive. You fucked me.
- What are you talking about?
- You fucked me.
- I will fucking kill you.
- I didn't have anything...
- I will fucking end you!
- I didn't have anything to do with this.
Sandra.
Sandra! Sandra?
- [Sandra] Merry Christmas, Max.
- [Max] Merry Christmas, Sandra.
[Sandra] Sandy. Everybody calls me Sandy.
[Max] We're gonna give people
the impression
that you're somebody that you're not.
And when I'm done with you,
it's gonna be 100% convincing.
And what happens if I stay?
[Max] You work for me.
[Sandra] Is this real?
[Tom] This is real.
How can I be sure?
[Sandra] I really like you.
[Tom] I really like you too.
[Sandra sighs] It's my brother.
He needs money.
- Jason. Keep your voice...
- Listen. Yo, listen to me for two seconds!
I live with my dad and his new wife.
He thinks I'm a disappointment.
[Sandra] But you're not a disappointment.
[Tom] I love you.
[Max] You can't cheat
an honest man, right?
That's why we never feel sorry
for the mark.
[Sandra] Max told me the whole score.
There was an old man who was dying
and was gonna leave behind a fortune.
We just needed to nudge aside the son
so that his very full of shit widow
could inherit it all.
I wanna confess.
Confess to it all.
I'm so sorry for all of this.
How you doing, Tipsy?
Richard's dead
and Madeline got all the money.
[Braddock] What she pulled
required a great deal of sophistication.
I don't see how this woman did it alone.
I think we're looking
for more than one person.
There's a white dude named Goldie.
We like to call him Goldie
'cause he got... he got, like red hair.
[Braddock]
We have to take this out of here.
[Tom] Yeah, you were right.
There was... There was this guy
who was her accomplice.
He taught her everything and trained her.
He planned the whole thing.
[Tipsy] No. One more time.
[Tom] He cheated her too.
He left her with nothing.
[Sandra] How can you do what you do?
[Madeline] Practice.
- [shopkeeper bell jingles]
- Hey, excuse me, I got a quick question.
- I need to know where the fuck…
- [laughs]
- …is my money? [grunts] Look at y'all.
- There he is.
- Look like undercover cops. What's up?
- What's up, baby?
- How you doing?
- Here's your money.
Oh, okay. Not bad, Sandy.
Max taught you well, I see.
All right, last chance, huh?
I really could use someone like you.
Sorry, Goldie. I'm done.
- Yeah, whatever. I heard that one before.
- I'm done.
- [Braddock] All right. We gotta bounce.
- [Sandra] Yeah.
- [Braddock] See you guys later.
- [Tipsy] Peace.
- Take it easy.
- Gonna invest in some real estate, baby.
- Let's get it! [laughs]
- Yep!
[chattering indistinctly]
Bye, Sandy.
[shopkeeper bell jingles]
[sighs]
You got a lot of money, Tom. [sighs]
I hope you can do some good with it.
I will.
- Thank you.
- You're thanking me?
I got everything taken from you.
You also got it back.
So, there's this great little
Japanese restaurant on Mott Street.
If you're not doing anything,
dinner's on me.
Well, I am single.
- [chuckles]
- And, uh, I kinda like being single.
Mmm.
[bottle thuds softly]
["Nobody Knows You When You're
Down and Out" playing]
[shopkeeper bell jingles]
[song continues]
[song ends]