You know who killed my cousin.
[Juice] I don't Know, bruh.
Talk, nigga, talk, bruh.
[Juice] I said I don't know, bruh.
(punching) (groaning)
Shut up!
You done killed my cousin.
I said I don't fuckin' know.
(punching) (grunting)
You better come up with
some answers real fuckin' fast.
'Cause they said my
cousin was with you last.
Bruh, I'm telling you I don't know
your fuckin' cousin, man.
- Oh, you know my cousin.
- Fuck.
[Stacy] Please
- don't kill him.
- Shut up.
(spitting)
Shut the fuck up, or your ass
will be floating with the fishes.
[Juice] Just do what they say.
Both of y'all gonna die tonight.
Damn, bruh.
Yeah, you know my cousin, man.
Who is your cousin, bro?
Yeah, Ruger, nigga, you know Ruger.
(punching)
Please don't... Shut up, bitch!
Before I off your top now.
Ruger fucked with you,
even after I told him not to.
[Juice] Damn, bruh.
Yo, hurry up and off that nigga, man.
Send him to his mama.
Fuck you!
Oh yeah, he going to meet his mama.
(train horn blaring)
Definitely doing that tonight.
Him and his little chick.
No balling for you, no more.
College boy.
Matter of fact, tell my
nigga, Ruger, I love him
when you get there.
[Narrator] You see, the streets-
It's not where it's at.
You can get killed or
you can end up in jail.
Your boy Juice?
He had to learn the hard way.
("Bring Them Racks In" by Lyonel Streets)
("Bring Them Racks In" by
Lyonel Streets continues)
(shoes scraping concrete)
Nephew, how's it going?
- What's up baby?
- Ah.
(hands clapping)
Good seeing you.
Oh yes, sir.
I hear you are taking your
talents to the next level.
You are going to college.
Yes sir.
That is wonderful.
Yeah man, I appreciate you,
'cause you was the only one there for me.
Pops locked up, Moms went away,
and Grandma just passed, so you all I got.
Yes, I will stand by you.
You are just like a son to me.
It's hard out here,
and I'm just trying to
keep my head on, and get to
college, and get up outta here.
'Cause these streets ain't playing safe.
Is there anything that I can do for you?
Help you with college in any kinda way,
or anything that you need?
Feel free to ask.
Well, I mean I'm pretty good right now.
I've been doing everything on
my own so I'm good right now.
But I'll let you know, for sure.
I see you have matured so much.
I think you're going to be all right.
But still, if there's
anything that you need,
I'm always there for you.
Unc, trust and believe me, I'm good.
I got ways of making my money,
just like you got ways of making yours.
I got this, believe me.
(beeping)
Ah, duty calls.
I will catch you later.
See you later nephew, you take care.
Yes, sir.
[Unc] Yes, Chief.
Yeah man, shit, whatever
you talking about.
Shit works perfect for me.
'Cause hell, I mean, shit,
You said the motherfucker's
gonna be gone all day,
shit, we can do the damn thing.
[Female Voice] He gonna
be gone all day, so pull up.
What you want me to wear?
That yellow outfit you be wearing.
Shit seem perfect to me,
and I ain't gonna bullshit you, nah.
[Female Voice] Yeah, you sure was in love
with that pink one, I got you.
So like I'm saying, shit,
I'm trying to see you
in that damn pink thing.
Shit, you know the one you had on
in the motel last time
- we hit.
- Definitely wear that
for you, baby.
That shit worked perfect for me.
But yeah, you know it's
all about that bread, shit.
Matter of fact, you got a friend?
- Yeah, I got friends.
- Shit, she can come down too.
You already know, shit.
My friends like
money, though. (suspenseful music)
Where my motherfuckin' money at, nigga?
Yo, I got your... Huh, where it at?
I got your money man,
look, just don't do it.
I got your money.
You been ducking and
dodging me, motherfucker.
I went by your job, you weren't there.
- What job, man?
- I went by your mama house.
Hey look man, look,
I was gonna pay you man.
But look man, you know how it
is with kids and shit, man.
Hey man, I had to do what I had to do, man.
Look, Smidge, please don't do it man.
- Huh?
- Look, look man.
Hey, hey, look, I did the
best I could, man, shit.
Hey look, I don't know
what he told you, man.
But look, I got the money right here, man.
Just don't do it, man.
- Where it at?
- Hey, hey.
Here's the money man,
just don't do it, man.
Don't shoot me, man.
Please, just don't shoot me, man.
(punching)
(dramatic hip hop music)
(plastic crinkling)
(dramatic hip hop music continuing)
("Do Yo Thang" by Lyonel Streets)
(papers rustling)
Let's go, baby.
Hello?
Yo, Stacy, what's good with you?
Hey, Juice, I'm good.
Look, I got some good news.
I need you to meet me right now.
Oh, you got some good news?
(chuckling)
I got some good news, too.
Okay, cool.
I'll meet you at our spot.
See you soon.
[Stacy] Dang, Speedy, you flew here.
[Juice] Nah, you just drive slow.
No, I drive safe, okay?
I'm a creature of habit,
you know I like safe.
[Juice] I'm just playin'.
I see you over there looking good though.
Oh my God, shut up, J.
What was the good news, you
said you got some good news?
I do, but ladies first.
Okay, I see you trying to be a gentleman.
Come on, you know I'm
always gentle with you.
Okay, I hear you. (Juice chuckling)
But good news, your girl got accepted
into the University of Virginia!
Whoo, oh, that make my
good news even better.
Check this out. (paper crinkling)
I got accepted, too.
Oh my God!
I am so happy for you.
Yes sir.
We gonna be in college
together, oh my god.
Don't get too happy,
I still gotta get my money up.
I ain't trying to be on campus, broke.
But, you know, you don't
have to worry about money.
I can go to my parents and,
y'know, they'll help you out.
Stacy, I understand.
But everybody ain't got
the luxury of rich parents.
[Stacy] But Juice-
- Listen, I ain't taking no
handouts from your family.
Just drop it.
Okay, Juice, okay, Juice.
I understand, but, you know what,
I'm happy for you, though.
We'll be in college together.
(cellphone ringing)
[Stacy] Your phone ringing.
Hold on, I gotta take
this call, I'll be back.
[Stacy] Okay, all right.
Oh my God, we'll be in
college together, God.
We always talked about this.
God is good.
Oh yeah, coach, everything going good.
Everything going good.
Ready to make my way up there.
Okay, you say nine o'clock?
Sound good, I'll be there.
Cool.
[Stacy] You good, Juice?
Oh yeah, that was coach, right there.
He want me to come for a workout tonight.
[Stacy] Oh, okay, okay, so you gotta go?
Yeah, I gotta go, I'll
catch up with you later.
[Stacy] Okay, all right.
I'm proud of you, here, take your letter.
Thank you. - [Stacy] I'm so proud, yes.
Woo. (chuckling)
(dramatic hip hop music)
(shoes scraping on concrete)
Oh!
(net whooshing)
I'm finna cook.
- You ain't gettin' that shit.
- Shit, you a motherfuckin'
liar, I'm gonna get that shit.
Know what I'm sayin'? Ah!
(net whooshing)
Yes sir, ya'll better get right.
(ball bouncing)
- Oh hell, no.
Ah!
Hell no.
Damn!
(shoes scraping on
concrete) (ball bouncing)
(ball clanging against hoop)
(slapping backboard)
(sucking air through teeth)
(ball bouncing)
(shoes scraping on concrete)
Yo.
(shoes scraping on
concrete) (ball bouncing)
(net swooshing)
- Yes!
- That's what I'm
talkin' about, that's
what I'm talkin' about.
He ain't got no defense.
Ooh, ooh.
(dramatic hip hop music continuing)
Oh, boy, huh?
(shoes scraping against concrete)
Oh yeah. (ball dribbling)
'Bout to cook tonight, baby.
Come on boy, what you got, boy?
Come on, boy.
(ball dribbling) Come on, boy.
(ball hitting hoop)
(shoes scraping concrete) (ball bouncing)
Ah-(net swooshing)
Ooh.
(shoes scraping concrete) (grunting)
(net swooshing)
Yeah.
Man, shit!
He ain't got no defense.
(lighter flicking)
Ooh, ooh.
(crickets chirping)
Damn, this game.
You got it this time, boy.
(ball dribbling)
- Ay, yo, college boy.
Heard you got a full
ride to Virginia State.
Heard you the best out here.
But you ain't better than my man, though.
[Juice] Your man who?
Rico. (chuckling)
[Juice] Rico?
He the best on the south side.
(scoffing)
- Best on the south side?
I'm the best on the north.
He gon' have to prove that.
You don't know where you at, do you?
I mean, you talking all that big stuff.
I know you nice.
$500, $500 on my man right now, Shootout.
All right, so this how it's gonna be.
This how it's going down.
My man gonna shoot five,
and then you shoot five.
Whoever miss, loses.
Whoever hits 'em all, wins.
(bills rustling)
Let's get it.
I hope you got a lighter for this I.
(ball bouncing)
(cash slapping against bleachers)
(suspenseful music)
First one to miss loses.
Straight up and down.
(ball bouncing)
- Buck.
(net swooshing)
You ain't gonna make it.
Miss, yes, miss-
(net swooshing)
Come on, college boy.
(crosstalk) College boy.
(net swooshing)
Green.
Yeah, it's looking good, but
it ain't looking that good.
(chuckling) - [Juice] Okay.
- Money bag.
- Money, money-
(net swooshing) (ball bouncing)
Show me what you got, Mr. South Side.
(ball bouncing)
That's it, show him
what time it is, Rico.
Buckets!
(mumbling) Been there.
[Juice] This a hoop, or a trap?
(chuckling)
Give it to him, give it to him.
That's it, that's it, - Yes sir.
They ain't ready for it.
It's south side, baby.
(net swooshing)
(ball bouncing)
(ball hitting hoop)
Ha, I told you!
[Juice] Fuck!
Look like a I, to me.
Give me my money, man.
Give me my money.
I told you, I knew it, now.
I told you, I told you.
So what you wanna do now?
You gonna get that money right?
Man, he got lucky.
Let's run it back, double or nothing.
- Huh?
- Double or nothing, let's go.
Double or nothing?
Double or nothing, let's go.
- No, you lost.
- Let's do it.
Double or nothing, what, you scared?
- Scared?
You scared?
Double or nothing.
Let's go.
[Juice] You got, like,
300 I can borrow, cuh?
Man, this is my rent money, man.
- The fuck, man?
- Man, I'm gon' win
the money, bruh, just let me get
double or nothing, bruh, trust me.
Man, you better win my
motherfuckin' money back, man.
That's my rent money.
I got you dog, believe.
Let's get it.
(ball bouncing)
Here go the rest, right here.
(cash slapping bleachers)
Double or nothing.
Let's get it, Mr. South Side.
You ain't the best, you
ain't touching Rico, bruh.
I'm sorry, you're not that good.
But you good,
- you a great player.
- He'll see.
Just not that great.
He'll see.
(ball bouncing)
In the one.
(scoffing)
He ain't got nothing, man.
Miss, miss.
Know where you at?
(net whooshing repetitively)
(chuckling)
Brazilian, no misses.
That's how we do it on the north.
I hope you're ready.
You better be.
(ball bouncing)
South side, huh.
(ball hitting hoop)
No!
No, no, no, no... Bruh,
you can't lose.
You can't miss a shot.
- You never miss.
- Man, that shot
was s'posed to go in.
No, no, ain't no suppose nothin'-
- Ay, you just said that.
- No, no, no.
- I never miss out here,
dude, you know this.
Well, if it wasn't for you,
I'd still have my 1,500.
Started off with five,
then we want to keep on-
Hold up, uh-uh.
That money still mine.
That is my money, you are not getting it.
(hip hop music)
You know what?
You just cost me $1,500.
We done.
I'll get y'all later.
(hip hop music continuing)
Yo, for real man.
Me and you team up together, man,
we can kill them boys, right there, bruh.
[Juice] You sure?
You ready for this?
I told you, man, I'm ready, man.
I need to make some money, man, shit.
I need some money too, my dog.
These bills ain't gonna pay they self.
You know I got them-
splash. (chuckling)
Y'know, I got the moves
to make the girls choose.
You dig?
Yeah, man, I'm telling you bro.
Tryin' to make all the bread I can, so-
- 'Sup.
Do you need a ride, or anything?
Oh nah, we good, Unc,
we good, everything good.
Just walking Kurt home.
Make sure he get there straight.
I'm on patrol, but still.
I mean, y'know, if you need a ride.
Oh nah, we good.
I'm just talking to my
boy right now, we good.
Okay then, well, I'll see you guys later.
(car rolling away)
Man, your uncle, man,
he's gotten nice, man.
Sometimes too damn nice.
Man, he coulda gave us a ride, man.
You know we gotta walk two miles, man.
Man, if it wasn't for you,
we wouldn't be walking anyway.
(tsking)
(door closing)
'Sup, son?
Can't keep your face
outta that game, can you?
That's all right, that's all right,
I love you anyway, 'sup babe?
(kissing)
(sighing) Got us some more money.
All right, sounds good.
- You doing all right?
- Yeah, just-
- All right, look, you know I'm out here
trying to stay out that eye.
'Cause, y'know, people trying
to watch what's going on.
- Yeah.
- You know,
I always feel like somebody watching me,
y'know what I'm talking about?
That's why you gotta
keep your eyes open, baby.
That's it.
Hey, remember that trip I told
you I was gonna take you on?
Oh, you wanna talk about the past?
Yeah, yeah, it's gonna happen,
know what I'm saying?
Just a little while longer.
We might have to take that
trip a little bit early.
- Why?
- 'Cause,
word on the street is,
Capone came home, and
- I don't feel safe.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
back up, back up.
Who came home?
Word on the street is, Capone came home.
(groaning)
- Wait, wait, wait,
whoa, whoa,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
How you find that out?
Listen baby, I was at
the grocery store today,
and I ran into a few people that know him.
And word on the street is, yeah, he's home.
Like I haven't seen him, but
you know, the town is small.
You heard this today?
I heard this today.
All right, all right, look.
This is my town, all right?
I think we should just pack up and go.
Like, we talk about taking trips and stuff.
Yes we do, but... And it's time.
But, look... Gotta get away.
All the operations is right here.
We up and move right now, you
know what that's gonna do?
You know what it's gonna
do to our credibility?
You know what it's gonna do to the supply?
We can't just up and move like that.
I mean, there's levels to this.
We gotta make a plan, execute that.
Just like we doing this, right here.
We gotta do something.
Look, we gonna do something,
don't worry about it.
I'll get some folks on them,
to kinda keep 'em at bay for a minute,
until we can get stuff
situated, we can leave.
All right, but look,
like I said, don't worry about it.
Ghost already took care of you, right?
You still alive, you still
breathing, healthy, looking good.
All right, don't worry about
it, I gotcha, all right?
- I know.
- Hey son, come here
for a minute.
Yes?
Last week, you told Daddy that you want
- that new 2K, right?
- Yeah.
All right, you've been
doing good in school.
I'm proud of you.
All right, look.
Hey, go get it, and whatever
else you want, all right?
- Okay.
- All right, I love you.
- I love you, too.
- All right.
But like I said, we're gonna be all right.
All right, this is only temporary.
After that, we opening up businesses.
Remember that hair salon you wanted?
Yes.
I ain't forgot about it.
You're gonna have that, all right?
Whatever it is that my
baby wants, she gonna get.
'Cause you been there for
me, when I ain't had nothin'.
All right, you've been there in the trench-
You ain't never left me.
From the mud, baby.
So I got you, all right.
Ain't no Capone, nobody gonna take you out.
All right, as long as Ghost is here,
- you feel me?
- All right, Ghost.
All right, so, like I
said, don't worry about it.
I'm gonna get this, all right.
I might have some goons on it, y'know?
And don't worry about who.
All right, don't worry about who,
the less you know about
that, the better, okay?
Like I said-
So where you trying to go?
(knocking at door)
Who is it?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, son.
Don't do that.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Damn, babe, you be rushing to the door.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I know who that is, man,
you can open the door.
Hey, what's going on?
All right.
What's going on, man?
What's goin' on, guy, what's goin' on?
(mumbling)
Good to see you, good to see you.
Good to see you too, bruh.
What you want?
I know why you're here, what you want?
Sit down, have a seat.
All right, time for you
to get up outta here,
'cause I'd hate to put down
a senior citizen in these streets-
- All right, man.
Where my motherfuckin' money at, huh?
What you talking about, man?
You know where my money at, man.
Capone, I don't know
where your money is, bro.
What you talking about?
You the only motherfucker
who knew where my stash was at,
my two kilos.
Somebody else know
that, man, I don't know.
Stop fuckin' playing with me man.
Look, I'm ya man, a hundred grand, bro.
I ain't gonna do that to you, now.
- You my man, a hundred grand?
- [Ghost] Yeah.
(punching) (grunting)
(whimpering)
Where my motherfuckin' money at, man?
It's the last time I ask you.
Is that my shit on the fuckin'
table, right there, man?
Take it, take it.
Get the fuck over there, man.
Get over there before I blow
your fuckin' brains out.
(murmuring)
Move out the way, get
over there too, you too.
It's alright, babe, just let him take it.
I'm not fuckin' playing.
(cash rustling)
You stole my motherfuckin' stash.
Why I'm locked the fuck up, nigga.
Don't play with me.
My motherfuckin' money.
Y'all motherfuckers got my shit,
taking their shit, living fuckin' good,
while I'm locked up in the cell,
living off my motherfuckin' shit.
Yeah, my motherfuckin' money, man.
(bag rustling)
Mom, what's going... Get your ass
over there, man.
Get your little ass over there, man.
How you gonna do me like that, nigga?
We went to high school together, bruh!
Hey, man, look.
You got what you need man,
you got what you need, bruh.
Just-
- Man, shut the fuck up, man, stop whining.
All right, all right.
Gimme this god damn money, man.
Y'all gonna take from me,
and think y'all gonna
get away with this shit,
and let it happen, nigga?
Fuck's wrong with you, man?
What you thinking?
Man, I'm sorry, bruh, like I said,
you got all the money,
you got the drugs, man.
Just let us live, bruh.
I should bust a cap in your
motherfuckin' ass, nigga.
Huh?
I shoulda killed you, man.
We went to high school
together and everything-
- That's right man, we did
go to high school together.
What you doing this for, man?
In front of my son?
Yeah, front of your-
I don't give a fuck about nothin', nigga.
I never did, nigga, you know me.
You gon' act brand new.
It's all right, man,
you got your stuff, man.
You got it, you got it, all right?
- Please, please, please.
- Just, just let us-
please, man, it's all right.
If I ain't know your
ass from high school,
I'd pop your ass right now.
I'm gonna let let you live, motherfucker.
But you ever cross me, or get in my path,
or get in my way, or come
after me, motherfucker,
I ain't lying, I'll kill you.
- Know that.
- A'ight.
(moody trap music)
(moody trap music continuing)
Yeah, man, you know
we gotta keep it going.
- Oh look.
- What's good?
You done got out, this nigga out.
Kept my mouth shut, I ain't said nothing,
I ain't know what the fuck happened.
See, you lucky you ain't
got all that fuckin' time.
You ain't get all that
time, that's this nigga.
Man, how the fuck you
get out, anyway, bruh?
- For real.
- Huh?
How the fuck you get out, man?
I kept quiet.
You know me, I don't say
a motherfuckin' thing.
Y'all niggas know me by now.
Y'all know what I do.
I don't say nothing, I don't talk.
Long as you don't say
nothing, they don't know shit.
They'll put everything against you,
like they know every god damn thing.
They don't know a motherfuckin' thing.
Well, I know who told on your ass.
I told you, like I'm thinking
with my head, I'm viewing-
That nigga, T-Bo, told on your ass.
Yeah-He told on me?
He know who the fuck I am? I'm Capone.
He ain't care about you.
Lemme tell you, T-Bo, he ain't shit, man.
This nigga!
Snitch nigga.
Hoe nigga.
Snitch nigga, you know
what happen to snitches.
You know where he live at?
He live on Rose apartments... He know.
Apartment nine?
Nine, man, Rosewood, bruh.
He ain't lie to you man.
If you gonna handle
something, I don't know nothin'.
- I don't play that shit, man.
- Kill bro.
Now that nigga about to
meet his motherfuckin' maker.
(indistinct)
It's 12 o' clock,
this boy still sleeping.
Hey, Juice, get up, come on, now.
Come on, it's 12 o' clock,
come on, bruh, get up.
What?
Come on, the mechanic just called,
your car's ready.
Damn, definitely no sleep.
Your car ready, what you gon' do?
What happened to your car?
I dunno.
What you mean, you don't know?
Man, I'll just go get the car.
Always waking me up on some bullshit.
Well I don't see no reason
why you sleep at 12, anyway.
You should be up, being
productive, let's go.
I had a long night.
Okay, so, what happened to your car?
Man... Your insurance gon' go up.
Just go on and tell me.
Kurtis scratched my car up, man.
Now see, your so-called friends
is getting you in a whole lot of trouble.
Now, where is Kurt at, now?
I don't know... Is he gonna have to
get it repaired?
- Probably not.
- You know what?
Don't even worry about it, let's go.
[Juice] You be trippin'.
I'm not tripping. (door squeaking)
You know the insurance gonna go up.
(net swooshing)
(ball bouncing)
(hoop rattling)
(ball bouncing) (mumbling)
Hey, this the guy I
was telling you about.
This Juice, man.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He supposed to be the one, man.
The prospect.
- Yes sir.
- See, we gotta put our money
on this nigga, then, man.
And that boy still hitting
that motherfuckin' dunker, man.
In the dark.
I hear you goin' to college, Juice, man.
Yes sir, trying to make something happen.
Man, see, you the only nigga
that made it out the hood,
bruh, for real.
Been a minute.
I'm tryin' to be.
Make it to college, and
then hit the league.
What's old boy from Petersburg?
Travis.
Shit, Travis... Boy, fuck that.
This nigga-
Fuck the color shit, we
gonna get us some money.
We tryin' to put some money in your pocket.
Like that nigga, LeBron.
Nigga the next LeBron.
Oh, that sound good.
Get some money in your
pocket, see, and the whole time,
we put money in our pocket.
You need something while you on the road-
- Need some shoes?
- You know he chasin'
- a little bit of hoes.
- Need a new pair
of shoes or something, man?
[Juice] Do I?
I don't even think LeBron
can guard this, dog.
Don't think about
getting no (indistinct).
You gon' bust them bitches.
(guffawing)
(mumbling)
- Yeah, good shot.
- Yes sir.
Prospect, number one prospect.
(crosstalk)
- Number one.
Yes sir.
Hey, young boy, lemme me see that.
Let me see if I still got it.
You got-
Lemme see.
(net swooshing) (exclaiming)
My boy!
- I'll get with you, though.
- Yes sir.
Hey, keep it up, baby.
My money on you, I'm countin' on you, baby.
You still
- had that shit, boy.
- I still got it!
But I'm betting on the young boys, now.
I'm betting on the young boys.
Ain't know you still have it.
Yeah, I'm bettin' on the young'uns.
(reverent choral music)
(reverent choral music continuing)
What you got on, girl?
Oh, you know I love that Versace robe.
Nah, nah, nah, I was just seeing-
what you and the girls doing next weekend?
Y'all trying to go out to The Bahamas?
Do I got it covered?
Trust me man, I just
came up with enough cash.
We'll be straight for a while.
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
All right, so, you tap in with them,
and I'll tap in with you,
and we'll make it work, all right?
Say no more.
Why would I be worrying about that?
You should be worrying about-
- What's good, nigga?
(suspenseful music) Huh?
They say you got all the
fuckin' drugs in the city.
But you know, nigga, this
is my fuckin' city, nigga.
I've been locked up.
[Dealer] Oh yeah?
You heard right then, brother.
I like the grills you got
in your motherfuckin' mouth, too, nigga.
It cost more than you, nigga.
Nigga, what, I'll
kill your ass right now,
you keep running your motherfuckin' mouth.
Give the money, nigga.
Hey, you got it, you got it.
Gimme, nigga.
You got it this time, but you ever come
lookin' for me, I'll kill
your motherfuckin' ass.
Sean Bryan, how you doing, man?
What's up coach?
- Man, it's been a minute.
- Yes sir.
You ain't even play on the team last year.
You still playing basketball
though, ain't you?
Oh, yeah, you know that.
You still playing point guard?
Always.
- Best point guard I ever had.
- Appreciate that.
You know the big street
tournaments coming up, don't you?
Oh yeah, I heard about it.
Yeah man, I need a good point guard,
if you're interested in playing in it.
(dramatic hip hop piano music)
(dramatic hip hop piano music continuing)
[Stacy] I just been thinking about us.
You know, we've been
friends since grade school.
Who would've thought we
would go to college together?
I know right?
I just hope everything falls into place,
'cause I ain't trying
to stay in those dorms.
You know what, you don't
have to stay in the dorm.
You can always live
with me, my parents will
get me an apartment across from campus.
[Juice] So you trying to stay together?
Well you know what?
We can stay together,
but don't think you gonna
bring them thots in and out my house.
What thots?
You know I ain't focusing on no thots.
M-hm, yeah. (chuckling)
Okay.
I can't stay with you.
You know your Pops will kill me.
What the hell, but you practically stayed
at my house every day, Juice.
Staying over and living
together is different.
Plus you a virgin, Pop's perfect princess.
Whatever, I'm not gonna
be a virgin for long.
Wait, wait, wait, what
that supposed to mean?
Don't worry about what it means.
Why do you care anyway?
Come on Stacy, you know I care.
You know me.
[Stacy] Yeah, I know you.
Come on, Stacy, we don't
keep secrets from each other.
Are you seeing someone?
No, I'm not seeing anyone.
The one that I want doesn't
even notice me for me.
What if he does notice?
Juice.
Stacy.
Juice, I want-
- Hold up, don't even finish that sentence.
See, that's what I'm talking about.
Stacy, hold up, hold up, hold up.
Wait, it ain't even like that.
We've been friends for a long time.
I love you and I don't want
our friendship to mess up.
I know.
Come on Stacy, I don't
ever wanna lose you.
I love you too, you'll
never lose me, I promise.
All right, but if we do decide this,
let's just take it slow.
Oh, so we gonna do this?
I guess.
(laughing)
- Oh, don't do that.
See, I knew you wanted me.
Oh, whatever, you wanted me too.
(chuckling)
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I got some good news.
Okay.
Coach want me to play in this big game.
I'm gonna be on the
north side and if we win,
I'm gonna have enough
money to get my apartment
for the whole year.
Oh, what's up, what's up?
Oh my god-
What you mean, if you win?
You were the recruiter's number one pick.
You were the best player in the district.
- Oh my God.
- You right.
I'm so happy for you.
You gonna win.
Oh my God.
(electronic hip hop music)
I got 50 on this.
- That's it?
- Yeah.
Let's get it.
(electronic hip hop music continuing)
♪ In the land of freedom, selling dope ♪
♪ Like it's my only option ♪
♪ Too much weight to flush this ♪
♪ In the safe house, case
the police knocking ♪
♪ Someone at the door ♪
♪ We gotta off whoever told 'em 'bout it ♪
♪ 30 clip, I hear they're doin' math ♪
♪ I heard they on their problems ♪
♪ 30 Perc' don't even get her high ♪
♪ She put it in her sinus ♪
♪ $30,000 in the safe off of Oxycontin ♪
♪ Either fall in line, or clear the way ♪
♪ You gon' fall behind us ♪
♪ Pop the Perc', then
build a wall so tall ♪
♪ It's gon' be hard to climb it ♪
♪ This the court of serving ♪
♪ Got 'em weighing like
the court'll find it ♪
♪ Been the hottest since hell ♪
♪ When I drop, I'm out
here, chains and chronic ♪
♪ When she get to talkin'
'bout some karma, ♪
♪ I gotta change the topic ♪
♪ Cash never touching her account ♪
♪ Now I can't make deposits ♪
♪ I made her exchange it ♪
♪ And I'm skating on some Tony Hawk shit ♪
♪ Lean get her actin' like
hoes, every homie hoppin' ♪
♪ Ballin' every day, I be goin' in ♪
♪ Like Kobe, shout it ♪
♪ You try to play the warrior ♪
♪ You end up out in Coney Island ♪
♪ On some private water by the time ♪
♪ The lawman try to find me ♪
♪ I be on this Trazo' high as hell ♪
♪ That's word to Shakari ♪
♪ It's a fast life ♪
♪ I got the memories all on my body. ♪
♪ Showcase all my art at
an exhibit if I ever die ♪
♪ Military grade artillery
made to protect narcotics ♪
♪ Nowadays, if you ain't ever flex it ♪
♪ You ain't ever bought it ♪
♪ It don't even look good ♪
♪ They just worry 'bout
how much it cost you ♪
♪ I stay in the cut ♪
♪ I like keepin' that shit to myself ♪
♪ Fuck it, we ain't even talkin' ♪
♪ Fuck it, he leavin' often ♪
♪ He gon' always score ♪
♪ The teachers scout him ♪
♪ Try to keep him off ♪
♪ If you got the keys
then you can't treat it ♪
♪ Like your secret molly ♪
♪ Plant the seeds, your family gon' eat ♪
♪ Plus you gonna feed your part ♪
♪ Plans to keep some fantasies ♪
♪ And they think I'm
still dreamin', probably ♪
♪ Three different accounts ♪
♪ I'm about to show you
just how even I'll be ♪
♪ Thinkin' like I'm Stephen Hawking ♪
♪ DB you don't need to know me ♪
♪ In the land of freedom, sellin' dope ♪
♪ Like it's my only option ♪
Yes sir.
(lighter flicks) (crickets chirping)
Yo P, go handle that shit
I told you about earlier.
All right, for sure, for sure.
- I'll hit you when it's done.
- All right.
(crickets chirping)
- Capone?
Sean Bryant, AKA Juice.
Long time no see.
Man, when the hell you get out?
I thought you was locked up.
I just got out.
I thought you was back back up north.
What you doing down here?
What's going on?
I seen you hustling boys
at Grove the other today.
You know, easy money.
You know I'm about that.
I see you doing your thing.
So what's up?
Let's take a ride, Juice.
I need you to run me somewhere.
(footsteps)
[Capone] Sweet. (chuckling)
You like that?
[Capone] Yeah, I like this.
Love this, boy. (phone chiming)
(upbeat hip hop music)
(upbeat hip hop music continuing)
Yeah man, I seen you and
that little punk ass white boy
doing y'all thing out there.
I appreciate that.
Y'all taking what y'all want.
Y'all making it happen.
Y'all just like me.
I take what the fuck I
want, and I make it happen.
I like that shit about you.
Y'know, we went to high school together,
we played ball together for that shit.
Ball ain't for me, ball for you.
- Yeah.
- Right now,
I gotta go get what's mine.
Somebody owe me some shit,
know what I'm saying?
So I'm going over here to get that shit.
Word, you gonna be straight?
Yeah, I'm gonna be straight,
know what I'm saying?
You ain't gotta worry
about nothin', just drive.
(turn signal clicking)
Know what I'm saying?
All right, bruh.
We gonna pull over right here.
We're gonna take that left,
and then we gonna make this right.
Wait right here, I'll be right back.
(door shutting)
(footsteps)
(hip hop music)
Hey, what's up, sweet thing?
I might have to bring you your favorite,
you know you love the crab legs.
(gunshot firing)
- Yeah, motherfucker!
(chains rattling)
(hip hop music continuing)
Hey, baby, I'm gon' call you back.
Let's go, nigga, let's go, man.
Man, what the hell you done did, man?
Man, I had to get back.
- Oh my God.
- Get the fuck
outta here, man. (engine starting)
(car accelerating)
Man, what the fuck you done did, man?
Don't tell me you done
killed somebody, bruh.
I heard gunshots.
Nigga, drive, man, take
me to the lofts, man.
Let's get the outta here, man.
I had to do what the fuck I had to do, dog.
[Juice] You just got out,
you couldn't resist, bruh?
Nah, I can't resist, man.
[Juice] God damn.
- Kill a motherfucker
when it's time.
[Juice] Man, you got me in this shit!
You better not tell no fuckin' body.
Man, I ain't tellin' nobody.
Just get out my shit, when it's time.
- Man, shit, drive, nigga.
- Oh my fuckin' god.
This nigga done got me in some shit.
(door squeaking) (TV quietly playing)
Damn door.
Hey, so wrong phone?
Huh?
Man, I ain't got time.
You been gone all day.
You don't call, I call you,
go straight to voicemail.
So what's the issue?
[Juice] I just got somethin' going on.
You wanna talk about it?
[Juice] Not really.
I mean something's eatin' you up.
It's not good to hold things in.
We talk about everything.
So what makes this
situation so special that
you can't talk about?
We talk about everything.
Man, I tried to look
out for an old friend,
and he done got me in some shit.
I done told you and I told
you about these friends.
You don't listen, I tell you to come to me
before things like this happen.
So who was it?
Tony, Anthony, who?
[Juice] Capone.
(chuckling)
That motherfucker I used
to date, back in the day?
Really?
Did he not just get the fuck out?
He used to keep money in my pocket.
I had to look out for him.
That's not the point.
Since Mama died, I've
done everything I can.
I know, I know... That was my promise.
To stick together.
[Juice] I know, and I'm grateful-
- We all that we have left.
But you taking a risk
every time you go out here
and do this stupid shit.
You got me here, stressed out.
You don't call, like I said.
I don't even know where
you be at half the time.
And it's unfair to me to have to sit here,
and worry about you like that.
Look man, I said I'm good.
Capone got me, so I got him.
Man, I don't wanna hear shit
about motherfuckin' Capone.
Because at this point right now,
the way I feel about him,
and what he put me through
when we was dating,
that's the last name you
should ever mention around me.
(sighing)
[Juice] Man, just hit me up.
It's not the point of hitting you up.
We need to figure out how
to get you out this situation
and cut his ass off completely.
Before you both will be
in the same damn cell.
So what we gonna do about this situation?
I mean come on, you-
we got to do something, and
we got to do something fast.
Because the way you going right now,
you either gonna be dead
or locked up with his ass.
And I'm not about to let
either one of those happen.
I got it.
Don't worry about it,
I got it. (snapping fingers)
I mean, come on.
[Juice] I got it.
And that's that same
(clapping emphatically)
attitude that I hate about you.
I said I got it!
It ain't the-
- Well you know what, since
you want to carry it like that.
Nigga, that's why I ain't even cook.
Go fix a fuckin' sandwich.
(mumbling angrily)
You know what nigga?
That's why you ate good all these years,
you still maining and containing.
And I tell you what, you better not touch
my fuckin' Kool-Aid either.
[Juice] I don't even drink
Kool-Aid, I drink Gatorade.
Oh, you uppity, nigga, okay that's good.
(suspenseful music)
Good morning, detectives.
I don't know if you guys have heard it,
but an informant was murdered.
No captain, we wasn't aware.
Well, to get you up to
speed, it was an FBI informant.
So Captain, do we have any
lead suspects, witnesses?
Sources say that it could be
Detective Kenyatta's nephew.
I want y'all to bring
him in for questioning.
- Okay Captain.
- We'll be right on it.
Now listen,
I don't need y'all messing around on this,
because the FBI's on my
head about this case.
So I need y'all to be on it, okay?
Okay.
All right, y'all can go.
Yo.
Yo, what up, Juice?
What's good with it. (hands slapping)
Nothin' much man.
Juice.
(hands slapping)
- What's good with it?
Funny thing, how we ran into you, though.
Yeah.
Y'know, so you playing
in the league this year?
Yeah, I think I'm gonna
take my talents out there.
Okay, okay, well, why don't you come play
for the south side?
Mm, south side?
Yeah, south side, man.
You know where we at.
I already holler at the
boys on the north, though.
You holler at the boys of the-
Forget them, man.
They don't need you, we need you.
Okay, south side.
- South side.
- What's in it for me?
$50,000, that's the pot.
We can all split it.
- Split?
- That's big money, man.
That sounds good, but I already
committed to the north side.
North side?
North side don't need you.
We need you, man.
(scoffing)
(mumbling)
Come on man, you on the
south side right now.
South side is where it's at, baby.
Man, I'm good everywhere.
But I already committed, though.
Look, you know who you playing for?
It's me, Cody, man.
Do you do you not know-
Four years in college, if I
hadn't blown out my ACL, man,
I would've been up there with Iverson.
Much respect, I respect that.
I definitely respect you.
Look man, I'm leading
triple doubles baby.
You know what I'm saying?
Leading score, assist, and defense.
Can't beat that, bruh.
He ain't with that-
- So, I don't think you
want to play against me.
So it's best to be on my team.
Oh nah, see, that sounds
like a challenge, baby.
You know I ain't backing
down from no challenge.
Bruh, you don't want to do that.
Hey.
So you don't wanna be on the south side?
Man, fuck you and the north side, man.
(scoffing)
- Yeah, all right,
like I said, have y'all money ready.
Have our money ready?
You right... You gon' disrespect
the OG like that though, dog?
You gonna-
- Man, fuck Juice, man.
Man, I can't believe this nigga.
Look, he probably got problems
paying tuition and everything, man.
Still eating Ramen noodles and shit, man.
That nigga named Juice, right?
- Yeah, he juice.
- Put the squeeze
on that motherfucker.
Put the squeeze on him, let's do it.
But, we do need him.
You still don't know
who the fuck I am, do you?
(tsking)
I just heard about the third killing,
and this whole entire scene.
Now, this happened to be a very big one.
'Cause otherwise, Captain
would not have us come this far.
Detectives.
- Captain.
- Good morning.
How you doing?
Detective Kenyatta.
Sources say your nephew's car was spotted
leaving the crime scene.
You are kidding me, right?
We're not 100% sure, but evidence shows
that it could be your nephew's car.
So, we're not a hundred percent sure
that it could be his nephew's car.
Well the both of you will
get to the bottom of this.
I will not have the FBI
take over this case.
We don't want it
either, but I mean, damn,
you just gave us this and we need to-
- Did you hear what I said?
I heard what you said.
Okay, well, I need you to get on the job.
I am your superior.
You listen to me.
You don't come in here
telling me what to do.
Oh and by the way, detective Kenyatta,
I've already sent two of my guys
to bring in your nephew for questioning.
I mean, come on, Cap', listen.
This cannot be his nephew.
He's like family to me, too,
and I know my damn friend-
- Hold on, we not in here for family.
We in here to do a job.
Don't make me take your badge,
because you will be out
there answering phone calls
for the rest of the damn month.
You want to take this badge?
Fine, fuck it. (badge clattering loudly)
You can leave your gun,
too, while you at it.
And don't expect no pay!
Captain, my nephew has
never been in any trouble.
I just cannot see him doing this.
Captain, he's going to college.
He's going to do something with his life.
We are going to find who really did this
because I know deep in my heart
that my nephew did not do this.
(sighing)
Captain, I'm sorry for the outburst.
(stammering)
There's no excuse, but
it just don't make sense
that his nephew, it's more like-
He's like a brother to me.
My nephew is going through this situation.
All these innocent, young, black men
constantly getting arrested and you just
have him brought in here
without even consulting us first.
That's his nephew, you
should have consulted him first.
That's all I'm saying.
But I understand you're doing your job
and I want to get to the bottom of-
I promise you, we going to
get to the bottom of it.
[Captain] I'm depending on
you guys to crack this case.
- We will.
- I ain't sayin' nothing
but a word.
- We will.
- Let's go.
(humming tune)
Sean Bryan, we need
to have a word with you.
About what?
Mr. Bryant, we need to take
you down to the precinct.
We got a serious matter
to question you about.
For what?
You don't need to worry about that.
You need to just come with us.
Come on.
Man, I ain't-
- Come on.
Come on man.
You tripping.
Come on.
(shoes scraping against concrete)
(distant speaking)
(slapping fist)
- That 50 stacks.
50 stacks, baby, you already know.
But look, if Juice don't
want to work with us,
we going to have to doggone get on John.
Bro, he out here buzzing in the streets.
I know he buzzing.
But that's why we get with John.
We convince John to throw the game our way.
Then we win,
(shoes scraping on concrete)
we secure the spot.
South side, nigga.
South side, that's what
I'm talking about, baby.
Woo! (chains rattling)
Lord, life is good. Look at
my babies, they're growing.
Success is in the movement.
Yes, beautiful.
What's up John?
What's going on, what's going on fellas?
Ah, man, Suzy Homemaker. (hands slapping)
I see you got the green thumb around here.
(church bells tolling)
- What's going on?
Always keep a green thumb.
This is my life, here.
My plants and everything else,
and my weed collection over there.
Oh, word.
I'll have some of that a little bit later.
- I bet you do.
- We came to you to talk
on some serious notes, man.
Serious about what?
Y'know, we need you to
swing the game our way.
Swing the game...
South side needs to win.
South side needs to win the game?
So, you... Yeah, nigga.
South side.
South side, bruh.
- Okay.
- You trying to
- save the streets, right?
- Yeah, I'm always
for the community.
Look, the only way you
gonna save these streets
is if you vote for south side,
and daggone ref the game our way.
- Otherwise, you got a problem.
- Look,
much love, so y'know, save yourself.
Save yourself, brother. (patting)
Seriously.
(punching) (grunting)
(grunting)
- Now do we got
- an understanding?
- Ow, man.
[Goon] South side, nigga.
You gonna ref for south side, right?
Damn, this sounds cool on a mix tape.
Whatever it takes.
Man, maybe we should hit
this motherfucker again.
Nah, I think he knows.
What side, what side?
South side, man.
There you go.
Sound like a winner now, eh?
Hey, bag me up some weed, too.
(giggling)
(groaning)
Street thugs, street thugs eat shit.
(hip hop music)
Hello, Captain.
My name is Detective Ray and this is-
- Detective Kittles.
[Captain] It's nice to meet you.
[Kittles] Nice to meet you.
You have a case that we
are mutually interested in,
and we would like to question the gentleman
that you have in custody.
Hold on, wait, this is our case.
We had this case first.
[Ray] That's true.
But the problem with that is-
the guy that you have in custody,
we believe he's our guy.
There was an informant that we had,
that we were working
with, and he was murdered.
So we really need to talk to your guy.
It's not up for debate.
We've got evidence, it's
really starting to mount up,
and it's imperative that we talk to him.
And the sooner the better.
Okay, well how about this then?
Could we, at least, be a part of this case?
I don't see a problem in that.
As long as your men stay out of the way.
Don't get too involved
and take just a step back.
And let us have the lead.
You got my word.
Okay.
What interrogation room
are you holdin' him in?
[Captain] Room three.
And what direction is that?
Down the hall, to your left.
Thank you.
[Kittles] Thank you.
- You're welcome.
(chair clattering) Motherfuckers.
Sean Bryant, I think
you know why we're here.
- I'm Detective Ray.
- I'm Detective Kittles.
[Juice] How y'all doing?
I don't know why I'm here, but-
- You don't have any idea?
[Juice] No ma'am.
[Ray] Where were you
at last Wednesday night?
Walk me through your day.
Mm.
Wednesday, early in the
morning, I had a workout
at the field house, y'know,
running up a couple bleachers.
That afternoon, I met
with my girlfriend Stacy.
We went out to eat.
[Ray] I'm gonna stop you there.
Take note of of his girlfriend's name.
What's your girlfriend's name?
[Juice] Stacy.
I need her full name.
[Juice] Stacy Marie Johnson.
And how can I contact her?
[Juice] Facebook, I guess.
No, I need her contact information.
[Ray] Does she live with you?
Phone number?
[Juice] No she doesn't,
she lives with her parents.
[Ray] Okay.
What's her phone number?
It's (434) 222-9834.
[Kittles] Okay.
And she'll be able to alibi
that you were with her the entire time?
[Juice] Yes.
[Ray] Okay.
We've got evidence that states otherwise.
So if we go looking further,
is there anything that you
think you need to tell us now?
Because you'll be in less
trouble if you tell us now.
If you don't tell us now,
we can't help you later on down the road.
We've got evidence that says otherwise.
So you might as well tell
us, because if you don't,
there's nothing we can do for you later on.
So if there's anything you haven't told us,
now is your best shot
of getting a fair deal.
Evidence?
[Ray] Yeah, evidence.
What kind of evidence do you have?
[Kittles] Well, we have evidence of a car
that looks just like yours at the scene.
Look man, I said it's not me.
I'm tired, I'm hungry and
I gotta go to the gym.
Can I go?
Is this your car?
[Ray] It looks just like your car to us.
You tell us, what are
we supposed to believe?
So you're gonna deny this.
It's not me.
There's thousands of Dodge Challengers,
and it could be anybody, it's not me.
And you expect us to believe this,
when there are probably
witnesses that we're gonna find,
that are gonna say that you were there.
[Juice] Well, ask your
witnesses, it's not me.
I'm telling you, it's not me.
This is your one chance,
and you're gonna blow it.
Do you realize how many
people actually come in here,
and they sit in that very same chair,
claiming that they're
innocent, it's not me.
You've got the wrong person.
And do you know how many
of those same people
are found later, as being
guilty and they're up there,
spending time in jail?
You don't wanna do that.
You're trying to go to school, right?
[Juice] Yes, ma'am.
Okay, then you don't wanna be doing this.
You don't wanna be lying to us,
because the truth is gonna come out.
[Juice] Okay, okay,
I get it, can I please go now?
Before we decide to let you go-
Who's this?
[Juice] I have no idea.
You've not seen him anywhere around?
[Juice] No clue, I have-
- None of the people you hang out with?
[Juice] No clue, can I go now?
Well, he was just released from prison,
and we have surveillance
of him leaving the scene,
and we believe he has
something to do with it.
[Ray] Are you sure
you don't know this guy?
[Juice] Nope, never seen him.
[Ray] It's very convenient.
[Juice] Never seen him.
All right, can I leave now?
You're free to go, but don't leave town.
(door shutting) I don't believe him.
No, there's too much evidence.
Yeah, there is.
I really think he has
something to do with it.
I think he knows this guy right here.
He's just not gonna tell us.
I think he does.
The look on his face, I think he knows him.
Oh yeah, yeah, definitely.
And I think they both had
something to do with it.
I totally agree.
We've just gotta get to the bottom of it.
Yeah, we do.
Gotta see if we can't find
some witnesses out there
- to make our case.
- We do.
(chair creaking)
We need to go tell the Captain,
and inform her of what we found out.
Yeah, this captain's not
gonna be too happy with us.
[Kittles] No.
Good afternoon detective, Captain.
[Captain] Good afternoon.
We talked to the guy,
and we really think that
he's our guy, y'know?
I don't think anybody in this precinct
is gonna believe his story, I really don't.
Everything adds up that it's him.
And to be honest with you,
all he's got for an alibi is a girlfriend.
Do you really think that
we're gonna buy that?
Well, do you guys have any evidence
that you can use to support this claim?
Let's be real here.
We're not gonna give
you everything we have.
I will give you a piece of evidence,
as I'm sure your team is
doing their own investigation,
even though we agreed to do this together.
So, I think it's only fair
that we hold back what we have
until we get more information.
But I'm gonna share this
little tidbit with you.
We believe he knows who he is.
[Kittles] And we definitely
believe he's involved as well.
Let's go somewhere
private and talk about this.
Okay, we can sit down
and have a discussion,
But I'm not gonna change my mind.
We're not gonna give
you everything we have.
[Captain] Okay.
Okay.
Lead the way.
(papers rustling)
(distant sirens)
Detective Kenyatta, we
have reason to believe
that your nephew is part of a crime.
Well, what information
do you have on my nephew?
[Ray] First of all, we're
not gonna give you everything,
like we told your Captain.
Then we might as well cut this chit-chat
and just stop it where we at, right now.
[Ray] No, I don't think
that would be a good idea.
Well, I think it would be awesome because
one thing for sure, two things for certain-
y'all not on this case, we are.
Let me break it down to you like this.
Do you know who we are?
Yeah.
[Kittles] We're definitely on it.
And we can shut you down at any time,
and we're not gonna have to give you
a shared partnership in this.
We told your Captain that we would.
Now y'all wanna play hardball,
we'll shut you down and
we'll just take the case
and solve it all by ourself.
It's your choice, the ball's in your court.
You know what?
Yeah sure, you'll be able to, y'know,
chop us down from this, no problem.
You'll be able to stop
us and take this case.
But guess what?
[Ray] What?
We already on the mission
and we almost finished it.
Oh by the way, one more thing.
Why don't you take your little tacky shirt
and you can get on outta our way,
and get your little princess too.
'Cause we about to go finish it, let's go.
Yeah, we got a case to solve.
Not if we solve it first.
Oh, we gonna beat you to it, princess.
(serene music)
(beatboxing quietly)
Yo, that's that nigga that
took my money the other day.
Sure is, that's him.
Yeah, that's him, that's definitely him.
(quiet trap music) (crickets chirping)
(ball bouncing)
(hoop rattling)
(ball dribbling)
(ball bouncing) (shoes
scraping on concrete)
(hoop rattling) (ball bouncing)
(hoop rattling)
(ball bouncing)
(hoop rattling loudly)
(net swooshing) (ball bouncing)
(hoop rattling)
Hey, yo, college boy,
you ever met a Ruger?
Don't nobody come to Grove
and try to take my money,
and live to see it.
Yeah, you got me the other day.
You got me.
You'll never play basketball again.
Never. (suspenseful music)
(ball bouncing)
(fence rattling)
(suspenseful music continuing)
(fence rattling loudly)
Nigga, I'm gonna get you.
I'm gonna get you, I'm gon' get you.
(shoes scraping dirt)
(metallic clattering)
(shovel clattering)
(shoes scraping dirt)
(crickets chirping)
(chuckling)
I know you out here.
Juice, I know you out here.
I'm gon' find you.
(crickets chirping)
I know you out here.
I know you hiding.
You couldn't have got away that fast.
I was right on you.
I know I'm close.
I can smell you.
Juice, Juice, Where you at?
I know you out here.
Come out, don't be scared.
Ain't no boys out here, just men.
Yo!
Yo.
VA Capone?
What you doing out here?
Nobody fucks with Juice, man.
It ain't got nothing to do with you.
Huh?
It got everything to do-
- It ain't got nothing
to do with you, Capone.
It got everything to do with me.
Stay out the way, Capone.
It's between me and Juice.
It ain't got nothing to do with you.
Stay out the way, Capone.
You in the motherfuckin' way.
Juice my little nigga.
If anybody got a problem with him,
they got a problem with me.
Stay out the way.
(gunshots firing)
I'm in the motherfuckin' way, nigga?
(spitting)
You in the motherfuckin' way, nigga.
It always gonna be my way.
Pussy-ass bitch.
Juice, come on, nigga, come on out man.
Capone?
Yeah, it's me.
Come on, let's go, man.
That motherfucker out here, dead.
Come on.
[Juice] Man, what the fuck?
Man, Capone, this shit is crazy, bruh.
(hands slapping)
Let's go make some money, bruh.
That's what we do.
(hip hop music continues)
All right, man, I'll get up with you.
All right, bro.
(hip hop music continuing)
Sean, are you in any trouble?
[Juice] No, I'm good.
I'm here for you, just let me know.
Unc, I got everything under control.
If I need you, I'll call you.
You keep popping up.
Sean, were you involved in any murder?
Nah, what made you say that?
The FBI had said they seen your car
in a place where a murder was committed.
Nah, not my car, it must be another car.
Are you sure?
Because if so, we can talk about this.
I'm here to help you.
Unc, I'm good.
Whatever they got on me, it ain't true.
Don't believe it.
Son, I believe you.
But if you are in any kind of
trouble, I'm here to help you.
I know, I know.
All right, Unc, for the thousandth time.
I know you got me, but I
got workouts in the morning
and I gotta go get some rest.
Well, look, if you need me, call me.
Let me know.
I know, I got you.
(footsteps) (crickets chirping)
Coach Nash.
Oh, detective Kenyatta,
how you doing, sir?
I'm doing great, sir.
How are you?
I'm good.
I just run into your nephew the other day.
He's playing for me in the big
Save the Street tournament this year.
Juice is in it?
Oh yes sir, yes sir.
He's the best point
guard I ever had, man.
I really think we gonna bring
it home this year, with him.
I'm looking forward to that.
No, I'm glad, he looks
like he doing good,
staying out the streets.
Ah, I might have to
correct you on that, sir.
[Coach] Oh, no.
- I'm trying to keep him
out of the streets.
But he's a good fellow and
he's going somewhere someday.
[Coach] Yes sir.
- I know this,
I know this.
Yes sir, he is.
Well, hopefully, this game will help
keep him out the streets.
It's supposed to be a lot of big scouts
at the game this year.
That's good to hear, yes sir.
I am happy to hear that.
All right, well, I'm gonna run in here
and get my order, and
get back to the house.
The whole family's starving.
It's very good seeing you, sir.
Well, I'll see you later, Detective.
I hope to catch you at the tournament.
Yes sir, I plan to be there.
Thank you.
(cicadas droning)
(door squeaking)
[Juice] Watch your step.
Hello.
And where have you been?
[Juice] I've been out.
(sighing)
They just showed another double homicide.
I be worried, that's why
I ask you these things.
Not to be nosy, not to pry.
I know you a grown man,
but I'm still your sister,
at the end of the day, and I worry.
Like I said, we all we got.
So when I ask you, where have you been?
Please don't get sarcastic.
I'm doing it outta love.
[Juice] Look, can we talk
about this another time?
I got things to do.
We did this situation for right now,
but we'll talk about it again.
Thank you.
Man, please don't be in
there fucking all night,
makin' no babies.
- Thank you.
- Man, don't listen.
Whatever.
What's wrong, are you good?
I'm all right.
You alright?
I think I gotta tell you something.
Okay.
What do you gotta tell me?
[Juice] You know Capone?
Yeah, your sister's ex, yeah.
(chuckling)
I think he got me into something,
and it's gonna be hard to get out of.
Something, like what?
What are we talking about?
I might be part of a double homicide.
A double homicide?
[Juice] Double homicide.
Stop playing with me.
I gave him a ride-
Knowing how Capone is,
I just wanted to thank him.
He always looked out for me, so
I felt like I had to do the favor.
(sighing)
We go to the apartment, he run in there,
and I think he murdered two people.
Juice, what about your scholarship?
What about us?
We just agreed to take our
friendship to the next level.
Oh my God, now, oh my God.
I'm an accessory to a murder
after the fact, Juice!
Man, we gonna be all right, just relax.
Relax, relax?
You know, I can go to jail for this.
Oh my God, I cannot.
Stacy.
Stacy, tell me you ain't
gonna give up on me.
I'm not gonna give up on us.
(sensual music)
(clapping)
(sensual music continuing)
So, see boy, y'know, I'm just-
wanted to see what's up with you,
and see if we can, y'know, kick it
outside of here sometime,
instead of, you know,
around everybody.
I'm gonna have to check my schedule,
see where I can fit you in at. (scoffing)
Oh really?
Yes.
Yeah, check your schedule.
- On gang.
- I want you to fit me in,
all right?
You know money come first.
Absolutely.
I got a little spot I wanna, y'know-
- So don't feel bad if I can't
put you in the first spot,
maybe I can put you in the second spot.
Well, I ain't trying
to be in the second spot.
I want to have that number one spot.
You gonna have to come a little closer,
if you want that number one spot.
Okay.
What I gotta do to do that?
I'll let you know.
- You'll let me know?
- Yeah.
Okay.
I'll get back right with you.
Damn.
All in your guts.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I may not like that shit.
Smoke a few blunts, if you don't like it,
the money gonna make sure you like it.
Mm, okay, I'm down with that.
(hands brushing denim)
I'm 'bout to have to pick you up
and take you to the back.
(giggling)
Bend that ass over.
- Oh really?
- Yeah.
Think you can handle that?
I ain't 'bout no talk.
It's gonna be more than talk,
cause I'm gonna walk it.
And I stand behind it.
Okay. Like, I stand up in-
(futon creaking)
Damn!
(metallic clattering) What the fuck-
(futon creaking) (moaning)
Oh, shit.
(door creaking)
Get up.
Yeah, T-Bo.
Oh, Capone.
It's me.
Yeah, nigga, we go way
back, don't we, nigga?
Yeah, we go way back to you
ratting on me, motherfucker.
So I caught your motherfuckin' ass, nigga.
I went by your mama crib,
you weren't over there.
I went by your sister crib,
look like you got some
undercover cops and shit over there.
They shot at me, so I shot
back at the motherfuckers.
Couldn't find you, so I had to get my girl
to set your ass the fuck up,
you know what I'm saying?
She one of my runners, do shit for me.
So you gonna go tell the feds on me,
get me locked up, and let them other niggas
go in my motherfuckin' stash?
We supposed to be a team.
Bitch ass nigga, you done fucked me up
from getting my nut, nigga.
Shit, fuck you, nigga.
I'm glad I told on your bitch ass.
[Red] Man, you thought you was
gonna get a motherfuckin' nut?
Stupid.
You gonna break fuckin' code?
And be a fuckin' rat?
And rat me the fuck out, nigga?
Cost me two years of my
motherfuckin' life, nigga.
Smoke a cigarette and
go back to trapping.
You take your ass to sleep.
Sleep.
And this bitch ass nigga
right in front of me
with his little bitch ass gun,
like he gonna do something, man.
Nigga, what the fuck you say?
You think I'm playing with you, T-Bo?
[T-Bo] Fuck you, Capone.
Nigga, you broke the
motherfuckin' code, nigga.
You supposed to be true to the code,
nigga, never snitch.
[T-Bo] What if I did?
- Motherfucker, you did.
- [T-Bo] Ain't no code
in these streets.
That nigga smoke me, you
gonna get it back in blood, nigga.
You got a fuckin' problem with me, nigga?
Blow me, nigga!
Every man for their fuckin' self.
You cost me two years of my
motherfuckin' life, nigga.
[T-Bo] Well, you still here.
(punching)
- Motherfucker!
You think I'm playing with you, nigga?
Huh?
Get the fuck up, T-Bo.
[T-Bo] Fuck you, Capone.
Get up, nigga.
[Red] Get up, snitchin' ass motherfucker.
Fuck you do, nigga?
You see this bullet...
You ain't no better than me.
[Woman] Shut the fuck up, T-Bo.
Shut the fuck up.
- [T-Bo] Ain't no better
than me, shut the fuck up.
[Red] Whatever.
[Capone] Get the fuck up, man.
- Fuck you, nigga.
- Get up.
The fuck up, nigga.
That ain't hurt you,
get the fuck up, nigga.
(hip hop music continuing)
(punching)
(gunshot firing)
You should've kept your mouth shut, T-Bo.
Let's go, Red.
(grunting)
(sensual music)
(suspenseful music)
(crickets chirping)
(car door shutting)
(suspenseful music continuing)
[Capone] Yo, Juice.
I heard you're talking to the FBI.
You mention my name to 'em?
Nah, bruh, they came to pick me up,
but I ain't told 'em nothin'.
Who's your little bitch right here?
(stammering)
Huh, who's your little bitch right here?
That's Stacy, bruh.
Stacy?
Miss Stacy.
[Juice] You trippin'.
You know you trippin'.
I don't trust no fuckin' body, man.
Why the hell you killed T-Bo?
Nigga, man, snitched on me, man.
Man got me locked up.
That's why I was locked the fuck up.
'Cause that nigga, man.
So I had to get him back.
[Juice] You killed him, man?
Oh my God.
Yeah, I killed that motherfucker, man.
He deserved it, he a snitch, man, he a rat.
Nigga run to the cops and started talkin'.
And I hope you ain't like that, either.
Or I'm gonna have to do you in.
Can you put the gun down, please?
Man, this is my motherfuckin'
savior right here.
I need this.
Without this, I ain't shit.
Please put the gun down.
- [Capone] Put the gun down?
- Please put it down.
[Capone] You know what... Please.
I ain't trip over niggas.
As soon as I think y'all
ain't shit, it's a rap.
You know something, if I hear anything,
I know you said something.
I won't be saying nothin'.
[Capone] You know,
you somethin' right now,
you cross me, you'll be nothin'.
Don't fuck with me, Juice.
[Juice] Come on, let's go.
Yeah, man, my nigga
pulling up right now, man.
I'm gonna hit you back bro.
(hip hop music)
- Yo, what up, what up.
- Sunny, my boy.
(hands clapping)
Man, they fucked around.
(hands clapping) said Ruger died, bruh.
What?
Yeah, smoked him, bruh.
That bitch ass nigga Juice?
The ball-shootin' nigga?
Man, we gotta go get... My cousin, bruh?
Gotta go get him, bruh.
Man, come on, man.
(muttering in agreement)
(hip hop music continuing)
Hey, yo, don't none of y'all niggas know
where that nigga live at, man?
Nah, I used to know
where that nigga live at.
But his mama died, man,
so that nigga gone ghost.
Shit, man, I think I know where he-
I think he be posted over
there by the college and shit, yo.
[Sunny] The joint downtown?
- Yeah.
Oh yeah, we about to ride through there.
[Goon 2] We need to swing by there, yeah.
[Goon 3] Go.
[Goon 2] Man, I got
this brand new ARP, man.
I can't wait to put it on the gat, yo.
[Sunny] Shit, I'm already gone, nigga.
This motherfuckin' nine can't
wait to blow this nigga out.
[Goon 2] Somebody got to get got.
[Goon 3] Got to.
I got 30 with mine, too.
Hell yeah-[Goon 2] Fireworks in the
motherfucker, and you heard me.
[Goon 3] Heard-
(hip hop music)
There goes Max,
just the biggest drug
dealer here in Virginia.
Man, we done looked for
this nigga everywhere, bruh.
That nigga ain't at the rec center.
Ain't at the college.
Nigga ghost, ain't he?
Oh yeah, that bitch ass nigga
gon' get what he got coming.
Definitely gonna find that nigga, for sure.
Man, somethin' gotta happen, bruh.
Damn bunch of hoodlums.
Really to crack to all our
good people, here in this town.
I ought to bust them right now.
But I got to wait, but I will get them.
Hello?
Yo.
What?
(suspenseful music) 33rd avenue.
All right, bet.
Come on, we gotta go.
Hell yeah.
(car door shutting) (engine starting)
(car accelerating)
(suspenseful music continuing)
(ball dribbing)
- Stole this ball
like I stole your heart.
Okay, you got a little skill,
okay, okay, - Yep, yep.
I like that.
- [Stacy] Mhm.
So, what you been up to?
(sighing)
[Stacy] You know, you
know, just studying.
That's about it, I know you've been busy.
Yeah, trying to make
it, trying to make it.
Trying to make it, yeah.
Hoops and hustle.
[Stacy] I'm so proud of you.
I ain't do nothin' yet,
but I'm gonna make you proud of me.
Okay, you already did.
You got a scholarship into one of the
highest schools in Virginia.
That's a blessing.
It is a blessing.
I believe you gonna take it for 'em.
I hope so, I'm putting in this work.
We'll see how far it go.
I believe in you.
Said 33rd Avenue, man,
it's right over here.
[Goon 2] Where they fuck they at, man?
Nigga's right there.
[Goon 2] Aw shit, hold on.
Lookin' pretty, motherfucker. (gun cocking)
(ball bouncing)
[Juice] Whoa.
[Goon 3] Get that bitch ass nigga.
[ Goon 2] Motherfucker,
get down, get down!
Shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up.
Bring your ass on, bring your ass on.
Put 'em in the back, yo.
[Goon 2] In the car.
[Juice] Damn, homie.
Do what they say, just do what they say.
(car door shutting)
(car door opening)
[Goon 2] Bitch, don't say a word.
(whimpering)
- Okay.
[Goon 3] Yeah, motherfucker,
we got y'all, now.
[Goon 2] Bitch, shut the fuck up.
Y'all know y'all gonna die tonight, right?
[Goon 3] I'm telling you, hell.
(whimpering)
Yeah, Juice, I've been
looking for you for a minute.
Yeah, I got you now.
(suspenseful music continuing)
Hey, lil' bro, I need you
to take this back to the spot.
Give me that strap, take
this bread back to the spot,
and pick us up in the hour.
Nah, nah, man.
Man, fuck that, we 'bout to do them.
Nah, nah, you got a
basketball career, though.
That shit means more to
niggas than anything, man.
You feel me?
So, lemme get that strap,
you take this bread.
Go on and take this car back.
We about to do 'em.
All right.
(plastic crinkling)
[Sunny] Get ya'll ass out the car.
(shoes scraping on ground)
(suspenseful music continuing)
[Sunny] Move.
[ Goon 2] He said move.
[Sunny] Let's go.
Move.
[Goon 2] Move, man.
Come on, man.
[Sunny] Get your ass up there.
(shoes scraping on ground)
[Sunny] Keep it moving.
[Juice] Do what they
say, do what they say.
[Goon 2] Man, let's
kill these motherfuckers,
and throw them in the river.
[Sunny] This enough right here.
Stop right here.
(Stacy breathing heavily)
[Juice] Do what they say.
[Sunny] Yeah, you know
who killed my cousin.
I don't know, bruh.
[Goon 2] Nigga, talk, nigga...
[Juice] Bruh-
I said I don't know, bruh.
(punching)
[Stacy] Oh my God.
- Shut up!
[Sunny] You know who killed my cousin.
[Juice] I said I don't fuckin' know.
(punching) (Stacy whimpering)
[Sunny] You better
come up with some answers
real fuckin' fast.
'Cause they said my
cousin was with you last.
I'm telling you, I don't
know your fuckin' cousin, man.
- Oh, you know my cousin.
- Fuck.
[Stacy] Please
don't kill him.
- [Goon 2] Shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
Or your ass'll be floatin' with the fishes.
[Juice] Just do what they say.
[Sunny] Both of y'all gonna die tonight.
[Juice] Damn, bro.
Yeah, you know my cousin.
Who was your cousin, bro?
Yeah, Ruger, nigga.
You know Ruger.
(punching)
[Stacy] Please don't kill him.
Shut up, bitch!
Before I off your top, now.
Ruger fucked with you, even
after I told him not to.
[Juice] Damn, bruh.
Hurry up and
off that nigga, man.
(distant train horn blaring)
Send him to his mama.
[Juice] Fuck you!
[Sunny] Oh yeah, he going meet his mama.
(train horn blaring louder)
He definitely doing that
tonight.
Yeah, him and his lil' chick.
(train horn blaring)
No balling for you no more.
[Goon 2] College boy.
Matter of fact, tell my nigga, Ruger,
I love him, when you get there.
[Goon 2] Give your mama a kiss, nigga.
- Freeze.
- Drop the weapon-
(gunshots firing)
(gunfire continues)
(gunshot firing)
(dramatic hip hop music)
Fuckin' pig.
(gunshot firing)
(dramatic hip hop music continuing)
[Unc] Are ya'll okay?
[Stacy] Thank you so much for saving us.
[Juice] Unc-
- [Unc] I was right,
I have been telling y'all
I kinda thought something was up,
so that's why I decided to follow.
[Stacy] Juice, what happened?
Who were they?
[Juice] I don't know, he keeps saying
something about his cousin, bro.
[Stacy] I cannot... [Unc] What about him?
- [Juice] I don't know.
- [Unc] Can you fill me in?
[Juice] I don't know, Unc.
[Stacy] Are you okay? (Juice spitting)
Juice, I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry, I know I
said I'll stick with you
through anything, but
we almost died tonight.
[Juice] Just gimme one more chance.
- One more chance.
- I can't do it,
I can't watch you die.
I'm sorry, I-
- [Stacy] I'm not gonna die.
[Stacy] No I can't, I'm sorry.
(sobbing)
[Juice] Damn, Unc.
Come here, Stacy.
(sobbing) Stacy, come here.
[Stacy] Just let me go, Juice!
(distant sobbing)
Man, thanks, Unc, man.
My bad man, you saved me again.
[Unc] That's what I am here for, nephew.
That's what I'm here for.
[Juice] Let's just go.
(reverent hip hop music playing)
Hey.
Yeah, I just called my brother.
Yeah, we gonna get that nigga, Capone.
We gonna kill him, yo.
So we can get our shit back.
Yeah.
(reverent hip hop music continuing)
Yeah, what's up?
So I touch down tomorrow.
And when I do, I'll call you.
Everything is done.
(reverent hip hop music continuing)
(car door creaking)
(gunshots firing)
(heavy gunfire)
(gunshot firing)
(magazine clattering on ground)
(magazine clicking)
(heavy gunfire)
(gunshot firing)
You motherfuckers try to kill me?
You know who the fuck I am, nigga?
I'm Capone.
Sweet kiss goodnight, motherfucker.
(gunshot firing) (gunshot firing)
(shoes scraping on ground)
Motherfucker!
(dramatic music)
Who the fuck is you, huh?
Take your mask off and show
your motherfuckin' face, nigga.
Ghost?
I'm ready to meet my maker, motherfucker.
You just be ready to meet yours.
(chuckling)
(gunshot firing)
(shoes scraping ground)
Motherfucker, man.
Look at this shit.
Ghost, you know what?
- [Ghost] What's up?
You'll die soon, motherfucker.
(chuckling) - [Ghost] Not before you.
[Capone] You'll die soon, bitch.
(chuckling) - [Ghost] Crawl for me.
There you go.
Yeah, crawl for Daddy.
(laughing triumphantly)
Look at this-
Look at you bleeding.
(chuckling) I run this now.
Oh yeah, I took your two kilos.
I took them, and I'm takin'
everything else you got, too.
(chuckling)
[Ghost] Ah, go on and breathe
your last breath, come on.
(gunshots firing) (Ghost exclaiming)
(hip hop music playing)
Oh man. this is going to be
a crazy, crazy game right here.
Now I have to get prepared for this.
Who's gonna help me?
And I'm the referee of this,
and I gotta deal with young thugs.
I'm all for the community.
Come on man, I'm an activist.
(sighing)
If it ain't one thing, it's another.
Now, they want me to throw the game.
With all seriousness,
I don't want to do this.
It's not worth it.
It's not my challenge.
It's not what I live for.
For God's sakes!
(electronic hip hop music)
Here, for the Save our Streets campaign,
with $50,000 on the line.
That's right, $50,000.
25 will either go to the north,
or the 25 could go to the south.
But we can guarantee you the other 25
is going of the respectable
community outreach programs
that that they are trying to do.
Bread on ya'll.
There you go.
All right, that's what I'm talkin' 'bout.
- There we go.
- Yes sir.
Oh!
(hoop rattling)
All right! That's what-
- Okay, bring it in guys, bring it in.
All right, y'all looking
good out there, real good.
All right, now, we got
$50,000 riding on this game.
50 percent of that goes to the city.
We get to split the rest of
it to do whatever we want.
(murmuring)
[Coach] Hopefully, well,
they beat us every year, so-
Hopefully this year we got it.
We got a good squad.
Got one supposed to be
coming, he might be a little late.
- We need him.
- Where's he at?
Where's he at?
Oh, there he go. (Juice clapping)
There he go.
- There he go.
- Let's get it, baby.
Let's go.
(crosstalk)
He played for me in high
school and everything.
He knows how I coach everything.
We all good.
All right, baby, let's
get these thousands.
I wanna know why y'all here.
We here 'cause we gon' win.
I said I wanna know - We gonna win,
we gonna win!
- why ya'll here.
Why are ya'll here?
We gonna win.
What side is it?
South side!
Line up, line up!
Yeah, yeah, woo!
Let's get it, woo!
Come on!
Bring it in, guys, north side, on three.
North side, baby.
1, 2, 3,
- North side!
- Yeah, baby,
we got money on y'all fellas, man.
Need this, man. (clapping)
This is what we've been waiting for.
We've been waiting on this.
Yes sir.
Get this line, ready, get this line goin'.
50,000.
Guys, we're done with warmups.
All right, let them hoop and holler
and psych their selves
out all they want to.
We gonna stay focused and
get our head in the game.
I don't mind you psyching yourself up, but-
Let's be a little bit
more classy than that.
Gotcha.
Let's focus on the prize.
- All right, let's go guys.
- Yeah.
One more time, north side on three.
1, 2, 3-
- North side!
(crosstalk)
They ain't ready for it.
Hey, too bad I didn't bring no pom-poms
to cheer y'all on, but
we about to win this!
Hey, tell your preacher
over there to pray.
Tell your preacher to pray for y'all.
Shouldn't have showed up.
Oh man, he's a bum!
Hail Mary, baby-
- You a traitor, he's a bum!
♪ No shot, no shot, no shot- ♪
Hey, somebody give them a record deal.
(laughing)
- Fuck outta here.
Fuck outta here.
We gonna let the ball
do the talkin', man.
- Yeah!
- I got 50 on me, right now.
Let's go, let's go.
Alright fellas, I got
a lot of bread on y'all.
Y'all looking good and warmed up.
Y'all feel good about this?
Gotta go out there... We got this.
South side, baby.
Yeah, rep that south side, baby.
(crosstalk)
For sure, let's do it.
Let's get it, let's get this money, baby.
- Get this money.
- Get it.
Matter of fact, I'm gonna
show you how we get down.
Show you how south side get down-
(shouting)
(whistle blowing)
(shouting, whistle blowing)
South side, baby, south side!
South side, baby!
What's up, baby! (whistle blowing)
Hey, hold it!
We're gonna have a clear
game, and a real game!
Save the beef for Arby's, okay?
(ball bouncing)
Let's keep this movin'.
Okay, let's get the ball
in the court, let's go!
Hey, remember what I told you, right?
South side's winnin'.
Sounds good on mix tape,
but don't make that no more.
Play your game, and do your hustle.
(team muttering)
All right guys, first
off, we got starting
Josh, Kurt, and Juice.
And we already see what they're all about.
They a bunch of thugs and hustlers,
like they are every year.
And will never bring real
basketball players to a game.
They always just want the money.
But we gonna show 'em what
basketball players do.
Alright, Juice, get
ready for the coin toss.
[Juice] Let's get it.
- Yeah.
- Let's do this.
(clapping)
Alright fellas, let's keep
it clean, like caffeine.
What do you want?
- Heads or tails?
- Heads, heads.
- What do you want?
- Gotta take tails.
All right, let's go.
Heads it is.
- Told you.
- All right,
I ball, good luck, boy.
[Juice] Let's get it.
(whistle tweeting)
Come get the ball, man.
Hope you brought your A-game, nigga.
♪ Decisions not to play with them ♪
♪ I ain't seen niggas in years ♪
♪ And I ain't never actin' like ♪
♪ I wouldn't live for them, facts ♪
♪ When shit got heavy ♪
♪ I had the mental space to hold it down ♪
♪ Gotta exercise your mental, day to day ♪
♪ You want to hold this crown ♪
♪ Who would've thought by making plays ♪
♪ I have a golden smile, the golden child ♪
♪ When I got off in that payday, ♪
♪ Had to throw the towel ♪
♪ Facts, they controllin'
you ♪ (clapping, whistling)
(hoop rattling)
(shouting)
♪ Yeah, only the finest of the finest ♪
♪ Can't stop, won't stop,
nigga, let's get it ♪
(shoes scraping on concrete)
(hoop rattling)
Let's go, bro, let's go.
(rap music)
(hoop rattling)
Man, what y'all doing, man?
Coach ain't see that!
You ain't see that, you ain't
see that, you ain't see that!
Coach, foul, foul me! (whistle blowing)
♪ Rap game was like a new Latin ♪
♪ And I can show the scars ♪
♪ Started rappin', it
was for the accolades ♪
♪ And foreign cars ♪
♪ Then I realized- ♪
Come on, let's get it
together, man, come on.
Lock up, play smart, let's go.
Come on, come on, come on,
what up south side?
South side, y'all ain't doing nothing.
Y'all ain't doing nothing, c'mon.
(rap music continuing)
I need you to get out there,
do what you gotta do.
Hurt, hurt, hurt somebody.
You feel me? (slapping elbow)
South side, come on, come on, man.
- Come on, man.
- Why?
We got this.
Got 50,000 at stake, you buggin'.
I'm buggin'?
Yeah, you gonna sit out.
What, how you gonna take me out?
Do what you gotta do, man. (murmuring)
Man, fuck.
(murmuring)
- South side.
All right.
♪ I been trying to work
on my reactions, whoa ♪
♪ Try to act accordingly,
and in a timely fashion ♪
Are you okay?
We got an injured player.
Take time out.
All right, come on.
- You all right, Kurt?
Get you some water,
buddy, get you some water.
Walk it off,
- you'll be alright.
- I got you, dog.
Alright Larry, you
ready to get in the game
and show him what you got?
[Larry] I'm ready.
Let's go, Larry.
Let's get it, let's get it, let's get it-
- [Coach] Can somebody get
Kurt some water, please?
(hands clapping)
- That's what I'm talking.
- You did your thing, baby.
That's what I'm saying,
we got money on the line.
We got money on the line.
(crosstalk)
Let's go get this money.
Some stacks, we gotta get this y'all.
Y'all doing great, that
50 stacks looking good.
You know what I'm saying?
Another one.
We need another one, for real.
(crosstalk)
Yo, that ref, man,
I dunno what's up with him.
We need to get the ref after this one-
- We gotta get you back in the game.
Keep bodyin' 'em, baby, south side.
- South side.
South side, south side!
(rap music)
(rap music continuing)
(concrete scraping) (whistle blaring)
(whistle blaring)
South side, south side!
Oh, motherfucker.
[Ref] Take care, time out, time out!
Time out, time out! (crosstalk)
Time out, here.
(whistle blaring)
This some bullshit, man.
Ref let all that shit slide.
(whistle tweeting) -
Takin' all our players.
Yes, Coach, we're gonna make
sure everything is secure.
Okay, I want you guys to make sure that
everything is okay with them, all right?
That's your job.
Hey coach, we gotta go harder.
Well, I mean, they got all our plays,
and look like they done bought the ref.
I mean you gotta figure him out.
Come up with something new.
We gotta go in, now.
They takin' out everybody.
[Juice] Hey, let's get it.
Let's go here. We got North.
(crosstalk)
North side, on three.
1, 2, 3.
North side!
Come on, come on, come, come on.
I got you, I got you.
Yeah, yeah, south side.
(ball bouncing)
- South side, baby,
south side. (ball bouncing)
(hip hop music)
(hip hop music continuing)
Man, what the-
(Stacy clapping)
- Yes!
(hip hop music continuing)
Go, Juice, go!
Get 'em, baby!
Man, what ya'll doin'?
(hip hop music ends)
(ball bouncing)
- South side!
(hoop rattling) (cheering)
Yeah, that's what I'm talkin' 'bout!
[Juice] Game.
Man, fuck you, you ain't win no game!
Didn't I tell you to call the shots, man?
Huh? (whistle tweeting)
Fuck this shit, man, fuck this shit.
Gimme the motherfuckin'
gun, - [Goon] Chill, chill!
Gimme the motherfuckin' gun!
Come on, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Didn't I tell you
motherfuckers, huh, huh?
(gunshot firing)
[Kittles] Drop the gun!
(gunshot firing) (gun clattering)
Shots fired, I need units-
Dispatch, all units to
the Save the Street event.
Please, soon. - [Narrator] Juice ends up
losing his scholarship,
and serving three years
behind bars for accessory to murder.
They finally figured it out.
His car was at the crime scene.
So now you see, how the street life
can change anyone's life.
People end up dead,
people end up locked up.
The street life is not where it's at.
(hip hop music)
(hip hop music continuing)