* What you want, *
* Baby, I got *
* What you need, *
- Excuse me, coming through here...
* You know I got it *
- Got a wet mop here.
* All I want you to do *
* for me is give it to me *
- Coming through, right behind ya.
* When you get home *
* Yeah, baby, whip it to me, when you get home *
- Coming through there! Watch your back
* R-E-S-P-E-C-T *
* Find out what it means to me *
* R-E-S-P-T-B-C *
* Take care, T-C-B *
* Oooh, a little respect *
* Sock it to me, sock it to me, sock it to me, sock it to me  *
* When you come home ba... *
- What you take me for,
you'll never work on this planet again!
- I'll just take this as my break!
- Heelpsa, meee-sa!
- Yoousa must warn everyone!
- Hey, aren't you that guy from...
- Yoousa must warn!
- Oh for heaven's sake!
-The Chubbchubbs are coming!
- But what's a Chubbchubb?
- Holy shoot!
* Ooh, your kisses, *
* Sweeter than... *
- Hey everbody!
- This guy just told me that....
- Whaat?!
- Look people I'm trying to tell you that..
- I'm just not good at this....
- Hey everbody!
- I just heard the Chubbchubbs are coming!
- Chubbchubbs?
- Everybody remain calm...
- This is no time to panic.
- Whoo! Maybe this is a good time to panic!
- Wait for me!
- Oh you guys!
- What are you doing here? You gotta get out of here...
- before the thing...
- Shoot!
- Come here guys.
- Come here, come here...
- Whatever you are.
- The Chubbchubbs are almost...
- here.
- Oooh.. we are toast.
- Don't move.
- Hey friends!
- Guys...
- Can't we be friends?
* Why can't *
* We be friends? *
* Why can't we be friends? *
* The color of your skin *
* don't matter... *
* To me... *
* As long as we can *
* live in harmony *
* Why can't we be friends? *
* Why can't we be... *
* we be friends? *
* Friends? *
- It's the Chubbchubbs!
- Mami...!
- Oooh... nice Chubbchubbs...
- Wow... you guys are like furry little prisonarts
- Aren't you?
- So eeh,...
- You guys into...
- Karaoke?
* Ooh, your kisses, *
* sweeter than honey *
* But guess what, *
* so here's my money *
* All I want you to do for me *
* Is give it to me *
* when you get home *
* Yeah, baby, *
* Whip it to me *
* Just a litle bit, just a little bit *
* C-B-S and M-T-V *
* Find out what it means to me *
* T-S-I-B-I-P take your T-V-C *
* A little respect *
* Ooh, baby, a little respect. *