(computer voice) Stasis interrupted.
Fire in cryogenic compartment.
Repeat, fire in cryogenic compartment.
All personnelreport to...
..emergency escape vehicle launch pod.
Deep-space Flight will commence
in Tminus 20 seconds.
(alarm)
Oh, Jesus Christ!
- What a way to make a landing!
- Get the torch!
How many?
- Don't know! Three, maybe four!
- Hey, Frank! Can we hurry this up!
lt's gonna be 40 below in five minutes!
Whoa!
- (dog barks)
- Come here!
- l'll kill him!
- What's that?
That stupid dog ofyours!
Get it out of here!
- Come on, boy. Come on.
- (barking)
- Get rid ofthat dog!
- He's gone!
A bad way to go, huh?
Hey, Frank, come on, let's go! Let's go!
Wait!
One ofthem is still alive!
Right. We'll need all ofthose.
That's it. OK. You're all right.
(barking)
This is Rumour Control.
Here are the facts.
As some ofyou know,...
..a 337 model EEV...
..crash-landed here at 0600
on the morning watch.
There was one survivor,...
..two dead, and a droid that was
hopelessly smashed beyond repair.
The survivor is a woman.
- (laughter)
- ls she pretty?
l just want to say that
l've taken a vow of celibacy...
..that also includes women.
We've all taken the vow!
Shut your gob, Morse!
l don't appreciate company policy...
..allowing her to intermingle
with the inmates and the staff!
Our brother means to say
we view the presence of any outsider,...
..especially a woman,...
..as a violation ofthe harmony,
and potential break in the spiritual unity.
We are aware ofyour feelings
in this matter.
You will be pleased to know
that l have requested...
..a rescue team.
Hopefully they will come this week...
..and evacuate her ASAP.
Don't give us that!
- What's her medical status?
- She doesn't seem too badly damaged.
She's unconscious.
Can't give a more specific diagnosis.
- Will she live?
- l would think so.
Look!
lt's in everybody's interest
she doesn't leave the infirmary...
..until the rescue team arrives.
Certainly not without an escort, right?
Sir.
Gentlemen! We should all stick to our
set routine, and not get unduly agitated!
Correct?
All right.
Thank you, gentlemen.
(sighs)
All right.
Better get here soon.
What's that?
Just a little cocktail of my own mix.
A sort of eye-opener.
You a doctor?
My name is Clemens.
l'm the Chief Medical Officer here.
- Here?
- Fury 161.
lt's one ofWeyland-Yutani's
backwater work prisons,...
..it grieves me to say. Do you mind?
This is a stabiliser.
l really ought to shave your head.
We have a big problem with lice here.
When you feel better l'll give you
some clippers for your private parts.
How did l get here?
You... crash-landed in an EEV.
Evidently separated from your mother
ship before you hit our atmosphere.
Any idea how long you've
been in hypersleep?
Coming out that way can jolt your system.
- l'll be sick for a couple ofweeks.
- lndeed.
Where are the others?
They didn't make it.
What?
They didn't survive.
l have to get to the ship.
- You're in no condition for that.
- You wanna get me some clothes, or...
..should l go like this?
Given the nature of our indigenous
population, l would suggest clothes.
None ofthem has seen a woman in years.
Neither have l, for that matter.
(Clemens)
This used to be a 5,000-convict facility.
But it's been reduced
to a custodial... staff of 25.
- Why?
- To keep the pilot light on.
Pilot light for what?
Blast furnace!
Natural methane!
We have a foundry, Lt. Ripley!
The inmates forge lead sheets
for toxic waste containment!
How do you know my name?
lt's stencilled on the back ofyour shorts.
(prisoner) Release the cable!
Where are the bodies?
We have a morgue. We've put them there
until the investigative team arrives.
ln about a week, l think.
- There was a droid.
- Disconnected.
He was in bits and pieces. We put
what was left on the rubbish tip.
The corporal was impaled...
..by that safety support.
Never knew what hit him.
And the girl?
She... drowned in her cryo-tube.
l don't think she was conscious...
..when it happened. l'm sorry.
- (gasps)
- What's the matter?
- Where is she?
- ln the morgue.
l have to see her.
l have to see what's left of her.
Oh, God, there you are!
l've been looking everywhere for you!
Where you been, huh?
(dog pants)
Come here!
You OK?
Let me see, Spike. Let me see.
Are you OK?
Let me see.
What have you been
sticking your face into?
Hey!
- (whimpers)
- Did somebody do this to you?
What kind of animal
would do this to a dog?
Um,...
..could l have a moment alone, please?
Yes, of course.
(whispers) Forgive me.
What's she doing?
OK?
No.
We have to do an autopsy.
- What?
- l told you.
We have to make sure how she died.
And l told you... she drowned.
l'm not so sure. l...
l have to see inside of her.
You're disorientated.
l have a very, verygood reason.
Perhaps you'd like
to share that reason?
Possible contagion.
What kind, exactly?
- Cholera.
- Cholera?
There hasn't been a case of cholera
reported for 200 years.
(whispers) Please?
Everything's in place.
There's no sign of infection.
No indication of disease.
Her chest. Open her chest.
Careful.
Lungs...
..flooded with fluid.
Ergo, she drowned.
Now,...
..since l'm not a complete idiot,...
..would you tell me
what we're really looking for?
(door opens)
Mr Clemens!
Superintendent!
l don't believe you've met
Lieutenant Ripley.
- What's going on, Mr Clemens?
- That's right, sir. What's going on?
First,...
..the lieutenant is feeling much better,
l'm happy to say.
Second,
in the interest of public health,...
- ..l am performing an autopsy.
- Without my authority.
There didn't seem to be time.
But it's turned out all right.
- There's no sign of contagion.
- Good.
lt might help if Ripley didn't parade
around in front ofthe prisoners.
As l am told she did in the last hour.
lt might also be helpful...
..if you informed me of any
change in her physical status.
- Or is that asking too much?
- We have to cremate the bodies.
Nonsense! We'll keep the bodies on ice...
- ..till the rescue team arrives.
- On ice.
There is the public-health issue.
The lieutenant feels there is still the
possibility of a communicable infection...
l thought you said
there was no sign of disease?
lt would appearthe child drowned.
But without proper laboratory tests
it's impossible to be certain.
l would consider it unwise to tolerate even
the possibility of an unwelcome virus.
An outbreak of... cholera...
..would look extremely bad on a report,
would it not, sir?
We've 25 prisoners in this facility,...
..all double Y chromos,...
..all thieves, rapists, murderers,
child molesters. All scum.
Just because they've taken on religion
doesn't make them any less dangerous.
l try not to offend their convictions.
l don't want to upset the order.
l don't want ripples in the water.
And l don't want a woman
walking around, giving them ideas.
l see.
For my own personal safety.
Exactly.
l will leave the details ofthe cremation
to you, Mr Clemens.
They may use the furnace, but l want
everyone back in lockup by 2200 hours.
We commit this child and this man
to Your keeping, O Lord.
Their bodies have been taken
from the shadow of our nights.
They have been released...
..from all darkness and pain.
(growls)
The child and the man...
..have gone beyond our world.
They are forever...
..eternal...
..and everlasting.
(dog barks)
Ashes to ashes,...
..dust to dust.
(Dillon) Why?
Why are the innocent punished?
(dog growls)
(dog whines)
Why the sacrifice?
Why the pain?
(growls)
(whines)
There aren't any promises.
Nothing's certain.
Only that some get called,
some get saved.
She won't ever know
the hardship and grief...
..for those of us left behind.
We commit these bodies to the void...
..with a glad heart.
(growls)
For within each seed...
..there is a promise of a flower.
And within each death,...
..no matter how small,...
..there's always a new life.
A new... beginning.
Amen.
(all) Amen.
l tellya, it's fuckin' weird.
The only one thatsurvived that crash
is a woman.
They'd already changed everything.
l knowshe's serious...
What the fuck are we supposed to do?
l mean it!
Not from round here, that's for sure.
Hello...
l just wanted to, uh, say thanks
for what you said at the funeral.
lt was...
My friends would've appreciated...
Yeah, well,
you don't wanna know me, lady.
l'm a murderer and rapist ofwomen.
Really?
Well, l guess...
l must make you nervous.
Do you have any faith, sister?
Not much.
Well, we've got a lot offaith here.
- Enough even for you.
- l thought women weren't allowed.
We've never had any before.
But we tolerate anybody.
Even the intolerable.
Thank you.
That's just a statement of principle.
Nothing personal. You see,...
..we've got a good place to wait here.
And until now...
..no temptation.
(Clemens)
Dillon and the rest ofthe...
..alternative people...
..embraced religion,
as it were, about five years ago.
- Take two?
- (Ripley) l'm on medication.
- Hardly.
- What kind of religion?
Some sort of... apocalyptic,
millenarian, Christian fundamentalist...
- Right.
- Exactly.
When the company
wanted to close the facility down,...
..Dillon and the rest ofthe converts
wanted to stay.
And... they were allowed
to remain as custodians,...
..with two minders...
..and a medical officer.
And here we are.
How did you get
this wonderful assignment?
How do you like your new haircut?
lt's OK.
Now that l've gone out
on a limb for you with Andrews,...
..damaged my already less-than-perfect
relationship with that good man,...
..and briefed you on the humdrum
history of Fury 161,...
..can you not tell me what
you were looking for in the girl?
Are you attracted to me?
ln what way?
ln thatway.
You're very direct.
l've been out here a long time.
ln the year 7510
(prisoner continues singing)
(singing stops)
Eurgh!
(whispers) Hey, Spike! Spike!
Spikey!
Are you down there?
What are you doing?
Aargh!
l really appreciate your affections.
But l am aware that they...
deflected my question.
ln the nicest possible way.
(Ripley) You're spoiling the mood.
l have ajob to do. l just want
to know why we had to cremate them.
l had a terrible dream in hypersleep.
And l had to be sure what killed her.
Anyway, l made a mistake.
Possibly.
And now l've made another mistake.
- Really? What's that?
- Fraternising with a prisoner.
Physical contact.
lt's against the rules, isn't it?
l'm not a prisoner.
You have a bar code
on the back ofyour head.
That does deserve an explanation.
But l don't think now is the moment.
(intercom) Mr Clemens.
Mr Aaron.
Superintendent Andrews wouldlike you
to report to ventshaft22. Now.
- We've hadan accident.
- Something serious?
You could callit that.
One ofourprisoners has been... diced.
Sorry. l have to go.
Official duties.
- Who was it?
- Murphy.
How do you know?
That's his boot.
l gave him the assignment, sir.
He was a wanker.
No apologies, Mr Aaron,
it wasn't your fault.
Well, not much to say, is there?
Death was instantaneous.
No shit.
l take it he was pulled into the fan.
Rush of air, l'd imagine. Except...
Right! Almost happened to me once.
l've told 'em so many times: stay away
from the fans. Nobody bloody listens.
Except the fan was blowing.
What's that?
- l don't know.
- l want to see you in my quarters...
..in 30 minutes, ifyou please,
Mr Clemens.
Have you got any ideas?
(beeping)
You know,
wandering around without an escort...
..will really piss
Superintendent Andrews off.
- Tell me about your accident.
- One ofthe prisoners has been killed.
Really? How?
ln the air shaft.
Poor sod backed into a 9-foot fan.
l found something
at the accident site.
Just... a bit away
from where it happened.
A mark.
A burn.
Like the one you found
on the girl's cryo-tube.
Look,...
..l'm on yourside.
l want to help,
but l need to know what's going on.
Or what you think is going on.
lf you really wanna help, find me
a computer with audio capabilities...
..to access this flight recorder.
We don't have anything like that here.
What about Bishop?
- Bishop?
- The droid that crashed with me.
l can point you in the right direction.
l can'tjoin you.
l have a previous engagement.
Listen to me, you piece of shit!
Screw with me once more,
l'll cut you in half.
l'm sorry, l don't think l understand.
At 0700 hours
l received word from the network.
This is the first high-level
communication...
..this installation has ever received,
to my knowledge.
They want this woman looked after.
- They consider her to be high priority.
- Why?
l have no idea.
Why did you let her
out ofthe infirmary?!
This accident with Murphy
is what happens...
..when one ofthese sons of bitches
gets a hard-on.
l'm a doctor, you're the jailer.
We both know exactly what you are.
Sit down!
l think it might be better if l left.
l find you unpleasant to be around.
lsn't that lovely!
Consider this, Mr Clemens.
How would you like me to explain
your sordid history to your new friend?
For her personal edification, of course.
Now sit the hell down.
Now,...
..is there anything l should know?
(thunder)
- Ohhh!
- Shut up, you fuckin' bitch!
Shut up, you bitch!
Let go of me!
Fuck you!
No!
- Hold still!
- Ssh! Ssh!
No!
Aaaaghhhh!
You OK?
Son of a bitch!
Take off. l gotta re-educate
some ofthe brothers.
We gotta discuss
some matters ofthe spirit.
This is like ten city blocks.
How many?
- This makes 176.
- (Golic chews noisily)
Can't you chew quieter? l'm trying
to figure out how big this compartment is.
- l can't think with this goddamn noise...
- You're not supposed to swear.
l'm sorry.
We've encircled this entire compartment...
Hey!
What?
- What the shit is doing that?
- Swearing!
Shut up! lt's all right to say "shit".
lt ain't against God.
What's going on with the candles?
Must be the wind
from one ofthe vent shafts.
Backwash from
the closest circulating unit.
But if all the candles go out,
how are we gonna know where we are?
Somebody will just have
to go back and relight them.
l guess l'm nominated.
Watch your step, brother.
OK, who are the comedians?
(screeching)
Agh! Agh! No!
Argh!
Go!
Aargh!
Quick, in here!
Help me, help me!
Go! Fuckin' go!
Go on! Go on! Quick!
(screaming)
Come on!
Give me that!
(pipe clanks)
Agh!
Get this fuckin' thing off me!
Oh, God, no!
Let me go!
Agh!
(screams)
(beeping)
(beep)
(whispers) Hey!
- (whispers) Hello, Ripley.
- (whispers) Hello, Bishop.
- How are you feeling?
- My legs hurt.
- Listen, l'm sorry.
- That's OK. l'm just a glorified toaster.
How are you?
l like your new haircut.
Can you access data
on the flight recorder?
No problem.
l'm home.
What happened on the Sulaco?
Why were our cryo-tubes ejected?
(female computer voice)
Stasis interrupted.
Fire in cryogenic compartment.
Repeat, fire in cryogenic...
What happened?
What started the fire, Bishop?
Can you hear me?
The fire was electrical.
lt was... in the subflooring.
Did the sensors pick up anything
moving around prior to separation?
lt's very dark here, Ripley.
l'm not what l used to be.
Just tell me.
Does the recorder indicate anything?
Was there an alien on board?
Yes.
ls it on the Sulaco,
or did it come with us in the EEV?
lt was with us all the way.
Does the company know?
The company knows everything
that happened on the ship.
lt all goes into the computer
and gets sent back to network.
And they want it?
l hurt.
Do me a favour. Disconnect me.
l could be reworked.
But l'll never be top-of-the-line again.
l'd rather be nothing.
You sure?
- Do it for me, Ripley.
- (Ripleysighs)
(metallic sigh)
(agitated voices)
lt wasn't me!
l didn't do it!
So help me! lt was the dragon.
Feeds on minds.
lt was... Nobody can stop it.
- What about Boggs and Rains?
- Slaughtered like pigs. lt wasn't me!
lt wasn't me!
Stark raving mad. lt wasn't anyone's fault,
but he should have been chained up.
You called it, sir. Mad as a fuckin' hatter.
Keep him separated. Don't want him
causing a panic. Clemens!
- Yeah.
- Sedate this poor idiot.
Not until we know about the brothers.
Now, pull yourselftogether.
Talk to me now.
- Now, where are Boggs and Rains?
- lt wasn't me.
(Andrews) You won't get
anything out of him!
We'll have to send out a search team.
There's a good chance
this simple bastard has murdered them!
And you don't know that.
He's never lied to me.
He's crazy,...
..he's a fool, but he's not a liar!
He's telling the truth.
l'd like to talk to him
about this... this dragon.
lt's a dragon!
You won't talk to anyone.
l'm not interested in your opinion.
You are not in full possession ofthe facts.
He is a convicted murderer,
known for particularly brutal crimes.
- lsn't that right, Mr Dillon?
- Yeah.
That part's right.
Then l'll talk to you. lt's important.
When l've finished with my official duties,
l'll be pleased to have a little chat. Yes?
Let me see if l have this correct,
Lieutenant.
lt's an eight-foot creature,
with acid for blood,...
..and it arrived on your spaceship.
lt kills on sight and is...
generally unpleasant.
And you expect me
to accept all this on yourword.
No. l don't expect anything.
Quite a story, Mr Aaron.
Right, sir. lt's a beauty.
Never heard anything quite like it, sir.
Expect not. Tell me, Lieutenant,
what would you suggest we do?
Well, what kind ofweapons have you got?
This is a prison. lt's not a good idea
to allow prisoners access to firearms.
lt keeps them from killing you.
There's no way to escape.
With the arrival ofthe next supply ship,...
..the company will eliminate it.
This is a maximum security prison...
..and you have no weapons of any kind?
We have some carving knives
in the abattoir,...
..a few more in the mess hall,
some fire axes.
Nothing terribly formidable.
That's all?
We're on the honour system.
Then we're fucked.
No! You're fucked.
Confined to the infirmary. Quarantined.
Mr Aaron will escort you.
You'll be safe from any large, nasty beasts
while you're there. Right?
Yes.
That's a good girl.
(intercom)
Let's allreport to the mess hall.
The superintendent wants a meeting.
Mess hall, rightaway, people.
lsn't there any way off ofthis place?
Some way to escape?
(laughs) No.
- A supply ship comes every six months.
- That's it?
That's it.
(whispers) Fuck!
They are sending somebody
to pick you up quite soon.
Really? (coughs) What's soon?
l don't know. Nobody's ever
been in a hurry to get here before.
Do you want to tell me
what you and Andrews talked about?
No.
You'd just say l'm crazy.
That's a bit uncharitable.
How are you feeling?
Not so hot. (clears throat)
Sore throat,...
..sick to my stomach.
Pissed off.
Understandable,
given the circumstances.
Perhaps l should give you
one of my specialcocktails.
(Golic) l don't know why everybody
blames everybody for everything.
Nobody's perfect. We're only human.
l don't know a perfect human.
Nobody l know.
You married?
Me?
You should get married, have kids.
Pretty girl.
l used to know lots ofthem. Back home.
They used to like me.
For a while.
You're gonna die, too.
(Clemens) Are you?
What?
Married.
Why?
Just curious.
No.
How about levelling with me?
When l asked how you got assigned here,
you avoided the question.
Then when l asked about the prison lD...
..tattooed on the back ofyour head,
you ducked me again.
lt's a long, sad story.
And more than a little melodramatic.
Try me.
lf you insist.
After my student years,...
..despite the fact that l had become...
secretly addicted...
..to morphine,
l was considered to be most promising.
A man with a future.
During my first residency
l did a 36-hour stretch on an ER.
So l went out
and l got more than a little drunk.
Then l got called back.
A boiler had blown in a fuel plant
and there were... 30 casualties.
And 11 ofthem died.
Not as a result ofthe accident,...
..but because l prescribed
the wrong dosage of painkiller.
And l got seven years in prison
and my licence reduced to a three-C.
(whispers) At least l got offthe morphine.
(whispers) l'm sorry.
l think l was let off lightly.
Did you serve your time here?
l got to know this motley crew quite well.
So when they stayed,...
..l stayed.
Nobody else would employ me.
So... do you still trust me with a needle?
Once again this is Rumour Control.
Here are the facts.
At 0800 hours, prisoner Murphy,...
..through carelessness on his part,
was found dead in vent shaft 17.
He seems to have been sucked
into a ventilator fan.
(panting)
At about 2100 hours,...
..prisoner Golic
reappeared in a deranged state.
Prisoners Boggs and Rains are missing.
There seems to be a good chance
that they have met with foul play...
..at the hands of prisoner Golic.
We need to organise
and send out a search party.
Volunteers will be appreciated.
(panting)
l think it's fair to say
that our smoothly-running facility...
..has suddenly developed a few problems.
l can only hope we are able to all
pull together over the next few days,...
..until the rescue team
arrives for Lt. Ripley.
- lt's here! lt got Clemens!
- Stop this raving at once!
l'm telling you! lt's here!
Aaron, get that foolish woman
back to the infirmary!
Agh!
Move it! Everybody!
Fuck!
(prisoner) What do we do now?
Who's in charge?
Organise!
We gotta organise, right?
Right! l'm next in line.
85's gonna be in charge.
Jesus! Give us a break!
Don't call me that!
Look, there's no way
l can replace Andrews.
He was a good man.
l know you didn't appreciate him...
Aaron, we don't wanna hear that shit now.
Hey, sister, what about you?
You're an officer.
How about showing us a little leadership?
Forget fuckin' Shirley Temple!
You take charge.
Right!
- You run things here anyway.
- No fuckin' way. l'm not the officer type.
l just take care of my own.
Well, what does this fuckin' beast want?
ls this mother gonna try for us all?
Yeah.
Ain't that sweet!
How are we gonna stop it?
(clears throat)
- You have no weapons. ls that correct?
- Right.
l haven't seen one exactly like this before.
lt moves differently.
But the others were afraid offire.
Not much else.
Can we seal offthis area?
No chance.
The installation's ten miles square.
There's 600 air ducts round...
What about video? We could find it
using these closed-circuit monitors.
The video system hasn't worked in years.
Nothing much works here!
We've got technology,
no way to fix it.
- 85 is trying to tell you...
- Don't call me that!
..we ain't got no entertainment centre.
No climate control, no video system.
No surveillance. No freezers.
No fuckin' ice cream.
No rubbers, no women.
No guns. All we got here is shit!
What the hell are we even talking
to her for? She brought the fucker.
Why don't we just get her head
and shove it through that fuckin' wall?!
Morse...
Why don't you shut the fuck up?
Right.
What are we going to do?
What's this?
lt leads from the mess hall...
to the infirmary. lt's a ventilation shaft.
Then we go in there. Flush it out.
Hey, look, there's miles and miles
of tunnel through there.
(Ripley sighs) lt won't go far.
lt'll nest in this area.
Right around...
..here.
How do you know that?
lt's like a lion.
- lt sticks close to the zebras.
- Zebras? Oh, right.
But running around here in the dark,
are you kidding?
Outside ofthis main shaft
there's no overheads.
- Don't we have flashlights?
- Thousands ofthem, but no batteries.
Torches?
Do we have the capacity to make fire?
Most humans have enjoyed that privilege
since the Stone Age.
No need to be sarcastic.
Never been used. They were
gonna dump nuclear crap in there.
Never got round to it.
lt's clean as a whistle inside.
This is the only way... in or out?
That's right.
Walls are six feet thick. Solid steel.
They knew how to build these babies.
You're saying,
we get something in there,...
- ..there's no way it can get out?
- That's right.
No fucking way.
(whistles)
lt's kept here.
Forget what this stuff's called.
- Quinitricetyline.
- l knew that.
l've gotta get these section arrangements
uh... organised with Dillon...
..for the... paint brush, uh...
So, um...
- David...
- Yeah.
- You can get these drums organised.
- Right, 85.
And, uh...
..don't call me that.
What's this... 85 thing?
A couple of us sneaked
a look at his personnel file.
lt's his lQ.
(Ripley chuckles)
(liquid sloshes)
l saw a drum ofthis stuff
fall into a beachhead bunker once.
The blast put a tug in dry dock
for 17 weeks.
Great stuff!
All right, let me get this straight.
You wanna burn it down
and out ofthe pipes,...
..force it in here, slam the door,
and trap its ass?
Right.
You want help
from us Y-chromo boys, huh?
You got something better to do?
Why should we put our ass
on the line for you?
Your ass is already on the line.
The only question is...
..what are you gonna do about it?
Man, this stuff stinks!
You miss Doc, right?
What makes you say that?
l thought you two got real close.
l guess you've been
looking through some keyholes.
- That's what l thought.
- Ohh! Ohh...
l hate this place. l hate this place!
There's definitely
something in here with us.
Don't light the fire until l give the signal.
This is the signal.
Got it? Can you remember that?
Agh! Shit!
No! No!
No!
Agh!
Agh! Agh!
Wait for the fucking signal!
Get down!
Agh!
Come on!
We gotta find the sprinklers!
We gotta help these guys!
(screaming)
Get to the waste dump.
Don't open the door!
Aagh!
Dillon! Over here!
Here's another one.
Oh, Jesus.
This makes ten.
Fuckin' great!
Well, now what are we gonna do?
- (groans)
- You OK?
Piss on her. The fuckin' thing's loose.
What are we gonna do?
l just said that. You miserable little shit!
Cut that shit out.
Tell your fuckin' bozo to shape up.
What do you think?
l've got to get to the EEV.
Why? What's up?
l just have to use the neuroscanner.
You don't look so good.
Who gives a shit! What are we gonna do?
Do you want a smack in the mouth,
you stupid wanker?
Stop causing panic!
Panic? You're so stupid, you couldn't
spell it. Don't talk to me about panic!
Shut up, both ofyou!
Shut up!
- Well, l'm out of ideas!
- Doesn't surprise me.
- What about outside?
- Oh, great idea!
The sun doesn't come up for two days, it's
40 below zero. That makes a lot of sense!
You want us to stay here
and let this thing have us for lunch.
Get everybody that's still left together.
Come down to the furnace.
OK.
Need any help?
l didn't mean to scare you.
You shouldn't be wandering around alone.
Do me a favour and...
run this keyboard, will you?
OK.
- What do l do?
- Hit B or C. What's C?
- "Display bio-functions"?
- That's it.
(buzzing)
OK, we're hot. Now what?
Let it run its cycle.
lt's real fuzzy.
Hit enhancement.
Keep looking.
l don't know how to read this stuff.
Haemorrhaging will show as a dark patch.
(clears throat)
Look for... hairline fractures
through the... base ofthe skull.
Little white lines.
What is it?
l think you've got one inside ofyou.
That's not possible!
What does it look like?
Horrible.
(Ripley) l have to see it.
Freeze it!
- You don't want to look at it.
- Freeze it!
l'm sorry.
lt's up.
What do you want to say?
Tell them the whole place has gone toxic.
Are you kidding? They won't come here.
The rescue team will turn back.
Yeah, l know.
What are you talking about?
Our only hope is that they kill this fucker.
Maybe they can do something for you.
l don't know, freeze you! An operation!
They've got the technology!
lf this organism gets offthe planet,
it'll kill everything.
The company doesn't care about that.
They just want it,
for their bio-weapons division, OK?
So we can't let them come here.
Fuck you!
Look, l'm sorry you've got this thing
inside you, but l'm getting rescued.
l don't care about these prisoners.
But l've got a wife and kid.
l'm going home!
l know. This is hard.
But l'm gonna send this message.
l need that fucking code.
l'm sorry, ma'am. lt's classified.
You stupid little shit,
this has got to be done!
There are no alternatives!
You're not getting it! No fucking way!
Look... it's nothing personal.
Understand? l think you're OK.
Thanks.
- Have you got any ideas?
- l don't know. Maybe l'll go find it.
See how smart it is.
You're gonna go and look for it?
Yeah.
l have a pretty good idea where it is.
lt's just down there.
ln the basement.
This whole place is a basement.
lt's a metaphor.
Do you wanna come?
Fuck me!
(buzzing)
(buzzing continues)
Where are you when l need you?
(hissing sound)
Don't be afraid.
l'm part ofthe family.
You've been in my life so long...
..l can't remember anything else.
Now do something for me.
lt's easy.
Just...
Just do what you do.
(drops pipe)
(hissing)
Oh!
lt won't kill me.
You're supposed to be laying low.
l have one inside of me.
- What are you talking about?
- l saw it.
On the CAT scan.
lt's a queen.
An egg-layer.
lt can make thousands more.
lt still sounds like bullshit to me.
lf it's inside you, how did it get there?
(sighs)
When l was in hypersleep, l guess.
l don't have much time.
And l can't do what l should.
l need you to help me.
(whispers) l need you to kill me.
- What are you talking about?
- l'm dead anyway.
l can't survive it.
But the one inside of me
can generate thousands more.
lt has to die.
So somebody's gotta kill me.
Are you up to it?
You don't have to worry about that.
(whispers) So...
No speeches.
No prayers.
(whispers) What's going on?
l don't like losing a fight.
Not to nobody, not to nothing.
That thing has already killed half my men
and got the other half scared shitless.
As long as it's alive, sister,
you're not gonna save any universe.
- You fuckin' coward!
- l want that thing!
l wanna get this thing
and l need you to do it.
And if it won't kill you,
then maybe that helps us fight it.
Otherwise fuck you!
(moans)
Dillon!
We waste this thing.
- Then you take care of me.
- No problem.
Quick, easy and painless.
(Dillon) You die sitting here on your ass,
or you die out there.
At least we take a shot. We owe it one!
What the fuck are you talking about?
l'm talking about
killing that big motherfucker.
That doesn't mean we should fight it.
Jesus Christ, give us a break!
You guys have got to be fucking nuts.
l've got a wife and kid...
Nobody gives a shit about you, 85.
You're not a believer.
You're a fuckin' company man!
Yeah, OK. l'm a company man,
not a fuckin' criminal.
You tell me how dumb l am. l'm smart
enough not to have a life sentence!
Piss off!
Weirdo!
And l'm smart enough to wait
for some firepower to show up...
..before we fight this thing! Right?
OK, just sit here, on your asses. Fine!
How about if l sit here on my ass?
No problem. Oh, l forgot!
You're the guy that's made
a deal with God to live for ever, huh?
And all the rest ofyou pussies
can sit it out, too.
Me and her'll do all the fighting.
OK. But l want the same thing as you.
l want to see it dead. l hate the fucker!
lt killed my mates, too!
Why the fuck can't we wait
for the company...
..and have some guns on our side?
Why go on a fucking suicide run?
Right!
Because they won't kill it.
They might kill you for having seen it
but they won't kill it.
That is crazy! That is horseshit!
They will not kill us!
When they first heard about this thing,
it was "crew expendable".
The next time, they sent in Marines.
They were expendable, too.
What makes you think they're gonna care
about a bunch of lifers, who found God...
..at the ass-end of space?
You really think they're gonna let you
interfere with their plans?
They think we're... we're crud.
And they don't give a fuck...
..about one friend ofyours that's...
that's died.
Not one.
Have you got some sort of plan?
This is a lead works, isn't it?
All we gotta do is lower the fuckin' beast
into the mould. Drown it in hot lead.
Oh, right. So how do we do that?
Yeah. What are we gonna use for bait?
Oh, fuck!
You're all gonna die.
The only question is how you check out.
Do you want it on your feet...
or on your fuckin' knees?
Begging!
l ain't much for begging!
Nobody ever gave me nothing!
So l say fuckthat thing! Let's fight it!
Fuck it! Let's go, boys!
OK.
What the fuck are we gonna do
if it runs at us?
Better have some fucking good ideas.
(computer voice) Door 1 open.
When was the last time
you used this place?
We fired it up five, six years ago.
You sure the piston's gonna work?
There's nothing for sure in this place.
We trap it here first,
then you pull the lever.
The piston's gonna push it into the mould.
One ofthe guys will pour the lead.
- End of his ass, end of story.
- What if somebody screws it up?
We're fucked.
You got one chance, one shot at it.
There'll be no time to reset it.
Now, remember,...
..you pull the lever.
For a few seconds you're gonna be
trapped in here with that thing.
You guys don't drop the ball, l won't.
You better be right about
that thing not wanting you.
Because if it wants out,
that's how it's gonna go.
Through that alcove, through you.
- Where are you gonna be?
- l'll be around.
What about the others?
Praying.
- l have a problem with this.
- What part?
Where we're running in the dark
fuckin' maze with that thing chasing us.
You lead it down channel B
to the piston chamber.
l'll close the doors behind you.
Hey! What if it won't cooperate?
What ifwe get lost?
This was her idea.
l don't know about this shit.
Hey, guys! My door ain't working!
What the fuck is he saying?
l think we better rethink this thing!
(distant) Aargh!
Did anybody hear anything?
Come on!
Come and get me, you fucker!
lt's behind me!
lt's started.
lt's still behind me!
lt's in channel B!
lt's behind me! Shut the doors!
Must be heading over to channel A!
This thing is really pissed off!
- Did you say B?
- No, E!
- But you said we should stay here!
- Move your ass!
Morse?
Kevin!
Yoo-hoo! Hey, fuckface!
Come and get me!
(hissing)
Aargh!
You can't get me!
A-7 closed!
(yelling)
Over in the east wing!
Door B-7 safe!
Agh!
- You, too?
- Yeah!
Over to E, everybody!
- Where the fuck is E?!
- This way!
Here! Here, kitty, kitty, kitty!
Here, kitty, kitty...
You bastard!
(hissing)
lt's coming!
lt's coming down through this tunnel!
lt's after us!
Shut the fucking doors!
Jesus! l can fucking see it!
Dillon, anybody! This is not a drill!
Kevin! Gregor! Where the fuck are you?!
Kevin!
Now l'm back in A!
(panting)
Door three, F channel closed!
l hope.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- What?
Don't hold it like that. Like this!
You could kill someone,
you fuckin' moron!
(hissing)
Aargh!
Morse!
Kevin!
Gregor!
All they have to do is
run down the damn corridor.
Stay here.
Where the hell is it?
(distant shouting)
(hissing)
Aargh!
(distant) lt's coming!
Oh, Jesus!
There!
(Ripley) No! Don't start the piston!
No!
We have to trap it!
What are you doing? lt's gone!
No! No.
lt's gone!
OK?
OK.
Oh!
(Kevin screams)
Argh!
Agh! Argh!
Kevin!
No! Don't move! No.
Aargh!
Come on!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
- The doors.
- lt's coming!
Take the piston!
- Ah! Oh!
- lt's all right.
lt's OK. lt's all right, Kevin.
Kevin.
Kevin!
(hissing)
(whispers) Leave him!
Leave him! He's dead. Lure it in.
(hissing)
Shit! How much time?
l'm not sure. Four or five minutes.
But we got to get it back in here...
..before the piston seals this place off!
Now let's move it!
Oh!
(yelling)
Help me!
Jude!
Dillon! Help me!
lt's coming at me!
Don't look back, Jude!
Run as fast as you fuckin' can!
You gotta help me!
Please!
Oh!
(door opens)
Jesus Christ! Thank God you're here!
Warder Aaron, sir. 137512.
Not many of us left, sir.
Where is Lt. Ripley? ls she still alive?
lf she's alive, she's in the furnace.
She's in the lead works with the beast.
Wouldn't wait.
Jesus Christ!
You fucker. Scared me shitless!
l thought you were the fuckin' beast!
You fucker!
(laughter)
Grrrh!
Wanker!
Move! Come on, you bastard!
Come on!
Get out ofthere!
Come here!
Ripley, we're running out oftime!
Ripley, where are you?
Aah!
No!
Dillon, over here!
Dillon!
Come on!
Get out ofthere!
- What the fuck is wrong with you?!
- No!
Let it go!
Yes, it's working! To the piston!
- Come on!
- We gotta get it in front ofthe piston!
- lt's following us!
- Come on!
Come on and get us!
- Up to the door!
Come on! Come on!
Come on, motherfucker! Come on!
Get the door!
Morse!
- Now!
- Shut it!
Shut it, Morse!
Morse!
Shut the door!
- Now!
- Shut the fuckin' door!
l'm going for the lead!
(screeching)
- Now!
- What about you?
- l'm staying.
- Bullshit!
- There'll be ten tons of hot lead in here.
- l wanna die!
We got a deal! lt dies first, then you!
l'm not gonna move without you!
Now get going!
(hissing)
Dillon?
l'm gonna hold it here.
- What about me?
- God will take care ofyou, sister!
No!
Pour the lead.
l'll fuck you!
- No!
- Go on, Ripley!
Go on!
Agh! Damn it!
Pour the lead, Ripley! Pour it now!
Come on! ls that all you got?
Fight, motherfucker!
- Come on, do it!
- Morse! Over here!
Ripley!
Pour the lead!
Aargh!
Pour it!
Agh! Agh!
(laughs)
l hate bugs!
(hissing)
Ripley! lt's burning hot!
Hit the sprinkler!
Douse the fucker!
(screeching)
Gotcha!
Yes!
(Ripley) Don't come any closer.
Wait! They're here to help.
Stay where you are!
- Ripley.
- Bishop!
- l'm here to help you.
- No more bullshit.
l just felt it move.
- You know who l am?
- You're a droid.
Same model as Bishop.
Sent by the fucking company.
No. l'm not the Bishop android.
l designed it.
l'm very human. The company
sent me here to show you a friendly face.
To demonstrate
how important you are to us.
To me.
- You wanna take it back.
- We want to kill it and take you home.
Bullshit.
You're wrong. We want to help.
What does that mean?
We're going to take that out ofyou.
Keep it.
We can't allow it to live. Everything
we know would be in jeopardy.
- You don't want to take it back?
- Ripley, time is important.
We've got a surgical bay set up
on the rescue ship. Come with me.
You still can have a life.
Children.
And most important...
..you'll know it's dead.
Let me help you.
What guarantee do l have...
..once you've taken it out...
..that you'll destroy it?
You have to trust me.
Please.
Trust me.
No.
What's this gonna achieve?
Argh!
Stop!
Oh, Jesus!
- Argh! Aargh!!
- Morse...
Will you help me?
What do you want me to do?
lt was a mistake.
There was no need for any of it.
Fuckin' android!
(Bishop) Ripley!
Think of all we could learn from it.
lt's the chance of a lifetime!
You must let me have it!
lt's a magnificent specimen.
What are you doing?
No!
(screeching)
(clicking)
Ah!
- Come on, you. Get going!
- Oh, fuck you!
(Ripley) Captain Dallas is dead.
Cargo andship destroyed.
l shouldreach the frontier
in aboutsix weeks.
With a bit ofluck,
the network willpick me up.
This is Ripley.
Last survivor ofthe Nostromo.
Signing off.
Subtitles by Visiontext
ENGLlSH