Yeah! Go, buddy, go!
That baby's going scared!
Give me one.
Get them.
Hey, boys!
How y'all doing?
What are you looking at?
You want to get shot?!
Go, baby!
-You got it!
-Pearl Harbor!
Here's another one!
Watch this!
100 points!
It's a beautiful day, isn't it?
Bye, Tonya.
Clean up that mess, boy.
Hungry?
You're having nothing?
I'm having them.
Shit.
Bye, girls.
Let's go!
You're on the house.
Harry Rex!
All those weekends...
...fishing...
...lounging, opportunities lost...
...to renovate yourself.
Tragic, just tragic, Jake.
Makes Carla happy.
Spent 4 marriages trying to figure
out what makes women happy.
You spent 4 marriages trying to
figure out what makes you happy.
Maybe that's it.
Yeah, maybe.
Swiggy?
Lord, let my car be fixed today.
Oh, dear.
Who's that?
She's young.
Hold this.
What're you doing?
If they're old enough to crawl,
they're in the right position.
What're you doing?
What're you going to do?
50 points!
You good, boy!
Shut up!
Daddy!
Go, bud.
Shut up!
I'll kill you.
My turn.
There you are.
Shut up!
Daddy!
Mama!
What is this?
Groceries!
Y'all see her?
How many appointments
do we have today?
Not a one.
But it is the first of the
month again and guess what.
The checks are pouring in.
We have enough money to pay our debts.
That'll be your last drink.
Just keep us no more than one
month behind on any vendor.
You have been drinking.
2 months.
These are the most delinquent.
The rent's in there.
I appreciate the practice, Captain.
But you could've left me a few clients.
Baby, here's Daddy coming.
I'm here, baby. Daddy's here.
Daddy...
...l'm sorry I dropped the groceries.
That's all right, baby.
That's all right.
Look at this.
Billy Ray.
Sorry, sir, but we don't allow
no African-Americans here.
Billy Ray Cobb...
...you and Willard must come with me.
I ain't moving.
The girl you took for a ride...
What girl?
I got bad news for you. She didn't die.
So unless there's another redneck
asshole with a yellow truck...
...with a Confederate flag--
Blue gums...
...get out of here and grab a branch.
Unless you got an explanation for
why this was in your truck...
...you're going to jail.
Get up.
You go to hell, nigger.
Goddamn!
Come here.
Now, you earn the
right to remain silent!
Here, just like you like them.
-Sugar, today I'm going to have--
-Go to hell.
I'll just watch baby eat his.
I didn't handle her husband's divorce.
I'm shriveling away here.
I'm shriveling.
What's up?
Didn't you defend Billy
Ray Cobb a few years back?
What for?
Caught him selling dope.
Spent time in Parchman.
Got out last year.
I think some Memphis
lawyer handled that.
Why do you ask?
Picked him up for rape.
Him and Willard.
Who'd they rape?
You know Carl Lee Hailey?
I defended his brother Lester.
It was his little girl.
Little Tonya?
How old's she?
She's ten.
Mr. Willard...
...l'm Sheriff Walls.
My mama voted for you.
I seen you play for the Rams.
Way I figure, a nigger
sheriff's okay, been on TV.
No offense.
What's your full name?
James Lewis Willard.
4, which is a difference of 110.60.
Who's there?
Carl Lee.
How is she?
She's holding on.
Doctor says she ain't out
of the woods yet, though.
They worked her over something good.
You remember them 4 white boys
raped that black girl last year?
They got off, didn't they?
I was in a jam, you'd help
me out, wouldn't you?
Sure, Carl Lee.
What kind of jam you talking of?
You got a daughter, Jake.
What would you do?
You dream some good dreams.
Good night, Daddy.
Night, baby.
Is she asleep?
She's so sweet.
Yeah, she is...
...next to you.
When I look at her though, I
cannot help but think about...
...Tonya.
Don't.
Don't do that to yourself.
Something wrong?
Tonya's father...
...Carl Lee Hailey...
...came to the office today.
Man's heart is torn wide open, baby.
I don't know, but...
...seemed like he was
going to do something.
Like what?
Something like killing those boys.
Was he serious?
I don't know. I don't know.
It could be just hurt talking.
But when you think it's
possible those two animals could...
...go free...
...and be walking the streets....
I don't know.
After what that man has been through,
he's capable of anything.
Somebody should do something.
You should call Sheriff Walls.
...to release the
owner from assessment.
I hope I'm having a heart attack...
...'cause then I get to sue you!
Don't stand on ceremony, come on in.
What? No clients?
Just waiting to pick yours up on appeal.
And you, are you on vacation?
Fortunately for me, my lovely...
...divorce doesn't go on vacation.
However...
...not even the richest, most
ridiculous settlement I get...
...will be as satisfying as
watching those two hyenas...
...get what's coming to them.
Oh, dear.
I'm a fool for those
German-type convertibles.
Come on, let's get to court.
Lucien thinks the two
hyenas just might get off.
You saw Lucien?
When? Where?
How is he?
Has he been eating better?
Just curious.
Refresh my recollection, how long
were you and Lucien together?
We were never together.
I was his secretary for 20 years.
Come on, old girl.
You can tell us.
He was your boyfriend.
I am an upstanding, God-fearing,
respectable woman...
...with unimpeachable morals who
has been happily married 27 years.
And I have never had or ever
will have any boyfriend!
And if I did...
...it would not be that old
pickled scoundrel Lucien Wilbanks!
-She did him, a lot.
-Definitely.
Step back.
Come on out.
Boys, today's your big day.
We'll go to the courthouse,
the judge will set your bail...
...then we'll come back,
nice and peaceful.
If I get any trouble out of you,
I'm going to integrate this jail.
Mama, Daddy's home!
Hannah, let's go inside for a minute.
Let's find a book.
Jake, are you hurt?
Jake, what happened to you?!
Honey, are you okay?
What happened to you?
What is this? What is
going on with you?!
Jake, baby, are you okay?
What happened?
I'll see you.
Will the sheriff comment?
He might make a statement, or not.
-Is it first-degree murder?
-I don't know.
Here comes the sheriff.
I got no comment. No comment.
Hey, Jake. Carl Lee
said you'd be coming.
Are you an attorney?
I'll make a statement.
Get these vans out of here.
Give us something for our newscasts.
Didn't think I'd do it, did you?
How you holding up?
I ain't had nothing against them
till they messed with my baby.
And I feel sorry for their
mamas and their daddys, but...
...l ain't sorry for what I done.
How's Looney?
You blew his knee off his leg.
Doctors are still with him.
What'll happen to me?
There's going to be a preliminary
hearing. Probably tomorrow.
Then Buckley'll push for a fast trial.
Who's Buckley?
Rufus Buckley...
...district attorney.
He's mean, he's ambitious and he'll
eat this up because of the publicity.
But you've beat him?
Yeah.
Not in a murder case.
Think I can win?
All depends on the jury, Carl Lee.
Pick the right jury, and you'll walk.
DA picks the jury and...
...you get the gas.
How much a case like this cost?
Probably 50 grand.
I can pay maybe ten.
There're not a...
...lot of white lawyers would've
took my brother's case.
You did and got him off.
I figure there's people out there...
...tired of all the
raping and killing and...
...they'd be sympathetic to a man who
took the law into his own hands...
...even if he is black.
You said you'd help me
out if I was in a jam.
Well, I'm in one now.
What do you say?
What can you tell us, sheriff?
Comment?
Are you with the police?
I'm a lawyer.
Are you Hailey's attorney?
Are you Mr. Hailey's attorney?
Yes, I am.
Your name?
Brigance. Jake Brigance.
That's with one 'G.'
Hailey's hired an attorney.
Jake Brigance.
And today ain't even my birthday.
Brigance couldn't tie his
own tie without Wilbanks.
He's never lost a murder case.
Well, he's never tried one against me.
What time's the preliminary?
Tomorrow at 3. Judge
Omar Noose presiding.
I was wrong. It is my birthday.
All right.
First, Brigance will file
for a change of venue.
He'd be a fool not to.
Why's that?
Why?
Should we tell our young,
uninformed law clerk...
...the reality of jurisprudence?
Evelyn, get me the state
file on race statistics!
See, it's quite simple.
This county's 26-30\/\
black, give or take.
Almost every other county is
40-45, in some cases 70\/\ black.
Blacks are more sympathetic to blacks.
If he gets it moved, he has a greater
chance of color in the jury box.
But if the trial stays here,
it's an all white jury for sure.
This is for you...
...to integrate your brain
with before tomorrow.
He means without blacks on the jury,
Hailey hasn't got a chance.
Noose is up for re-elect?
Yeah, November.
Reach out to our legislature friends.
Have them call Noose. We'll help
him decide to keep the trial here.
Also, send a case of whatever
he drinks to Lucien Wilbanks.
Dewars.
Keep that old drunk on the sidelines.
Get me Sam.
And, gentlemen...
...no mistakes.
This is what we've waited for.
Justifiable homicide'll never hold up.
My only chance is to find a shrink...
...to say Carl Lee was
insane at the time.
Now I might know a man
who owes me a favor.
You file for a change of venue?
Of course.
If Judge Noose denies it...
...then you'll get an all
white jury and you'll lose.
Thanks.
Bear in mind that Mr. Hailey is guilty
as sin under our legal system.
It does not permit vigilante violence...
...and he took the law
into his own hands.
He murdered two people.
Two people who raped his
10-year-old daughter.
You know...
...you can win this case...
...and justice will prevail.
But lose...
...and justice will also prevail.
Now that's a strange case.
I could use your help.
The sons-of-bitches
decertified me, Jake.
I swore I will never enter
another courtroom. Ever!
You're the best lawyer I've ever seen.
I know how much it hurt when
they took your license away.
But they can't take your
mind unless you let them.
Good speech.
I had a good teacher.
Remember when I came to you?
In that ridiculous blue suit.
You sat me down and said to me...
..."l cannot promise you riches.
What I can offer you...
...is a chance to save the world...
...one case at a time."
I'm saying the same words
back to you right now.
How about it, Lucien?
"The Lord is my shepherd.
I shall not want.
He maketh me to lie
down in green pastures.
He leadeth me beside still waters.
Yea, though I walk...
...through the valley of the shadow
of death, I will fear no evil...
...for Thou art with me.
Thy rod and Thy staff comfort me."
Sure am sorry about your brother.
Old Willard, too.
Good boys both.
10 years ago...
...that nigger'd be hanging
by the end of a rope.
Tell me what's wrong with this country.
Klan would know what to do.
My granddaddy, he was Klan.
Ain't no Klan here.
There's still some boys around.
Skinheads who want to
blow up the government?
No, sir. Good God-fearing Klan.
I got a friend, used to be active.
I could call him.
You do that.
You tell them boys we need
some Klan here in Canton.
I mean, right quick.
Hurry up.
Coming, coming.
Look, there's Ozzie.
To our family's TV debut.
To the big time.
I can't believe he didn't take
you seriously about Carl Lee.
Baby, some folks think those
boys got what they deserved.
Here.
Carl Lee Hailey may spend life in jail.
His family doesn't deserve that.
-You did call Ozzie?
-Look here.
Daddy's on TV.
I'll show the men and women of the South
will look past color and see the truth.
That in the South, justice
is and will be colorblind.
Impressive. Honey,
that was really good.
Isn't Daddy smart?
Brigance.
That was great.
No, we just saw it.
All right, Harry Rex.
I'm proud of you.
Good stuff, huh?
Hear this? Think it's a press agent?
Don't be gross.
F. Lee Bailey's office.
You nigger-loving son-of-a-bitch,
you won't live if the nigger walks.
Do you have sympathy for the defense?
Of course I do. You're
a mother, I'm a father.
We all have families. Who wouldn't?
Don't presume the DA is insensitive.
But the people of this state entrusted
this office to uphold the law.
Our society cannot condone men who
take the law into their own hands.
If you get a conviction,
will you ask for the gas chamber?
Yes, I will seek the death
penalty for Mr. Hailey.
What do you think of Brigance?
Isn't he still in law school?
Say hey to your husband for me.
That's all.
Hey, Cora Mae, don't you worry.
Wayne, how are you?
You plead him guilty, I'll ask
for life. Otherwise, he dies.
You drop your case now, I won't
bury you before the county.
All rise!
Court is in session.
The Honorable Omar Noose presiding.
Good afternoon, citizens.
Be seated.
Counsel.
And you, sir...
...are you Carl Lee Hailey?
I am holding a copy of an indictment...
...returned by the grand jury...
...presenting that "Carl Lee Hailey...
...did murder Billy Ray
Cobb, a human being...
...and James Willard, a human being...
...and did attempt to kill
Dwayne Looney...
...a peace officer...
...against the peace and
dignity of Mississippi."
Do you understand the
charges against you?
How do you wish to plead?
Not guilty.
The defense enters a plea of not
guilty by reason of insanity.
Your trial is set for July 22.
All pre-trial motions and matters should
be filed by July 8. Anything further?
Yes.
The State requests the defendant
be examined by its own doctors.
Granted.
Additionally, the State
opposes any request for bail.
We have not yet asked for bail.
Now Governor Buckley...
...cannot oppose a
request until one is made.
Your Honor...
...even Mr. Brigance's meager legal
experience should have taught him...
...l haven't been
elected governor, yet...
...and he is required to request bail.
The State opposes any request.
In the future, why don't we
wait till he makes the request.
Thank you.
We would like to request bail.
Denied.
I never allow bail...
...in a murder case and don't feel
an exception is called for today.
Good enough. We will be
filing for a change of venue.
I anticipated this.
Let me save you some time.
Your motion is denied.
We have not yet filed.
We are simply indicating our
intent to file in writing--
I said, "Request denied."
Your Honor...
...how can you summarily
deny this request?
It is quite clear that Carl Lee Hailey
cannot receive a fair trial in Canton.
Sidebar.
We have a right--
I will not tolerate
grandstanding in my courtroom.
Get to work.
Excellent technique, counselor.
Your Honor.
It would be remiss not to tell
you that in State vs. Johnson...
...and State vs. Fisher...
...both in 1985...
..."Failure to consider
a change of venue...
...has been a reversible
decision on appeal."
No trial judge...
...likes his rulings overturned.
I guess you get to submit
that brief after all.
Have it on my desk Tuesday.
Mr. Hailey...
...you are hereby ordered...
...to remain in custody of the
Madison County Sheriff until trial.
Dismissed.
Find me that state doctor, Rodeheaver.
Get him down here to interview Hailey.
I want to find who Brigance is using
for a shrink. I want him discredited.
Professional or personal dirt?
Just get me enough to
shatter him in court.
We can do that.
This is $900, Carl Lee.
We said a thousand down.
My kids got to eat.
Mine too.
When do I get the rest?
Them folks at the bank, they
won't lend me money on my house.
Why? The house is almost paid for.
You borrowed on it before Lester's trial.
Say I wasn't in jail then. Say to Gwen,
how will I pay if I'm on death row?
And I lost my job at the mill.
They called Gwen.
Worked 20 years, I'm out
5 days and they fired me.
Carl Lee...
...l can't try a capital
murder case for $900.
I need to live.
Me too, Jake.
I need to live too.
Nice night.
Finder of precedents, mystery
woman of the courthouse....
Care for a beer?
I assume that's the infamous
change of venue motion.
Ellen Roark. R-O-A-R-K.
That's Roark in Boston, but it
seems to be Row-ark in Mississippi.
Boston.
I was born there. My father's
the notorious Sheldon Roark.
Attorney to the stars, yes.
Duly impressed.
What brings you to Mississippi?
Slumming?
No, law school at Old Miss.
It's a family tradition.
Mom was a sweet little sorority
girl there till Dad married her.
I married a sweet little sorority
girl from Ol' Miss myself.
They have an excellent selection.
They do.
No, really, what brings you to Canton?
They have cars to sit on on campus.
Carl Lee Hailey.
I'd like to help you.
What makes you think I need help?
You're trying one of the largest
murder cases these parts have seen...
...and you work alone.
You have no paralegals,
clerks, researchers...
...nor can you afford any...
...so if Noose doesn't
accept that motion...
...you go to trial in less than a month.
Trust me, you need help.
How do you know this?
I'm an excellent researcher.
I've played gofer for 7
capital murder cases...
...l've witnessed 2 executions.
I have written briefs for the A.C.L.U.
I'm top 5\/\ of my class, editor of the
law review, I'm published, I'm young.
And when I graduate...
...l intend to spend a glorious career
stomping out the death penalty.
Let's see, what else?
Genius runs in my family.
You'll get me on the way up...
...and I really think now
is a good time to grab me.
Anything else I should know?
Let's see, anything else?
My father's rich so I'll work for free.
What do you think?
I think I'll drop this brief
off in Noose's night slot.
Go home, see my family.
Thanks, but I can handle the case.
You might look at these precedents.
State vs. Cooper...
...and State vs. Roundtree.
Revenge killers, both acquitted.
You'll change your mind.
See you.
Get out.
Come on.
Come here. Come on.
Mr. Cobb...
...this is Stump Sisson,
Grand Dragon of Mississippi.
You were looking for us?
You were right to call us,
Mr. Cobb.
They say the Klan is dead.
Klan don't show up
for a few years and...
...people say the Klan is dead.
Fact is, it just looks dead.
The Klan has always been right there...
...under the surface...
...just waiting for the opportunity
to deliver God's justice.
I want help.
I want to kill that nigger.
Niggers got...
...plenty of protection nowadays.
They got the NAACP...
...and the A.C.L.U.
Even the federal government.
Hell...
...white folks ain't got a chance.
Except the Klan.
I'm going to tell you what.
You get 5 or 6 of your
friends of similar thinking...
...and we'll initiate...
...the Madison County Klavern.
Even make you leader.
Now, you tell me...
...who's that nigger's lawyer?
Local boy.
His name's Brigance.
He's got a pretty good reputation.
He got family?
Yes, sir. He has a wife and a daughter.
Good.
Why's he here?
Calm down, son.
Calm down. Come on, now.
He has no right after what he did.
Don't get your mom upset now.
Looney?
Dwayne?
I made Ozzie bring me.
Shit, Dwayne, we...
We knowed each other since childhood.
It's my fault.
No matter what's said in court...
...l knew what I was doing, and I sure
didn't intend to hurt you, but...
...just them two boys.
I know it don't mean much now, but...
...l'm sorry.
Some folks think a black man can't
receive a fair trial in the South.
I'll show the men and women of the South
will look past color and see the truth.
It sure is a nigger's world.
Not for long.
Boys...
...l'm very proud to invite
you to become soldiers...
...in the war to protect our
Christian homes and families.
To resurrect our country...
...from the fires of racial degradation.
And to make whites...
...the sole masters of
our nation's destiny.
What I'm saying, fellas...
...it's time for the nigger to pay.
Is your telephone broken?
We just had the number changed.
That's what the operator said.
To an unlisted number.
Sorry you had to come up here.
I should've called you, but this case--
This case has us all
worried sick about you all.
This thing could get ugly.
And dangerous.
Jake, he shot them in cold blood.
They raped, almost killed his daughter.
What if that happened to Hannah?
May we ask a few questions?
Can we get a quote?
Excuse me, I'm going to
go take a few questions.
This isn't the time.
It's really good for Carl Lee.
Thank you for coming.
Guess we'll have to read
about it in the papers.
Praise Jesus!
Reverend?
I'm lsaiah Street.
It's an honor to meet you, Reverend.
I saw you march with Dr. King.
The struggle continues today...
...here in Canton.
Carl Lee Hailey's on trial because
he's black. No other reason.
These people are with the NAACP.
How do you do?
How are you?
The black community's concerned
that Mr. Hailey's attorney...
...isn't sensitive to the
needs of the movement.
The NAACP...
...wishes to provide
him with a new lawyer.
We need to raise funds to
support Carl Lee Hailey.
I don't know, Reverend.
Time's awfully tight here.
Obviously...
...we would expect you to take...
...a modest administration
fee for your troubles.
Your loyalty...
...has been forged...
...in a baptism of fire.
Rise, knights...
...of the Ku Klux Klan...
...and let your brethren...
...never regret...
...they believed you worthy...
...of fellowship.
Welcome to the Klan.
I need to talk to Jake.
He's not in. Who's calling?
Mickey Mouse.
-Who?
-Mickey Mouse.
Get out right now.
Who's this?
Get your daughter out of the
house right now!
Hannah, what is it?
Oh, my God!
Max, come on!
Fire!
It's a good thing Hastings
was nearby and got here fast.
The whole place could've burned.
I appreciate it.
Take care.
She asleep, baby?
The Ku Klux Klan is burning
crosses on our lawn.
There's been no Klan
around here for years.
This is just some dorks with too much
time on their hands and too many beers.
I'm sorry.
About what?
That you weren't home when they
almost burned our house down?
That you missed supper and didn't call?
That you've become more interested
in getting on the news...
...than in your own family?
That Hannah comes home bawling
because kids call her a nigger-lover?
What exactly are you sorry about, Jake?
Remember the other night?
I told you Carl Lee came by the office?
Remember what we talked about?
Calling Ozzie.
You never called him, did you?
You never called Sheriff Walls?
I didn't call him.
Lord have mercy, Jake,
you had a responsibility.
Carl Lee chose you.
He told you what he was thinking.
He told me what he was thinking,
but I didn't know--
Jake Tyler Brigance, we agreed
you'd call the sheriff.
Now look at everything that's happened.
I am sorry to tell you this, but...
...those 2 boys are dead and you
were in a position to prevent it!
Are you and Daddy fighting?
Come here.
Come here, come here.
Mommy's just upset because some
silly man played a bad joke.
It's nothing.
Nothing at all, okay?
What did the Memphis doctor say?
She's doing good.
Her jaw is healing.
She can't run and jump yet, but...
...it won't be long.
How about the other?
There was too much damage.
She ain't gonna never have kids.
You know, I think about them two boys.
Dead, buried...
...probably starting to rot...
...and I remember them
walking in court...
...one proud, the other scared.
I remember how they fell.
One on top of the other, screaming
and squirming and not going nowhere.
God help me, Gwen, but...
...that's the only
thought gives me comfort.
They took up a collection
for us at church.
Some kind of defense fund.
Reverend Agee gave a good service.
We need some money 'round
the house, Carl Lee...
...for groceries and bills.
How much you got?
Less than 50.
I'll think of something.
How you think you going to get
money when you stuck in jail?
Trust me, Gwen.
I just get scared.
Look here...
...tell me exactly what
Reverend Agee said...
...when he passed around
the collection plate.
I don't care. We're dealing
with life and death here.
-I must talk to my supervisor.
-Go talk to him.
Get out!
How are things at the electric company?
That is the second time this
week I've had to hold him off.
How much we owe?
$2,000.
-How much do we have?
-$100.
Look, this week nothing
has come in at all.
What about Buck Britt's retainer?
There's 2 grand.
That check bounced.
What do you mean?
It bounced, Jake.
It sat on your desk all week.
Not that you'd notice.
Since you took this case, you
stopped talking to your clients...
...you don't take your calls...
...you're obsessed! You are!
You're obsessed!
Your obsession is going to break us!
What's wrong? We've
been through hard times.
No, not like this, Jake.
Not like this.
We've been getting calls.
At home.
Threats.
You know Bud has survived two strokes.
I don't think he'd survive a third.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why, Jake?
Would you drop the case?
Jake Brigance's office.
Until they cut the phones off.
Oh, right.
That was Sheriff Walls.
You better get down to the jail.
What's going on here?
I'm lsaiah Street.
Jake Brigance.
I believe you know Reverend Agee.
And this is...
Norman Reinfeld, I've seen
your picture in the paper.
I assume these boys carry your things.
Just a small part of
my legal defense team.
Pleasure, Mr. Brigance.
If it's a party, where's the beer?
Otherwise...
...your being here seems a bit like
illegal client solicitation...
...with Carl Lee
already having a lawyer.
Just a minute.
Carl Lee invited us here.
Mr. Brigance...
...let me be frank.
Mr. Hailey's case has
far-reaching ramifications.
Carl Lee's acquittal for
killing 2 white men...
...would do more for
black people than...
...any event since we
integrated the schools.
His conviction, on the other
hand, will be a slap at us.
A symbol of deep-seated racism.
Perhaps enough to ignite a nation.
See how important this case is?
Enter Mr. Reinfeld's death squad, right?
It's an unfortunate
nickname, but apropo.
My lawyers and I handle
only capital murder cases.
Of all your cases...
...how many are supposed to be
lost so you can martyr the victim?
How much a defense like that cost?
What, about $100,000?
We are prepared to accept $7,000
in litigation expenses.
Carl Lee doesn't have $7,000.
Do you?
The NAACP...
...has raised $5,000 for Carl
Lee's legal defense fund.
And we raised an additional
$2,000 from local churches.
Let me ask you something.
How much of that cash you
offer my wife and kids?
That money...
...is to go to pay for lawyers' fees.
That ain't what you told the church.
You almost cried when you told them...
...how my family might starve
if they didn't donate.
The money is for you
and your family, but...
...we thought it'd be better
spent on the legal defense.
Speaking of that defense fund...
...can I use that for any lawyer I want?
It's not that simple, Carl Lee.
Actually, it is that simple, Carl Lee.
Unless the NAACP...
...wants to go on record as soliciting
funds under false pretenses.
Listen...
...we raised that money...
...for these men to get you out of
here, not for this cracker to--
Now, hold on. Hold on right there, now.
Let me just get this
straight here, Reverend.
If you don't give my wife...
...that cash...
...l'll see to it everybody in this
town knows you're a lying crook.
Your congregation will
be interested to know...
...Gwen and the kids can't eat
because you want in with the NAACP.
That's right.
When I'm through with you...
...you won't be able to collect
2 cents in the collection plate.
We'll expect the check for
the Hailey family today.
I sure do appreciate your fine work...
...but I'll take my chances with Jake.
Thanks for coming down.
We'll expect that check...
...for Jake's legal services
around the same time today.
Good day, men.
You set that whole thing up.
Couldn't have done it alone.
Make one hell of a team.
You out there.
I'm in here.
We ain't no team.
There's trouble.
Look there.
No, here's trouble.
You are?
Meet Harry Rex Vonner...
...the most effective, morally-
compromised lawyer in the country.
Ellen Roark, brilliant law student.
Do what you will.
Looking forward to it.
This might interest you.
In assessing murder trials, the
insanity plea only makes up 1\/\ overall.
And of the 1\/\ that resulted in acquittal
success rested almost wholly on the--
Defending psychiatrist regardless of the
quality of the psychological testimony.
Shazam. She is brilliant.
"She." That would be me?
Who else?
She would be me.
She is saying that if I
take this plea to trial...
...the verdict will hinge on the
shrink the jury finds more credible.
She will be correct.
She would.
Sure you don't need help?
I do.
I'm hiring. Right now. Me.
Roark, I am sure that I don't need
any help. Thank you, though.
I guess that would just
have to be your loss, then.
Nice to meet you, Morally-Compromised.
Pleasure's all mine...
..."She."
You've got to love the Lord
for making things like that.
Sure you don't want to look at
her rsum? You could use help.
No, I don't want to look at
her rsum, because I have you.
You do?
Yeah, buddy.
This is your chance to put aside your
shady sources and greedy divorcees...
...and do some real law for once.
Mr. Vonner, in short...
...you have the opportunity to
work on a case that matters.
Let me get this straight.
You want me to put aside my
empty, soulless, shady...
...astonishingly lucrative,
divorcee practice...
...come work with you on an unwinnable,
lose-all-my-friends case...
...because it matters?
It's a novel idea, I know.
No way. Never.
Presumptuous little shit.
Goodnight, y'all.
I need the sheriff.
He's asleep.
Well, get him up.
Who is this?
Someone's going to die tonight.
I got him!
Get his ass!
What's in the case?
It's ticking.
What is it?
I ain't saying.
Family out?
It's locked.
Open it.
My God!
Oh, man....
Defuse it.
I'm going to take you and this...
...nigger-lover to hell with--
Ain't nothing more dangerous
than a fool with a cause.
Lay that thing back down there
real easy-like. Let's go.
Carla loves this house.
Come here.
Are you coming to Grandpa's too?
Daddy must stay here and work.
You and your mom have a good time.
You be good.
Go get your stuff.
You said you'd quit if it got dangerous.
I know.
I can't quit now, you know that.
Carl Lee is facing the gas chamber.
The man is counting on me.
I understand that, Jake.
Remember that we're counting on you too.
What if something happens to you?
Nothing's going to happen. Come here.
Hug?
Everything will be okay.
I'll be fine, you'll be fine.
Okay, babe?
I promise.
Don't make promises you can't keep.
You ready?
Good afternoon. Come in.
Good afternoon.
You may come this way.
The judge is upstairs.
Thank you, sir.
Judge Noose.
Thanks for coming.
Heard you had trouble last night.
Makes you wonder about the
sensibleness of taking this case.
This is a beautiful place you have here.
I'll get to the point.
I've thoroughly reviewed
your brief request and...
...a change of venue.
And I agree with you. It's impossible
to find an impartial jury in Canton.
I think it's impossible to find an
impartial jury anywhere in Mississippi.
As such...
...a jury here would be...
...as fair as a jury anywhere else.
So I decided to deny your
request for a change of venue.
I guess that...
...gives me something to appeal.
Actually, no.
I spoke to Judge Dent...
...and he believes that the Supreme
Court would uphold my ruling.
You certainly covered your bases.
You're a good lawyer.
You're bright and ambitious.
Talented.
You could be someone.
You sure you want to be known as
the man that defended that murderer?
Could be very unpopular.
Talk to your client.
He pleads guilty...
...Buckley'll accept manslaughter.
He'll be out in 20.
And how's his wife supposed
to raise his family alone?
Better than being a widow.
Think about it.
Why toss away a promising career?
Good day.
Thanks for coming.
Where the hell is this guy?
Born alcoholic.
But the man cannot hold his liquor.
Allow me to present
Dr. Willard Tyrrel Bass.
Expert witness for the defense.
This is Jake Brigance...
...my protg.
Are you kidding me?
Relax.
When he's sober, he's terrific.
He has his license.
His credentials are impeccable.
Well, I need a drink.
3 in the afternoon?
My, oh, my, what would your wife say?
I am my own man. I drink when I want.
-When did she leave town?
-This morning.
God!
That's enough!
Now you tell your boss...
...next time people are going to die.
Morning.
Nice parking job. Late night?
So, here.
Thank you.
Your wife lets you sleep here?
My wife left town.
That's too bad.
Listen, I heard that...
...Noose turned down your motion.
It's time I take you to breakfast.
Lunch.
Quit playing with that food.
Y'all come back. You need to
finish that before Christmas.
Thank you.
Now....
You are opposed to the death penalty.
Why?
You're not?
I'm in favor of it.
I'd like to go back to
hangings if we could.
You're kidding.
No. The only problem with the death
penalty is that we do not use it enough.
Have you told Carl Lee this?
The men who raped his daughter deserved
the death penalty, not Carl Lee.
How do you decide who
dies and who doesn't?
Simple. You take the crime
and you take the criminal.
Now, say...
...a crack dealer guns
down an undercover cop.
You strap him to a chair and turn it on.
For some reason, I thought
you were a liberal.
I am a liberal.
What I am not is a
card-carrying A.C.L.U. radical.
I don't believe in rehabilitation.
I believe in safety.
I believe in justice.
I see. Well, let me ask you something.
Ever seen an execution?
Not that I recall.
I suggest you go watch
a man be executed.
You watch him die, watch him beg, watch
him kick and spit the life out of him...
...until he shits and is gone.
Then come back and sing
this crap about justice....
Spare me your Northern
liberal cry-me-a-river...
...we-are-the-only-enlightened-ones
bullshit.
I'm sorry, yes, you are the enlightened.
That's why you brought me to this
diner in this black neighborhood.
So you can convince me you're
this JFK-meets-Christ white boy.
Is that it?
Or is it because you're a repressed,
hypocritical provincial...
...who didn't want to be seen
around town with a woman like me.
Yes, siree, you sure are enlightened.
I'm terribly sorry, I've made a mistake.
I thought you were one of the good guys.
Thank you for your time.
I'm a little worked up.
That's not the best
way to apply for a job.
I don't want the jury to see pictures of
the dead rapists. Can we keep them out?
It's vital the jury know
the details of the rape.
I'll need briefs on both.
I don't like your politics,
but you do have passion...
...and that's something Carl
Lee needs, and maybe so do l.
You getting this?
I'm writing it down.
Here's what we got. It's official.
Hailey's trial will be held in Canton.
Today, presiding Judge Noose issued
150 summons for potential jurors...
...in a sealed envelope.
To prevent tampering...
...that list will be kept
confidential until selection begins.
No one, not even
Mr. Brigance or myself...
...will know the identities
of the potential jurors.