[Girl]
Cinderella flew through the air...
far from all things
ugly and ordinary..
When she landed at the ball,
she found herself...
most impertinently surrounded
by pirates.
There was AlfMason,
so ugly his mother sold him
for a bottle ofmuscat.
BillJukes,
every. inch ofhim tattooed.
And worst ofthem all,
Hook, with eyes bl ue
as forget-me-nots,
save when he clawed your belly
with the iron hook he has...
instead of a right hand,
at which time...
his eyes turn red.
"Girlie," said Hook,
"we have come
forye glass slippers."
Who beyou to order me about
and call me girlie?
Take that!
Take that! Take that!
Commoner!
-[ Girl]
Hook came at her.
- [ Screaming ]
[ Gasps ]
[Boy]
What happened then?
[ Girl]
The brave Cinderella settled
the matter once and for all...
with her revolver.
With her revolver?
[ Woman Narrating ]
The night on which
the extraordinary. adventures...
ofthese children
may be said to have begun...
was the night Nana
barked at the window.
But there was nothing there,
not a bird or a leaf.
So the children forgot
about it,
for what troubles a grown-up
will never trouble a child.
- [ Cuckooi ng ]
- [ Al I Gasp ]
Oh, dearest George, dear Mary.
Oh, what a journey I 've had.
Bath time.
- [ Whooping ]
- [ Barks ]
[ Screaming ]
[Screaming Continues ]
[ Barks ]
Not fair!
[Narrator]
Not fair, indeed. But Nana was
the finest nurse on fourpaws.
No. No, I will not
forgive you.
@@ [ Piano ]
[ Narrator]
There never was
a happier, simpler family.
Mr. Darling was a banker
who knew the cost ofeverything,
even a hug.
Mrs. Darling was the loveliest
lady in Bloomsbury....
with a sweet, mocking mouth
that had one kiss on it...
that Wendy could never get.
Though there it was,
perfectly conspicuous
on the right-hand corner.
And sometimes there
was Aunt Millicent...
who felt a dog for a nurse
lowered the whole tone
ofthe neighborhood.
Al I ri ght, al I ri ght,
al I ri ght, al I right.
Less noise.
- Let's settle down.
This is not a farm.
- [ Whines ]
- [Millicent ]
Bravo, George. Bravo.
- Wendy's turn.
Wendy must tell a story.
@@ [ Piano ]
Cecco, who carved his name
on the governor at Goa.
Noodler, with his hands
on backwards.
- Heavens.
- Hook!
- Hook?
- Hook, whose eyes turn red
as he guts you.
Upon my soul, how children
are educated nowadays.
- [ Chuckles ]
- I'm afraid I am not
learned at all, Aunt.
- But I do know a thing or two
about pirates.
- Ooh.
My unfulfilled ambition is
to write a great novel in three
parts about my adventures.
- What adventures?
- I'veyet to have them,
but theywill be
perfectly thrilling.
But, child, novelists
are not highly thought of
in good society.
And there is nothing
so difficult to marry as a novelist.
- Marry?
- But, Aunt, Wendy is notyet 1 3.
Walk toward me, dear,
that I may appraiseyou.
[Mr. Darling]
Go on.
Walk toyour auntie.
Stand up straight.
[ Giggling ]
[ Whines ]
- Stop it!
- Turn around.
[LaughterContinues ]
Shh.
Mm, yes.
Oh, it's Quite as I expected.
Wendy possesses a woman's chin.
Haveyou not noticed?
Observe her mouth.
There, hidden
in the right-hand corner,
is that a kiss?
[Mrs. Darling Gasps ]
- A kiss?
- Like Mother's kiss.
- [Millicent ]
A hidden kiss.
- But what is it for?
It is for the greatest
adventure of all.
They that find it...
have slipped in and out ofheaven.
Find what?
The one the kiss belongs to.
MyWendy--
a woman.
Almost a woman.
She must spend less time
with her brothers...
andmore time with me.
[ All Gasp ]
She must have her own room.
A young lady's room.
Leave the--
George, the daughter
of a clerk cannot hope to marry
as well as that of a manager.
You must attend more parties,
make small talkwith
your superiors at the bank.
Wit is very fashionable
at the moment.
Wit.
[ Snoring ]
[ Gasps ]
- [Barking]
- [ Gasps ]
- [ Screams ]
- [ Growling ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Barking ]
[ Growling ]
[ Moans ]
[Narrator]
But there was no sign ofa body,
fornone had fallen.
Certainlyshe had been dreaming.
- [ Loud Bang ]
- [ Gasps ]
If this is you in bed,
what is this?
A boy.
[ Narrator]
Miss Fulsom dispatched a letter
ofoutrage to Mr. Darling...
that set new standards
ofprudery., even for her.
Yes, miss.
Mr. Darling had been practicing
small talk all afternoon.
I say, it's nice weather we're having.
And now his opportunity had arrived.
Sir edward Quiller Couch,
the president ofthe bank,
was a man who enjoyed small talk...
almost as much
as a good balance sheet.
Wendy walked as one condemned.
And then... fate.
[ Bel I Ri ngs ]
The letter! Wait! Stop!
[ Michael ]
Wendy, wait!
Come back!
I say, what a splendid tie.
[ Mumbles ]
Wait! You there! Stop!
- Wendy! Nana, come back!
- [ Barking ]
That's $200 saved.
Ajudicious investment?
I ndeed.
Uh--
Hi. Um--
[ Muttering ]
I, uh--
You there, stop! Wait!
Stop! Wait!
[ Thunder Rumbling]
Uh, uh, uh-- I, uh--
[Stammering]
[Pounding]
[ Wendy]
Father!
I can explain!
No!
[ Grunts ]
[ All Screaming ]
[ Crash ]
[ Men Grumbling ]
[Mr. Darling]
I have been humiliated!
[ Wendy Chattering ]
No!
I must become a man
that children fear
and adults respect,
orwe shall all
end up in the street!
George, not so loud.
The neighbors will hear.
Let them hear.
Let the whole world know!
This is not a nurse! This is a dog.
[ Whining ]
[ Gasps ]
Tomorrowyou begin
your instruction...
withAunt Millicent.
It's time foryou to grow up!
[Barking]
[Michael]
Mother?
Can anything harm us
after the night-lights are lit?
No, precious.
They are the eyes a mother
leaves behind to guard her children.
Mother, mustyou go
to the party?
Please, Mother.
Yes, Mother,
you don't have to go.
Father can go by himself.
Please, Mother.
By himself?
Your father is a brave man.
But he's going to need
the special kiss to face
his colleagues tonight.
Father? Brave?
There are many
different kinds ofbravery.
There's the bravery ofthinking
of others before oneself.
Now, your father has never
brandished a sword nor fired
a pistol, thank heavens.
But he's made many sacrifices
for his family...
and put away many dreams.
Where did he put them?
He put them in a drawer.
And sometimes, late at night,
we take them out and admire them.
But it gets harderandharder
to close the drawer.
He does.
And that is why he is brave.
And remember, every cloud
has a silver lining.
Oh.
Oh. No, it's snowing.
Oh, we'll catch our death.
Better death than gossip.
You will enter that drawing room
with your head held high.
[ Hinge SQueaking ]
[ SQuealing ]
[ High-Pitched Chattering ]
[ Gasps ]
Oh!
[ Grunts ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Chattering Continues ]
Shh!
One, two,
[BellJingling]
three!
[ Gasps ]
Aha!
[ High-Pitched Scream ]
Come here, you!
I got you.
[ Gasps ]
- [ Shouts ]
- [ Shrieking ]
Ha!
[ Gasps ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Panting ]
Boy, why areyou crying?
[ Gasps ]
You can fly!
What is your name?
Wendy Moira Angela Darling.
Peter... Pan.
Where doyou live?
Second to the right and then
straight on till morning.
[ Gasps ]
They put that on the letters?
Don't get any letters.
Butyour mother gets letters.
Don't have a mother.
No wonderyou were crying.
I wasn't crying
about mothers.
I was crying because I can't
get the shadow to stick.
And I wasn't crying!
[ Chuckles ]
I could sew it on foryou.
[ Grunts ]
This may hurt a little.
[ Groaning ]
- [ Loud Groan ]
- Might I borrowyour knife?
[ Whimpers ]
- Thankyou.
- [ Mimicking, Growls ]
[ Chuckles ]
- Oh, the cleverness of me!
- Of course, I did nothing.
Aw, you did a little.
A little?
Good night.
Wendy?
One girl is worth more
than 20 boys.
You reallythinkso?
I live with boys-- the Lost Boys.
They are well named.
[ Gasps ]
Who are they?
Children who fall out oftheir prams
when the nurse is not looking.
Ifthey are not claimed in seven days,
they are sent to the Neverland.
- Are there girls too?
- Girls are much too clever
to fall out oftheir prams.
Peter, it is perfectly lovely
the wayyou talk about girls.
I should like to giveyou...
a... kiss.
Don'tyou know what a kiss is?
I shall know when you give me one.
I suppose
I'm to giveyou one now.
Ifyou like.
[ Clears Throat ]
Thankyou.
How old areyou, Peter?
Quiteyoung.
- Don'tyou know?
- I ran away.
One night, I heard my mother
and father talking ofwhat
I was to be when I became a man.
So I ran away to Kensington
Gardens and I met Tink.
[ SQuealing ]
- Tink?
- Tinker Bell.
She's my fairy.
- But there's no such thing as--
- Don't say that.
Every time somebody
says that, a fairy
somewhere falls down dead.
And I shall never find her
if she's dead.
You don't mean to tell me
there's a fairy in this room.
We come to listen
to the stories.
[ Grunts ]
I like the one about the prince
who couldn't find the lady
who wore glass slippers.
Cinderella.
Peter, he found her
and they-- and they...
Iived happily ever after.
I knew it.
Peter.
I should like to give you...
a... thimble.
What's that?
[ Growls ]
-[Screaming]
- Tink!
Tink! Tink, no!
[ Chattering ]
She's not very polite.
She says ifyou try.to
give me a thimble again,
she'll kill you.
Oh.
And I had supposed fairies
to be charming.
[ Blows Raspberry]
Peter, don't go.
I have to tell the others
about Cinderella.
- But I know lots of stories,
stories I could tell the boys.
- Come with me.
I-- I cannot fly.
I'll teachyou.
I'll teach you to ride the wind's back.
And awaywe go.
Could John and Michael come too?
[ Snoring ]
- Michael! Michael!
- [ Grunts ]
-John! John!
- I didn't do it.
There is a boy here
who is to teach us to fly.
You offend reason, sir.
Mm-hmm.
I should like to
offend it with you.
You just think happy thoughts,
and they liftyou into the air.
[ Chuckles ]
It's easy.
I've got it! I've got it!
Swords, daggers, Napoleon!
-[Wendy]
Standback.
- Yahoo!
[ Screaming ]
[ Grunts ]
John!
- [ Groans ]
- [ Laughing ]
[ Gasps ]
Wendy! Wendy! Watch me!
Puddings, mud pies, ice cream,
never to take a bath again!
[ Screaming ]
[Wendy]
Michael!
[ Barking ]
Whoa!
[ Gasps, Giggling ]
Come away.
Come away to Neverland.
Oh. What about Mother?
Father?
Nana?
- There are mermaids.
- Mermaids?
Indians!
[ Both ]
Indians?
- Pirates!
- [ Both ]
Pirates?
Whoa-ho!
John, wait forme!
[ Barking ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Chuckling ]
[ Laughing ]
Mayl introduce mywife...
Mary?
Mary.
Delighted.
Thankyou, Sir Edward.
[Barking]
[Banging]
- [ Guests Gasping ]
- [ Gasps ]
Forget them, Wendy.
Forget them all.
Come with me where you'll never,
never have to worry about
grown-up things again.
What is it? What's wrong?
Never is an awfully long time.
[Narrator]
It wouldbe delightful to report
that theyreached the nursery.in time.
But then there
would be no story..
[ Michael, John Shouting ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Shouting ]
[ Woman ]
But you're covered
in dog hair, my darling.
- [ Peter] Hello, old chap.
- [ Wendy] Good evening.
[John ]
Thankyou.
Whoa-ho!
[ Shouting ]
Higher!
Who areyou?
I'm John.
[ Chattering ]
John.
Take hold ofthis.
Ta-da!
Both hands.
[John Shouting ]
Pass it on.
Michael, take hold ofmy ankle.
Wendy, take hold ofmy ankle!
Andwhateverhappens,
don't... Iet...
go!
[ All Screaming ]
[Wendy]
Neverland.
[Birds Twittering]
[Men ]
@ Lying, thieving
a life ofsin @
@ A pirating we go @
@ We're sure to meet below @
@ Fire the cannons
Pour the rum @
@ Deal the cards
For night has come @
@ A pirating we go @@
[ Grunting ]
[ Snoring ]
[ SQuawking ]
[ Screaming ]
Devil bird!
[ Sighing ]
[Rumbling]
[ Men Shouting ]
Cap'n?
Cap'n? As I was sitting
wide-eyed on mywatch,
I noticed it was
wintertime on the water
and springtime on the shore.
I says to meself,
"That's early for spring to be astir.
Spring's not due till 3:00 p.m."
Check the timeyourself,
Cap'n, and then tell--
I was dreaming, Smee, of Pan.
Pan, Cap'n?
And in my dream,
I was a magnanimous fellow...
full offorgiveness.
I thanked Pan...
for cutting offmyhand...
and for giving me
this fine hook...
for disemboweling
and ripping throats...
and other such homely uses...
as combing my hair.
[ Groans ]
So, Pan did you
a favor then, Cap'n?
A favor?
He threw my hand
to a crocodile.
The beast liked it so much,
it's followed me ever since,
Iicking its lips
for the rest of me.
[ Shouting ]
You call that a favor?
No. No. No. No.
Thankyou.
Thank Lucifer the beast
swallowed a clock.
Ifit wasn't forthe ticking,
it'd have had me bynow.
[ Groans ]
Why did you wake me, Smee?
Like I said, Cap'n,
the ice is melting.
The sun is out.
And the flowers are all in bloom.
He's back.
[ Chattering ]
Forty gunner.
She must do 12 knots
underfullsail.
[ Gasps ]
Noodler, with his hands
on backwards!
Bill J ukes!
Every inch of him tattooed.
[ Gasps ]
Hook!
[ Whispering ]
Let's take a closer look.
Yahoo!
[ Wendy ]
Peter!
Watch this.
Whoa-ho-ho!
[ Shouting Continues ]
[John ]
Whoa! My hat!
Ugly Smee!
Ugly, fat Smee!
[ SQuawks ]
Solar eclipse.
Dark in here.
Let me out. Let me out!
[Squawks ]
Can't see.
Dark in here. Candle.
I need candle. Help! Help!
Fetch Long Tom.
Fire!
[ Screaming ]
- Help! Help!
- [ Laughing ]
[ Grunts ]
[John, Michael Screaming ]
Tink, find Wendy.
Leave the rest to me.
Wendy.
Oh, Captain Hook!
Pan!
Staywith him!
You can't catch me.
Overhere!
Fire!
[Pan Laughing]
Timber!
[ Both ]
Whoa!
Michael, are you shot?
I haven't checked yet!
But there's something worser!
Oh, what could be worse?
My thoughts aren't very happy!
Happy thoughts!
Happy thoughts.
What would Mom and Dad do?
Napoleon!
[Hook]
Damnation!
Reload the cannon! Quickly!
Reload the cannon?
But, Cap'n, he is gone.
[Hook Piercing Flesh ]
Any other contributions?
Search the jungle!
Bring me those children!
[Boy] What is it?
[Boy#2 ]
It's a large white bird.
Quite ugly too. No!
Give me it!
When Peter's away,
I'm in charge!
I get to look
through the telescope.
It's coming closer.
[ SQueals ]
[ Gasps ]
My God, I've gone blind!
[ Laughing ]
[ Mimicking ]
I'm blind. I've gone blind.
I'm blind.
Hello, Tink. Where's Peter?
[ Both ]
Hello, Tink.
She's blinded me!
- Any more news ofCinderella?
- [ Chatters ]
[Narrator]
Now, TinkerBell was not all bad.
Sometimes she was all good.
But fairies are so small they only
have room for one feeling at a time.
Ti nk says the bi rd's
cal led a... "Wendy."
And Peter wants us to--
[ Gasps ]
Oh, Peter! Oh!
shoot it down.
Well, we have our orders.
Shoot the Wendy bird.
[ All ]
Aye, aye!
Ready? Aim!
- [ Gasps ]
- Fire!
Bye-bye!
Three, two,
one!
[ All Gasp ]
I got it. I got it!
[ All Shouting ]
[ Laughing ]
That is no bird.
It is a lady.
[ Both ]
And Tootles--
[ All ]
Tootles has killed her.
Ha! I'm back! Great news.
I know what happened
to Cinderella.
She defeated the pirates.
There was stabbing, slicing,
torturing, bleeding...
and theylivedhappilyeverafter.
Well, that's a relief,
I must say.
Greaternews!
I have brought you she
that told ofCinderella.
She is to tell us stories!
She is--
Dead.
Tragic.
Awful.
Good shot, though.
Whose arrow?
Mine, Peter.
Strike, Peter.
Strike true.
[ Moans ]
- The Wendy lives!
- [ Screams ]
It's my kiss.
My kiss saved her.
I remember kisses.
Let me see it.
Aye, that is a kiss.
A powerful thing.
Let us carry her down
to the house.
Hands.
They're a bit dirty.
She muststayhere anddie.
No!
Oh, how could I have
thought that? Stupid.
Sorry.
We shall build
a house around her.
[ All Cheering, Chattering ]
With a chimney!
And a door knocker!
And windows!
[ Both Whispering ]
Tink did it.
TinkerBell?
Oh, TinkerBell?
[ SQueaks ]
- Was it you, Tink?
- Hallelujah. Hallelujah.
[ Snickering,
Chattering ]
Then I am your friend no more.
[ Whimpers ]
[ Chuckling, Gasps ]
[ Chattering]
First impressions
are very., very.important.
[Hammering]
Here she is.
Look loveable.
Wendy lady, foryou we built
this house with a door knocker.
And a chi m ney.
One, two, three.
[ Al I ]
Please be our mother.
Oh.
Well, it is frightfully fascinating.
But, you see,
I've had no real experience.
Do you tell stories?
Yes.
Then you're perfect.
Verywell.
- I will do my best.
- Hooray!
[ All Chattering At Once ]
Sorry about the blindfold.
We must be cautious.
There are some nasty
characters about.
If Hook discovers our hideout,
he'll gut us.
How dreadful!
Oh, we live for it!
But I--
Time to meet Father, Mother.
So looking forward
to being your son.
[ Screams ]
[ Both Grunt ]
Welcome, Mother.
Discipline. That's what
fathers believe in.
You must spank the children immediately
before they try to kill you again.
In fact, we should kill them.
[ Shouting ]
[ All Screaming ]
Peter!
Father!
I agree that they
are perfectly horrid,
but kill them
and they shall think
themselves important.
So important.
And uniQue.
I suggest something...
far more dreadful.
Medicine.
It's the most beastly,
disgusting stuff.
[ Sniffs ]
The sticky, sweet kind.
[ All ]
Kill us, please!
Littlest first. Michael?
- Michael.John. My brothers!
- Who?
[Animal Roaring]
Hello?
[echoing]
Hello? Hello? Hello?
[Ticking]
It's louder from inside
this rock.
How very peculiar.
[ Low Growling ]
- [ Roaring ]
- [ Screaming ]
[John ]
Happythoughts!
Swords, daggers, Napoleon!
[ Both Screaming ]
How humiliating.
John, there's something worser.
[ Both Screaming ]
Princess TigerLily.
[ Gasps ]
We search as everforPeterPan...
and his secret hideout.
Luckily, two boys
ofhis acQuaintance...
were seen falling
into this part ofthejungle.
Have you seen them?
[ Speaking Foreign Language ]
She says,
"Sorry, but, no."
My Hook thinks
you have, Princess.
I say, unhand that savage, you--
you--yousavage!
[Narrator]
Now, mermaids are not
as theyare in story.books.
Theyare dark creatures...
in touch with all things mysterious.
IfHook had captured
Wendy's brothers,
the mermaids would know.
Oh, how sweet.
Are mermaids not sweet?
They'l I sweetly drown you
ifyou get too close.
[ Clicking Tongues ]
- [ Hisses ]
- [ Screeches ]
Hook has your brothers
at the Black Castle.
[Thunderclap ]
Like all surprise attacks,
it must be conducted...
improperly.
Put the children on the rock.
@@ [ Humming ]
[ Laughing ]
Sorry, Your Highness.
Any last words?
Beg foryour lives.
Sirs! My brother and I
are English gentlemen.
English gentlemen do not beg.
Please!
Please! Please!
Please don't kill us!
Please don't kill me, either.
I've never done anything--
Aah! It's cold! It's cold!
[Michael]
Help!
Come on. Fly to the rescue,
and then I'll shootyou right
through your noble intentions.
I brought these.
Can you use it?
Promise me one thing.
Leave Hook to me.
I promise.
- Wait here for my signal.
- Wait here?
Peter!
[Narrator]
Thus Wendyfirst laideyes on
the dark figure who haunted herstories.
She saw the piercing eyes
and was not afraid,
but entranced.
[ Men ]
@ We're sure to meet below @
[ Laughi ng ]
[ Hook ]
Mr. Smee?
That you, Cap'n?
Brimstone and gall, man.
What do you thinkyou're doing?
Well, we've put the children
on the rope, Cap'n, like you said.
Set 'em free!
Set 'em free?
- Well, what about your trap?
- Set them free, or
I'll plunge my hook in you.
[ Sword Clanging ]
[ Gasps ]
I don't know what he wants with 'em.
I'm just a blithering idiot, aren't I?
Chain 'em up. Let 'em go.
- And takeyour cat with ya.
- [DoorOpens ]
[ Whispering
In Foreign Language]
Mr. Smee?
Aye, Cap'n?
- Any sign ofhim?
- No, Cap'n.
Where are the children?
It's all right, Cap'n.
We let 'em go.
You what?
- [ Chuckling ]
- [ Both Laughing ]
You... Iet... them... go.
- [ Hook's Voice ]
Mr. Smee!
- [ Screaming ]
Who areyou, stranger?
I amJames Hook,
captain ofthe Jolly Roger.
Ifyou are Hook,
then who am I?
You are a codfish.
[Pan Laughing]
Tell me, Hook,
haveyou anothername?
Aye.
- Vegetable?
- No.
- Mineral?
Animal?
Yes.
- Man?
- [ Own Voice ]
No!
- Boy?
- Yes!
-Ordinary.boy?
- No!
- Wonderful boy?
- Yes! Doyou give up?
- Yes!
- I am--
- History.
- Peter, look out!
[Laughing]
There he is!
It is your reQuiem mass, boy.
[ Shouting ]
Ready to lose the other one?
Not this time.
[ Gasps ]
[ Chuckling ]
Ooh-ooh, girlie.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Screams ]
Who beyou to call me girlie?
- [ Peter Laughing ]
- Ow.
[Michael]
Open the gate!
- [ Shouting ]
- [ Screams ]
Teddy!
[ Groans ]
Ew.
Oh.
[ Grunting ]
If I were you, I'd give up.
Ifyou were me, I'd be ugly.
No!
Ready?
Fire!
[John ]
Get the boat!
- [ All Shouting ]
- [ Screaming ]
[ Coughs ]
[Thunderclap ]
Turn the boat around.
Turn it around!
And now, Peter Pan,
you shall die.
To die will be
an awfully big adventure.
[Ticking]
Oh, no.
[ Roars ]
- Shoot it!
- [ Men Shouting ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Children Laughing ]
You.
[ Gasps ]
Smee!
It's all a bit tragic,
really, isn't it?
[Children Whooping]
@@ [Woman Chanting]
@@ [Drum Beating]
[Boy]
The warrioris wounded.
She is calling forth
the spirit of the eagle
to heal the warrior.
It's so impressive.
The warrior is healed.
- [Man Shouts In
Foreign Language ]
- [ All Shout ]
[ Whooping ]
Peter?
Shh.
[ Gasps ]
Evil day.
He has found himself a--
[ Chattering ]
Wendy?
And Hook is all alone.
Me too.
You too?
Banished? Tsk, tsk.
The dog.
[ Chatters ]
I thinkyou and I...
should talk.
Wendy?
It's only make-believe,
isn't it?
Thatyou and I are--
Oh. Yes.