My name is Hope Cassidy.
Sometimes all you have
is your name. Hope.
Attention, attention!!
Suspect Kelly Roos is heading
for the Grand Bazaar.
Cover all the exits!!
Move!
My parents planned
on having three girls:
Hope, Faith and Charity.
A plane crash prevented
there being any Faith or Charity...
...leaving only Hope.
Get out of the way!
My dad used to say to me:
"In times of trouble, you only
have to remember who you are.
Because no matter how bad things
will get, there's always hope. "
Get out of the way!
My father was an eternal optimist.
That's what made him think his plane
wouldn't go down in that thunderstorm.
He was wrong.
I'm not Kelly Roos.
English.
Hope!
My name is Hope Cassidy.
Where am I?
In Capa Hospital. Istanbul.
Feel like talking, Kelly?
My name's Hope.
Put this on.
Not my color.
Can I see what else you have?
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
Where--? No. No! No!
You can't just leave.
What are you doing? No. No! No!
Where are you taking me?
Where am I going? No!
Who's watching me?
Dr. Kavak.
Where am I?
Jail. In Istanbul.
Maximum-security.
But you're not a doctor, are you?
You're a shrink.
Here to see if I'm fit to stand trial?
-I'm Dr. Kavak.
-And I'm Hope Cassidy.
That is why we are here.
To see exactly who you are.
I know who I am.
-What--? Do you think I'm crazy?
-No.
-Delusional?
-Yes.
You need to tell me how
this happened.
Oh, you fixed it.
-You're a genius.
-No.
It is my job.
I just returned it to normal.
-I'm really tired of normal, James.
-Hope, we've been over this.
-We were gonna live together anyway.
-I have my studies.
You can research dinosaurs anywhere.
A little thing called the Internet.
-I've pulled up some websites for you.
-I'm settled here.
-Do you want me to go alone?
-Better still...
...not at all.
Can you--? Can you put this down
for a second?
Someone has actually requested me.
Actually wants me.
Besides, we need a change.
I-- I need a change.
-I need some adventure in my life.
-Order the steak tartare.
Mad cow is on the rise.
-Have you decided?
-I've decided what I want.
How about you, James?
Well, she's waiting.
-So am l.
-I'll come back.
What?
I love you.
But come on, Istanbul?
It's the other end of the world.
-It's not safe, it's full of terrorists--
-No, no, no.
I've checked.
I talked to the State Department.
There's probably more terrorists
in your vertebrate class...
...than there is in Turkey.
I don't have a ticket.
Yeah, you do.
I got them to give me two tickets.
First-class. Look, I've never
done anything first-class in my life.
This is a major corporation.
Suzer International
has offices all over the world.
You've got a job there.
What is the point of me going?
I'd be there.
You know what,
I'm on that plane tomorrow, okay?
Here's your ticket. I know
what it means if you're not there.
This is crazy. Come on.
Did you think about this?
Do you know what you're getting into?
For once in my life, yeah, I do.
Hope. Hope.
-Hello.
-What?
-Hi.
-Get it all the way up.
-Okay.
-Are you in here?
-Yes.
-We're having fun...
-We're having fun.
-...making little videos for ourselves.
-Bye.
Ladies and gentlemen...
...the final boarding call
for flight 101 to Istanbul.
I don't understand how they do it.
-What's that?
-Internet on these planes.
Well, it's very technical.
It's what you would call magic.
Good explanation.
The only thing that makes any sense.
Roxelena. Pretty name.
Is it your first time to Istanbul?
-Coming for a job.
-You'll love it. Many places to see.
You must go to Ortaköy.
To the cafés there.
I'm always there
when I'm not here.
-Ortaköy.
-Yes.
Thanks. You know what?
I'll give it a try.
Okay.
I'm Hope.
Just plain Hope.
-Not a name I would've chosen.
-You don't like it?
As a kid, I always wanted to be Diana.
Like the Greek goddess.
-Goddess of the moon.
-Yeah.
Diana. All right.
Look, since this is your first time,
you could use this.
-No, I'm sorry, I can't take this.
-You must.
Turkish hospitality.
This is an evil-eye bracelet.
Turkish people believe that it protects
you from evil eye or bad luck.
You see, nothing is ever
as it seems in Istanbul.
Thank you.
You sure you don't want something?
Champagne?
To celebrate the new job?
-Why not?
-Okay.
-Here you go. Enjoy.
-Thanks.
You know, this could happen to you.
To anyone. Do you have
credit cards, driver's license?
-Of course.
-Okay, well, I guarantee you...
...that someone has used your identity
and you don't even know it.
But how can they steal who you are?
When there's not much to steal.
Thanks. Next, please.
-Thanks, ma'am.
-Thanks.
-Wait, this says "tourist."
-What it is.
No, I have a work visa,
I'm moving here.
No work visa.
Your passport expires too soon.
-Next one, please.
-No, no, wait a minute.
The Turkish consulate said--
Go to American consulate, get
new passport. Next, please! Please.
Suzer International.
Yes, my name's Hope Cassidy,
I'm trying to reach Ali Abay.
-Okay.
-He hired me.
You're at the airport now?
I just arrived from America...
...and someone
was supposed to meet me here.
There should be a driver.
No, no. No one's here,
there's no driver or....
Oh, I'm sorry,
you'll have to take a cab.
Take a cab.
I exchanged a few dollars
at the L.A. airport.
Twenty-seven million
two hundred thousand.
-What?
-I said, 27,200,000 Turkish lire.
-I take you to hotel.
-Twenty-seven....
-I don't have 27--
-Twenty dollars, same thing here.
Hey. No, no, wait a minute!
You don't even know what hotel I'm at.
Hotel Sultanahmet Palace.
Just near the blue mosque.
It's very nice. Don't worry about it.
Wait a minute, how do you--? Hold on.
Could you tell me what hotel I'm at.
-Sultanahmet Palace.
-The Sultanahmet Palace. Thanks.
How the hell did you know that?
I think you are American.
Americans stay there.
You have a lot of luggage.
There, people stay long time...
...and you dropped this,
your schedule.
-Right?
-Right.
To the hotel? Yeah.
But first I need to go by the U.S.
Embassy to get my passport fixed.
Sure, as you wish, no problem.
Here.
Istanbul has population
of over 1 2 million.
It was founded
in the seventh century...
...and was the capital
of Byzantine Empire...
...and then of Ottoman sultans.
It was once called Constantinople.
-Hang on. Sorry.
-Yeah.
Istanbul is beautiful city.
-I hope you like it, yeah?
-Yeah, excuse me.
-Yeah?
-I'm sorry, I don't know your name.
Oh, sorry. Osman.
My name is Osman.
Osman. Look, I really appreciate
the tour, I do, but I'm really tired.
-Jet lag, you know?
-Sure, of course. This is why I talk.
I see you have come alone. You will
be joined by, how you say, boyfriend?
How you say, horse's ass?
Yes, of course. Horse's ass.
I am sorry. Traffic is very bad.
I can do this. I can do this.
I can do this.
Sign there and date, please.
How long do you think it will take
for my passport? A few weeks?
No, no, no. We're a small office...
...but I e-mail Washington,
assuming no hitches...
...you can walk in tomorrow
and walk out with a temporary.
-You're a hero.
-Thanks. Please, tell that to my wife.
-We open at 9.
-Okay, I'll be here. Thank you.
Great. Next!
A butterfly tattoo...
...on his hand.
Find this guy, he can vouch for me.
He knows I'm not Kelly Roos.
This is the best you can do,
an embassy clerk?
I know no one here.
-Yes.
Right.
You need something, anything
or even nothing...
...you call. I'm good for anything,
good for nothing. I'm always here.
Okay, I'm sure I'll be fine.
-Here you go.
-Yeah, thank you.
Bye.
Here you go.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-Thank you.
Do you know how long this will take?
I don't know.
I think no more than an hour.
-No, no. No, and I won't calm down.
-This is no problem.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look, first, my luggage is just gone...
...like the guy I'm supposed to travel
with, and now I can't get in my room.
-No, I just wanna go to my room--
-Hey, hey.
-What?
-Are you all right?
No! Wait a minute.
Are you American?
-Yeah.
-Oh, my God, thank God!
Oh, my God.
I just wanna go to my room,
you know?
Yeah, I do. Well, they said
it's gonna be about an hour.
Oh, no.
Hey. You wanna get a cup of coffee?
My treat.
I have a better idea.
Can we have a drink?
Okay? Okay.
Oh, thank God.
What kind of name is Z.Z.?
Apparently, I was conceived
to a ZZ Top song.
So I don't know,
this is not what I expected.
I actually didn't know
what to expect.
-I'm glad I'm here, though.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-For a job?
Someone called me out of the blue,
had apparently checked me out.
I was so excited,
I sent him a dozen roses.
I haven't sent a guy roses in my life.
-So are you gonna stay?
-Yeah, I....
I kind of have to.
-You have to?
-Yeah, whatever.
Just make the best out of whatever
situation you're in, you know?
Right.
Well, I'm glad you're here.
Maybe we can explore together.
-It'll be fun.
-I'd like that.
-Hope, listen--
-Hello!
I'll make a good deal for you, huh?
-Pretty scarf, see?
-No.
Are you married, girls?
I can give you a tour in the harem...
...like no one ever seen before.
-At the Topkapi Palace.
-Okay.
No?
No!
-Hello?
-It's Ali. Good morning.
We have your first assignment.
Galata Financial.
Their security system is failing,
vulnerable to attack.
They need our best...
-...smartest, cleverest.
-I'm anxious to get started.
First I need to go to the consulate
and get my visa straightened out.
Then right after,
they'll be expecting you.
Sounds great. Just send the directions
and info to my Pocket PC, please.
Yes, okay.
Hi.
Could you connect me
with Z.Z. Jackson's room?
Of course.
I'm sorry, but we don't have anyone
registered under that name.
Well, that's impossible.
She checked in yesterday.
No.
There seems
to be a misunderstanding.
Okay. Thank you.
-Taxi.
-Taxi!
Thank you.
-Look what I have for you right here.
-Yes!
Brand-new. You won't have any
problem getting a work visa with that.
Thank you so much. That was
so easy. It usually takes, like--
-This is not me.
-Everybody hates their picture.
-You should see mine.
-No, that's my picture...
...that's my address.
But that's not my name.
My name is Hope Cassidy,
this says--
-Kelly Roos.
-Yeah.
-Are you sure this isn't you?
-Yes, I'm sure this is not me!
-You have to change it.
-We're just a consulate.
We can do renewals of passports
here, but reissues...
...has to be done
by the embassy in Ankara.
-I can't-- I can't believe this.
-I don't know what to tell you. I mean....
On the computer,
I have you as Kelly Roos.
-And so maybe there's some error or--
-This is not normal.
I'm sorry.
I'll try and clear this up
as quickly as I can.
Can you come back Thursday?
Friday, maybe?
Okay, thank you.
Next!
I'm so tired.
-Can we please just take a break?
-No.
No?
Tomorrow you will be charged
for a double murder...
-...and the theft of millions of dollars.
-I want a lawyer.
-I have one day to see you--
-No, I want a phone call!
And I want to know everything
about the murders.
-About the money!
-You can't keep me locked up!
I'm an American citizen
and I have rights!
I want my phone call, I want
my lawyer, and I want it now! God!
Let's continue.
What are you doing here?
Are you following me?
-No, no, no. I'm just trying to work.
-You've got to stop following me.
-It's freaking me out.
-All right.
-How will you get to next appointment?
-Well, l....
All right.
-How many millions will this cost me?
-Don't worry, it's no problem.
We will come to an arrangement.
I'll take you wherever
you want to go.
So this is Galata's offices?
Yeah, they are wealthy company
and eccentric.
I know these people.
-I'll probably be a number of hours.
-All right, I wait.
Okay.
My name is Hope Cassidy
to see Mr. Ibrahim Zoralan.
ID?
-Oh, I have a driver's license.
-Yeah, okay.
Well, I had my driver's license.
I don't know--
-It has to be in here somewhere.
-Hope Cassidy!
So pleased to have
you be my acquaintance.
Ibrahim Zoralan, come with me.
I've heard so much about you.
This is our new offices.
Built in late 1 800s
by one of the last sultans.
You can still see the construction
going on.
Galata is an international
holding company.
A hundred million dollars
a day go through here...
...through our supercomputer.
Right this way, please.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
-You tripped the alarm.
-You're lucky I'm here.
-To turn it off?
That, and....
Don't worry, I'll protect you.
Ibrahim Zoralan.
Voice-activated security?
My own design.
And cannot be duplicated.
So this is it. Galata's nerve centre.
Our supercomputer.
I call it Ibrahim.
After myself, of course.
-Impressed?
-With the computer?
Yes.
You've got firewalls tripping
all over each other...
...routers that date to Constantine.
Also, you see that,
what's going on up there?
You are about one broken
security key away...
...from someone having access
to every dollar going through here.
Well, that's why you're here.
Ibrahim needs protection.
He's tense, he works very hard.
He needs your women's intuition.
Your comforting.
Mr. Zoralan, I'm being paid
about $475 an hour...
...because I'm fast and good.
When not distracted.
Now, if you feel you like
my company that much...
...this could take about a month.
-If I back off?
-I'll be done by tomorrow.
I'll miss your wonderful company.
I'm sure your wife will take
your mind off of it.
I will have my security liaisons officer
to watch you until it is time to leave.
Why, you don't trust me?
With the amount of money
going through here...
...I do not trust Allah
to be alone here.
Good luck, Miss Cassidy.
Thank you.
What's that?
The consulate guy.
He was found floating
in the Bosphorus an hour ago.
Don't you get it?
These people are doing
everything they can...
...to keep you from finding out
who I am.
Are you sure it's not you doing
everything to stop me?
Don't give me that
psychological babble.
These people are trying
to destroy me!
-Who are you?
-What? I'm sorry?
Who are you?
I don't understand.
I'm Hope Cassidy.
-No, you're not.
-Excuse me?
I just spoke to Ali Abay
from Suzer International.
I was telling him how happy
we were to have you here.
He told me you were an impostor.
I'm sorry, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Do you have an ID? A passport?
Of course. I.... I just--
I don't have it with me.
Look, you know what?
Let me give Ali a call...
...and we'll get this whole thing
cleared up. Okay?
-Okay.
-Suzer International.
Yes, my name's Hope Cassidy,
can I speak with a Mr. Ali Abay?
-Hope Cassidy?
-Yes. Hope Cassidy.
Please hold.
Hello, this is Hope Cassidy. Hello?
-Hope Cassidy, can I help you?
-No! Okay.
Hello? Hello?
No, there's--
There's been a mistake!
No, you're not listening!
-Where's your passport?
-See, that's the problem!
ID. Identification.
Yes, well, I had my driver's license,
but I think I left it at the hotel.
Hey, hey, hey.
Let's go, let's go. Keep walking.
Don't look back. Don't look back.
What happened there, Osman?
What did you say to them?
I said I was your uncle
and you were a crazy person...
...like everyone from
the United States.
-Right?
-Great.
-What happened?
-I don't know.
Look, someone has taken my place.
It's this crazy, weird setup
or something.
My passport, my credit cards,
my bank accounts, everything.
Someone has taken me.
I always knew that trouble
was at this building.
Why? They....
They seemed fine.
Ivanakov.
-Ivanakov?
-Yeah.
Arms dealer. A Russian.
He's very bad man.
-A man with no soul.
-So he owns Galata?
I suggest you be careful.
Let's go.
-Where we are going now?
-Take me to Suzer.
-So you'll wait?
-Sure, of course.
Thanks, Osman.
If you weren't here,
I'd think I was going insane.
-All right. I'll be in the garage.
-Okay.
Bye, Osman.
Suzer International.
Hi, I'm here to see Hope Cassidy,
could you tell me where her office is?
I'm sorry, but I need your name.
Just a moment.
-Excuse me, can I help you?
-Not unless you have a gun.
Excuse me?
Z.Z.?
-Excuse me?
-What are you doing?
-Look, whoever you are--
-No, you know exactly who I am.
You're wearing my clothes!
I'm sorry, I really don't know
who you are.
I'm Hope!
Why are you impersonating me?
I called you at the hotel,
you never checked in.
Ok-- Okay.
Look, you can't be Hope,
because I'm Hope Cassidy, okay?
-Selim!
-Miss Cassidy?
-Yeah, we have a problem here.
-Hey, I saw that.
Look, I just wanna know why
you're screwing with me, okay?
-What do you want?
-What's all the talking about here?
Ali, thank God you're here. This crazy
woman, she just barged in here!
Ali, thank God.
-Who are you?
-I'm Hope Cassidy.
-Hope, what's going on?
-I don't know.
No, don't call her Hope!
She's a fake!
Z.Z., Kelly Roos.
Or God knows what her name is.
I'm Hope, okay?
She stole everything. My name,
my credit cards, my clothes.
Yesterday we had a conversation
and you wanted me to do a job.
-You called me--
-"The best, brightest, the cleverest."
No.
She must have tapped in on our call
or something.
You remember when you gave
me the job, what did I do?
I sent you roses.
I never sent a guy roses before.
-Yes.
-No, I told her that. I told you that!
You remember what else I said?
I said I needed to get my passport
straightened out. Remember? Right?
Hope Cassidy.
Do you have your passport?
No, that is--
This is crazy, okay?
I can prove to you that
I'm Hope Cassidy.
-The Galata job--
-Look, miss--
I can tell you access codes,
the security system.
-Security's on their way.
-Wait!
-Call the police as well, now!
-No, I have done nothing wrong!
Miss, you say you have
all the access codes.
-Exactly.
-We just had a call from Galata.
They are missing $1 4 million
out of their system.
-Oh, God!
-Stop her, stop her! Get Security!
Hey!
-Move!
-Hey!
Come on, come on, come on.
No!
Osman! Osman!
Osman! Come on,
we gotta go fast, okay?
I'll explain later. Come on, come on!
Osman! Come on.
Move!
Go, go!
What do you want from me?
Great, what else?
Get out of the way!
I can't believe this!
Hope this works.
Yes!
Sorry.
Okay.
Please pick up, pick up.
Hey, this is James,
leave me a message...
...and I'll get back to you
as soon as possible.
James, it's me, Hope.
Please answer.
I'm in a lot of trouble.
You were right.
It's just gone so wrong.
I just really--
I really need your help right now.
Look, if you're there, could you
just please pick up, please?
James?
Look, I know this is difficult.
Do you?
Do you know what it feels like...
...to go an entire life...
...and realize that none of it matters?
That, basically, the person
you thought you were...
...doesn't exist?
Chai with cream.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Hey, hey!
What did you do next?
What could I do?
I had no place to stay...
...no identity, very little money.
I had the police
and some Russian arms dealers...
...and God knows who else
were after me.
There was really only one place
that I could go...
...to find out why
this was happening to me.
Galata.
I thought it had very strong security.
I didn't say it was gonna be easy.
See, if I could get into their system...
...then I could find out
how they moved the money...
...and to where.
That would give me my start
to who these people were.
I knew that I would
have to work at night.
So the first problem
was how to get in.
-Galata Financial.
-Ibrahim Zoralan, please.
I'm afraid he has left for the day.
Can you hold for a second?
I'll see if I can get him on the phone.
I'm sorry, who am I speaking to?
Ibrahim Zoralan, who is this?
Gotcha.
Ibrahim Zoralan.
Ten minutes. This better work.
Damn it.
They changed the codes
after the break-in.
So, what did you do?
I did a probability search.
-A probability search?
-It's a surface program that I wrote.
I asked the computer to tell me...
...which keys are most probable
to be struck at a certain time.
For example, in the morning,
when they're accessing the system.
It could take a while...
...but I knew that it might be
my only chance.
Almost there, almost there.
Come on.
Yes! Okay, let's get started.
Fourteen million dollars,
where are you?
Where would you be?
Whoever did this set up
phony accounts...
...and moved them
over a dozen times...
...in order to cover up their tracks.
Finally making one mistake.
They put it in my name.
She's left the terminal.
I'm tracking her Pocket PC signal.
Attention, she's moving.
She's heading down the main hallway.
Yes, upstairs.
She's up here.
She's in the conference room.
Where did she go?
Where is my money?
Kelly Roos.
Find her before the police do.
The minute she gets on a computer,
she'll have a signature...
-...something that will give her away.
-We track her, then we kill her.
No. Bring her to me.
So you got the money?
No. Not yet, at least.
I knew I couldn't stay on the streets.
-I needed help.
-But you said you knew no one.
Not no one.
Roxelena.
-Oh, hey, Diana, the moon goddess.
-Yeah.
So you took my advice.
What do you think of Ortaköy?
I'm in trouble. I need your help.
Okay. Come.
We'll go to my place.
Hey, you hungry?
I have Turkish food.
-Very special, very famous.
-Yeah, that sounds great, I'm starved.
Here you are.
Hey, Roxelena,
I just wanted to say thanks.
I don't know what I would've done
if I hadn't found you.
Hey, maybe I found you.
It's no problem.
-I don't understand, Hope.
-I know.
This sounds crazy.
And I don't expect you to believe me.
You know what? I want to.
-Are you able to get on the Internet?
-Okay, here we go.
Oh, my God.
-What is in the bottom of that?
-The grounds. Don't drink them.
God.
Here, look.
-Put the saucer on top of it, okay?
-Okay.
-I can tell your fortune.
-Really?
Now turn it upside down.
-Okay.
-Yes.
-Okay, now what happens?
-Wait.
Americans are always in
so much of a hurry.
Yeah, well, it happens
when people are trying to kill you.
I just don't understand any of this,
you know.
The cops are after you...
...they stole the money
that you didn't take...
-...but now you're gonna try and steal--
-Borrow.
-Borrow the money back.
-Okay, borrow.
How do you even expect
to get it out?
Well, they used my name
for the bank account.
-Hope Cassidy.
-That is my name.
So, basically,
I'm just gonna re-create myself.
Come here, sit down and watch.
See, that's the president
of the bank...
...Abdul Hamit,
and that is his e-mail address.
We can bounce an e-mail
to the local bank from his account...
...to make it look like
it came from him.
So here we go.
"To all, I would like to make sure
that everyone extends...
...the greatest hospitality to one of
our most-favored American clients."
-Hope Cassidy.
-Exactly.
"She will be visiting tomorrow.
Please ensure
her transaction requests...
...are handled smoothly
and efficiently.
Best regards, Abdul Hamit."
It's in English.
Yes, but....
There you go.
Will they let you in without ID?
No. But I thought of that too.
We do a search for an image of him.
See?
All right, watch.
And now you just print it out.
Brilliant.
You're a genius.
Anyway...
...what's my fortune?
-Duck!
-No!
Hope, run! Run!
Where is it? Where is it?
Where is it?
Roxelena...
...it's okay. Listen. Listen to me.
I am so sorry, but we have to get out
of here. We have no time, all right?
Do you have somewhere
you can go until this is over?
-Yes.
-I want you to go, okay?
What you gonna do?
Fight back.
We sent the police to the apartment.
They did not find the body.
No sign of a struggle.
But he was there when I left.
Nothing. Like it never happened.
And where is Roxelena now?
I don't know.
-I told her to--
-Vanish.
Very convenient.
You know what?
I was scared...
...and I was concerned for her and
I wasn't thinking about my damn alibi.
Now, I'm sure you and your guys
out there can find her.
The airline has no record
of her working there.
If you could tell me her last name....
How many people do you pass in life
and you don't know their last name?
-Or any name at all?
-This woman could be your only hope.
You think I'm making
this whole thing up.
-Do you speak English?
-Yes.
My name's Hope Cassidy.
I believe Mr. Hamit said I was coming?
It's a pleasure to have you here.
-Simit?
-No, thank you.
Chai?
Mr. Hamit has spoken greatly
about you.
-Thank you.
-How may I help you?
-Here is my account number.
-Yes.
I would like to move all my money
into a new account...
...and purchase Turkish bonds
for security.
This, of course, is no problem.
How much would you like
to purchase?
It's all written down there.
Yes. Certainly, yes.
-Is there a problem? Abdul told me--
-No, no.
No problem.
But there will be a fee.
-Which I am more than happy to pay.
-Yes.
Of course.
And, you see, we may need
some form of identification.
Of course, yes, l--
I'm sorry. Could you please give that
to Mr. Hamit next time you see him?
Yes. Of course.
Now then,
should we start the paperwork?
-Absolutely.
-Yes.
I have your money. I'll trade you.
I really don't know
what you're talking about.
Fourteen million.
I'll trade for my life.
-That's it, no questions asked.
-I really don't know what you mean.
I either get my life back or
let the Russian arms dealers...
...know where it is and who took it.
-Arms dealers?
-Yeah. Not nice people.
Especially when it comes
to stolen money.
-You're not serious.
-I'm dead serious.
-You have to understand. I haven't--
-You took my life away.
-I thought that I was helping.
-Helping who?
I don't know. They said that
this wouldn't be dangerous.
Who said? Z.Z., who said?
Who is doing this?
I was in jail, this guy came and said he
was from the American Embassy.
He said, "Trust me. I'll turn
this nightmare of yours into a dream."
-That's what he told me.
-Okay, so they used you.
They used me.
Okay, we're in this together.
So please tell me who's behind this.
Okay, look, we'll make a change,
just come to the office.
My terms.
The Süleymaniye Mosque, 6 p.m.
Z.Z.
Look, I'm just here to make a deal.
You can have it all...
...I just want my li--
Oh, God. Oh, God, Z.Z.
Z.Z.
No, no!
I didn't do it, okay?
I didn't do it!
And now I'm here.
That was everyone you met?
Yes.
No one else who could
verify your story...
...vouch for you?
No.
So?
Yes?
So you believe me.
You believe that I'm Hope Cassidy.
I believe that you believe
you're Hope Cassidy.
-You've gotta be kidding me.
-Guardians!
-I cannot believe you!
Why have you done this to me?
You've kept me locked in here
for days.
And you haven't listened
to a word I've said.
-Let go of me! Oh, I hate you!
-There is no evidence...
...to support what you say. There's
no record that you're Hope Cassidy.
No, I explained that.
You had the knife
that killed Hope Cassidy.
No! That was not me!
That was Z.Z., okay?
I was trying to save her.
I'm Hope Cassidy!
Why won't you listen to me?
Someone has to know me!
Oh, no!
Please.
You have no proof
of any of your story.
No, I have proof.
The money. I can tell you where it is.
Does anyone else know where it is?
-No.
-Good.
It may be the only thing that will
buy you off the death penalty.
This is your last hope.
Hope.
Hope, sweetie, wake up.
You okay?
God. James.
Come here.
I can't believe it.
You're here.
-You're here.
-I'm here, Hope.
I've never been so happy to hear
someone say my name.
What are you doing here?
How did you even find me?
I've been here for days.
I looked at the hotel,
but you checked out.
I even looked at the morgue.
-You won't believe what's going on.
-I heard, they told me.
At the police station.
-They had me in--
-Jail, I know.
Once I was able to verify your identity,
they were all so embarrassed.
I made a quick, angry phone call
to the embassy...
...I had you out in seconds flat.
You don't remember any of this?
Some things. Little bits, I guess.
-Where are my clothes?
-Your clothes are trashed.
I ordered new ones,
they'll be here soon.
-Thank you.
-Anything else...
...we put in this.
-What the heck is that?
-It's my evil-eye bracelet.
It wards off bad luck.
I think you might wanna
check those batteries.
I can't wait to get out of this city
and go home.
First flight out tomorrow morning.
Oh, I can't believe this is almost over.
I'm so happy.
I gotta run over to the embassy
before it closes...
...to do some paperwork
before we leave.
-No, please don't go.
-Well, I'll be back in less than an hour.
You're gonna be fine,
nothing's gonna happen to you.
Police even have a guard
outside the door.
Tomorrow morning
we leave for Los Angeles. All right?
All right.
Trust me. I'll turn this nightmare
of yours into a dream.
I was in jail and--
This guy said he was from
the American Embassy.
He said, "Trust me, I'll turn this
nightmare of yours into a dream."
Okay. Okay.
Who are you? Who are you?
Come on, tell me who you are.
Who are you working for?
Hello, Hope.
Let him go.
-No.
-I said, let him go.
No!
Let's go.
You were in on this
from the beginning?
Who do you think gave Suzer
your recommendations?
You were good, but we had
to get them to hire you.
You set me up!
This all could have been so easy,
you know.
Easy? Easy for who?
You just had to
leave the money alone.
You stole my life.
People were trying to kill me.
Hey, we all had to make sacrifices.
I had to pretend I was in love with you.
There're some perks I am gonna miss.
That was the problem with you
from the start.
You never appreciated what you had.
-Why me?
-Why you? Because we could.
No parents, no friends, no life. No one
would miss you when you were gone.
Hey, you wanted adventure.
Well, you got it.
You could have
stolen the money yourself.
From Russian gunrunners?
We'd never live to see any of it.
No, we needed a patsy,
somebody expendable.
Hope!
Shit.
What?
Open the door!
Who are you?
I'm an intelligence officer for Interpol.
Computer Crimes Division.
We've been tracking
your boyfriend, James...
...whose real name is
David Thompson...
-...and Dr. Kavak for years.
-Kavak's involved too?
She's a cop gone bad.
The money.
I can tell you where it is.
-Does anyone else know where it is?
-No.
So, what do you want with me?
We left you alone too long.
It's not safe anymore.
-Not safe anymore?
-Time to bring you in.
So you bring me in,
and for the rest of my life I'm running...
...looking over my shoulder?
I don't think so.
You haven't got a choice.
Yes, I do.
They wanna go to the bank,
get the money?
I say we let them get it.
I had her. The bitch pulled me
down the stairs.
-No. No-- Hold on.
-No!
Take it easy.
Calm down, calm down.
Don't do anything stupid.
-Where are you taking me?
-I think you know where.
You're gonna kill me
after you get the money?
Oh, it's not that simple.
Once I get my money,
you're free to do whatever you want.
But as long as you're alive...
...I don't think those Russians
are gonna forget about you. Do you?
Kavak?
-Didn't know you made house calls.
-Bank opens in five. Let's go.
-And here I thought you were the boss.
-Come on.
Look, can I go to the bathroom?
-I've been sitting in a car all night.
-No. You stay in our sights.
I can cause quite a scene.
It's fine. I'll go with her.
Wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
Leave the door open.
You've taken everything else I have,
how about leaving me a bit of dignity?
All right.
Come on, we haven't got all day.
I'm coming. Hold on.
-Done?
-I'd just like to wash my hands.
Let's get the money.
Hi. I would like to go
to my safety-deposit box.
Yes, of course. Come with me.
-I'm sorry, ma'am, box holders only.
-Of course.
Don't worry, I just want this thing
to be over.
Here she is.
I drop the bag in the car
and then I'm walking. I'm done.
You do as we tell you.
We count the money first.
Get off of me!
Let me go!
Who the hell are you?
You took our money.
Get off of me!
Who has the money?
-You are?
-Hope Cassidy.
-And you are?
-Kelly Roos.
Kelly Roos.
It seems you took
a great deal of my money.
You can have it back.
-And then I let you go?
-Something like that.
You can keep the doctor
and her boy toy if you'd like.
It doesn't work that way.
Who would respect me?
How could I do business
if I was so generous?
I'll let you pick who goes first.
-No, look, we don't have to do this.
-Choose.
-We can talk about this.
-Choose!
-No, this doesn't have to happen!
Choose!
How the hell did you even find us?
Sometimes you just
have to have hope.
A lot of good it did her.
Captain...
...thank you for your help.
Anytime. You can ride
in the ambulance if you'd like.
I really should.
-Can I get up yet?
-Yes, you are safe.
It's not easy being dead.
The only way they wouldn't
come looking for you.
I was panicked this wouldn't work.
Come on, we haven't got all day.
Here, put this on.
You know...
...I was wondering.
-How did you find me at the hotel?
-We knew where you were at all times.
Hey, why do you think
I gave it to you?
So this whole thing was a setup
from the beginning.
I told you on the plane...
...nothing is ever
as it seems in Istanbul.
-You could have told me something.
-I did.
At the appropriate time.
Here you go.
New passport and new name.
You remembered.
And some money and clothes
to get you started.
So will it ever be safe
to go back to being me?
Not until we know how far-reaching
the organization is.
Even then....
That's all right. I was getting
a little tired of being me.
By the way...
...all of the money burned in the car
with Ivanakov...
...that was all the money, wasn't it?
Here I thought
we trusted each other.
I had to ask.
Do you think we can trust her?
We have to.
We may need her again.