ln July 1937
Japan started
the Marco Polo Bridge lncident
Beijing and Tianjin fell
one after another. Huabei was in danger
The Chinese nation's existence
was at stake
For the whole nation's interests
CPC joined hands with KMT once again
Red Army was recomposed into
KMT's 8th Route Army
Following the order of
CPC's Central Military Commission
l crossed the Yellow River
and rushed day and night
for the frontline against Japan
Between Henan and Hebei
is the Yellow River
while between Shandong and Shanxi
is Mt. Taihang
After we marched through Shanhaiguan
from Manchuria
the vast North China Plain
is right in front of us
As the Chinese saying goes
He who has conquered Taihang
will be invincible
Shanxi is right between
Mt. Taihang and the Yellow River
The goal for this army is to
capture northern China via Shanxi
How come the area and shape of Shanxi
are so much like those of Japan?
lt is more like the spine of China
Seizing Taihang is like
breaking the back of the Chinese
Chiang calls for
'resistance by burning the land'
Yours must be more meaningful
lf the land is burnt
what is there to fight for?
Defending the land is our main goal
Resistance is just
a way of achieving the goal
Excellent...
Sir, Zhu De is here
My uniform
My friend
Your Excellency Commander Yan
Zhu De is here to report for duty
By no means...
Please...
As your Party's declaration said
the whole Chinese nation
is being endangered
We've been anxiously
waiting for your coming
l'm sorry to say that
we're poorly equipped
We may not be of much help
to the war situation
Help yourself...
Get tea ready
But all my soldiers
vow to fight together with you
Resistance by defending the land
l hereby officially confirm to you that
CPC has made the resolution to
launch a campaign against the Japanese
Please give your comment
Pingxingguan is ideal for
setting an ambush
lt's the only route for
ltagaki troops to enter Shanxi
lt's the chance of a lifetime
l wonder how many of you
have got here in Shanxi?
The CPC and Mao Zedong are aware that
the Japanese army
is bearing down upon here
and ordered us to rush here
even before the recomposition
is finalized
Lin Biao's 1 15th and
He Long's 120th Divisions
are at the frontline now
Liu Bocheng's 129th Division
is on its way there
Together with HQs led by Peng Dehuai
we've got 32000 men here
Sir, tea is ready
Please Please...
Lin Biao, He Long, Liu Bocheng
Peng Dehuai and you
All the five red tigers are here
Shanxi is honored, so is 2nd Theater
and me myself too
We're flattered
But we really need your troops to
help Lin Biao
intercepting fleeing enemies
Look out!
Sure...
lt's really good
for setting an ambush here
Will they really pass through here?
Absolutely
They've got so many supplies and gear
They can't possibly fly over here
We 1 15th Division is put in charge
This is the first campaign
of our 8th Route Army
How should we beat them?
We must build up confidence
What if KMT troops don't cooperate?
We need their cooperation
But we can't count on them
We have to fight, even without them
Sir, here they are
lt is an ideal place for an ambush
But l wonder if you have
sufficient men and power
One enemy regiment overruns
one of our army groups
Your 1 15th Division is poorly equipped
How can you fight?
l personally appreciate your courage
Human factor is more important
lt's going to rain
What if you can't get there on time?
The main issue is
whether we can count on
your efficient support and cooperation
Please rest assured
l've mobilized my reserves
We'll attack the Japs from the north
to help you pinning them down
That... will be wonderful
Sir, HQ orders us to speed up
Captain Yes, sir!
Your company stays for rescue
Yes, sir! Follow me, men!
Stand up. Go!
Doc!
Stop...
Sir
we met resistance from the Chinese ahead
Get rid of them
Yes, sir
Charge!
Fire!
Sir
we've smashed a team of KMT army
March on
1 15th Division
is heading towards the location
Any ltagaki scouts are seen over there?
No, they are marching in a queue
No scouting or covering forces
The Japanese are still blindly arrogant
lt shows our timing is good
We've got to be cautious
Ask Lin Biao
to control the heights in the valley
and make sure our flanks are secured
02... come in
02, this is 01 , come in
02... this is 01 , come in
02... come in
Get away!
Get away
The Japanese has got into our ambush
Their vanguard
has walked out of the valley
Their supply vehicles
are all within the range
Go!
lt's up there
Sergeant...
Chinese army ambushing us? lmpossible!
They must be guerrillas. Wipe them out
Yan Xishan?
l know him the best
He is my
lmperial Military School classmate
He doesn't have the guts
Shall we ask for help
from our air forces?
No need
Sir, do please give it a thought
Ok, then
The enemy's bombing is fierce
Get our men down there to mix them up
Charge...!
The Japanese is taking Laoyemiao
That's a height
Tell Li Tianyou he mustn't lose it
Colonel!
Captain, reinforce the height
Go! Yes, sir!
Sir, Gao Guizi, Commander of 1 7th Army
ordered his men
to abandon their positions
Lin Biao's troops are still fighting
Their flanks are exposed
lt's too dangerous
What's to be done?
He isn't under my control
Shall we get our 71st Division to attack?
so as to cover Lin Biao's men?
ltagaki's reinforcement
is coming from the north
Yan's troops don't do anything
1 15th Division's flank is totally exposed
Lin Biao is prepared for that
He's deployed troops along Yimaling
to check their reinforcements
Ask him to finish the fight
and get out of there
Get the horses!
To Pingxingguan
We've got no ammunition
Neither do l
Let's go!
Charge bayonets!
Remove bullets
Charge!
What...?
Bayonet charge?
Who the hell are they?
They must be 8th Route Army
101 ... come in, 101
lt's their 1 1th charge now
We have to fight with bayonets
Hold it at all costs!
Give up! No harm!
Give up! No harm...!
Get out of here
Come here, he's still alive
Coming
Make sure to keep him alive
No!
Attention!
At ease!
Today, September 25, 1937
is a day that astonished the whole world
that will be recorded
into the history of China
Because we defeated
the most ferocious enemy
the ltagaki's troops
Who is this ltagaki?
He is one of the plotters
behind 9.18 lncident
He also made the last Qing emperor Puyi
emperor of the puppet state of Manchukuo
Down with ltagaki!
Down with Japanese lmperialism...!
You defeated the scoundrel today
This is the most severe setback
for the Japanese invaders since 1937
To date back further
it's their most severe setback
ever since
the First Sino-Japanese War in 1894
Your confidence and braveness
crushed the myth of
Japanese imperial army
Your willpower of iron
and spirit of sacrifice
declared to the world
the Chinese people and nation
can never be conquered
Long live the Chinese nation!
Long live the Chinese nation...
Long live 8th Route Army!
Another compliment
lt's a pity l can't take the credit
Now 8th Route Army stands firm in Shanxi
Commander-in-chief...
Comrade Rongzhen
Look
This is a Japanese military map
This is where we are, Nanru Village
But Yan's map is too simple
to mark the village
This map of China drawn by the Japanese
is more detailed and accurate
lt shows their conspiracy
existed long long ago
How is the result of the campaign?
Over 1000 enemy soldiers were killed
Our casualty is about the same
We've never had such kind of a fight
They're really tough
They were brain-washed by militarism
Any POWs?
We've checked it out, no POWs
Not a single one? No
Ren, can l interview Zhu De now?
l'm afraid not
Comrade Zhu De is now
in command of the battle
So he has no time for the time being
He never has time, always busy
When ever will l finish the biography?
Commander-in-chief
in common people's eyes
lt can best show
the truth of our people's army
Ren, you're really a politician
At such a critical moment
you two agreed to be
vice commanders of my 2nd Theater
l really appreciate your support
The fate of this nation is at stake
l have to
Mr. Chiang is afraid that the Japanese
would go all the way
to Sichuan through Shanxi
and outflank from the southwest
to take China
So the Xinkou Campaign is vital
lt can never be underestimated
We wish we could be of some help to you
Please... Please
Since we are Chinese armies
and we're all anti-Japanese
we should break away with the systems
and set up a united anti-Japan force
to fight together
Our armies will be mixed
into three routes
The east route will be headed by Zhu De
The middle route by Lihuang
And l'll take care of the west route
What do you think?
Ok, all forces of Central Army
along the east route
will also be given to Zhu De
lt applies to my Shanxi Army too
You two can take our men
on the middle and west routes
There's no problem with that
l only hope you can see
if there is anything good
about 8th Route Army
it is that flexible as we are
we can start guerrilla warfare
behind enemies
lt is also our fighting principle
and has been endorsed
by the Generalissimo
Of course...
The treasure of Jinci is not the temple
lt's the three fountains
lt's rather peculiar
Wherever originated
they are merged here
irrigating the vast farmland
in central Shanxi
So even three waters in Shanxi are united
Yes, united
To fight against the Japs
Damned! Dare you come down here?
ls that Liu Bocheng?
Judging from the taking off frequency
there must be a Japanese airbase here
Find it and blow it up
Very good!
We don't know
how to deal with air bombings
Chen Xilian blew up their entire airbase
120th Division led by He Long
also had a marvelous ambush at Yanmenguan
and cut off the enemy's supply
Wei Lihuang will have
an easier time guarding Xinkou
Dare you come up here?
Where are your planes?
Are they hatching now?
Chairman Mao believes
the recovery victory is temporary
Taiyuan will be lost soon
Our army's principle
is still the guerilla warfare
Yan and Chiang have the same idea
Both want to stick to Taiyuan
and ask us for help
Chiang's passive recovery
will fail for sure
But Yan's still fighting against the Japs
we must help him
Here is my idea
Our main force will attack the Japs' rear
to support KMT's recovery efforts
As Chairman Mao said
we'll also set up four bases
in northeastern, southeastern
southwestern and
the border area of Shanxi
Some family members
of most of these women
have died at the front
And their Save-the-nation
Committee organizes
the villagers to make shoes
for the Red Army soldiers
Which kind of flower is it?
They are lotus flowers
But there is only one usually
how come there is two?
She said there should be only one flower
instead of two
They are twin-lotus-flowers
ln the Chinese folk culture
the twin-lotus-flowers
are a symbol of love
Of love?
She made the pads
for her husband
But he's gone to the front
only 3 days after their wedding
Did he go willingly or was he forced to?
l took him there myself
He himself demanded to go to the front
lt's no wonder
All his family except himself
were killed by the Japs
Our victory at Pingxingguan
crushed invaders' morale
and stimulated that of all the Chinese
The Resistance movement's
spreading across the country
Japan sent even more
armed forces to China
to attack Taiyuan
a strategic city in North China
At Yanmenguan and Niangziguan
the two sides are engaged
in vehement fights
Guys, we'll die sooner or later
Killed by Japs
we are at least heroic martyrs
Guys, charge!
Charge!
Please send reinforcements right now
Hello...
Taiyuan is lost...
Commander He...
More enemies are coming
lt's the guarding gate of Taiyuan
Your One-armed Colonel
Get him up there
Not a single enemy can be let go
Yes, sir
Colonel...
He's up there already
Sir
Now you've seen for yourselves
your Brigadier has died for the country
l'll be taking his place now
We must get Height 1 300 back
lf someone backs off just one step
my pistol will not tolerate
Should l back off
everyone of you can shoot me
Tommy gun!
No, you can't go up there
You can't get through
Right, you can't get through
Please wait, sir!
We'll go
l'll fight to death together with you
Yes, sir
Tell Colonel to retreat
Sir, we're ordered to retreat
What? What did you say?
Niangziguan was lost
Why?
This is the latest intelligence
on the Japs
They moved forward so fast that
even before Yan's
2nd defense line was formed
they've broken through
Dispatch work groups
to all the counties in Shanxi
to set up anti-Japanese
democratic regimes
and train local guerilla teams
just like hens laying eggs
by making hen roosts everywhere
Fu Zuoyi is
a well-known defending general
He won't give up Taiyuan easily
l've persuaded him not to be
too particular about
the loss of one or two cities
We are good at guerilla warfare
But they are not so flexible
Our HQs will move further south
to be prepared for the loss of Taiyuan
Sir, telegram from the Generalissimo
Move to the south?
People can move, what about properties?
No Parties or Armies can be counted on
We have to rely upon ourselves
l will live or die with the city
We can't afford to lose Taiyuan
lf the city is lost
so will the province be
Sir. Doihara's division
is rushing here from the east
while Tojo Hideki
is coming down from the north
Taiyuan is about to fall really soon
Maybe we should have done as Zhu De said
ln Shanxi and North China
the frontal warfare by KMT is over now
Self-dependent mountain guerilla warfare
by CPC will play major roles in the War
From the telegram by Chairman Mao
The Situation and Our Tasks
After the Loss of Taiyuan
Our experiences so far show that
Chinese armies are still
no match for the Japanese
Sir, an unknown cadre is here to see you
He mentioned a suicide team
Just outside
Suicide Team! Get him here
Yes, sir Wait, l'll go and see him
l'm here to see Commander Zhu
l am Zhu De
Commander-in-chief Zhu!
l'm Bo Yibo, a CPC member
l know who you are
Before l left Yan'an, Mao mentioned you
saying you're young and talented
You set up a Suicide Team
and an anti-Japanese base
in the Wutai Mountains
You're really something
l'm embarrassed
This is the first time l met you
You're not what l expected
You look just like an ordinary farmer
Peng said our 3 divisions will go
to the Japs' rear area
l wonder what my suicide team
is supposed to do
You'd better evacuate from Wutai
lt's not easy for you to set up the team
lt's led by CPC
but it's also a part of Yan's troops
They're all youngsters from Shanxi
We must make the best use of them
Ok then
take your team to southern Shanxi
They are all from Shanxi
They know how to stimulate
the local people
The North Bureau of CPC
Command of 2nd Theater
and Office of 8th Route Army need
at least 3 to 4 days
to evacuate from Linfen
We decided that you take 2 companies
to check southbound enemies on your way
The Guard has only 3 companies
l'll take just one with me
One company is not enough
With two you can have two defending lines
But... They're more important to you
You take two companies
we're fine with just one
and won't be exposed so easily
Besides, the three companies
will meet in a few days anyway
l'll go right now Ok
You take care
Zhu, l've never heard such a thing as
Commander-in-chief has no troops
and vice chief of staff's striking
in the battlefield
Get ready and set out now
Guo Yes, sir
Hongdong County men reported that
the Guangshengshang Temple in Huoshan
houses a copy of 'Dazang Sutra'
Tell Bo Yibo right now to have it
remove to a safer place
Yes, sir
Commander
Commander Zhu
Xiaoping, Bocheng, how come you're here?
386th Brigade will stay with HQs
lt's too dangerous
without guarding troops
Chen Geng with 386th Brigade
is here to report for duty
No need, the harder you strike out there
the safer we will be here
Biaolishan River, Shanxi
lt's easy to defend
and hard to attack here
l don't think so
This Fenhe River Valley is in front of us
lf we march along the valley
once we're in the Taihang
who can stop us?
Our capturing Taiyuan
shows their defending
has crashed thoroughly
They are fleeing to southern Shanxi
to a small town called Linfen
We can wipe them out right there
The communists are guerilla guys
They won't stay inside the town
The KMT army has well been defeated
So our focus is to eliminate
CPC's 8th Route Army
l'll go and capture Zhu De alive
China's population is 450 million
and 80% are farmers
So far, none of the farmers
has said to the world
what he wants to say
But you have become Commander-in-chief
of 8th Route Army
ln our 8th Route Army
Peng Dehuai and Zuo Quan
are also guerrilla experts
ln our 8th Route Army
Peng Dehuai and Zuo Quan
are also guerrilla experts
But it has been four days
Zuo Quan hasn't come back
from the battlefield yet
But it has been four days
Zuo Quan hasn't come back
from the battlefield yet
Please
Where are our 3 divisions now?
Zuo Quan is back
Really? That's great!
Well, l'll take you to Zuo Quan
So you won't always interview me
Please
We have no photo studios here
See handprints of our daughter Beibei
My dear wife. Got your letter
Although you are not able to
take a picture of our daughter
l feel satisfied to see her handprints
Back from the 4 days and 3 nights battle
the first thing l did was to write to you
lf l died in the battle
l wouldn't have any regret
for all my life except that
l've never seen our daughter
and done nothing for her
as a father
So please kiss her more since l can't
Hi, Commander-in-chief Hi
Ms. Smedley, Ms Zhang interprets
Commander-in-chief
Peng Dehuai's troops have started out
We shall leave at once
What about me?
You'll be sent to Yan'an as arranged
l wouldn't go anywhere
lt's hard for a woman like you on the way
l didn't want to be a woman
God made me one!
Ms. Smedley
l hope you obey the orders
Your biography will be named
'The Great Path'
lt's not that great
Actually it's a tortuous path
just like this one under our feet
Commander-in-chief of 8th Route Army
is seeing off a foreign female journalist
l'd say it's the son of Chinese peasants
seeing off the daughter
of an American miner
Can l bid farewell to you
as Americans do?
We both are wearing uniforms
of 8th Route Army
and armbands too
So we should bid farewell as soldiers do
l love 8th Route Army
The rear guard is fighting with
over 1000 enemy soldiers
Great
Hold them down till dusk
The more are attracted to us
the safer HQs will be
Got it
The KMT men crossed the Yellow River
Yan Xishan retreated to Qiulin, Shanxi
Wei Lihuang to Luoyang, Henan
We won't
We'll be guerillas on Mt. Taihang
Planes are coming, go and hide
Yes, sir
Got it
They bombarded Guzhen in Qinshui
Guzhen?
Leave here
Follow up
He is really a prophet
lf he said they won't bomb, they won't
lf he said they will, and here they are
He knows their minds too well
The town they're bombing
is also called Guzhen
lt shows their real target is us
They bombed the wrong place
so they'll come back
Follow up
He's really smart
Hurry up
Lie up
We knew 104th Brigade has got into
the heart of 8th Route Army's base
The Japanese national flag is flicking
on the roof of their HQs
l can imagine
you're reading my telegram
on Zhu De's chair
We are exited about and jealous of this
Where is Zhu De now?
Sir, we've monitored
radio signals near here
lt must be Zhu De...
lt must be Zhu De? Good
Set out now
Right turn! Eyes front!
Guo Yes, sir
Everyone will be given a bayonet, rifle
Have they got them?
Yes, sir Where's mine?
Set out! Yes, sir
Hurry up
Lie up
Load
Bandits, you Japanese bandits
Guo Yes, sir
Telegraph to Liu and Deng
to come and rescue local people
Wait. No telegraphing
They've decoded our telegram
so they're here so soon
You Japanese bandits...! Let me out!
Those can tell where their radio is
can be released
Yes, sir
Listen carefully
lf you tell us where their radio is
l'll let you out
Go and send it now!
What are you waiting for?
Turn it on, l'll talk to Liu and Deng
l really mean talk, uncoded
My classmate...
l want to...
What?
What did you say?
Commissar Deng
HQ's talking, l can't understand
to my classmate at Frunze
lt's Zuo Quan
l'm your classmate
at Sun Yat-sen University
ls Commander-in-chief safe now?
l'm your classmate at Frunze
Got it
Ye's 772nd Regiment is close to you...
Sir
They're talking in an unknown language
not Chinese
What?
l'll send Ye right now to close them in
lt sounds like Russian
Yes, it is Russian
l wish l had
a Russian Japanese dictionary
You Japanese bandits!
Hurry up
You bandits
Let's go
Retreat
Ye Chenghuan's here
Retreat...
Spear Team is here to report for duty
Ok, go and rescue them Yes, sir
No, retreat
Charge
How about the local folks?
They're safe now
But Commander Ye was killed
Go get them!
Go get them now!
Please
Vice Commander-in-chief
The Japs wanted to drive us
across the River
And we're having the meeting
in their rear area
Congratulations to you
Let me introduce them to you
Vice Commander of 129th Division
Xu Xiangqian
Commander-in-chief of Red 4th Army
We fought but never met each other
We now met each other
and will never fight
No discord, no concord
Commander-in-chief Zhu
l'm Zhu Huaibing
l hope you won't be
as stingy as Yan Xishan
Better show us
some secrets for resistance
Mao's 'On Protracted War' is the secret
Our enemy now is more powerful
but we've got more people
China is always
on the side of righteousness
As long as we count on the local people
and adopt the right way of fighting
we'll get them into stalemate
depleting their forces
and eventually win over Japan
Excellent
lt sounds like the best way
for the time being
Mao Zedong's 'On Protracted War'
lsn't that guerilla thing?
We're all armymen
No military theory
takes guerilla as tactics
Protracted war is not merely
a guerilla thing
But to raise it to a strategical level
is really something new
l'm a veteran armyman
l never care about
the origin of a certain fighting method
What do you care then?
l care if it works or not
lf it works, it is a good one
Salute!
This is Cui, head of local guerrillas
What military school are you from?
Sir, l have never studied
l like 'Generals of the Yang's'
l've enjoyed playing with spears
When the Japs came
l just do as what l played
to fight with the devils, finished
'Generals of the Yang's'?
you militia can fight with the devils?
lf you civilians can fight
what are we armymen supposed to do?
lf all the ordinary people can fight
can the Japs stay here long?
Cui, just show them some of your trophies
Yes, sir
Even more than
we professionals have captured
That's true
Guerilla
lt really has a tactic of wasps
They only sting
the stupid horse of Japanese army
its ass, its ears
and even its penis
Ok, you can pick up trophies for your own
They're gifts from Commander Zhu for you
This is a Japanese sword
That's a 38' rifle
Commander-in-chief Wei
Do you know what l want most?
A group of commissars from 8th Route Army
Ok
The scrap iron
is donated by the local people
Some women and kids even carried it here
lt's really hard for them
Those are from troops to be repaired
Some are from 129th Division
Good...
We captured these mortars
at the Xiangtangpu Campaign
They're still in good condition
Can we make them?
No problem, we've got engineers
old workers and students from Beijing
No problem at all
Wonderful
Let's invite Commander-in-chief
to give us a speech
Thanks, comrades
l'd like to thank you
on behalf of all the soldiers
With your wisdom and labor
with the local people as our backing
we'll win the people's war for sure
You know lyrics of 'Song of Guerillas'?
No guns, no cannons
Our enemy will make for us
We'll not only take what they made
but also make them ourselves
To achieve the final victory
spears and swords are not enough
landmines and grenades are not enough
we have to make guns and cannons
even planes and warships
Bravo!
Lieutenant General!
We actually first met each other
at a parade of 8th Division, is that so?
Yes, l was Commander of 32nd Company
of 16th Regiment of 8th Division
l was a Captain
Only two years passed
and you are a lieutenant general
This is peerless in the lmperial Army
The credit goes to His Majesty Mikado
l'm very honored to have you
Senior General Hisaichi here
l'd like to express our gratitude
and wish Abe a sweeping victory
Thanks
Please prove that
you're the pride of Japan
l understand
This is my super honor
The honeymoon between KMT and CPC
against us is over
This is very helpful to lmperial Army
Abe is about to attack
Nie Rongzhen's troops
l wish you success
Cheers Cheers...
At 6th Session of 6th Conference of CPC
Comrade Mao Zedong's leadership
in the Party
has been reaffirmed
The Central Committee praised
8th Route Army
for its resistance against Japan
Come on it and sit
The session also made strategic plans
of gaining the leadership of resistance
Comrades
the Committee ordered
to arouse the local people
and start up guerilla wars
against the Japs
A brand new phase is about to come
CPC must bear the whole country in mind
Mao Zedong asked
the whole Party to be alert
United front doesn't mean solidarity only
Struggle is equally important
We must be ready for
KMT's anti-Communist attacks
Hidenori Abe of Japanese army in Mongolia
has been transferred to Hebei
He's the mountain warfare expert
Stop
Buried there are 500 of our soldiers
who were ambushed and killed
in an encounter
Cremate the bodies
and take the ashes with us
The guerilla thing of Zhu and Mao
won't work with me
l'll deal with you the same way
as they deal with us
You just swallow the bait
Get rid of him
Only days ago he got promoted
Now he's attacking the heart of our base
He's really ambitious
The Japs got assistance
Zhu Huaibing's attacking our base
in northern Hebei
Sun Chu's attacking our Suicide Team
in southern Shanxi
Yan Xishan befriended the Japs
A Japanese called Kawada Daisaku
was a senior staff officer
in Guandong Army
Now he is head of
Shanxi lndustry Co., Ltd
He is colluding closely with Yan
Chiang's also manipulating forces
to attack our bases in Yan'an
We're under attack from both sides
Go and rest early
Right
Ok, you too
Who is this?
Commander-in-chief
lt's frozen
Warm it up
Where are you from? Wutai
Sorry, Yan Xishan is also from there
What's there to be sorry for?
Xu Xiangqian
Vice Commander of 129th Division
is also from that place
l'm no match to him
When did you join the army?
Just two months ago
At Nanru Village
Yes, when our HQs were in our village
Cold?
Better now?
Go and run for awhile
No, l have to stand guard
l'll do it for you
Go ahead
Horses are marching along the mountains
ln October it is snowing on the mountains
Soldiers are thinly clad
They eliminate the Japs day and night
We can't wait for them to shoot at us
can we?
They're not Japanese after all
We must be patient now
and won't shoot before they do
Zhu Huaibing is here
Show him in
Please
Commander Zhu, please sit down
l'm not here for no reasons
l'm here for getting Jinzhou back
We're also fighting the Japs at the order
of the Generalissimo
We never borrowed this place from anyone
How can we return it?
l'm also following the orders of Chiang
to combine military
and governmental systems
l can't give away my territory
l have to get it back
Good
30 kms away is the Japanese occupied area
lf you resolve to get it back
we'll assist you at all costs
This place used to belong to 97th Army
l'll do anything to get it back
For the sake of
overall resistance situation
you'd better do anything
that'll please the Japs
Save the crap
There're only two options for you now
To leave
or to fight
We'll never leave our resistance base
To fight is your choice then?
Should someone insist
l'll be with him to the very end
Aren't you afraid that
your United Front policy will be wrecked?
Eliminating those national traitors
our United Front policy
can be better carried out
l'll see you on the battlefield
Stop
What do you want?
You were talking to
Vice Commander of 2nd Theater
also Commander of East Route Army
your direct superior
You don't even know basic army protocols
Aren't ashamed of yourself?
Even a pawn dares to checkmate
Because it is backed up by its king
Tell His Excellency Hisaichi
l've lured Nie Rongzhen's men
to Huangtuling
Please urge 26th, 1 10th Divisions
and 8th Brigade to rush there
and eliminate them
We can't afford to lose the chance
Sir
we captured a Communist spy
That's unusual
Sir
l'm Miki Kimura, a private with
3rd Squad of 2nd Platoon
under Captain Tsujimura
Nonsense!
Tsujimura's troops died for our country
No, all of the POWs joined the League
of Antiwar of Japanese Army Soldiers
But l insisted to come back
You're a real armyman
Do you want to go back to your platoon?
l...
Speak out
l want to go home
Home?
Where are you from?
A small village at the foot of Mt. Fuji
You came here just to go back home
Ok, you'll be gratified so that
our hero can propagate
patriotism back home
Thank you, sir
l'll leave the damned Mt Taihang at last
Stop
What did you say?
My home is at the foot of Mt. Fuji
Why come to Mt. Taihang in China?
No, l...
Ok
l'll pardon you for your baby act
and send you home for family reunion
Thank you, sir
l mean your bone ashes will be taken back
Your family will be given
special treatment
since you'll be in the roll of honor
No, sir
Take him away Yes, sir
Lieutenant General...
8th Route Army spared me
but the lmperial Army won't
Your Majesty, the lmperial Army is doomed
This war is abosolutely wrong
it makes no sense
Mom
Why?
Why is that?
As a Japanese
edified by imperialism for so many years
How come in just a few days
you've been brainwashed by
Communist propaganda?
Why the hell is that?
Emergent telegram from Chiang
Read it
We are ordered to retreat
to east of Bai-Jin
Major KMT forces are moving towards us
ls Chiang helping the Japs
or the Japs helping Chiang?
This isn't an ordinary military struggle
Defeating Abe
can stimulate the morale of the Chinese
Defeating KMT's anti-Communist troops
will force Yan Xishan to hang on
Chiang's got a merit
lf you win, he will learn the lesson
We're not artists after all
Chairman Mao's theory of justification
is the art of struggle
We'll never shoot first
But if he does
we won't let him go easily
Frictions... always frictions
Get rid of him once all
then he won't bother us anymore
Counterattacking Zhu Huaibing
is a political fight
Commissar Deng'll be in charge
lt's a go!
Counterattack now!
We've besieged
Zhu Huaibing's army command
What shall we do with him?
First, don't kill him
Second, don't capture him
Third, escort him out of our base
Violators will be executed
Fourth, make it clear to everyone
No retaliation what so ever
Violators will be executed
Halt!
Left and right turn!
Dress left and right, dress!
Eyes front!
Sir, under orders of
Vice Commander-in-chief Zhu
we're here to escort you out
You're Cui...
Cui Erdan
Director, Commander Cui
l'm honored...
Salute!
Sir, we failed to crush the Suicide Team
Wei Lihuang didn't help at all
A letter from Mao Zedong
Read it
lt's his personal letter
He hopes the conflict in Shanxi
be resolved peacefully
CPC sincerely wants to
fight against the Japs
not here to expand their domain
What about the telegram from the Japs?
Keep it
lf the resistance fails
Shanxi'll belong to the Japs
lf we win, it'll be taken by KMT
Chiang, the Communists, Japan
they're all troublesome
l'm dancing on three eggs
None of them can be broken
Really tough
My friend
Chiang appointed me
to be the chief negotiator
the most important reason is that
he thinks we are personal friends
But l told him the Communists
care nothing about personal friendship
No...
we are not heartless and ungrateful
l like to be direct
Now the justice is on your side
l have to beg you not to
let me go back empty-handed
At least some sort of fruit
l know you're telling the truth
l'll be equally sincere
The map
ls this map of garrisons
of both sides accurate?
Very accurate
The road from Linfen and Tunliu
all the way to Changzhi
Pingshun and Cixian
will be our boundary
Please say it again
Along Linfen, Tunliu, Changzhi, Pingshun
and Cixian, we can draw a line
all our men south of it
will be withdrawn to its north
You said all of your troops?
Exactly
You won't even keep a bridgehead?
Not a single one
And you're asking for?
Only one thing
Don't overstep it to pick quarrels
Resistance is more important
My friend
so now our negotiation is finished?
Finished
Do you mean it?
l mean it
Commander-in-chief
Zhu De is a victor
how come he gives away his territory?
He's benevolent and uprighteous
Telegram from Nie Rongzhen Ok
Local farmers at Huangtuling said
a Japanese general was spotted over there
Something big
lt's so nice of the local people
Our way is to rely on the people
This advantage can never be copied
by our rivals
Remind Nie Rongzhen
to use all his men and power as well
They've got captured mortars
and what HQs sent them, enough
107... it's a big fish
107 roger
The guy dares to stare at me
Get rid of him
Front left, 793 Height
Front left
793 Height is 8th Route Army's command
Fire! Yes, sir!
Get ready!
Sir, we're all set
OK
All mortars, get ready, fire!
East...
'Asahi Shinbun': The Flower of
a General Withered on Mt. Taihang
May, 1940
l went back to Yan'an as ordered
Chairman Mao mentioned
a stubborn old man in ancient times
who removed Taihang
saying Commander-in-chief Zhu
is doing the same
l'm not that capable
Since September 1937
when we crossed the Yellow River
2 years and 8 months have passed
We've annihilated
1 30,000 Japanese soldiers
while our own army has been expanding
and has created a situation of stalemate
in North China
What are the secrets?
First, we relied on
Mao's military strategy thoughts
Second, we relied on
3 divisions of 8th Route Army
Third, we relied on
the local people of Mt. Taihang
Chairman Mao also expected you to
go back
for the 7th National Party Congress
and to take care of
national military work in Yan'an
l miss...
l miss Mt.Taihang very much
Half of my life l'd been engaged in wars
but all civil wars
only to fight against invaders
in the last two years
lt's the responsibility of
a veteran soldier to our nation