I've wasted a lot of my time
looking for you
It's strange, how you're the one
who comes to me
So, you're ready to tell me
all that happened, right?
If the same
thing happened to you...
You might not ever
want to see anyone again.
Are we almost there yet?
This stuff is heavy and you
won't let us use the elevator
What's the big deal anyway?
Will you just stop complaining!
It's damn annoying!
Damn it!
We were doing fine playing
in Bangkok
But no, we had to change the
scenery
Who's idea anyway?
Mine
I found a better paying place
for you
What else do you want?
In Bangkok better musicians
will just eat us alive.
Isn't this place here close to
where you live?
Why don't you go sleep
at your place
so we have more space here.
That's none
of your damn business.
Come on guys
We'll play cards and in a couple
of hours it'll be morning.
Hey!
What's the matter with you?
Go to the bathroom
if you need to take a piss.
Totally insane!
Hey, What's that you're
staring at?
See that piece of cloth?
Did you see it when we came in?
I don't know
Didn't notice it...
But I didn't
You bastard!
Always trying to scare me.
Hey! I didn't see it either
This is the first I've seen it.
Hey! What the hell!
Hey! What the hell is wrong
with all of you
Just this and you all look as white as
boiled chicken.
You asshole!
This is your idea of a joke?
Don't you dare!
Don't!
I'm serious!
Boy! How are you?
What are you holding me
down for?
If you don't quit it,
I'll get serious.
Where the hell did Kob go?
Don't know
what's wrong with him
Just left one after the other.
Why is it so hot in here?
Who the hell turned off
the air conditioner?
Noone did
Uan, what's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing
Who took this down?
If we don't put it back,
we won't hear the end of it
Hyai, put it back.
Why me?
Just do it.
Can't a friend ask you
to do something
Hey! If you can't do it then don't.
I'll do it myself
What the hell is wrong with you!
Hyai, where are you going?
Hey! Hyai!
Damn you!
Now, I have to do it
Uan, What's wrong?
Hello?
Pim, don't do anything
Just quickly come downstairs.
Wait
Hello
Nui, let's go
Nui... Wake up
Nui...
Nui, let's get out of here...
Nui
You all saw it, right?
Boy!
You're going to be Okay
Help!
Boy!
I think it was more of an accident...
What do you think?
Hey, what are you so afraid of?
That woman
Pim, Have you called his home?
Pim...
Pim
Did you call?
I called but noone answered.
I want to go home
And what about Boy?
You're going to just leave him?
He's dead!
But he's your friend, man
But I'm going home
I thought you said
you didn't want to go home
Didn't you say that your home
was worse than prison
So, how come now
you want to go home?
I don't know
But right now I want to go home
I also want to go home
My name's Tawan,
I've been here for so long
I can't find my way back home
Take me back home with you.
What the hell?
We don't live at the same house.
That's alright
I want to stay with you.
Crazy!
It's Okay, I'll have
someone else take me home.
Wait. Well, where do you live?
Here, this is my home.
Here, let me see.
Is it the same?
Who's the woman in the picture?
Oh! That's my sister Saeng Daow
She works in the hotel
Don't know what she does
She goes upstairs
with men for hours.
It took days before they found
her body hidden under the bed
but without her head.
Did they catch the person
that murdered her?
Hey Wait, forget about that now
So, where's her head?
He cut off her head and tied her hair
to the air condition vent.
And how did they find her head?
You dumbass
So smart on everything else
They found it
the same way you did.
Get away!
Don't come near me!
Get the fuck away from me!
I said don't come near me!
Stay away from me!
Put the gun down
Kob
Kob don't!
Stop shooting!
Kob put the gun down first
Kob!
What the fuck is wrong
with you!
Don't you leave me!
Let me go!
I don't want to die!
I want to go home!
Go home!
Let go!
Kob!
Hurry!
Did all of you normally do drugs?
No
Really?
But from what
you're telling me now
it's completely opposite to the
police report
The hallucinations
could've come from this.
The police found it in your friend's
pants after you all took off.
Anything?
Noone knows of anybody
by the name Tawan
Noone by that name was ever
on the patient list either
And what about the dead body
that was found in the hotel?
Everyone claims that they've
never heard of this
and of the headless body ever
entering this hospital at all.
We're talking about a dead
person here, not a patient
Noone here knows.
Damn it!
Who the hell
do you want us to ask?
I don't know
what her name was
She had no relatives or friends
So, we just cremated her
even though they haven't
found her head.
Did the hotel claim
any responsibility for this?
Noone wanted to talk about it
After the cremation,
everyone just went silent
They didn't even
bring back her head
So, it's become a curse
that anyone who sees her.
Will either die without reason
or go completely insane
like Saem.
So, there was someone
who saw her like we did?
Saem
Saem, come out here
Saem was the one
who took her head
out from the air condition vent
From then on, he has seen her
face everynight while asleep
He didn't dare fall asleep
until I took the curse off him.
How's that?
He had to sleep in the coffin with
a person who died a violent death
every night before midnight
for 7 days
with my help
will release the curse.
Does this mean that all 4
of us must do the same?
And what about the lady
behind you?
Won't she also join you?
Behind us?
Who?
There's only the 4 of us
Hey! Aren't you like blind?
No wonder Saem didn't want
to greet you
It's because she also came
with you...
You see, I've never heard of
anything like this before
But if there really has been
a murder committed
and even
the Buddhist priest knows
about it then so does the police
Manoon, I want all the details
on the prostitution
murder case immediately.
On that day
the Buddhist told me to stay
inside the temple church
while the rest set out finding
those dead coffins
before their time runs out.
What happens when it becomes
after midnight?
Hyai, What the hell
are you looking at?
Did you notice
All the cars are blinking their
head lights at us.
I blink in return but then they
honk their horn at me.
There! There's another one.
Damn it!
What is it with these damn
dead coffins?
So damn hard to find
Are we going to survive this?
Shut your fucking mouth!
Damn!
That's it
Can I not go?
I want to go home
Just drop me off at home,
alright pal?
Damn!
What the hell is your problem?
Pleasel'm asking you
Here, turn here
My house is just here.
Aren't you afraid to die anymore?
I'll be safer at home
The most I'll get is a good beating
At least my father won't kill me
Turn hereTurn here
Stop. Stop right here.
You don't believe in this
curse, right?
If I do, then what?
I'll have to sleep inside a coffin
like that crazy guy?
Right, you guys go ahead
We'll see what happens
tomorrow See ya!
Hey!
Wait! Hyai!
Nui... Forget about him
We can look for it by ourselves.
Where is everyone
Ma! I'm home!
Hey, little one
Did Aunty spank you again
Sir, there's only 2 coffins
Is there maybe just one more?
You got two for one damn
bottle of whisky
What else do you want?
Why don't you die,
then you'll have another one
Hey! Don't have to be rude.
Calm down, man
It's better than nothing.
Gets two and complains
We've got to hurry back
or we won't make it on time.
It's already past midnight
The Buddhist priest said
the ritual won't work
That's not true
He's lying to us
It's hard enough finding
the coffins
he has to do the ritual
What have I done wrong?
Why do I have to wait for death?
Uan, when it's time
we all must die
There has to be another way
Another way?
What other way?
Anyway I'm going to die
Even the Buddhist priest
can't help me.
That ghost will break my neck
You too, she don't let you servive.
We get the curse,
all we get the curse.
Finally, all of us can not servive.
Uan, that's enough
Where's Hyai?
We can't leave him alone.
What's wrong Nui
Hurry up.
Hyai!
No more!
Let me go!
Help!
Help me!
Don't come near me!
Wake up
Is this the wrong house?
No, I remember the mailbox.
Alright, then let's go in.
Hey! I'm not going in
I'll wait in the car
It might get stolen.
How the hell is it going to
get stolen
We'll be right out
We'll just drag Hyai out to
sleep at the temple...
It's safer.
I still want to wait here.
That's okay Nui
Let him wait.
I can guess that it was suicide
Your friend had problems
at home.
Before we left his house
his parents came back
We didn't know
how to explain it to them
They wouldn't listen
They just kept blaming us
And where did you go
all that night?
That night we decided
to go back to the temple
But Uan
Uan had this stupid idea.
This is the safest place.
Aren't you going to keep it
for the ritual.
Let's just get past tonight
lt'll be kind of like being reborn
Don't think of me in a bad way
I'm asking you
Nui
What?
Close the coffin for me.
Okay.
Uan, wake up.
Uan.
The reason for his death.
We believe it to be caused by
lack of oxygen
But what do you expect from
someone stupid enough
to sleep in a coffin with
the lid closed
But actually he didn't close
it all the way
He left an opening
for air to breathe.
There's only the two of us left.
Pim, would you like to meet
Saeng Daow?
How? This is not a living
human being.
Are we just going to wait for her
to come to us?
But where can we find her?
We'll start from the place
where she was murdered.
He cut off her head and tied her
hair to the air condition vent.
Did you see anything strange?
No, none at all.
Here, that's all that is left
Oh, there is one thing that
you should know
Saeng Daow was pregnant
when she died.
The letter that the hotel
employee gave us
was written by Saeng Daow
but was never sent
We decided to go to the address
that was on the front of
the envelope
and deliver that letter
hoping that it might
release her from this pain
and suffering she is in.
Who let you in?
I'm sorry
Excuse me Ma'am
Ma'amThe name on this letter
is addressed to you, right?
It's a letter from Saeng Daow.
Saeng Daow
Saeng Daow my child
Saeng Daow ran away
from home a long time ago
I never received any news
from her
I didn't know where to find her
Her father died
when she was just a child
I raised her with the money
from my new husband.
Who's the girl standing
next to Saeng Daow?
Oh, that's Tawan
My other daughter
Saeng Daow loved her sister
very much
They went everywhere together,
never were separated
Tawan was close to her sister,
she cried wanting to go too
Saeng Daow just ran away
and didn't tell anyone
She left her sister even though
they've never been apart
Tawan must've been really lonely.
And what happened to Tawan?
Tawan would just keep herself
in the room
Everytime I saw her
she would be sleeping here
I never thought that one day
she wouldn't wake up
Who's in the next room?
That's just my husband
He's probably hungry
Go on
It's getting dark, I think the
both of you should be going
It's dangerous driving back
at night
Go on now
Go on
It's nothing
Go, go, go, go
And don't come back
I'm sorry Saeng Daow.
So, we still don't know
anything, right?
Why is Saeng Daow
so angry at us?
It might not have anything
to do with us at all
She probably just doesn't like us.
And wants to kill us
because she's crazy
So, what now?
You want to go back and sleep
in the coffin?
So, I can die the same way Uan did?
No, thanks
We'll just let the Buddhist do
the ritual for us first
It might work.
Don't you want to know more
about Saeng Daow?
The more we know
the faster we die
Oh... Did you see anything
over at her house?
Like what?
Like under the bed?
Sa... SaSa
Saeng Daow
You've wasted a lot of time already
Will you please tell me something
I can put in my report?
Like in the accident
Did anything peculiar happen?
I really can't remember much of it
Everything seems to be a blur.
Pim...
Where are you?
Come out of there...
Pim...
It's dangerous...
Come out of there, Pim.
Pim...
I don't know
what else to ask you
All your responses just end up
back on the same story
It's because of a ghost
Alright then,
what about your friend?
Where is he?
We had a difference of opinions...
He thought that the Buddhist
priest would be able to release him
from the curse by performing
the ritual
So, he went back to the temple to
try the ritual one more time.
What about you?
Don't you think of doing
the same?
If I did I probably wouldn't be
here now telling you about it.
Because from then on,
Nui just disappeared.
To this day, I still can't find him.
Your story is quite unbelievable
It's creepier than any book
I've read
But your characters seem to
have the same names as mine
I'll tell you what
I'll tell you a story of my own
I had a suspect here once,
waiting for interrogation
He was a psycho
We believed he killed people
as a sacrificial offering
What ever that is
Later that night,
he tore his clothes off
and hung himself on the jail bars
There was a writing
on the wall written in blood
He might be the murderer
in your story
So, do you still see Saeng Daow?
Is she here now?
Anyway, you're probably tired
You can go
but I'll still need you to come back
and make your statement
one more time
I hope you'll cooperate.
If the same thing happened to you
You might not ever want
to see anyone again.
With all do love and respect to
my dearest mother.
I'm so sorry that I ran away
without telling anyone.
I know it must've caused
you much pain and sorrow.
But did you know that this
daughter also felt the same pain
and sorrow as you did?
All I could do was cry
for what I've done to you.
I'm such a bad person
for leaving you and my sister
isn't that right mother?
But please believe me mother.
I have my reasons in making
this decision.
If I had to stay
in that house any longer
my life would surely be filled
with such heartache
and would finally end
without meaning.
Please don't ask me
to go back to that house
because I don't think
I have the courage to face you
or anyone ever again.
My sins can never be erased
for as long as I live
and I will never forget the people
that have done me wrong...
especially those men which
to this day I curse them all.
In conclusion
I ask you to please explain to
Tawan so that she understands
because I really worry about her.
She is still so young
and probably very disappointed
in me for what I've done.
With Love, Saeng Daow