Always late
With your kisses
Won't you come to my arms,
sweet darlin'
And stay?
Always late
With your kisses
Why, oh, why do you
want to do me this way?
How long do you think
I can wait
When you know
you're always late
Always late
With your kisses
Why, why, why do you want
to do me this way?
That was Lefty Frizzell's
"Always Late with Your Kisses."
Before that,
we heard Buck Owens.
Get your waders out.
It's seven days before the state
officially drowns Northfork.
It's sunny skies
with the highs being 51...
"To the loving O'Brien family.
"It has been brought
to our attention
"that the remains
of a Mrs. Patricia O'Brien
"have yet to be excavated.
Please make arrangements
immediately."
The hardworking citizens
of Northfork
will be able to have
their much-needed power...
as well as...
the pleasure of the recreation
that this body of water
will provide.
Let me add this:
the good people of Northfork
will be able to have their cake
and eat it, too.
Two, three...
Where are we going to start...
right in here?
Where should we start?
Let's start right in here.
Then the water
shall become a flood
and destroy all flesh...
and the bow
shall be in the cloud,
and I will look upon it,
and I will remember
the everlasting covenant
between God
and every living creature...
of all flesh
that is upon the earth.
And that's what we have here.
Our town is dying.
I have seen the concrete
monument...
the headstone
for the town for Northfork.
This dam gate will close...
the water will rise
over the plains,
and cover our businesses...
our homes...
and our well-being.
We have lost Northfork.
We will be losing
our dear son...
but we will gain the hope,
the courage...
to move
to a higher ground.
We're all angels.
It is what we do
with our wings
that separates us.
What are we waiting for?
Well, Mr. and Mrs. Hadfield.
Father, his health
isn't getting any better.
Rose has had to stay
by his bed.
All the doctors
have left Northfork.
You're returning him then?
He's a very ill child.
We cannot make the journey
with him in this condition.
We apologize, Father.
We appreciate your honesty,
and will ask for forgiveness.
Forgiveness?
Let's be honest, Father.
You gave us a sick child.
I gave you an angel.
You're misunderstanding us.
We love Irwin.
Halo Home is deeply regretful
about the grief
Irwin has brought
to your family.
God bless.
Have a nice journey.
This is wrong.
This is just downright wrong.
When did you get this letter?
I received the final
notice yesterday.
I don't like this damned cake.
This is wrong on every level.
Yeah.
Where did my parents go?
We don't want to go
where they're going.
You rest now.
Father, everybody's leaving.
Oh, I know.
I know.
Oh, let's stay here.
Huh?
You're the caretaker?
Yes?
Cookie takes care of the yard.
Maybe you can help me?
Who are you looking for?
A relative.
Hold still.
Marvin, Matt, Eddie, Arnold.
Walter, Willis,
Eddie, Arnold.
Walter, Willis, Eddie, Arnold.
Walter, Willis, Marvin, Matt.
Marvin, Matt, Walter,
Willis.
Marvin, Matt, Eddie, Arnold.
Anybody voted for him
voted themselves
right out of Northfork.
Have a good journey.
Nice concrete cork.
I have done countless evacs.
And as long as
I've been doing this job,
it is never come down
to 48 hours before.
That's two days,
and by the time I'm through
with you, it's gonna be 47.
So you'd better listen up.
And remember
one very important thing.
Despite the tertiary
inconveniences
we're putting
these people through,
we're giving them new power.
All right.
Matt...
Marvin.
Please go pay a visit
to the Youngs.
Eddie, Arnold.
Arnold.
I want you to get down
to Hungry Horse Road,
and I want you to nail Jigger,
do you understand?
You betcha.
Now, you can't go into this
treating it like
you're throwing out
homesteaders,
poor old homesteaders.
Look at it like you're saving
some poor dumb son of
a bitch from drowning.
Mr. Rudolph.
It says here that,
uh, there has been
some previous attempts
at evacuation.
Walter,
Willis.
Stallings. Highway 93.
Remember, the one single
most important thing:
it is not our business
to tell anybody else theirs.
You just come in like
you're their guardian angel.
You give them wings
and then you move'em on up
into higher ground.
Good luck now, gentlemen.
In the early 1800s,
European settlers
named Northfork
after the river
that embraced their town.
Word traveled
around the world
that angels roamed
these plains like bison.
I find the humor quite parched.
19th century.
A remarkable piece.
Artist used the finest oils.
Organic pigments.
Magnificent.
The artist has
a religious vocabulary.
He used the luxuriantly
white wings of the swan.
Fascinating representation
of the angelic messenger.
Lovely bird.
If I do recall correctly,
the Celts employed the majestic
swan as their sacred symbol
and messenger
to the other world.
Their link that existed
between the realm of their gods
and the realm of humans.
Very relatable.
I can only speculate...
that the man with swan wings,
or in this painting,
the wild bird man,
is a creation
of the overtaking
by Christianity.
Bless the imagination.
Walk, walk, walk
- Just a closer walk with Thee
- It's wrong.
It's just downright wrong.
702.
For Thou art strong
Departed.
Jesus keep me from all wrong
It's wrong,
and I'm not gonna do it.
And neither should you.
It's death till you part.
She's your mother.
I'll be satisfied as long
- As I walk
- 705.
- Let me walk close to Thee
- Departed.
Just a closer walk with Thee
Grant it, Jesus, is my plea
Daily walking close to Thee.
Have you ever smelled death?
I don't recall smelling it.
Death smells like
nothing you've ever
smelled in your life.
What does it smell like?
You know when
you've smelled death.
'Cause when you smell it...
you say to yourself, "Damn.
Something die?"
Anything?
Does it say anything
about a child?
No. Not specifically.
There was a small child
roaming the garden.
Oh, Flower,
it said nothing about children.
Wait.
Narrator fluctuates between
the first and third person.
Quite interesting.
I would have to say that
he's above the age of a child.
Flower,
every town you go scurrying off
looking for offspring.
Wait.
Would you like a cup of tea?
One lump or two?
My name is Cup of Tea.
To my right,
as you may already know,
is Flower Hercules.
To my left, Cod.
And behind us all,
but in front of you, Happy.
And you are?
Irwin.
Hello, Irwin.
And your surname?
Sir Irwin.
Well, Sir Irwin
of Northfork,
my family and I have traveled
a long way,
and we are having trouble
finding a loved one.
Are you familiar
with the unknown angel?
Yes.
Now...
this is where we can be
of help to each other.
What could we offer you?
When you leave,
just take me with you.
No.
Never.
We do not
take children.
Then I can't help you.
Now, Sir Irwin...
you're being unreasonable.
Where we're going,
we can't take you with us.
Then take me a thousand miles.
A thousand miles
in anybody's book is a long way.
How about a hundred miles?
- A thousand.
- 200.
- 300.
A thousand.
400, and that's it.
A thousand, and that's it.
Do you know how far that is?
A thousand miles
is a far, far, faraway place.
500 miles.
A thousand.
All right.
We'll take you
a thousand miles
if you bring us
the unknown angel.
In the morning?
Deal?
You the pain livin'
of a heart full of shame
You broke the law...
Ursula.
- Of God and man
- You have two customers.
You stole from me the one whose
ring was on my hand
I'd say that you...
But through that came livin'
with a heart full of shame...
Oh, I tell you,
these sons of bitches
are harder to yank
than a tick on the touch-hole
of a chicken.
I hear ya.
Ursula...
Good morning.
You have six customers...
now seated.
Well, if it ain't
the bottom feeders.
Go ahead, Willis.
Eggs?
Bacon?
Mm-mm.
Sausage?
No meat?
Mm-mm.
Potatoes?
Soup.
Mm!
Uh-huh.
Chicken?
Mm-hmm.
Broth?
Cup or bowl?
Yeah!
Good work, boss.
Nice work, Walter.
Thank you, boys.
I'll have a bowl.
Same.
Okay.
Dent.
It's only dirt.
Afternoon, boys.
Good afternoon,
Father.
Walter.
Your wife, Patricia...
Henry...
Irwin's still sick.
I'm sorry, Father.
Mm...
Well, you got anything
that'll keep his spirits up
and his fever down?
If I was those parents,
I'd be ashamed.
Well, most parents
can't see their child ill.
So they throw him in a lake.
All depends, Henry,
on how you look at it.
Either you're halfway to heaven
or halfway to hell.
Here we go, Father.
It's an antibiotic.
Inject five cc's
of this into his arm.
Okay.
All right?
Bless you.
Have a safe journey.
Thank you, Father.
All right.
We thank you in advance
and hope you have...
a pleasant journey.
Pop?
Yeah, son?
You suppose he's got two
of everything in there?
I suppose we'll find out.
Now, I don't care
If I'm not the first...
Damn it.
That you picked...
I know.
Darlin', I'll never ask...
Not one, but two Chevys.
Yesterday's gone...
I know.
...from now on
They heard of me...
This is going
to be difficult.
...about the past
Yep.
Now I don't care if I'm...
Ever since we started
moving folks out...
we've never done well
with people
that owned Chevrolets.
...I'll be the last.
Matt...
...this country is being divided
into two types of people...
Chevy people...
...and Ford people, Matt.
Yep.
Now, I don't care
If I'm not the first love
you've known
Just so I'll be the last
Now, I don't care...
Looks like he got
some kind of hammer.
...that you picked
Darlin' I'll never ask...
No, it looks more like a...
I think
he was holding a shotgun.
I think you're right.
Every town we come to,
you want a child.
Once again, selfish.
How observant.
The noble Englishman.
How I longed to be Earl Grey.
The wit that got us here.
It's a splendid
acquisition.
Unknown architect.
Probably owner-builder.
A true visionary,
I might add.
Jesus.
No, no, he was a carpenter.
We-we-we're searching
for the unknown.
The unknown doesn't just
come knocking on your door.
If it is unknown, how would you
know if it did come knocking?
Well, it won't be
in the shape of a child.
I would have to agree.
Happy.
Do you ever disagree?
I disagree with
the Englishman's use of starch.
What do the Scriptures say?
"Temperature, 105 degrees.
High.
Please look after him
when I leave."
What do you suppose we do?
We're going to wing it.
It appears they've...
worn out their welcome.
Good afternoon, Mr. Stalling.
My name is Walter O'Brien.
This here's my son, Willis.
We're with
the evacuation committee.
It's been brought
to the state's attention
that you are seeking
some assistance.
I'm not going anywhere, son.
We're aware of that, sir,
that's why the state has
asked us to come to your aid.
The state understands
your difficulty
with moving on.
The state
will not hurt, destroy,
nor harm you physically
in any way.
It is our civil duty to assist
you in making this transition
as easy and pleasant
as possible.
Your agreement is this...
you will each be assigned
65 households to depart.
Having fulfilled
said obligation,
you will then
each receive 1.5 acres
of prime, lakefront property.
Your lot size
will be increased
by one fifth of an acre
for every additional household
that you assist in evacuating
beyond the initial 65.
Have I made myself clear?
I will take your vacant
stares as a yes.
I could live
with an acre and a half.
Okay by me.
May we, sir?
So...
...the prodigal son returns.
Already packed.
A little ahead of yourself.
I've brought
what you're looking for.
You have?
Outside.
I don't see anything.
We still have a deal?
Yes, yes, yes.
We have a deal.
Yeah, we still have a deal.
Where is it?
Oh, my.
Hello.
We'd appreciate it
if you both would stop
screwing around.
Well, what do you want to do?
The Youngs are going
to have a moving sale.
Perfect.
Now, all I need is a pair
of sinners like yourselves
to mount up there now.
We appreciate
very much your giving us
this time to discuss
this matter.
A pair of wives?
At least they're not mounted.
You know,
it appears to me
that you folks
are preparing for a flood
in Biblical proportions.
You got that right, son.
A flood is going to wipe
through this place,
cleansing the soil of all sin.
Understandable.
When God tells us
to get a move on,
we're gone at the first holler
of a rooster.
We ain't needing the State
to come in here
and tell us when
to pick up and get going.
That's God's doing.
This is God's land,
and by God,
we ain't movin' until we get
that sign from above.
Yes, sir, uh...
we aren't telling you
to pick up and get going.
No, sir.
Look at us as your
life preservers.
You can use us if you want,
or not at all.
We give you that choice.
We're all in the same boat.
So, sir, if you
don't mind, sir,
I'd like to bend you
and your wives' ear a bit
and tell you
about the signs of God
that we are familiar with.
This could be
that sign.
A what?
He said he was a relative.
To us?
Yes.
You're the unknown angel?
The one you're looking for.
Optimistic.
He is unknown.
The angel part's
questionable.
Very.
How romantic.
There's a novel about you, too.
I started to collect these.
This is the first one I grew.
Now I'm not saying
that this boat
you have built isn't worthy.
From the looks of it,
you've done a mighty fine job.
But for the sake of my job,
let's just say
it doesn't.
Doesn't what?
Your boat doesn't float.
Imagine this, if you will.
One day,
a town on the plains,
let's say Northfork,
was hit by a catastrophic flood,
similar to
the days of Noah,
and you husband
and yourselves
are standing out there on
the roof waiting to be rescued.
A friendly neighbor
comes paddling by in
his little wooden boat,
and he yells, "Hey, there,
Mr. and Mrs. Stalling,
"and... uh, Mrs. Stalling,
jump on in
and I'll take you to dry land."
What do you say?
I don't know.
The water's rising.
You shout back,
"No, thank you,
thy friendly neighbor.
I'm waiting
for a sign from God."
No, thank you.
I'm waiting for a sign from God.
Yes, exactly.
And your friendly neighbor
paddles away.
A few days later
a state rescue team
comes by in a larger boat.
And let's just say
me and Willis are on board.
And we offer you the same deal.
"Jump on in,
"and you, Mrs. Stalling
and... Mrs. Stalling,
will be saved."
And you say...
No, thank you.
We're waiting
for a sign from God.
A few more days pass,
and the water level has risen.
It has risen above the roof.
And unfortunately,
you and Mr. Stalling
have drowned
and now are in heaven
in front of God.
Dear, we died.
What about our belongings?
We died?
Oh, yes, you three have died
because you waited
for a sign from God
and it never came,
and you three died.
But why?
That's the exact question
you would ask God.
You would say, "We waited for
the sign and it never came."
And you and she...
and Mr. Stalling... died.
Now what
do you suppose
God is going
to say to you both?
I don't
know.
Mr. Stalling?
I'm dead, remember?
May I?
Yes.
I'll tell you
what God will say.
"I sent you two boats...
"Two boats.
...to save your lives."
What more of a sign
did you three want?
May I?
Fascinating.
You have a lovely
collection of feathers.
Thank you.
And your halo.
Where's that?
They took it off
when I was little.
I didn't need it anymore.
And these must be your wings.
Oh, mighty.
Look at this.
And where did we get this?
These are quite stunning.
The grace of God.
Yes, they are.
We're offering you
a pair of something
that only the man upstairs
is willing to give you.
Where'd you get these boys?
Born and raised
right here in Northfork.
Dear, what
are you thinking?
I'm thinking,
what bird suffered this?
Oh, there's nothing
fowl about these wings.
I understand your initial doubt,
but how many times
have you seen wings
of this size and beauty?
This is what
most of us were shot with.
Tranquillity at its finest.
This could make
an elephant fly.
It stuck in me
right here.
May I look?
Appears to be lengthy
needle of some sort.
Five years, maybe
six years of age.
Used numerous times
for injection.
You were shot with
this rifle?
Yes.
I was running with my flock
and they shot me.
You were running
with your flock?
Yes.
Flock of what?
Doves? Geese? Seagulls?
Angels.
Angel wings, huh?
I'm here to tell you
these wings is worthless.
And to remove all doubt,
we included this certificate
of authenticity.
Signed, sealed and blessed
by your own Father Harlan.
"Found near the glaciers,
these wings, blah, blah, blah."
From what they could tell,
this particular pair were
detached from a juvenile
who probably strayed
from the flock.
"Perhaps no wiser
than four years of age.
"The abbreviated
wingspan reveals to us
"that he weighed
no more than 25
to 30 pounds
before they were removed."
A bit too disturbing for me.
Happy...
are you looking at this?
Would you say amputated?
Yes. Amputated.
Fascinating.
Angel. Huh.
Aren't we all?
I'd say quite the opposite.
Probably a little devil,
and daddy gave him
a good strapping.
There's a back
story for you.
Does this cause any pain?
No.
This would be
recognized
as a highly dangerous
procedure without
anesthesia.
Some people would just
bite a bullet.
A highly
skilled surgeon
was overly concerned
with muscle stabilization.
There's no evidence of
curvature of the spine.
You're discovering
feathers in this area?
Yes.
What time of day?
Morning.
Can you run your fingers
through his hair?
What can you tell us
about your relatives?
My mother and father were
12th generation angels.
My great grandpa
and grandma
had wings the size
of bombers and would
glide the plains
of Northfork.
Come on, you ladies,
can't you just smell
the bird shit?
I mean, I'd like to believe
these wings is authentic,
but the feathers,
they ain't attached
to anything.
You take those moose antlers
back there.
Oh, dear.
Yeah, it's a fine
set of antlers, but it's more
than just a rack of horns
attached to a piece of board.
That wouldn't be enough.
It's an okay place
to hang your hat,
but there ain't no pride in it.
What you need is the whole
head hanging up there.
And these marble eyes just
a-staring on down at you.
Then you know you've got
something really worth having.
We're still not leaving.
I've got a thousand-dollar
check from the state,
or would you rather use that
for your funeral services?
No.
Then you best get the hell
out of here right now.
Use these to fly
the hell out of here.
Wow.
Eddie. Hey, Eddie.
I think Jigger's asleep.
Let's go.
Jesus Christ.
The scars on his forehead
tell me he did
have a halo.
Most likely metal.
To stabilize his...
Oh.
Everything all right?
Dankish, beetle-headed
foot-licker.
What is wrong with you?
Happy?
You should be asking yourself
that question.
Fired from a long barrel rifle.
Ten feet away.
Needle meant
to penetrate two
to three inches of skin.
Perhaps the hide
of a herbivore.
Beast of a hallucinogenic.
Would you like a cup of tea?
This isn't tea time.
Given my weight,
calculated dosage...
this could be a lengthy trip.
Moist.
Mother...
may I?
No.
Yes.
Plenty more
where that came from.
Here.
Shoot me, shoot Cod.
And then shoot yourself
in the foot.
No!
You saucy, sheep-biting,
flat-mouthed dewberry.
This could be a family...
Oh.
Santa's everywhere.
I'm happy.
This should back off
some evil spirits.
Hmm?
Oh.
Hmm.
Two out of three ain't that bad.
Damn it. I say
we hook that thing up
to our bumper
and drag it out ourselves.
What are you talking about,
Willis?
You know why?
I'll tell you why.
That there was number
65.
I know that, Willis.
I'm marking them down
as departed.
We can't.
The state makes their
final pass-through,
and they find that Mr. Stalling
locked up in that
boat with his
moosehead.
It's our butt.
It's our job
to move them out of Northfork.
It's not our job
to know where they go.
Willis...
it's our job
to move people,
not change their beliefs.
What more
could we have said?
Without the proper words,
this is just a man, nailed
to two pieces of wood.
Oh, he's cute.
Father?
Yes, son.
I don't think they want me.
Oh, no, they do.
They do, son.
They came a long way for you.
Then,
can I go with them?
I will still have to speak
with them.
Then,
can you tell them I'm an angel?
I will.
Because I want them
to see my wings.
Do you have wings?
Yeah? Me, too.
But mine got old and fell off.
You get some sleep now.
All right.
Mr. and Mrs. Hope?
Yes.
I'm Father Harlan.
Father.
Thank you
for coming on short notice.
Irwin is
a good boy.
I could go on, but
that would seem
like I'm selling him to you.
And I'm not.
What?
You're not...
Well, given the chance,
I'm sure Irwin
would do a better job
at selling himself...
- Oh.
- than me.
Can we meet him?
Unfortunately...
you will have to make a decision
before you can meet him.
But, Father, it says right here
that we can spend
the afternoon with him.
Yes, I know. I...
I'm sorry. I apologize.
But Irwin is a fragile boy.
I can't let him
get his hopes up too high
only to have them diminished.
His health can't afford
that kind of a disappointment.
Oh, Father, we can't
make a decision
based upon viewing
him from a window.
I'm sorry.
Why don't you go
wait in the car?
Father, we come here
attempting to adopt a child,
and you turn it
into window shopping.
He's not a puppy.
Oh.
Well, maybe that's
what you and your wife
should be considering.
I'm sorry
if I have wasted your time.
Have a pleasant journey.
Many townspeople have speculated
that the body of Jimmy Miller,
son of Doris and James Miller,
still lays in the Northfork dam.
One worker has said,
"There is a slight lump
in the interior wall
that will hold back
19 million acres of water."
Another worker said,
"Yes, Jimmy is in there.
"They never could retrieve him
from the dam.
He is resting in peace."
Tom Johnson, a fisherman,
put it this way,
"Heck, you can't exactly
troll a hundred feet
of just-poured concrete
fishing for a body."
Marvin. Matt.
Walter. Willis.
Tours of the Northfork dam,
and possibly Jimmy Miller,
will be starting in January.
For more information,
please contact Montana's
Water and Power.
Somebody is laying there.
You feel a heartbeat?
No.
You can figure...
a death of a person is
still considered progress.
Son of a bitch is getting
the biggest headstone
this side of Rushmore.
Yeah.
Congratulations.
65 residents departed.
Good job.
You sign on that bottom line,
1.5 acres will be transferred
into your name.
Hmm.
Well, your log reads
64 residents departed.
Is this correct?
Well, sir...
Yes, sir, it is.
Well, you know what?
I'd like to thank
you personally
for your hard work
and dedication
in the evacuation
of Northfork,
and hope to see you boys
out there enjoying the lake.
Wait a minute.
That's it?
We get nothing?
That's correct.
Sir, there...
there is another house
that we did not confirm
their departure.
Well, then, you best
go out there
and get it confirmed, huh?
Duck.
Goose.
Boy was a tad pigeon-toed.
What do you think?
For most, Vincent Van Gogh
was a fine artist.
To some, he lacked technique.
Paint straight
from the tube,
very heavy-handed.
How Van Gogh cut off his ear
is what is most intriguing
to folks.
In each piece I've ever
appraised, the story
is always more fascinating
than the actual piece itself.
And?
It's a fantastic yarn
the boy has spun.
Unfortunately...
the story is more valuable
than the actual piece.
What about his collection
of feathers?
Perhaps...
from the stork
that dropped him.
Feathers are inconsistent.
I couldn't find
any connection
in the scriptures.
And that spleeny
ill-nurtured gnat.
Are you positive?
Oh, Flower, please,
be open to inconsistency.
What did the feathers
come in?
A book.
The book
was in a pillowcase.
I presume that the pillow
that the boy
lays his head on
is stuffed with feathers.
He is not
what we are here for.
La Fleur
was touched by an angel.
Is it snowing?
Can I go?
You're not mine anymore
This is it, son.
Looks pretty vacant.
Indeed it does.
If you don't ever
change your mind
Trick or treat.
Smells like something
died in here.
That is precisely why
we're not going to get mother.
Willis, you smell that?
Yeah, it smells
like something died.
Go upstairs and check
all the rooms.
Then we'll leave.
What?
You're kidding.
You go upstairs
and check everything out.
Willis, go upstairs,
and see if anyone
is up there.
I'm personally not ready
to face death.
This is number 65.
Go upstairs, check it out,
and let's get this over with.
I'm checking out
the other side.
Willis.
Willis!
Hello?
Hello there.
Pop.
Pop!
Do you see anything?
No.
Come on. Jump.
It's about
five feet, come on.
You can make it.
Jump.
Come on.
Pop, come on, jump!
You can make it. Come on.
Are you okay?
Would you like a cup of tea?
I would qualify this
in the area
of concussion.
A frothy, clay-brained snapper.
Let's help you get up
onto your feet.
Definitely
going to feel that
in the morning.
Willis, let's go.
Did you see anyone?
Nope.
Come on!
Get in the car!
Get!
What's got you
so spooked?
If you don't ever
change your mind
To take me back again
Grab the book.
Pop...
Just do it!
Mark them down as evacs.
Evacuated.
Do it!
Okay, I will.
Since the day you say
we're through
I'm even more
in love with you
And it's my fault that
you're not mine anymore
And I think we should
go get your mom.
These have the same texture
as the feathers that were
in the boy's book.
Mm-hmm.
No more than four years of age.
Weighed no more than 30 pounds.
These were attached
to something very young...
I'm going to have
to evaluate the other side.
Fascinating.
Oh, Lord...
Let the holy angels come
to Irwin.
And carry him
to your heavenly city.
Free his spirit...
from the prison of his body.
Fascinating.
No.
Please, no.
I'm sorry.
I'm a man of faith.
Forgiveness is my job.
But right now,
I can't forgive my faith.
Hmm.
Here.
He grew two inches this summer.
- Pop.
Still stacking wood?
Yep.
Pop?
Yeah?
You're not even close
to what death smells like.
I'm sorry.
I'm coming to get you.
I didn't forget you.
I'm sorry.
Pop.
Come here.
What?
Can you see?
Look closer.
No, I can't see anything.
What am I looking for?
There's a nick in my paint.
There's a nick in my paint!
Don't make it worse.
- Don't make it worse.
- It's only dirt.
I was rubbing it off.
- What color is dirt?
- Brown?
If Marvin weren't blind,
he would see
that it was gray...
the color underneath my paint.
Willis, the speck is brown.
Look.
Brown after Marvin's
filthy hands rubbed it.
Well, I can't see
how you'd think
you could keep your car perfect
the way you drive anyway.
It hurts.
The first one... hurts.
You just never know
when it's going to come.
You know,
that's fate for you.
A little rock.
You do not have a say
in the matter.
Now that you've gotten
the first one...
...the rest comes easy.
You spend all your time...
polishing your car,
making everything perfect.
Then this rock...
flies out of nowhere,
and puts all your
hard work to shame.
Nothing you can do about it.
Absolutely nothing.
- Holy cow.
- Oh, my God.
...into the hole... take that...
...soft, so when you get
down in there,
you just thread this rope
through the top handle.
What?
You jump down there and do it.
- Willis.
- No more. No, no, no, no.
This is downright wrong.
Once something's buried,
it should stay buried.
I can't show no more respect.
You know,
when this small town
becomes the biggest lake
this side of the Mississippi,
your mother will be
the catch of the day!
Then throw some rocks on her.
That should keep her down.
Where you going to take her?
What about California?
What's there?
I heard in California
they're serving cheeseburgers
and a soda
in less than two minutes flat.
Wow...
That's fast food.
I know you've been praying.
Not to worry.
A family will come soon.
You may be an orphan...
but you're still a child of God.
We must go get him, Flower.
If I didn't know your voice,
I would think it
was my subconscious.
Could he be?
He is.
You don't want to believe him,
do you?
You do?
He's just a child.
I can't accept that.
Yes,
I know.
We can't.
We have to.
You have to.
Don't let
your motherly nature
cost you your manhood.
He prayed for us.
1.5 acres
of lakefront property.
Hmm.
Northern Pike?
Might be.
Pike's not a fish.
It's a dog.
Skull full of teeth.
Pick those suckers up
by their eye sockets.
Weapons of massive destruction.
They drop that
pike's milt into this lake.
You can forget
all about the fish
living in peace and harmony.
Pike eat their children.
What they should do
is introduce a nice game fish
like the Muskie.
Now, that's a fine species.
- Mm.
- No fish
from Minnesota
should be allowed to swim
past the Missouri.
The fine citizens
of Northfork knew
that Muskie was swimming
through their houses,
we would've never been able
to get'em to leave.
Canada ought to claim
that bug-heap they
call Minnesota.
Throw in Wisconsin for free.
You have to think
that this must have been
his last day on the job.
You ready?
1,000 miles?
Farther.
You're a relative.
Hercules...
the strongest man
ever to wear a skirt.
Are you going to be my mother
or my father?
I'm both.
Considered the perfect soul,
I search for no one,
and no one looks for me.
Whatever
I need I look
within myself to find.
I am
complete.
I am not king nor queen,
yet I am both.
A mother and a father.
You prayed to be this way?
Isn't that
what Father Harlan says?
"Pray and you shall receive?"
Would you like a cup of tea?
Irwin?
Well?
There you go, son.
And in that journey of dying,
you see many things.
But all issues I had passed.
Because I was to be a witness.
A helper.
And that's the thing, I think,
is important about death,
is the ability for us
to be witnesses.
Not only for our births
of coming in,
but going out.
And that's what we have here.
We've lost our town. It's gone.
But maybe there's
a birth someplace else.
Maybe there's a blessing
from that experience.
I'm no longer afraid of death,
but it's a lesson
that's taken me
60 years to learn.
As you stroll around Northfork,
take your last walk
down the dirt road
that leads to where
your house may have been,
and look at the trees
that you once climbed.
Smile, and remember those trees
for what they will become:
future snags
for fishing tackle.
As you continue your walk,
think to yourself,
"This is the only time
I will ever be able
"to walk
on the bottom of a lake
without having
to hold my breath."
Remember when you leave
to pack all your good memories.
No one else will pack them
for you.
Good night to you all.