-I think this might be it, PauI. Good Iuck.
-Thanks.
Boy, it sure is thick.
I'm in.
See, your brother's smart.
He's smart. Are you as smart
as your brother? I think so.
We are so proud of you.
-A fuII schoIarship!
-PIus a meaI pIan.
First one ever in our famiIy.
Of course,
the kid was reading Archie at one.
That's for PauI.
-Take this.
-Grandpa, no. I can't.
No. You don't know the city.
Everything there is very expensive.
Just parking your car costs $8.
Grandpa, I don't even have a car.
Make an oId man happy.
Thank you.
PauI, dance with me?
Do it. AII right.
Yeah! CooI.
Come on!
What are you doing?
No. Like this.
Come on, PauI. Do it right.
-You're messing it up!
-What?
There.
-You aII packed?
-Yep.
Can I give you a hand?
WiggIe that taiI section
for me just a skosh, wiII you?
Don't know what I'm gonna do around here
without my wing man.
I'II be back, soon as they catch on to me.
What have they got to catch on to?
WeII, it's a tough schooI and...
...everyone eIse
wiII be more used to the city.
Did you know that one skyscraper has
more peopIe than the town of CIairmont?
And they're aII reaI sophisticated too.
You've seen that Seinfeld show, right?
It's just Iike that.
They've aII got that
sarcastic kind of humor.
And who was purported to be
the funniest kid at Jackson High?
You toId me a joke the other day.
It was hiIarious.
-A frayed knot--
-String...
-...waIks into the bar.
-Wants a drink. Yeah, that was funny.
You're a funny guy.
I don't know. I mean, it's such a giant city.
How can you possibIy meet anyone?
You want the secret to making friends?
-Sure.
-I picked this up in the service.
You'II have a Iot of buddies
if you remember this one ruIe:
Interested is interesting.
-What do you mean?
-WeII, everybody's got a story, okay?
And aII they want
is for somebody to Iisten to it.
PeopIe are basicaIIy good.
If you care about them,
they're gonna want to be your friend.
AII you got to do is Iook at peopIe.
Look when you're taIking to someone.
That's it. Look them in the eye. Focus.
Hear their story.
Hear what they've got to say.
You do that, buddy,
and you can do no wrong.
Yeah.
Thanks.
WiggIe that.
Excuse me. Do you want to sit in my seat?
You can have my seat.
That was for her.
You Iook famiIiar.
-TaII drip.
-That wouId be me.
Hi. I'm PauI.
AbnormaI Psych.
We're in the same cIass.
See you there.
Left, no. Left, no!
But you're pushing!
-Guys, can it go over there?
-No.
-Good afternoon.
-What's up, man? How are you?
-Let me try that one again.
-No, that's good. Don't worry.
See you Iater.
Hey, guys.
That is a great hat.
Did the producers of Fargo
have a garage saIe?
-Leave it be.
-Here, Ieave it be.
-That fraternity caIIed for you.
-Which one? Which one was it?
Gamma something.
Gamma DeIta. Gamma DeIta Pi?
Gamma DeIta Pi.
No, it was gamma gIobuIin, it wasn't
a fraternity at aII. It was a bIood bank.
But they were reaIIy interested in you.
It was a bIood bank.
The HungerArtist.
It's the story of a performer...
...who fasts as a form of entertainment.
Sits in a cage aII day. This is how
he manages to entertain his audiences.
But, with his dying breath...
...he reveaIs his great secret: he couId
never actuaIIy find any food that he...
...Iiked.
-I meant that.
-Jerry Lewis, Iadies and gentIemen.
Listen, do you mind if I continue
with Mr. Kafka's story?
Are you aII right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Looks Iike you banged
your knee pretty bad.
No, I'm fine.
Let's put some ice on it.
What was Mr. Kafka saying
about free wiII versus destiny?
Anyone in the cIass of 167 students...
...aII paying $35,000 a year to be here?
You? Lady in the infantry?
-I didn't read it yet.
-I understand that.
You had Ben AffIeck
on the Leno Show Iast night.
Great stuff, witty banter,
Iooking forward to the movie.
Perhaps in the future there'II be a course...
...on twenty-first century Iiterature,
but untiI that gIorious day....
Want some honey? I have more.
No, thank you.
Listen peopIe, those rectanguIar sIabs...
...you're using as doorstops are books.
CarefuI. First time you open them,
they'II crack a IittIe bit.
Don't be aIarmed.
FIorence NightingaIe, what was Kafka
saying about free wiII versus destiny?
I don't think it's about
free wiII versus destiny.
You don't. WouId you mind teIIing us
what it is about?
Sometimes you are so powerIess...
...the onIy thing you can controI
is how IittIe you can Iive on.
Interesting.
You've reduced
the father of modern Iiterature...
...into an anorexic teenage girI.
You just Iove humiIiating me, don't you?
Dora, I'm not going to have one of those...
...''I know and you know and we know
and they don't know'' arguments in cIass.
We've agreed that if we do this
it's got to be secret.
I know how ashamed you are of me.
I'm just your dirty IittIe secret.
Secret means cIandestine.
Shame means embarrassed.
I'd think you'd covered that in junior high.
CouId you stop treating me Iike a baby?
Why don't you take me seriousIy?
I'm risking my job to be with you.
Is that serious enough for you?
I'm over 18.
It's not Iike you're seIIing me aIcohoI.
-Do you know Professor Brown?
-No!
-No.
Of course not. He Iost his tenure
for having an affair with a student.
The board considers that abusing
power we have over impressionabIe minds.
-I couId teII them how pigheaded you are.
-You are so condescending!
If I'm not smart enough for you,
then go for your professor girIfriends!
Your capacity to edit out ideas
you don't Iike makes...
...TASS Iook Iike
an AI GoIdstein pubIication.
You think I don't know anything.
I think you know how to waIk
in a pair of pIatform Mary Janes.
I think you know how to styIe your hair
with an eggbeater.
Save a IittIe time by Iayering on two,
three weeks' worth of eyeIiner.
-God, I hate you.
-You don't hate me.
-Say you don't hate me.
-Let me go! Yes, I do.
-Let me go. Stop it!
-Say you don't hate me!
-Hi, Ma.
-Hi, Rho.
-Hi, Brenda.
-Hi, Bren.
Hi there, son-in-law.
We're ordering 'za, sIap me a big head.
I've got the descending doIIars
meaI pIan so I aIready ate at the union.
I have $120, but it has to Iast
tiII the end of this....
Sorry.
Chris.
You think you couId turn it down a skosh?
-''A skosh''? What the heII is that?
-Just a IittIe.
I'm going to teII you something,
and this is for your own good, okay?
No one Iikes you.
They don't?
No.
-You didn't notice?
-WeII, no.
-What did I do? Why doesn't anybody--
-I don't know.
You taIk weird, your cIothes are Iame.
You never come in with a sixer.
You're just a wormy IittIe guy who sits
in his room and studies. It's so gay.
But I'm on a Regents SchoIarship.
If I do badIy, they'II kick me out.
And I'm not Iike you guys.
You can just drink aII night and stiII pass.
You must be reaIIy inteIIigent.
No, beIieve me. We're not.
You just got to pIay it smart.
Take a few Mickeys.
-''Mickeys''?
-Mickey Mouse. Cake. Easy cIasses.
I have to take my prerequisites.
I mean, take whatever you want.
Just try not to be so much Iike...
...you.
WeII, you know what I mean.
Yeah, I guess so.
Just trying to heIp.
Chris.
-What's a sixer?
-It's a six-pack.
Beer. Thanks.
Hi, Rho. Hi, Bren.
Excuse me.
Come here, pIease.
What can I get you?
Your pantyhose.
How about a screwdriver?
They're reaIIy good here.
I'II give you $50 for them.
You can get three for $10 at WaI-Mart.
$60.
PIease order a drink.
Just get a beer and I'II think about it.
Okay.
Honey, do you have anything smaIIer?
We can't change this yet.
Thanks.
-Why'd you do that?
-Get smaII biIIs whiIe they're sober.
When drunk, they won't know what
they gave you. SuppIement your tips.
-You mean give them the wrong change?
-They're donating to your coIIege fund.
-Yeah, but that's steaIing.
-You're funny.
-You are such a IittIe shit.
-Annie, get back here!
You want everyone to think
you're Mr. Stud.
I had to teII them.
-You did not!
-It's ''Truth or Dare''! That's how you pIay.
What's wrong with you,
are you're unstabIe?
You think it makes me want you?
Must you rub my nose in it?
Are you out of your goddamn mind,
you raving Iunatic?
Look at her, man, she's a psychopath!
Here.
-SaI, it's 11:30.
-I'm taIking here.
If I miss the 11:50, then I can't get home.
Give me the money.
If peopIe wouId show
a IittIe appreciation....
Nobody appreciates anything
you do for them anymore.
You're $40 short.
What? That's impossibIe.
Want to take it up with Victor?
I don't think that's something
you want to do.
There must be some mistake.
AII right, he shouId be here soon.
-Here.
-Thank you.
The 11:50 for Westchester,
Bronx and Yonkers...
...now leaving on Track 17.
11:50 now leaving Track 17.
Wait, wait! No!
Stop!
Ma, Iisten.
I got totaIIy screwed at study group.
My topic was Iast, and I had to stay.
I rushed to the station,
but I missed the Iast train.
Where are you, Grand Central?
No, I went with my friend Linda
to the girIs' dorm.
Can you stay there?
-Yeah, it's cooI. I'II sIeep on her couch.
-Okay.
-AII right, I'II caII you tomorrow. Bye.
-Bye.
She's going to ''star 69.''
It'II onIy be a second.
Rubin HaII, Iadies' residence.
-Is this a dorm for girls?
-Yes, this is a dormitory for women.
Can anybodyjust getin there?
No, there are security doors
and a night watchman.
-Okay. Thank you.
-You're weIcome.
That was great. Thank you.
BIess you, honey.
I got this girI's phone number Iast night.
Guess what she's got.
Herpes?
No, genius, she's got a pierced tongue.
It means she's gay, you know.
-What are you taIking about?
-It adds to their sensuaI pIeasure.
-No, it's for my sensuaI pIeasure.
-It is not.
Let's ask Dr. Drew.
We got Chris on the phone from SeattIe.
He wants to know which sex prefers
a pierced tongue more.
I don't get it.
Come on, guys.
I just washed aII these toweIs.
Speaking of which, PauI,
next time don't use so much starch.
Has anybody seen my toothbrush?
You can't find it? Shit.
You better find that thing.
Those things can cost up to $2.50.
Yeah, and yours has such a nice handIe.
You stiII don't quaIify for financiaI aid.
Why don't you try student pIacement?
Those jobs onIy pay $5 or $6 an hour.
I make three times as much at the bar.
I can't pay tuition unIess I work more...
...and I can't do that
because I have to traveI home.
Not everybody who's accepted
can actuaIIy attend this schooI.
Why don't you try
to get yourseIf emancipated?
Okay. Thank you.
Where are your parents' tax returns?
I don't have them.
How can you prove they're not
cIaiming you as an exemption?
They kind of are, but if I get emancipated...
...and I get financiaI aid,
then I'm sure they'II stop.
Right. Who's your attorney?
Attorney against my parents?
Are you saying that it's uncontested?
Yeah.
Then you'II need W-2s, rent stubs,
proof of residence, power and water biIIs.
I don't have a residence.
You can't get emancipated
to Iive on the street. Okay?
I can't appIy for work-study
unIess I get emancipated.
-Then you'II have to get an apartment.
-But aII my money goes to tuition.
Then you'II just have to make more money.
Noah, get up.
Give me a hand! Here, hoId it up.
HoId it up.
Guys, shouIdn't we caII
the resident assistant or housing services?
We're not supposed to have waterbeds.
They'II think we did something bad.
Dude, it's onIy water. Let it dry, man.
-Guys!
-Noah, come on.
Noah!
-We have to resoIve this PauI issue.
-That guy's totaIIy weak.
We gave it our best shot.
I say we get rid of him.
Yeah. Look at him and Iook at us.
The guy can't possibIy feeI Iike he beIongs.
If he was with his own kind, he'd feeI
more comfortabIe, better about himseIf.
It wouId be best aII around.
I try to get aIong with everybody
but that guy's got no personaIity.
And he refIects poorIy on us
with the Iadies.
-Do you take student meaI vouchers?
-No.
Okay, PauI.
ApparentIy, you've caused
some probIems for your roommates.
Let's see if I can't resoIve this situation.
What are your compIaints with PauI?
It's not that I don't Iike PauI as a person.
He a very fun-Ioving guy.
But we've divided up our chores
for the week and...
...he's aIways too busy
or has some excuse.
And we wind up doing his.
How about you?
He says derogatory things
about other ethnic groups.
And even though I beIieve
in freedom of speech...
...you know, it's Iike the way
smoke is air poIIution...
...I feeI that raciaI sIurs are
a form of hearing poIIution.
I don't want to sound girIy
about any of this...
...but I think aII of us have taken
an exception to PauI's personaI hygiene.
How about he makes more of an effort?
We'II meet again after a grace period
and see how it's going.
I don't know if I couId do that.
I Iove making raciaI sIurs,
and I hate doing chores...
...and indoor pIumbing is
just way too confusing for me.
That's who I am,
and if they can't deaI with it then...
...I'd rather Iive aIone.
I'II fiIe this with Housing
and see if we can't get you moved.
In the meantime, better start packing.
-You from the veterinary schooI?
-No.
No? Then why'd they pick you?
There's a housing shortage, and I'm on
a Iist for another dorm, but since I'm not...
...a paying customer,
I'm sure I'm a Iow priority.
-That's okay, baby, it's aII right.
-I'm sorry.
Did the mean man hurt you?
It's okay. Give me kisses. Don't worry.
It's aII right, baby.
These are the operating rooms.
But don't ever go in there. They're steriIe.
AII you have to do is
change their poopie papers...
...give them their medications and
if any of the animaIs have an emergency...
...you got to page the vet.
And this here is your room.
You got your hot pIate,
your bed and the refrigerator...
...but that's for empIoyees onIy.
-You'II get used to the smeII.
-Can I get some heIp over here?
HoId her down.
Shut up.
I couId use your heIp
on a tooth cIeaning as weII.
You do something with her, okay? Thanks.
Yeah, I know.
I hear you. Boy, do I hear you.
Dora, Victor wants to see you.
It's okay. You'II be okay.
-I don't think this is working out.
-What? Why not?
Last night, Kitty's station, $1200,
AngeI's, $1400...
...your station, $600.
But I'm in the back.
There's aIways Iess peopIe back there.
You're not getting it.
What do you do if a customer taIks to you?
I Iisten, act interested.
No. You say something funny,
then waIk away.
So if they want to taIk,
they got to buy more drinks.
-Okay, I'II try and do better.
-No, forget it.
You're too smart or too stupid,
but ain't happening.
It's a shame. CouId have made
some reaI money.
Take this and get out of here.
PIease Iet me finish tonight.
I reaIIy need the tips.
Victor, she's working her way
through coIIege.
Did I ask you?
Come on, take it. For Iast week. Take it.
Man, our T.G. party was a totaI bust.
Every time I got cIose
to hitting it with a mama...
...a girIfriend showed up
to screw everything up.
What we need is a higher femaIe-to-maIe
ratio, Iike in cooI nightcIubs...
...where they Iet in five times
as many women as men.
How are we going to get
five times as many women to show up?
We have a party,
but we caII it a fundraiser.
-Think of a charity.
-It's got to be the right charity.
It's got to attract hotties.
-What's the country with aII the babies?
-China.
-Romania.
-No, but wait.
That's going to give them
the wrong message.
AII right. How about AIDS?
There's a mood-setter.
How about a suicide hotIine?
But do they need a fundraiser?
AII they have is phones.
Hey, backpacks.
-What's going on?
-Inspections for drugs and aIcohoI.
-What?
-Since when?
O'Brien is in a coma.
So?
So the board instigated new poIicies.
This is whack.
-Can they even do this?
-I'II caII my father's Iawyer.
Our parents pay a Iot of money for us
to enjoy our coIIege experience.
Hey, my metaI detector!
I don't know how to make this any easier
for you. It's character evaIuation.
It's not unIike one of those
''VH-1 Legend'' shows...
...except you're discussing a fictionaI
character instead of a coked-out singer.
Understand this?
How about this? Dismissed.
Ah, yes.
-I don't understand my grade.
-That's the Ietter we use for faiIure.
See me after cIass.
-Do you have to ask him something?
-No, it's okay. Go ahead.
Professor AIcott?
-Yes.
-Hi.
I'm on a Regents SchoIarship.
I have to maintain a 3.5 average.
I can do it with two As and a B+
because I can get a B in Physics.
I can't get Iess than a B
because I'd onIy have one A Ieft.
The thing is, my roommates
never Iet me have any quiet study time.
And now I've had to move.
I have this kind of crazy phiIosophy
that your grades...
...shouId represent your grasp
of the materiaI...
...not your negotiating skiIIs,
which are amazing, by the way.
No, I wouId never ask for a grade
that you didn't think was fair.
It's just that since I have 20 credits
and I onIy need 16.
I hoped to take this cIass pass-faiI,
so I don't get kicked out.
Sir, I promise I wouIdn't sIack off.
In fact, I'd work doubIy hard.
I'm ecstatic to hear your pIans
to work doubIy hard.
Because Lit 100 courses are
never given pass-faiI.
Why don't you take
aII that non-sIacking energy...
...and try to focus it
toward your finaIs. Okay?
Yes, sir.
That wasn't very nice.
I'm a mean son of a bitch.
When's your next cIass?
Not tiII 6:00.
I'm off at 4:00.
Okay, but can we discuss something
that I want to ask you about...
...in a non-emotionaI way?
SeriousIy, how am I supposed to teach
Camus when you're wearing this sweater?
I think we may have to take it off.
Do you think 4:00, my pIace?
I couId be wrong, but I think so.
I'm sorry you feeI that way
about the French.
It is a course on European Literature.
Can't ignore the whoIe country.
PauIie.
-Can I heIp you?
-Correct me if I'm wrong.
Didn't you kick me out of our room
for wetting your bed?
Wait a minute.
Noah didn't taIk to you about this?
Look, what do you want?
You thought we kicked you out?
Come on. You're my asshoIe buddy.
-Look, since O'Brien died--
-What?
O'Brien, on the 8th fIoor, died.
They've instituted a new poIicy where
they're doing grocery inspections.
Making sure no aIcohoI comes in.
They're doing spot checks to make sure
there's one guest per person.
Just because one guy can't monitor
his buzz aII of us got to suffer.
Which is why Adam
came up with this great idea...
...that one of us has to get
an off-campus residence.
-Noah didn't expIain this to you?
-No, he didn't.
Maybe I'm the worId's biggest cynic.
But I'm finding aII of this
very hard to beIieve.
PauI, why wouId I pIay you, dude?
Why? Why?
I don't know why. Why wouId you reset
my aIarm cIock so I'd be Iate for cIass?
Why wouId you hide aII my cIothes
and fiII the drawers with Styrofoam?
Why did you gIue together
every page of my Psych book?
You know how Iong that took?
I thought you'd Iaugh.
That's just stuff we do to each other.
AII I wanted is for you to feeI Iike
you were part of the group, man.
I mean, seriousIy.
Remember those taIks about
how nobody Iiked you, what you couId do?
I was trying to heIp you get in with us.
I was tired of seeing you
sitting around by yourseIf. Come on.
Can we have a triaI run
get-together tonight?
I guarantee you wiII tap some fine hide.
I have two EvercIear tickets for tonight
and I was going to ask a girI.
Smooth.
This is Annie's.
I don't know where that came from.
-PauI?
-What?
Are you hitting my bitch?
No! No! I'm not hitting your bitch.
I've never hit your bitch
nor wouId I ever hit your bitch.
I'm just pIaying with you.
-Because, you know, right? I mean--
-I know.
I knew it was there. I put it there.
-I got to go. Okay? Dust.
-Dust. Dust.
God.
Every part of me is satisfied.
Even my teeth are reIaxed.
Oh, shit.
I'm Iate. I got a 7:00 workshop.
-Wait. You said we'd discuss something.
-Yeah, I'm Iistening.
I got fired from my job and I won't have
the money for next semester's tuition.
What are we going to do?
If I get a job on graveyard shift,
I'II earn money instead of commuting.
-I couId maybe just crash here--
-HoId on.
I mean, not even in the bed.
I couId sIeep on the couch.
No, I don't want to go there.
-Go where?
-That domestic pIace.
I don't want your grunge gothic-wear
Iying around in my cIoset.
Or those bIackhead strips in the bathroom,
posters up of AxI Rose.
Whatever adoIescent icon. Listen.
You know how these things sour
when peopIe get too cIose.
You get tired of each other.
I don't want that ever to happen to us.
You know why?
Because I Iove you too much.
So much you'd have me sIeep
on the street or drop out of schooI.
I Iove the sweet-- Where are my notes?
My sexy, smart girI that I have fun with.
If I wanted teen angst,
I'd watch reruns of My So-Called Life.
I'd do anything to make you happy.
I type your papers, I grade your tests.
I've toId you not to do that
unIess you want to.
Just because I'm giving doesn't mean
I can expect a man to Iift a finger for me.
If she were aIive, Betty Friedan
wouId appIaud your IittIe epiphany.
If Kafka were aIive, he'd say:
''Stop misinterpreting my noveIs,
you pretentious bonehead!''
Hey, again.
Hi.
I eat here every night.
I've never seen you come in.
You eat in the student center every night?
There's Iike 20 restaurants on every bIock.
Yeah, I don't know New York that weII.
You shouId do some expIoring.
It's the best city in the universe.
See you.
-Where are you going?
-Job interview.
-I'II waIk you.
-Okay.
I don't see why AIcott
wouIdn't Iet you go pass-faiI.
RuIes are ruIes, right? What can he do?
Say, do you know this group EvercIear?
-Are you kidding? They're my favorite.
-They are?
I Iove seIf-Ioathing compIaint-rock
you can dance to.
You want to see them tonight?
I've got two tickets I came across.
Shut up!
But you know, I got these three interviews.
But there's an opening act, right?
Yeah. There's an opening act.
Can I meet you there at 9:30?
9:30 wouId be great.
But here.
Why don't you take one,
and if your interviews go Iong--
I couId just meet you inside.
Thanks.
Now, don't go scaIping that.
Okay.
Why did you ask me?
You hardIy know me.
Sure I do. I know you're smart.
You care when peopIe bang up their knees.
You don't waste money on food
when you can get free honey.
You're cute.
You take a train from somewhere, right?
The Number 6. I know that.
AII right.
AII right, I'II meet you there.
PauI.
I'm Dora.
-I'II see you, PauI.
-Yeah, I'II see you, Dora.
Dust.
When did O'Brien die?
-After you Ieft.
-Before the crackdown.
First they changed the dorm code.
Then we got our idea
which we thought Noah toId you.
My bad.
I feeI awfuI I never got to know him better.
Yeah, that wouId've saved him.
I'II never forget how weird it feIt...
...when I Iooked out the window
and I see this body go by.
-I thought he was in a coma.
-Yeah. He feII into a coma.
Come check out my Iighting design.
Look at this. You ready?
Lighting changes the party decor entireIy.
Pretty extravagant.
Women expect you to set the mood.
We're not in high schooI anymore.
What about in here?
That's the operating room. Not in there.
I'm going to go grab a sIice.
Want to come?
-Sure.
-Let's go.
-Look what I found.
-Come on.
That's for the animaIs.
You don't need fIea medication, do you?
I don't know.
He has sIept with a Iot of dogs.
AII right, come on.
-What's this?
-An appIication for the night shift job.
-Where you get this?
-From the guy who was just here.
Night shift is dangerous.
We can't have girIs.
This is the third time this has happened.
Why don't you say so in your ad?
-He shouId not have given you.
-I don't know if that's even IegaI.
ActuaIIy, it's not. It's in vioIation
of sexuaI discrimination Iaws.
-CaII next week.
-Yeah, right.
Thanks for trying to heIp out.
It's disgusting the way women get treated.
I just wish they didn't waste my time.
Do you have pIans tonight?
There's a great fundraiser.
It's bIowing off the hook.
I have a date,
but it doesn't start for 45 minutes.
Come drop by. It's for a good cause.
HomeIess animaI sheIter.
I don't have any funds to donate.
It's okay. Just come in out of the coId
untiI your date.
Okay. But onIy if I can heIp you carry that.
What's up, man? How's it going?
Hey, how are you?
You Iook amazing. I Iike this very much.
That's very nice. Come in.
So, how've you been?
What a turnout, huh?
I don't know how I'II find my date.
Excuse me. I'II take a T-shirt.
You know what? I'II take two.
It's just juice. Drink it up.
You Iook a IittIe dehydrated.
It's good. It's got juices and cranberry.
Do you know cranberry juice is good
for your urinary tract?
-What time is it?
-It's earIy.
So, which do you Iike better,
yeIIow or checks?
Why?
Because I want to know which kind of cab
to caII when we're done.
Dude, come here. Come here.
You got to heIp me. Lisa is aII primed,
but her heIpfuI friend, fat Rita...
...wiII take her home
unIess she gets some action, too.
First of aII, I'm way too wasted
to be operating heavy machinery.
Second of aII, I got this IittIe spinner
aII G-ed out. She's Iiquid.
Leave her on the back burner.
Take one for the team.
You owe me one.
-Count on it.
-AII right.
Where's the bathroom?
I don't feeI so good.
-What is it? Your head?
-No, it's my stomach.
Here, this'II settIe it.
-What is it?
-It's for your tummy.
Drink it reaI fast.
That'II heIp your stomach.
Where is the bathroom?
Yo, Dora, where you been aII night?
You got to give me your number
before you go, okay?
Excuse me. This seat's taken.
-What?
-This seat is taken.
-This seat's taken!
-What?
I know. We'II move when they come.
Taxi, here.
Good girI.
How'd you get out of your cage?
Okay. AII right. Roxi, come on.
Come on, Roxi.
Come on. Okay.
You, up there.
Come on, party's over. Let's go.
Dora?
Perfect. Hey, Dora, come on. Wake up.
Wake up. I don't beIieve
in sIeeping together on the first date.
EspeciaIIy one you didn't show up for.
Come on.
Dora?
Come on, Dora, wake up. PIease.
AII right, I got you. Come on. Let's go.
I'm sorry, that's aII I got.
-What's her name?
-Dora Diamond.
-How Iong has she been unconscious?
-I don't know.
-What drugs she ingested?
-AII I found was beer cans.
-Are you a reIative?
-No.
I found her Iike that.
My friends had a party.
Nice party.
I got to put my glasses on because
itlooks like hair growing there.
And all Ron does is spray this.
Going baId sucks.
They say it comes from your mother.
-My mother's got hair, you know.
-Of course she does.
-Is she okay?
-She's stabIe.
We pumped her stomach just to be sure.
If she took RohypnoI,
she'II be out for another eight hours.
The probIem is,
on her student emergency card...
...she has Professor AIcott
as her next of kin.
You wouIdn't happen to know
where her parents are or if she's insured?
No, I don't know.
Did you caII Professor AIcott?
He doesn't know her.
And we can't keep her here.
I can take her. I'm her boyfriend.
-I thought you just found her Iike this.
-Yeah, I did. And boy, was I angry.
Okay.
Just fiII this prescription.
Am I a man of my word or what?
-What the heck went on here?
-I came by to heIp cIean up.
I suppose you don't have
any idea about Dora.
No, who is that?
The girI who aImost had
an OD in the bathroom.
-She aImost OD'd?
-Yeah.
I found her passed out
and took her to the hospitaI.
Shut up. AII right. Where is she?
Man, what kind of drugs
were you giving out here?
Drugs? Man, aII we had was beer.
You can't pass out from beer.
You can, if you take something
before you drink it.
Her?
What do you mean, ''Her?''
Adam found her at a Iiquor store
Iooking for a party.
Last time I saw her she was aII over Noah.
Who knows
what she took before she got here.
It's impossibIe.
Why is that impossibIe?
These are bridge and tunneI girIs.
They sIeep around to avoid the commute.
We were going to the concert.
She never showed up.
Come here.
I'm going to heIp you out with this, okay?
Look. AII right.
We're going do this again next Friday.
I'II hook you up with a nice girI.
The kind of girI that you deserve.
What wiII we do with her?
She just has to sIeep it off,
rest a coupIe of days.
-Okay, what about her parents?
-I don't know.
She put Professor AIcott
as her in-case-of-emergency person.
What's that aII about?
I don't know.
I'm getting out of here.
-You'II caII me if you need anything.
-Yeah, sure.
You can't sIeep whiIe you tan.
Look at you. You're aII burnt.
The tan is underneath. I have many Iayers.
-What's this genius pIan you've devised?
-Okay, Iisten to this.
We figure out which cIass
we're doing worst in and drop it.
Then we transfer into European Lit 101,
but it has to be Professor AIcott's cIass.
We dump a D and transpIant it with an A.
And why is AIcott
suddenIy giving us aII A's?
I'II make him an offer he can't refuse.
AII right. Quiet, you guys.
Hi.
Good morning.
-How Iong have I been asIeep?
-Since Friday night.
Oh, my God.
-I've been in your bed and everything.
-It's no probIem.
-Can I ask you something?
-Yeah. Sure.
-Are you on any speciaI medication?
-No.
-Did you have a Iot to drink?
I was at a convenience store
appIying for the night shift job.
There was a guy who toId me
about a fundraiser he was having.
And he brought me back here.
I drank some juice.
I don't reaIIy remember much after that.
I think somebody
sIipped me a roofie or something.
Boy, I have got to stop trusting peopIe.
You want some Iunch? Yeah, you do.
You haven't eaten in days.
I'm starving and I ate this morning.
When you took me to the hospitaI,
did they caII anybody to come get me?
No.
They said you couId go home
and rest a coupIe of days...
...and drink pIenty of Iiquids.
And you need to take these.
CharcoaI?
So I can start a fire in your heart.
AII right, that'II be ready in just a minute.
You just Iie back and veg,
as you young peopIe say.
And I'II read The Plague
so we don't behind in Lit cIass.
You know, I don't know about you,
but I reaIIy need a B+ in AIcott's cIass.
AIcott hates neediness.
You know how oId he is?
He's onIy 34 and he's been
a fuII professor for aImost 10 years.
He was the youngest
in the history of the university.
Is that going to be on the finaI?
I'm sorry. I shouId have toId you
that he was my boyfriend.
We've been together aII semester.
I wish they wouId've caIIed him
instead of causing you aII this troubIe.
It's no troubIe. I enjoy having you here.
Yeah, but I've been asIeep.
I guess it's a good thing
I'm easiIy amused, right?
Why are you so nice?
I don't know.
Hey, buddy.
Yo. 420, Iater.
Yo, going to see you Friday, right?
AII right.
Professor AIcott.
I need to taIk to you about Dora.
I'II cut you the same deaI
as I cut the others.
Sir, the thing is, she's at my pIace
and she had her stomach pumped...
...because she was given some drugs
and she's been sick aII weekend.
Her fiIe Iists you
as her in-case-of emergency person--
Look....
PauI.
Miss Diamond has kind of Iike this
schooIgirI crush on me.
You know how they buiId these entire
reIationships up in their head.
It's great of you to be concerned.
-Sir, you don't understand.
-No, I understand.
Okay, I understand. I get it. It's fine.
We'II work it out. Okay?
Sir.
-Good girI.
-Hi.
-Thanks, Dora. I can finish up.
Good girI.
Come here. I got to show you something.
What do you think?
I Iike it.
Kind of institutionaI, yet post-Victorian.
Very nice.
Wait, but Iook.
She's pregnant. We've got to Iet her out.
-She doesn't want to have them in here.
-She might run away, though.
But Iook at her. She's reaIIy unhappy.
She's got to find a safe spot.
Okay. Sure.
Come here, sweetie. There you go.
I found these on your desk.
Oh, my God.
It's aImost not Iike him.
I know he Ioves me,
but he's never committed to paper before.
How can I ever thank you?
-For what?
-For saving my Iife, for taking care of me.
You've been amazing.
-Wait. Where are you going?
-I'm going home.
I feeI better now
and I've got to Iook for a job.
I'm sure you want a good night's sIeep
in your own bed.
No. I mean, if you stay tonight,
you can get an earIy start tomorrow.
But I don't have any cIean cIothes.
ActuaIIy, I was just about to do a wash.
We can both wear
my extra-fashionabIe Iaundry cIothes.
What is this?
Mid-90s hip-hop for the heartIand.
My mother tried to heIp me be cooIer,
so she went to Sears, where...
...they take the guesswork out of
exposing underpants.
If this is aII you have,
then I think we'd better do a wash.
I'II change in there.
I'm sorry.
I was Iooking for another bag
to put the Iaundry in.
-I'II get you--
-Yeah. Thanks.
I'II get you a bag.
You didn't get it from me.
Then how did I getit?
What are you talking about?
-Is it burning and itching?
-What's going to happen?
Is there some.... Is there a discharge?
Suddenly you know all aboutit, don'tyou?
Don't peopIe taIk gross on ceII phones?
You'd think they'd be embarrassed
to have private conversations in pubIic.
-I hate peopIe with ceII phones.
-AII of them?
Yep.
I hate everyone in there because
can get the new Garbage CD.
I hate them because they can eat
whatever they want to eat.
I hate anyone who has time to study.
-You hate a Iot of peopIe.
-I'm a rotten, nasty IittIe person.
-No, you're not.
-Yes, I am.
Not having any money isn't ennobIing.
It makes you mean.
Yeah, I get it. That's why
aII the reaIIy nice peopIe are rich.
-So who do you hate?
-No one.
ReaIIy?
Yeah.
I wish I couId be more Iike you.
So how come you aIways wear that hat?
'Cause something Iike 90%  of your body
heat escapes through your head.
But you're not particuIarIy attached to it,
are you?
No. Not reaIIy.
Why?
-Come on.
-What?
-These beIong to someone.
-No one who needs them more than you.
Howdy, Miss Dora.
Wait, here. Try this.
-Yeah. Yeah, that's the one.
-Yeah.
ReaIIy?
Okay.
ShouId I Ieave this one here?
No, Ieave it in the park
for a homeIess person.
-After you.
-WeII, thank you.
Honey, I'm home.
-Who are you taIking to?
-The dogs.
-What about the kitties?
-Kitties, I'm home.
It's moving. It's aIive.
Come on, we have to hurry.
Here, put it on the heating pad.
And get some gIoves, okay?
I can't Iet it pick up our scent,
otherwise the mother wiII reject it.
-Oh, no.
-So we have to carefuIIy...
...cut it out of its membrane.
What I need you to do....
Okay. Ready.
-Okay, hoId--
-God, be carefuI.
-Don't poke it.
-Don't worry.
-HoId that...
-Okay.
-...for me right Iike that, okay? You got it?
-Yeah.
-I'II cut the membrane.
-Be carefuI.
We'II get this IittIe guy out, okay?
Watch the head.
Watching it.
-Okay.
-Be carefuI.
-PuII it back.
-AII right, I'm aImost there.
-You got it?
-AII right. Yeah.
AII right, I'm just going to cut
right underneath there.
And, okay.
Here we go.
-Here he comes.
-Look at the head. It's so cute.
-Is it aIive?
-Yeah. It's aIive.
Let's go.
Let's see.
Here. Come on.
Come on.
Now what?
We'II just keep it warm
and we'II try again in a few minutes.
I aIways wanted a kitty,
but my mom was aIIergic.
I wasn't aIIowed to have pets.
My girIfriend, Janet, she had a Siamese.
You have a girIfriend?
Ex-girIfriend. We dated in high schooI.
-Do you stiII see her?
-No.
She Iost weight over the summer
and dating a Iot more now.
You know how it goes.
It sounds Iame to someone in a Iove affair.
-ReIationship. Whatever it is.
-I don't even know what it is.
He thinks I'm too young or something,
so he doesn't want to have a reIationship.
But then he says things Iike...
...how he feeIs
we're the same person inside and...
...if he was femaIe, he'd be me.
But he said he didn't want
a reIationship with you.
Yeah, and that he'd aIways Iove me.
And he said he didn't want to be
in a reIationship.
Yeah. So?
WeII, sometimes when someone's
teIIing you something...
...they're trying to teII you something.
Right. Like men know
what's good for them.
-ShouId we try again?
-Yeah. Let's see.
She's Iicking it.
ToId you.
What do we do now?
Get some sIeep and I'II stay
to make sure she doesn't toss him out.
Thanks.
Do you reaIIy need modeIs of aII sizes?
I'm onIy 5 ft 4 in.
-That's not a probIem.
-I don't have a portfoIio.
We'II take your pictures free of charge.
What? I don't get paid for the pictures?
This is an agency. We'II send 'em out
and hopefuIIy somebody wiII bite.
You can take your cIothes off in there.
What makes you
so interested in Iithography?
I've aIways Ioved posters
and caIendars and stuff.
EspeciaIIy the way the coIors get put on
separateIy, then aII come together.
Are you in the union?
It didn't say anything
about the union in the want ad.
This is a union shop.
-Hi, I'm caIIing for the gaI Friday job.
-Thejob's taken.
Hi, I'm caIIing about the ad
for heaIthy girIs with good SAT scores.
Is this for some sort of drug triaI?
And what is the
foremost principIe of banking?
Remembering your secret PIN number.
Forgive me if I reserve my chuckIes
for when I grade your finaI.
-Guess what?
-What?
I won't have to Ieave schooI.
I'II have the money. I got a job.
-Doing what?
-Harvesting eggs.
-In New York?
-What?
You're going to be a farmer?
No.
I grow baby eggs and at the end
of my cycIe they take them out...
...and give them to infertiIe coupIes.
I get a shot every day.
I'II have enough money for tuition
and time to study...
...and I'II get my mom a dishwasher.
-What kind of shots?
-I don't know.
Like hormones and girIy stuff.
-Let's ceIebrate, okay?
-I onIy have $30.
It's on me. Come on.
Wait. I'm a student member.
I can come any time. It's aIways warm.
There's artsy fiIms and the paintings rock.
Thank you.
You know what'd be fun?
If we pretend we're reaIIy rich...
...and we can have
one painting from each room.
Okay.
-That one.
-Puppies.
They're cute.
This one.
That.
That? That's chick art.
Then I suppose you Iike this one.
As a matter of fact, yes.
What guy wouIdn't Iike a pIate of breasts?
What?
-Are you hungry?
-I couId eat.
-Wait, isn't that steaI--
-Come on.
Isn't this totaIIy pIeasant?
This has been the best ceIebration.
Thank you for incIuding me.
Ever been to a Broadway pIay?
No, but Iike I said, I onIy have $30.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Here you go.
You missed? Here, Iet's try again.
-You get it? You missed?
-No.
Don't they check the tickets?
No. Just pretend Iike we were
out here for a smoke. Come on.
How much money do you have Ieft?
$30. I can't beIieve
we didn't spend one cent.
-Do you know why?
-Why?
''The moon beIongs to everyone
''The best things in Iife are free''
-Don't you get whimsicaI on me.
-Sorry.
Where's the nasty girI
who hates everyone?
I don't know. I have fun with you.
-What's that aII about?
-I don't know.
-Look at how good he Iooks.
-I know.
He's so happy.
He's resting with his brothers and sisters.
You know,
we ought to start thinking about preschooI.
What time is it? I want to take the 11:50.
Why don't you stay another night?
You know, I'II just get a video and a pizza.
It's better than waiting
on the train pIatform.
-We'II just chiII in.
-You mean chiII out?
Either one. Your choice.
Yeah. Okay.
You caII your mom,
I'II go get the video and the pizza.
Don't you go anywhere.
Thank you.
Excuse me. HeIIo?
-What's up?
-Hi.
Okay.
Of these two...
...which wouId be good for me and...
...you know, if I was watching aIone
with a girI?
Yeah. There you go.
When Harry Met Sally.
CouId you maintain a rod
and watch BiIIy CrystaI at the same time?
Don't feeI bad. No one can.
The Piano.
I don't know. FuII-frontaI on Harvey KeiteI.
-Not good?
-No, that dude's a 90%  wiener.
-ReaIIy?
-Even on the smaII screen, that'II hurt you.
Here's your winner:
Simon Birch.
About a IittIe goofy kid with probIems.
Can't go wrong, you'II Iook Iike a stud.
And this is sexy?
Good for the girI?
Yeah, works for me.
Thank you.
Honey, I'm home.
It's so much better saying that
to an actuaI person.
Do you think peopIe said it before TV?
-HeIIo, PauI.
-HeIIo, Professor AIcott.
This has been the best day of my Iife.
Edward asked me to stay over.
It's going to be so amazing.
Isn't that great?
He must reaIIy respect you.
Did he know you were in the hospitaI?
I guess. He did get me those fIowers.
It's a reIief, because the pressure's off.
Taking these fertiIity drugs...
...gives me financiaI freedom,
so I won't be annoyingIy needy.
I may actuaIIy turn out to be
one of those Iucky peopIe.
What Iucky peopIe?
You know those coupIes that stay together
because they can't do any better?
Or those peopIe who are sad
and miserabIe and Iive aIone?
But then there's this microscopicaIIy
teeny group of Iucky peopIe...
...who get to be with the person
they're madIy in Iove with.
You ever consider being in Iove
and Ieaving out the madIy part?
What's the fun in that?
Dora, come on.
Take care of the baby.
How about some change, man?
No, I mean that in a good way.
And don't forget my Somalian beans.
They don't have SomaIian.
-Can I just get ItaIian?
-All right.
You sat so far away yesterday.
I thought you hate ceII phones.
It's digitaI. Edward got it for me.
I miss you guys.
You know, Taxi, Roxi, Penny and the baby.
Is he eating soIids yet?
Kitten Chow.
I printed this up for you.
It's about those fertiIity drugs.
Hormones that make you
produce more eggs...
...aIso make cancer ceIIs grow faster.
You shouId take a Iook at it.
-You Iooked this up for me?
-No.
I came across it when I was doing
some research, so I thought....
Do you Iike Monty Python?
The fiIm schooI is having a series--
-HeIIo?
-I think I'll do a dessert.
-Like a biscotti.
-With nuts?
Yeah, it'll be great.
-I'II be right back.
-Hurry.
Bye.
So anyway, I was thinking of going,
and if you're free--
I reaIIy don't have any time.
If I Iet my grades faII, I'm out of here.
I didn't get much work done Iast week.
-I'm sorry.
-It's not your fauIt.
I'm under a Iot of pressure, you know?
Right.
-If you change your mind....
-Yeah, okay.
-Bye.
Isn't it great how comfortabIe this is?
I have this feeIing of bIiss.
Do you feeI it too?
What changed your mind
about me being here?
Can we turn down the intensity
just a notch?
I was thinking how beautifuI you Iooked
whiIe you were quiet.
Okay.
What did you want to say?
I wondered what made you change
your mind about me being here.
I figured as Iong as I suffered
the consequences...
...I may as weII have you here mending.
Suffer what consequences?
As you probabIy know, I'm Iisted as
your next-of-kin on your medicaI records.
-I wanted to taIk to you about that.
-I don't want to discuss it.
Your fraternity buddies
want to spread the word...
...of a student-professor affair,
date-rape, medication and stomach-pumps.
-WouId you make me a cup of tea?
-Yeah.
-But I was drugged.
-Oh, it's fine.
They've agreed to siIence
in exchange for A's in Lit.
PIunge the tea bag four to six times,
remove it and squeeze in a haIf a Iemon.
And two and a haIf teaspoons of sugar.
PauI had nothing to do with it, right?
PauI, Adam, Chris, Noah.
They're aII my IittIe honor students.
Bet they couIdn't get through a copy
of Rolling Stone between the four of them.
Here.
Not in a mug.
It needs to be in a cup with a saucer.
PIease.
So they aII came to you together
and bIackmaiIed you?
I'm reading now.
Dora, Dora, hoId up. Wait, wait.
-You've been an inspiration to us.
-What?
We got this kiIIer scheme.
We want you in.
-It was Chris' idea.
-It wouId heIp us if we got a girI.
What are you taIking about?
This spring, when we pIan our programs,
we want to target...
...professors that are singIe, IoneIy.
For us, women, for you, men,
for more choices.
You know the driII after.
Once they're romanticaIIy interested,
you hint you're IegaIIy underage.
It's genius!
MeanwhiIe, we aII get fake IDs,
except instead of being 21, we're onIy 17.
-See where we're going with this?
-Imagine how high your GPA wiII be.
Just coordinate your scheduIe with us.
You guys are amazing.
-Thank you.
-Thank you. AII right, she's in.
-She's in. She's in.
There you go again with those books.
What is that?
Studying?
Good one, man. Don't forget about Friday.
What, you didn't raise enough money
at your Iast fundraiser?
We bareIy made enough to cover the beer.
But I got it in check. I scored some rope.
NormaIIy, chicks can drink six
to seven cans and they don't feeI it.
But these bad boys, one, and you're done.
CarefuI.
Thanks, dude.
So, Friday.
Can I heIp you?
I'm Iooking for white piIIs that come
in a pop-out package.
We have aspirin in bubbIe pack.
These have writing on them.
I'm Iooking for piIIs without the writing.
There's this.
-What do they do?
-Pretty much nothing.
-Any harmfuI side effects?
-Might make you a bit smarter.
Oh, my God. Are you guys taking Psych?
-Did you ever Iook in the book?
-No.
Look at this retard.
-What's cracking?
-I Ieft some books in the cIoset.
-You mind if I get them?
-Of course not. Want a beer?
Ever heard of autism?
Are we stiII on for the sheIter on Friday?
I heard they might be painting the pIace
on Friday. I'II have to find out.
See what you can do.
Otherwise we're up shit creek.
Okay.
HeIp us out, PauI.
It costs a Iot to rent a bar.
-Thanks, guys.
-Thanks, buddy.
Don't be a stranger now, buddy, okay?
Put your pants on.
Cover that up.
No need to argue, pIenty for everyone.
Just Iine up in an orderIy fashion.
That Iooks Iike a penis, but smaIIer.
Don't knock it tiII you tried it.
You got two minutes to cover it or Iose it.
-This sucks.
-I wouId've said ''bIows.''
Look at KeIIy and Gwen.
I sIipped them rope an hour ago.
I gave one to SheIIy and Iook at that.
Maybe girIs are deveIoping an immunity...
...the way pesticides don't work
on a Iot of bugs.
-Look how amped these chicks are.
-Great.
If this doesn't work,
we'II have to reIy on our charm.
-That stuff you got was useIess.
-You stiII owe me $150.
The stuff I had had writing on the package.
What are you taIking about?
This isn't them.
-Someone snagged our rope?
-Who knows where I keep my stash?
-PauI.
-Weak.
Do you see what's wrong with this?
The Greeks use a coIumn
to hoId something up.
Form foIIows function,
and it's beautifuI in its simpIicity.
This Roman coIumn is
incorporated into the waII.
I assume from your mocking tone
you have an opposing viewpoint?
No. But don't you ever Iike
Iooking around because it's pretty?
Pretty?
-Not everything needs a Iecture.
-Christmas decorations are pretty.
The cast of Friends is pretty.
This is a worId-cIass museum.
You onIy get what you put into it.
Sorry.
PauI Tannek to see Professor AIcott.
-He's in a meeting. Have a seat.
-Great, thank you.
-Peter.
-PauI.
-ShouId we go inside?
-What can I do for you?
Dora Ieft these, and I'm not sure
if she's supposed to take anymore--
Goodbye, Professor AIcott.
Thanks for heIping, Kristen.
Let's taIk in here.
How is Miss Diamond?
You know Dora. A IittIe goes a Iong way.
She's a sweet kid, though.
Keeps the pIace immacuIate.
You're Iucky.
She cares about you a great deaI.
That's for you.
-What is this?
-FinaI exam.
-The finaI's a take-home test?
-For you it is.
That's the deaI I worked out with Chris.
I gotta have something
to substantiate an A.
-What's the matter?
-I wasn't aware of a deaI.
I guess it's a good thing you dropped by.
Sir, if it's aII the same, I'd rather not.
Are you pIanning
on saying anything to the dean?
No.
-You're going to teII Dora about Kristen?
-No. I'm not.
I don't understand.
Maybe I don't Iike the idea of being bought.
-You couId Iose your schoIarship.
-I guess I couId.
Is this a moraI stand?
Is that what you're doing?
I gotta teII you,
I don't think that's very smart.
You know what?
I reaIIy don't give a fuck what you think!
What are you doing?
You stoIe over $200 of our medication!
You mean the iIIegaI drugs
you disperse at parties?
Are you going to turn into a narc on us?
No. I want to be Iike the cooI guys.
The guys who never go to cIass.
The guys who hit on girIs
who are unconscious.
AII the girIs want you
when they're straight.
-You're with that Dora girI.
-What is that supposed to mean?
There's no veIvet rope at CIub Dora.
Any asshoIe can get in.
You okay?
Good Lord, I am so sorry. Come on.
-Are you okay?
-I'm aII right.
Let's get that Iooked at. Come on.
Oh, great news.
What?
I know it vexes you
we never do anything together.
So I'm taking you to my parents'
for Thanksgiving.
-You toId your parents about me?
-Yeah.
I toId them my girIfriend's out of town
so I'm bringing my assistant.
But it'II be great.
-Hello.
-Hey, Dad.
Hey there, coIIege boy!
What's the matter?
You sound a IittIe bIue.
How's New York?
It seems Iike this city is one big orgy.
And if you actuaIIy care about anyone,
you're a chump.
-I'II go, but which cIeaners?
-It's the one on 8th Street--
Can you hear me?
Sounds like things are rocky
with you and Dora.
It's not Iike that, Dad.
I don't even think she knew
I Iiked her that way.
It was just so fun having her around.
I don't know.
Maybe I shouId come home.
I don't think I beIong here.
At your age, you'II get your heart broken
no matter what city you Iive in.
Yeah. I guess.
I just miss her.
God, it's aII so expensive.
''What we obtain too cheap,
we esteem too IightIy.''
Thomas Paine.
Why don't I make something to wear?
Maybe. HeIp, pIease.
If they think I'm your assistant,
I'II go as myseIf.
Dora, it's my parents.
I can't even go as myseIf.
That Iooks fabuIous on.
I'II start a room for you.
I feeI funny about you buying me an outfit.
Consider it a Ioan untiI you're weaIthy.
The cIothes, the haircut.
-A haircut?
-I made an appointment at BIiss.
Just do a IittIe shaping thing.
Okay.
Thanks.
Oh, thanks for the fIowers.
What fIowers?
The yeIIow fIowers.
When I got my stomach--
Don't mention it.
-Those just came in.
-Thank you.
-Let's get started.
-Okay.
BeautifuI there, huh?
Dora! We're going to a dinner,
not a fox hunt.
I just shouIdn't go with you.
I'II take you to CaIvin KIein.
Maybe they are more borough-friendIy.
-I had a IittIe scare today.
-What happened?
Dean HackeIman said
he wanted to taIk to me.
I was afraid PauI had informed on us.
Why PauI?
My ''speciaI'' students
got to take the finaI home.
BasicaIIy carte blanche to get an A,
and he wanted nothing to do with it.
I thought they were bIackmaiIing you.
That's just it. ApparentIy he wasn't
in on it. It was just the others.
He even gave me a discourse
on how he can't be bought.
-So what grade did you give him?
-B.
-Why didn't you give him a B+?
-It was a B paper.
Yeah, but his schoIarship?
He wanted that whoIe fairness thing,
not me.
When we get to my parents, none of this....
HeIIo?
Come on in.
I came by to warn you that AIcott
was giving you a B.
I knew that was going to happen,
so I dropped his cIass.
I can take an extra credit
and keep my average up.
Great!
You cut your hair.
Yeah, I did.
Got to keep up with the times, right?
I was kind of going for that...
...''George CIooney, my face is too cute
to hide behind my hair'' Iook.
It Iooks good.
What's with the pizza?
I reaIized we never watched
that video you rented.
So I got another one, and got a pizza
just in case you were hungry.
Look, Dora.
I can't just go around watching movies
and eating pizza with you.
Not that I don't want to.
You know, there's other stuff.
I know you're thinking,
''What about our stuff?''
And you're right. I miss it a Iot.
But I know AIcott is your boyfriend.
And to teII you the truth, I don't Iike him.
Not that that has anything to do
with how I feeI about you.
It has a Iot to do with how I feeI about you.
That's why I can't have any pizza.
-Maybe I shouId try that again.
-PauI, he's not my boyfriend anymore.
Don't you want to be one
of those Iucky peopIe?
I do! Don't you?
You can't waItz in here with your videos,
and Iooking aII cute.
-UnIess, unIess...
-UnIess what?
UnIess you mean it.
What was that?
A kiss.
You caII that a kiss?
A botched hairpIug operation
caused Chris to Iose his ''good Iooks.''
He hoped women wouId see
his other good quaIities....
Except he has none.
Adam was recruited
by a Iarge corporation
and setup to take a faII
for their shady practices...
He now has an active sociaI Iife... in jaiI.
Noah used himseIf as a guinea pig whiIe
trying to create a stronger party drug.
He's currentIy reIearning to tie his shoes.
Professor AIcott is serving 3 to 5 years
for having an affair
with a seventeen year-oId.
Dora used the animaI hospitaI
as her residence and got financiaI aide.
She didn't have to seII her eggs.
PauI has first dibs on them.