25.000
Slow down Siham.
-If they want Bashu's wool...
...I will get all the money, right?
-Oh honey, you raised him.
What do I buy? I never
had money before.
Oh no, he doesn't
look well.
They told me, I'd find help here in Mecca.
-And you have.
Siham.
-Papa, where are you going?
We can't just leave. We have to
take care of this man first.
But what about Bashu?
-Remember what the Quran teaches...
...about charity Siham. For those who
give in charity men and women...
...and loan to Allah, a beautiful loan,
it shall be increased manifold.
If we don't live by that, well then we
are all not better than the people...
...who used to
rule this city.
You know Siham, Mecca
was a different place then.
Hundreds of idol gods
surrounded the Kaaba.
And for people who were poor like
myself, life was very difficult.
I thank you sir.
I'll take that.
When I loan money, I
expect to repaid back.
Please, I need it.
My family is hungry.
You should have
thought about before.
Get him!
Welcome to Mecca. You've
all travelled so far.
Remember, be generous in
your offerings. Very generous...
...and the gods
will bless you.
What?
- Oh great and holly lshizar...
...now l'm giving you
everything i owe.
You are pay to polish
not to pray Sumayya.
It is the pilgrimage season,
I want these gods to shine.
O Mecca! They lean his kindness
and our virtue is like...
...a flower in blue.
I paid you, now give
me the answer.
Patience Suhayl. The prophesy of
the divine arrows can not be rushed.
Well chosen Suhayl. Go ahead with
your scheme to cheat the sword maker.
For the arrow say, you won't get caught.
- Indeed.
Thief!
Ah, you have good
eye for slaves Umayya.
Please set me free, please.
I'll take him.
Bilal.
Remember this. They can whip
your body, but your soul is free.
It belongs to noone.
You, out of the way!
Throw them again boy. But remember,
loose, and you become my slave.
No!
-Come on.
Thank you.
Get up and
get out of here!
Look at all these people. The most
successful pilgrimage in years.
Good thing that gods
are here in Mecca.
Some of these pilgrims
are'nt too bright.
They are paying twice
what the goods are worth.
No, no. It's true. We have been stupid
not to raise the price on everything.
What has become
of our charity?
These pilgrims are on a
sacred journey to a holly place.
We use to take pride in supplying
water and shelter for the people.
Now it seems we pride ourselves in
taking advantage of their devotion.
I won't listen to this! -Ease Abu Jahl.
Abu Taalib is our leader.
Yes. And he is my brother. But that
doesn't mean I have to sit here...
...and listen to
false accusations.
The pilgrims are dry up and
glow away if it were not for us.
We were ten times
what we take.
He thinks he can lecture us just because
his clan takes care of the Kaaba.
We must change our ways.
Carefull Abu Taalib, change
can be dangerous.
Little did Abu Taalib know that the
nephew he raised, Muhammad (peace...
...and blessings be upon him ) was
about to change the world forever.
For at that time, at the age
of 40 he was climbing...
...toward a cave
outside the city.
To be alone,
to pray and ponder.
He was troubled by all
the injustice of Mecca.
Slavery, the mistreating of
women, greed, gambling...
...the sacrificing of babies...
...and the reliance on idol gods
made of wood and stone...
...proper one god of Abraham,
Moses and Jesus.
So as he did every year,
he came to the cave. Suddenly.
He was surrounded by light.
When he looked up...
...he saw the Archangel Gabriel
standing before him.
He was speechless.
''Read'' said the angel.
''I don't know how''
was the reply.
Gabriel repeated his command
three times. And each time...
...the reply was the same. And
then Gabriel taught him.
''Read in the name of your Lord the
creator. He created men...
...from a clotted blood. Read, your
Lord is the most bountiest...
...who taught to use of a pen. He has
taught men what he did not know.''
And then Gabriel vanished.
Muhammad, (piece and blessings
be upon him ) shocked with...
...fear and confusion. He stumbled out
of the cave and ran for home.
He doubted what he had seen. But
on his way down the mountain...
...Gabriel appeared again and said:
''Muhammad, you are the...
...Messenger of God
and I am Gabriel.''
He tried to turn away but no matter
where he look, Gabriel is there...
...repeating his message: ''Muhammad,
you are the Messenger of God...
...and I am Gabriel.''
Once the angel was gone, Muhammad
(peace and blessings be upon him )...
...struggled for home.
When he finally arrived,
he was shivering.
He asked Khadija to cover him. He told
her everything he had seen and heard.
He told her he feared for his sanity or
that he had become possessed.
But Khadija assured him that God
would not allow evil spirit...
...to overtake a man like him.
Who had always told the truth,
cared for the poor and needy.
Soon after, Khadija went to
her cousin religious scholar...
...and told him
what it happened.
Your husband is a
Prophet of God.
The people will accuse him of
lying and many other evils...
...and he will be cast out.
Despite her cousin's warning, Khadija
believed all her husband had told her.
And she never hesitated in
becoming Islam's first believer.
And soon, others followed.
I keep hearing rumors about
Muhammad's secret meetings.
Please Abu Jahl.
- But he is teaching something. I don't...
...know what it is yet, but his adopted
son Zeyd has joined him and...
...so has his cousin Ali.
- So what? The rest are beggars...
...and slaves.
-But he must be punished!
For what?
- For teaching something different.
Look, if his followers were men of
power, if his teachings...
...were dangerous, I'd fall on him like an
ocean. But this is Muhammad...
...Abu Jahl, El-Emin,
the honest one.
For three years the Prophet (peace
and blessings be upon him )...
...preached in secret.
It was during this time Siham,
that i first heard his teachings.
I am not sure we should be doing this.
- You have to hear him mother.
We'll be allright Celile.
Insight, quickly. There is more tonight
than ever before. - Thank you Cafer.
Where do you go every night?
- To hear a Prophet of God.
What a feeling to learn
the way of Islam from...
...God's Messenger (peace and
blessings be upon him ).
His revelations, the Quran, offer the
most beautiful words we had ever heard.
He taught us all the gods of Mecca are
powerless. There is only one god.
The god of Abraham, Moses and Jesus.
You have to surrender everything to him.
There is no such thing as rich or slave
in the eyes of God. All are equal.
And the poor aren't to be put down
and despised, there to be cared for.
The Quran says, in the name of God
the merciful, the compassionate.
The most honored of you in the sight of
Allah, is the most dratious of you.
Woman are'nt possessions. They are
God's creations and just as important...
...as any man.
Respect them.
The earth is a gift from God.
Treat it gently.
You are it's caretaker. And
remember you will all be judged...
...according to your deeds.
Many became
muslims that night.
We showed our faith
with a simple pledge.
There is no god but God and
Muhammad is his Prophet.
There is no god but God...
...and Muhammad
is his Prophet.
No god but Allah...
...and Muhammad
is his Prophet.
You won't believe it Amal. He
says all man are created equal...
...in the sight of God.
- You have to take me to him.
I knew you would see the danger
of Muhammad's preaching.
Of course i see it.
He must be stopped.
You can not stop Muhammad.
-What?
Bilal come back you will be whipped.
- They can whip my body...
...but not my soul.
-Fine than leave your soul there...
...but get your body back here.
-What do you know about Muhammad?
I know he is a prophet. -Prophet?
You see, it spreads like a disease.
The gods will punish for
those words Bilal.
Muhammad says the idol gods
are powerless. -Powerless?
Powerless he says. A slave
says all the gods are powerless.
Now, what do all of you say about
Muhammad's harmless teachings?
Our nephew preaches
against us Abu Taalib?
We also believe in an allmighty God.
-Well yes. But we don't say all the rest...
...are worthless.
- What harm can be done by it?
Those who listen to him
are te poor and weak.
Not all. They have been
joined by Abu Bakr.
Oh yes! Muhammad's mighty
friend has also deserted us.
He is only one man.
- No! He is the first spark of a flame...
...that must be extinguished.
- Yes.
If Muhammad's preaching becomes
popular and our gods are abolished...
...there will be no pilgrims.
And if there are no pilgrims...
There will be no more us.
The Messenger of God has
sounded a warning call.
What? Is Mecca under attack?
-I don't know, come on.
Sumayya come to the Kaaba, hurry.
-Yasir quickly, come.
What's going on?
-I don't know.
There he is.
-Up you go.
You see the Messenger of God Huda?
-There!
He's about to speak.
And then The Prophet (peace and
blessings be upon him ) said:
'' O people of Mecca. If I told you there
is an army behind the hill come to...
...invade us, would you believe me?
-We would believe anything from...
...you Muhammad.
- You've always spoken the truth.
And so he continued: '' O people of
Mecca I beg you, abandon your gods...
...and worship the one and only God.
Save your self from the fire of hell...
...for I can not keep you from God's
punishments. I am only like the man...
...who sees the enemy coming and goes
to warn his people of the approaching...
...danger in order
to save them. ''
Our nephew is making a fool of us.
Stop him Abu Taalib.
Boo to you Muhammad!
Have you assembled us for this?
We believe Muhammad!
Is'nt it wonderfull?
- Do you believe this man?
Oh yes, every word.
He is leaving the hill.
Let's go join him.
How dare you betray Mecca?
-The gods are'nt good enough for you?
We will protect you
Messsenger of God.
How dare, insult the gods!
-Prophet?
Block arms, don't let
them hurt the Prophet.
Stay together.
Don't let them through.
You can not do this Bilal.
-If the Messenger of God no longer...
...preaches in secret,
I will not follow in secret.
What is this?
No, don't tell me. My slave
has become a muslim.
You may own my body, but my soul...
-Let me guess. You think your soul...
...is free.
- No my soul is also a slave, but...
...not to you. To God.
-That's where your wrong Bilal!
It all belongs to me. Everything you are,
everything you think, everything!
Say it! Deny Muhammad's words and
say your soul belongs to me!
Say it Bilal
say it.
There is only one God and
Muhammad is his Prophet.
Let's see what you'll
say under the lash.
They desevre it.
- Yes he does!
Deny Muhammad's words.
Bilal.
One God.
Say I am the owner of your soul
and I remove the stone.
Say it.
Punish him!
One God...
- Say it!
Umaya. I come on behalf of Abu Bakr.
He wants to buy this man from you.
Name your price.
- Allright. 10 gold pieces.
You think you've won
something don't you?
You tell Abu Bakr I would have taken 3
pieces of gold for that worthless soul.
He would have pay 100.
Despite the beatings Muhammad
continues to preach and make...
...convertes of our pilgrims. How?
- The answer is simple.
It lies on the Quran.
- What? His, so called revelations.
They are nothing more
than idle babblings.
All due respect Abu Cahal Muhammad's
revelations are neither idle nor bablings.
They are powerfull, simple. Not
of this world. - Magic?
lt's the only
reasonable explanation.
Well than, we must stop him from
using his magic poetry against us.
Abu Taalib we have the
greatest respect for you.
But time and again we have pleaded with
you to stop your nephew's preaching.
You have done nothing.
- He is threatening the peace in Mecca.
A few years ago he brought peace in
Mecca. You praised his wisdom then...
...Abu Cahal. Remember when the
Kaaba was being rebuilt. We were...
...about to kill each other for the right to
place the black stone.
But Muhammad came and...
-The point is this!
Abu Jahl.
- Stop him or someone else will.
Out! Do you want bloodshed and
fighting among Quraysh? Out now!
You can see my situation Abu Taalib. lt's
getting more and more difficult to keep...
...the peace. Please
talk with your nephew.
For the peace of Mecca,
l will talk to him.
Muhammad, close the
door and come in.
Please sit.
Son of my brother, Quraysh demand that
you stop your preaching. lf you don't...
...l fear l can not protect you.
l am an old man Muhammad.
l can not fright these people. My
own neighbours, my own tribe.
People, we have
known all our lives.
ls what you preach so
important Muhammad...
...that you and l
must die for it?
That there must be
bloodshed in this city?
For the peace of Mecca,
stop your preaching.
This made Muhammad (peace and
blessings be upon him ) very sad.
But he answered saying: '' lf they put the
sun in my right hand and the moon...
...in my left, l will not stop what l am
doing. l will continue until either...
the word of God prevails,
or l perish in the process.
Muhammad. Say and do what you
please, this uncle will never...
...abandon you. Not now,
not as long as l live.
l say we are Muhammad's clan and we
will stand by him and protect him.
No matter what the cost.
- Why?
Why must we become the enemy
of Mecca for one man?
Because he is our nephew and
because he has done nothing wrong.
The great Hamza speaks. Good thing
you are swift with the sword brother.
Because Muhammad is
forcing you to use it.
l am not dying for him just because
he says he saw an angel!
Muhammad continues to preach despite
all we do to him and his followers.
Please stop him before
he ruines everything.
He is coming.
He is praying.
Infidel!
l won't let you
overthrow our gods!
Here it is!
How dare you walk away!
Oh Hamza you're back.
- What is it?
Abu Jahl insulted your nephew. He said
a horrible thing in front of the whole city.
What did my nephew do?
- Nothing, he just walked away.
He tried pray here just this morning.
But l thrown him away.
Hamz...
If you want to fight someone
fight me you coward.
How dare you insult Muhammad when
l too am of his religion. - No.
l did'nt know you followed Muhammad.
- l do now.
Do what you must.
l know what you teach is true nephew.
l feel it in every word you've spoken.
That's why l can say this.
There is no god but Allah...
...and you are his Prophet.
Punish them.
- This way.
Where are you taking her?
Stop! Let her go.
Where is my husband?
- Nevermind that.
Deny Muhammad and confess
the gods or die! Do it.
No, no.
- Do it!
Say it mother. Tell them
what they want to hear.
Listen to your
son Sumayya.
Tell me truthfully would you deny
God and his Prophet just to live?
l...
And neither will l.
There is only one God,
and Muhammad is his Prophet.
Do you mug me? Than those
words shall be your last!
No!
The first martrys of Islam.
Poor Sumayya, poor Yoosuf.
- Thank God Ammar lives.
How is he?
- The prophet is doing all he can...
...to ease his pain. But he fears for our
lives. And says that those who can...
...should go to Abyssinia.
- Abyssinia?
lt's ruled by a christian king, a kind man
who might allow us to live there.
And l've been asked to lead the group. l
need some strong man to help me.
Go Malik, we'll be fine.
We better keep going. We have got
a lot of ground to cover before...
...they find out we're gone.
They could be in Abyssinia by now.
- Tell Halit to take some man and...
...go after them. They must be brought
back and punished so all will know...
...that rebellion will not
be tolerated in Mecca.
Here lies my most precious
neckless, it is yours.
Now bless me
for my generosity.
Well, excellent work. - l understand
you know the Abyssinian king.
l do, quite well as a matter of fact.
- Good. This is for him.
You will get your share if you can
convince him to turn the muslims...
...over to us.
- If anyone can do it, it is l.
lt's good to see you again Amr.
- All these gifts are for you.
Your generosity is overwhelming.
- You deserve much more.
l understand you are concerned about
this few who have emigrated...
...from your city.
- Rebels sir. They started up trouble...
...in our city and they will do the same
in yours. Let us do the favour of...
...taking them from you.
- They seem peacable enough to me.
They have created a new religion
which means to destroy all others.
How you answer?
- Dear king...
Bow to the king!
- We bow to no man sir, only to our God.
You see dear king,
anarchy allready.
l let it pass. l am
more concerned...
...about their attitude before God
than before me. Continue.
Not very long ago, dear king, we
were people living in ignorance.
Than God has sent us a Prophet.
He called us to worship one God...
...and to always tell the truth. He asked
us to love and care for our parents.
To help our neighbours and give to the
needy. He taught us that our time...
...here is brief. And everything
around us is a trust from God.
The earth, our bodies, we must take
care of them and we will stand...
...before God in a coming day
and answer for our deeds.
What they teach Amr is
the Gospel of Jesus.
No dear king. They do not respect
your religion. They say that...
...Jesus is not the son
of God but merely a man.
Of Jesus, we say what our Prophet said
to us that he is the servant of God...
...his messenger, his
word and his spirit...
...which he cast upon
Mary the Blessed Virgin.
What we believe
and what you believe...
...are like these
two beams of light.
Separate, yet coming
from the same source.
l would not give you up
for a mountain of gold.
You may live here
as long as you like.
As for you Amr, take your
gifts and return to Mecca.
Abu Jahl.
Couple of reach pilgrims thought that
they can out gamble Abu Lahab...
...won everything they had.
lt was'nt you two
l beat was it?
Abu Jahl's nephew Omar lbn
El Hattar has joined the muslims.
Omar? My...the great...my Omar?
Yes, Omar yes!
- No, not Omar.
lt seems he heard the Quran. The
beauty of it cleaned his heart he said.
l know just what to do.
Hear me holly gods!
We can't do anything to stop the
muslims, maybe you can help.
Oh shut up you drunken fool.
- Spread them with plague.
Would you ple... That's it.
You've solved it. - l did?
We'll threat them like outcasts.
Cut them off from everything.
Great. Then they'll leave here and
spread their lies throuhg all of Arabia.
We won't let them go anywhere. We'll
keep them right here and watch them...
...starve. - Starve? How?
- We will sign an agreement and...
...hang it in the Kaaba. lt will say that
noone shall sell or buy anything...
...from Muhammad's followers or those
who protect him. No one shall mary...
...them, no one shall assist them in
anyway. They will be as outcasts...
...to all of Mecca until Muhammad
sees the error of his ways.
Thank you Muhammad.
The muslims were cut off. Most were
afraid to stay in their own homes.
ln order to survive, they
fled to a nearby hill.
Thank you.
- l am sorry there could'nt be more.
l am still hungry mama.
- l know darling l know.
Papa can we go find Malik in Abyssinia.
- They won't let us go my son.
Do you think Malik knows
what's happening to us?
l sent a message
but l don't know Hadi.
You can't leave now Malik, not alone. - l
can't stay here while my family suffers.
That's all day's Ammar.
- Prophet's wife Khadija has sold...
...everything she has for these few
provisions. Still it won't last for long.
Who would have tought this
would go on for three years?
You are weak Messenger of God.
l know lslam teaches patience and...
...perseverance but you can't keep
giving up your food for others.
What is it?
Tell Muhammad...
...l will deliver his message to Quraysh.
- You are not well.
l am well enough.
l am sorry to see you are
not feeling well Abu Taalib.
l doubt that. lf l die the rule
of this council falls to you.
And than it would be easier to deal
with Muhammad, would'nt it?
Yes it would.
- Well than, what l have to say may...
...please you. Muhammad has
reviewed something to me.
lf it is false, he is yours to
do with as you please.
lf it is true, you will end your
boycott on him and all muslims.
What is it?
- lt is this; the boycott that you signed...
...and hang in the Kaaba
has been eaten by insects...
...except for the
following words...
...''In the name of God''.
Malik.
You have come.
- Mother.
Just in time to go home.
lt was a better time and
little season of peace.
Oh it looks wonderfull.
- Thank you Celile. Malik.
Celile come quickly. The
Prophet's wife is sick.
Khadija, oh no.
Go Celile.
She's gone.
25 years they shared. She was
the mother of his children.
The first believer, his friend.
We called this time the year of sadness.
Because Abu Taalib was dying too.
Come here Muhammad.
Quraysh asked one
thing before l die...
...that l will get your word...
...to leave their
religion alone.
We will not attack or preach against you
if you agree not to preach against us.
Than the Prophet peace and (peace
and lessings be upon him ) said:...
'' l will. ''
- Did you here? lt's over.
And quickly added: "All I ask is one word
of assurance from you. If you give it...
...all of Arabia and Persia will be yours.
- Speak then.
Witness with me that there is one
God and deny all the others. ''
Oh nephew l knew
when they brought...
...you to me
as a boy that...
...you were
something special.
And you are.
You are.
My day has finally arrived.
l am now your leader.
Yes. Well at name at least.
Call your self king if you want.
But don't ever
get in my way.
Good. Now let's solve
problem number one shall we.
The muslims.
- No, Muhammad.
l can't stand to see them pray
and walking around so free.
Peace Abu Jahl, where swords have
failed us, words shall cut deep.
Ah, our poets.
- They are turning the people against...
...Muhammad as we speak.
Even Abu Lahab is doing well.
Beware friends.
My nephew, over there has revolution
in his heart. - Revolution?
He says he is a Prophet. But what he
really wants is to make himself king...
...over us all!
- Make him suffer.
When Muhammad says our ways are
wicked, when he says our gods are...
...nothing more than silent stone,
he's not only attacking you...
...he's attacking your fathers.
He's saying they are all
wicked and stupids.
Shall we endure such dishonor?
- No!
lt won't be long before
the beatings begin.
Now there is no Abu Taalib to
protect us. And nowhere to go.
Bilal, right.
- Yes do l...
l am Barrah. l came last year with
twelve others to hear the Prophet.
Oh from Yathrib, yes.
- We follow lslam, with all our hearts.
You hear that, twelve
believers in Yathrib.
No, hundreds. The Prophet must
come to Yathrib, we need...
We can't talk now.
Messenger of God will meet
you on hill El Akaba, tonight.
Messenger of God, please say you'll
come to Yathrib. Our city is filled with...
...bloodshed, brother fighting brother.
Only you and your message can bring...
...peace. Say you will come.
lf you do, we promise to
protect and defend you.
God has opened a door
O Messenger of God.
The Prophet (peace and blessings
be upon him ) accepted.
And he instucted all of
us to leave for Yathrib.
l am too scared to leave at night.
-The Messenger of God does'nt want...
...anyone to know we are leaving.
- Why could'nt we leave with...
...everyone else?
- We could'nt all leave at the same time.
That would be too dangerous.
- lt's time.
Muslims have all gone. But Muhammad
stayed to protect those who...
...were left behind. Now it's time for us to
decide what to do with Muhammad.
Throw him in prison.
- No, exile the man.
Yes, yes. Take him to the edge
of the desert and drop him off.
Let him go. lt's out of Mecca
is'nt that what we wanted?
Not if he's going to build
an empire in Yathrib.
Well, what if we...
-Kill him.
But whoever kills him will be attacked by
Muhammad's clan and others.
Who will be the one?
- Who said it must be just one?
Take one strong man from
each clan and kill him together.
That way the blood of Muhammad
would be on everyone's hands.
Then, there can
be no revenge.
Good idea.
Muhammad (peace and blessings be
upon him ) knew what they planned.
And on that night he asked his cousin Ali
( God's blessings be upon him ) to sleep...
...in the Prophet's bed. Knowing
no harm will come to him.
He's there.
- When do we go in?
We don't. We will wait until he leaves
the house for his morning prayers.
Then...
As the night through on, the Prophet
(peace and blessings be upon him )...
...prayed. And one by
one the assassins fell asleep.
He went to Abu Bakr and
together they left Mecca...
...and hid in a nearby
mountain cave.
Are you all waiting here for Muhammad?
l passed him hours ago on his way out...
...of town.
- That's impossible.
Where is he?
One hundred camels to the
man who finds him. Go!
What are you doing?
Get out of my
tent!
Take this!
This way.
lnto the mountains, are you sure?
- l am sure. ln a few hours your 100...
...camels will be mine.
ls he in there?
l don't see any foot prints.
- He is in there.
There is no way he could have got in
here without braking off this web.
Or this nest.
You fool!
Later that night before leaving for
Yathrib, the Prophet (peace and...
...blessings be upon him )
looked down the Mecca.
lt was a city build
with memories for him.
Where his children were born,
where his wife had died.
He said: '' Of all God's earth,
that are the dearest place underneath...
...and the nearest under God and
have not my people driven me out...
...l would not have left thee.
No man can survive this
warm in the desert.
Maybe the reports are wrong,
maybe he was cought after all.
He was'nt captured
and he will be here.
He is coming!
The Prophet is coming!
For the first time we were
able to worship without fear.
The days were long and
filled with hard work.
But , we were happy.
Now be good with him, mind
your teaching. Come on Hadil.
l am going to stay here and help
papa and Malik build the mosque.
After your lesson. Prophet
says you must learn to read.
Hi papa.
- Hey papa, l am going to stay here...
Lessons first.
and bes...tow
plenty upon...
its...people.
lncredible.
- Can l go to the mosque now?
You may Hadi.
And be...
- Bestow.
Oh, bestow plenty...
For my children's teacher.
- lt's beautiful.
Messenger of God let me carry
that, you are the Prophet.
lt's time for you
to take a rest.
The Prophet (peace and blessings
be upon him ) taught us that all...
...muslims were brothers and sisters.
One community standing shoulder to...
...shoulder in prayer. And he
wrote document declaring...
...all people in Yathrib would
live as equals in peace...
...regardless of race or religion.
Look.
What is it?
- He's calling us to prayer.
Mama, are we the happiest
people who ever lived?
What do you think?
l think....yes...
...because...
Yathrib was renamed the city
of the Prophet, El Medina.
That's it.
Everything the muslims left
behind has been accounted for.
Good. We'll take it all in our caravan to
Damascus and trade every last scrap...
...of it. lt belongs
to us now.
They have taken all of our possessions.
And after they sell them in Damascus...
...they'll be on their way back to
Mecca with baskets full of gold.
They continue to cut off trade to us
and we are starving again.
O Messenger of God, l know
you hate violence but...
And then The Prophet (peace and
blessings be upon him ) said:...
'' We will go out and
meet the caravan...
...and take back
what is ours. ''
Muhammad has left Medina with
300 men to take this caravan.
Ride to Mecca. Tell them to send an
army as fast as they can to protect...
...these riches.
Turn here and take the
sea root back home.
Our army leaves this morning and
you are going to fight in my place.
l won't do it!
- Fight for me and l'll consider your...
...dept paid. Refuse, l will
kill you here on this spot.
l....
What's this?
Finally.
Abu Jahl is just two days
march from the muslim camp.
Tell them l am out of
danger and turn back.
But he has outnumbered
three to one.
Not good enough!
Not against Muhammad.
Tell him to turn
back to Mecca.
By all the gods l have not
come this far to turn back!
No, not until
Muhammad is dead!
When The Prophet (peace and blessings
be upon him ) found out we were no...
...longer facing 30 armed
escorts, but an entire army...
...he called for sura, a
council of his people.
l guess l am the last to speak.
Whatever you choose, we will do.
Then The Prophet (peace and blessings
be upon him ) said: '' Go forward full...
...of faith. Or God has
promised either the caravan...
...or victory on the battlefield. ''
They met the Meccan army
at the wells of Bedir.
Have my spears ready, stay close to
me. And above all, help me find Bilal.
The battle began
according to tradition.
Hamza took up his sword
and called two to join him.
'' Ubayda, Ali. ''
For Mecca and the gods!
They fight like lions.
Bilal.
Umayya.
Sound the retreat.
They are running!
Abu Lahab.
- You've returned.
l have paid my dept.
One last thing you should know, God
fights on the side of your nephew.
Help me. Noone
will help me?
Please.
That fool! ldiot l told him to turn back!
- We'll get another chance.
That's not the point.
We lost our first chance.
Now they think God
fights on their side.
Mark my words, it will be near
impossible to bring him down.
He's only a man.
- No! You're only a man. His kind...
...comes around much once. As the
gods are our witness...
...every scrap of this gold
will be used against him.
We'll buy weapons and horses.
l will show Muhammad...
...who's power is greater.
Mecca has raised an army
of 3000. And they are coming.
We are only 700.
After consultation with Prophet (peace
and blessings be upon him ) declared:
'' We will meet the approaching
enemy at the mountain of Uhud. ''
We are ready
Messenger of God.
The Prophet says you must not leave
this hill whether we're winning or losing.
You must not let them
attack from the rear.
Muhammad.
Hamza!
They killed Hamza.
The Meccans are falling back.
What are you doing?
Fight. Fight!
Stop! Turn back and fight!
They are breaking wings.
We have to retreat.
- No, not yet. Look.
Where are you going?
- To help fight.
No, The Prophet says stay put.
- But they are running away.
To the battlefield!
Stop!
Now!
No!
Turn and fight!
Attack!
Look out!
Muhammad is dead!
No!
Stay with us O
Messenger of God.
Surround him, take
him to the hill. Retreat!
lt's all gone wrong.
ls Muhammad dead?
- l saw him fall my self.
Hear me!
Today is in return for Bedir.
Today our gods have won.
Our dead are in paradise.
Yours are in hell fire!
Believe what you wish. So long
as Muhammad is dead.
Muhammad lives!
Then let him live to know this. For
everyone of our man who died...
...today, we have
killed 4 of yours.
Muhammad lives?
This is the glory Mecca
was meant to have.
Finish your sacrifices and
come out Abu Sufyan.
You are the one
who got us here.
Muhammad lives.
- So what? He's lost Hamza and so...
...many others. Come,
join the celebration.
How dare anyone accept the glory?
When these two words...
...can still be spoken!
Muhammad lives!
Then it is settled. This is no longer a
battle between the muslims...
...and Mecca alone, no. Every
tribe leader pledges no rest...
...until all of Arabia is against
Muhammad, until the words...
...''Muhammad lives'' become
Muhammad is known over.
Islam is through.
Not will be left alive.
l will give all of l have to
put an end to Muhammad.
10000?
We've defeated armies twice our sizes,
four times our sizes. But 10000?
There is no way we can keep them out.
They'll divide and come at us from all...
...directions.
- What do you say Messenger of God?
ln Persia, when we feared
attack led by horseman...
...we dug a trench
around us.
What is this?
Such a thing has never been done.
Not in all of Arabia.
l say we wait.
- Find the narrowest section and...
...lead your men over.
Now!
Keep trying!
- Sir...
Keep trying at one place and fill
in the blasted thing in another.
30 days we've tried. The
troops are loosing heart.
Talk with tem then. You are a man
of words, get them excited.
Whip them into a frenzy.
That won't do!
They think God is
with the muslims.
Very well then. Prepare for
one last all-out attack.
At dawn, from all sides. We'll take
them by sheer numbers.
God willing, only a few of their
soldiers will clear the trench.
And we'll handle them before
they get in the city.
But, if they do
enter the streets...
Would you drop these from the windows.
- Yes.
Oh Cahab, l am so scared.
- Don't be. lf we die, we'll be...
...together in paradise.
Barricade the door after we go.
Now is the time to prove
that thou art mighty.
Muhammad also prayed (peace
and blessings be upon him ).
God, revealer of the Book,
caller to account.
Whatever the power it is the
protects Muhammad, overcome it.
Turn the confederates to flight.
And show these muslims once and
for all thy power reign supreme.
Turn them to flight and
cause them to quake.
Men of Arabia!
Hold your ground, it will pass.
Hold your ground!
Back to Mecca.
God has saved us.
One day, The Prophet (peace and
blessings be upon him ) looked at us...
...and said: '' l dreamed that l enter the
Kaaba with it's key in my hand. ''
We shall journey to Mecca
for the pilgrimage...
...and worship at
the holly Kaaba.
He's coming here?
Without weapons?
He knows we can't crash
our peacefull pilgrimage.
All of Arabia will
rise up against us.
Blast him!
Blast Muhammad!
There is nothing we can do.
Let them in.
What? Bear the shame of
let in Muhammad worship in Mecca.
lt's over. lt's over.
l am sending Suhayl. l will
let him promise the world.
But the muslims
will not enter Mecca.
We suggest a compromise.
A peace treaty.
We promise not to attack any of your
people and you'll promise the same.
For ten years.
We will be allowed to enter Mecca,
worship at the Kaaba?
Most definitely.
Starting next year.
You came back without
even entering Mecca?
But we will next year.
- And every year after that.
For ten years.
- For three days at a a time.
Do have ten years of peace.
Ten years.
Yes. The message of Islam
can travel far in ten years.
Amr?
- Why are you going to Medina?
To see Muhammad.
For what reason?
What reason!
To become a muslim.
l thought you were coming to kill him.
- You ment to defend him?
How can we deny it any longer?
He is God's Prophet.
l bare witness that there
is no god but God...
...and you are
his Messenger.
And l bare witness that there
is no god but Allah...
...and you Muhammad
are his Messenger.
Many muslims
have been killed.
They have broken the treaty.
The Prophet (peace and
blessings be upon him ) decided,...
'' lt's time to return to Mecca.''
- Yes Messenger of God.
We are ready Messenger of God.
-On to Mecca!
Now they are the army of 10000 with
our greatest leader is at their head.
Hold! Stop where you are!
-l've come to speak with Muhammad.
Show your hands.
No! lt would be foolish of
me to trying hurt him now.
That never stopped you before.
- l come in peace.
You can't blame these men. Naturally
they are concerned. - Yes.
Forgive us. We have
been cruel and unjust...
...we have stolen,
tortured, killed.
We will not, can not
resist you any longer.
The Prophet (peace and
blessings be upon him ) said:
'' There will be no
executions, no purchase.
Mecca will be healed
by the spirit of Islam.
l am certain it will. And
i too must witness...
...that there is
no god but God.
And that you Muhammad,
are his Prophet.
l'll prepare the city.
l am glad that despite
my best efforts l can say...
...''Muhammad lives''.
From rulers to the
simple robes of Islam...
...may it always be so.
You are free forever now my
friend, with body and soul.
Home at last.
- Thanks to God.
l'll never forget
the feeling of that day.
lt was filled with
indescribable joy.
A few years later in Medina
after a short illness...
...The Prophet (peace and
blessings be upon him ) died.
He was 63. He always lived
a simple and humble life...
...giving everything
he had to the poor.
l wish l had met The Prophet.
l wish l had heard him speak.
Yes. But the words
of God live on.
Where will you go now?
- l don't know.
l know. Maybe you can stay
here and work in Mecca.
What kind of
working you do?
lt's beautiful.
- l used to have a loom like yours...
...but l lost it,
l lost everything.
lf he had some wool, he could
use our loom don't you think?
Yes, yes he could.
Sir, you could have Bashu's wool.
- No, it belongs to you.
No it belongs to you now.
Come on, we'll take him
to the market together.