We have with us today a man who
is so much a part of the culture...
that he scarcely needs
an introduction.
Pootie Tang.
Good to have you here with us.
Sepatown.
You've had incredible success...
and you've had it
in a variety of fields--
music, films,
martial arts, pottery.
How do you do it?
Well, Bob, I'm a pone toni.
- Got my dillies on a peppatain.
- I hear that.
Now, Pootie, a lot of young artists
say that you are their inspiration.
Well, I can't say
the nay-no, my brother.
Wa-da-tah.
You got a new movie
coming out, right?
Yeah. Yes, it's called
Sine Your Pitty on the Runny Kine.
- And who's in it besides yourself?
- Oh, well, there's Trucky...
Bad Bitty, Dirty Dee...
Lacey, J B...
Biggie Shorty
and Robert Vaughn.
- You have a clip to show us?
- Yeah, baby.
All right, let's take
a look then at this clip...
from Pootie Tang's new movie,
Sine Your Pitty on the Runny Kine.
It was the year 2001.
It was the best of times.
It was the worst of times.
The big city was thriving,
but the inner city was dying.
Who was killing it?
This man. Dick Lecter.
The head
of corporate America.
But the people had hope because
they knew that there was one man...
who could fight the power.
One man who could stop
the madness.
One man who could beat
Dick Lecter like the LAPD.
And that man--
that man was Pootie Tang.
See that guy? That's Bad Bitty.
The baddest drug dealer
in town.
Hey, Bad Bitty,
here comes Dirty Dee.
Dirty bastard!
That's Dirty Dee,
the dirtiest dude around.
He handles all
of corporate America's dirty work.
Next to Dirty Dee,
that's Froggy, the Enforcer.
Yo, Bad Bitty!
How you be?
I'm bad, Dirty Dee.
You're still dirty, I can see.
Let's deal, baby.
- You got yours?
- Froggy.
- It's dirty money.
- You got yours?
Right!
But how do I know
if they any good?
Let's test'em out.
Hey, kid! Come over here!
That's kid,
the dumbest kidin town.
- What you want, mister?
- Here. Have some of this.
- Is it candy?
- Told you.
Yeah. It's the kind of candy
that you smoke out of a pipe.
Pipe candy.
Capachow.
Yea! Pootie Tang.
You a baddy
daddy lamatai tebby chai.
Get that Pootie!
That's a canapan,
all the way down.
You mother--
Shut up, bitch!
Okay, I quit.
My face!
Run, Pootie!
Aw, hell!
Come on!
Get out! Get out!
Get out! Out!
Yeah.
No car wash.
No soap! No soap!
Sa da tay.
He's got it all
He's on the money
And he's maintained
He knows what he wants
He's got it all
He'll sine your pitty
And it's no thang
He's that Pootie Tang
Somebody's on the floor
It's another
smooth-talkin' brother
Everybody's lookin' at him
As he puts his tie down
the ladies on the dance floor
He's got the whole world
wrapped around his finger
A one-woman man
and you know he understands
Casanova with a fancy car
You can tell
he's gonna go all night
He's got it all
He's on the money
And he's maintained
He knows what he wants
He's got it all
He'll sine your pitty
And it's no thang
He's that Pootie Tang
He's hip to the core
Got a belt buckle locket
You know where he got it
He's a player by trade
And you can see him on the corner
doing business on his tippi tai
He's the C.E.O.
of his own world
He commands R-E-S-P-E-C- T
And you know he's
good to go all night
He's got it all
He's on the money
And he's maintained
He knows what he wants
He's got it all
He'll sine your pitty
And it's no thang
He's that Pootie Tang
Turnin' heads
Can't let'em take ya
Pootie be packin' Crys
and ladies be payin' paper
Let me see you
do your thing
Turnin' heads
Can't let'em take ya
Pootie be packin' Crys
and ladies be payin' paper
Yeah, yeah, yeah
He's got it all
He's on the money
And he's maintained
He knows what he wants
He's got it all
He'll sine your pitty
And it's no thang
He's that Pootie Tang
Pootie Tang was born in a small town
outside of Gary, lndiana.
And that town
was called Chicago.
As he grew...
everyone noticed something different
about the way Pootie would talk.
It baffled everyone--
doctors, scientists.
Let me break it down
to you like this.
Pootie Tang is, was
and will always be...
too cool for words.
Pootie Tang was
the most popular kidin town.
We didn't always know
what he was saying...
but we always knew
what he meant.
Like I knew I was his best friend.
That's me. Trust me.
Yeah, he had
a special effect on people...
especially on the ladies.
Not girls. Grown-ass women.
- Hiya, Pootie Tang.
- I'm a tine cappy, my damie.
- All right, Pootie Tang.
- But for some of the ladies...
Pootie was just
too hot to handle.
Damn you, Pootie Tang!
I can't take no more of this!
Who do you think you are,
treatin' me this way?
I've had it with you! You hear me
talkin' to you with your nappy head!
This is it!
I'm finished with you!
Get out of my life,
Pootie Tang!
You think I'm jokin'?
Take your shit!
Take your shit and get out,
Pootie Tang! I'm sick of you!
Pootie-- Pootie, don't go.
Pootie Tang
was an only child.
His father, Daddy Tang,
worked hard to raise Pootie right.
He had this belt.
He was so fast with that belt...
that before Pootie could do wrong,
Daddy Tang would set him right.
Don't you grab them peas
without askin' your mama, boy.
May I dane on the cherries,
Mama Di?
Yes, you may, Pootie Tang.
That's better.
You got to have respect
to get respect, Pootie Tang.
So, do you have any girlfriends
at school, Pootie?
Aw, Mama Di. There's a sine
tippi in a classi-ti.
She's a cole toni.
Don't you talk dirty
to your mama, boy.
Always got your head
in them girls.
You need to have
your head in the books.
Leave the ladies alone.
And that's the way it was.
Daddy Tang and his belt
was always there...
teaching Pootie the difference
between good and bad.
Now, when I say he was always there,
I mean he was always there.
Hey, Pootie, let's
steal some apples.
When Pootie was only six,
his mother died...
Leaving him
and his father alone.
- Pootie was very sad.
- I know, son.
But his father
was a comfort to him.
Don't slurp your soup
in here, boy.
Two weeks later,
another terrible tragedy.
His father was fatally injured
at the steel mill.
What the fu--
Gorilla! Gorilla!
It was incredible.
Only the third man to be mauled
by a gorilla at that steel mill.
On his deathbed, Daddy Tang
had Pootie make a solemn promise.
Pootie...
I know
I brought you up tough...
but that's
'cause I love you.
It's tough
out there, Pootie.
You got drugs,
crime, gorillas.
Yeah.
I ain't gonna be here much longer,
so I'm gonna give you this.
Pootie, that's my belt.
As long as you got
right on your side...
you could whoop anyone's ass
with just that belt.
I know
you love the ladies...
and Lord knows
the ladies love you.
Don't let the ladies
come between you and the belt.
Those were Daddy Tang's
last words.:
"Don't let the ladies
come between you and the belt."
But there was something
else about the ladies...
that Daddy Tang forgot
to tell little Pootie.
Pootie Tang
turned out just fine.
Daddy Tang
would have been proud.
Pootie had it all--
hit records, movies...
magazine covers, fancy cars...
famous friends, beautiful
custom-made clothes...
and ladies, ladies, ladies.
Through it all, I was right there
by his side. That's me. Trucky.
And that's my man,
Pootie Tang.
Big-time celebrity,
ass-kickin' crime fighter...
and role model
to the children.
Pootie Tang has a message...
for the children of America...
so you better
wapatah to the bammies 'cause:
Pootie says cigarettes and fast-food
burgers are bad like netatai.
Don't drink malt liquor 'cause you
don't need to 'cause you're okay.
Sa da tay. Also, eat
all your vegetables...
and don't bang the dillies.
That's Frank,
Dick Lecter's right-handman.
So what do we care?
We care because
he's making these.
People have been making PSAs
for years. Hasn't made a difference.
Eddie, hit me
with those figures.
Since the inception
of Pootie Tang's PSA campaign...
sales of Lecter burgers
are down 30%...
Lecter cigarettes
down 20%...
and Lecter whiskey...
almost out of business.
For the first time, somebody's getting
to these kids, and it's killing us.
It's killing us.
Hello, Mr. Lecter.
Frank, I have a job for you.
Yes, sir.
I tell you, man, Pootie Tang
is one bad brother, man.
That's J.B. and Lacey.
We make up Pootie's crew.
Pootie Tang will draw you a picture
of how he's gonna kick your ass...
then mail it to you
ten days in advance.
The picture
gets there, right?
You go,
"What the hell is this?"
Then Pootie Tang knocks on your
door, properly kicks your ass...
and you still won't know
what happened to you.
You got that right.
He is a kick-ass artiste.
Know what I'm sayin'?
He like the Da Vinci of ass-kicking.
That sounds kind of good. Pootie
Tang, the Da Vinci of ass-kicking.
Aw, man, Pootie Tang
whoop your ass so bad...
that you could
write it off on your taxes.
That's right. You got right here,
ass-whooping number one...
ass-whooping number two.
This here, you can't write that
off. That's just gettin' beat up.
I like to also add that Pootie Tang
can kick some ass too, boy.
Oh, here come Pootie Tang now.
Hey! Pootie Tang! All right!
- We was just talkin' about you.
- All right, Pootie Tang!
Pootie Tang, you going to Biggie
Shorty's party tomorrow, man?
I guess you're wonderin',
who is Biggie Shorty?
I'm Biggie Shorty.
Let me tell you
about me and Pootie Tang.
Since the very day we met,
I knew Pootie was to be my man.
I knew all I had
to do was wait...
and one day all that bullshit
would catch up with Pootie...
and he would be mine.
Hey, man, you going to Biggie
Shorty's party tomorrow, man?
Ranacan.
- We gonna party tomorrow, man.
- There's gonna be bitches there.
You right. You right. Respect
the women. Respect the women.
- Look at that car!
- Damn that car big!
And long
like an old snake.
Man, that car's so big,
it's got its own sky.
Yeah, it's big too.
- Keep it running.
- Yes, sir.
Hiya, fellas.
- Kinda hot for a hootenanny, huh?
- You hear that?
A hootenanny? What the hell
is a damn hootenanny?
I'm looking
for Pootie Tang.
Pootie Tang? What you want
with Pootie Tang?
I need to talk to him.
All right, look, Pootie.
I'm a representative of Lecter Corp.
Do you know what that is?
Great.
Well, Dick Lecter...
the CEO, mind you,
of Lecter Corp., he likes you.
He likes you, Pootie, and he wants
to make you a very rich, rich man.
I have a contract here
for Pootie to endorse.
Tasty Heavy
Pork Chunk Cereal.
It's delicious. It's a wonderful
product. Kids love it.
And kids love you.
We just wanna put that together.
That's a canapan
to the semachai.
I didn't even tell you
how much it pays, Pootie.
Twenty million dollars
to sign with us for just one year.
Oh, what do you say,
Pootie?
I got to say
the nay-no, my brother.
- Wa-da-tah.
- Wa-da-tah?
How do you say the nay-no
to 20 million? Why?
Maybe Pootie don't wanna sign
because he knows you're full of it.
Yeah. First of all, he knows
that cereal's full of sugar.
And number two, that's not all
that you guys sell.
You sell cigarettes, whiskey,
Bad Time burgers, switchblades.
It also says here that you will no
longer have Pootie doing PSA's...
telling the kids to eat
healthy and to be smart.
Well, sure, exclusivity
goes without saying.
I'm sure your ugly intentions
go without saying.
Take a walk, money man.
See, my damie, Pootie Tang don't
wa-da-tah to the shama cow...
'cause that's a cama
cama leepa-chaiii, dig?
Hey, Tang, to you, they're children.
To me, they're dollar signs.
Cover your grill.
Sa da tay!
Aw, man!
You funny, man.
You are a funny man.
You's a wild boy.
Pootie smacked the taste
out of Frank's mouth.
Oh, man, that
was funny to us.
But there was one man
who was not laughing at all.
Pootie Tang goes out there
and makes everybody love him.
He tells them
not to buy my products.
He steals from me.
And what do I do?
I say take my money. Here.
Take it. Fine. Huh?
And he says no.
I guess you're wondering,
who is this bitch here?
That's lreenie,
Dick Lecter's main squeeze...
and the most dangerous
woman on the planet.
Now, she don't look it,
but she can bring any man down.
I know what makes
Pootie Tang...
tick, tock, tick.
That's cool. All right.
Cut the drums too.
It's all gone now, Pootie.
What do you wanna do?
Lepa time.
What's he got on his mind?
We're starting
from scratch, I guess.
Pootie knows what Pootie do.
This is gonna be good.
Okay, Pootie, I'll play back
the levels the way you set them.
No instruments, no vocals,
no levels, everything silent.
Set it on me. Bleed.
Pootie don't need no words.
Don't even need no music.
We have got a hit, baby.
I like it.
Everybody seems to like it.
But right now I got somethin'
I know you all gonna like.
We got the world premiere
from Pootie Tang...
and you know it's gonna
be out of this world.
That's right. 'Causeyou
all loved his last record...
"Sine Your Pitty
on the Runny Kine."
Well, you all gonna
love this new one.
The new one is called--
So let's listen up to the new
record by Pootie Tang called--
From Pootie Tang.
Oh, yeah.
Damn, this is good!
This is good!
Man, Pootie done did it again!
Pootie too good!
Turn that noise down, damn it!
Legendary Pootie Tang has done it
once again with his new song--
Already considered one of
the greatest hits of all time.
- This was the scene earlier...
- Oh, you are so fine.
as fans mobbed Pootie Tang
in the streets...
many saying they hadn't heard
an artist this profound...
since AIB. Sure.
I love you!
Pootie was blowin' up now.
We talkin' big. I mean,
we talkin' "Macarena" big.
We talkin'
electric slide big.
We're talkin' Bentleys
and drinkin' Crys big...
girls in bikini thongs big.
Everybody want a piece of Pootie.
You think I'm playin'?
Here we go, baby.
Come on. Get up here.
Aiight!
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
We got Pootie Tang
in the house tonight.
Come on up, Pootie.
Come on.
I need you to sing
a song with me.
Beloved.
I love you,
Pootie Tang. Damn.
That's a batu shane,
my tellie.
I'm
Falling in love
with you
Because you are
my man so right
Tippi tai on my capa-town
And I'm
Oh, yeah
Thinking of only you
Because you move me
so right
All around my damie
I feel you
All on me, baby
I got you
I got you, baby
Whoa, yeah, yeah
On my clammy dees
On my damie kings
I'm a cry the pooster
Pootie Tang
up in this joint tonight.
I love you. I want you.
Oh, take me with you.
Please, Pootie.
Pootie, please. Please.
Wait! Oh! Pootie!
Wait!
Oh, Pootie, I love you.
I want you.
I love you, Pootie.
Please!
Don't leave me out here
in my lonesome.
Give a girl something!
It's not right.
She's fine!
Why did Pootie pass that up?
'Cause she's crazy. Look at her,
licking milk out of a bowl.
Oh, Pootie Tang, you gonna
sine that pitty Pootie Tang
- All right!
- Bata shane, my dillie?
Same as always, baby.
You come by tomorrow.
We gonna have a party!
Talk about
all the sisters and me.
You gonna be there?
All right, Pootie!
Hey, young boys.
Hey, look at her, man.
Pink lady.
Pull up, man. Pull up.
Pull up!
What you want?
- You want somethin'?
- Yes, baby, I want it.
What you want?
I want you to do
the two of us.
How much?
Hey, baby,
what's your problem?
Just 'cause a girl
like to dress fancy...
and stand on a street corner
near some whores...
you automatically
think she's hooking?
Wouldn't you?
No, I wouldn't.
I'm a lady,
you greasy bastard.
Oh, yeah! Pootie Tang
and his boys are here!
Yo, man, a Biggie Shorty party
is exclusive, man.
They don't let nobody
in a Biggie Shorty party.
They got a line around the block.
Ain't nobody in, man.
You know what? Nobody we know
can get in this party, man.
They don't let no light in.
They don't let no electricity in.
They don't let no water in.
They don't let no air in.
Air is going, "Man, I'm air.
I'm on the list. Let me in."
And they won't let air in.
And you know air gets in everywhere.
That's how exclusive
a Biggie Shorty party is.
You know what else?
It's hard to get in too.
I hate you!
Go, Trucky! Go, Trucky!
Go, Trucky!
Pretty girl. Pretty girl.
Where you go, girl?
Pootie, you are the sexiest
bastard on God's green earth.
- Yeah.
- I tell you, though.
Someday I'm gonna get me
a piece of you myself.
- Sepatown.
- Sepatown, my ass.
You gonna be inside
of a bed with me someday.
You mark my words,
you skinny, wonderful man.
Pretty girl!
Sexy!
Pretty girl? Pretty girl!
How does a woman
get to you anyway?
It's like a state secret.
How to bed Pootie Tang.
Get off him already.
He don't want none of your mess.
I tell you what, Pootie.
Someday you gonna meet
your match in a woman.
the Darth Vader of T. and A.
Some woman's gonna kick
your ass and love you to death...
and then you gonna be
lying in the Dumpster...
done banged to death
by the dark side of love.
And on that day, Pootie...
I'm gonna be there.
And I'm gonna make
sweet love to you.
Sexy girl!
- Damn, man.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought she was
somebody else, man. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, man. I'm sorry.
Damn. I didn't get
your name, did l?
Damn. Do I know you?
Do you want me
to pull your legs off?
- Pardon me?
- You wanna make out?
I might enjoy that.
I just might enjoy that.
I might enjoy that. You know,
Shut up!
Okay, wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute!
Look here. Call me a sissy,
but you need to stop, baby.
You are tearing me apart.
You're killing me.
- You want me to stop?
- Well, yes, I do.
Okay, then,
you tell me something.
- What do you wanna know?
- What's Pootie's secret?
I can't tell you that.
Now, I would never do
anything to hurt Pootie Tang.
But like I said, Ireenie knew
how to break a brother down.
- I can't tell you that.
- You can't? All right.
Okay, wait. I'll tell you.
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
It's the belt.
It's magical.
He can kick anybody's ass
with that damn belt.
Freeze, sucker!
Yeah. Give me your money,
you fancy pants bastard...
or I'll stick this
in you deep.
Wa-da-tah,
my damie.
Hey, I'm not your damie. Now, give
me your cash. I know you got it.
Hey, I told you to back off!
Pootie, the craziest thing
just happened to me.
I'm in the club, man.
I'm-- Pootie, look out.
Bang! Bang! Bang!
Pootie?
Everything under control?
Kayed a brother, di.
Kayed a brother, di!
I'm a shamey day!
Oh, it hurts Pootie
to kill a man...
but he knows
he's got to do it.
But it hurts him so bad...
to right those wrongs.
My man Pootie Tang!
Come back
on the bettie tai!
Come back on
the bettie tai!
Come back
on the bettie tai!
Hey, all right, my damie.
Why didn't Trucky tell Pootie that
he told Ireenie all his business?
Just runnin' his mouth.
I guess when you see a man
being brought back from the dead...
you forget shit.
Or maybe you just
a dumb-ass.
Stop the movie. Remember when
Daddy Tang told little Pootie--
Don't let the ladies
come between you and the belt.
Well, what Daddy Tang forgot to tell
Pootie was about his only weakness.:
ho's.
Even Pootie Tang's belt
was no match for Ireenie.
You can't beat a ho' with a belt.
They like that shit.
I'm sorry.
Did my cart hit your cart?
I'm so sorry about that.
Did I hurt you?
Oh, what a drag.
Again, I am...
very sorry!
Pootie, will you do
something for me?
Will you do something
for Ireenie?
Sign your pretty name.
Sign it.
Sign it. Sign it.
He signed it.
He signed it. Oh, God.
Signed it?
Nice job, Ireenie.
You're a damn genius, baby.
"I, Pootie Tang, do surrender
to Lecter Corp...
all the rights to
my image and likeness."
Oh, yes, yes.
"I will whole heartedly endorse
all Lecter Corp. products...
and will do my best to convince
the children of the world...
that the above mentioned
are all clean, safe...
and should be bought
and used by all of them."
No, not
the tippi tais, no.
No, no. You are part of the
corporation, just like us.
Thought you could stay
out of it, huh?
Welcome aboard,
Pootie Tang.
Are you looking
for something, my friend?
Are you?
I've got it all now.
Shocking news today as beloved
Pootie Tang has agreed to endorse...
several controversial
products for Lecter Corp....
the infamous
giant corporation.
Yo, fellas, somethin' on the TV
about Pootie Tang.
Even my kids, man, looked up
to him. You know what I mean?
They don't even look at Dad
like they look at him.
But now since he crossed,
man, my little--
my little man came up to me
the other day and was like...
"Man, how could he do
that bullshit, man?
-- that--"
I'm lookin' at him like, "Whoa."
Pootie Tang has made my children
cry. I'll not support him anymore.
Lecter Corp. effectively owns
the name Pootie Tang...
his image and all copyrights
that go along with it.
Mr. Tang agreed to do commercials
endorsing our sneakers...
food products and cigarettes,
whiskey, mace, switchblades...
rat poison.
Mr. Lecter,
can we have a statement--
You know, Biggie Shorty,
I got to say...
I always had a high opinion
of Pootie Tang.
But the way things are going now,
not only has he sold out...
he's scraping
the bottom of the barrel.
Pootie Tang was drugged
by that crazy-ass Ireenie.
- Haven't you been watchin' the film?
- And that's what disturbs me.
He's out there telling kids
not to go to school...
to eat fast food,
to do drugs.
This is not the Pootie Tang I
thought I knew and I used to admire.
- He would never tell kids that.
- You're in denial.
He's out there doing dirt
to his own reputation.
- You don't know Pootie Tang.
- I don't know Pootie Tang?
Believe me,
I know Pootie Tang...
and this is not the Pootie Tang
I thought I knew.
I thought a man of your stature
would have better sense...
than to fall
for no mess like that.
Look, this thing
has all fallen apart.
The man used to be admired
by people of all walks of life.
And you know what?
If the world is gonna fall for
this mess about my Pootie Tang...
then maybe the world
don't deserve Pootie Tang.
What do you think Pootie Tang
needs at this point in his life?
He just needs some
of my good lovin'...
and he will be all right.
- You watch.
- I hope you're right.
- I know I'm right.
- Yeah, we'll see.
- That's right.
- Watch.
- I will.
Pootie Tang was messed up.
- Punk bitch.
- Sellout.
- Look at him. Damn, Pootie!
- Get a job, you bum.
Get it together, man. Pootie
looked like who did it and ran.
Pootie turned to the only woman
who could help him.
Poor Pootie Tang.
That's all right.
Mama's got you.
Biggie Shorty's
gonna take care of you.
Don't you worry.
Gonna have sex
with you too, you know.
Finally.
Are you sure you
gotta go, Pootie?
Yeah.
That's a damn shame.
You were the best piece
of man I ever had.
You know, you could just stay here
and live between my bosoms...
for the rest of your life.
Pootie gotta flittie tai,
Biggie Shorty.
Man's gotta do, I suppose.
As long as you gone they can't
make you do no more commercials.
Where you going?
I tell you what. I got a little
farmhouse outside of Greenville.
It was my mama's. It ain't much,
but nobody's livin' there.
You go out there,
find yourself.
But then you come
back to me, okay?
That's a fine tine, baby.
Give me some of that bony ass one
more time before you hit the road.
Man, I hates prison.
Prison sucks.
I reckon it's supposed to.
You got somethin'
for me?
Oh, this some fine dirt.
This is some good dirt.
You know I'm
gonna hook you up.
Man, I hate
these bastards.
They make me shower
every day.
They never let me get dirty. I need
to be dirty. I'm Dirty Dee, damn it!
You gonna be dirty
again soon. I promise.
It's that Pootie Tang.
He got to be stopped.
I'm the one that's got to stop him.
Pootie goddamn Tang!
You gonna, you gotta
Thank you.
Pootie was headed to the farm.
I wanted to go with him.
- I wanna go with you, brother.
- Everything was all my fault.
Pootie, everything that happened,
man, it's all my fault.
- I told that bitch all about him.
- I told this bitch all about you.
- She just used it against him.
- And she just used it against you.
- I was sorry.
- I'm sorry, man. I'm so sorry.
- It was killing me.
- Only did it for the ass.
- Only did it for her ass.
That deri-teri was
all the dinie, huh?
- I felt like he saved my life.
- Pootie, man, I just feel like...
you saved my life.
- And I messed his all up.
- Now I messed yours all up.
- I wanted him to forgive me.
- Can you ever forgive me, man?
You my main damie, man.
Ain't no bad tammie
between us.
- I wondered if he meant it.
- You mean it?
- I'm a Baino Denny.
- I wanted to go with him.
Can I go to the farm
with you, brother?
Wa-da-tah!
All right! Me and Pootie
going to the farm!
I'm lookin' forward
to this farm life.
Enough of the city for me.
Yeah, this is just
what we need, Pootie.
Live off the fat
of the land, work hard.
Farming, farming, farming.
I can't wait, man.
I cannot wait.
We're gonna milk that cow.
Get all that milk.
Two percent, fat free.
Skim milk. All that, man.
Chocolate milk.
I don't need
no television, cappuccino...
partying all night long.
I'm want some blisters on my hands,
some sweat on my back.
That's what I want.
Shit!
Oh, man. My pants.
Oh, man! My damn pants.
All right.
Farming, farming, farming.
This is not the thing, man.
This ain't cool, man.
Dirty shoes, dirty pants...
dirty shirt, musty, stinky.
It's hotter than
a camel's hump out here, man.
And mosquitos all over my shirt.
I can't do it, man.
Whose dog is this dog
following me around?
Whose dog is that?
You don't know who dog that is.
That could be anybody's dog.
It's too hot.
You know you're hot.
I didn't wanna leave Pootie...
but I wasn't trying to hear
all that survival shit.
Outback, my ass.
I need conveniences, man.
On the other hand, Pootie was
lovin' every minute of it.
He was rejuvenated.
You hear that? Rejuvenated.
He was "juvenated" before,
lost it...
and got "juvenated" again.
Rejuvenated.
And when Pootie planted
his first cornstalk...
he was happy.
Too damn happy, if you ask me.
It was just corn.
But that was just what he needed
to take his mind off his troubles.
Rown on the crowny town.
Mornin'.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Not now, Stacy, honey.
There's a new fella here in town.
He's coming in here in a minute.
So?
So? So maybe you can
marry him, that's what so.
Aw, Daddy!
Oh, come on.
Cut that shit out, Stacy.
Here he comes.
Yeah. Hey there.
You got your can
filled all right?
This here is my daughter.
Stacy.
Dillie on...
my damie.
And she's a looker,
ain't she? Huh?
God, you stink.
Thank you.
I wanna talk to you
about Pootie Tang.
You mean Public Enemy Number One
in my world.
Right?
We learned that anything
can be addictive.
We took our burgers
and pumped them so full of MSG...
that people can't even
taste real food anymore.
Today American kids don't eat
'cause they're hungry.
They eat 'cause they just gotta
have another Lecter burger.
You see,
I own Pootie's name.
He's mine. I don't need him
to sell my products anymore...
because I've got thousands of them
all over the country.
I'm just gonna give them
the clothes and this training tape.
And remember, when making
a public appearance...
Pootie Tang always
struts like this.
Next week we're opening a brand-new
nationwide chain of burger stands.
Pootie's Bad Time Burgers.
In fact, the only thing that
could mess up our little party...
is if the real Pootie
showed up.
But that ain't good enough.
- I want him dead.
- Yeah.
I'd like to put that bitch in the
ground myself, but I ain't magical.
I been tryin' to get
that Pootie for years.
He done jailed or offed all my boys.
All I got left is Froggy.
Nobody know
where Pootie's at.
I know where he's at.
I got people
everywhere, baby.
Nobody can hide
from corporate America.
And as far
as how to beat him...
maybe this will help.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Uh-oh. Look at this.
Remember her? That's Stacy,
the sheriff's daughter.
He's been trying to get her ass
married since she was 12 years old.
Hello? Is anybody here?
Why--
I'm sorry, l--
Well, I made you a pie...
cake.
Do you want the pie?
I know I'm not pretty or...
or sexy.
You probably like a--
a sexy girl, right?
Baby...
I'm gonna sine your pity
on the runny Kine.
Now, see, that's what makes
Pootie Tang a real hero.
He can't stand by and see a woman
not lovin' herself.
He's gonna put the love in her.
Now, me, I say just give her
a compliment.
Hey, I like your shoes.
Have you been working out?
Girl, what you doin'
with your hair?
But I tell you what...
I'm only gonna buy this hero shit
but so many times.
Meanwhile...
back in the big city, all hell
was breaking loose, y'all.
I'm talking about
drug dealin', drug usin'...
booty shakin '...
too much damn TV...
drinkin', people eating too much,
gettin' all fat and sloppy...
fightin', kids out of school,
ain't nobody readin'...
people actin '
a straight damn fool.
And corporate America
was just lovin' it.
Look at 'em.
It's a party now.
Since he left, it just changed.
Everything just went bonkers, man.
Everybody lost their mind
and whatnot.
Pootie Tang,
you shouldn't do this.
You should come back to the city,
where you belong.
Back on the farm,
the worst happened.
Pootie Tang's cornstalk died.
And for the third time
in his life...
Pootie lost the only thing
that was important to him.
First his family, then his belt,
and now his corn died.
Farm life was driving Pootie crazy.
He must have lost his damn mind.
Look at him.
Down on his knees,
crying over a piece of corn.
Not even popcorn.
Regular damn corn.
Pootie Tang had lost all hope...
and it was gonna take a miracle
to bring him back.
Up here, Pootie.
Hey, watch the leaves.
- Daddy?
- You damn right I'm your daddy.
Pootie, what you doin'
runnin' away from your problems?
Did I teach you like that?
Hey, don't you mumble, boy!
Pootie, my boy.
Mama Di.
Pootie, you're a good man.
I'm proud of you.
You have so much love in you,
and you can give it like a gift.
Your father was wrong to tell you
to guard it like a secret.
- What was that?
- Shut your mouth!
- Woman!
- You corn-ass fool!
Teach the world
right from wrong...
but love the world
at the same time.
That's the key.
Where's your belt, boy?
You let some girl get your belt.
You let the ladies get your belt.
I knew that would happen.
Now you done lost
all your confidence.
I'll tell you something, ain't
nothing special about that belt.
I bought it at Piggly Wiggly
for 95 cents.
You don't need that belt 'cause
you got goodness in your heart.
Now you need to go out there
and take that and kick some ass.
Hey, don't you mumble, boy!
Now, go out there,
take that goodness...
and teach the world
right from wrong.
Now git!
I, uh--
I think maybe you and me
got something to talk about, huh?
I, uh--
I understand
you and Stacy there...
got to know each other, huh?
Had yourself
a little time there?
Yeah.
That's terrific!
Well, partner,
when's the wedding, huh?
Like I say...
I sure would be mighty proud
to have you for a son-in-law.
What the hell?
What you doin' way out here?
You know these guys?
I come to call you out,
maggot-eatin' bitch!
You ain't come one,
but many tine tanies.
Well, I gets by with a little help
from my friends.
Now, listen here, fellas,
we don't want no trouble here.
Why don't you just
move on through, huh?
- What up, Hop along?
-Just back off there, young man.
- I'm sheriff of this here county.
- Damn! Hold up! Hold up!
Rewind that. Go back. Go back.
Let me see that one more time!
I'm sheriff of this here county.
Oh! That had to hurt his ass!
I know he's embarrassed.
Slap him like a bitch!
Ooh, he shouldn't
have done that.
He done messed around
and got Pootie Tang mad, baby.
Come on, Pootie!
Question:
Where do you think you--
Wait! Hold up!
Hold up, Pootie!
Capa-town, my ass!
Oh, you not so bad now,
are you?
Guess you, um,
slapped him like a bitch, huh?
Yeah.
Now...
Like I was sayin'--
I was searching for Pootie
high and low...
then I finally remembered
he was at the farm.
All this time I had been
talking about the farm.
How the hell did I forget
he was at the damn farm?
Anyway, I got there
just in the nick of time.
Oh, Pootie, you got to
come back to the city right now.
- What's the dabble, di?
- There's a wedding going on here.
Man, they are using
your face, man.
They're making you sell products
even when you're not there.
I'm talking about cigarettes, man.
And look. Malt liquor?
Pootie Tang malt liquor?
They got all these Pootie-alikes.
You know what I'm saying?
Hawkin' all this shit.
And everybody thinks
it's you, man, really.
Come back to the city and let
everybody know the truth, man.
Come on!
All right, Pootie Tang!
I ain't the marrying type.
I don't make my bed.
I leave the toilet seat up
all the time. I'm a single--
Oh, but she is
a lovely lady though.
Pootie Tang and I are thrilled
to be opening this...
the first Pootie Tang
Bad Time Burger restaurant.
Right, Pootie?
Sa da tay.
Sa da tay. Got that?
Man, that ain't Pootie Tang.
That's Doodie Tang.
You know,
that ain't Pootie Tang neither.
I know it ain't Pootie Tang!
I just said it ain't Pootie Tang!
It's Doodie Tang!
Shut up!
Sepatown, tipi tais.
There you go.
- Oh, Christ.
- Hey, that's Pootie Tang.
Wa-da-tah.
Don't pay attention to him.
That's nobody.
This is Pootie Tang here.
Yes. I'm Pootie.
Now, clap it up, my hammies.
Rinatine, my America.
Coola may, my ca--
You think you've solved the problem?
Well, guess again.
See, I got more Pooties
than you, Pootie.
You're not only late,
but you're outnumbered.
And by this time tomorrow, there'll
be so many Pooties out there...
you won't matter.
He ain't alone, Mr. Rich Man.
I'm here too.
Bitch!
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
You looking at my ass?
You bastards
ain't going anyplace!
Bye-bye, Bad Time!
All right!
I got 'em, Pootie!
Pootie Tang is back!
I got to say the nay-no,
my brother.
What will you do now, Pootie?
We're gonna get married.
Yeah.
And that's the way it went down.
Pootie Tanggot his man,
and Biggie Shorty got her man.
But not before she handled
one little piece of business.
Ireenie left Dick Lecter.
She now works for the city,
counseling teen-ho's.
Dick Lecter quit corporate America.
He is no wan actor appearing
in the touring company...
of Wesley Snipes'
Murder at 1 600 - The Musical.
Dirty Dee is still dirty
because he is Dirty Dee, damn it!
Man, it is hot today!
Ooh, it's hot out here, man.
It is hot today!
You know, it's hot out.
Yeah, I just said that.
I said it's hot out here, man.
Yeah, you know, it's hot too.
Yeah, that's why I said it, man!
It is hot out here!
I know.
I'm just saying it's hot too.
Lacey is still
getting on JB's nerves.
And he's getting on his nerves too.
And as for me, Trucky--
- Oh, shit! My lasagna!
- What?
Oh, goddamn it, Trucky!
I can't believe you burned
that lasagna again!
Who I look like?
I'm not Chef Boyardee!
You've been burning things
since the day--
You know, that is the longest damn
movie clip I've ever seen.
But then again,
you're Pootie Tang.
Well, sa da tay.
Exactly. Pootie Tang,
it's been biddie having you by.
Bob, I dabe ba samie, my brother.
Cole me on the panny sty.
I'm sorry.
What was that?
Cole-- Cole me
on the panny sty.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Cole me down
on the panny sty?
Oh, cole me down
on the panny sty!
All right! Thank you, Pootie Tang!
Thank you, Pootie!
Oh, I love him!
I love Pootie Tang!
Oh, he's so sexy!
He's so sexy! I love Pootie!
Oh, I love you, Pootie!
Cut!
Pootie Tang got
three gold records.
Pootie get all the Grammys
because he's Pootie Tang.
- Yes, he's terrific.
- I don't think he's so great.
Uh-oh, girl. Uh-oh, now.
Pootie's got you now.
Pootie about to make
reservations on you now, girl!
Oh, girl,
the red phone is blinkin'!
It's over for you now, baby.
It's over now for you.
You know it's over!
He done got you in the radar, baby.
Pootie got you now, girl!
Red phone ringin', baby!
Red phone ringin'. Red phone--
Man's gotta do, I suppose.
I guess as long as you gone, they
can't make you do no more movies.
- Oh! No more movies.
- Let's do that line again.
I'm gonna sine your pitty
on the runny Kine.
We don't like no trouble
around here, you know.
It's a quiet town.
You look all right, though.
A little weird, though,
ain't ya?
That's my panny, di.
Well...
I suppose so.
Yeah, baby,
it's time to get dirty!
I can't hear a word you're saying
'cause I got earplugs in, my man.
But I'm gonna try somethin'.
Yeah!
Boom! That's it.
And everybody run away!
Run, run, run, run, run!
No, Pootie stays!
I'm gonna sine your kitty
on the sepatime.
Baby, I'm gonna sine your pitty...
on the runny...
Kine.
Man! Pootie Tang
done did it again!
7-0-2
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
Pootie is a shot-callin'player
Stackin' nothin' but papers
- He gets his mack on with flavor
- Always playin'
When he goes kickin' and clubbin'
or when he's with bb bumpin'
He knows the ladies
They love him Pootie Tangin'
And he's got this look in his eyes
like I'm his number one prize
And yet still he
maintains composure
So when you're doin' your thing
do it like Pootie Tang
He hangs for some time
We get to know ya
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin'
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin'
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin'
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
Pootie, you know
you're one in a million
You speakin'
what you be feelin'
And now you got me
I'm willin'
Wanna breathe the air
that you're breathin'
Shall we tell you the reason
I think I'm what you be needin'
Come on, baby, let's take a ride
Just wanna be by your side
Got a feeling like
it's my duty
To let you share my world
Just wanna be your girl
'Cause I like the way
you're tangin', Pootie
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
Boy, you kill me
Ooh, he's Pootie Tangin '
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right
If you think
you're Pootie Tangin '
On the dance floor, shake your thing
It's all right, all right