I grew up slowly, beside the tides
and marshes...
... of a Carolina sea island.
We lived in a small, white house...
... won by my
great-great-grandfather...
... Winston Shadrach Wingo...
... in a horseshoe game.
Last one around the tree is a ninny!
Joop, Joop! Come here.
Boys, boys! Careful, now.
- I'll race you, Tom.
- Wait up, Luke.
There are families
who live their entire lives...
... without a single thing of interest
happening to them.
Don't run so fast, Tom!
I've always envied those families.
Luke, mind you,
don't torment that dog.
It's my dog!
Tom, you're gonna step on him.
He's only a pup!
Here, Joop. Come here!
Mom, did you see me run?
Savannah, you want a bean?
Boys, you want a bean?
Quit squealing, Savannah.
You're next, Tom.
The child of a beautiful woman,
I was also a shrimper's son...
... in love with the shape of boats.
Luke, he's pushing me.
I'm not pushing her!
As a small boy, I loved to navigate
my father's shrimp boat...
... between the sandbars.
I suppose Henry Wingo would have
made a pretty good father...
... if he hadn't been
such a violent man.
From my mother, I inherited
a love of language...
... and an appreciation of nature.
She could turn a walk
around the island...
... into a voyage of purest discovery.
As a child, I thought she was
the most extraordinary woman on earth.
I wasn't the first son to be wrong
about his mother.
I am sick and tired...
...of you never showing me
any respect in my own house.
I don't know when my parents began
their war against each other.
But I do know the only prisoners they
took were their children.
Wait, you guys.
My shoes are falling off!
Keep up, Savannah.
When my brother, sister and I needed
to escape, we developed a ritual.
We found a silent, soothing world
where there was no pain.
A world without mothers or fathers.
We would make a circle
bound by flesh...
... and blood...
... and water.
And only when we felt our lungs betray
us, would we rise toward the light...
... and the fear of what lay in wait
for us above the surface.
All this was a long time ago...
... before I chose not
to have a memory.
Daddy!
I think something bit me!
Mr. Brighton, are you selling dope
to my girls again?
Stop bugging us, Dad.
- Bye, Mr. Brighton.
- Come on in. It's getting late!
It's a conch.
Bring him home.
I'll send him to college!
How do you know it's a boy?
Well, let's examine him.
Girls, have I ever told you
the facts of life?
Oh, no. Not this again.
Stay away from boys because
they're disgusting beasts...
...that pee on bushes
and pick their noses.
- Gross, Dad!
- That's completely gross.
Anyway, I'm not gonna stay
away from boys.
That's the spirit. Never do
what parents tell you.
Hey, Mom, look what I found!
If you don't quit smoking, you'll die.
That's what they told me at school.
Well, no more school for you.
Mom, Dad's smoking again.
Oh, no. Well, you know what to do
with that. Put it in the sink.
Give me a kiss.
I wanna play.
You look tired, doctor.
I'll fix you a drink.
That would be so nice.
It's been one of those days.
Hey, honey, it's tough work
being a saint.
Sal, can you get it?
Something smells good.
- Hey, Dad. Come and play with us.
- Later.
- Your mother, from her car.
- I'm not here.
Okay, Lila. She's coming over.
Why didn't you tell her we were
under quarantine?
She said she had to see you.
- Dad, they won't share.
- Work it out, girls.
She said it was urgent.
She was crying.
I can't remember a day
when Lila wasn't crying.
Be nice to her, Tom.
I hate my mother, Sally.
I enjoy hating her.
Don't kill one of the few
pleasures in my life.
Can we talk about
something else?
- Sure, what?
- Us.
I need a stiff drink
for that conversation.
Girls?
- Girls!
- What?
- Anyone want to sit on Daddy's lap?
- No!
- There's money involved.
- Okay!
I'm gonna ask you
a serious question.
- I want you to answer honestly.
- I know the question.
Who's the greatest human being
on this earth?
Mama? I've gotta develop
some new routines.
Come on, everybody. Pick up, now.
Come on, wash. It's bath time.
Gotta pass inspection.
Lila's coming over.
Lila, Lila, Lila.
Why can't we call her Grandma?
- You'll know when you're a grandma.
- I will?
Pick up and get into that tub.
How does bouillabaisse
sound to you?
Yuck! Can't we ever have normal food?
Do you think we could talk seriously?
Not now, Sally.
My mother's close.
Can't you tell?
The air stopped moving.
Sometimes I think what you need is
a good smack across your mouth.
Here she is. Sally, tie
this garlic around my neck.
Do we have to invite her for dinner?
She won't stay. You know that.
Then let's invite her.
Lila.
Hello, Sally, dear.
Those shrubs need watering.
Yeah. I have to do that.
- You're looking well, Lila.
- Don't be glib, Tom.
- Will you have dinner with us?
- No. I can't stay long.
What a shame.
- Where are the children?
- They're taking baths. Why?
I have some bad news.
They cancelled
your American Express card?
Your sister tried to
kill herself again.
You wanna make another joke?
- Oh, my God, Lila. When?
- I'm not sure.
She was in a coma when they found her.
How is she now?
She's alive, thank God.
I spoke to her psychiatrist.
Some Jewish woman in New York.
She wants one of us to go up there
now. I told her you'd go.
If she's a shrink and a Jew,
you can't go?
I didn't say that. I'm just not
entirely sure I'd be welcome.
Savannah will probably blame me.
My children blame me for everything.
Do I detect a note
of guilt, Mama?
Don't give me that
psychological horseshit.
Why don't you just say it? I'm
responsible for all your problems...
...including you not having a job.
Let's hit way below the belt!
Don't pretend you didn't start this.
I just can't go right now. It's your
stepfather's birthday this weekend.
I can't go either. I gotta
wash out Sally's pantyhose.
I'm going to the cleaners.
Why don't you get a job
as a standup comedian?
It pays better than teaching did.
Which was far beneath me. Right?
Beneath your abilities, yes.
What do you know about my
abilities, for chrissake?
Just stop it, now, the both of you!
I'm sorry you're hurting.
You wanted to talk?
It can wait.
Let's walk.
Tell me what you're thinking.
I'm trying to calculate the exact
moment everything got so fucked up.
I'm also worried the Braves
are gonna finish last.
I don't feel like laughing.
Oh, come on, Sally. Come on.
Do you know that this is the first
time you have touched me in weeks?
My life's a mess, Sally.
Our life's a mess, Tom.
Look, there's the Big Dipper.
I don't give a shit about
the Big Dipper!
Damn it, I care about us.
I care about why you keep
pushing me away.
I thought you said this could wait.
I've been waiting for two
years, Tom. Ever since Luke died.
I know how you feel about him.
I just don't know how you feel
about me anymore.
Don't take it personally. I don't
know how I feel about anything anymore.
God, you're pathetic.
Don't blame it on us.
Blame it on Con Ed!
Get this truck out of here.
Come on, I'm in a hurry!
I've got a doctor's appointment.
Hey, lady! What are you
honking at me for?
It was only my sister who could force
me to come to this God-awful city.
This city that roars down on you.
She loved it all.
The muggers, the winos...
... the bag ladies,
the wall-to-wall noise.
She loved it because it had nothing
to do with our childhood.
Luke and I hated it for
exactly the same reason.
You're...
Hello.
I'm Dr. Lowenstein.
You must be Tom.
Yes, ma'am.
Why don't you come in?
You can leave your things there.
Am I supposed to lie down on the couch,
or are we gonna make polite chitchat?
How about a cup of coffee?
Oh, we're gonna make
polite chitchat first.
Was that yes or no to the coffee?
It's a yes, ma'am.
Cream and sugar?
And you don't have to call me ma'am.
That's my good home-training,
and I'm a little nervous.
Cream, no sugar.
Why do you think you're nervous?
I get nervous every time my sister
tries to kill herself. It's a quirk.
A quirk?
I'm sorry. I was being cynical.
It's a family trait.
Oh, I don't think Savannah's cynical.
No? She's suicidal.
I wish she was cynical.
How is my sister?
She's out of physical danger, but...
When can I see her?
You have to wait until tomorrow.
Why can't I go now?
She's very agitated today.
We're trying to quiet her down.
I think it would be too upsetting.
Wouldn't upset me.
No, but it might upset her.
How's your coffee?
Is it hot enough?
It'll do.
In Savannah's poems...
...are you the shrimper or the coach?
The coach.
Luke's the shrimper, or was.
Savannah's last suicide attempt
was right after his death, correct?
Yeah, she had a few bad days over it.
Were there other times?
I don't know.
There might have been another time
when we were young, but I'm not sure.
How are you getting paid?
Why change the subject?
Because I don't like it much.
Is it okay if I smoke?
I'd prefer it if you didn't.
How well do you know
your sister's poetry?
I said I was a coach, Lowenstein,
not an orangutan.
I was also an English teacher.
I know her poetry. She's my twin.
I know it a hell of a lot better
than you do.
You don't like
psychiatrists, do you?
What good do you people do?
You ask a lot of questions.
I'm sick of this whole damn routine.
I'm sick of my sister's
attraction to razorblades.
And I'm sick of shrinks who can't
do a fucking thing to help her.
I don't know if I can
help her either.
But I do know I'm not
gonna give up trying.
Why not? Maybe she just wants
to die too damn much.
And that's okay?
You sound resigned to losing her.
Hell no, it's not okay with me.
Yeah, but I am resigned.
Then I don't think you can
help me with Savannah.
I'm sorry you had
to come all this way.
What do you want from me?
Information.
You see, I've only been Savannah's
doctor for a few months.
There's so much more
I need to know about her.
I need her childhood stories,
and she can't tell me...
...because she's blocked portions of
her life out. Blotted out.
So I need you to be her memory,
in a sense...
...and fill in the missing details.
I've spent my life trying
to forget those missing details.
- I beg your pardon?
- I...
God, she's a pain in the ass.
What time tomorrow?
I'll meet you at the hospital at noon.
Do you have a headache?
A doozy. You wouldn't have any
morphine handy, would you?
Morphine?
That's a joke, Lowenstein.
Come on, get out of the way, kid.
You're gonna get hurt.
Screw you, man.
You gonna help me with the bags?
You out of your mind?
I ain't helping you with no bags.
Come on, move!
Get out of the way, huh?
Yo, taxi!
Shit! Shit!
Move your ass an inch...
...and you can kiss it goodbye.
Hi, Eddie. Go ahead and shoot,
I've had a rotten day.
Tom! You should have told me
you were coming.
The gun, Eddie, the gun.
I'm sorry. Savannah and I have
been robbed twice this year.
They're leaping from fire escapes.
One landed on my air conditioner.
I greased my windowsills.
That didn't help.
I love New York.
Tell me about it.
- How's Andrew?
- Gone.
Said he needed space, so he found
a younger man with a duplex.
It's his loss, Eddie.
Bless you.
Savannah was an angel.
I practically lived over here.
So you're alone now, huh?
Unless I can tempt you into
crossing the line while you're here.
I got enough troubles, Eddie.
Actually, you look terrible, Tom.
You're not even cute anymore.
If that's your idea of seduction,
no wonder you're alone.
Well, it isn't easy.
Did you know Savannah was seeing
a psychiatrist?
Of course. I recommended her.
She's a friend of mine.
It was a bitch washing it out.
You found her?
We've been giving her 50 mgs
three times a day.
I'd bring it down to 25.
Don't expect too much.
Dr. Lowenstein, I need to see you.
Hey, Savannah. Hey, darling.
It's me. Tom.
I have a cancellation,
so why don't you meet me...
...here at the hospital
in 45 minutes, okay?
I'm on the third floor.
What the hell is going on here?
Why is she strapped down?
Her team felt she had to
be restrained...
Why? She has enough drugs
to anaesthetize a whale!
- Her team decides...
- Quit calling them her team!
Sounds like she's trying out
for the Giants.
What should I call them?
Let's be creative.
Call them assholes.
Let me tell you something
about those assholes.
I'm grateful because they
saved your sister's life.
I don't like...
I don't care.
She's still a threat to herself.
There's no point to this
unless we keep Savannah alive.
And I don't care if it takes drugs
or voodoo or reading tarot cards...
...I want her alive.
Do you understand me?
When I'm not picking straw out
of my teeth, I'm a very smart man.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to sound condescending.
You're tough, Lowenstein...
...and I'm starving.
Any interest in lunch?
Only if you let me pay.
Oh, I insist.
I wouldn't have objected to
Lutèce or Le Cirque.
Their chili isn't as good.
Thank you.
Tell me something.
Why didn't your father
answer my telegram?
Dad only likes good news.
Besides, the shrimp are running good.
And your mother? Why didn't she come?
She was the one I spoke to.
Priorities. My mother's too busy
hiring a caterer...
...for my stepfather's birthday.
Do you always make jokes
in place of conversation?
It's the Southern way, ma'am.
The "Southern way"?
My mother's immortal phrase:
"When things get too painful,
we either avoid them or we laugh. "
When do you cry,
according to the Southern way?
We don't.
Jesus, even Sally makes
better chili than this.
- I have a good recipe. Interested?
- No, thanks. I never cook.
What the hell is it with you doctors?
Does " Callanwolde"
mean anything to you?
No. Why?
Savannah kept repeating it
when she first came out of the coma.
" Callanwolde, Callanwolde. " No?
I don't know.
I have to get back to the hospital.
It's late.
I can't see you tomorrow
till about 7:30. Okay?
Lowenstein!
What's your first name?
- Why?
- Why not?
It's just that my patients
call me Dr. Lowenstein.
But I'm not your patient.
Susan.
Thank you, doctor. I won't use your
name. I just wanted to know it.
Be on time.
- Eight bucks a pound.
- Eight bucks a pound? For shrimp?
- Are they fresh?
- Yeah!
They're today's. They're gorgeous.
- I'll take a pound.
- Let me at the scale.
Shrimp Newburg? For chrissakes,
Lila, it's got wine in it!
It's garbage!
It's elegant food, Henry. And it's
gonna get me into Colleton League.
That's a joke. Why do you think
they got a Colleton League?
To keep people like you out.
Joop!
Why do you want to join anyway, Mama,
if they don't want you?
Of course they want me.
They just don't know it yet.
Even the dog won't eat it.
Goddamn it! I work hard all day long
to come home and eat this shit?
I think it's good.
- Who asked you?
- Nobody.
Nobody.
Tip your head up, boy.
You ain't gonna cry, are you?
What did I tell you about crying?
What did I tell you about
crying in this house?
Put the hands in your lap.
Sit up straight!
Come on, sit up straight.
You gonna cry now?
Savannah, get this little girl
one of your dresses.
Why are you so mean?
Henry, why don't I get you
another supper?
There's leftover hash and rice.
I'll heat it up.
Give me a hand, Tom.
You go out in the kitchen
with the rest of the girls.
Bully on somebody your own size.
Can't anyone take a joke around here?
I'll help, Mama.
I want you to melt
this butter, Savannah.
Heat up this rice. You chop that
onion into fine little pieces, Tom.
And the Yankees are back out in front.
I'm sorry, Mama.
There's nothing to be sorry for.
Marry into nothing, you get nothing.
Add some pepper, Tom.
Hand me that Worcestershire sauce.
Your mouth is hanging open, child.
Nice and spicy.
All I want is a good,
plain American meal!
Here you go, darling.
Now, this is food, Lila.
Eat up, children.
So your mother fed him dog food, huh?
He even asked for a second helping.
Maybe you got your sense
of humor from your mother.
Very funny.
She called today, very concerned
about Savannah.
Don't believe a word she says.
She's a liar.
That's interesting. She said
you'd tell lies about her.
That figures.
I saw Herbert Woodruff come out of your
office. He sure can play the fiddle.
You're changing the subject.
What's wrong with him?
Just kidding.
I can't believe anybody
with that kind of money has troubles.
- Are you really that provincial?
- Oh, hell, yes. So is Savannah.
When we were kids, the only way
to get off our island was by boat.
We grew up on a tidal plain.
A tidal plain? What does that mean?
Tides mean everything, Lowenstein.
They measure everything.
Moods, seasons,
the time to plant...
...to fish, to mate.
It's primitive. Biological clocks
ticking all over the place.
Sounds like a nice way to live.
What else did she say, my mother?
She said that she was the one who
encouraged Savannah to become a poet.
Is that true?
Jesus Christ!
That woman has no shame.
Wanna know how
she encouraged Savannah?
- By burning her childhood journals.
- Why'd she burn them?
Because Savannah was being disloyal,
writing about our hideous family.
What's hideous about your family?
Are you asking me to be disloyal?
If that's what it takes
to help Savannah, yes.
Aren't we about done?
What time is it?
We still have a few more minutes.
What did Savannah do after your
mother burned her journals?
She took her fingers, and she
wrote in the sand.
And then she wrote in the air.
She wrote poetry so mother
wouldn't understand it.
Your mother helped to create a poet.
Bullshit, Lowenstein.
She created a schizophrenic.
My mother should've raised cobras,
not children.
Can you tell me anything good
about your parents?
No.
Try.
They did two really good things:
Luke and Savannah.
Incredible people.
Passionate, defiant, not for sale.
What about you?
Oh, I was a courteous Southern boy
that did what he was told.
I was responsible and normal and dull.
I don't know what normal is,
and you're anything but dull.
Compared to them, I was.
Your sister's in the hospital,
and your brother's dead.
You must be doing something right.
You can go now.
Time's up.
Good night.
"Women and men
Both little and small
Cared for anyone not at all
They sowed their isn't
They reaped their same
Sun, moon, stars, rain
Children guessed
But only a few
And down they forgot
As up they grew. "
So this began a series
of confessional days...
... when I spun out the history
of Savannah's past...
... in order to keep her alive.
By the second week,
I'd developed the New York willies.
The guilt that every
out-of-towner feels...
... if he's not improving his mind
every goddamn second.
I made a list of things I should do.
Museums, plays, run six miles
in under 50 minutes.
See three foreign films
all at the same time.
Anything not to feel guilty.
Tom, how old was Savannah when you
first realized...
... something was wrong with her?
About seven or eight.
Anything specific happen?
My mother had a baby at home.
It was stillborn.
She told us it died
because we were bad.
Anyway, we were gonna bury it
the next day...
...so Dad wrapped it in some towels
and put it in the freezer.
That night, I got up
to get a drink of water...
...and I saw Savannah sitting
in the rocking chair...
...with the dead baby in her arms.
She was saying...
..."You're the lucky one because you
don't have to live with us. "
Did you say anything to her?
The next day I did, but she didn't
remember anything about it.
When I told her, she said...
..."Why would anyone do a crazy thing
like that?"
So you were her memory even then?
I guess so.
Goddamn locks!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
What was that again?
I'm learning to speak the language
of the natives here. Hi, Sally.
How's it going down there?
It's just sort of blowing up a storm.
I got the girls' drawings.
- Did they get my letters?
- Yes, and they loved them.
Good! Did you get my letter?
Tom?
It's not a good idea for you
to come home this weekend.
Why not?
I'm just not sure that I want
to see you right now.
I have a lot to figure out.
What's the point, Tom?
I mean, let's face it...
... we don't make each other
feel good anymore.
Right.
Look...
...I didn't want to tell you this
on the telephone.
I wanted to tell you before you left.
But the way you left...
...there wasn't any time.
What did you want to tell me, Sally?
What's his name?
What's his name, Sally?
The man must have a name.
Jack Cleveland.
Oh, no. Oh, no!
Oh, Jesus, Sally!
Jack Cleveland?
That aging, pompous hippie from the
hospital who still rides a motorcycle?
Oh, for chrissakes, Sally!
Why him?
Because he knows how he
feels about me.
Oh, Sally.
This is too difficult to talk
about over the phone.
Just think about it carefully, okay?
I hardly think about anything else.
Good night, Tom.
What?
Are you really in love?
I'm not sure.
I might even be doing this to hurt you.
I gotta go.
Dear Sally:
I wish the words,
"I love you"...
... weren't so
difficult for me.
I've missed you.
I miss touching you.
I don't know what keeps me
at such a distance.
I'm sorry I disappoint you, Sally...
... but you're right to feel that way.
How else could you react
to half a man?
How could you not be disappointed?
Hell, I seem to disappoint anyone who
tries to find the best in me.
Tom?
Ma'am?
Come on in here.
Come on, lie beside me. Come on.
You're the only Wingo
who's gonna amount to something.
Luke can't do it,
because he isn't smart.
Savannah can't,
because she's just a girl.
- But Luke's smart, Mama.
- Not like you.
Or me.
Nobody knows this yet...
...but I'm an amazing woman.
Do you believe that?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm not gonna die in a house
like this. I promise you that.
Something else, Tom.
I love you
more than I love any of them.
- But, Mama!
- I do.
I can't help it.
You're my favorite.
That's gonna be our little secret.
You keep a secret?
Yes, ma'am.
Can I go now?
Not till you tell me you love me.
I love you, Mama.
It took me 20 years to tell Luke
and Savannah about my secret.
And when I did, they just fell
on the floor, howling.
My mother took each of them
into that room...
...and told them exactly
the same thing.
Why did you tell me that story?
To prove that Lila Wingo would...
Just to show why Savannah
could never trust her.
You mean why you could
never trust her.
I'm sorry. That's the wrong story.
Let's just skip it...
...and I'll try
to think of a better one.
What's bothering you?
Global warming, acid rain,
the national debt...
And my wife's having an affair with
a heart surgeon in South Carolina.
Jesus! I feel like such an idiot.
I never even knew it was going on.
- Maybe you weren't paying attention.
- Bullshit!
Let's face it, Lowenstein.
Women are more devious than men.
You're great at hiding things. You
keep secrets. You smile when you lie.
You expect a man to be
a tower of strength.
When he's got a few weaknesses
and insecurities...
...what do you do? You turn around,
and goddamn it, you betray him!
You feel that your mother
betrayed you?
I was talking about my wife!
Oh, God, I hate this Freudian crap.
It's not your job to listen
to my problems. I'd like to go.
You're free to leave anytime.
Good!
Goddamn shrink.
Who was I kidding?
I was a champion at keeping secrets.
Better than any woman.
Until Susan Lowenstein came along.
A man who never talked...
... now is doing nothing else.
Her questions making me
as dizzy as her perfume.
Excuse me.
Would you like to dance?
- Who, me?
- Yes, you.
Come on.
Come on, just loosen up!
Hands to yourself!
He's spoken for.
How's Savannah?
When can I see her?
I don't know, Eddie.
It's like talking to a fern.
I'm glad she's improving.
Come on, let's dance.
Give me a break, Eddie.
I'm a lousy dancer.
Walk on the wild side.
You're in the big city.
Oh, hell. All right...
God, you are a lousy dancer!
Go mingle.
Get in here.
Get into the party.
Where are my chairs?
I found four of them,
and I have a lead on another two.
Roberta, have I got a settee for you!
Don't laugh.
- You're laughing!
- I'm sorry.
I'm surprised to see you here.
Why? I like Eddie.
You know, I...
You really pissed me off today.
But you made me think
about some things.
Don't make it a habit,
or I'll charge you.
Oh, we do have a sense of humor!
I thought you had it
surgically removed.
You look mighty pretty tonight.
Thank you.
Are you all right?
Oh, God, I'm great. I'm just great.
Now that I finished lying,
can I ask you to dance?
No?
You'd be the first woman
I've danced with in New York.
I'd rather not.
Come on, Lowenstein.
Walk on the wild side.
It's a party. Come on.
Don't worry, I can't dance and make a
pass at the same time. I lose count.
You came alone?
Yeah, it's funny. I never went
anywhere alone until I got married.
Well, that speaks well
for matrimony.
No, it's just that...
...my husband travels a lot.
What does he do?
You know, it's late.
I really should go.
- I'll take you home.
- No, it's okay. I'm fine.
I'm a Southerner, ma'am.
We take our ladies home.
How do you do it?
How do you listen to people's sob
stories? Doesn't it depress you?
No, not if I think I can help them.
Anyway, you learn to separate your
patients' problems from your own.
Now yours, I think I could handle.
Oh, yeah? Don't be so sure.
Tell me something.
Did you ever want to write
like Savannah?
You're changing the subject,
Lowenstein.
Am I?
It's a technique
I'm learning from you.
There he is again. You see him?
That guy is following me.
So you're a shrink to the stars, huh?
He's not my patient.
He's my husband.
Really? Herbert-fucking-Woodruff
is your husband?
Herbert Woodruff is my husband, yes.
How'd you meet him?
I saw him perform at...
...Carnegie Hall. I was 22 years old.
I had never heard anything like it.
I mean, that kind of...
...passion, artistry, whatever
you call it. It's like Savannah's.
They have that gift
to make people feel.
I fell in love with him instantly.
So you married him, and then
you lived happily ever after, huh?
I married him.
Are you saying mine isn't
the only screwed up union?
- I'm not telling you anything more.
- Wait. No fair. I spill my guts.
I tell you my marriage is full
of holes. But you got nothing to say?
I think it's your turn
to give a little.
Come on, Lowenstein, be human.
Talk to me.
- Tell me about yourself.
- I can't.
Why are there never any cabs?
I'll ask you a few simple questions,
and you just answer.
- Simple?
- Very simple.
- What's your father's name?
- Douglas.
What's your favorite car?
I like old Ford Woodies.
Good! Who's the first boy
you ever kissed?
Dick Berkowitz. He was very cute.
Do you have any idea how beautiful
you look in that suit?
Is this " Make Lowenstein
Feel Better Day"?
And you got a great smile.
You should smile more.
- Stop.
- You don't believe me, do you?
Come here. Let me show you something.
Come here. Let me show you.
- A painting?
- No, you. Look at you.
You. Your face,
your smile, your suit.
- Great stuff here. Beautiful.
- Okay, you convinced me.
Now, would you please get me a cab?
Come up for a minute.
I'd like you to meet my son.
Sure. Okay.
Come on in.
Bernard?
I'd like you to meet a friend.
How do you do?
- Mind stepping out of the way?
- Oh, excuse me.
Mr. Wingo is
a football coach, Bernard.
Oh, yeah?
Dad called from Vienna today.
Said to say hi to you when I saw you.
Did you practice this afternoon?
No, I've been too busy watching TV.
You're being rude, Bernard.
No, he's being a teenager.
I used to be one myself.
No kidding?
Where are you from?
Your accent's weird.
South Carolina.
- Is this TV or...?
- I'm trying to watch this movie.
All right, it's late. Come on.
It's time for bed, Bernard.
Let's go.
- Turn down the TV and go to bed.
- I'll see you, Bernard.
I'm sorry that he was so rude to you.
You don't have to apologize,
Lowenstein.
Teenagers, by definition,
are not fit for society.
That's true.
Bernard wants to play football.
That's why I brought you to meet him.
I thought that maybe you could
coach him a couple of days a week.
You see, he never gets a chance
to play while his father's around.
Herbert's on tour.
I thought maybe...
Is this a job offer?
Yes, and I would insist on paying you.
What would you consider
a reasonable rate?
What are your rates?
I charge $150 an hour.
Fine, I'll take it.
You must be a very good coach.
Forget it, Lowenstein.
I'm not a charity case yet.
Tell Bernard we'll start Monday.
Good. Good night.
First rule of thumb, Bernard.
Never be late.
I didn't want to come anyway, okay?
Your mother thinks you want to play.
Is that true?
Maybe, maybe not.
Where do you coach, Mr. Wingo?
Hillbilly country?
We're a little
class-conscious, are we?
Do you go to Miss Porter's?
Phillips Exeter, smart-ass.
You didn't get to play last year,
did you?
How'd you know?
Because any snot-nosed punk that
would dare call his coach a smart-ass...
...wouldn't get to haul water,
let alone play.
With your attitude, you belong
in the bleachers, kid.
When you want to play football,
get my number from your mother.
Catch.
You need help.
This is not an attractive look
for a middle-aged man.
You can take me shopping. Did you
ever hear of Renata Halpern?
No, who is she?
I don't know, but she writes poems
about growing up Jewish in Brooklyn.
Was she staying
with Savannah recently?
Not that I know of. Of course,
I've been out of town a lot.
- Bloomingdale's on Saturday, big boy.
- Okay.
Coach Wingo?
You know, yesterday, I...
You know, I...
I accept your apology, Bernard.
I didn't play last year,
because I never made the team.
They made fun of me.
If I coach you, I promise
they won't make fun of you.
But you gotta promise something.
You gotta shut up, Bernard.
Your mouth pisses me off.
"Yes, sir" is the way
to address me.
First thing we'll do
is follow certain courtesies.
You'll do whatever I tell you
and do it with enthusiasm.
I'm gonna teach you
to play football well.
- I'll run your ass off every day.
- I have my violin lessons.
- Shut up, Bernard.
- Yes, sir.
After I run you till you drop,
make you lift weights...
...tackle till your arms cramp...
...something will happen to you
that's never happened in your life.
What's that, sir?
You're gonna be happy, kid.
Keep moving. Move them.
Hit it!
Come on! Get up.
Drop that leg. Roll.
Drop this leg. Roll.
That's it. All right,
let's see that smile.
Do it again with a smile.
Cross. Back. Cross.
That's it. Cross them over. Cross!
Bring this shoulder out.
This shoulder.
Keep your eyes on the ball.
Concentrate!
Come on, Bernard.
Get your hands up.
Get it. Look behind!
Turn around and run!
You're the greatest person
in the whole world, Daddy.
What? I don't even get the pleasure
of asking the questions anymore?
- When you coming home, Daddy?
- Soon.
Well, if you miss my birthday,
I'm gonna kill you.
Chandler, how could I miss
your birthday?
I was there the day you pushed
your way into the world.
I want an alligator!
You go down to the marsh
and you get one.
I want a stuffed alligator
to sleep in bed with me.
That's a dangerous habit to get
into, kiddo. Is Mama there?
Daddy wants to talk to you.
Oh, hi, Sal.
I want to come home
for Chandler's birthday.
It would only be...
We'd all be upset if you
didn't come, Tom.
Oh, good. Well, thanks, Sally.
Okay. I'll talk to you. Bye.
All right. Bye-bye.
Hustle. Hustle. Hustle!
- You got a broken cigarette.
- You gonna take it away?
So this became my routine.
Coaching Bernard in the morning...
... and in the afternoon, telling the
Wingo family secrets to his mother.
And looking forward to telling them.
Or looking forward to seeing her.
It's as if Savannah has
some kind of a splinter...
...that she's neglected. It festers.
It festers inside you until you...
...you get it out.
You know what I mean?
The stories you're telling me
are helping her remember...
...and I'm very proud
of the work we're doing.
Know what I mean?
Time's up. Out.
Lowenstein.
- Here. Catch.
- My nails!
- Throw me the ball.
- Throw you the ball?
Coach, are you trying to kill yourself?
- I'm not quitting, Bernard. You hear?
- Then I'll smoke.
No, you're not smoking.
You're not smoking.
Then throw them out.
- All right. I will.
- All of them.
All right. All right!
- Congratulations. How do you feel?
- I feel better already.
You know, it's an art form
to hate New York properly.
No, it's not. It's a cliché.
You're not such a dumb kid after all.
Let's go to the bookstore.
It's my daughter's birthday.
She wants an alligator.
There's a crocodile in Peter Pan.
Think she'll buy it?
It's my mom's birthday next week.
I bet you got her exactly nothing.
Come on, we'll see if we can
find her something.
Shit! Shit.
Who's Renata Halpern?
What's she to do with my sister?
Sit down and cool off.
You knew about this, didn't you?
It's difficult to conduct a session...
It's not a session!
I'm asking you a question.
You're doing a shitty job
of evading it. Who wrote this?
What's so disturbing?
That's not the issue.
Why didn't you tell me?
It wasn't my place to...
You're a piece of work.
I tell you everything, and you
withhold important information!
- Maybe you're withholding.
- It's not about me!
Why are you so upset?
I don't like being lied to.
I don't like secrets.
I could report you.
Have your license suspended.
Stop acting like a petulant child.
You haven't answered me.
Who wrote this book?
You tell me.
I will. My sister wrote it.
It's all about my goddamn family.
If my mother read it,
she'd rip out Savannah's pancreas.
Why? Why would she do that?
What are you hiding?
I don't answer any more questions
till you answer mine.
Then sit down and listen.
That is, if you're not too exhausted
by your temper tantrum.
Shit!
When Savannah came to see me, she
told me her name was Renata Halpern.
- She's even crazier than I thought.
- Shut up, or I won't continue.
She said her father was a furrier and
both parents were Holocaust survivors.
She couldn't fool me about being
Jewish, but what fascinated me...
...was why she was
the child of survivors.
What was, or is
she trying to survive?
- How would I know?
- I think you do.
You're supposed to be answering me.
Why'd she do it?
Writing made her want
to be someone else.
- That was okay with you?
- It wasn't okay.
I said she had to resolve her
problems, or she'd have no chance.
People pay you for this?
To turn them into someone else?
You're not listening!
What do you think I do every day?
- Complaining! Avoiding!
- Fuck you, Lowenstein!
Fuck you, Sigmund Freud and
Renata Halpern. It makes me sick!
Your reaction makes me sick!
What do you expect?
What if I'd done this to your son?
It's not the same thing!
I'll make him
a Presbyterian quarterback!
It's quite different.
My son didn't try to kill himself.
Give him time, Lowenstein.
Give him time!
You son of a bitch!
My God, I'll go get you some ice.
I see a malpractice suit coming
out of this, doctor.
I am so embarrassed.
What a day.
I get dropped by a dictionary...
...and I find out my sister's
become a Brooklyn Jew.
Here. Here.
I don't need that.
I'd rather bleed to death.
Just be quiet and take it.
After you've stopped bleeding,
I'll take you to dinner.
No chili today.
This time it's gonna cost you.
This is therapy, huh?
Yeah, pretty bloody, isn't it?
I still can't believe
I did that to you.
Face it.
I bring out the animal in you.
- I owe you an apology.
- I accept.
- That was a terrible thing to say.
- Yes.
I know it. Jesus.
Thank you for accepting.
Would you like to order now?
We would like to order now.
Do you want me to order for you?
I eat here all the time.
How can I trust a woman
who can't even cook?
Just because I can't cook
doesn't mean I can't eat.
Go ahead. I'll do anything
to make you happy tonight.
I think...
...we'll start with the artichaut
garni de champignons au safran.
And pour monsieur...
La mousse de canard
aux baies sauvages.
And then we'll have the soupe de
poisson au crabe.  Delicious.
And for our main course,
râble de lapin.
The rabbit is superb.
God, there's nothing sexier than
a beautiful woman...
...ordering food in French.
Read me the whole menu.
- Are you flirting with me?
- Yeah, I think I am.
I'd like you to find me attractive,
bloody nose and all.
I'd like to ask you about Savannah.
- Don't you ever take a night off?
- No.
You said you'd do anything to
make me happy. Just one thing.
Savannah told me her children's book
came out of a dream.
More like a nightmare.
Images in it terrorized her,
but she didn't know why.
Like the three stray dogs.
What do you think it means?
Lowenstein, you're incorrigible.
We're at a wonderful restaurant...
...and you want me to interpret
my sister's dreams?
You wanna interpret dreams?
Do mine.
I had a great one about you
last night.
You had a dream about me?
- You wanna hear?
- I'm not sure.
Don't worry.
This one's G-rated.
This one?
Tell me.
There was a blinding snowstorm
right here in New York City.
I went out for a walk,
and I ran into you.
We decided to go to the Rainbow Room.
No one was there.
So we started to slow dance.
What do you think it means?
You said it was a snowstorm?
Blinding snowstorm?
Maybe there's something
you're afraid to see.
Maybe I wanna get to know you better.
Maybe you're trying to snow me.
Maybe I have cold feet.
Maybe you just miss winter.
Move those legs. Move them!
That's it. Get in position.
Keep your head up. Come!
Is that my son?
Is that you in there, Bernard?
I don't think this was
such a good idea.
Stop being a Jewish mother.
I am a Jewish mother.
I brought sandwiches.
Oh, good. I'm starving.
I got delicious ones here.
Take a break.
Great. I got one for you.
Slave away in the kitchen all day
making those?
I bought them as usual.
Would you like one?
No, I'm not hungry.
So can I watch you play?
I promise I won't be overprotective.
I don't feel like playing anymore.
Let's toss the ball around
for a few minutes.
Am I a trained seal?
I gotta do what she wants?
Oh, you got it tough, kid!
Let's lie in the grass and cry for all
the terrible misfortune in your life.