A little more throttle
when you want to bank left like that.
- You're a natural.
- I practice on a computer.
- I can point down a little bit?
- Yeah, okay.
Good job.
Easy.
You're going too fast and too low!
We go back to airport now.
So exciting. My heart is beating fast.
Excuse me!
- Sorry, I didn't get your last name.
- Bob from Nepal.
To be truthful, Mr. Davis, I'm still not
sure exactly what you're trying to report.
To tell you the truth, I'm not exactly
sure myself. It was just weird.
The guy didn't really want to
learn how to fly as much as he wanted...
- to learn how to aim the plane.
- You got his name?
Barbir Alkazar. A-L-K-A-Z-A-R.
Are you going to be there
for a while, Mr. Davis?
- Maybe we'll take a drive out.
- Yeah, you bet, I'll be here.
I study art.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You're an artist, too, yes?
What medium?
Mortician. Body prep, that sort of thing.
Makeup, sculpt out the cheeks,
little cotton up there.
Catch it just right,
they almost come back to life.
Yes, I can imagine this.
It was nice meeting you.
Never fails. Damn it!
Tonight, real fast
hello-goodbye-type deal.
The base killed two guys last night.
Both had kids in my madrassa.
- What was that about?
- Osama paranoia.
Brothers going all crazy right now.
- Plan biggest operation ever.
- What kind of operation?
Same time targets, Tanzania, Sudan.
Only this time, big American cities.
Where and when?
I find out more, but then Hamburg no
good for me. I need Green Card, Brand.
Achmed, you just got
a very thick envelope.
Two weeks, here.
I give you dates, places, maybe even
names of brothers already in US.
If you don't be here, I go back Tunis.
Forget hajj to land of Kentucky-Fried
forever, and you, Brand...
maybe you never sleep
good again, ever.
'Cause this time...
your country bleeds.
He doesn't work, he doesn't go
to school, he doesn't have visitors.
He has no visible means of support.
He plays with Flight Simulator
all day long.
I thought you were here
to get a warrant.
Okay, so we watched him a little bit.
But we also talked to a phone-guy...
who installed a DSL line
in his apartment.
No TV, no stereo, no furniture,
just professional flight charts...
Arabic newspapers
and a computer with a joystick.
I want to see what's on this guy's
hard drive, Oscar.
Because of some goof-ball flight lesson
and computer games?
Not due cause, gentlemen.
I won't embarrass myself
in front of a Federal judge.
Go do other things.
I'm e-mailing headquarters in DC, Hank.
- You're kidding.
- Screw the consequences!
I've got a really bad vibe
on this thing, I really do.
It's Farsi.
"Praise the brave young brothers...
"and may God put courage in their
hearts the day of their longest journey. "
The speed, the inflections, the slang...
they got their adrenaline
going over something.
But what? It's all a-specific.
Shards of scripture, old poetry,
parabolic gibberish...
Maybe not. Our group thinks
we're seeing a theme.
Numbers being repeated, 9s and 11s...
Laurie, turn that off.
The quotes from Quran,
always from Sura 9.
If not 9, they're from 11.
Sometimes it's out in the open:
Everybody's got 11 girlfriends,
9 siblings or...
- 9 cars, 11 goats.
- Okay, people. 9s and 11s.
A codebook correlative?
A time? A date?
September 11?
Or November 9, the month
comes after the day in the region.
Pete, memo both CIA and FBI.
You know what, send it out
to the whole alphabet soup.
'Cause if this is the date,
we might be just about on top of it.
Harrison, good job. Keep working it.
Come on, Achmed.
So it's about 50-50.
Rudy, Jack, Drew bet you are.
Frank, Billy Noble, and Wally
bet you're not.
- How much are people betting?
- $20 a piece.
- So where'd you put your money?
- Me? Didn't bet.
Don't ask, don't tell, strictly by the book.
You're not being recorded. You can talk.
I'm just curious.
I bet you're a dyke.
We can probably surveil your ass.
Find out for sure
so some money can change hands.
Not without a DOJ bust for violating
my civil rights, you couldn't.
Hell!
Do it!
I'll sue the bureau for $10 million,
settle for $5, retire rich.
How about I set it up, make it happen,
then you and I split the ticket.
- Why not? It's really a very cool idea...
- Shut the hell up!
He's on his way.
Okay, they're coming out.
I'll take the first leg,
you stay on the parallels.
Affirmative.
Peace, my brother.
Damn it! What the hell?
Stay where you are!
Don't move!
Fulbar, are you okay?
Peachy! ATF just screwed us!
Get in there. Take him! Move!
Move it!
FBI!
Get your hands up! Kneel down!
Counter-Terrorism Task Force.
Do you have any idea how long we've
been waiting to follow the guy you shot?
- Who's in charge here?
- Command is up front.
- Damn it.
- I'm hit.
Sorry, pal, he's ours. The dead guy
might have been Al Qaeda.
I don't care if he's Alfalfa.
There's C-4 in that truck,
illegal weapons in that building.
- He's coming with us.
- Sir! Messina's been hit!
How bad you hurt, Messina?
- I'm good.
- It's all right, boss.
It went in his bicep,
came right out again.
Where's my prisoner?
- Did she take him?
- Agent Fulbar?
She wouldn't do a thing like that.
In fact, I'm concerned.
This bust is all illegal.
Trunk not proper cartage.
There's cameras down here!
Sorry. It must be that time of the month.
1998. Vintage Al Qaeda year!
Two perfectly timed
simultaneous explosions...
at our embassies
in Kenya and Tanzania.
258 killed, over 5,000 injured.
'99, the near-sinking of the USS Cole.
He's getting good.
Somebody want to get the lights?
So, what created the monster?
We know he's cranky.
He's got a bad back.
Uses a staff to walk.
Bad kidneys. He's on dialysis, but
what else? The psychological aspect?
His mum was one of 20 wives.
His dad stayed with all the others...
but he left Osama's mum
right after he was born.
Never looked back.
So, in a culture
where parentage means everything...
Osama's almost an orphan.
- He's got 'Daddy Issues'.
- I think a lot stems from that.
Raised almost secular, he embraces
radical fundamentalism as a teenager.
Rebellion against a father
who's westernized...
really just a filthy-rich playboy.
Love it. Why does he hate us so much?
We desecrate the Islamic Holy Land by
building bases near Mecca and Medina.
We've got female troops
walking around with uncovered hair.
Kind of like bringing
a stripper to church.
So, as this old warrior retires,
this is the world they leave you with.
Nice guys like this.
Other asymmetric threats...
not to mention bio, chemical and
nuclear weapons in all the wrong hands.
So, good luck in your careers...
and watch your asses.
Don't become a gold star
in the lobby down there.
Thank you.
Good luck.
To a long and wonderful service.
God.
Why does everybody make it
sound like a funeral?
There's some upsides to this.
You won't have to get up
at 6:30 every morning.
No. We're not co-workers anymore.
And this means...
I guess that's kind of up to you.
You have reached
the voice-mail box of Joe Johnson...
and in that Mr. Johnson no longer works
for his former employer...
your message will not be recorded
by any damn beeps.
Some spook. I can hear the barroom
in the background.
- Are you on a secure cell?
- Just like you taught me.
Happy retirement, teach.
Well, thanks.
So how are you doing over there?
Not too bad.
Margaret says hello.
Ditto.
So, you're retired now...
you're in a bar with Margaret...
Bet my last buck
what you have in mind right now.
Are you still in Hamburg?
Not for long.
Flying to Al Qaeda land tomorrow.
First Uzbek, then Afghan.
- The Massoud thing?
- Yeah.
Apparently some of the bad guys
got away. Two of them.
Full-blown American citizens.
That's interesting.
So, how are you going to get into
Afghanistan, white boy?
I don't know.
But I'm guessing
it's gonna be kind of a drag.
The glamour of it all.
You went over my head?
I had to, Oscar. I'd do it again.
- It didn't get you very far, did it?
- No, it didn't.
Request a transfer out of here.
It wasn't personal! Oscar!
Yeah, well, this isn't personal either.
Request a transfer.
I won't work with you anymore.
Come on. Let's go.
- Give me your bag.
- I'm gonna be late.
- Step on it.
- Okay.
Stop!
Wasn't I just walking her
to kindergarten yesterday?
Seems like that, huh?
A college sophomore? Oh, God!
Honey, you can't bring King with you.
He's so spoiled, he's gonna
ask for a first-class ticket.
He can at least come to the airport
with us. I'm going to miss him.
- Come on, step on it, let's go.
- Okay.
We have the dorm address,
but not the phone number.
So you call as soon
as you get there, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
I've been thinking about the dorm...
and we could probably save a ton
of money if I got an apartment.
Honey, in our price range,
you'd wind up in an Oakland slum.
Probably a communist Oakland slum,
right, Dad?
Nothing like fascist Annapolis.
- Are you really going to take that job?
- I don't know, honey.
I really don't.
They'd kick me out of Berkeley
on general principles.
That they might.
- Tight driving, Dad. Time to spare.
- Okay, honey.
I'll park the car and walk you to the gate.
No, you don't have to do that.
King will be alone.
- King's okay.
- I'll be okay.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'll be okay.
- I'm a grown-up now, remember?
- Okay.
- I love you guys.
- Love you, too.
- Bye.
Boy.
Last boarding call for Flight 93.
Good morning.
Is that black dog visiting again?
You only have one class today.
Why don't you drop by Dr. Goldman's?
He can readjust your medication, Fazul.
The depression will lift, Catherine.
It always does.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Did you say
your morning prayers, Josef?
Dad, come on.
I don't even know the direction
of Mecca from this house.
No.
Didn't I see you wearing
that shirt yesterday?
Yeah, it's clean.
Please, you're picking up Melissa.
Change it.
Okay, Mum.
Oh, my God.
Mum!
Apparently a plane has just crashed
into the World Trade Center...
here in New York City.
It happened just a few moments ago.
It's a terrible accident.
If it was an accident.
I think that look is a very good look.
No regrets?
Only that you didn't retire
a little sooner, maybe.
- I'll make coffee.
- Okay.
I gotta get going.
- The second building was just hit.
- This is a piece of tape.
We may actually see another plane
enter the picture here in a second.
Here comes the videotape
we just showed you.
That appeared to be at least a 727
we saw a second ago.
You will see a large plane right there...
maybe even bigger, flying right into
the side of the World Trade Center.
Katie, thank you very much.
I'm joined by Tom Brokaw.
- You're coming back in?
- We're at war, Maggie.
The Federal Aviation Administration has
shut down all air traffic nationwide...
Flight 186 Center, turn right,
heading 240, contact Atlanta...
Approach on 128.75. Over.
We've still got 11 flights not responding.
What's the matter with them?
Gentlemen...
the Pentagon's been hit, too.
FAA's still got seven aircraft
still not responding.
3 are off-course from filed flight plans.
General, Chairman of Joint Chiefs,
line one.
Yes, sir.
All right, sir.
The President has just ordered...
the fighters to arm
their missiles at this time.
Any aircraft not responding
to visual command is to be shot down.
Confirming that the South Tower of the
World Trade Center has just collapsed.
Who knows how many people
were inside...
Sweet Jesus, what's going on?
Oh, no.
Cleveland Center, confirm your flight...
What the...
You're clear for missile-lock. Engage.
Oh, man.
Respond or you will be fired upon.
- What the hell is going on?
- Rock your wings. Come on, man.
Do you read, 182? What is your status?
I got a missile-lock.
I need orders here.
Do I launch on this aircraft or not?
Don't shoot. We copy you! We copy!
Are you on the wrong frequency?
Do I shoot?
Negative, One. Negative. Abort.
Repeat. Abort. They're responding.
Bring them down. Take a deep breath
and start escorting them to O'Hare.
Standby for O'Hare. 2-7.
Again, Jim...
here's the flights
we know were hijacked:
American Flight 11, Boston
to Los Angeles, American Flight 77...
both of those
in the Trade Center attacks.
United Flight 175, Boston to LAX...
we don't know, we haven't confirmed
the status of what happened to that...
and United 93,
Newark to San Francisco...
believed to be down in Pennsylvania.
Jim, have officials given us any
indication of what communications...
- preceded these crashes?
- He didn't say United 93?
Ted?
Tell me that he didn't say that!
No!
My baby.
NSA, the NSC, ourselves,
it's pretty much one voice, sir:
Al Qaeda.
That would be supported by the
Massoud assassination the other day.
They didn't want
an Anti-Taliban leader...
just waiting to aid us
if we decide to go in.
We'll go in, all right.
That city hadn't been touched by
another nation since the War of 1812.
This operation called
for planning, funding.
Why didn't we see it coming, people?
Why?
We have numerous
unconfirmed reports...
Latest chatter intercepts.
They're celebrating like
it's New Year's Eve.
We knew about
the possibility of hijacking.
But using commercial airliners
as missiles?
No.
You notice the date?
Yes, sir, I did.
God above.
Those fighter planes,
did they almost shoot at us?
Ted McKee.
I'm screwed, Dad.
I missed my plane. I got the next one.
Where are you, Melissa?
Chicago. O'Hare.
Who's doing this to us?
I don't know, baby.
Melissa, honey?
Hi, Mum.
The sound of your voice...
And I want to thank
Governor Pataki for...
the incredible cooperation
and coordination...
including deploying the National Guard.
We had all of it.
All the dots,
we just didn't connect them.
- We screwed up.
- No, Frank. The system did.
We screwed up.
Some believe United Flight 93
was headed for the White House.
Although President Bush
was in Florida at the time...
What?
Melissa?
I'm okay.
Where are you now? Where?
Which ones are friends
of yours, Vlenko?
You've been attacked.
Bad for you, good for me.
I got lots to say.
But not until I get immunity.
Full American brand, Big Time G-Man.
I get written guarantee.
- That son of a bitch.
- This one.
He recognized him.
He's got dual citizenship.
Syria and here. Right here. Seattle.
- And guess what else?
- What?
He just got back from Afghanistan.
CIA believes he was involved
in a political assassination over there.
- He's Al Qaeda.
- Can we get a warrant?
Today? I think we can get
a warrant on Nancy Reagan.
"Brutal US foreign policy
in the Middle East...
"being primarily dictated
by the powerful 'Jewish Block Vote'...
"in American domestic politics. "
Who's the author, Joseph Goebbels?
Some poli-sci prof down in Berkeley.
Adel. Doctor Fazul Adel.
Wait a sec.
Let's get a translation.
But now you must put aside
your petty differences.
Fight as one.
Because if you don't,
the Taliban will never be defeated...
and we all might just
as well go home right now.
He says he will not join this fight
because of Hezmir...
that guy over there, who he says
he hates more than the Taliban.
Ask him if...
three ounces of pure gold
would soften his position on Hezmir.
He says fine.
Man, forget it!
Hey!
How's it going?
Bad diplomatic-hair day?
I thought you were off
grazing in a pasture.
Yeah, right.
They're a bunch of raggedy-ass
gang-bangers!
There will never be an alliance.
Karzai!
- What the hell did he just say?
- Inspirational words.
You know how to ride, don't you?
- Wouldn't a truck be better?
- No.
Come on, son. Ass-kicking to be done.
- I want to get an apartment together.
- Okay.
I, Tom Ridge, do solemnly swear...
- ... that I will support and defend...
the Constitution of the United States.
Ted McKee.
Annapolis has been informed
you'll not be taking...
the position as Academic Dean, sir.
- Who is this?
- Please, sir.
Be standing by for your
Commander-in-Chief.
Honey, what was that all about?
I don't know.
Your immunity agreement says
you have to tell us everything you know.
So if you get caught in a lie,
even a teeny itsy-bitsy one...
this means nothing.
You understand that?
Were the men you were dealing with
members of Al Qaeda, Vlenko?
Some American gang kids.
Some Al Qaeda.
But this, I only think,
they don't wear badges on forehead.
Aside from the C-4...
we have tapes of you saying...
you could provide uranium
for one of your "customers".
Did that transaction ever take place?
Was crap from bull.
So maybe I fake...
just make some bucks, who knows?
- Recognize him?
- Khan.
Like Genghis. Nice guy for Moslem.
Was he the man who tried to buy
the Uranium from you, Vlenko?
Will you testify to that in a court of law?
Only if she don't do more beat-ups.
Do you, Admiral Theodore McKee,
without any mental reservation...
or purpose of evasion,
solemnly swear to defend this nation...
against all enemies,
foreign and domestic...
and swear to uphold the Constitution
of the United States of America?
I do.
Congratulations. I'm due back in court.
You're gonna like working
for Tom Ridge.
I have no idea what the Office
of Homeland Security is tasked with.
So you're going to have to
fill me in a little bit. Okay?
I called general accounting,
petted some fur backwards pretty hard.
If they don't have those desks
and computers here in just about...
All right. Move it on in!
In World War II, they called
this kind of thing war-born.
I guess it'll come together.
Your staff.
Is there anyone you'd like me to call?
God.
I think he's a little busy right now, Ted.
How about Sol Binder?
He knows his way around the Beltway.
Sol Binder. NSA, Lorraine.
Give him a call.
I know...
plus the porous borders,
a free and open society...
privacy laws guaranteed
under the Federal Constitution.
No, it's more than that.
A lot of it's structural.
Take the FBI. Great investigators.
Probably the best in the world. But they
don't bash in doors and shoot people.
They build legal cases against them.
CIA, DIA, they may be a little more
go-get-'em-type outfits...
but they're not really supposed
to work these shores.
We don't want a national Gestapo.
Stovepiping. You know what that is?
Every agency channels its own smoke
up and out its own chimney.
Don't want it wafting
into the other guy's office.
Agencies are in competition. Funding,
internal promotions, you name it.
- That's what the Army and Navy do.
- No, not like this.
This is a political town.
Look, say we stumbled onto something.
We're pulling on a little
investigative thread.
We share it with another agency.
Maybe they've got something
that can help us.
You want to know what's happened
more than once?
What?
We've read about it in the next day's
Washington Post.
Or it goes the other way.
The other guy's operation is tight as
a drum, only they don't help us...
they just follow it up.
Maybe they make an arrest,
catch a few little fish...
and we were after the whole school.
Bureaucracies in action.
I don't know how long
Homeland's going to last.
It's not official, but, Sol, if it were...
what if we had a chance
to build a bridge...
that would link all the agencies together
in some coherent way...
would you come help us build it?
What you are asking is a lot, my friend.
If I bolt the fold, I could be
committing career suicide.
I'm a little desperate, Sol.
I think the country's
a little desperate, too.
- Let me talk to Sarah.
- Talk to Sarah.
The Third Pillar of Islam?
Al Zakat: The Giving of Charity.
Originally, this was a free-will donation,
but now it is largely compulsory.
Two-and-a-half percent of every Moslem
income goes for the needy. Excuse me.
- What?
- They just took Dad away in handcuffs.
- Who took him away?
- They wouldn't talk.
They just put him in the car and left.
Class is dismissed.
We shall reconvene next Friday.
Class dismissed.
Azul, get those things out
of here! They stink.
- Americans.
- Tango 12 is in the building.
A- Teams. They've been in the country
since the 13th training the locals.
- Oh, yeah. I'm all shook up.
- Here we go.
So here I am. I'm being shelled.
I've got blisters on my ass,
I'm laying in mud.
I'm looking down on myself
from a UAV...
bouncing a video signal off a satellite
to a laptop lying in horse crap...
and Elvis just walked by.
Is this a dream?
You haven't seen the best part yet.
Meet your enemy.
Looks like they're dialing in the range.
Why aren't we sending in
something of our own?
Talking to the missus?
They're trying to talk the Taliban
provincial boss into surrender...
without spilling
all kinds of Afghani blood.
Call it in.
Just keep it outside the city walls.
Show them what we got.
Delroy 87 requesting a JDAM strike.
Coordinates, 32...
...7, one minute east.
Oh, yeah. They're all shook up.
- Town's ours. Let's go.
- Move it out!
Karzai!
You go, girl, I can relate!
Al Qaeda.
Losers!
Azul, it's my job
to download these people.
Next time, ask your friends
to take some of them alive.
- I'll give them back when I'm done.
- I'm sorry, sir.
Taliban Al Qaeda headed this way.
Yo! Tango 12!
- They're trying to take back the town.
- Let's set up a perimeter.
May I have a towel or something
to wipe my hands?
Just use the towel on your head, sheik.
Get in the cell.
This is a horrible mistake.
Dr. Fazul Adel.
What's your relationship with him, Saif?
We know you know him. You have
notebooks filled with his name.
You've got some other names
in your notebooks, too.
They all Al Qaeda, Saif?
Or maybe you were just buying rocks
over there.
I quote the words of...
our American Constitution:
"The right of the people is to be secure
in their person, houses, properties...
"and effects against
unreasonable searches and seizures. "
You have ignored these words
of our Founding Fathers.
I would like to speak to my attorney.
Personally, think it's the Agency's
biggest embarrassment...
- since the Angleton affair.
- Do you know what's hard?
We can't talk about all our successes,
and there's a lot of them...
I nearly lost my seat over NAFTA.
And if I get behind
a new non-union agency...
- it'll be the end of the line, believe me.
- Come on.
We're talking about security
of the homeland. We're at war.
"I think I'll just have to call my
union rep before I charge that hill, sir. "
Give me a break.
Admiral, the FBI
is a civil service operation.
Are you saying their performance
suffers because of it?
I think the President and Gov. Ridge...
want to keep us
out of the civil service system...
to get us up faster,
make us more adaptable. Fluid.
- CIA isn't fluid enough for you?
- I didn't say that, you did.
We could be creating a domestic
paramilitary operation here...
which may give comfort to some...
but I'm sure even you know
the dangers of the precedent it sets...
- Even me? Really?
- Ted.
Darling, hi. This is my wife, Alise.
- It's a pleasure.
- Hello, gentlemen.
- Are you okay?
- I think so. These darn shoes.
Let me get you out of here.
I better sit you down.
- Excuse us, gentlemen.
- Excuse us.
Certainly.
- Paramilitary?
- Well, it's a strong...
The Lone Ranger to the rescue.
Oh, boy, I was just about to
hang myself in there.
I'm sure you were fine.
- Admiral McKee, right?
- Yeah.
Well, well, well.
How does it feel
to be a cardboard target?
What?
The Administration, the Bureau,
the Agency...
all those wonderful elected officials
in there.
They know suicide attacks
can't be stopped.
Somebody's got to take the fall, right?
"Let's grab a couple of out-of-towners. "
That'll do it, right?
Brilliant.
You know, you and Ridge...
are the biggest patsies
since Lee Harvey Oswald.
They're all just scared, McKee.
I am. You are.
Everyone is.
Tell them to swing around south.
There's a big hole just over that berm!
No! They're going the wrong way!
Not that south! That south!
They just broke through our right flank!
What? No! We can't even communicate
with our friendlies.
All they've got
are a few fouled-up cell phones!
- You okay?
- Yeah, just get some damn Air here.
Get rid of that technical.
Delroy 87, this is Delroy 82.
Requesting vehicle strike coordinates.
Requesting close-end support.
- We're being overrun!
- 52s are still loitering.
Call it in.
87, our position is being overrun.
Requesting JDAM strike
right down on top of us!
Coordinates 32.33...
Everybody down!
Not exactly the James Bond lifestyle
I signed up for.
No!
God.
We need to interrogate them.
I need to find bin Laden.
It was courageous of you
to call the air strikes.
I'm proud to fight beside you.
No. He ain't on this list.
- Try the SFPD?
- We have been to the police.
We have been to the INS,
District Attorney, the US Attorney...
we have been everywhere!
This is outrageous!
- Come on, Mum.
- Outrageous!
Mum, come on,
the country's been attacked.
Mistakes are gonna happen.
"When an American suburbanite stands
at a service pump filling his car...
"he is not pumping gasoline.
He is pumping Islamic blood. "
Yes, I wrote that, too. In 1972.
I was a young academic,
trying to bring attention to myself.
- It was a phase.
- Recognize any of these men, Dr. Adel?
Not him? You sure?
He's Al Qaeda, Dr. Adel.
Both of you in the same cell?
Cell?
Terrorist cell?
Listen to me.
I lecture in many places. Afterwards,
I converse with many people.
I don't know who they all are.
I don't know this man.
This is a copy of your credit card
statement. December last year.
- It shows a $150 donation...
- This is a fabrication.
It's insane. Am I formally
being charged with a crime here?
Am I?
We have a magic wand.
We wave it
over all the intelligence agencies.
We mesmerize them,
put them under our hypnotic spell.
Then we induce them to send us
all their data...
so that we can get it into one central
computer. Our computer.
Right here:
The Office of Homeland Security.
Then we design a program.
We feed in a name. A time. A place.
A street. Anything.
Press enter. Everything known about
that name, or time, or place, comes up.
All the dots, Ted. All the dots.
Right there in front of you,
just waiting to be connected.
So?
Hell, it's safe.
Compartmentalized.
Computers don't talk
to the Washington Post.
And we keep the loop
practically down to you and me.
If there's a leak, they can just come
right down here and shoot us both.
The only trouble is going to be
getting the other agencies to comply.
They've gotta send us
everything they have. Everything.
Or it won't work.
You know, it just won't work.
So, those stovepipes you talked about...
I think they went into the junk heap,
September 12.
... first American was killed
today in combat...
against hundreds of Osama bin Laden
foreign fighters...
during an uprising at a makeshift prison
in Mazar-e-Sharif.
We know you're Al Qaeda, Damhir.
The equivalent of a major, I'm told.
That about right?
You know where Osama is?
What about Atef?
Get him out of here.
Benai. Benny. You're right up there.
Something like a colonel, right?
Tell me where Osama is, Benny.
- Did it work?
- You think you can sing?
- That guy sounded like a bird.
- Well, thank you. Thank you very much.
Learn anything in Taloqan?
Osama's in Tora Bora.
His number two, Mohammed Atef...
Kabul. I know.
You know Osama's exact whereabouts?
- No.
- Hill 8823.
I had a little thermobaric present
sent up that way.
- This man, here. How bad is he?
- Dying.
- Who is he?
- Member of an AQ cell, back in Seattle.
FBI thinks they're working
on a dirty bomb.
They've been on this guy
since the Kabul airport.
He needs to be medevaced
out of here, Joe. Now.
Go with him. Download him yourself.
We got an interrogation unit
in Kandahar.
A dirty bomb? You do it yourself.
You follow him all the way
to Gitmo if you have to.
Yes, sir.
Look, if they have someone
who even mentions your name...
and the word "radiologic"
in the same sentence...
- we're screwed.
- My fate...
is in the hands of Allah.
You look stunning, Vlenko.
Right out of GQ.
Sorry to be a fashion-smasher, Vlenko.
Put that on.
- Makes me look fat.
- Vlenko, you are fat.
Come on. What the hell are you doing?
- Shots!
Seattle, this is SE-21.
We've taken sniper fire in the alleyway.
Witness down.
- Fulbar, you see him?
- No!
Damn it!
My client is a victim of ethnic profiling
and nothing more, Your Honor.
Now, I'd like to think that this isn't
Nazi Germany or Stalinist Russia, but...
Counsel, we're here today
to determine your readiness for trial.
- Is the Prosecution ready to proceed?
- Yes, Your Honor.
Just a minute, Your Honor.
I've just been informed that our key
witness has met with an untimely end.
- Mr. Kahn.
- Khan.
Your Honor.
Mr. Khan, you're free to go.
However, I suggest
that you don't get picked up for...
Found this on the rooftop
two blocks away.
Is Mr. Simms or Miss Alrazi here?
That guy's working on a dirty bomb and
it is not a high school science project.
Suspended from his teaching duties?
For what?
My husband has been serving
that institution for 17 years.
Well, I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
I'm going to resign my position
in protest...
and then I'm going straight
to the media! Do you hear me?
- Is there anything I can do, Mrs. Adel?
- No. Please, both of you...
I'm just not fit
for human contact right now.
It's okay, Mum. Don't worry.
He'll be okay. Don't worry.
We'll get him out of there, all right?
He doesn't even have his medication.
Dad, you have to do something.
Mel, it doesn't sound right. I'll get into it.
Now, how does Josef's father
spell his first name? F-A-Z...
U- L. Fazul.
I'll make some calls.
Mel, are you okay?
Yeah. No.
Is anybody okay right now?
Agent Jane Fulbar?
Special Agent Roland...
Office of Professional Responsibility.
What you're doing here is illegal.
He has a restraining order against you
and you know it.
You'll probably be suspended for this,
maybe more.
We're going to
the Federal Building now.
Do you know
what that guy is working on?
You wanna follow us or you wanna
come in one of our cars? In bracelets.
Let's go.
For a non-drinking,
respectful Islamic man like yourself...
that morphine must've felt like...
27 virgins, hey, Hessan?
I'm no doctor, but I know this:
That morphine's worn off.
You're a man in great pain.
Now, this...
this is non-pain.
This is a double-dose. 54 virgins.
We know about your dirty bomb.
Only with your Russian friend
no longer with us...
you'll probably have to go with waste
as originally planned.
Where are you keeping that waste?
If you've lost your English skills,
there's someone else who can use this.
Jamaitja...
brings from Vancouver.
Jamaitja? Your friend here.
He's in Canada now?
One more question, and then I plunge.
Where in Seattle does your cell meet?
An address, Mohammed.
- Not Seattle. Oakland.
- Where in Oakland?
I've been in Afghanistan for six months.
I don't know. Please.
Detainee had a fly on his face.
I was just gonna get rid of it, sir.
Let him be.
Understand the sentiment, though.
They're all coming through.
If it relates to Homeland Security,
we've got it. All of it.
The new weapon of war.
Not a ship, not a plane. A computer.
- Information.
- It's a new world, Ted. New kind of war.
- Yeah.
- Admiral.
- Bradley Brand. I'm Agency.
- Good to meet you.
- Sol Binder.
- Hey.
I just got back from Guantanamo.
I hear this is the new information
clearinghouse for homeland threats.
We're getting there.
What can we do for you?
Are you aware of an Al Qaeda cell
operating out of Oakland, California?
They're playing with a dirty bomb.
LAX is the intended target.
We knew they were sniffing around
radiologic material.
We didn't know it was LAX.
- Excuse me.
- Tell me what you've got.
I've got some data on where the
dirty material may be coming from...
but not enough for an interdiction.
I was hoping you guys
could fill in some blanks.
- I'll do my best.
- What do you know about this man?
His name's Jamaitja.
He's got Canadian papers.
I don't know. Let's feed him
into the big boy, see what we've got.
Yeah, honey, I got the call
just a few minutes ago.
Oh, Dad. Where was he?
Some unused juvenile facility
outside of San Jose.
Is he being released?
There are some things
he'll have to explain later on...
but there's really nothing to hold him on.
They're gonna release him now.
Dad.
- Thank you.
- Mel...
I had a little difficulty
getting this number.
- Someone at the dorm room said...
- I got to call the Adels, okay?
They've been through hell.
All right, I'll call you back.
I love you, Daddy.
- What the hell are those for?
- Sorry about your suspension.
Come on in.
Well, it's bad.
Khan got another lawyer,
and he's raising holy hell.
And it's not my first offence.
I think they're gonna fire me.
Oh, man.
Where are they bringing him from,
Antarctica?
My dad said he was somewhere
near San Jose.
It's a long drive.
Anyone from the family of Adel?
Dr. Fazul Adel?
Yes.
- You're related to Fazul Adel?
- Yes, I am his wife.
This is his stepson, Josef.
I'm afraid I have some bad news for you.
Your husband committed suicide.
This is insane.
Dr. Adel didn't do anything. Nothing.
Melissa, honey, please.
I don't know how Dad expects
any of these people to help him.
Melissa, will you talk to your father?
He's as upset about this as you are.
Fine.
- Mel...
- You're a part of all this, Dad.
I used to be proud to be a McKee.
- I should go out there.
- It's better if I go alone, Ted.
At least until she calms down.
... findings are preliminary.
A member of Sen. Daschle's staff
is being treated for exposure to anthrax.
Members of Congress are asking...
Heinhoff.
... what can possibly happen next.
Khan is fair game again?
Isn't that just supreme. He's probably
in freaking Bahrain by now.
Oakland?
1893 Lake Merritt Boulevard.
Yeah, I got it. I'll catch the next flight.
Good guy. Don't shoot.
Come on in.
- A spook? A real one?
- Yeah. Why?
I just never met one of you guys before.
Well, from here on in,
I think we'll all be working a lot closer.
Amen. Frank Heinhoff, Seattle office.
Bradley Brand. Kromberg Station.
You guys get any action over there?
The place has been empty for two days.
You hungry?
- Yeah.
- Hold on.
We got some action.
They're speaking Arabic.
Okay, they're meeting,
the others are late...
We might be able to grab
their whole damn cell.
You guys have something to do
with locating this place?
No. It's this new outfit, Homeland.
I had some intel. They cross-referenced
it with stuff they had...
- and this address popped up.
- Oh, yeah. Here we go.
I don't see Khan.
You're looking
for that son of a bitch, too?
Hold on. They have a cell call.
They know we're here.
We've been burned. Execute.
Do you have a point of origination
on that signal?
They're a block from here.
FBI!
Get against the wall!
- Show me your hands!
- Put your hands behind your head!
Turn around!
How much do you want to bet Saif
Khan's prints are all over that thing?
Damn it!
Al Qaeda cell boss from Hamburg.
According to Langley,
he's carrying new marching orders...
to his brothers in Pakistan.
Boy, I'd sure like to know
what route he's taking.
Yeah, Langley, too.
I think they'd like to drop him
a nice card or note or something.
- You guys find anything?
- Yeah.
Blank American passports.
They're perfect looking.
Training camp locations, list of camp
grads already stateside...
- It's a goldmine, sir.
- Right.
Tell the mortuary boys
to do a good job in here.
I want matched body parts in every bag.
Hope these arms and legs
got serial numbers on them.
They must've dropped
a damn thermobaric up here.
Yeah, I guess.
- Somebody taking x-rays down here?
- He's on dialysis.
Son of a bitch.
Just need to see your driver's license
for a sec.
Have a nice stay in America, sir.
Put your hands behind your head!
Hands behind your head!
Sweetheart.
I don't want to talk to you.
Melissa.
He left me, Mum.
- Baby, I am so sorry.
- I loved him.
It's really clicking out there.
It's working better than I ever dreamed.
We have a problem, Sol.
There are people being held...
because they have dark skin
and the wrong accents.
I know, it will clean itself up.
It'll just take some time...
Not good enough.
Damn it, Sol.
The people of this country
are losing their civil rights...
and the bad guy's already won.
No.
Now you're preaching to the choir.
You remember when I said
we don't want a national Gestapo?
I meant it.
Let me see if I can't get those big boys
to help us...
speed up the processing
of these names...
separate the good apples from the bad.
I'm on this thing, Ted. I'm on it.
Thanks, Sol.
In four short months,
our nation has comforted the victims...
begun to rebuild New York
and the Pentagon...
rallied a great coalition...
captured, arrested and rid the world
of thousands of terrorists...
destroyed Afghanistan's
terrorist training camps...
and freed a country
from brutal oppression.
I'm happy that you're back.
I don't know if I'm happy
that we're co-workers again.
We're spies.
We can get away with anything.
... and terrorist leaders who urged
followers to sacrifice their lives...
are running for their own.
America and Afghanistan
are now allies against terror.
We'll be partners
in rebuilding that country.
And this evening we welcome
the distinguished interim leader...
of a liberated Afghanistan:
Chairman Hamid Karzai.
Guess what?
I'm not a mortician anymore.
The President's speaking, jackass.
... and use technology
to track the arrivals and departures...
of visitors to the United States.
Homeland Security will make America
not only stronger...
but in many ways, better.
For too long, our culture has said,
"If it feels good, do it. "
Now America is embracing a new ethic,
and a new creed:
"Let's roll. "
She won't return my calls.
Time, honey.
Just have to give her a little time.
We have known freedom's price.
We have shown freedom's power.
And in this great conflict,
my fellow Americans...
we will see freedom's victory.
Thank you all. May God bless.
I guess I'll never be
a part of this fight again, will I?
We don't know that yet.
I know you are the best of the best.
Which probably means you people are...
- the ones with the most to lose.
- How's that, sir?
Because if you jump ship
and come aboard ours...
which may or may not stay afloat...
you may not be welcomed back.
And we could sink.
Congress hasn't approved
our existence yet.
- Yes?
- Lf we sign on with Homeland...
would we be restricted to
working only domestically?
No. In that we've been given
no official mandate...
we've sort of made up our own.
This has to be both a domestic
and an international operation.
Those of you who've worked the foreign
venue, you'll continue to work there.
Those who worked the domestic side,
you'll continue to work here.
But the overall singular mission...
is the defense
of the American homeland.
That's about it.
I won't blame any of you
for not joining us.
But I would appreciate a response
within 24 hours.
We need to know ASAP.
Thank you.
I'm in.
I'm in, too.
- I'm in.
- I'm in, sir.
- Question, sir.
- Yes.
- Osama bin Laden. High on our hit list?
- Top of the list.
- Old dog, new tricks.
- Welcome aboard.
Did that just happen?
I did tell them how tippy all this is, right?
Yeah. You told them.
Talk to you alone a moment, sir?
It's kind of important, Admiral.
At least, to me.
Bad news. They're not backing off.
You don't resign quietly...
they'll indict you on abuse
under the color of authority.
- Thanks. I kind of knew that.
- There's some other bad news.
Are you a sadist?
We're still partners.
Really?
I used his credit card
to make a donation.
I assume they found it.
I feel nothing. I didn't hate or love him.
- He was nothing like my real father.
- You did not know your real father.
I've read about him.
I've spoken to my mother about him
many times.
She never knew the glory
that filled that man.
The struggle within, the struggle without
against the Kafirs.
He never lost God in either struggle.
Never once.
I wish he could have seen me.
With that rifle? That Russian pig?
You were filled with your father that day.
You would have made him
so proud to heart.
Except for this.
Your mission is to assimilate, Josef.
What is this fuzz?
Me not shaving, nothing more.
That relationship of yours. Renew it.
Fan its flames.
Do you have any idea
how valuable that is for our future?
Melissa.
Please forgive me.
I'll never leave you again.
Ever.
Ripped by:
SkyFury