Manuel.
Manuel!
I think....
I think I found you one.
Look, I called you, right?
Soon as I couldn't pull it out myself,
I called you, John.
It's okay, it's okay.
We had to tie her down, okay?
It's okay.
This is Constantine.
John Constantine, asshole.
Sure.
What the hell?
I need a mirror.
Now. At least 3 feet high.
Move! Go, now!
This is Kramer.
Chas Kramer, asshole.
Asshole.
What? Oh, this is Kramer.
Chas Kramer, asshole.
- Chas!
- What?
- Move the car.
- Why?
Move the damn car!
"Chas, move the car. "
There, car's moved.
Lift it up over the bed.
Tie that end off.
Hennessy, over the top.
Close your eyes.
And whatever happens, don't look.
No!
Show yourself.
Smile pretty, you vain prick.
For your boss.
Pull it!
Ma? Ma?
Like I said, I found you something,
didn't I, John? Didn't I?
What happened in there?
Going to a lot of meetings, I see.
Keeps the voices out so I can sleep.
I have to sleep, John.
I need some help, Father.
You do?
From me?
What kind of-?
- Hey, listen, I-
- That exorcism wasn't right.
Listen to the ether.
Anything unusual, you let me know.
Come on, you don't need its protection.
It'll be like back in the day.
A few days.
Okay.
Okay. For you, John.
John, why would you do that
if you know it's not my car?
- I told you to move it.
- You did tell me to move it...
...but if you'd said you were dropping
a 300-pound mirror with a demon...
...I would've moved it further, John.
- Take Alvarado.
- Yeah, thank you. I know what to take.
You ever think if you told me more now
that maybe I could help out?
- No?
- Nope.
Nope?
Of course it's a nope.
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
It's been...
...two weeks since my last confession.
I killed a man today.
Another one.
I didn't even see his face, I just...
...pulled the trigger, and he went away.
Most cops go 20 years
without firing their guns.
Why do I always know
where these guys are?
Where to aim, when to fire.
I'm wondering, is there
something wrong with me, Father?
Something damned?
God has a plan for you.
He has a plan for us all.
You mustn't let your faith
be overshadowed by guilt.
Yeah, I'm trying.
I'm trying real hard.
Isabel.
Things I've beaten.
Things most people never even heard of.
And now I'm gonna be done in by this.
Wouldn't be the first, John.
Come on, Les.
You saved me before,
you can do it again, right?
This is aggressive.
Twenty years ago,
you didn't wanna be here.
Now you don't wanna leave.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
John, you really need to prepare.
- Make arrangements.
- No need.
I already know exactly where I'm going.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
- Detective.
- No, no, no.
- Angela, wait.
You don't need to see this, okay? No.
Give us the room, please.
Isabel.
She fell from the roof?
She jumped.
- No.
- Look...
...I know it's hard to accept.
She was sick.
- Isabel wouldn't kill herself.
- Angie.
- She wouldn't kill herself.
- Detective.
- Period.
Period!
Angie, there were security cameras.
- Hold the door. You going down?
- Not if I can help it.
A new case?
The big score? The mother lode?
The one you've been waiting for?
- Humor me.
- Don't I always?
Oh, yeah, that's-
Much obliged. Thank you.
How you feeling, John?
So, what's new?
Bullet shavings from
the assassination attempt on the pope...
...holy-water ampoules
from the River Jordan...
...and- Oh, you'll love this.
- screech beetle from Amityville.
Yeah, it's funny to you, but to the
fallen, that's like nails on a chalkboard.
What is it, exactly, with you and bugs?
I just like them.
Yeah. Who doesn't?
Yeah, easy there, hero.
- That's dragon's breath.
- I thought you couldn't get it anymore.
Yeah, well, I know a guy
who knows a guy.
So, what's the action?
I just pulled a soldier demon
out of a little girl.
Looked like it was trying
to come through.
Yeah, I know how it sounds.
No, we're finger puppets
to them, John...
...not doorways.
They can work us, but they can't
come through onto our plane.
Check the scrolls anyway.
See if there's any precedent.
Sure thing, John.
Anything else?
Wouldn't happen to have
anything for a-?
On the house.
All right, question. How much longer
do I have to be your slave, John?
You're not my slave, Chas.
You're my very appreciated apprentice.
Like Tonto or Robin.
Or that skinny fellow
with the fat friend.
Right. So then why don't I apprentice
something besides driving, then, John?
John? John.
I love our little talks, John.
May I take your coat, Mr. Constantine?
No, thanks,
I'm not gonna be staying long.
- How about you, ma'am?
- Oh, no, I'm not staying long either.
I really need to speak with him.
It's important.
First come, first served.
So you're rude no matter where you are.
- Father.
- Hi.
- You have news. Yes.
- Yes, I spoke with the bishop.
I know what you want, son.
Still keeping your all-seeing eye
on me, Gabriel?
I'm flattered.
Well, I could offer something...
...about how a shepherd leads
even the most wayward of his flock...
...but it might sound disingenuous.
She has to have a Catholic funeral,
Father. She has to.
- Angela, it's still considered a mortal sin.
- She didn't commit suicide.
The bishop believes otherwise.
You know the rules.
Oh, rules.
Father.
David.
This is Isabel.
God was the only one
she ever believed loved her.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I've been seeing some unusual
soul traffic lately.
You might consider
giving me an extension.
I could do your side some good
these days.
You still trying to buy your way
into heaven?
What about the minions I've sent back?
- That alone should guarantee my entry.
- How many times have I told you?
That's not the way this works.
Why, haven't I served him enough?
- What does he want from me?
- Only the usual.
Self-sacrifice, belief.
- Oh, I believe, for chrissake.
- No, no, you know.
And there's a difference. You've seen.
I never asked to see.
I was born with this curse.
A gift, John.
One that you've squandered
on selfish endeavors.
I'm pulling demons out of little girls.
Who's that for?
Everything you've ever done,
you've only ever done for yourself.
To earn your way
back into his good graces.
Impossible rules, endless regulations...
...who goes up, who goes down
and why.
You don't even understand us.
You're the one who should go
to hell, half-breed.
Why me, Gabriel?
It's personal, isn't it?
I didn't go to church enough,
I didn't pray enough...
...I was 5 bucks short
in the collection plate. Why?
You are going to die young...
...because you smoked 30 cigarettes
a day since you were 15.
And you're going to go to hell...
...because of the life you took.
You're fucked.
At least it's nice out.
He always had a rotten sense of humor.
And his punch lines are killers.
John!
Constantine, it's raining! John! Hey!
Twenty-two women were found buried
in the assailant's back yard.
So much damage had been done
to the bodies, police had to match...
Police report she had been
physically penetrated...
...over 100 times and buried alive.
- found locked in a storage freezer,
his head severed and his organs...
He stuffed Holly's body into...
- The bodies ravished by the unknown...
- He used a small handsaw...
Had nearly decapitated...
Even his eyes were gouged out.
Isabel.
I'm so sorry, Izzy.
Constantine.
Dodson.
Hello?
Hello.
Hey. Hey, buddy, got a light?
Should've minded
your own business, exorcist.
I know where you're going, John.
You're going to Midnite's.
You're supposed to wait in the cab.
It's a haven for those who rise and fall.
I remember reading about this, John.
- You read too much, kid. It's a bar.
- It's a bar?
It's a bar. Papa Midnite is a crusader for
good. He swore the oath of neutrality.
- John, the man's a legend.
- Yeah.
Can you please get me
into this bar, John, please?
I'm begging you, John, please?
- Sure, you can get in.
- I can get in?
If you can get in.
If I can get-? It's a bear, though, right?
Or two ducks in a cloud?
Two frogs on a bench.
No, no, I'm with the guy you just-
John! John!
I'm with him, though.
Rat in a dress.
Of course it is. Rat in a dress.
I'm just testing. I'm just testing.
Don't get up.
You've been absent some time.
Have you come here with relics to sell?
No, I'm out of that now.
I've been too busy.
Perhaps peddling forgeries has ended up
being bad for your health.
Midnite, Jesus...
...I thought the thing was authentic.
I see now.
Your health is bad for other reasons.
How long?
A few months, maybe a year.
I thought I heard thunder last night.
Must have been
Satan's stomach growling.
You're the one soul he'd come
up here himself to collect.
So I've heard.
Well, I am most certain
you did not come here...
...for a sympathetic shoulder
to cry on.
A demon just attacked me,
right out in the open on Figueroa.
They don't like you, John.
How many have you
deported back to hell?
Not some angry half-breed, Midnite.
A full-fledged demon, here, on our plane.
Clearly I do not have to remind you
that is impossible.
And yesterday I saw a soldier demon...
...trying to chew its way out
through a little girl.
Listen, John, demons stay in hell,
angels in heaven...
...the great détente
of the original superpowers.
Thanks for the history lesson, Midnite.
You've been a tremendous help.
Now...
...I need to use the chair.
John, forgetting the fact that it would
almost certainly kill you...
...you know I am neutral.
And as long as the balance
is maintained, I take no sides.
Before you were a bartender...
...you were one witch doctor
against, what, 30 Ashgar?
- And I-
- You were Constantine.
The John Constantine.
Once.
This isn't the usual game, I can feel it.
Something's coming.
Spooky.
Balthazar.
That expression alone
has made my entire night.
I'll make your night.
I'll deport your sorry ass right where
you stand, you half-breed shit!
You know the rules of my house.
While here, you will abide by them.
Johnny boy.
Word is you're on your way down.
Fresh meat.
Finger-licking good.
We have a meeting now, John.
What? I didn't catch that.
Welcome to my life.
Mr. Constantine.
- I saw you-
- I remember.
- And then I saw you at the-
- Regular kismet.
I'd like to ask you a few questions,
if that would be okay.
I'm not really in the talking mood
right now.
Well, maybe you could just listen then.
Please?
Always a catch.
My sister was murdered yesterday.
- Sorry to hear.
- Thanks.
She was a patient at Ravenscar.
She jumped off the roof.
Thought you said she was murdered.
Yeah, well, Isabel wouldn't
have taken her own life.
Yeah, what kind of mental patient
kills herself?
That's just crazy.
Look, I've heard your name
around the precinct.
I know the circles you travel in.
The occult, demonology, exorcisms.
Just before my sister was committed,
she became deeply paranoid.
She started talking about demons,
angels.
Now, I think someone got to her,
Mr. Constantine.
I think they brainwashed her
into stepping off that roof.
Some kind of legion or cult.
Sounds like a theory, detective.
Good luck.
I thought with your background,
you could at least...
...point me in the right direction.
Yeah, okay, sure.
It wasn't a suicide.
My sister was a devout Catholic.
Do you understand that?
If she took her own life-
Her soul would go straight to hell...
...where she'd be ripped apart over
and over in screaming, brutal agony...
...for all eternity. That it?
That about right?
Goddamn you.
Detective.
What if I told you that God
and the devil made a wager...
...a kind of standing bet
for the souls of all mankind?
I'd tell you to stay on your meds.
Humor me. No direct contact with
humans. That would be the rule.
- Just influence. See who would win.
- Okay, I'm humoring you.
- Why?
- Who knows.
- Maybe just for the fun of it. No telling.
- Oh, so it's fun.
It's fun when a man beats his wife to
death, when a mother drowns her baby.
And you think the devil is responsible?
People are evil, Mr. Constantine. People.
You're right. We're born
capable of terrible things.
Then sometimes something else comes
along and gives us just the right nudge.
Well, this has been real educational...
...but I don't believe in the devil.
You should. He believes in you.
It's a power outage.
Not likely.
- What?
- We should go. Now.
What is that?
Wings.
Maybe talons.
You're kidding. Of what?
Something that's not
supposed to be here.
That's really not going to help.
- Close your eyes.
- Why?
Suit yourself.
Demons stay in hell, huh?
Tell them that.
Don't worry. Happens to everyone
the first time.
It's the sulfur.
Sulfur.
What were those things?
Demons.
- Scavengers of the damned.
- No, no. It's impossible.
Yeah. And I don't think
they were after me.
You really believe
she wouldn't commit suicide.
Isabel?
Never in a million years.
Well, let's be sure.
Let's see if she's in hell.
Oh, was it supposed to be hot or cold?
In front of the chair.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
- These are all Isabel's things?
- Yeah.
- How about the cat?
- Duck?
Yeah, why?
Duck.
Oh, you think that's strange.
Cats are good.
Half in, half out anyway.
If this is some kind of spell
or something...
...don't you need candles
and a pentagram for it to work?
Why, do you have any?
- This is crazy.
- Yes.
I need you to leave.
- I'm sorry?
- Angela, please.
The apartment.
Okay.
Be careful with that cat.
God, I hate this part.
- Isabel.
- Constantine.
Angela.
Jesus.
- Constantine, what-?
- Twins.
Jesus. What?
- You were twins.
- What did you say?
- She killed herself.
- What?
And she's damned for it.
How is this possible?
I need to eat.
Hey! Hey, what are you doing in here?
Relax, man.
Slow down!
What the hell kind of place is this?
John.
When I was a kid, I could see things.
Things humans aren't supposed to see.
Things you shouldn't have to see.
My parents were normal.
They did what most parents would do.
They made it worse.
You think you're crazy long enough...
...you find a way out.
- You tried to kill yourself.
- I didn't try anything.
Officially, I was dead for two minutes.
But when you cross over...
...time stops.
Take it from me,
two minutes in hell is a lifetime.
When I came back...
...I knew...
...all the things I could see were real.
Heaven and hell are right here.
Behind every wall, every window.
The world behind the world,
and we're smack in the middle.
Angels and demons can't
cross over onto our plane.
So instead we get
what I call half-breeds.
The influence peddlers.
They can only whisper in our ears, but
a single word can give you courage...
...or turn your favorite pleasure
into your worst nightmare.
Those with the demon's touch...
...like those part angel,
living alongside us.
They call it the balance.
I call it hypocritical bullshit.
So when a half-breed breaks the rules...
...I deport their sorry ass
straight back to hell.
I don't get them all...
...but I've been hoping to get enough
to ensure my...
- ...retirement.
- I don't understand.
I'm a suicide, Angela.
When I die, the rules say
I've got just one place to go.
You're trying to buy your way
into heaven.
What would you do
if you were sentenced to a prison...
...where half the inmates
were put there by you?
I guess God has a plan for all of us.
God's a kid with an ant farm, lady.
He's not planning anything.
When we were little...
...Isabel saw things too.
Dodson.
Guard spotted him groping the body,
then he ran across the street.
Came in here, and he had a go
at the entire stock.
He drowned himself in alcohol
in under a minute.
Could've been a member
of my fraternity.
Hey, what the hell is he doing here?
He's okay.
Why didn't you call me,
you son of a bitch?
Yes?
What do you mean?
What?
How?
Got it. Bye.
I need to see where Isabel died.
Séances, Ouija boards, channeling.
Our father thought she was
just trying to get attention.
She certainly did that.
She'd tell everyone about the things
she said she saw.
She'd scare my mother half to death.
And then she stopped talking
for almost a year.
So you had her committed.
Yeah.
How long?
Two weeks.
This time.
She'd get better, and then she'd
get worse. Recently, a lot worse.
That symbol that was cut
in the dead guy's hand...
...does it have something to do
with this?
I'm a cop, John, remember?
You don't walk off the roof of a building
without leaving something behind.
And I showed you everything
she left behind in that box, but feel free.
Maybe she left something else.
Not something a cop would find.
Something just for you.
You were her twin, Angela.
Twins tend to think alike.
- I'm not like my sister.
- But you were once.
When you were kids.
When you'd spend every second
with each other.
You'd start a sentence, she'd finish it.
You'd get hurt, she'd cry.
That was a long time ago.
That kind of bond doesn't
just disappear.
There is nothing here.
- Hey. Come on.
- She planned her death in this room.
She thought it up right here.
Right where you're standing.
She knew you'd come. She counted
on you to see what she saw...
...feel what she felt,
know what she knew.
- What did she do, Angela?
- How should I know?
- I don't know.
- What would you do?
What did she do, Angela? You know
what she did. What did she do, Angela?
You know what she did. What are
you afraid of? What did she do?
- What did she do?
- I don't know!
When we were girls...
...we would leave each other messages.
In light.
In breath.
On the windows.
John, there is no 17th act
in Corinthians.
Corinthians goes to 21 acts
in the Bible in hell.
They have Bibles in hell.
Paints a different view of Revelations.
Says the world will not end
by God's hand...
...but be reborn in the embrace
of the damned.
Though if you ask me...
...fire's fire.
16:29, 16:30.
Oh, my, this is certainly not good.
"The sins of the father would only
be exceeded by the sins of the son. "
- Whose son?
- But he can't cross over, B.
- Impossible to cross over.
- Whose son? God's son?
No, the other one. Devil had a son too.
Here it is.
This is the sign of Mammon...
...the son of the devil.
Well, hold on, it says here-