Tequila and tonic with a wedge of lemon.
Why were you yelling ?
The girl at the check-in counter ?
I'm sorry, uh...
Do I know you ?
I'm on your flight.
L. A. ?
No ring 'cause you're single or
because you don't like wearing one ?
You're asking me if I'm married ?
Are you married ?
No. No, not anymore.
So what's your name ?
Ana-Lucia.
So tell me, Ana-Lucia,
why are you drinkin' tequila
and tonics at ten to noon ?
I hate flying,
and they stuck me all the
way in the back of the plane.
So where are you sitting ?
23B.
42F.
Wanna trade ?
Oceanic flight 815 departing
Sydney for Los Angeles...
a flight like any other.
A plane full of strangers,
among them a doctor
and a con artist,
a soldier
and a lottery winner,
an addict
and a prisoner.
But en route to its destination,
something goes wrong.
Ladies and gentlemen, please return to
your seats and fasten your seatbelts.
It's normal.
Oh, I know.
Just never been a very good flier.
My husband keeps reminding me
that planes wanna be in the air.
Well, he sounds like a very smart man.
I'll be sure and tell him that
when he gets back from the bathroom.
and somehow 48 passengers...
survived.
Walt !
Haa... my leg...
Help !
Please help me !
Help me ! I'm having contractions.
Aah ! Get away ! Get away from...
Excuse me.
Did you ever use a needle ?
I made the drapes in my apartment.
That's fantastic. Listen,
do you have a second ? I
could use a little help here.
Help with what ?
With this.
Look, I'd do it myself. I'm a
doctor. But I just can't reach it.
You want me to sew that up ?
If you wouldn't mind.
Of course I'll.
Thank you.
They are complete strangers,
stranded on a faraway island,
scared and waiting.
You'd think they would have come by now.
What ?
Who ?
Anyone.
I don't know your name.
I'm Kate.
Jack.
and the only thing more mysterious
than the people they're stranded with...
is the island itself.
Terrific.
A new day arrives,
and still no rescue.
I used to have a stomach.
How do you know how to do all that ?
I was a military communications officer.
Oh, yeah ?
You ever see battle ?
I fought in the Gulf War.
No way. What were
you, Air Force ? Army ?
The republican guard.
The comic's in spanish.
You read spanish ?
No.
I found it.
But in the face of
disaster, hope remains.
Is it working ?
It seems to be,
except we're not picking up a signal.
There is one thing we could try.
What ?
Seeing if we can get a
signal from high ground.
Hey !
We've got a bar.
Mayday ! Mayday !
What is that ?
Feedback.
Feedback from what ?
What would do that ?
We can't transmit because something
else is already transmitting.
- Transmitting from where ?
- What ?
Somewhere close. The signal's strong.
It's  the rescue party. It has to be.
That's french ! The french are coming !
I've never been so happy
to hear the french !
Does anyone speak french ?
She does.
"I'm alone now.
I'm  on the island alone.
Please, someone, come.
The others... they're...
they're dead.
It... it killed them all.
It's a loop.
Iteration... it's
repeating the same message.
It's a distress call. It's
been playing over and over...
for 16 years.
Guys...
where are we ?
There's gonna be a memorial service
back at the camp for those...
for those who didn't make it,
for everyone to say good-bye.
I'd like to be there for that.
Okay.
Maybe if you wanted to
say something, you know,
about your husband ?
Doctor,
my husband is not dead.
Rose,
he was in the tail section of the plane.
It broke off in mid-flight. I'm sorry,
but everyone who was in the
rear of the plane is gone.
They're probably thinking
the same thing about us.
The mysteries of the
island begin to unfold.
Doctor ?
You coming ?
And as one man looks for answers...
another finds purpose.
How are they...
the others ?
Thirsty.
Hungry.
Waiting to be rescued.
And they need someoneto
tell them what to do.
Me ?
I can't.
Why can't you ?
Because I'm not a leader.
And yet they all treat you like one.
I don't know how to help them.
I'll fail. I'll...
I don't have what it takes.
Why are you out here, Jack ?
I think I'm going crazy.
No, crazy people don't know they're going
crazy. They think they're getting saner.
I'm an ordinary man, Jack.
I live in the real world.
But this place
is different.
It's special.
The others don't want to talk
about it because it scares them,
but we all know it.
We all feel it.
I've looked into the eye of this island,
and what I saw
was beautiful.
What if everything that happened here
happened for a reason ?
So... why are you out here ?
Chasing something.
The white rabbit.
"Alice in Wonderland."
Yeah.
Wonderland, because who I'm chasing,
he's not there.
But you see him ?
Yes.
But he's not there.
What if your leader is a reluctant one ?
What if the pain he
holds gets in the way ?
you want to tell me what happened ?
Couple guys jumped mark silverman.
But they didn't jump you ?
You don't want to be a hero.
You don't want to try
and save everyone. Because
when you fail...
you just don't have what it takes.
Never thought I'd see the day, Jack.
You barge into my O. R.
You work on my patient.
How many drinks did
you have at lunch, dad ?
Now in my professional opinion, ladies
and gentlemen, and that's all I have,
by the time I was called in,
the damage was irreversible.
Okay then. I think we're done
here. A final report will be filed.
Okay.
I need to...
revise my statement.
I didn't come into the O. R.
until well into the procedure.
J ack...
I was warned by one of the nurses
that my father was operating
under the influence.
Jack, this is not the time...
by the time I got there, it
was clear that my father was
not  only incapacitated
but that he had also
severed the patient's hepatic artery,
which, in my professional opinion...
caused the crisis
which led to her death.
He's gone, Jack.
He'll be back.
This time it's different.
I want you to bring him back.
I can't.
"I can't ?"
You don't get to say "I can't,"
not after what you did.
You bring your father home, Jack.
Where is he ?
Australia.
The maid says he hasn't used
the bed in the past three days.
Did he rent a car from the concierge ?
No, sir.
Quite honestly, Mr. Shephard,
I don't think any rental agent in Sydney
would lease your father a car in his condition.
He left his wallet.
Perhaps you should talk to
the police, Mr. Shephard.
That's him.
What do you mean, you
won't put it on the plane ?
I'm sorry, Mr. Shephard, but our policy is that
the body must have the proper documentation.
- There's just no latitude.
- No latitude.
Chrissy,
in 16 hours, I need to land at L. A. X.
And I need that coffin to clear customs,
because there's gonna be a hearse waiting there.
And I need that hearse to take me
and that coffin to a cemetery. Why ?
Chrissy ? Why can't I just bring him to a
funeral home and make all the arrangements ?
Why can't I really take my
time with it ? Because...
Because I need it to be done.
I need it to be over.
How great is the need for the leader
to finally emerge ?
It's been six days.
We're all still waiting,
waiting for someone to come.
But what if they don't ?
Last week, most of us were strangers.
But we're all here now.
And God knows how long
we're gonna be here.
But if we can't live together...
we're gonna die alone.
Hey, hey !
What's the matter ?
That pregnant lady fell down.
Claire, can you hear me ?
Hi.
It's me. It's Kate.
Just take it easy, okay ?
She needs water.
Don't move, okay ?
How do you survive on an island
The water's gone.
Someone stole it !
When you don't know who you can trust ?
Well, it's about time.
For what ?
Where's the water ?
That's  better.
Get off of me.
Give us the water now !
Touch me again, huh ?
Do you really think I
stoled your damn water ?
We know you gave two
bottles to the korean.
It's not here.
I traded Mr. Miyagi the last of
my water for a fish he caught.
You gave him your last two bottles ?
Water has no value, freckles.
It's gonna rain sooner or later.
And hell, I'm an optimist.
Here.
Figure that makes us
even for the tampa job.
What could possibly make
us even for the tampa job ?
How about the known whereabouts
of the man who ruined your life ?
That guy... Frank Duckett... runs
a shrimp truck down in Sydney.
This is him ?
That's him.
What brings you to Sydney ?
Business.
What's your handle
back in the states ?
I was a
a chief of surgery.
Was ?
Yeah, was.
I have a
a son. He's about your age.
Right now,
he thinks that I hate him.
There's a pay phoneover here.
One simple phone call,
and I could fix everything.
Why don't you ?
Because I am weak.
It's fate.
Some people are just supposed to suffer.
That's why the Red Sox will
never win the damn series.
This, uh,
this business that you have,
will it ease your suffering ?
Yeah.
Then what are you doing here ?
Can vengeance be so blind
that a man is unable to see...
the man he's killed is
not the man he sought ?
Tell Hibbs I would have paid.
How do you know Hibbs ?
You don't know what
you're doing, do you ?
It'll come back around.
That's why the Sox will
never win the series.
What did you just say ?
I said that's why the Red
Sox will never win the series.
What the hell's that supposed to mean ?
It's just something
my father used to say.
Your daddy...
he a doctor, too ?
Was.
He's dead.
Why do you want to
know about my father ?
No reason.
What do you think his story is ?
Who ?
Locke ?
No offense, mate, but
if there was one person on this island I
would put my absolute faith in to save us all,
it would be John Locke.
- Hand 'em over !
- How about no ?
There's other people here,
or don't you give a crap ?
- Knock it off !
- Stay out !
In the absence of law,
how do 48 people coexist ?
What's going on ?
Jethro here is hoarding
the last of the peanuts.
What about the rest of the food ?
We  kinda
ate it all.
What ?
How are we gonna find sustenance ?
We hunt.
Who is this guy ?
You've got to move, colonel.
Your troops are across enemy lines.
Patience...
the quality which you lack,
GL-12... is the hallmark of a leader.
Hallmark, huh ?
Tell me more about
being a leader, Locke.
I'm just playing a game, Randy. It's
my lunch hour. I can play a game.
Yeah.
Tell me, what's a walkabout ?
"Experience the dream journeys
of the fabled australian outback."
You have no right
taking that off my desk.
So you
wander around
hunting and gathering food, right ?
On foot ?
Not that you would
understand, but a walkabout
is a journey of spiritual renewal where
one derives strength from the earth
and becomes inseparable from it.
I have vacation days. I'm going,
Randy. I already made a reservation.
Why do you torture yourself ?
I mean, imagining you're some hunter
on walkabouts ? Wake up.
You can't do any of that.
Just...
don't tell me what I can't do.
I booked this tour a month ago.
You've already got my money.
Now I demand a place on that bus.
- You misrepresented yourself.
- I never lied.
You neglected to tell
us about your condition.
My condition is not an issue.
I've lived with it for four years.
It's never kept me from doing anything.
Unfortunately, it is an issue
for our insurance company.
I can't keep the bus waiting any longer.
It isn't fair to the other people.
Hey, don't talk to me about fair !
Hey. Hey, don't you walk away from me.
You don't know who you're dealing with !
Don't ever tell me
what I can't do, ever !
This is destiny. This is my destiny.
I'm supposed to do this, damn it !
Don't tell me what I can't do !
How common is the common man ?
Does he have potential ?
Locke.
Does his destiny ultimately matter ?
In the search for answers
to the island's mysteries,
they find proof
that they are not alone.
Please just listen to me !
I'm a survivor of a plane crash.
I found the wire on the beach.
I followed it.
I thought it might have
something to do with
the transmission we
picked up on the receiver
with a french woman repeating
on a loop for 16 years.
Has it really been that long ?
You.
Nearly two months we survived here.
Two months before...
your distress signal...
the message I heard...
you said,
"It killed them all."
It was them.
The others.
What others ?
Have you seen other
people on this island ?
No.
But I hear them...
out there in the jungle.
They whisper.
Help me !
He held me down.
Which way did he go ?
I don't know. I couldn't see.
What's going on ?
He just ran away.
He was trying to hurt my baby.
It's okay.
We're so intent on pointing the finger
at one another that we're ignoring
the simple, undeniable truth that
the problem isn't here, it's there !
They've attacked us !
Maybe it's time we stopped blaming
us and started worrying about them !
We're not the only people on
this island, and we all know it !
scared and in danger,
and looking for any way to get home...
What are we talking about doing now...
looking for another excuse to get chased down
and killed by whatever lives in the jungle ?
We can't keep doing this.
We need to get off this island.
You think any of us want to be here ?
No.
So are you suggesting something ?
Yeah.
We build a raft.
What are we looking for again ?
Any long piece of metal or plastic
tubing. Anything that looks like a...
That could work as a frame.
Am I being punished ?
What, you think working with
your old man is punishment ?
Feels like punishment.
This is us taking
control of our destiny.
We've talked about
taking some time apart.
You're not taking my son.
You can go if you want
to, but Walt stays with me.
I'll give him everything he needs.
Except for his dad. He's
not going with you, no !
We're not married, Michael.
I'm his mother, and
I'm steadily employed.
Who do you think the
court's gonna side with ?
Michael Dawson ?
Can I help you ?
I'm Brian Porter.
Susan's Brian ?
Susan know you're here, man ?
Susan died yesterday.
Hey, Walt.
Who are you ?
I'm your father.
Where's Brian ?
Brian's not here.
I come to...
bring you home with me.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
See this knife Walt ?
Right here.
Focus on it. Picture
it in your mind's eye.
Now do it again, but see it.
Wow...
Yes !
You had it in you, Walt.
It was weird. I actually saw it in my
mind or something, like it was real.
Who's to say it wasn't ?
Hey !
What the hell is going on ?
Give me that.
But I...
Take Vincent and go back to camp.
- But Mr. Locke was...
- now, little man...
Michael...
I know it's been difficult
to bond with your son.
You know why he's formed
an attachment to me ?
Because I treat him like an adult
and you still treat him like a boy.
He's 10 years old !
He's been through more than most
people in their entire lifetimes.
You haven't spent enough
time with him to see it, but
he's different.
You stay away from my son...
and me.
Wow, you're making a lot of progress.
Got this bamboo for the decking,
got a piece of the fuselage for a cabin.
It's not the Queen Mary.
I only got room for
four people.
What's the matter, doc ?
Feeling left out ?
You're taking Sawyer with you ?
I needed a halyard to the mast.
Good thing I'm a saver,
not a spender, huh, doc ?
With some determined to leave,
the island reveals itself to others
with a reason to stay.
I think we should go back, man,
suit yourself.
Boone !
You need this more than I do.
What is that ?
That's what we're gonna find out.
A mysterious hatch...
is it the key to survival
or the path to disaster ?
My god.
What is this thing ?
I guess it's time we talked about this.
How long have you known about this ?
Three weeks, give or take.
You've been out here for three weeks digging
this thing up, and you never told me about it.
All due respect, Jack, but
since when do I report to you ?
So how do we open it ?
What ?
You want to open it ?
Yeah.
I brought you here to talk
him out of this insanity.
Anything could be inside.
Best case scenario, there's supplies.
Worst case, we use it as a shelter.
Actually, Jack I can think
of much worse cases than that.
Dad ! Dad, wake up !
- What ?
- Somebody's here !
Who is that ? Calm down, everyone.
It's all right.
Danielle ?
What are you doing here ?
The others are coming.
You have only three choices...
Run,
hide...
or die.
Look, I know you're all scared.
All I can tell you right now
is that we do have a plan.
We've gotta go into the jungle to get some
supplies. We'll be back in a few hours.
Do everything you can to help
Michael get that raft on the water.
And after that,
go to the caves.
We'll be back as soon as we can.
Promise.
Hey, nice speech.
Plan's a little flawed,
but hey, nobody's perfect.
- My plan ?
- Yeah, your plan.
You're gonna go into the jungle and
get some dynamite and blow open a hatch,
and then you're gonna
hide everyone inside.
You want to keep a secret,
don't tell the fat guy.
I salvaged a few things for you.
This is the plane's radar emitter.
It needs to be mounted on the
mast or the top of the cabin.
This was in the plane's toolbox.
There's only one flare.
Choose wisely when you use it.
Going into the jungle
after the boom sticks, huh ?
Yeah.
By the time you get back,
we'll be in the water.
Guess this is pretty
much good-bye then.
Good luck, Sawyer.
Jack.
About a week before we
all got on the plane,
got to talking with this
man at a bar in Sydney.
He was an american, too.
Doctor.
It turns out this guy has a son.
Son's a doctor, too.
They'd had some kind
of big-time falling out.
The guy knew it was his fault,
even though his son was back in the
States thinking the same damn thing.
There's a pay phone in this bar,
and this guy...
tells me he wishes he had the stones
to pick up the phone and call his kid...
to tell him he's sorry,
and he's a better doctor
than he'll ever be...
that he's proud...
and he loves him.
I had to take off, but...
something tells me he never
got around to making that call.
One, two, three, lift !
and keep it straight !
Go, go !
Come on, go !
That's it !
We did it !
You...
as one ship sets sail,
another provides needed supplies.
Jack. John.
Over here.
How many do we need to blow the hatch ?
Two should take care of the hinge,
three to be safe.
"Safe."
So what's this stuff even do ?
Well, the transmitter
sends out an S. O. S.
in case someone's listening.
And if there's anything out there,
we'll see it on this radar screen here.
In the journey to the hatch,
danger threatens.
Yeah. I saw it.
Locke, what are you doing ?
- Locke ?
- Just let me go !
- What ?
- I'll be all right.
No ! Let me go ! I'll be all right.
I got it. I got it.
Be careful unwrapping it.
- Now throw it in.
- No ! It'll blow us up !
- Just do it ! Hurry ! I can't hold him !
- Don't do this, Kate ! Kate !
Know what I like about you, Mike ?
You got the patience of a saint.
Why do you say that ?
I've seen the way he talks to you.
I'd have showed him the back
of my hand a long time ago.
Is that what your father did to you ?
Daddy never got a chance to beat me.
Shot himself when I was 8.
That why you want to die, man ?
Since the day you told me you wanted
on this raft, I couldn't figure it out.
Why does a guy who only cares about himself
want to risk his life to save everyone else ?
You're either a hero,
or you want to die.
I ain't no hero, Mike.
What the hell was all that
about back there, John,
what was what about ?
You asked me to let you go.
That's right.
Now that thing was taking you down the
hole, and you asked me to let you go.
It wasn't gonna hurt me
No, John. It was gonna kill ya.
I seriously doubt that.
I need to know why you believe
that that thing wasn't...
I believe that I was being tested.
I think that's why you and i don't
see eye to eye sometimes, Jack.
Because you're a man of science.
What does that make you ?
Well, I'm a man of faith.
Do you really think all this
is an accident ?
Do you think we crashed on
this place by coincidence ?
Especially this place ?
We were brought here for a purpose.
And who brought us here, John ?
The island.
It's destiny.
I don't believe in destiny.
Yes, you do.
You just don't know it yet.
Nothin'.
Is that what I think it is ?
Something's out there.
It's closer.
So what was that about back there ?
There's something that you need to know.
If we survive this, if
we survive tonight...
we're gonna have a Locke problem.
Are we ready ?
Wait a sec.
And I have to know
that you've got my back.
I got your back.
Hurley ! You've gotta get back.
What does destiny hold for the
survivors of Oceanic flight 815 ?
And was it destiny that brought
them to this place of mystery ?
Where does their salvation lie ?
Yo ! Hey !
Hey !
- We're saved !
- Oh, man,
are we glad to see you.
What are you folks
doing this far out here ?
We were in a plane... the plane crashed.
We've been on a island for months, man.
A plane crash, huh ?
Well, how about that ?
We're on an island. Flight
815. Hey, where are we ?
Hey, it's a good thing we found you.
Yeah, we survived, and there's a
whole group of people on the island.
Well, ain't that somethin' ?
Yeah !
Only the thing is,
we're gonna have to take the boy.
What ?
What did you say ?
The boy...
we're gonna have to take him.
Hey, what the hell is goin' on here ?
Who are you people ?
Just give us the boy.
I'm not givin' you anybody.
Well, all right, then.
Hey, hey !
Sawyer !
Dad ! Dad !
No ! Walt, no !
Dad !
Walt !
No, dad, help me ! Dad !
Dad, help me !
Dad ! Please !
Dad !
Walt !
Help me, dad !
Please, no !
Walt !
Traduction par Cedr_c Synchro
par Kiff - www. forom. com -