Tea for Two
Picture me upon your knee
Just tea for two
and two for tea
Just me for you
and you for me alone
Nobody near us
to see us or hear us
No friends or relations
on weekend vacations
We won't ever known, dear
That we own a telephone, dear
Day will break and I'll awake
And start to bake that
sugar cake
For you to take for
all the boys to see
We will raise a family
A boy for you, a girl for me
Oh, can't you see how happy
we would be?
Thank you
On January 161938 Carnegie
Hall was the home of one
of the famous jazz
concerts ever
Outside it was a cold night,
but inside
Well, that was another story
The music was blazing hot
Thanks to Benny Goodman's band
and his famous quartet
Who were joined on stage
for ajam session by Count Basie
And sidemen from Basie's
and Duke Ellington's Orchestras.
Ever since then almost every
important jazz musician
has graced
the stage of Carnegie
In no small measure that was
due to the fact that
the Carnegie Hall was
the New York home for
Norman Granz's Jazz
at the Philharmonic
Those landmark shows, which began
in Los Angles fifty years ago
Were the foundation of
Verve Records
In fact J. J. Johnson who played
trombone in our opening number s
was at the very first concert
Actually the lineups for
those Jazz at the Phil shows
Were virtual who's
who ofjazz history
So tonight we salute those
composers and players
Legendary masters who've made jazz
an uniquely American art form
You know way back in the 1950's
when I was a kid in school
studying classical music
There was one jazz artist
who showed me that to play jazz
You didn't have to abandon
your formal training
One player who whether he was
performing jazz or classical
could still blow everybody
outta the water
Of course,
I'm talking about Art Tatum
Very simply, Art Tatum
was one of the most incredible
instrumentalist
jazz has ever known
His technique was awesome
And his genius has intimidated
virtually every other jazz pianist
Including me
As Fats Waller once said
when he saw Art walk in to a club:
"God is in the house"
To play "Willow Weep for Me"
in tribute to Art Tatum
Here is one the most versatile
and accomplished players
in modern jazz history
Ajazz master
in his own right
This smooth and gifted musician
has been an important part
of the jazz scene
for five decades
Please welcome Hank Jones
Willow Weep for Me
You know I was just backstage
thinking what it means to me
to be here tonight
Singing with these great
musicians on stage at Carnegie Hall
My parents were both music
teachers are so proud
And Mr. Morosco
my high school orchestra leader
Well, if he could see me now
I sang "Tea for Two" with
high school orchestra and also
with a small swing
band back then
And one of my dreams is that
someday be in front of a big band
like the Count Basie Orchestra
Count Basie was born in New Jersey
and studied with Fats Waller
But it's sound springs
from the Kansas City blues
Basie's spare and precise
playing contrasted to
his band's locomotive power
And defined one of the most
distinctive and popular styles
in jazz history
After World War II when the
decline of the big bands began
Basie survived
by scaling down to an octet
But thanks to Norman Granz who
signed an account to Verve Records
Basie was be able to reform
his big orchestra
Some of his best later-day
moments came in collaboration
with singers like Frank Sinatra
and Ella Fitzgerald
Frank Foster's "Shiny Stockings"
was a hit in 1955
In '63, Quincy Jones
rearranged it for the now classic
"Ella & Basie" album with the
lyrics by all people Ella herself
Here with the J. J. Johnson
and the Carnegie Hall Jazz Band
Is a versatile performer
who started singing jazz with
the Thad Jones & Mel
Lewis Big Band
And has even earned
a Tony Award for her role
on the Broadway musical
The Wiz
with "Shiny Stockings" please
welcome Miss Dee Dee Bridgewater
Shiny Stockings
Those silk shiny stockings
that I wear when I'm with you
I wear cause you told me
that you dig that crazy hue
When we go to a dance
Do you think of romance?
Oh no, you take a glance
at those shiny stockings
Then came along some chick
with great big stockings, too
Then you change
your mind about me
Why I never knew
I guess I'll have to find
A new some other kind
The guy who digs my shiny
stockings, too
Shiny stockings
Then came along some chick
with great big stockings, too
And then you changed
your mind about me
Why I never knew
I guess I'll have to find
A new some other kind
A guy who digs
my shiny stockings now
He'll dig my shiny stockings
whoa and how
J. J. Johnson, Kenny Burrell
Thank you
Well as you just heard
To put the music across
ajazz singer needs a terrific song
Sometime even more importantly
she needs a wonderful arrangement
That's something that Ella
always had when she did
an incredible songbook series
Many of those records
feature brilliant arrangements
by the great Nelson Riddle
So I'm very happy to say
that this next song
Cole Porter's
"Just One of Those Things"
Just One of Those Things
As Dorothy Parker once said
to her boyfriend, "fare thee well"
As Columbus announced
When he knew he was bounced
"It was swell, Isabel, swell"
As Abelard said to Eloise
"Don't forget to drop
a line to me, please"
As Juliet cried
in her Romeo's ear
"Romeo, why can't you face
the fact, my dear"
It was just
one of those things
Just one of those
crazy flings
One of those bells
that now and then rings
Just one of those things
It was just one of
those nights
Just one of those
fabulous flights
A trip to the moon
on gossamer wings
Just one of those things
If we'd thought a bit,
of the end of it
When we started
painting the town
We'd have been aware
that our love affair
Was too hot, not to cool down
Well good-bye, dear, and amen
Here's hoping
we meet now and then
It was great fun
But it was just
one of those things
Just one of those things
Just one of those crazy things
A trip to the moon
on gossamer wings
Just one of those things
Just one of those nights
Just one of those
fabulous flights
A trip to the moon
on gossamer wings
Just one of those things
If we'd thought a bit,
of the end of it
When we started
painting the town
We'd have been aware
that our love affair
Was too hot, not to cool down
So good-bye, dear, and amen
Here's hoping we meet
now and then
It was great fun
But it was just one of
those things
Thank you, thank you
In his early days
Bud Powell quickly earned
a reputation for his phenomenal technique
And he was often
compared to Art Tatum
One night Tatum went
to check out the competition
Before seeing Powell play
Tatum was heard to say:
"He is all right hand"
But Powell overheard that
remark and when he came out
He played the entire set with
his right hand behind his back
One of the great innovators
in the history ofjazz
Bud Powell was to the piano
what Charlie Parker was to the alto sax
A leader
who set the style for his generation
and many generations
of players
Powell was purist in the fast tempos
but no matter what the pace
Powell played with an
emotional fury and fire
He was the quintessential
bebop pianist
Here to pay tribute to
Bud Powell
Please welcome Japan's premier
jazz pianist Yosuke Yamashita
Parisian Thoroughfare
Almost fifty years ago Dizzy
Gillespie and Charlie Parker
led their pioneering bop quintet
at 52nd St's Downbeat Club
Just around the corner from
here where we are tonight
They tell the story of day
when a young Miles Davis said:
"Hey Dizzy, I can do everything
you can do on the trumpet"
And Dizzy replied:
"Yah, but an octave lower"
Dizzy Gillespie is one of
the real giants ofjazz
A founding father of bebop
His speed, high notes
harmonic sophistication
and technical brilliants
Even the shape of his horn
made him a one of a kind player
In the mid 40's
Dizzy and friends made history
as part of the legendary bop band
Formed by the great vocalist
Billy Eckstine
One of Dizzy's busiest
contributions was that he brought
the Afro-Cuban rhythms
of the Caribbean into jazz
His 1947 collaboration
with Chano Pozzo
a legendary Cuban Conga player
Is an exciting mix
of rhythm and horn cadenzas
Here are trumpet soloist Roy
Hargrove percussionist Don Alias
Steve Turre on shells and
the Carnegie Hall Jazz Band
In a salute to Dizzy's many
recordings of "Manteca"
Manteca
In the late 1950's
Bill Evans joined
the Miles Davis Quintet
Bringing with him an entirely new
harmonic approach to jazz piano
According to legend
On Bill's first night with
the band when Miles wasn't playing
He stood directly over the piano
studying what Bill Evans was doing
Now having come to jazz
through Bill Evans
I know why Miles was paying
such close attention
As did his idol Bud Powell
Bill Evans brought the harmonies
of the classical composers to jazz
Evans showed that
impressionism could swing
That cool could embrace
the warmth of romanticism
Right now, I'd like to pay
tribute to one of my idols
By performing his classic
"Turn Out the Stars"
To do that, I've asked an
old friend of mine to join me
He is John McLaughlin
Turn Out the Stars
In the 1960's the American public
seemed to turn away from jazz
But there were a few artists
who managed to break through
And one of the most successful
was the instantly recognizable
Signature guitar sound of
Wes Montgomery
He began by emulating his idol
Charlie Christian
But as the story goes
his original style wasn't really
influenced by anybody
Montgomery played with his
thumb instead of a pick
Because he didn't want to
disturb his neighbors
Or wake his sleeping children
Right now we are fortunate enough
to have one of the legendary
musicians from that period
with us tonight
With "Walk on the Wildside"
his biggest hit from the 60's
Here is a man who was a frequent
collaborator with Wes Montgomery
And a great innovator
in his own right
Please welcome the world's
greatest jazz organist, Jimmy Smith
Walk on the Wildside
Thank you very much
thank you, thank you
Long time ago
Wes Montgomery and I did a thing called
"Down by the Riverside"
And God bless his soul
We're gonna try to do it tonight
I have another friend of mine
Mr. Kenny Burrell, a great guitarist
And we are gonna do it for you
thank you
Down by the Riverside
Yellowstone
Here are
Herbie Hancock and John McLaughlin
with their homage to Miles Davis
It's About That Time