( Woman #1) To lose
an 18-year-old brother.
He didn't get a chance to graduate
from high school. It was a blow.
It destroyed me.
It made me feel like--
I was afraid
to love anybody.
I was really afraid
to let people get close to me.
I feIt
if I loved somebody,
deeply, you know,
like I do my family,
they would be taken away.
( Man ) I said, "Where'd you learn
to do that?"
She said, "Practicing on
an old flame since I was 16."
( Audience Laughs )
Look at this guy here. He's lookin' at
me and beatin' his meat. I like that.
There she is. Right?
Miss America, 1912.
lna !
Let's hear it for lna.
Comes here every night,
huh, sweetie?
Right.
Let me have a kiss.
- ( Man ) Bring out the broads !
- ( Audience Cheers )
Let me at him !
Somebody throw a net
over this broad.
Did you see him kiss
that fat fucker?
( Woman #2 ) Steve.
I'll always know him as 18.
He, uh--
He was killed by a drunk driver just
a month before he was to graduate.
And--
( Woman #3 ) It's hard when you have
two policemen come in and say,
"Your daughter's dead."
I op-- I opened the door
and I saw 'em standing there,
and I said,
"Mandy's dead, isn't she?"
A mom knows.
- ( Men Cheer )
- All right !
Freddy, he's comin' over here.
You better slide in... a lot.
- He needs half a booth.
- Sunny. How ya doin', Sunny?
Everything good?
( Men Laugh )
How 'bout that?
How'd you like to spank it?
- Nice !
- Oh, yeah ! But softly.
- Sunny, you had to spank that, right?
- Nice.
My wife,
you know Joan.
We got a step-down living room.
It's like two steps down.
So the bitch don't wanna walk.
She wants me to raise it.
She don't wanna walk down
two steps.
I still have to get over that.
It's something that...
-you have to work with on a daily basis.
-it's not gonna come back.
It's just something of-- It's yours.
It's like your body lost...
something inside,
something ofyourself.
I miss me.
I miss... me.
It's over five years now,
and...
I look in the mirror,
"Where's Bobby?"
I don't know.
My family drives me
up the fuckin' wall.
I mean, they, I guess they still,
they still think I'm me, Bobby.
But... they joke about it.
They call me...
sibling number three, all right?
And... it's like a nickname
for Bobby depressed.
It was my older brother Danny
that we lost.
And...
he was sibling number one.
they, th-they didn't--
Did they forget?
I don't know.
I'm gone !
( Chuckles )
And--
I miss me.
So...
that's it.
Who's runnin'
this fuckin' show?
( Traffic Noises )
( Grunting )
- ( Freddy ) You oughta go.
- ( Girl ) What?
( Freddy ) Go.
- You should go.
- Okay, yeah. I'm gonna go.
Um... Freddy,
can I use your shower?
Help yourself.
( Sighs )
## ( Girl Singing )
## ( Singing Continues )
# Woke up this mornin' #
# There was a chill in the air #
# Went into the kitchen
My cigarettes were lyin' there #
# Jacket hung on the chair
the way I left it last night #
# Everything was in place
Everything seemed all right #
# But you were missin' #
# Missing #
# Last night I dreamed
the sky went black #
# You were drifting down
Couldn't get back #
# Lost in trouble
so far from home #
# I reached for you
My arms were like stone #
# Woke and I'm missin' you #
# Missin' you #
# Missing #
# Oh #
# Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ##
( Bell Ringing )
Jefferey.
It's five after 10:00. I got a window
display of gray feIt. What's goin' on?
Mr. Gale, you took all the vauIt keys
home last night.
- For fuck sakes.
- I think...
it would be wonderful to put emerald
pieces in front of the diamonds.
I trust your preference
in stones, Jefferey, but...
I'm very busy,
you know what I mean?
All the time,
I'm very busy.
So, uh, think ahead
a little bit.
I'm walkin' out the door,
you're closin' up,
you don't have the vauIt keys
in your pocket, stop me.
Yes, sir.
Emeralds in the front.
Wonderful.
( Chirping )
( Woman Crying )
( Crying )
( Man Chuckling, Laughing )
- ( Laughing Continues )
- What's so funny?
( Laughing )
What are you
laughing at?
Ah, it's been
six fucking years !
I mean, I have my son here.
Can't I be happy?
I've never heard
that word out of your mouth.
- ( Chuckles )
- And in front of John.
Ma !
I've been in prison.
Don't make excuses for him.
Listen, do you still have
that little TV I sent you?
- Yeah. It's in the box.
- Oh, good, because...
I'm cleaning out the trailer for you
if you want some privacy.
Oh, yeah.
That'd be great.
- Or you could stay in your own room.
- No, no, no. Trailer's great.
( Laughing )
Because that's
a good fucking TV.
Oh, my God !
( Children Shouting )
( Girl Giggling )
( Giggling Continues )
( Doorbell Rings )
Freddy.
How's it goin' ?
Roger.
Good to see you.
Come in.
Uh, can I get you
something to drink?
- Phil, yeah. Let me call
you back in five minutes.
- No, I'm fine.
All right. Thank you.
I'm sorry?
Uh, no, thank you.
Emily really loved
this thing.
We used to keep it
over there on the counter.
Stretch her whole body out
trying to reach it.
Last joint
on her little finger.
( Sighs )
What?
N-Nothin'.
Come in.
Sit down, Freddy.
Boy. Tch.
You really look like a natural family.
You could be their father.
Thank you, Freddy.
Spectacular looking family,
really.
Um, what can I, uh,
do for you?
I really came to see Mary.
Oh. Well, I don't mean to be
nosy, Freddy, but what about?
Well, I'd really rather
talk to Mary about that.
Well--
Well, well, well.
- Um, you sure I can't
get you something to drink?
- No, I'm fine.
( Boys Chatting, Keys Jingling )
- Anyway, I think they're here.
- Oh, yeah.
- ( Boys Chatting )
- ( Mary ) Hold on, guys.
Hold on.
- ( Boys Together ) Hi, Dad !
- Hi, guys.
- ( Boys Together ) Hi, Freddy.
- Hi, darling.
- We've got a visitor.
- Come on, Dad.
Well...
look at this.
My own kids
call me Freddy.
- You look wonderful.
- Wonderful, I think,
would be pushing it.
No, you do.
You look wonderful.
Thank you.
So, how's business?
So-so.
You know, it's a little jewelry store.
What can I say?
It's business.
What about you?
You still doin' the real estate?
Well, it's a tough market
right now.
I'm still representing
some properties.
But Roger's been doing so well,
I've been able to back off some.
Spend more time with the kids.
Oh, well, wonderful.
That's, uh, yeah--
That's, uh, really wonderful.
Um--
Um...
Mary, there's, uh, something
that you should know.
It's the reason
I came here.
- Freddy--
- I've got something I wanna tell you.
You made me a promise.
I hope you're gonna keep it.
Two things:
I made you a promise. That's one.
And I have great news.
That's two.
Now, you gonna let me speak
or not?
I'm sorry.
What's your great news?
( Sighs, Muttering )
It's really great news.
I mean, spectacular news.
- I'm tellin' ya.
You wanna hear it or not?
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- Are you ready?
He's out.
John Booth is out.
I'm gonna kill him.
Get out of here, Freddy.
I'm not goin' anywhere until I see you
courageous enough to tell the truth.
The truth?
What truth, Freddy?
- You promised you wouldn't.
- Wouldn't? Wouldn't what, Mary?
- Mention our daughter? Why?
Because you'd blackmail me?
- Blackmail?
If I ever, ever want to speak
to the mother of my children,
I must never mention
my daughter !
- Get out of our house !
- This is my house.
By any natural law,
this is my house !
If my children live here,
my children,
then who's to say that I can't come here
to see 'em any fuckin' time I want to?
- You had to do it, huh?
- Nobody's talkin' to you !
- You want me to call the police?
- Call whoever the fuck you want.
Where do you get off calling
them your children? You haven't
been a father to those kids.
- You stopped with our daughter.
- Emily is her name.
Yes, Emily. Emily !
And she is dead.
But I owe those two little boys
up there all the love I've got.
And it kills you that I can
give it to them and that you can't !
( Roger ) Freddy, I want you
to leave our home--
- Tell the truth, Mary. You
want me to kill John Booth !
- Let go of him !
That's my job in life, and your job is
to go on as though nothing happened !
- Let go of him !
- Freddy !
Freddy, why don't you let me go?
I'll make us some coffee.
Come on.
Coffee. Good.
I'd like some coffee.
Why don't we all just sit down,
have some coffee and
talk about this civilly?
Come on.
( Sighs )
You know what?
I don't want any coffee.
I--
I don't like coffee at all.
It makes my heart-- ( Slapping Chest )
- You just said you wanted coffee.
- No.
You sure?
Yes. Uh... no.
I'm gonna go.
I feel good.
- He just showed up
at the door. I didn't--
- Jesus, God, Roger.
I just want to say this.
I've done a lot of things
for you, you know.
A lot of things.
And I think it's cheap of you
that you won't hear me out
on things. I really do.
- Mary's just upset.
- Excuse me, but I am not upset.
If you think I'm gonna keep
score on who's done what to who,
you're very fucking wrong !
And if you think that's cheap,
then fuck you !
I don't know if you're serious
about killing this man or not,
but I do know this.
It has nothing to do
with our daughter.
Our little girl is gone, Freddy,
and she's not coming back...
no matter what you do !
You've never even been to the
cemetery, Freddy. You've never
even been to Emily's grave.
Why?
Because I didn't go to
your little party? Your funeral?
I went on my own time,
Mary... in private.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Then you're a braver man
than I thought.
What's the inscription
on the stone, Freddy?
What color is it?
Is it on a hill?
Is it under a tree?
Does it lay flat or does it
stick up out of the ground?
That's what I thought.
Roger, man to man,
when you two read
in the newspaper...
that John Booth
has been shot dead,
I want you to look
into her face and tell me if
you don't see pride and relief.
Pride and relief,
Mary.
## ( Whistling )
## ( Whistling Continues )
( Man ) So, listen to me.
I'm comin' out of the bathroom,
right?
And these two Orientals,
they're arguin', they're hollerin'.
They're screamin'
at one another, and all in Japanese.
So, I told 'em.
I said, "Hey, you're in
America now. Speak Spanish."
- Geez, you fucking guys.
Have a miserable evening.
- ( Men Laughing )
- What was he doin' in the mens' room?
Hey, Freddy. Freddy.
What?
Hey, Freddy, you with us?
I think we hypnotized him.
Freddy !
- Yeah?
- He's on the rag.
( Men Laughing )
Did any of you guys ever have
a sound build up in your head...
over a period of days?
Like a vacuum cleaner?
That the last time
you had an original thought,
you got cocky
and rode on it?
- Rode what?
- Rode on the thought.
Enjoyed it...
'til you started hearin' that
vacuum cleaner in your brain.
- But you don't mean tonight.
- ( Laughing ) No.
He means some other night.
Take my advice, Freddy.
Get yourself a "youngie" and go
on one of them Laguna weekends.
( Men Laughing )
I gotta take off.
I'll see you guys later.
Freddy, where you goin' ?
It's only 11:00.
Oh, man.
Commitments.
He's gonna go turn off the fuckin'
vacuum cleaner ! ( Laughing )
( Engine Revving )
( Tires Screeching )
Pride and relief, Mary.
( Groans )
( Gun Clicks )
Goddamn it !
- ( Gun Clicks )
- Goddamn it !
Fuckin'--
Fuckin' clip is empty.
This fuckin' gun ain't got
no fuckin' clip. You cock.
All right
I get a cigarette?
All right.
You know--
Would you mind closin' the door?
I don't want to wake my parents.
Might fuckin' wake
his fuckin' parents.
When the thing happened,
I wanted to be dead.
But there wasn't--
You know.
I didn't want
your forgiveness.
I didn't think I deserved it.
And I don't think I do.
But...
I guess you, uh...
you've been waitin' for this day
for a long time.
It's all right.
Sit down.
I know it's been
a long wait.
But I'm not goin' anywhere.
I'm not callin' any cops.
I'll just be here,
trying to get on with things.
Would you maybe,
you know--
Would you take
a couple days...
and maybe think about
not takin' my life?
Look.
I'm a jeweler.
I got a jewelry store.
That's all I got.
That's it. That's what I am.
- Understand what I'm talkin' about?
- I think I do.
Shut up ! Because you don't.
You don't understand. You don't !
All right.
I'm gonna give you
three days.
Three days.
Then maybe I'll remember
the fuckin' clip for this gun.
Son of a bitch !
( Speaking Spanish )
( Woman On TV ) And up. Let's go !
We're warming up.
Get that blood flowing.
Again.
Now tuck your arms.
Front and back.
And step.
I don't want another ring.
I want this ring in a size seven.
Don't you understand?
I was a seven on Tuesday and I'm
a seven today. This is not a seven.
( Jefferey ) You have a swollen
finger one day, not the next.
( Woman ) I want to speak to the owner.
It's not a seven.
It's maybe a six,
a six and a half.
- I sized your finger two times.
- I wanted to wear this ring tonight.
I have a very important
engagement tonight.
No, I don't want another ring.
I want this ring...
- in a size seven like I ordered it.
- May I help you, ma'am?
- Are you the owner?
- Yes, I would be
the proprietor in question.
Thank God. I told this Jap faggot
I ordered this ring size seven.
My ring size has always been a seven.
This is not a seven.
- It won't even fit on my hand.
- May I see the ring, please?
Yeah. It won't fit on my finger,
my hand. It won't fit anything.
It's a six and a half.
Six and three-quarters maybe.
Does that look like a
six fuckin' and a half to you?
Ahh.
You were right.
You're a perfect seven.
A perfect fucking seven.
Do you know where
this bus turns around?
Pardon?
Does this bus stay
in Glendale?
I don't know.
Does it turn around
and come back to Marge Street?
I don't know.
- Do you come back to Marge Street?
- No.
My sister has a car.
A Valiant.
-Did you ever get to ride in a Valiant?
-No.
My sister has
a green Valiant.
I ride the bus
all day long.
( Laughing )
I have
a disability card...
so I don't have to pay.
( Laughing )
( Girl ) Daddy !
( Phone Rings )
Hello.
Mary Manning.
Hello?
- Hey, what's in the news?
- Hey ! Get in the car.
Okay, we're late.
- But you got the job.
- Yeah.
- You start at 6:00 in the morning.
- Oh, man.
It's a boat.
It's a good job.
Second, there's a bunch of people
at my house. It's a party for you.
- A party?
- Girls.
- Wow.
- But we're not goin' anywhere until--
- ln the joint,
- Yeah?
did you get
butt-fucked?
It only hurts
the first time.
I know.
# I was born a cowboy
And a cowboy I will die #
And I'll die #
# I was born a cowboy
And a cowboy I will die #
- # I was born a cowboy
And I'll die #
- Yee-hoo !
# I will die before my time
But then my kind always do #
I will die ##
- ( Laughing )
- ( Sunny ) Take your hands out
of your pockets. Let's hear it.
That's Verna. Come on, now.
Let's open up your sphincter...
and let the sunlight in.
Verna !
Oh, Verna,
come on, girl.
You better hurry up.
We're gonna be late. Nicky Blair's !
- I didn't know. Is she goin' ?
- Of course she's goin'.
I thought it was just
gonna be you and me. Dinner?
Well, we can't do it
in a restaurant, Verna.
What difference does it make?
Geez.
You wanna go or not?
Come on. Huh?
Whoever wants to go, come on,
let's go. I'll wait in the car.
( Woman ) Hey !
The train's
a-movin' on.
Get your stuff.
Get your stuff. Let's go.
- Yeah, let's go. Let's have fun.
Let's, ha-ha, party, huh?
- Verna?
( Woman ) And I'm talking
to you before about compassion,
how you have compassion...
for people, and you decide every day
who deserves compassion and who doesn't.
That's your spirituality.
If somebody is black and dying on the
street, then they deserve compassion.
And if somebody is rich and their sister
dies, they get a little bit.
But if somebody is rich and they
have a bad day, forget it.
They don't deserve a bit of compassion.
You haven't lived that person's life.
But because they don't have
any identifiable things
that deserve compassion,
you don't give it to them.
Not once have I seen you
do that.
Oh, I make him feel bad.
Let me tell a joke.
Okay. Well--
( Laughing )
## ( Jazz )
Nine is taken.
I'll give him 22. Okay?
- Hello, Mr. Gale. Good to see you.
- Nick, how are you tonight?
You look so good.
Hello, ladies.
Mr. Gale, listen. I've got
a great, great, great booth for you.
It's a half a booth, but we're
gonna get the other half--
- Here. Take their coats quickly.
- Uh, half a booth?
Yes. But don't worry. We're gonna get
the other booth in about 15 minutes.
- At nine, you mean.
- It's right by the bar.
I couldn't get that one.
- Is it nine?
- No, no. Don't worry about nine.
Here, take this.
Come on, girls.
Look how beautiful they are.
- You're always with
pretty girls, Mr. Gale.
- ( Girls Giggling )
# Can't last #
# Any time
Any place #
This-- This is, uh,
a nice table, huh?
- It's fine. Fine.
- I guess.
- We can see the bar really good.
- ( Laughing )
Forgive me. I have this painting.
Jojo did this painting.
After years of bullshit,
I'm sorry, finally reaches a point
where she does this incredible work.
She smears herself with paint,
she rolls herself around...
on a,
on a piece of canvass--
- Paper.
You were trying
to represent God.
Right? Okay.
Uh, just allow me this.
But what she ends up with
is an image of herself.
She looks for God
and she finds,
she finds herself.
( Laughing )
( Laughing Continues )
Whoo !
( Verna ) Ate all the clams
in the house, did you?
( Jennifer ) Oh, don't torture
yourself, sweetheart.
She wants to be your woman,
motherfucker.
- Better watch your ass.
- Come on !
- ( Freddy ) Go easy now.
- ( Laughing )
You girls seem to be having
a good time. You must be a funny guy.
I'm a riot.
- Now get the fuck outta here.
- I didn't mean anything.
I just stopped by, having fun.
- Nothin' personal.
- Go have your fun somewhere else.
Just get the fuck outta here.
Relax. I don't mean any offense
by this. I just thought maybe
you'd like extra help here.
You got some pretty girls here.
Maybe you need some help.
- I don't need no fuckin' help !
- Hey, hey, hey !
Take it easy !
Hey, hey !
( Women Screaming )
## ( Piano Player Singing )
Are we having fun now,
you motherfucker?
# ln my bowl
I ain't foolin' #
# I want a little sugar #
- # ln my bowl ##
- ( Shouting )
- You had to drag me into this?
- Not to put too fine
a point on it, but...
you know
something about confinement.
- I think we all know
- Well, there's confinement...
and there's...
confinement.
I know what you mean.
Yeah, at the risk of sounding like
I know what I'm talking about,
I think freedom's overrated.
What you're talking about.
You know, if there isn't
something bigger than, uh,
than freedom,
then freedom
is just entertainment.
Entertainment?
- ( Freddy ) Like a central
computer, you mean?
- We transmit downtown.
- Everybody?
- Everybody that gets booked.
- Murderers too?
- Especially murderers.
- Ever do any murders?
- Not personally. Have you?
( Peter ) # Ain't it funny to see #
# How blind a man can be #
# Ain't it funny
to look back on love #
Hmm.
You all right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. I'm just--
No, I'm f--
You know, fine.
I'm John.
I know.
I'm Jojo.
- You know. You know about me?
- Peter told me.
Mmm.
The father of the, uh,
the girl I killed,
he threatened to kill me last night.
It was an accident,
right?
Was he serious?
You, you-- Serious?
I think he was serious.
I think he's a serious man.
You're the only person
I've told.
Why?
Well, I--
I think I thought
it would be romantic.
Why would you
want to be romantic?
How'd you get
that scar on your head?
Banged my head
against the wall.
- ln jail?
- Uh-huh.
You or somebody else?
- You?
- Mm-hmm.
You just couldn't stand jail?
No. I just couldn't
stand me.
Yeah, I was gonna call, but
it got so late, I didn't think
you guys would be up.
( Helen ) Of course we're up !
You just got home.
We want to see you.
I'm sorry.
It's just, uh--
- I got the job.
- Ah, good.
And Peter and his brother threw me
a coming-home party.
The day
just kinda happened.
- When do you start on the boat?
- Actually in a few hours.
Why do you stay out so late
before you start a job?
Your friends don't care
if you get any rest.
Something hit me tonight.
It was a strange night.
You know, uh,
( Sighs )
I've done a horrible thing.
And, uh,
I'm always
gonna feel the guiIt...
and remorse.
But...
when you hear about
a thing like that,
about someone who has
to carry a thing like that,
when you're in it,
it's just, it's--
( Sighs )
It's very different...
from what you might think.
( Sighs )
I'm not an unhappy person.
I'm just--
( Clears Throat ) I'm just--
I'm someone who has caused
a lot of... unhappiness.
And a person
who's caused death.
I, uh,
I love you...
both so much.
Not just as my parents,
but...
as two people who,
who stood by
and kept giving...
your love... to that person.
That person...
who has also caused you both
so much pain.
You're our son.
Of course we love you.
No matter what.
( Verna ) Let's get this straight,
girl. Everyone gets paid by the hour.
- Listen, I'll see you in a bit.
- Ah, Jefferey. Thank you.
Here, hold this.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine, thank you.
I'm, uh,
I'm fuckin' delighted.
- Please. We can do
a fashion show outside.
- Thank you.
- Who is that, Jefferey?
- It's my boyfriend Gene.
- Did you get the car?
- Yeah. The car's outside.
- Let's get the fuck out of here.
Okay. All right.
- ( Women ) Finally !
- Are you okay?
- I'm just fuckin' great.
- Thank you.
- I can't get this thing.
- Where's the fuckin' car?
- Over there.
# I might
just change my mind #
# Sometimes
you can never tell #
# Where a story
will unwind #
# How deep is
a shallow well #
# Sometimes
you would never guess #
# Who's all talk
and who just might #
# Find a way
or lose themselves #
# On the King's Highway
tonight ##