I gotta lock up, son.
You looking for faith,
forgiveness?
I'm lookin' for the Bulls
to cover the spread.
Duffy's here.
You better have his money.
I got it. I'm gonna have it.
What's the score?
You're into Duffy for at least five
grand. Who gave you an account?
I laid six grand
with the Barber to get me even.
Chicago's down by four.
- I got Chicago gettin' eight.
- Less than a minute to go.
Hang on!
Just hang on.
Did you bet the Barber with
my money? You're not that stupid.
Shut up, Duffy. In 18 seconds,
you'll have your money.
Oh, and he gets hammered,
and in it goes!
Shit!
Okay, if he makes both,
it's eight. I push. I'm even.
Flagrant foul.
He shoots that first.
- That's bullshit!
- You're screwed if he makes three.
Grab him!
Get off of me!
I'm first, O'Neill!
You always pay me first!
You wanna kick my ass?
No one can kick my ass
better than I can.
Hey, Conor, it's Ticky!
Did you bring money
for the summons?
- What's that?
- Did you bring money to get me out?
- Damn, you got "zactly's" breath.
- "Zactly's breath"?
Your breath smells zactly like
your ass. Damn, that's nasty.
Did you pay them?
They said it's 580.
- I need the tickets.
- Which ones?
You got two pair on the floor
for the Bulls-Rockets.
I'm gonna hawk those myself.
The game's not till 7:00.
- It's 5:00. Tell me where they are.
- What?
- Shit.
- Come on.
They're under the religious statue
on my dresser.
Wait, Ticky!
You gotta get 1,200.
- You gotta pay to get me out!
- I already did.
- Yeah?
- It's Ticky. Let me in.
Ticky. Thank God.
I really need that money. How much
did you get for the tickets?
Jesus!
Hey, O'Neill. Remember me?
They grabbed me outside
the United Center.
- Yeah, you're the Barber's son.
- Yeah.
Remember making that phone call
from Michael Pistone's wedding?
- Get off of me.
- You talked to me.
You said, "This is O'Neill,
number 55. What's my limit?"
So I check 55,
and I see you got six grand.
So you put that six grand down
on Milwaukee, and they tank.
So I ask my old man about O'Neill
on 55, and guess what he tells me.
- That guy died four months ago.
- Look, tell the Barber--
You bet six grand on your
dead father's account.
- I need some money right now!
- I'll give you everything I got.
All right. That's a start.
Relax.
Forty-seven dollars.
All right, you owe 6,600.
You pay me a grand a week
until I say stop.
- That's ridiculous. 500.
- 750. Bring it to the barber shop.
You don't want me
to come back here.
They grabbed me outside
the United Center!
Excuse me. I'm Conor O'Neill.
I got an 11:30 with James Fleming.
Can you lend me...
twelve grand?
What-- do you need to
bury your father again?
What?
Did you dig the guy up
or something?
- What are you, freakin' sick?
- I'm sick?
Four months ago
you come in here crying...
about how you need $5,000
to bury your old man.
I talked to Mahoney
at Mikey's wedding.
It seems he also gave you
5,000 to bury the guy.
And I'm gonna pay Mahoney back.
I don't give a shit
how much you owe Mahoney.
Listen, Jimmy, I'm really up
against it right now with Duffy--
And I really don't give a shit
how much you owe the bookies.
Come back in here.
You know, this...
just might help you.
- Jimmy, this is only 500 bucks.
- I know.
You're going to coach
a kids' baseball team with me.
Jimmy, I don't think you understand
how serious my situation is.
I'm gonna pay you $500 a week
for the next ten weeks.
That's week one.
- Jimmy, I ain't no good with kids.
- You know, Conor...
I do this to give something
back to the community.
You don't want to do it,
give me the check back.
So, I'll see you
at the field tomorrow.
- 3:30.
- Where is it?
Right behind that Baptist church
where you used to buy reefer.
The only thing behind that church
is those shitty housing projects.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll whack this shit to the gate.
You ain't gonna mess with me.
Shit.
Yo, check out Coach Jimmy's whip!
Oh, damn, this shit is pimped.
Whoa, guys,
don't touch the car.
Yo, Coach Jimmy.
Here's my extra inhaler...
and here's my Sugar Babies
for when my blood needs sugar.
Mom says I do better
when my blood's got sugar in it.
What's your name again?
- Jefferson Albert Tibbs. But--
- Everybody listen!
That gentleman behind you
is Coach Conor.
He'll be taking over
the day-to-day operations.
- What?
- That bum guy's our coach?
Coach Conor just stopped by
to give you the equipment.
Jimmy, I can't do this by myself.
Here's your roster, schedule,
Sugar Babies, inhaler.
I gotta be in New York three weeks.
Training seminar. Can't be avoided.
- Good luck.
- Hey, wait, Jimmy.
- Wait.
- What's wrong with that man?
Wait, wait, wait!
How am I gonna get my money?
Every Monday, Ellen will have
a check for you. Gotta go.
- Five hundred, right?
- Every Monday.
- Five hundred every Monday.
- You bet.
I'll see ya.
- Andre Ray Peetes?
- 'Sup, my brother!
- What position do you play?
- Big Willie.
Whatever, man--
back catcher or center field.
I got mad power.
I pound the shit to the gate, yo!
Damn right.
Miles Pennfield II?
- This dude.
- Him.
What position does he play?
He says he can pitch, Coach Conor,
but I might pitch too.
- What's your name?
- Jefferson Albert Tibbs.
Mom says I can play anywhere.
My asthma and all,
I should probably play first.
I gotta keep my sugar up too.
You know, Mom said that
some boys just plain big-boned.
And some boys
just plain fat-assed.
Hi. Matt Hyland,
head of the coaches' committee.
- You the Kekambas?
- What?
- Are you the Kekambas?
- Yeah, bitch, we the Kekambas.
So, what's up?
Where's James Fleming from
Smyth and Stevens Securities?
He's out of town on business.
I'm assisting him.
What do you got--
six or seven kids?
If you can't field a team,
the league'll drop ya.
I'll tell Coach Fleming--
This is Darryl Mackey.
He's the president of the league.
Last year was a mess.
We had to cancel games
because we'd show up...
and the other team
would have five kids.
Waste of everybody's time.
We're just trying to save everyone
a whole lot of trouble, okay?
If you can't field a nine-man team,
you and the Kekambas should go home.
Talk to Jimmy Fleming at
Smyth and Stevens Securities...
and submit a roster by Friday.
- Friday.
- All right?
Yo, Coach.
Kofi and Ray Ray want to play.
Is that Kofi Evans and...
- Raymont Bennet?
- Yeah, Coach.
But Miss Wilkes
ain't gonna let them play.
Wait, hey, hey!
Who's Miss Wilkes?
She teaches Saint Malachy. She gets
on my damn nerves, I swear to God!
She is real mean, Coach.
She's an old nasty lady. She tell
your moms every little thing.
Do you know she called my house
every night last year? Every night.
- She won't let these guys play?
- Hell, no!
She said they couldn't play ball
until they do these book reports.
- Kofi ain't doin' shit.
- Ray Ray neither. They're like...
"Bitch, quit that noise. "
Hey, can we cool it
with the "bitches"?
Shit, man.
Coach, it's gettin' kinda late.
We gotta go soon. We practicin'?
Not today.
Thursday, 4:00 here.
Cool.
Miles, wait up!
My mom's meetin' me at Southside
Pizza. I ain't walkin' by myself.
I wanna go to Southside
with you.
- You wanna just cut up Ashland?
- Whatever, man.
I don't wanna walk through
folks' loop. Damn Disciples.
Glock, nine millimeter.
Hey, you know about
my karate right?
- Man, do you mean karate?
- Nah, it's karate.
Learned it from my cousin
who was in Japan in the army.
Lightning quick!
This is the tiger.
No man can defend himself from
the fury of a karate tiger man.
Yeah, Dre-- a tiger.
Okay.
I only use the tiger when I'm
fightin', like, a dozen guys.
More than that,
I use the bear.
- What's the bear again?
- I can't show you!
Man, that's the secret code
of the karate honor.
Hey, wait up!
- Yes?
- Sister Wilkes?
I'm Conor O'Neill.
I wanted to talk to you about--
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's just my head.
Who are you here to see?
- Sister Wilkes.
- I'm Miss Wilkes.
- Do you teach here?
- Yes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was just expecting...
an older woman.
- Well, I'm not a nun.
- Thank God!
I mean, that's great.
Is Kofi Evans and
Raymont Bennet in your class?
Are they in my class.
Yes, they're in my class.
I need them to play baseball
for the Kekambas.
Oh, yeah. That's something you
should take up with their mothers.
- But the kids told me--
- Both mothers agreed...
the boys would read one book before
they start baseball in the spring.
Hey, I got
no problem with that.
You know, I think reading's
real good for kids.
You work for
Smyth and Stevens Securities?
- Yes.
- What deal did you blow?
What?
Well, I'm sure you're not
coaching this team by choice.
My associate, James Fleming,
is in New York for three weeks...
so I volunteered to help out.
I would have loved
to have coached that team.
I was away on business--
Canada--
the day Mr. Smyth
and Mr. Stevens chose the team.
Canada.
That must have been nice.
Lovely.
I was in the business part
the whole time though.
It's wonderful you're teaching
these boys to play baseball.
It's just a shame no one spends
any time helping them to read.
Listen, I'm Conor.
Elizabeth.
I'm only helping out
with the team for two weeks...
but I'm willing to get together
with you and help the boys out.
- Why don't we exchange numbers?
- I have a better idea.
I'll give you a copy of the book
the boys are supposed to be reading.
You read it, and then you can
talk to them about their reports.
God.
That would be great.
Conor O'Neill,
coach of the crack babies.
I can't coach that team.
I'm serious. I'm bailin' out.
- How'd it go with the nuns?
- God, she was beautiful.
You picked up a nun?
Shut up.
You still want your half
of the Blackhawks seats I got?
Yeah. Where are they?
I'm gettin' them tomorrow.
Bring 'em to the baseball field
on Loomis...
tomorrow between 4:00 and 5:00.
Loomis?
That's the friggin' projects!
Don't screw me.
I'm not in the mood.
- I need that money.
- I'll be there at 5:00.
- Before 5:00.
- O'Neill.
Easy, slugger, all right?
Relax.
You got some cabbage for me?
Can we talk outside,
without the bat?
Duffy, you knew my dad.
And I wouldn't be callin' in a favor
if I wasn't completely racked.
- You smashed up my bar.
- I'll pay you. I just need time.
It ain't my money.
Now, I can't carry you anymore.
I'll help with the book, take bets.
I'll bring in business.
No, that's not gonna work.
Listen, I gave them your name
because I couldn't carry you.
What?
Are you saying some jag-off goombah
is gonna come and break my thumbs?
Duffy, I'm desperate.
I'm coaching
a kids' baseball team...
in the projects for a guy
who's paying me 500 a week.
But I'm paying the Barber off.
What should I do?
Should I tell the Barber to back
off? Start paying you every week?
Keep payin' the Barber...
but don't come around here
unless you got the money.
I'm Pearla Evans, and this one's
Kofi. This is my youngest, Jarius.
Everybody call me
G- Baby, so--
This is my sister's boy,
Raymont.
Miss Wilkes said you're going to
help with their assignments...
- so they could play ball.
- Yeah, that was before I had this--
Miss Wilkes said she had
a good feelin' about you.
- I figured I'd give it a try.
- Miss Wilkes said that?
No. She said she had a good feelin'
about them all playin' ball.
- But I'll tell you now, Mr. --
- O'Neill. Conor O'Neill.
You don't help these boys,
they don't do this work...
hell will be paid
with your ass.
I can reach you at Smyth and
Stevens to plan a tutoring session?
- Yes. Of course. Anytime.
- Good.
- Go on, boys.
- Yeah, come on!
Yeah, come on, man.
I'll beat you up, man.
Come on now. Yeah.
- What?
- This ain't no giddyap show.
No, like this.
Like this.
Come on, Ticky.
You're killin' me.
We usually quit at 5:30.
Mom needs me home.
- We eat around 6:30.
- No, keep practicin'.
I'm waiting for somebody.
We'll be done soon.
- I'll let you know, Albert.
- I'm Jefferson.
Come on, man, pitch the ball!
Shut up!
- You wanna hit me? Huh, bitch?
- Oh, shit.
And if I did, what you gonna
do about it, you little punk?
Hey, that's enough!
That's enough, all right?
- Shit, I wanna see some blood.
- Will you guys cool it?
Practice Saturday, 1:00,
all right?
- What?
- Can I walk with you?
No. I'm not goin' that way.
Sorry.
But--
Yo, what's up, my B?
What's up, shorty, man?
Hey, gimme that pizza, my man.
- What up, boy?
- Open the bag.
Take it! Just let me go!
- Let go the bag, punk.
- You got it. Let's go!
Thanks for the bag, fool!
I think it makes you
look tough.
- Is he okay?
- Who are you?
I'm the coach.
Conor O'Neill.
Why did you
keep them so late?
Fool, I called you
at Smyth and Stevens Securities...
and at first, some little girl
didn't even know who you were.
Then some man named Fleming
got on the phone...
and told me you were
out of the office today.
Please, take my home number.
You can't keep them boys
out there after dark.
Thank Jesus
for Jefferson's strength.
That smell?
That might be a lawsuit.
Look at you. You don't even look
like you're holdin' it together.
Jefferson, I'm sorry.
I shoulda called practice,
you know, when it got dark.
I just came by because...
as soon as you're ready
we expect you back, huh?
And...
I needed to know
what number uniform you wanted.
You're never gonna stay
being our coach.
Enjoy the game.
Nice wheels, soccer mom.
- Up yours.
- What's with the wagon?
Smyth and Stevens took shit when
a kid got beat up after practice...
so they lent me this car
to get 'em all home.
Ah, man. Who got beat up?
Who needs tickets?
- Jefferson Tibbs.
- That's the fat kid, right?
Yeah--
How'd you know?
You told me about
every kid on the team.
Aw, shit. I hate it when people
mess with kids.
Jesus. It's so wrong.
How can I help you fellas?
Mister, you just sold us
tickets to last night's game.
Don't make me shoot you! When a man
needs crack, a man needs crack!
You're unbelievable, man.
- Need seats? Need two?
- How we doin' tonight?
"We"?
We aren't doin' so good.
San Jose's not such a hot ticket.
- Did the Bulls cover last night?
- Yeah, they won by nine.
Shit.
I couldn't get any action.
I need to find someone
who'll take a big bet.
Fink's minimum bet's two grand.
- The guy at the cement plant?
- Yeah, Fink the cement guy. Why?
- I wanna lay 12 G's.
- 12 grand? On what?
Since Jordan left, the Bulls have
never covered at home against Miami.
- You serious about this?
- They play Miami on the 26th.
- You shouldn't do this.
- I don't have a choice.
Take me to meet Fink.
- Come on.
- Programs here!
Okay. Okay.
I'll take you to see Fink.
Sell some tickets.
- Who need tickets, folks?
- Who needs tickets?
- Pay up, bitch!
- I'll kick your ass, bitch!
Cool it! Cool it!
What's goin' on?
All right. Let me break it down
to you right quick.
Andre say he can catch any
pop- up ball anybody can throw.
Kofi say "That's bullshit.
You a busta."
Andre say, "Roll up, bitch. "
Kofi say, "I'll give you all
my gum if you catch this ball. "
He threw the ball. Andre caught it.
Andre say, "Pay me my money."
Kofi say,
"You a cheatin' bitch. " No, wait.
- Kofi say, "You a motherf--"
- Okay, I got it. Thanks.
Okay, I want everybody
to take a position. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's practice.
Damn, man, you suck,
just like my girlfriend.
Nice catch, Andre.
You jackass.
Keep chasin', punk.
Give me the ball.
- Damn!
- What happened?
Kofi just jumped
out of the way like a baby!
- What's your problem?
- Why is everyone so quiet?
What's up, Kofi?
You scared of the ball?
New rule!
No one can say anything bad
to anyone else on the field! Got it?
What?
You can't talk shit
you got nothin' to say?
Let's hear it.
- Got it.
Way to use your head,
Jamal.
It's cool, Jamal, man.
Don't worry about it.
"Four Spanish men with hiking boots
had surrounded me close.
I could tell they were banditos
because they had taco breath...
and they called me 'hombre.'
I spun around and hit the biggest
one. I punched him in the gut.
And as he was falling,
he grabbed my backpack.
I said, 'Stop, you banditos! I don't
want to have to hit anyone else. '
But because they were Spanish,
they didn't understand me.
Two more jumped me, and I hit one
of them in his--" Between his legs.
"My mouth banged on his head.
And that was where
I got my fat lip. The end."
- So where'd you get your fat butt?
- Andre, that's enough.
That was very nice, Jefferson.
Excellent use
of the first-person narrative.
I was scared of the banditos.
It was good.
Okay, sit down.
Mr. O'Neill.
Fresh from the office?
Why don't you invite your pants down
to your shoes so they can party?
Everyone,
this is Mr. O'Neill...
who coaches a baseball team
that some of our young men play on.
He's taken the time out of
his busy day to give us a hand.
So give him your attention.
A Wrinkle in Time is
an important book...
and I liked it very much.
I'm just sayin'
it ain't like that.
Fantasy ain't reality.
I like to read stuff that's real.
- Give me an example.
- Michael Jordan's book.
- Nice book, man.
- Excellent choice.
A strong piece of literature,
a great read.
- Yeah.
- That's a biography.
That's the real story of his life.
This is fiction.
The story's made up.
It's meant to entertain you
and make you think.
Kofi, you haven't spoken up. All
you've said is you didn't like it.
That's right.
If you can't say more, I'll assume
that you didn't really read it...
and your mother's gonna
want me to call her.
- Did you read the book?
- Yeah.
- Tell me something about it.
- It was booty.
Okay. I'm gonna
call your mom tonight.
That girl Meg is dumb.
She think her father
comin' back from wherever.
That's stupid to believe in.
That girl and her mom is
both trippin'.
'Cause where I'm from,
don't nobody's father come back.
Come on, right here!
Yo, let's do this!
I'm ready to beat 'em!
Come on! Hurry up!
Maybe this year you could
turn a double play.
Got the uniforms, Coach...
and your check.
- I take it you're not staying.
- Sorry. Can't.
Next time.
Good luck today.
Thanks. Thanks for
giving back to the community...
dickhead.
- I want seven like last time.
- I want number four!
Find a shirt that fits
and put it on, okay?
This shirt smells like
my grandma.
Good to see you, Jefferson.
- Who's got number 11?
- Coach, I got it here.
Thanks. Jefferson, this is
the biggest shirt we got, all right?
Everyone, the shirts go up
in sizes from two to 11, okay?
Coach, I need a shirt.
Who's got number ten?
- I got it.
- Give it to Jamal.
Where's my shirt?
Hey, guys. Guys?
Why don't you guys play catch
in the outfield, okay?
Warm up. G, hang on.
Hang on. I wanna talk to you.
- How old are you?
- I'll be nine in October.
You're supposed to be nine before
August to play in this league.
But I wanna play.
There's only ten uniforms,
11 players.
So I gotta give the guys
who are old enough first pick.
But I'm on the team, right?
Hell, yeah!
Play ball!
Strike.
He's out!
- Strike!
- It's all right, Ray Ray.
Strike!
Strike! Out!
- Come on!
- Throw it!
Damn!
- Come on! Get down! Get down now!
- Safe!
Oh, my God, he caught it.
Throw it!
What the hell--
Damn it!
- Okay, I'm gonna break your ass!
- What the hell is wrong with you?
Come on, baby,
you can do this.
- Keep goin', Kofi!
- Go! Come on, Kofi!
Keep going!
Safe!
Good job.
Strike! Out!
That's all right. That's the way
to take your cuts. Good job.
- Yeah?
- Coach, I guess that's it.
I mean, the league says we can't
start another inning after 6:30.
- Really?
- Well, yeah.
It's 6:37 now,
and we're up 16 to 1.
- That's cool. Thanks.
- Good luck the rest of the way.
Two, four, six, eight,
who do we appreciate? Kekambas!
Damn, Miles, you don't even
know how to throw the ball!
Shut up, Ray Ray. At least
he ran after it when it went by.
Shit went through your legs
like five damn times.
You a little punk, Dre.
Least you throw like one.
I'm tired of your shit, bitch.
- Kick his ass!
- Hey, that's it! That's it!
- That's it. That's it!
- I'm gonna kill you!
- Kofi, you're close to being done.
- I quit!
- This team sucks, man!
- Oh, hell, no. Damn it!
- Shit! This is you, Dre.
- This is all your fault, Dre.
Anybody hungry?
How 'bout pizza?
I'm down with that shit,
my brother.
You got three large pies,
11 pops.
It's 44.65.
You like hockey?
Blackhawks fans?
I take the wife and kids every year
to the Negro Hockey Hall of Fame.
Man, the only thing black
at a Blackhawk game is the puck.
I'll give you two loge seats
for the Bulls/Mavericks on Sunday.
- For the pizza?
- For the pizza.
Done deal.
Yo, Coach! If I get a home run next
game, you gotta buy me pizza again.
Every run I score,
I get one slice.
You bustas is trippin'.
Only me gettin' pizza every game.
MVP--
Most Valuable Pizza eater.
Yo, Coach,
I should be pitching.
- You wanna pitch, Miles?
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah. You can pitch on Wednesday.
- Yes!
Coach, is there any chance
that we'll get trophies this year?
Let's see.
There are eight teams
in the league...
play everyone twice--
We gotta win more games
than we lose.
- Yes!
- So we go to the 'ship, right?
- Yeah, we could.
- Man, we goin' to the 'ship.
We goin' to the 'ship, whoa.
We goin' to the 'ship.
All right, Andre.
This is it, right?
Don't you wanna
see my house?
Sure.
What?
Everyone's sittin' on the floor.
You stay below the window.
What?
Bullets.
What do you do
around here for fun?
Play baseball with you.
- See ya on Wednesday.
- Okay.
Safe!
You ready, Miles?
Want me to hold
your Walkman?
Come on, Miles.
You do your stuff now.
- Let's go, pitcher!
- Come on, Miles!
- Strike!
- Damn.
Strike!
- Strike! Out!
- Shit.
- What's he listenin' to?
- Same song...
- over and over.
- What is it?
"Big Poppa" by Notorious B. I. G.
Want one of his tapes?
He made five of 'em.
How's it go?
I love it when you call me Big Poppa
He waves his hand in the air
if you a true player
I see some ladies tonight
that should be havin' my baby, baby
Strike!
Strike! Out!
Strike! Strike!
We won our last game.
Miles is an amazing pitcher.
Oh, I heard.
Nine to three over the Gandas.
I'm just helping out till
my colleague returns from New York.
- You're great to take the time out.
- Hey, listen...
why don't we have
dinner tonight?
What good is an expense account
if you don't pad it once in a while?
I can't.
It's a school night.
- Maybe some other time.
- After the game on Saturday?
- Saturday.
- The boys would love you to come.
- Maybe.
You're not really tryin'
to get Miss Wilkes, are you?
- No. Why?
- Good.
'Cause I already tried,
and she ain't havin' it.
Do it, Jamal!
Kofi wanna come back...
but first I have to
"regotiate" his contract.
- Ball one!
- Okay.
- What are the terms?
- One, you tell Andre...
that Kofi's the best player.
Two, only Kofi gets pizza
when he hits a home run.
Three, if he whacks it over the
gate, he gets a pizza to take home.
One, when the season's over, the
team votes on who's the best player.
Two, Kofi can have the same
pizza bonuses as everyone else.
Three, if he hits it
over the fence...
I'll buy him a pizza.
Okay. Let me discuss
the regotiations with my client.
Put your back into it,
Jefferson!
Here! Light this sucker up!
- Go, baby!
- One more run!
What's up, Coach?
Kofi Evans.
- I spoke to your agent.
- I can come back?
If it's cool with the team.
But you start shit with Andre...
and you're done-- okay?
- Run!
- You're out!
Two, four, six, eight,
who do we appreciate?
The Kintus! The Kintus!
Yea, Kintus!
You're great with them.
Thanks.
Are we on for tonight?
- Tonight? I don't know.
- It's not a school night.
Come on--
just for dinner.
Look, the place is well-lit.
People can hear your screams.
I'm not sure. Where?
It's on the corner
of Clark and Addison-- Slugger's.
How 'bout 9:00?
9:00. Clark and Addison.
- All right.
- All right?
Yeah.
Did you miss a payment
with the Barber?
Yeah.
I shined him this week. Why?
That goofy dork Gino
came into Duffy's asking for you.
Oh, Jesus.
- Ticky, this is Ed.
- Ed.
- How you doin'?
- Pleasure.
This is Conor O'Neill.
He wanted to meet you.
What do you do
for money?
I'm a trader
at Smyth and Stevens.
Bullshit. First lie.
You gonna beat me one time so you
can pay off whoever else you owe?
- I wanna make a big bet.
- How big?
- Twelve grand.
- And?
And, if I win...
I wanna get paid.
No bullshit to keep bettin' it.
This guy's too serious.
I got a handful of clients,
they lay a hundred grand a week.
- They're not emotional about it.
- I can cover it.
You seem too emotional about
this 12 grand. Desperate.
What are you,
a psychiatrist or a bookie?
Don't you want your number?
You gonna take my bet?
- Ed, what's the next number?
- 27.
You're account 27 when you call in.
And your handle is?
Kekambas.
What? Kekambas?
- Kekambas.
- Ed, you got it?
- Got it.
- You're a strange kid, Kekambas.
I'm interested to see
what happens with you.
Gino, get him.
Fuck this.
Account 27. Kekambas.
Yeah. What's the line on Chicago
tomorrow night against Miami?
Gimme Miami minus six.
Twelve grand.
Wait. Wait.
I'll take Chicago
and the six points.
Yeah. Twelve thousand.
- Let's eat.
- Okay.
Why don't we sit?
So, I wanted to talk to you.
Yeah, I wanted to talk
to you too.
- Do you want a drink?
- No.
What's wrong?
I come here all the time
with the guys I work with.
Look, I know you don't work
at Smyth and Stevens.
Look at you. I could tell
right away you weren't a broker.
What's that mean?
Nothing. You just don't look like
you work at Smyth and Stevens.
You look like a freakin'
boring schoolteacher.
Hey, why'd you come here?
To bust me in the lie
about where I work? You win.
You coach my kids.
I thought we had a common interest.
Elizabeth, I get paid under
the table to coach that team.
And I only do that...
'cause I'm in a big hole with two
bookies who are lookin' to kill me.
- What?
- Nothing.
You know all this.
I spoke to Jimmy Fleming after
Jefferson got beat up. He told me.
- You just think I'm a big joke.
- No!
You know, it's people like me
that make people like you...
feel better about your tiny life.
This is unbelievable. I can't
believe I came down here for this.
Yeah? Then why did you come
if you know I'm a liar?
Because those kids trust you.
And they don't trust anybody.
- I told you, I coach for money.
- Well, I teach for money.
I've had the best fifth graders in
the world, but some don't make it.
There's nobody besides their mother
or me telling them what to do.
So what?
I'm done with all that.
Well, I just came down here
to see what they see...
because they're never wrong.
Take a good look.
See what they see.
- I came to talk to you about a job.
- Yeah?
Well, unless it pays
12 grand an hour...
I'm not interested.
- Did you play it?
- Yeah.
- Twelve grand? Yes!
- Twelve grand.
- Coach! Can we have a word?
- How many points you givin'?
I'm getting six.
You took Chicago?
Are you on crack?
- You laid 12 grand on those--
- I'm under a lot of pressure.
- I said now!
- Win or lose, I'm outta here.
- Darryl Mackey, league's president.
- We met.
Coach, we're concerned about the age
of some of the boys on your team.
Can you produce birth
certificates for your players?
All I got is what Coach Fleming
at Smyth and Stevens gave me.
Here they are.
What are the names of those
two boys at second base?
- Andre and Jamal.
- Which one's Jamal?
The taller one.
This birth certificate's
been altered.
What?
The eight's been turned
into a nine.
You have to be born
after September of '88.
Well, the kid is out of the league,
and the Kekambas are on probation.
Look, what are you guys--
the cops?
What's the point
of the league, Coach?
To teach kids it's okay to lie, as
long as they can get away with it?
It should be about
these kids playing ball...
not the trophy
you bring to work.
Look, the kid goes now.
Okay?
Jefferson bats seventh,
plays first base.
Miles pitches and bats eighth,
and Clarence...
you play third and bat ninth.
- Cool.
- Okay, let's go.
Why I not playin'?
You mad at me?
Jamal, the other coach--
'Cause I'm sorry about pushing
Ray Ray. I just want to play.
They know you changed your birth
certificate. I can't let you play.
But my mom said it was okay.
She said that she would tell them
if they asked. She said it was okay.
- I just wanna play.
- There's nothin' I can do.
Look, why don't you
just sit--
Miles, do your stuff now.
Strike.
Strike! Out.
Yeah, baby.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Time, Blue.
I can't have this kid out here
with these things on.
- What now?
- We're just all in agreement.
The kid can't wear headphones
while he pitches.
Matt makes a good point
about safety.
You're kidding me, right?
What if he gets hurt because he
can't hear in a dangerous situation?
- There's liability issues.
- Bring it in, fellas.
- Come on, bring it in.
- What are you doing?
I want you guys to explain
to them why they lost Jamal...
and why Miles can't
wear headphones...
and why the Bua Was and the Waatas
have nice uniforms...
and we have shitty T-shirts.
Easy, Coach.
You're already on a warning.
This is the president...
and that is the coach
of the goofiest team in the league.
They kicked Jamal out because
he was born two weeks early...
and now they're makin' Miles
take his headphones off...
'cause he's pitchin' too good.
It's a safety issue.
Fellas, you understand everyone
has to follow the same rules.
That's some weak-ass bullshit,
you bitch-ass, mother-freakin' bustas.
What did you say?
I believe he said,
"That is some weak-ass bullshit."
- Was that it, G-Baby?
- Yeah, that's it.
You are on thin ice, pal! I could
have you removed from this league.
This is my last game. I quit.
What?
I'm out.
I got business out of town.
Kekambas, back on the field.
Son, no headphones.
Coaches, get back to the dugouts.
Come on, let's go.
Get out there.
Come on! Let's go!
What'd you expect? I was gonna
coach this team the whole year?
Rally, rally,
the pitcher's name is Sally!
All right, Calvin.
Big stick now.
What have you got, son?
Shit!
Hang on. You guys suck.
- Whatever. I just quit.
- Finally.
- I'll see you at the game.
- Yeah.
- Slugger's.
Next practice
is Saturday, right?
01:00. Someone's gonna be here.
Right?
I'll make sure someone's here
on Saturday for practice.
Coach, can't you at least
give us a ride? I mean--
- It's early. You can walk.
- Could you drop us off?
Don't you think I might have
something more important to do...
than worry about you guys and
your stupid little baseball team?
Can we please go in now?
I gotta take a piss.
- We're watching through the glass?
- I feel better out here.
All right.
He can't get in there.
Jones fires.
Shit!
- Jones is ice cold!
- It's all right.
Fourth quarter, we're up
by two points, you're getting six.
- I don't know what I'm gonna do.
- Come on. You're up right now.
Ride it out.
Nice play by Tillman.
He's got it.
Here we go.
Smith throws up a prayer.
It's good! Holy shit!
- Should I look?
- No, no!
Not looking is working.
Keep not looking.
Oh, God, Ticky.
Am I out of the woods?
Here we go.
Miami inbounds.
Don't foul!
Shit! They fouled him!
Williams will shoot two!
Oh, God, Ticky. Never again.
- Shit!
- What's happening?
Talk to me!
What's happening?
Williams at the line.
- Williams makes the first.
- Shit, shit!
- He makes the second, you're dead.
- Williams shoots 80%.
Williams shoots. It's in.
Shit.
- What am I gonna do?
- Miami by seven.
Oh, my God, Ticky.
I was down 11 grand
before I made this bet.
Smith dribbles inside, half-court.
Heaves a 30-footer!
It's in!
- You covered! Yes, it's good!
- What's the final score?
Miami by four! You covered!
- You covered 12 G's!
- I covered!
I love it when you call me
Big Poppa
Throw your hands in the air
if you's a true player
I love it when you call me
Big Poppa
Got a gun up in your waist
Please don't shoot up the place
What
'Cause I see some ladies tonight
- That should be havin' my baby
- Baby
Hey! You take this party
somewhere else.
Kiss our ass, Duffy.
He beat Fink tonight for 12 grand!
- You got my six grand?
- Tomorrow.
Hey, no-neck, play this.
Make yourself useful, huh?
- So you took Fink for 12 large.
- Yeah.
Now what?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean, you don't know?
We're rolling it on the Bulls
Saturday night.
I'll take that action on Ticky's
number if you wanna play it.
We'll bet it with Fink.
We covered tonight.
We got Vancouver Saturday night.
We'll cover again. 24 grand.
Yeah. 24 grand.
Then what? Hey, you think
you just won the game of life?
- What next?
- I don't know.
If you win that, what
are you gonna do with your life?
You gonna coach baseball
for black kids?
I don't know.
I don't know, Duffy.
Maybe I'm just a loser, right?
Not like you.
Mr. Big Time, huh?
- I'm just a loser.
- All right, O'Neill.
I want my money tomorrow.
Night-night.
Time for beddy-bye, Coach.
Don't talk down to me!
You don't know shit
about those kids!
Come on. Let's go, let's go.
Chicago landers brace for
the long-awaited interleague...
crosstown matchup between the Sox
and the Cubbies tonight at Comiskey.
In a battle between two of the
game's brightest young hurlers...
21-year-old Jon Garland will face
off against the red-hot Kerry Wood--
It's Ticky.
I'm alone, I promise.
I'll take off my underwear and stand
naked in your hallway to prove it.
I'm naked now.
It's beautiful. Come on.
I'll slide my nuts under
your door till you let me in.
What's up?
I paid Duffy.
We're square.
Did you call Fink? Are we down
on the Bulls? How many points?
Fink wants to see
that I've still got his money.
Great. Let's go by there, flash him
a little cash and bet the 12 grand.
What's with you?
We're gonna do this, right?
Yeah, okay. I just gotta
go by the baseball field.
- Jesus Christ. I thought you quit.
- I did quit!
- I gotta drop the equipment off.
- I don't know.
... matchup between the Sox
tonight at Comiskey.
Sammy Sosa will attempt to go yard
for his fifth consecutive game...
and the Big Hurt will attempt to
break his 11-game hitting slump.
We're just an hour
from game time.
We'll be back
to take your calls.
All right. See ya.
Hurry up, okay?
- You here to tell us you quit?
- That's old news.
I left a message for Coach Jimmy
I would drop off the equipment.
He should be here
any minute.
- Yeah. Keep goin', sucker.
- We goin' to the 'ship alone.
I can't bet the 12 grand.
Fine. I understand.
We should just bet six grand...
and wait till we get
breathing room--
No, I can't.
Get your bum ass outta here, 'cause
we a better team without you anyway.
I'm not listening to any of you.
I'm not listening to you
or any of you!
So good luck.
Good luck on your own.
Call me when you get
to the 'ship without me.
Cold.
Good luck. I'm so glad
I'm done with this.
Let's go. If Fink thinks we're
coming, we should at least stop by.
If we don't want to bet it,
we don't, you know, technically--
How many of you guys been to a big
league park for a baseball game?
That's what I thought.
You guys will never be a team until
you see it played right. Never!
Gimme that.
Listen, you're stressed out.
Let's grab a bite.
- We can call and lay the bet.
- I'm out!
You hear me? I'm out!
I'm out, I'm out, I'm out!
- You're out.
- I'm done.
I'm done with all that.
Well, you gotta call Fink
for me.
You can't just dissolve
a partnership like that.
I'm flapping
in the breeze here.
Seriously. I got nothin' now.
I'm flappin' in the breeze here.
Kekambas. Come on.
Let's go. Get in the car.
Game starts in an hour.
Come on. Let's go.
What's this? What are we doing?
What is happening here?
Hey, let's--
Let's bet three grand.
Three grand will be fine.
I mean, what's goin' on?
Where we-- What are we doing?
Come on, wait.
Come on.
Now wait, wait!
This is against everything
that's right!
Hot dogs!
Get your hot dogs!
- Second row!
- Big league right now.
We got second row!
Coach, thanks for the seats.
They hot, yo.
Yo, check it out!
That's Sammy Sosa over there!
- Where?
- Right there!
Man, that ain't
no Sammy Sosa.
Shut up, man!
Look, y'all, look!
There's Sammy Sosa right there!
Look! Right there!
Yes?
Missed me.
I wanted to apologize
for the other night.
I have had better dates.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I heard about the baseball game.
The boys loved it.
Yeah. It worked. We've won
three in a row since then.
Do you have any idea
how much that meant to them?
I was thinking...
how the other night you knew that
I wasn't really a stock trader...
and that I had
a big gambling debt.
And if you were there
to offer me a job...
it might still stand.
So you're not here
to ask me out.
Am I supposed to be?
We need a physical activities
coordinator.
- You and me?
- The school.
You know, someone to supervise
after-school recess...
organize games and sports.
- We'd like to get a guy because--
- I think you like me.
- What?
- I just got this gut feeling...
when you were looking at me...
that you like me.
Are you interested?
In the job?
What are we talking about here?
I'm interested.
I'm interested in anything
I'm supposed to be interested in.
Let's go, Bua Was!
What's everybody
lookin' at?
Why we gotta play them damn boo-boos
again, man? They kicked our ass.
The best records in Division A
play to see who goes to the 'ship.
If we win,
we go to the 'ship.
If we win.
Everybody sit down.
Take a seat.
Come on, Dre.
No matter what happens today...
you guys should be really proud
of the season you've had...
'cause you played like a team.
And because you played
like a team...
I thought you should look
like a team.
Jefferson Albert Tibbs...
I believe this is yours.
- Man, that shit is tight!
- Look at that!
Fellas.
- There's no more shirts in the box.
- Nope.
What is destiny?
Destiny is you're supposed to win.
Since you're supposed to win,
since I expect you to win...
don't you celebrate when you strike
out one of these ridiculous--
Hey, dogs, hats!
What are you doing? Sit down!
Sit down and act like champions.
Come on!
Safe!
You're out!
Bua Was! Bua Was!
- Blue.
- Time!
- Good job, Clarence.
- Thanks, Coach.
Good job. Miles. Come on.
Listen, we're tied two-two.
We just need to get one guy out.
Coach, I can't pitch. These guys
are really gonna sweat me.
They're gonna yell,
and then I can't think.
This guy is one of the best
hitters in the league.
You're in charge out here.
Okay? Don't rush.
Hey, you can hear "Big Poppa"
in your head, right?
Yeah.
Just sometimes I lose the rhythm.
Miles, you're great.
I'm not worried.
Rally, rally,
the pitcher's name is Sally!
If you's a true player
'Cause I see some ladies tonight
That should be havin'
my baby, baby
I love it when you call me
Big Poppa
Throw your hands in the air
if you's a true player
'Cause I see some ladies tonight
that should be havin' my baby
Baby
I love it
when you call me Big Poppa
Throw your hands in the air
if you's a true player
'Cause I see some ladies tonight
That should be havin' my baby, baby
Strike one.
I love it when you call me
Big Poppa
Throw your hands in the air
if you's a true player
'Cause I see some ladies tonight
- That should be havin' my baby
- Two!
Strike three!
Out!
Good going, Miles.
All right.
We're tied two-two.
- Yeah!
- This is it. Last licks.
We pull this out,
we goin' to the 'ship.
Leading off, we've got Andre, we've
got Ray Ray, we've got Clarence.
After that, it's you, Kofi,
and then we've got Jefferson.
Let's go to the 'ship.
- Safe!
- Way to go, Dre!
Good job.
Strike one!
Two!
Strike three!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nice job, Ray Ray.
- Damn!
- Let's go, Kofi!
Yeah, yeah.
Almost, Kofi. Almost.
Two down.
Jefferson, how're you doin'?
You're up.
Time, Blue.
We've got Jarius Evans
batting for Jefferson Tibbs.
All right.
Wednesday night practice.
Thanks for the uniform,
Coach.
- Thanks, Coach.
- See you guys later.
Hey, kid. You can't
come in there right now.
- How long it's gonna be?
- Don't know.
Jamal, what's up?
Why can't we go in
right now?
- They're gonna cap somebody inside.
- What're we gonna do?
Come on.
- Shit! Come on.
- Move!
Come on, man!
- Quiet. They'll pass by.
- Come here!
What's up?
Shit!
- Get outta here! Come on!
- It's all right. We're okay.
G, we're okay.
G, come on, get up.
It's okay. We'll just wait
for somebody to come.
It'll be okay.
What?
Oh, Jesus.
I must
Tell Jesus
Jesus
Can help
Me
Jesus
Alone
We've heard testimony from those
very close to our community.
Praise Jesus.
I want to give a few more people the
opportunity to say something on--
on Jarius's behalf.
Please, Mr. O'Neill.
Come on up.
Good morning.
Jarius was a player on the Kekambas
baseball team that I coach.
Honestly, he--
he was too young to play.
But he wanted to be a part
of the team so badly that...
I couldn't say no.
G- Baby. You're up.
He had a great smile too.
I know I'm not telling you
anything you don't know.
I've got Jarius Evans
batting for Jefferson Tibbs.
He was a really tough guy.
Just a boy, really,
who...
wanted to be
around his older brother.
Hang on, Coach. I don't have Jarius
Evans on this roster anywhere.
Oh, you know what?
There he is. He's okay.
The other day...
we played a really important game
against a good team.
And, two outs
in the last inning...
I had no choice
but to let Jarius bat.
You can swing if you want,
but you don't have to.
Okay? If you go down looking,
none of us care.
But if you want to swing,
swing.
Get back in there.
Do what you feel.
He was fearless
as he stepped to the plate.
I was terrified for him.
With two strikes
and our hopes dwindling...
he hit a shot
down the first baseline...
and won the game.
And watching him...
raise his arms in triumph...
as he ran to first base...
I swear...
I was lifted in that moment
to a better place.
I swear he--
he lifted the world
in that moment.
He made me...
a better person...
even if just
for that moment.
I am...
forever grateful to Jarius
for that.
That was nice...
what you said.
His mother was very moved.
Thank you.
Wait.
There's some people who want to talk
to you about the baseball team.
The team is done.
That's what they want
to talk to you about.
They're in the auditorium.
We know the league wants to cancel
the championship game.
Mom said it was all up to us
'cause of G-Baby.
Yeah. It's over.
You guys don't have to play.
You guys had a great year.
You can keep the uniforms.
Wait. You're quitting again?
What do you mean?
We wanna play, bitch.
- You guys wanna play?
- Hell, yeah!
For G-Baby.
I'll see you tomorrow
at 11:00.
I came to make sure
you guys win.
I even made a bet
with your friend, Ticky.
Knowing Ticky bet against us
improves our chances.
Did you really fill out an
application to work at the school?
Good luck today.
Thank you.
- Andre, Ray Ray.
- What's up, Coach?
Why don't you bring
everybody in?
- Hey, y'all, bring it in!
- Let's go!
I want you guys to take a good look
at yourselves today and feel proud.
We made it here.
We're here.
What I've learned from you
is that...
really, one of the most
important things in life...
is showing up.
I'm blown away
by your ability to show up...
through everything
that's gone on.
The league never wanted you
to play this game...
but you showed up.
But we only have
eight players, so--
- God.
- We can't play.
He was my brother.
He loved to watch us play.
He's watching us right now.
We gonna play today.
Here you go, Kofi.
- Okay, this is for G-Baby.
- G-Baby.