Five thousand years ago...
a fierce warrior known
as the Scorpion King...
Ied a great army on a campaign...
to conquer the known world.
After a vicious campaign
which lasted seven long years...
the Scorpion King and his army
were defeated...
and driven deep into
the sacred desert of Ahm Shere.
One by one,
they slowly perished...
under the scorching sun...
until only the great warrior himself
was left alive.
Near death...
the Scorpion King made a pact
with the dark god Anubis...
that if Anubis
would spare his life...
and let him conquer his enemies...
he would give him his soul.
Anubis accepted his offer
and spared his life.
Anubis gave theScorpion King
command of his army...
and like an evil food,
they was hedaway...
all that lay before them.
When his task was done...
Anubis forced the Scorpion King
to serve him for all time.
His army was returned
to the sands from whence they came...
where they wait, silently...
to be awakened once again.
Alex?
What wereyou thinking,
a mummy had come back to life?
I'll tell you a story some time.
What are you doing down here?
I told you to wait for us in the temple.
- But, Dad, I saw--
- No "buts." It's dangerous down here.
- But I saw your tattoo.
- You saw what?
On a wall by the entrance.
There's a cartouche just like it.
With the pyramid and the eye...
and the two kings and everything.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Okay. Well, I'll be up to take
a look at that in a minute.
In the mean time, I want you
to wait for us up there.
Pick up your stuff,
and I'll see you up in the temple.
Go.
Go on.
And what should I do?
I don't know. Surprise me.
- Build a better mouse trap.
- Okay.
While your mother goes
and desecrates another tomb.
Go away.
- Those are poisonous, you know.
- Only if they bite you.
What was all that about?
Oh, nothing.
Alex wanted to show me something.
I swear...
the kid gets more and more
like you every day.
What, you mean
more attractive, sweet...
and devilishly charming?
No, he's driving me crazy.
Now, where were we?
Hammer and chisel.
All right, all right!
Let's do it your way.
Thank you.
Ever since I had that dream...
this place is all
I can think about.
Ever since you had that dream,
I haven't had a decent night of sleep.
I feel like I've been here before.
I know I've been here before.
Evy, nobody's been here before,
not in at least 3,000 years.
Except for these guys.
Then how do I seem to know
exactly where I'm going?
Let's go.
Knock, knock. Anybody home?
You two check out that stuff,
see if it's there.
I'll sort out the O'Connells.
You know, if you move that fast enough,
you can almost write your name.
I just had a vision.
It was like my dream...
but it was real.
It was like I was actually here
in ancient times.
Well, if you actually were here...
could you show me
how to open this thing?
Hold this.
- Now you're starting to scare me.
- I'm starting to scare myself.
What is this?
Look at the state of this rubbish.
The Egyptians never had a clue.
Look at that stuff.
It's all chintz and stuff.
Look at that.
Cheap pottery, this.
Ancient rubbish.
Jacques,
something's hit me head!
Shut up, Spivey.
This place is cursed.
We don't want to wake the gods.
That's the emblem
of the Scorpion King.
He's supposed to be pure myth.
No trace of him has ever been
found before. No artifacts.
No archival evidence.
Maybe they didn't want
any body to find him.
- Let's open this.
- Evy, I don't know.
-I don't have a good feeling about this.
-It's only a chest.
No harm ever came
from opening a chest.
Right, and no harm ever came
from reading a book.
- Remember how that one went?
- Come on. We can't stop now.
Just remember,
I was the voice of reason here.
For once.
Rubbish.
Dreck. Chintz.
Only half of this--
God, that hurt!
Hon? Let's do it your way.
The bracelet of Anubis.
I'll take care of this.
Oh, my God
It's a bit late for that!
- Put it in your rucksack.
- Let's leave it here.
- It's a bit late for that!
- What's it say?
"He who disturbs this bracelet...
shall drink from the Nile."
That doesn't sound too bad.
Jacques is gonna make
a nice fillet out of you, my son.
Oh, please.
Spivey! Jacques!
Let's get the hell out of here!
Come on.
This is bad, Evy.
- We've had bad before.
- This is worse.
Mom? Dad?
I can explain everything.
The Book of the Dead gives life.
And the Book of the Living...
takes life away.
I thought that was my job.
We're getting close.
Did you acquire it?
We're getting very close.
We found him.
We found him! We found him!
Step aside there.
Out of the way.
Imhotep.
It's him. It's lmhotep.
Now we must raise
those that serve him.
Get out of my way.
Get out of the way.
Get out of my way
or I'm gonna shoot you in the face.
He means it.
He shot someone before.
Give it to me.
The opportunity passed us by.
- We need that bracelet.
- We need it before it opens.
Enough.
My dear Hafez...
I told you
I should have handled it.
I did not want
your past history...
to cloud the issue.
Don't worry. We know where it is.
We'll take care of it.
No, we'll take care of it.
I have a different chore
for you now.
Where is the bracelet?
It's on its way
to merry old London.
Then London is where we must go.
I think the bracelet
is some sort of guide...
to the lost oasis of Ahm Shere.
Evy, I know what you're thinking...
and the answer's no.
We just got home.
That's the beauty ofit.
We're already packed.
Why don't you just give me
one good reason?
It's just an oasis...
darling.
A beautiful...
exciting...
romantic...
oasis.
The kind with the white, sandy beach
and the palm trees...
and the cool, clear, blue water?
We could have some of those big drinks
with the little umbrellas.
- Sounds good.
- Sounds too good. What's the catch?
Supposedly it's the resting place
of Anubis's army.
You see? I knew there's a catch.
There's always a catch.
How did I know that?
And let me guess.
It was commanded
by that Scorpion King guy?
Yes, but he only awakens
once every 5,000 years.
And if someone doesn't kill him,
he's gonna wipe out the world.
- How did you know?
- I didn't, but that's always the story.
The last known expedition
to actually reach Ahm Shere...
was sent by Ramses the Fourth
over 3,000 years ago.
- He sent over a thousand men.
- None of them was ever seen again.
- How did you know?
- I didn't, but that's always the story.
- Did I mention the pyramid of gold?
- Twice.
Alexander the Great
sent troops in search of it.
- Hooray for him.
- So did Caesar.
- Look what happened to his career.
- And Napoleon.
Yeah, but we're smarter than him.
- Taller too.
- Exactly.
- That's why we're gonna find it.
- Because we're taller?
- That's why I loveyou.
- Nice try.
Mom!
What do I do with this chest?
Sucker weighs a god dang ton.
Alex, watch your language.
Rather weighty, this.
Evy, that first weird dream of yours
was exactly six weeks ago, right?
Yes, but what's that
got to do with anything?
It just happens to coincide
with Egyptian New Year.
That's right.
What a coincidence.
Maybe.
All I'm saying
is let's be cautious.
If anything happened to you,
I would never forgive myself.
You and Alex are the only thing
that matter to me.
Well...
the Bembridge scholars
have been begging me...
to run the British Museum.
Cripes, how do you get
this thing off?
Have I kissed you today?
I hate it when you do that.
Why?
- Makes me agree to anything.
- Anything?
Those knickers are not mine.
Jonathan.
Alex, behave yourself
for five minutes, all right?
You betcha.
- Happy to be home?
- Couldn't be happier.
It's the Year of the Scorpion.
- Neat.
- Thought you might like that.
So I killed the mummy and his minions
and stole his scepter.
Oh, you're so brave.
And rich.
Did I mention rich?
What do you think I'm doing here?
- Sorry, we must be in the wrong house.
- You said this was your house.
- I didn't.
- Call me!
- You're not Sheila's husband?
- No.
If you work for Johnny,
I was gonna pay him back on Tuesday.
I don't know any Johnny.
We are looking for
the bracelet of Anubis.
Oh, good for you. Good thing to have,
the old bracelet of Anubis.
Where is it?
Ah, you're looking here
for the bracelet. I see.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Mr. O'Connell,
you try my patience.
Mr. O'Connell? Hold on a minute.
You've got the wrong ma--
That bracelet.
Now I remember.
- I lost it in a card game.
- For your sake, I hope not.
It can't be.
- Where's your wife?
- My wife?
You mean Evy.
I think she went off to Baden-Baden
orTibet or something.
The girl's a free spirit.
Did I mention I was single now?
Egyptian asps
are quite poisonous.
It's downstairs.
There's a safe.
The combination is 3-20-58.
393-something.
It's in the safe downstairs.
I told you!
And your point is?
- I told you so you wouldn't kill me.
- When did we make that arrangement?
Jonathan, I thought I said
no more wild parties.
Well, when you're popular--
I'm serious. If you've lost
that key, you're grounded.
I haven't lost it. I just can't find it.
There's a difference.
Well, you better
start finding it then.
I will, Mom.
There's nothing to worry about.
Good evening.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for the chest,
of course.
Give it to me now.
Get out of my house.
Whoa, Mom.
- Maybe not the best idea.
- Alex, get back there.
Definitely not the best idea.
I think it's time
to yell for Dad now.
- I will kill you and take it anyway.
- I think not.
Ardeth.
What are you doing here?
Perhaps explanations
are best kept for later.
Ardeth Bay.
Lock-Nah.
Hey, folks,
knowing my brother-in-law...
he probably deserves whatever
you're about to do to him...
but this is my house.
I have certain rules
about snakes and dismemberment.
Shoot him!
Whoa, Mom!
- Where did you learn to do that?
- I have no idea.
That I learned from your father.
I'll take that.
Not bad for a Medjai.
Let go!
- What's in the chest?
- The bracelet of Anubis!
They must not get the bracelet.
Get it and get out of here!
Mom, look out!
Evelyn!
What'd you do this time?
I haven't done anything
to anybody.
- Lately.
- Come on!
Rick!
Look out, Rick!
Dad! Dad!
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
What the hell are you doing here?
Scratch that. I don't care.
Who are those guys
and where are they taking my wife?
My friend, I'm not sure...
but wherever this man is...
your wife will surely be.
Hey, I know him.
He's the curator.
- He works at the British Museum.
- Are you sure?
Better believe him. He spends more
time there than he does at home.
Okay, you're here.
The bad guys are here.
Evy's been kidnapped.
Let me guess.
They once again removed
the creature from his grave.
Not to point fingers, but isn't it your
job to make sure that doesn't happen?
That woman with him knew things
no living person could possibly know.
She knew exactly where
the creature was buried.
We hoped she would lead us to
the bracelet. She obviously did.
Now they have it.
I wouldn't get
too nervous just yet.
Is that gold?
When I stuck it on,
I saw the pyramids at Giza.
Then whoosh-- straight across
the desert to Karnak.
You have started a chain reaction that
could bring about the next apocalypse.
You, lighten up.
You, big trouble.
You, get in the car.
I am sorry if alarmed your son,
but you must understand.
Now that the bracelet's on, we have
7 days before the Scorpion King awakens.
We? What we?
If he is not killed,
he will raise the Army of Anubis.
- I take it that's not a good thing.
- Oh, he'll wipe out the world.
The old "wipe out the world" ploy.
Whom ever can kill
the Scorpion King...
can send his army back
to the Underworld...
or use it to destroy man kind
and rule the Earth.
They dug up lmhotep 'cause he's tough
enough to take out the Scorpion King.
That is their plan.
Alex, I got a big job for you.
Stay here and protect the car.
- I could do that.
- Protect the car?
Come on. Just because I'm a kid
doesn't mean I'm stupid.
- I know.
- Dad!
If you see anyone come running out
screaming, it's just me.
Maybe you should stay here
and watch him.
Now you're talking.
- You want the shotgun?
- No, I prefer the Thompson.
If l were to say to you, I'm a stranger
traveling from the east...
seeking that which is lost--
Then I would reply that I am
a stranger traveling from the west.
- It is I whom you seek.
- Then it is true.
- You have the sacred mark.
- What, that?
That got slapped on me
in an orphanage in Cairo.
That mark means
you're a protector of man...
a warrior for God, a Medjai.
Sorry.
You've got the wrong guy.
Mr. Hafez.
They found him.
Imhotep.
Do not be frightened.
I am not afraid.
You know...
a couple of years ago, this would've
seemed really strange to me.
Lord lmhotep will be much pleased.
Where is it?
Where is the bracelet?
I think I know.
At the very top of the gold pyramid,
there was a huge diamond.
How huge?
It was so big,
it would refect the sun...
and wink at distant travelers...
beckoning them to their deaths.
Get off. Get off.
Oh, my God.
You wait!
I'll put you in your grave again.
Our thinking was, not if we
put you in your grave first.
Burn her!
You bast--
- Open it! Open it!
- I'm trying!
- Hurry up!
- Come on, come on!
- You broke it!
- Be quiet!
If there's gonna be any hysterics,
they'll come from me!
Go, go, go, go! Go!