From the karate championships
at the Stardust...
you know him as Oharra
from "Enter the Dragon"...
please welcome our celebrity
announcer, master Bob Wall.
Ladies and gentlemen, this will
be an exhibition fight.
The challenger, local kung-fu
favorite, Jack Tanaka.
And the champion, dewey
"the black cobra" cooper.
-Hi, dad.
-Hi, son.
You were good tonight
but uh, a little off...
Thanks, Erik.
Where's Brad?
Son, Brad did
not want to come.
There's a lovely young lady
I brought that I want you to meet.
I'm just not ready
to meet anybody.
I'm just not ready.
Alright...
I'm going in...
-What was that?
-A moth.
Your a/v enhancement
was set too high.
I'm pickin' up
several targets.
Move in.
Feels like a trap.
My family's got money.
Please, don't kill me.
Why'd you turn off the program?
I almost had 'em.
Everything is fine Dean...
Uh... however,
the hostage is dead.
It's a good thing
it was a simulation.
Oh, it's much more than that.
We're trying to make the simulation
as real as possible.
I see you killed
the hostage again.
Well ya know, I keep screwin' up
just so I can come back and see you.
But you're still not good
with computers.
I just can't put my faith in this
new technology, you know.
I don't have a PHD
in computer science like you.
Well,
professor Tanaka has four...
So I think
you're in good hands.
That's right Dean...
this new program
that we've developed...
is so advanced that soon
most of your training...
will be done here in the lab, facing
computer generated opponents.
Come on, you can't replace...
real opponents or real targets.
I wouldn't be too sure of that.
These computer
generated fighters...
have been programmed
to respond, adapt...
and learn any movement
they can encounter.
Ya know pretty soon they might
be able to think on their own...
I'll believe that when I see it.
This program is going to prepare you
for the ultimate confrontation...
whether it be astreet punk
or fighter or terrorist.
-It could save your life!
-You're probably right, doc.
I guess I'm still just
a little old fashioned.
There's a lot to be said about
being old fashioned that's good...
but I believe that eventually
the man, and not the machine...
can ultimately make
the difference...
...isn't that what I was saying?
-Here go clean yourself up...
Doin' anything tonight?
Yeah... I'm studying
for my second PHD...
Great...
Yeah, that's a good
snap there. Put a little more...
there you go.
Tighten that up. Good.
Class, over here. Break.
Okay, class remember... relax
as you go through your moves.
Because when you tense up,
you're fighting two people...
yourself and your opponent.
Everybody understand?
Okay, ceremonial bow. Hut!
Class dismissed.
-You still workin' on the game?
-Oh, hi Sally. I'm almost through...
Well just a few more
tweaks and adjustments...
and uh SCl-Fighter
will be completed...
SCl-Fighter...
I like it! How'd you
come up with that one?
I... I think it's
the perfect name.
SCl-Fighter...
where modern science meets
the ancient art of self-defense.
I think Brad's going to love it.
Not if you're late for
his birthday party.
Oh geez... I always lose
track of time...
It's past nine.
I've gotta get going.
Sally, oh... uh please will you...
shut off the computer and pack
the game up for me please...
Alright, okay. Go get ready...
I'll take care of everything.
Well Sally...
how do I look?
You look great.
Relax.
How am I supposed to relax?
Look how many people are here.
My dad's going to kill me!
Well, since it's your birthday,
I got you a really special gift...
Here, careful with it.
Don't get it wet.
Ha how'd you get these? Alright,
concert tickets for this Friday!
-Thank you.
-Happy birthday.
-You want some?
-You know I don't drink.
Come on, just one sip.
Brad.
Brad!
-Sr. Tanaka, I'm so...
-Don't waste your time...
-Brad was..
-Don't waste your time!
I want everybody
out of here now!
Does this look ok to you?
Looks good.
Except for this code...
-It's a fragment.
-I missed that.
-Good job though.
-Thanks.
Hey. I heard you met
doctor Tanaka's son.
Is he hot?
Well I haven't really met him
but I saw him fight...
and he looks really,
really cute!
Brad, Brad!
Sit down,
I want to talk to you.
Sit down.
What's gotten
into you lately?
Is this going to take long?
Answer me, Brad.
Look, I know there's a problem.
I want to know what it is.
-You wouldn't understand.
-Try me.
Okay...
go to your room.
You're grounded for a week.
Damn.
-Hello.
-Yeah, hi. Jess?
Hey, Brad. Oh, I'm so sorry about
getting you into trouble tonight.
Don't worry about it. He's being
a jerk. It's not your fault.
Yeah, but I know
that beer didn't help.
So, um, aren't you excited about
the concert this weekend?
Um, actually
that's why I called you.
-Yeah?What do you mean?
-I can't go. I'm grounded.
Well, we can sneak out.
-I would, but he took the tickets.
-You let him take the tickets?
Brad, I've been saving up for those
tickets for the past six months.
I know. I'm sorry. I wish there
were something I could do.
Alright, alright. Don't worry about
it. I'll figure something out.
-You promise?
-Yeah, I promise.
-You're not stillmad at me are you?
-No.
-I'll see you in school, alright?
-Alright.
-Goodnight.
-Bye.
Come in.
Happy birthday.
I got you a new kung fu uniform...
Great.
You know, Brad, you were gonna
come back to class tonight.
It's my birthday. I should
be able to do what I want.
Skipping class is
one thing, but...
what are you doing throwing a
party without asking permission?
It's my house too, you know.
Kung fu is not just asport
It's away of life.
And if you would dedicate
yourself just a little bit...
your grades
might improve too.
Thanks for the gift, dad.
Hello.
-Hi, Jack.
-Hi, dad. You're late...
you know I got carried away
at the lab, son. I'm sorry.
The party's over?
What's going on?
Brad missed class again.
And he threw this party,
didn't even tell me about it.
-Son, it's his birthday.
-I caught him with a beer tonight.
I mean, no wonder his
grades are slipping.
Jack, I meant to talk
to you about Brad.
You know lately he's been a
little rebelious and acting out.
But growing up is
a hard thing to do, son.
Especially when you lose your
mother at such an early age.
That can be devastating.
So try to be patient
with Brad, please.
You don't understand, dad.
Kids are different today.
They're not that different.
You remember you when
you were younger?
You used to sneak out and
try to see your girlfriend...
you used to get me in
a lot of trouble too, you know.
I don't wish to dishonor
or disrespect the love...
and the feeling you had
for Stephanie.
I know it's been painful. The reason
I wanted you to meet Sally...
was because she's a decent
woman. She's intelligent.
-Now will you meet her?
-Ok, I'll meet her.
-When?
-Soon.
Let's just go give Brad his gift.
Oh, good Alright, uh you know.
I have an idea.
Why don't we set it up here
and give him asurprise?
Okay?
That's cool.
What do you want now?
What?
Brad.
That's a hell of away
to treat your grandfather.
-How you doin' granpa?
-I'm doin' alright. I'm doin' alright.
-How are you feeling?
-Alright.
I've got something for you.
What is it?
Ah, it's something
I made especially for you.
It's avideo game.
It's called SCl-Fighter.
-SCl-Fighter?
-Yes...
so come on.
I set it up in the living room.
Go ahead, try it out.
It's going to be alright, Jack.
Come on.
Brad, put it in. Come on.
-Are you sure this thing's safe?
-Jack, of course it's safe.
There's nothing wrong with it.
It's cool, uh?
Hi, you must be Brad.
Yeah, who are you?
Veronica.
-Nice graphics.
-Let's see what suits you.
Cool...
-What's he doing in there?
-Ah, he's trying different uniforms on.
What kind of game is this?
It's a hand to hand combat
training simulator.
With artificial intelligence that
can adapt and adjust itself to...
its opponents strengths
and weaknesses...
and provide maximum challenge.
By the way,
I used real people as models...
to play the computer
generated fighters.
Come on Jack.
Go ahead, try it.
I don't think so.
You said you wanted
to be close to Brad.
A family that plays
together stays together.
-A video game?
-Yes, avideogame.
Come on.
Jack, I designed this game
for the both of you.
So that you can connect.
This is an opportunity.
Well I don't see how this
is going to help any.
Come on. No ands or buts. Everything
isn't what it appears to be. Okay?
-Jack I'm so glad you made it.
-You know me?
Only what doctor
Tanaka told me...
Iwas so looking forward
to meeting you in person.
You are much more handsome
than I had imagined.
Thanks! Dad,
I'm sure you're enjoying this!
Maybe you'd look good
in a Shaolin monk's outfit.
I don't think so...
orange is definitely
not my color...
...that's it, a superhero costume.
-No...
...what is your name?
-Veronica.
Veronica get this off me!
You're a tough one to please. Ok
how 'bout something simple like this?
-That's cool.
-This'll do.
Then you're ready to go.
Step through the portal...
and you'll make your way
to the first level of the game.
Thanks.
Jack...
Come back
and see me sometime!
Good luck, guys.
I am the karate master.
If you are prepared for battle,
we can begin.
Choose your skill level.
Skill level?
Yes.
Are you master or beginner?
Master.
You better make
it beginner Brad.
Chill out dad,
it's just a game.
You have chosen.
-Brad you ok?
-Yeah, I'm cool.
Kick his ass dad!
Time to give you
a taste of reality.
Welcome to SCl-Fighter!
What's the matter?
There's no way Brad's
playing this thing.
Dad,
I can take care of myself.
A game's just a game,
but that really hurt.
You're overreacting.
It's just adapting to your
player's skill level.
Just fix this thing
or get rid of it.
Alright, alright, alright.
I'll fix it.
See what I mean?
He never listens.
Uh, I'm sorry about that Brad.
He's such a hypocrite.
He gets hit all the time and
he says it's part of training.
Alright.
I'll fix it and then I will...
I'll talk to your father.
And I'm sure I can talk him into
letting you try the game again.
-Deal?
-Deal.
Okay, deal. Good.
Now let's see what's wrong
with this sucker here.
SCl-Fighter
diagnostic activated.
Your father loves
you very much.
He wants to do the best for you. I
know he's trying to understand you.
He doesn't understand me.
He never will.
Not like mom did.
Your mom would be
very proud of you today.
Well, I guess it's time
to check this game out.
Everything appears
to be normal.
Nothing seems to be wrong
with this game.
Program end.
Interesting weather.
Come on, mom.
It looks horrible.
-It looks good!
-It looks horrible!
He's going to hate it.
Brad!
Stop.
I love you...
Okay, dad's going be home.
Let's get this done...
Okay, we need the candles.
Brad, you didn't forget
the candles?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
He's going to be home. We need to
get to the store and get back quick.
Mom, I can't.
I'm expecting a phone call.
Come on we need to go
to the store. It's late.
Oooh! Come on, please?
Okay. Clean up
and I'll be right back.
Mom!
Hey, Brad, where's Jack?
He's busy.
Oh, too bad.
Same uniform?
Yeah!
-Where's daddy?
-I can do this on my own.
You are not worthy.
Wanna bet?
Go home and
practice little boy.
You are not worthy
of fighting me.
Are you sure you don't want
to go get daddy?
Such a pity. I have to finish
this futile display.
Brad.
Brad, take that thing off. Aah!
System now operating
on back-up power supply.
What the hell is going on?
Dad, get over here fast.
It's Brad.
Just get over here.
-Jack?
-Dad, it's... it's Brad.
-What's going on?
-He was playing the game.
I tried to take the helmet off
and I got shocked.
It's not even plugged in.
What's happening?
I... I don't know, son.
His mind is trapped in the game.
You have to go into the game.
You have to find Brad
and you must...
defeat all the fighters
and get to the last level.
That will give me the opportunity
to transport you and Brad...
out of the game.
But we don't have much time.
-I'm going in.
-Careful, Jack.
Brad!
Brad, where are you?
Dad! Dad, help me.
Dad, over here.
Sally? Sally, code black!
My worst nightmare.
Can you please get
the recovery discs and...
and come to Jack's house
as soon as possible?
Yes, please.
Thank you.
Dad, over here.
Dad, I'm over here.
You're getting closer...
Here I am.
-Daddy.
-What did you do with my son?
If you get through me...
you just might find him.
Where's my son?
He's not on this level.
I hope he's dead!
Hello, Bradley,
it's about time you got here.
Thank you Jack...
-You know me?
-We all do.
I'm the white dragon.
Why did you help me?
You remind me of someone.
Brad's not here. Go find him.
-Hey, what are you doing?
-Hi, Dean.
I have to bring these
to professor Tanaka.
You're not supposed to
take anything out of here.
I know.
This is an emergency.
Okay, go out the back door.
I'll cover you.
Thanks.
Professor,
how did this happen?
Brad!
Jack!
How did you get in the game?
There's no time for that
my power's draining.
I'm sorry son I only programmed
two fighters for this level.
The game has learned
all your moves.
-How do I beat these guys?
-You have to be innovative.
Use your reflexes and instincts.
Be focused.
Your subconscious mind
is the key.
Well done, Jack.
Come on!
Come on, Jack.
He's okay.
Stay strong, Jack.
Stay strong.
What's happening?
I'm afraid avirus has gotten into
the game. It has corrupted and...
destroyed all
the safety codes.
Son, you are fighting
for your life and Brad's.
You've got to get
to the next portal.
I'll get you this time.
Surprise!
Two heads are better than one.
Dragon twins, activate.
We'll get him this time.
Well there's a one for the money,
two for the show.
Here I go...
Help! Dad!
What have you done
to my world?
The program's been poisoned.
-I swear it wasn't me.
-You lie.
You and your father are
the only new ones to the game.
Run away, little boy...
When you and your father return,
I'll kill you both.
Hello, Jackie.
It's time to play.
Ready?
Got you...
Oooh, got you now!
Okay, Jackie,
let's see what you've got.
Try that again! Come on. I'm
going to get you now! Look out...
You are going to regret.
You have felt my anger.
Alright, are you ready
to give up? Huh?
Go. Find the boy
If you can!
Come back when
you want some more.
I can't get outta this place.
Spare change?
What are you supposed to be?
They call me street fighter.
My world's not
so pretty is it Jack?
Ready for this?
Where's my son?
Jack, you know the rules, baby!
You gotta beat me!
He's not here, baby.
Ah, not this place again!
There's got to be a portal.
Dad!
Granpa, anybody
can you hear me?
Who am I kidding?
I'm stuck and it's all my fault.
Pretty clever granpa.
I'm going in.
That's odd. It's Dean!
A residual image from the lab.
Please don't kill me!
I don't want to die.
You don't have to do this. My
family's got money. We can pay you.
Please don't kill me...
Please.
Jack?
Dean?
Hey. Hey. Up here!
-Where are you going?
-I'm looking for my son.
Brad.
You're going the wrong way.
Go this way.
Go through the tunnel.
Not bad for a beginner.
Oh, by the way, I forgot one thing.
You gotta go through me before
you get to the next portal.
Ha, piece of cake.
I know why you're here.
You're looking for
the portal to your son.
Where's Brad?
Now I can't tell you that.
It wouldn't be
as fun if I did.
Where is he?
I hate kids Jack.
They're awaste of time!
Brad's already interfering
in our relationship.
If it wasn't for him,
we could be.
Friends?
Sorry, you're not my type.
They call me the scorpion.
Taste my venom, Jack.
Where's Brad?
I like it when you're
rough with me...
You wouldn't hit a lady now
would you Jack?
You hit me.
You win Jack...
Brad's not here!
Come back and see me sometime.
I'd like to play a different
game with you.
What a beautiful picture
of Brad and his mom.
They were inseparable.
Relax.
No more fighting...
Jack!
-Dad...
-Jack!
Is that you?
Yes.
Jack, what are you
doing, what's goingon?
-I have to catch her.
-Who?
The white dragon.
Jack, she's not real Icreated her.
You have to find Brad and get
out of here as soon as possible.
Time is running out.
I have to find her.
Jack...
time is running out.
Wake up Jack...
wake up.
Why did you return?
I wanted to see you again...
You shouldn't have
come back here...
you have to keep moving
forward in the game...
don't give up...
defeat all the levels
and save your son.
But I don't want to leave you.
Listen, listen to me Jack...
I'm trying to help you...
I can't let you stay here
at this level...
and my programming
won't allow me to go with you.
Find your son...
Wake up. Wake up, Jack.
Wake up, Jack.
Wake up.
Hey you're messin'
around with my girl friend!
Come here.
Lets go, Jack.
I wanna see you get
out a this one, Jack.
Dad how did you...
-What's wrong?
-You're what's wrong.
You deliberately disobeyed me...
And this is what happens!
I'm sorry... I didn't mean
for all this to happen...
Don't apologize...
You've always been a loser and
it's your fault your mother's dead...
I'm sorry.
Now that she's gone...
I don't have to put up
with you any more.
-Dad don't leave please
-Don't touch me...
you disgust me.
Get outta my sight.
Shut up.
What did you say?
I said shut up.
That's no way to talk to your...
daddy...
You're not my father...
my father loves me
and so did my mother.
Go to hell!
Brad.
-What are you doin'?
-Get off of me.
Brad what are you
doing it's me?
Dad?
Are you alright?
Yeah.
I am now...
I love you, son.
I think they found each other.
We've got to get to the last level.
So we can get out of here.
What are we supposed to do?
Andrew Dean.
Doctor Tanaka here,
look I need your help.
You've played the game more
than anyone else...
can you tell me if there's a pattern
in the path to the last level?
Well you know the path
to the last portal is randomized...
but I've seen a pattern that depends
on the skill level of the player...
if he's any good it will
be the middle path.
Is there a problem doc?
I hope not,
I hope not Dean...
thank you very much, bye.
-We're back on level 1...
-What's going on...
Granpa.
Brad.
-Jack.
-What's going on?
The game ends
where it begins...
and now you must find the correct
path to get to the last level.
Which one?
I'm not sure, son.
The virus has corrupted
the game and...
I believe that...
You should take the middle path.
I don't know, dad,
I think it's this one...
Gotta go with my gut
on this one dad...
Let's try your way then.
I picked the wrong porthole...
we're never gonna
get outta here alive.
Don't give up on me Brad...
We're gonna get outta here and
we're gonna do it together.
Just like mom. It's all
my fault she died!
It was not your fault.
A man with a knife
killed your mom...
not you.
We have to live up
to what she wanted for us...
which means we have
to get out of here!
How we gonna get out?
I've got an idea.
-Come on Brad...
-I can't do it!
They're not real...
Come on...
-They won't hurt you!
-I can't!
You can do it Brad
they're not real...
Don't be afraid...
I can't do it!
They won't hurt you trust me.
We're running out of time,
we've got to go now.
Do it Brad, do it.
How do you know
they weren't real?
I didn't but remember
what granpasaid...
things here aren't always
what they seem to be...
Sometimes in life son... The biggest
obstacles are just in your mind.
Let's go!
I guess granpawas right.
Yeah, I guess sometimes the old guy
knows what he's talking about.
One more fight and
we're out of here...
everything's going
to be all right Brad.
I'll take the guys on the left...
That portal's gotta be
here some place, son...
Dad, wait...
I think it's over here...
Wait here...
I'm going with you!
I've got to do this alone...
I'm not lettin' you
go by yourself...
we're family...
that's why ya gotta trust me, son!
What's happening?
Dad!
Where do you think you're going?
You destroy my world,
now I'll destroy yours...
Jack.
Come on, Jack I thought
you had more than that!
Wanna go another round?
This might be interesting
after all...
Dad!
Brad I told you to wait for me...
You gotta trust me too dad...
Consider yourself ungrounded.
Let's go home, dad...
The porthole is opening.
Brad!
-I'm so happy you made it.
-What about Jack?
-Jack?
-Dad?
You're not finished yet...
Oh, my god.
Jack is left behind...
Your time is up Jack. Your life is mine.
-Transport him back professor...
-I'm trying.
-I can't stop it...
-I'm going back in after him...
No, Brad you can't. Pease, don't...
Dad, don't give up.
I need you
I am the virus.
I needed a worthy opponent...
so I used your love
for the boy to bring you here!
I will destroy this world
and then yours...
What's a matter, Jack.
You lose your nerve?
Back up power supply
shutting down.
-We're out of time
-Dad, I need you.
I don't want to lose you too.
I love you.
Ilove you. Ilove you.
Dad, Dad...
I don't need this to finish you.
Dad.
I thought you were the virus...
I was wrong.
Jack...
Oh I'm glad you're safe.
How did you get here?
I've learned to overcome
my programming.
What's wrong?
You must use my energy
to open up the portal...
to your world...
What do you mean?
It's over. He's gone.
Professor, professor.
He's alive,
Brad take the visor off.
Brad.
Dad!
I'm so happy. Thank god.
Jack, this is Sally.
Hi.
Block punch.
Ooooh, excuse me guys...
Stop guys.
Whose is this?
Excuse me.
Break. Class, this way.
Sometimes life's greatest
obstacles are just in our minds.
If I put a two by four on
the ground here and...
stretched it across the class, asked
you who wants to run across it...
How many of you would do it?
Okay, very good. Very good.
If I take the same two by
four and I put it on top of...
two one hundred-story skyscrapers
And now I say who wants
to run across it...
how many of you would get on
there and run across that board?
Not even you?
Well the reason is...
when you concentrate
on the negative result...
of making a mistake, you can't
put one foot in front of the other.
It becomes almost impossible.
The easiest thing is walking.
So that lesson that you
learn from this is this.
Life's greatest obstacles many times
are just, just in our minds...
and if you concentrate and put
one foot in front of the other...
soon you can overcome
any obstacle.
One foot in front of the other.
Don't even think about falling,
but getting to the other side.
Everybody understand?
Okay, back to training.
Back to the workout.
Sifu...
Got room for one more?
And your winner in junior
black belt forms...
Brad Tanaka.
Does anybody
else want to play?