Each guest
Today ratio wu from Shanghai ocean
company total meeting of four representatives
HUO an AN of the challenge
jinwu gymnastics meeting
A ratio wu rule
Fall flop with an among those
squares
Or signal hint to admit defeat
for victory or defeat standard
Beginning
Good
The teacher beat good
Today the last ratio wu
ls from Japan nine the peaceful in inside
in farmland that ghost absolute beings flow
To HUO an AN of the Chinese
jinwu gymnastics meeting
Young master young master
Walk quickly to walk quickly
Stop
Very courageous son
Who let what you come in
l am to come to give the dad
the tea of
How much times did l say
Can't come in the here
Return to practice the word
quickly
Continue
Hum each time is l practice
the word for you
Your dad if know
Beatvatoing death not you
can't hum
You do not say that l do not say
Who will know
l take you to see the kind
thing leaves
The agriculturejinshu hurries
Come
The oh how beat the top again
Beat the to walk quickly
to walk quickly
ls from the boon of HUO
of the HUO house hed today
And the Chao inside of the
Chao house hed is strong
On the platform a definitely
superiority
Good good
You two are why
Seek the dead
l see today of your dad is
to lost to settle
My dad will let your dad tasting
Our HUO house hed of severe
You wait and see
The life and death form has signed
Victory or defeat at person
Life and death on day
Two teachers game beginning
Chao your dad this descended
to taste at last
Our HUO house hed of severe
The of today is a v-
The Chao inside is strong
Thanked to thank
An AN an A
Rain pain
Rlease
An A we leave
Return with me an A v-
You is not stilljust now
pretty gutty
Now how grow and then do not
resemble the rat similar
Hide at disappear the person
below stand up
Chao you do not be has gone
too far in insult
Shut me the top to the mouth
You are a dullard
You HUO house hed is also
a dullard
Grow and then come out to have
a competition with me
l let you also tasting our Chao
house hed severe
Appear on stage
An A do not beat
Do not beat
Ah won to win
You accepted our Chao house
hed at last today
Do not say again later on
with me what HUO house hed
l won me to win
An A v-
An A you get up
We leave
l swear
HUO an A can'ts allow again
the anyone to knock down me here
Young master you
l wipe you to order the medicine
Come to
You are first out
ls
How got angry
The dad of does not let me
practice the wu why
Your dad that is painful you
You harm the short wind naturally
The body is weak to can not
stand to do exercises in gymnastics
Rracticing the wu is not
can then strong body ?
You like to practice the wu so
Be for the sake of strong body
Rractice the hed l want
to revenge
l want to let the Chao know
our HUO house hed severe!
Child
The most severe place
in martial arts
Do not knock down other people
But want the gram to love
to excel the heart ownly
Anyway kind andjustice morals can't
Rracticing the wu is for the sake
of strong body for helping other people
ls not to call you causing
trouble more not is to use to revenge
lnterpersonal way to get along
with people
To know to respect other people
treat kindly the others
Then can get other people
esteem highly
Who practicing the wu practice
good to dare to do not respect
Other people fears you
Follows to esteem highly you
are a different thing
Come at once good like write
Otherwise the dad beats
you again
H'm
l win
Flew to fly
Dropped down to drop down
Drop to do not come down the v-
l bump you down
Drop to do not come down
Drop to do not come down the v-
You come again
l drop to do not come down
You act to be quick the son
Alas!
Beware of
early
An A
You forgot to drink the
medicine again this morning
l after fly the strong body
inwu
This asthma early not hair
The young lady is slowly
Your lo this child
Have no to all let you ising
out of order to since the childhood
You also should re-marry a waits on
Let the person take care of
her for good good tube
l now in
Develop the prestige of
the house of we HUO
l want to let the door of
inside the no man do not know
The no man is not the
Where attend to ascend
to re-marry
You can not catch the dad of v-
l want to beat the with you
These years you although
did not be vanquished
Can the biggest opponent
is your oneself
You are real to to win of
Toojust you oneself
Know
Challenge
Young master v-
ls
your
Dad
The your hed in that year is not
enough quickly notter enough and malicious
However you trust me at
The HUO house hed is by no
means again under charge in others
The life and death is definitely
l will attain the family status
of certainly a
Dad
The son of
Give mine
Give me
Do not give
That you howjust give me
Waiting the dad wins the
platform me tojust send the dad
TRUE
Rulling the hook is to settles
The lo of HUO your
Big inHUO
HUO an A you the time is
the family status of a
l do not know that you say
On today on today
HUOv-
Chao
So many year which do you hide
go to
My Chao is some to walk river's
south 17 provinces
38 County
Rractice good effort in whole
body
Beating river's south have no
enemy
Blow to rob to occupy
Youjust brag
The life and death form has
signed
Game beginning!
Come come up
How
Fear
Come up come up to fall dead you
You wait for
The teacher was too the stick
My the horse of iron practice
motionless such as the mountain
Fall to the ground voice
l must win yourHUO house
hed today
Good l give you an opportunity
Lose
Good good
Cat claw
Tiger claw
Descend to go to
Cat claw
Tiger claw
You lost
Carefully which
Teacher
Teacher teacher
Have no matter have no matter
Have no matter like this and all
Do not touch my teacher
HUO an A
The good teacher was too
the stick
Rolite and polite
Congratulations congratulations
Come to come to come
The big inHUO beat good
Upstairs of HUO stay you
the seat
Very good v-
An A
jinshu
Howjust come
The old place walks
HUO congratulations HUO
congratulations
Congratulations HUO
Everybody's good everybody
is good
Come to full top
jinshu
You month in this floor can
more and more red fire
That is all the to give the
friend to still manage to pool
Remember the childhood days
The book of your whole body
is angry
Who would have thought that does to rise now
business to clear and convincing presentation
Alas this morals of the world
is not the
That elephant l study the person
like this
lf do not do business
l have no another exit right
An AN eat quickly
Spending my not a few efforts assembles the
mother of the north every locality in south
Taste the flavor tunnel
Come to come to come to v-
HUO you please
This is what where come
Under the next HUO at the
is big to living
Rleading the HUO be accepted
the disciple accepts for disciple
Teach the skill in martial
arts
Go through fire and water
regardless the sacrifice
lt is good to resemble a man
Top wine
Drinking this glass wine is
a brothers
Fuck
Big inHUO in congratulations
Thank teacher
So happy today
All debts records at me
good good
Come to eat
The son of do not wait
To sleep
Come to take the young lady
return to building
The young lady returns to
building to sleep
The good little boy obeyed
to to sleep
Come to v-
This is what flavor
This call coffee western thing
Drink not
Hour the easy moves the
chaotic in power
The common people wants to
self-renewal
That must study orders the
thing of other people's forerunner
Resembling me to learn like this
text can't think only of to make money
Learn the wu of
Too can't remember to beat
the platform
The national affairs is heavy
The national affairs has you
the scholar to worry
l am a plain soldier to do
my the family status of a
The family status of a really
so important
AhCome to come to come
jinshu
You have always been is all to
stands in the platform top and bottom of
Stands now in the top
you feel to have different
Have what different
Under the platform
The life and death of the on
the stage did not close with you
Youjoin a crowd for fun however
But stand in this inside
You can win and can't lose
That you can need not ascend
the platform
jinshu you hear
Hear what
l what did not hear
l heard the v-
HUO you are ours hero
Good good
Liked to like too to like too
Big the world of inHUO the first
lron a
Accepted to let
Too stick teacher
Feeding do not bother so
Had to sign the life and death
form last together
All challengers all goes up
HUO an A
You the time is the family
status of a
You say
On today on today
How you is why
The wish does obeisance big in HUO as
the teacher goes through fire and water
Regardless the sacrifice
Good good good
Each is all a man
Top wine top wine
Drinking this glass wine
everybody is a brothers
Come to drink
Come to come to come to everybody
Ah! HUO congratulations
Often thank to often come come
Stay to order the face
in the teacher
Boss this is all the debt of the
HUO
Line line
Drink
Change big you do not drink to
punish you
You haven't won my adopted
father
Come to fuck
An A you have connected to
win 38 field
This the door of inside had
no your opponent any further
Wrong
Still have a
Still beat not can't
To like to be the real the
family status of a
Beat not can't
That door excluding
Capital city two wide
mountain west Hunan
You beat when is a head
These my did it everses
that you say unknown white
But l can't stop l only beat
Beat the talent proof me
stronger than other people
Rroof you are again how
An A
Should affirm on stopping
to like to like to want
This is what
This is the debt that your disciple
in this month owe with the friends
l pack
You recruit to come of is a
group of disorderly bands
There is several individual
true taking you for brothers
This river the business
on the lake
That is the sense of honor
This righteousness v-
Good
l will hit persons to send
the money past tomorrow
An A
l am not to come to seek
you want the money
Accepting the makes friends
You also should see their
personal character wu article
ls not a wine to depend
to drink big bowl
HUO you walk good
HUO early
Ah Qin's Qin's early
This is not the big inHUO to
claim to be the family status of a
How so 3G
Qin's
Be missing for a long time
l think you old already high returned
to the west of to enjoy life to go to
Come to my iron knife a for doing
obeisance teacher learning not unique
This be called to can not
but carry on
lndeed as expected is to
can not but carry on
Returned to have a big
gift for the oneself
Congratulations
Rolite
This big gift is to buys
to give yours
Help your teacher
Qin's justs come in a
justs come in
Young master
The income in the building of wu connects
to support family to all return not enough
Those discipleses on credit in
outside is again more and more
The savings of the home
Three had used up month ago
Use up
Teacher teacher
Good good usually call you good
to like to do exercises in gymnastics
The nobody hears
Who fuck of
Qin's
Teacher v-v-
Teacher
ls the day of Qin's life now
''Wish Qin's such as East
China Sea, ''
Good
Adopted father
''l wish your,such as East China
Sea life, compares the south mountain''
Good
Teacher
son you are a good good
Wishing your loose crane
postpones the year good good
Wishing your benefit life
Today of HUO is a big life
in my adopted father
The pack descended the wine
shop
You want to drink the wine
pleases change a place
Ask HUO to appreciate a face
Have no the place that you talk here
Hi
Today is a some birthday dinner
in my Qin
l do not would like to the hand
Occupy we to discuss it later
another day
You are as the elders
You do not know to shame to
harm my disciple
Today of my HUO an AN is to
comes to begs for ajustice
You think to be how
Word l have signed
Enough you sign
Want to be not you kneel down
to compensate in public is not
Let an A
The guest of Qin's is all at
You all too
Have what matter can't the
another day say again
The disciple humiliates l can't
sit on the sideline to ignore
Not l take place what matter
l disallow you the monkey business at the
time of somebody else holding birthday party
You say that l commit tomfoolery
An A
You are to fear me failed your
wine shop
My HUO an A shines on the
price indemnification
l really dare not believe you
will say such words
Calculate us so many years white
hands over a field
You bomb me to walk
So the friend of many years
You did not recognize me
The knife do not grow the eye
The owner all backs the bottom
Do not need the wound innocence
Walked to walk
To beat
The ah ah fucks what
Teacher
The teacher won
Drinking the wine has no wine
to have no to return
Drinking the wine went to
too stick
How drink the wine went to too stick
Drinking the wine went to
Too stick
Hire a car quickly to hire
a car quickly
lt is slow and slow to
beware of
Fantastic world in teacher
the first
Have another cup of the teacher
severe and severe
Without equal in strength
Surname Qin's old man is not
an opponent
He not line ah see his
that appearance
Big inHUO
Congratulate you
You now has the wish fulfilled
the family status of a
But l tell you
Two hours front
Qin's died
You the time is the family
status of a
On today
HUO an A
The family status of a
On today
Young lady house young
lady's house
Rerson l kill
The one person works the one
person is
The foster mother took good care of
You say to the teacher that you
all did what
l am sorry you are all mistake
of the pupil
Observe a festival with Qin's
ls a keep woman that l commit
adultery with Qin's previously
Qin's just the punished me
Teacher
Other brotherses in these
affairses all know
l think they will tell your
teacher
Teacher teacher teacher
Teacher
Teacher teacher
Alas! have a fever
l go to the cook orders the
medicine let him drinking
Outed to order the sweat
and then liked
This liked this and then liked
Walk
He wants to go to bed to walk
13- year old time
l start seeing the not
pure thing
Eye the gross seems a the layer
turns fog that do not open
l cried every day at that time
The mother-in-law tells me
Rublic not pleasurable must cry
Cry over you still have to
start onjourney
Can my in the mind what can
see pure
Your letter
l help you to wash
Time grew
Hair tie knot easily
Much wash smoothly clean
The mother-in-law often says
Rerson ah want to often wash
the oneself
Like this the talent walks clear
dryly in the in this world
Having no the knot is what
turn to do not open
The cow of
The cow of you can really
sleep
You are similar to our Huang
to sleep
So l call your the cow of
Come to come to come with
me come
The cow of you are awake
We grasp the butterfly of
Tomorrow
You take him to fuck to order
the agriculture to farmland live
Like
The cow of
cow cow cow
Walk to walk with me with me
Walk to hurry to come over
You see you to is all a to
fuck in the daytime
Month the aunt do not let
us saying
She is helping you to put afresh
Rice seedling too is to
have vital
They can't depend too near
Near will hinder the growth
Resemble our person
Life the inside wants to know
the mutual respect
Like this everybody the talent
is live peaceful happiness
l will remember of
The mother-in-law has a meal
Good
Mother-in-law
Month
ls the day that visit grave
in a couple of days
The goes to the graveyard
ascend and see
Your dad goes to with your
Good
The mother-in-law says that amount's
day will visit grave my father and mother
Drink to order the water
l want to follow your company
measures a matter
You wanted to walk
l want to return a trip
Also give parents top a grave
The exhausted filial piety is an
important event and should go to of
l will still come back of
You are in village so many year
l know that your one day there
will will leave here of
ln fact my v-
These change to do laundry
all the way and up
You take the top
l haven't told you that
l call what name
You need not tell me
You from where come to
want to where go to
l also do not need to know
l only know that you call
the cow of line
l call huo an A
l will remember of
Have here delicious of
Money money
The god's words is the truth
Letter the God forever get
Really true
Letter the God gets the
eternal life
His talk all here
The god's words is a v-
huo an A
The family status of a
Came back to beat the again
huo an A came back to beat
the again
Young master
Beam uncle
You come back
Good good good
l come me to come
Sorry l did not guard this
family possessions for you
Young master sorry
l have been thoughting of that
the young master come back that day
Thing here what did not change
ls really difficult for you
This is as it should be
Young master
You walked hereafter creditorses
come to make track for the every day
The thing a piece per piece
of the home all gave to take away
still say afterwards that
to take the house to mortgage
Each a thing in this the
building of can keep down
Thered is individual delivering
a pack of money luckily
Afterwards l am on cutting
and polish
Do this matter of should be an
agriculture agriculture young master
No longer needed them
l miss my dad that my is too
to does not hope to see again
these things
Father's adult
The child is not filial
Till now l amjust real
understand
That year you are on the platform
why not that is on recruiting
You isjust real the family
status of a
Mother's adult
That year you teach the truth
that me behaves in a life time
The child asininity coulds
not the realization
Stop worrying
Child l no longer be
ungrateful to you
Child
You time in a life time l did
not look after you thoroughly
Still brought trouble you
suffer the such big disaster
l am not a good father
Madam
That year in an A to Qin's
Today is to comes to faces
Qin's filial piety of
mm
Extra extra
The foreign muscle man ratio
sweeps China
Connect to win 32 field
25 teacher harms the feeling
miserably heavy
Beat the without equal in
strength hand
''He satirizes the Chinese is a''
'' east Asia disease man''
No one dares to go on stage
the challenge
l have the in you
A lot of affairs only have
in the after the event
Youjust knew mistake
Mistake get the in the mind
very painful
l do not want that lift again
the past matter
They all have ends
l really very difficult openings
But l can seek you
l hope you to borrow
l order the money
Still want to beat
again your platform
Yes
l have no your this friend
l have the necessity
to lend to your money
Young master
The boss of huo
This is my house host
to give me to give yours
Your house host is
My house host the surname
agriculture calls agriculture
Mr. ladies
Will appear today at
everybody's in front of
ls to can be then
single to overthrow a train
the one punch can
break through the Great Wall
What is a hideous mess
a little finger head can strangle
to death a Chinese the teacher of
Dying the false foreign
devil pleases
There is since then the most
strong muscle man in history
v- ratio v-
The challenger of today
huo an AN of Tienjin
Good good
Sign first the life and death form
Tell him
ls mutually thin with
the life on the platform
ls a vulgar practice that
China is in times gone by
Can we have another
a kind of tradition
Call with the member
of association of
Good good
He says that he want to teach
your at one feed mercilessly
Come
Game formality beginning
Good
Good good
The teacher beat good
Accepted to let
Thank
Good
The game was too the stick
He says that also thank you
Thank you again
Thank
Teacher someone asks you
to attend party
l am true to have never
thought is you
You return to take me for friend
lt is impossible for me tos
forgot your this friend
lmpossible
Come to sit an A
l prepared you the wine
that your favourite drink
Come
How
Quit
Quitted a lot of years
''You that year but see
the wine,such as life, ''
l is for quiting past mistake
Good
That we with tea on behalf wine
An A
You that field competes
to the people foot face
The foreigner all forced
to a top to us
The gross should have
a Chinese stands out
Be the friend
l am true to substitute
you happy
Eat the vegetables
Walk this time and when
l came and then do not
walk since
The business of the month
in that your floor
Sell
ls your business very good
You want to establish the
gymnastics meeting
Have no money you how establish
But NM6 month floor is you
life strenuous efforts
Compare with your the ambition of now
l very small business in floor
in month in that unworthy on lifting
An A
l am not the person of the
l can with this a little
humble effort
Help you successful
This according to you the contents that my
company measures the meeting that draft rules
You see the line is not line
The gymnastics of will
emphasize three teach
Teaching teaches the
teaches virtuous
Martial arts is door to
teach the moral culture
Have no a parties of the cent
With the exchanges enters
with each other for its essence
The sturdy build is virtuous
to have concurrently
The citizen then can develop
to self-renewal
Rrohibit with me its is added
in the body of the compatriot
no abusing martial arts ocean
row outside
Kind andjustice is this
Exert and strive without stop
Rreparation
Sir this wager notes a lot
too big
l play to do not have
l play the game that have
confidence only
So you would be interested in
perhaps with us together
Rlay on the Human body in
this so-called huo an AN a
This time he had better lose
''ratio that field can let me
compensate francs 1,000''
Have three farmland the Sir is
protecting this time you can not compensate
Can still earn perhaps a
This time l suggest huo
an A with
We these national expert handses
hold four ratios
Let they the nothing important
can blow any further
Four rightnesses a
You rely on what to think
huo an A will accept this
proposal
Self-respect reputation
These are all of no account
He hases accepted to challenge
Sir l also come to play a
But for letting you this
gambling party interesting
l buy the Chinese wins
Three farmland you guarantee
huo an A will lose
Only do according to my plan
This time we won to settle
An A
This time compare the opponent
of the center
Have a Japan the person calls
peaceful in inside in farmland
He want to be roughly you see a
l hear of
He but expert hand in the
expert hand
Learning by exchanging views with
the expert hand would have the result
An A
This time the foreigner board
of trade invites to compare
l see to have no so in brief
Otherwise can how let you
A has together the field
replies four persons
l think
They are to want to borrow the
machine let the face of we swept floor
Will let the gymnastics of did not
have a foothold in Shanghai its ground
Yes
A to four must still complete
victory
ls really inequity
But life is in a life time
Have who can guarantee the each
and every item matter all fair
For the sake of the
gymnastics of
l do not have no choice
But in case of
Following your company
measures a matter
What matter
This time after comparing the
This president of association
from you to do
Why ah
l want to take time to return to country
to see the amiable mother-in-law Sun in month
l promised of
The Sir of huo say so that the difficult
way does not understand the tea really
ls not l do not understand but
is l do not wish to understand
l do not think to divide the
tea high and low
ls a tea good
''But, this tea has high and low with
the cent of the different character''
What is high what is low
They oneself is all to grow
in the nature center
Have no the high and low cent
Look the you and really does
not understand
Otherwise of the words nature
meeting article outs high and low
The Sir's words too to
So look at me
The top and bottom of the tea
article is high and low
And is not to be come by tea
to say to me
Rour is from person to decide
The different person has the
different choice
l do not wish to do this choice
Why
Drinking the tea is a
kind of mood
lf your mood likes
Tea of high and low still
have so important
The peaceful has never thought
As Sir sees it worldly
martial arts group
Such numerous
The difficult way says too have no
what high and low top and bottom of cent
l want to is like this
So the peaceful in Sir wants to ask
Since the martial arts has
no high and low cent
Why to still compare the tournament
l think the worldly martial arts the
definite having no the high and low cent
Only the talented person of the who
there is cent as the strong or weak
Rassing to contest us can discover
With know a real oneself
Because real opponent in my
May be myself
Only there is sad tournament
then can know the real oneself
Might it not be the Sir's
meaning
The most terrible tournament
at oneself heart
The Sir's a words
Make peaceful respected
and admire very much
Today we with tea member
of association
Do not patronize to talk to
forgot to drink the tea however
Come to sample tea's flavor
Sample tea's flavor
Each guest
Today the last ratio
ls from Japan nine the peaceful in inside
in farmland that ghost absolute beings flow
To Chinesejinwu gymnastics
meeting huo an A
This is what is the row
Four beat a
You do not tell me why and
in advance
This is this board of trade with
The gymnastics ofjinwu will agree
after negotiation in advance of
You also need not make a fuss
over minor things
This where is to compare the
This is the premeditated murder
You worried needlessly
huo an AN is on the
platform ever with
The all countries martial
arts elite ratio excels
The arrangement of today
is also what he agree
Three farmland
You after all is what calculate
ls for the sake of
Japanese heavy
Still for the sake of
your own gambling party?
To me the real important
is a martial arts
The game is an in order to win
Beginning
An A
This game is unjust to you even
lf you choose to fight
again another day
l would like to
keep company with
Your good intentions
l appreciated
But since l have stood
in this on the stage
Want still result
Rlease!
The teacher was too the stick
The this time matches
the dead heat
The next time matches
for barehanded the shot of
Both parties' contestant
preparation
Three farmland which
do you ascend go to
See the appearance we
lost to settle
l arrange
Need not anxious about
An A
Rause
What is the row
What is the row farmland inside
An A
The farmland inside walk quickly
An A what's the matter with you
What's the matter with you
l poisoned the poisoned
Roison how can
ls what is the row after all
You want to be why water
Not how
Water
Water poisonous
The proof was all taken
away by them
An A walk the hospital
The teacher goes to
the hospital Okay
l carries the dint is excessive
The poison is already the
psychological attack was too late
Teacher l find they revenge
Flap voice
You wants to do of is
not to revenge
Old grudge only will
living more old grudges
l do not want to
see the old grudge
The most important is
a strong oneself
An A teacher
An A we did not beat
l take you to go to the
hospital walks
jinshu
l amjust a plain soldier
l used a lot of years to just
understand what is a martial arts
Can the student with the
martial arts
The game hasn't ended
The person can't choose the
vital beginning
But must be courageous to walk
over one-step finally
Teacher v-
What's the matter with you
Descend the heavy hand
hurriedly
You this words is what mean
You need not ask so this field
much must win
lgnoring to adopt to grow
why must win
Exert and strive without stop
Your lo is all right
Do not beat
lt is live to descend to go
to aller important than what
You hear
lt is on the hoof to have always
been all is not a business of person
Toing beat me will still overcome
with entire effort
That is my honor
He lost huo an A lost
Go to go to quickly
Go to declare the result
quickly
Wait a little while
huo
Dollar
A
An A
huo an A v-
Teacher
huo an A
Young master
An inside you this guy
Lo you fucked the amount what
l lost
Who say that you lost who say of
l know it in heart
l lose admire sincerely
to take orally
You with for yourself is who
Rely on what from make the
assertion do you go together with
Three farmland
You are true to give our
Japan shameful
huo an A v-