Welcome.
And thank you for
choosing to view
We here at Forefront Films
and Sneak Preview Entertainment
understand that some
of you may have never seen
homosexuals
engaged in any sort
of positive physical contact.
So we would like
to take a moment,
before we start,
to acclimate you.
This is a lipstick-lesbian,
so called because
of her feminine beauty,
her rose-colored lip cosmetics,
and her homosexual predilection.
And this is another
lipstick lesbian.
You see?
Nothing to be frightened of.
In fact, many heterosexual men
consider such images beautiful
and/or sexually arousing.
Now, les move onto men.
This is a gay man,
or what some in the community
might designate as a "gym queen,"
so called because of his time
spent at the local gymnasium
perfecting his musculature.
And here is another
homosexual man.
You see, just like two buddies
after a ball game.
Again,
nothing to be afraid of.
Thus ends our introduction.
We hope this has been informative
as well enlightening.
Enjoy the show.
Okay, so I'm going down on this guy.
I like him and is a million years
since I've been with anyone and,
maybe is only a month
since I've had sex,
but it seems like a million years.
Anyway, is been years since
I've been with someone I liked.
Not that I know him that well,
but he reminds me of an ex.
Anyway, he's got a great body
and there's a real
physical attraction,
so at least thas a start.
To be honest, I feel like
I could really love this guy.
Okay, so I can't remember
his name right now,
butat the time I felt like
I really, really loved him.
Or could love him.
It was intense, thas the point.
So I had been down on him
for like all of one second,
and all of a sudden he cums...
Okay, okay, so I'm thinking,
what should I do?
Should I spit it out
on his stomach?
In my hand?
On a nearby towel?
Should I swallow?
What would Miss Manners do
in this situation?
And suddenly I remember
what my friend Tara once told me.
So I was brought up to be a good,
obedient Catholic girl, who always
did what was expected.
Who knew you could spit?
Until my friends told me
I was nuts.
They ask me if I'm a spitter
or a swallower,
like there's a friggin'choice.
And then they tell me that they
spit it out all the time,
and guys don't even notice.
So, never do anythin'
you don't want to,
even if it seems rude
at the time.
Because all men, basically,
are dogs.
Some are poodles, some Dobermans,
but you're all dogs.
So that got me to thinkin',
what do straight guys do?
I asked Tara's man if straight guys
swallow when they go down on women,
and if the women notice one way
or the other.
But he was just vague.
I don't know.
Usually, they're just so stoked
that is happening,
they don't really want to ask
any questions.
So then I decided ask
my friend Megan
about lesbians but she was no help.
No, Vincey, we don't swallow.
We spit it out into Mason jars
and then examine it at our weekly
Womyn's Encounter Sessions.
Okay, so some people don't like
talking about this stuff.
But I think is important,
'cause to tell you the truth,
I don't mind swallowing.
It makes me feel closer to the guy.
Lsjust all this HIVstuff.
And I did want to prove my love
to whas his name here.
And then I started thinking about
this guy Ned and decided it was
all his fault.
One night I spent eight hours,
count 'em, 8 hours! Tryin'
to make this guy cum.
After the first hour,
it is no longer any fun.
After the second hour,
it becomes a thing of pride.
After that, is like being stuck
at an Andrew Lloyd Webber show.
You're prayin'for it to be over.
All of a sudden I just said,
Fuck it.
I'mjust gonna swallow.
This'll prove to Speedy here
that I love him
and then we'll move in together,
get a dog,
pick china patterns,
get Lakers season tickets
and live happily ever after.
So I swallowed.
And at that moment I felt love.
I really did...
For about twenty seconds,
it felt really great.
- And then this guy says,
- 'You really shouldn't have.
Ls really not considered safe."
"Nothing's a hundred percent
safe you fucking idiot!"
Thas what I wanted to scream.
Instead, I just smiled.
Thank you Dr. Jocelyn Elders
for that safe sex tidbit.
And then he says to me
he can't stay, but he had
a good time so he hopes I call.
Then he makes a big deal about
giving me his pager number,
and les get together again.
So then I rush into my bathroom
and I gargle furiously
with extra-strength
disinfectant mouthwash.
I even swallow.
Why do I always swallow?
And now I'm gonna die.
Would you stop being such
a drama queen about this?
"Hy? I never get to be
the drama queen.
Vincey, get this
through your thick skull.
Javi's the drama queen,
I'm the drama queen mother,
and you're just
a little princess.
I'm gonna die and I never
had any of my plays produced.
- You did too!
- I mean in New York.
"Naked Busboys,"
last summer?
Poughkeepsie doesn't count.
Well, so you're not dead yet.
Why don't you stop whinin'
and start writin'.
Well, at least I know now
that I am definitely over men.
This has finally made me see
that I'mjust the type of person
who doesn't mate for life:
A lone wolf,
a free bird, a Kennedy.
So I'm giving up
the illusion right now.
I am not going to waste
any more of my time
searching in vain for someone
to share my life with.
Sleeping around is dangerous.
Being in a relationship
is impossible. Men are scum.
And I want nothing more
to do with them.
Tara, guess what.
I just met the cutest guy.
So here's what happened.
- We started talking...
- Right.
One thing led to another...
- and we're having dinner Friday.
- Wait a minute.
- Friday night?
- Gym-boy's coming Friday night?
"Hat, are you nuts?
"E're going to Marix.
- Marix?
- Yeah. Javi suggested it.
No, Vincey!
"Hat about dinner with us?
- You said it was no big deal.
- No no.
Ls no big deal if you come.
If you don't come,
is a huge deal.
Why?
"Ell...
Because...
Robin and Sarina
are gonna be there.
And you know how lesbians
make Gus nervous.
Ever since he saw
"Basic Instinct"...
and that was years ago.
Okay, so, whas going on?
Nothin'.
Oh, really?
I'm not supposed to tell you.
But you're going to, right?
Okay, but you have to swear
not to tell anybody.
- You're a tough nut to crack.
- Vincey, you have to swear.
Just swear, Vincey,
or forget it.
I swear. There, you happy?
Okay...
Javi just found out
he's HIV positive.
What?
Yeah.
My God, I was just talkin' to him.
- What are his T-cells?
- Don't make a big deal about this.
Has he started the cocktail yet?
He's fine, okay?
End of discussion.
Man.
Just let Javi tell you the way
he wants to, okay?
Just be there Friday night.
Because ill be
depressing for him
to be around his brother who's
in a good relationship with me,
and Dwight and Diego,
and Robin and Sarina and,
you know even Megan and Jared...
You have to be there to remind him
there are other Ionely,
desperate gays still around.
Well, as long
as you put it that way.
Vincey, you know
what I'm talking about.
You have a lot going for you,
but you're not in a relationship.
Yeah, well, thas all gonna
change real soon.
Oh, really, Vincey. Do tell.
What?
I don't want to discourage you
from gettin' involved,
but les be realistic.
You're a Christmas Eve type person,
you can never enjoy the presents
after they're open.
As soon as you find there's
a living, breathing person
behind the image,
you lose interest.
Ls not my fault all the guys
I date turn out to be psychopaths.
- Well, is certainly not mine.
- You know what it is?
Ls this sick culture
we're living in.
Gay men are brought up
to be liars.
Vincey,
don't start on one of your theories
'cause I'm not buyin' it.
The point is that this guy,
Buzz, seems at least
not to be a bullshitter.
Vincey, baby,
I've got a newsflash for you:
All men are bullshitters,
gay or straight.
All men?
You got a dick, you're a liar.
Ls a simple rule.
Oh, wait, not that one.
No, is fucking ugly.
Get rid of it.
I like it. Put it back.
Some poor, sick, homeless,
gay man
needs this a lot more than you.
Selfish.
- What time's dinner?
- Wait a minute!
You told Javi you had a date,
so you can't come.
- I said I'd be by for dessert.
- All right,
then, thas what you gotta do.
- Tara it doesn't...
- No, or he'll know I told you.
Stop being such a fag-hag
about this. I want to be there.
You stop being a fag,
I'll stop being a fag-hag.
Dessert. Friday night.
My house.
Ten o'clock. Period.
He knows it pisses me off
when he calls me that.
Fag-hag. I hate that.
But then again I had to
cut Vincey some slack,
'cause he'd been trapped in datin'
hell for a full year back then.
He was getting a little testy.
I don't know how two guys
ever make it work.
Ls hard enough with one penis
in a relationship, let alone two.
And then on top of that
you got all these politicians
and so-called religious rightists.
And you have those gay-bashers
on the street.
He had a lot
on his mind back then.
Then on top of that
you have the HIV,
AIDS, all that shit.
So if sometimes Vincey,
or any of my boys,
aren't as much fun
as they used to be, well,
who can really blame 'em?
I see, all I have to do
is have the right attitude.
Concentrate hard enough,
and my virus will go away?
Well, it never worked
with my ex-boyfriends,
so I doubt ill work for HIV.
I'm not sayin' that, I'm saying
right now, you're healthy.
But I feel the disease looming
over me. I don't know where,
I don't know when,
but I know is gonna happen,
like the shark in "Jaws".
You're gonna be a barrel
of laughs tomorrow night.
Excuse me, if I'm putting
a crinkle in your social calendar.
Look,
Javi, I'm sorry.
I don't pretend to know
what you're going through.
I hate the fact I can't
do anythin' to make it better.
You know I love you.
Why couldn't you have been
a gay man?
Some people suspect I am.
You know, is not getting any
easier to deal with, Tar.
Did I tell you?
I finally got the dirt on what
happened between Megan and Sarina.
Really? Do tell...
- Okay, but swear to tell nobody.
- I swear.
Cross your heart and
hope to... whoops.
Ljust knew something was off.
I could feel it in her embrace.
I wasn't saying anything, yet.
Because I am an African
American,
Lesbian Woman
I have strength.
I have resolve.
And ways of tricking two-timing
bitches into telling me the truth.
Megan?
I know you had an affair
while you were gone,
so don't deny it.
I want you to tell me about it,
and why it happened.
I promise I will not get mad.
I don't know what you're saying.
Ls very, very important for you
to tell me everything.
I...
Okay, how did you know?
I wasn't certain.
Not until you just said that.
Damn, worse than my mother.
Megan, please tell me.
- I'm so sorry, Sari. I swear...
- Don't swear, please.
Just tell me.
Is it someone I know?
Someone from the company?
- I don't know what to tell you.
- Try the truth.
- Sari...
- Please,
just tell me.
Okay.
Then, yes,
is someone that you know,
and yes, is someone
from the company.
Younger or older?
Older.
Is she pretty?
Well, no.
But thas because...
well...
ls a guy.
Awhat?
A man?
"Ith a penis?
You want the truth?
I'm telling you.
Ls Jared.
Jared?
- Jared my cousin?
- Your second cousin by marriage.
You mean the same Jared
that moved in
with us because
he lost his job?
"Ho I got a job? Who I got
an interview at your company?
Is this the same Jared?
Sort of ironic, really, isn't it?
Oh my God, this has to be
some kind of sick joke.
He feels really bad about it.
He's gonna feel really bad,
I get my hands on him.
Come on, Sari, les face it.
The spark went out
between us long ago.
I can't believe you're saying this.
I can't believe you're sleeping
with my cousin.
Sarina, we haven't had good sex
since Martina won "imbledon.
The passion is gone, Sari.
"E're going through a dry stretch,
thas all.
The tide'll come back
if you just give it a chance.
Sari, there is no tide.
The lake has dried up.
That is a lesbian death bed.
Oh, no is not!
Because that would mean
both of us are lesbians.
And you, apparently,
are no lesbian!
I'm as much a lesbian as...
As who? As Jared?
So how do you feel?
Feel like a real woman now?
Stop it! Please!
You promised you wouldn't get mad.
And you promised you'd love
and be faithful to me!
I know.
And I do love you, Sarina.
But I don't have anything inside
for you anymore.
Not sexual, anyway.
- Les cut our losses now, while...
- Great idea.
Good idea. Move onto
the next business transaction!
The next deal!
The next client!
Les not be drama queens.
We're dykes, not fags.
Why keep referring to yourself
as a lesbian?
Did Jared have a sex change
and not tell anyone about it?
You can have Mr. Mittens.
I don't want him.
I never liked that cat.
- Now the truth comes out.
- I love that cat! He's my cat!
Oh, baby girl.
I'm sorry.
You want me to go over and beat
the crap out of her? I'll do it.
I want you to go beat
the crap out of him.
Nah, he'd probably like it
too much.
You know how perverted them
straight guys are.
In fact, he probably
lured her, using drugs
or something.
They always recruit people into
their sicko straight lifestyle.
You're right.
Maybe he tricked her, I...
Hello. I'm kidding.
Nobody lures Ms. Megan into
something she doesn't want to do.
Besides, I gotta tell you,
I always had my doubts
- about that lady.
- What?
You suspected Megan was straight
and never said anything to me?
And say "Sarina, I think your
girlfriend wishes you had a dick."?
You just never liked her.
Ever since she dropped out of your
stupid Friday night poker game.
No,
don't get defensive with me, girl.
I'm on your side.
Megan tipped out on you to sit on
some guy's overgrown clit.
So don't even try.
I'm sorry.
Babe I'm sorry.
"Ant to go rollerblading?
Want to go on the
new Superman ride?
Want to rent bad porno movies
and see if we recognise anyone?
Shut up!
Now, what I wanted to say was,
"Drop the bitch like a bad piece
of meat and jump in my bed!"
As you probably guessed,
I had a huge crush on Sarina
ever since the first moment
I looked at that pretty face.
But she was with Megan
and they were in love and had been
together for like a hundred years.
So I just kept
a little half step back.
Besides, girlie-girls like Sarina
don't go for sporty gals like me,
despite what they tell you
in the dykey-dyke press.
Ls all scandalous lies.
So I just tried to hug her
like an older brother
and tried not to get my hard-on.
I feel so guilty.
I know. So do I.
Les call Sarina up and ask her
to join us in a three-way.
She's your cousin.
Second cousin, by marriage.
We owe her a lot. Both of us.
You don't have to sleep with her.
You were leaving her anyway,
so what difference does it
make who you're screwing?
Let me put it this way, if things
didn't work out between us,
would you mind if I fucked
your cute younger brother?
Why would I mind?
I'djust have both of you killed.
See if we had any other relatives
I could fuck.
People say I'm blunt and sarcastic.
Come on, Meg.
There's nothing you can do.
I'm sorry,
but I just can't help thinking
about her lying in bed, crying.
But I'm fertile right now.
Thas why I came home for lunch
and we did it for two hours.
But we've gotta do it
as much as possible.
These eggs aren't gettin'
any fresher.
Tara, you've got plenty
of years to have babies.
No, you've got years of sperm left.
I'm on a schedule.
Atime's-running-out-get-your-sperm
- while-the-eggs're-fresh schedule.
Tara, at this particular moment,
I'm spermless. Gun isn't loaded.
The well is dry.
The cupboard is bare.
- Goddammit, Gus, you're Latino!
- I'm American.
"Hat good is it being a Mexican
if I can't get the sperm
I need to make my baby?
Do I ask you for much, Gus? No!
Do I ask you for jewels?
Do I ask you for furs?
Do I ask you to take me out
to a fancy restaurant?
No!
Not even to Burger King!
All I ask for is your honesty
and your sperm.
I don't even ask for your love.
If I gotta ask for that,
I don't even want it.
But I gotta have your sperm.
Especially now if you're gonna
be running off to China,
or God knows where...
- It always comes to that.
- Yeah.
How many times will we have this
argument? 10 times? A hundred?
I say, les get 'em all right
now, and get 'em over with.
"Hat are you saying?
You want to talk?
No, Tara, I want to sleep.
But I need your sperm!
Maybe I should get it from Diego
and Dwight like I planned.
If it means me gettin' sleep,
I'll help you with the
turkey baster myself.
- Did you remember to get the...
- Milk?
They only had the 2%, not the 1%.
But I got some Chardonnay to bring
over to Tara's tomorrow night.
- Will it go with...
- The calamari?
- Yeah. She's doing it in...
- Her fresh tomato pasta?
I like the way she does that.
- She uses...
- Fresh parsley.
But I think is also the market
she gets it at on Fairfax.
Everything's so fresh there.
On the way home from church
Thursday, we'll get some salmon.
For Friday's barbecue?
Perfect.
Oh wait, I'm...
There.
Jesus!
Thank you, Lord!
What are you doing?
- You need as much sperm as possible.
- What? Now?
Company's coming
in ten fucking minutes!
- They're never on time for nothing.
- No, no, no, sweety.
I'll get all messy. I don't have
time to freshen up. Stop.
Hold on a second.
Let me get horizontal so the sperm
don't all come spillin' out.
Oh, goddamn!
Thas the doorbell!
Hold your fucking horses!
We're coming!
Get off! Get off!
Hold on! Hold on!
Coming!
In the kitchen?
Very Jack Nicholson,
Jessica Lange of you two.
I knew this was gonna happen.
Hey, Sarina.
You did not just say, "Hi, Sarina."
He said, "Hello, Sarina.
How you doing?"
Hello.
You've been doing well, I hear.
- You look nice tonight, Sari.
- Oh, Megan, please.
I was saying it as a friend.
If we're friends, shouldn't we be
able to say friendly things?
Moi?
No. You don't want
to know what I think.
The only reason I came tonight
was because, you know why.
I want to remain friendly,
but I don't want to be friends.
So les not get carried away.
Look, I know I wasn't as honest
as I coulïve been, but...
Megan, please, les not turn
tonight into the Oprah show.
- Hey, you guys.
- Oh, they're here. Some friends!
Food! Food! I hear food!
Hey, everyone!
You look great!
Looking terribly buff there.
- Have you been working out?
- Yeah, you're bulking up there.
God, you're all here at once!
What did y'all do, van-pool?
"E decided to try to be
on time for a change.
Well, come on in, girlfriends.
'Cause the first course is mud pie.
The dirt will be flung tonight.
Tara, a gay man trapped
in a woman's body.
I am so sorry about Marix.
I always forget how crowded
that place gets.
Not that I go there all
that much, or anything like that,
is just that since
I don't get out much,
- I forget people go out Fridays.
- Vincey, is okay, man.
- You think?
- Sure...
So, you don't go out
that much, man?
- Good-Iooking guy like you?
- I go out. Just not with men.
On dates.
So, is been a while since
your last serious boyfriend, huh?
Yeah, the last time
was in college.
That didn't count 'cause he
didn't know he was my boyfriend.
One of them, huh?
Yeah, we've all been there.
Hello, thank you.
How come you're still single?
Me, now, I've got a real excuse.
Oh, yeah?
And just what might that be?
Dead boyfriend.
Oh, jeez, I'm sorry.
Ls cool, man.
Ls been a while,
so I'm just getting back
into this whole
dating thing again.
Yeah, well, welcome to hell.
- Tell me about it, man.
- You know, my friend Tara,
says she can't see how two guys
ever figure out the dating thing.
'Cause, like, with straights,
everything's much clearer.
Like with sex, did you know that
unless there's vaginal intercourse,
- is not considered real sex?
- Really?
Handjob, not sex.
Blowjob, not sex.
If a guy goes down on a woman,
a miracle, not sex...
Now, you see, I say, if I cum
and I'm not alone in the room,
then is sex.
It all gets kind of complicated.
Yeah, and then you got AIDS
on top of everything else.
Yeah, but AIDS doesn't really exist,
so that doesn't count.
Excuse me?
AIDS doesn't really exist, man.
Come on, not really.
Ls just a construct.
Ls another way of labelling
sexuality as a disease.
Look,
I don't know why Vincey brought him
but I'll just ask him to leave.
You don't have to reveal your HIV
status to some shmo off the street.
Screw it. I'm tired of
this whole psycho-drama anyway.
Javi?
Listen, everyone.
Since there's no gracious way of
saying this, I'll just say it.
I recently found out that
I'm HIV positive.
And, well, I wanted you
to hear it from me
instead of whispers behind my back
like Bette Davis in Dark Victory.
Does anyone want dessert?
You already knew. Didn't you?
We also have ice cream
if anyone would like it.
You told them. Didn't you?
How am I gonna keep something
like that private, Javi?
- You didn't tell me.
- I told you guys to act surprised.
Look, the important
- thing is that we're here for you.
- Lf you ever need anything...
I'm not sick yet.
- You didn't tell me.
- He's telling you now.
- You haven't told Mommy and Daddy?
- And what if I did?
They're gonna find out sooner
or later.
If I'd gotten a "respectable"
disease like cancer,
I would have told them,
wouldn't you?
Excuse me, but AIDS isn't
a disease. Ls a syndrome.
You know, acquired
Immune Deficiency Syndrome.
Javi, if we're not saying the
things we should be saying
is because
we don't know what to say.
No, don't feel bad for me.
I knew this was eventually
gonna happen,
and in a sense, I'm relieved.
I don't have to dodge
the bullets anymore.
I'm one of the walking wounded,
like Vanessa Redgrave in "Julia".
I mean, I'm not dying.
At least not yet.
Look, we don't have to harp on
the subject all evening long.
Look, let me tell you something.
When I went for my test results,
in the lobby there was this
really gross Ozzie and Harriet,
West Hollywood type couple
that we all hate.
Like you two, but without your
charm or grace or intelligence
or genuine human warmth.
I smiled at them, you know,
to wish them luck,
but they looked back at me
as if just glimpsing
my way would infect them.
And I didn't even know
I was HIVpositive yet.
I took it as a bad omen.
When they came out, of course they
turned out to be HIVnegative.
As they ran to live
an AIDS-free life together,
I thought...
Anne Rice is so right:
God does kill indiscriminately.
Life is so unfair.
And thas when it happened.
Believe it or not, they both got
hit by a Metro bus.
Not hard to believe if you'vee
seen the way they drive.
Those two beautiful,
HIVnegative bodies lay
bloodied and mangled
in the middle of the street.
And I thought, how wonderful!
Life is unfair for everyone.
And even if is not,
who cares?
Your time is up
when your time is up.
- HIVor no HIV.
- Exactly.
Besides, is not like HIV has
anything to do with AIDS.
Look, Javi,
I don't know you, but I suggest
you seriously look into
what we know about HIV
before you start taking
- any so-called medical treatments.
- Are you saying
that HIV doesn't cause AIDS?
- Have you seen conclusive evidence?
- Excuse me,
but every medical expert,
the CDC, the NIH...
We carry around dozens of
harmless little retroviruses
in our system,
and HIV is no different,
not in its makeup,
not in its RNA...
Don't go there. This lunatic theory
is so old and so disproven...
Drugs, unchecked syphilis,
hepatitis.
Cancer, malnutrition, hell, AZT.
All these things cause the
immune system to break down.
How can you say that? People were
not this sick in the seventies.
Remember those first cases were
guys who took ten drugs a night?
- Poppers, screwed anything.
- I have a good idea, Buzz,
just blame the victims.
When you mess with your body,
you get sick from a thousand things.
But the medical community lumps
them together and calls it AIDS.
Now they're all saying you have to
have a co-agent with the HIV.
Now tell me,
thas sort of like admitting
that HIV doesn't cause AIDS.
"Rong. It just means things
aren't so simplistic.
Look at the common cold. No cure
doesn't mean it doesn't exist.
We're not sure is appropriate
to have this conversation now.
No, I disagree.
Right now is the time
you should have this conversation,
before your friend does
something stupid
like taking AZT
or one of these protease cocktails,
and winds up killing himself.
Now, wait just
one darn moment there, Buzz.
Protease inhibitors have performed
miracles in combination therapies.
Yeah,
on white, A-list homosexuals
who can afford the medication.
We know nothing about the
side effects, the long-term...
Buzz, honey,
You don't get the point so let me
state it clearly and succinctly.
Shut the fuck up!
- We're not interested!
- Tara!
Don't you "Tara" me.
I can't believe you bring this
wackadoodle to ruin my dinner party.
AIDS is the biggest tragedy
of the twentieth century.
Even Madonna said so.
Wait,
wait.
I'm sorry.
All I'm saying is that gay men
are being used as guinea pigs.
Both Dwight and I know
what you're saying.
Fact: HIV has not been proven
to cause AIDS.
- Only a correlation has-
- ls not fair to offer false hope.
- Javi is very vulnerable right now...
- Diego,
please.
I am not Marlee Matlin
from "Children of a Lesser God."
And I can speak for myself,
- and I want to hear this.
- You neglect to mention the
University of Pennsylvania...
study that shows how HIV
does cause its damage.
Could we maybe talk
about something else,
please?
Hear about those two gay guys
who got the crap beat out of 'em
just five blocks from here?
Vincey tells me you're
an ex-artist, Buzz.
Your last name isn't "agner, is it?
Yes.
Oh my God! You're Buzz "agner!
This man's a genius!
Just encourage him.
Maybe he'll talk more.
No, I saw one of your shows
at the Fergimont Station.
Why did you stop painting?
Ls a long and not very
interesting story.
So what is this,
payback for me tellin'
you not to come for dinner?
Look, I know it sounds crazy
at first,
but we had this great,
long conversation over dinner.
Let me ask a favour of you.
The next time I go to my doctor's
office, would you come with me?
I want to find out what I can
about this and I get intimidated.
Especially when I start to bring up
alternative theories or treatments,
he turns into Nurse Ratched from
"One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest".
Okay, I'll tell you what.
I'll make you a deal.
You model for some paintings,
and I'll go to the doctor with you.
But if you just listen to him,
he makes a lot of sense.
And he hasn't even gotten
into his whole adjacent theory
about how AIDS
is just like Vietnam
in the sense that some early
mistakes were made,
but we sacrifice blood 'cause we
can't admit the young died in vain.
Just what the world needs.
Another theory freak like yourself.
- I thought you and Vincey were...
- Wait, Javi, time.
Look, I'm just asking you
to model thas all.
Besides, I think Vincey and I
know that this is not a date.
- Why would he bring me here?
- To ruin Tara's party?
You don't really think
I ruined her...?
Oh, man, I really get adamant
in my beliefs and...
You really care about this guy,
don't you?
And is great to be out
with somebody whose that sexy
and also has ideas about things.
He is a cutie-pie.
I think everything I'm saying
has a certain amount of merit.
- Don't you?
- Sure.
- Vincey thinks there's more...
- Wait, wait.
I'm sure Vincey's
a real nice guy, right?
But there is absolutely no
romantic spark between us.
But I tell you what.
I'd love to paint you.
Even if you decide you don't want
to do that, I'll go to the doctor
with you anyway, all right?
Okay.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Oh, Vincey, man, thank you.
Thank you for hooking me up
with Javi, man.
And I'm gonna wind up painting him.
Thanks again.
What?
Fuck him.
Yeah,
I wish.
Buzz,
you got Javi a little excited
about this whole HIV business.
So I'd like to ask you something.
- I normally wouldn't ask, but...
- But what?
You want to know if I'm
HIV positive, right?
Yeah, I'd like to know.
As a matter of fact, no.
I don't have it. I'm negative.
Bye.
Don't you think is unfair for
you to be talking all this talk?
Because ultimately, is not
your life on the line, Buzz.
You could be wrong,
and go on living your life.
- Misinformation could cost his life.
- Yes.
You're absolutely right.
It is a big ass responsibility,
and I could be wrong.
But let me ask you a question...
what if I'm right?
What if HIV doesn't kill
T-cells and your friend starts
taking protease inhibitors
and dies?
Who's gonna be responsible then?
You?
I think there's been
enough death
and suffering for everybody to take
a little piece of blame, don't you?
And on that cheery note,
I want to remind y'all,
regarding Javi's condition you
have to swear not to say anythin'.
Good night, Spalding Gray,
is been really nice
having a conversation with you.
My God, where does Vincey
find these guys?
Okay, sugar-dumpling,
tell Auntie Miriam
what the problem is.
Oh, I know.
I bet is that, I'm not in
a relationship thing again, huh?
Look, here it is again.
These gay-bashers
are all whining about how they
in fact are the real victims.
That the only reason
they killed those gay guys
is because the gay guys put the
moves on them. Give me a break.
What makes every straight guy think
all these queers are after them?
Well darling,
you may not know this,
but I'm often mistaken
for being straight.
You don't know what is
like being pursued
by all those gorgeous homos
all over town.
I mean is like a living hell.
You couldn't begin to imagine.
Ls not funny, Mike.
Yes it is.
No, is not.
Nothing ever changes.
The cops never even looked for the
fuckers who beat me up in college.
It seems like is
still all the same.
You know, darling, that kind
of violence
has been around since time began.
I was there.
I really am that old.
Okay, now tell Aunt Miriam
what the problem is.
I mean, I don't mean this
as a put down,
but you've come this far
without a boyfriend,
Maybe you should
examine that.
I've just been unlucky.
I mean there's nothing wrong
with a person going
through life single.
Lots of people do it,
and they love it.
It doesn't mean they're Ionely
or damaged goods
or anything like that.
Please, we don't have to mimic
heterosexual coupling patterns.
"Hat radical homo group
are you with this week?
Now don't take that tone
of voice with me, young lady.
Where's it say that two men have to
settle down and register.
I just don't understand, Mike.
I'm sorry.
I'm tired of kissing strangers.
I don't know
if I can do it anymore.
I know where you're coming
from with that.
I really do.
So what are you saying?
I'm saying that I'm sick tired
of hanging out with your fiends.
- What?
- Of hanging out with your friends.
- You mean, like your brother?
- We're together because of him.
Thas not what I mean.
You mean you're tired of hangin'
out with faggots and dykes.
- That sounds too fucked up.
- Gus, is a fucked up world, okay?
- We just gotta live in it.
- We don't have to live here.
I have to live here.
My job is here.
My life is here. My friends.
And your brother who has HIV.
Weren't you listening to Buzz?
HIV's got nothing to do with AIDS.
- Everyone knows that.
- He could be right.
Or a lunatic. Thas my point.
I can't friggin' tell anymore.
So, why don't you just run off
to China then?
"Hy don't you run off
to Mongolia or Russia?
I'm sure life is simpler
anywhere but here.
- Why do you treat me this way?
- Oh, fuck off!
She's pissed 'cause if I do go,
she won't get that baby.
You see, thas
what I like about Megan.
- She's not into that baby crap.
- Newsflash, hombre: All chicks
want babies. And they'll say
or do anything to get 'em.
- All chicks?
- Yeah, you got a uterus,
you're a fucking liar, man.
Ls a simple rule.
Sojust go on your trip.
Who's stopping you?
Tara. My brother.
Tara's a good thing.
I'd be stupid to walk away.
She is a total pop'n fresh.
Not that I'd ever,
that she'd ever...
Besides,
me and Megan are strong.
Real strong.
I just meant, you know...
Tara, she's a nice-Iooking lady.
There's a lot to be said for that.
And then there's
that shit with my brother.
How could he let himself get
fucked up like that, man?
"Ith that HIVand shit? You know
how my parents are gonna react?
They're gonna get heartburn?
No, they're gonna fuckin' die.
Everybody fucking dies, man.
Your parents don't have to live
with the shit Javi's gonna get.
And neither do you.
So, what are you sayin'?
If it were my brother, I'd make
sure he knew I was there for him.
Yeah, well, Javi already
knows that shit.
Oh, he does? All right, then.
Just take your fucking shot, man.
- So, you think is bullshit?
- I don't know. Javi's
at the doctor's right now.
My question is,
how are you about all this?
Dwight, be careful, baby,
thas heavy...
I know you were really hopeful
about the relation.
Look, Sarina, I talked to Javi.
And I told him, "Go for it."
I still don't see it.
I know the world has been
populated by strange couples,
Sonny and Cher, Fred and Ethel,
Bert and Ernie...
But if is going okay for them,
then I say go for it, you know...
But what is up with you
and Robin?
- Yeah, whas up with that?
- We're great.
And thas why you're moving out?
I need my own apartment.
I've cluttered up this place.
Why not get a two bedroom?
Robin's wanted to move for years.
I've never lived on my own.
I went from home
to college to Megan.
I need to try this.
Living alone's not that great,
Sarina.
There's no one to blame
if the bathroom's dirty.
Thas it,
you work on her, Vincey.
- Think of the money you'd save.
- You would save money.
Can I have this?
Can I have it?
No.
I don't want to rush into anything
this time.
You think you love her?
I don't know.
She's great.
She's supportive.
She gives me my space,
though she'd prefer that space
to be in the same apartment.
- We have good times. I just...
- But?
But I don't know.
I don't know anymore.
Yeah, I know. I hear you.
But believe me,
love is hard for everyone.
I hate them.
Thas my ex, David.
Is that gonna be me soon?
Don't have to be.
You got that right.
So, are you going
to want me naked or what?
For... for what exactly?
Anything.
Anything?
What do you say,
that we just start
with the painting?
Right...
Sounds good to me.
So why did you really
stop painting?
You know, same old shit, man.
I had a great lover.
He was positive.
I'm negative.
We thought AZT
was a good idea.
He gets sick.
I take care of him.
And he dies.
And I try to get back
into art scene again.
But by then nobody's interested
in my shit anymore.
So I say fuck it.
I'll go into teaching.
You know, less hassle.
Less stress.
And now you're ready
to take up the cause again.
This time with me.
Look,
I thought we just agreed
that we were going
to take this slowly.
Okay.
Yes.
- It starts 8 o'clock tomorrow.
- We don't want you to pray.
Just Kool-Aid.
I'm busy!
There're gonna be a lot of single,
interesting guys there.
- Right, guys we know from church.
- I'm so not interested.
We both feel awful
about Javi and Buzz
- and you and what happened...
- Why? I'm got dumped.
You shouldn't be so
self-defeatist about it.
You have to have a better attitude.
Would you just relax,
I'm just cleaning crevices.
But if you keep annoying me...
We just know a few guys
you might get along with.
You know what, you guys,
I know you mean well,
but the worlïs different for me
than for people who look like you.
Things come so easily to you guys,
you just have no idea.
That is just so not true.
First of all, you are just
as good-Iooking as Diego or I.
To some people.
- To others you're better looking.
- Yeah, you got the whole writer,
artsy, goatee thing happening.
Very attractive.
Exactly. Mechanic. Everything.
On top of that, you have
to remember that Diego and I
have our ups and downs
just like anybody else.
The difference is we work
at our relationship, Vincey.
Oh, really?
When was the last time you two
had a fight?
- This morning.
- Right, it was just this morning.
I wanted to make pancakes
for breakfast.
I hadn't cooked in a while,
so I wanted to cook.
Except, I cannot make pancakes,
so I figured
I'd make omelets instead.
In the end, we compromised
and we went out for breakfast.
We went out for breakfast.
Rooty-tooty-fresh-and-fruity.
- I can still taste it.
- Oh, it was so good.
Vincey?
- Come on now, stop.
- Come on.
No, I did not meet anybody,
because I was stuck talking to your
church friend the whole night.
You know, the one who dresses
Barbie dolls like the Virgin Mary,
and puts them in his window to guard
the apartment against evil spirits.
No, no, no this is not funny,
you guys,
because now I am horny
and I'm depressed,
and I might just kill somebody,
and it may be just one
of you two.
Look, I'm sorry that none
of my friends came to see you.
- Where'd they go?
- I had a good time.
I'm sure you did.
With all the girls
throwing themselves at you.
I was ready
to smack the shit out of
that green-eyed bitch
hanging all over you.
- Sister Elizabeth was friendly.
- Oh yeah, sure, right, sister.
- Is she a stripper?
- I gotta go pee.
- Vincey, now?
- Come on.
- Pee?
- What is it with you men?
Look, I want to apologize.
Sarina told me
how you felt about Buzz.
Oh, please, is no big deal.
I just got my signals crossed.
It happens all the time.
Are you sure?
Are you gonna break up with him?
What good would that do me?
If you guys are happy,
then great.
There's so much shit in this world,
if you can find something good,
I want you to have it.
Now don't pee on my leg.
Look at these cocksuckers.
Rise and shine boys!
Where you going', baby?
Hey, faggot,
ever get a bat shoved
up your ass?
Fore!
Oh, thas gonna leave a mark.
You gonna take out your wallet,
or are we gonna have to knock
your fuckin' teeth out first?
- Suck us off better.
- Yes!
Hey, I bet you take it up
the ass real nice, fag-boy.
Yeah,
yeah, like that.
- Dude, beer bottle.
- On it.
Hold still, baby.
Honors?
Help!
Help me! Help me!
Help me!
Now baby, you gotta relax.
Or this isn't gonna be pleasant
for you.
You get away from him!
Get away from him!
Motherfuckers!
Motherfucker!
You want to fight?
Vincey!
"Hat about you, huh?
Don't fucking come near me.
Stay the fuck away from me.
This fucker was about to shove
a beer bottle up my ass.
All right man,
just fucking let him go, okay.
- Where are your buddies now?
- His friends might come back.
I don't see 'em anywhere.
Tell me you guys feel sorry
for this little shit!
Fucking let him go!
- His friends might come back!
- You gotta stay away because,
otherwise I'm gonna have
to cut his neck.
Vincey!
- Put that goddamn knife away!
- I'll cut his throat.
And then I'll be a murderer,
and you'll all be accomplices.
Tell me one court in this world
that wouldn't put us all to death.
Don't think I won't do it!
I'm sorry.
- Oh, yeah?
- What are you sorry for exactly?
Are you sorry for getting caught?
Are you sorry for taking
my wallet?
Stop it right now.
- Let him go, Vincey.
- Sorry for getting it up the ass
while total strangers watched?
But you're the one got me
all heated up, baby.
Cute little straight boy like you,
You gotta let me get my rocks off.
Leave me alone, man!
Relax,
this is not gonna be pleasant
for you at all if you don't.
Stop it, Vincey. Stop it.
Remember who you are.
Vincey, put the knife away.
Relax!
Relax.
Ls just sex.
You see, gay boys have learned
how to relax,
so we can enjoy the secret pleasure
of being fucked over all the time.
Get the hell out of here!
Now!
Man, don't you even want
my pager number?
Don't I even get a kiss?
You're just like all the others!
You motherfucker!
Let go of me you fucking assholes!
Les get out of here, Diego.
We're sorry, Vincey. We didn't know
what they were doing.
What?
Maybe we should go to the police,
and report the whole thing.
I ain't saying shit.
Dwight, hello. I'm a fag...
who was drunk in an alleyway
and raped a straight man.
They'd put me away for life.
They got cute boys in prison.
You could finally get a boyfriend.
Vincey, what if the guy goes
and reports it?
Somehow I doubt that dickhead is
gonna go to the cops and tell them
he got it up the ass by a faggot.
Vincey's right,
- we should just drop it.
- Thank you.
Reverend Nelgood said harboring
secrets causes horrible nightmares.
You told your pastor?
"Hat are you, nuts?
Doesn't he have to report it
now or somethin'?
No, is priests who can't mention
what they hear in confession.
You guys shouldn't be
tellin' anyone.
Coming from Miss Tight Lips.
Hey, look who's talking.
We didn't do anything wrong.
- But you think I did?
- We didn't say that, okay.
Vincey, you did kind
of rape a guy.
I think the motherfucker got
off easy, personally.
If that were me, not only would I
have fucked up the motherfucker,
but I'd have shoved the bat up
his ass till it bust his skull.
- Thas what I'm saying.
- Then kick him down the street.
- This is pretty, very pretty.
- You guys aren't saying this.
Believe it. You guys are Christians.
- You believe in things, right?
- Yeah, like forgiveness.
And what exactly am I supposed
to be forgiven for?
I didn't mean that, Vincey.
Vincey, you really didn't have
to humiliate the guy like that.
Maybe you took the whole thing
a little too far.
You think maybe, what?
I shoulda let him fuck me?
- I mean, he was cute, but...
- You don't have to makejokes.
Then what do I gotta do?
Cry all day?
Go to the cops
and have them lock me up?
Go kill myself?
Look, you guys, I don't know
why I didn't run away
or how I got a hard-on,
or what I coulïve done differently,
except that what happened, happened,
and I'm glad that at least
this time, I fought back.
All right, I should shut up but,
maybe you need to talk
to a counsellor.
No, no, I can't do this anymore,
you guys.
I'm sorry.
In the last seven days,
we have talked about nothing else.
I gotta get away from you all.
Ls nothing against any of you,
isjust...
- Vincey, wait we didn't mean...
- Stop it!
I'm sorry! I know. I know.
But I have got to get away.
I will be fine. Don't worry
about me. Okay?
Just...
Honey, give the man some room.
He'll be fine.
You know, Megan told me,
when he was in college, some guys
beat the shit out of him on campus,
and then he disappeared for weeks.
"Here is she, anyway?
Megan?
Her parents are in town.
You wanted to tell them what
happened with Megan's parents.
Nah, don't feel like it.
But you hafta swear
- not to say anythin'.
- I don't sound like that.
- You sound exactly like that.
- No I don't...
Anybody want to hear about her?
A new story?
Okay.
I hope you like the salmon,
father. Ls the best in town.
Sarina used to cook us
the most exotic dishes every time
we came into town.
- Didn't she darling?
- Yes.
Absolutely divine.
It was a new taste thrill
every time.
Not that this isn't lovely, dear.
It really is.
Megan can't cook.
But you must know that now.
But that Sarina...
Did we tell you Sarina
sent us flowers?
My God, exquisite!
Absolutely gorgeous!
You know, Jared just got
a promotion at work.
He's our new Vice President
of Video Planning.
Well, thas terrific, Jared.
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations, darling.
Thank you.
Where Sarina got you the interview?
And they gave you the job?
Extraordinary. Really?
"Ith that long hair.
How progressive of them!
- He knows Sarina?
- They're cousins, darling.
- Second cousins. By marriage.
- Really? You don't look like her.
She is such a pretty, pretty girl.
"Here is she living now?
Could we not talk about Sarina
for five minutes, please?
You don't have to be testy, dear.
After all, you did live together
for a very long time.
God, Mother, anyone else's
parents would be thrilled their
daughter was out of a lesbian
relationship and seeing a man.
A handsome, successful, good man
at that, but you two just carry on.
She always was a testy one!
Alicia, I think thas enough.
No! Ls time for honesty.
Here, at this table, honesty.
You,
at a very young age,
you came to the two of us
and you said to us
that you were a lesbian.
And that we should
just get used to it.
And now you bring in this.
- Sarina was like a daughter.
- Enough.
"Hat do we say at P-FLAG?
That is what I'd like to know.
- P-FLAG? - Parents and Friends
of Lesbians And Gays.
Emile and I have been very active
in the organisation.
I'd also like you to know that
your father has written a book,
about our experiences which
was just
about to get a rave in
the New York Times Book Review.
They love it.
And now this.
This is really,
a little bit embarrassing.
You bring in...
You've changed everything now.
All right, thas it.
I'm not going to mention
another word about this.
I've said my piece, and darling,
I would love a drink.
Thank you so much.
All right.
To Sarina.
To such a lovely girl.
You see,
despite the hugeness of what
happened with Vincey,
our own lives still went on.
And we still all had
our same old problems.
And what was weighing down
on my brain was...
I wanted a wedding.
A full-scale ceremony.
I wanted bridesmaids,
freaked-out relatives,
flower girl, ring-bearer girl,
the whole she-bang.
And,
if not that,
I wanted us to move in together.
If not that then a commitment
to more nights together.
And if not that, just more.
I wanted more.
More, what? I don't know.
But just lately,
I'd had the sneaky suspicion
that Megan,
that greedy little bitch,
was using the Vincey Incident
to wiggle back into Sarina's life.
He'd introduced them, so they're
on the phone all the time.
I didn't want to deny Sarina
her friendships or anything.
I...
just felt that...
Megan still had some kind
of control over Sarina's heart.
Robbie, are you okay?
Baby, I need more time.
For what?
Everything's great.
Ljust don't understand.
I don't understand
why we can't just get
a place together?
I just moved in here.
Yeah, and you hate it here, baby.
I know, honey,
but I can't make
a commitment right now.
I don't want that.
Not until you're ready to take it
to the next level.
You talk like we're trapped
in a video game.
No, you talk like you're trapped in
a sick relationship game with me.
Look,
I told you on the first night,
that I cannot
make a commit.
Not yet.
I mean, I was
in a nine year relationship
with the same woman.
What?
You want to sleep around?
You want to try men?
You want to get back with Megan?
Is there something specific you
want to do besides torture me?
- Bobby-bear...
- No!
Ls because I'm too butch.
What?
I know I'm not girlie-girlie
like Megan.
I'm not even girlie-girlie
like Ru Paul.
Shit, next to me,
Janet Reno looks fem.
But at least with me you know
what you're getting.
I'm not some confused straight
girl playing games with you.
You know that butchlfem stuff
means nothing to me.
Yeah, on a theoretical level.
But when it comes to taking me
to the teachers' picnic,
and everybody's wondering
if thas your little brother,
well thas just
a whole other story, isn't it?
I want to ask you a question.
Why is it that everyone
can have problems,
except for me?
Why is it that I always
have to be the understanding one?
Who do I turn to when I need it?
You turn to me.
Thas what I'm here for.
Yeah, thas what I thought.
But you can't even
allow me the "privilege" of
getting over a 9 year relationship.
No, no, no.
Sari, I'm sorry.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I don't want to see you sad.
I don't want to see you cry.
I'll wait, okay?
I'll wait.
I'll wait a whole lifetime
if you want me to.
And then I think: You idiot!
Whad you tell her that for?
You have trouble waiting
for microwave popcorn.
So are they going
to stay together or not?
I don't know.
But you know lesbians are like
Catholics or Saturday Night Live,
going on no matter how bad it gets.
Speaking of mates for life,
- guess who I just saw?
- Vincey and Mr. Beer Bottle?
Tara...
Don't tell me Diego and Dwight?
EXactly! Now get this.
Buzz and I finished work-out and
ran into them in the parking lot.
I swear, it was
like they were avoiding us.
They came up with some lame
excuse about being in a rush.
Well, maybe they were.
When have they ever been
in a rush to get anywhere,
except an Amy Grant concert?
Besides, it was the way
they looked at us.
They can't possibly be mad at us
for not reportin' Vincey, can they?
My guess is that they're still
wigged over the whole thing.
Thas why we should
all get together again.
- And nobody's heard from Vincey?
- Nope.
Not since the barbecue.
And thas been five weeks.
I don't know what to do anymore,
Javi.
I've gone over there ten times.
He's never home.
I call every day.
I only get his answering machine.
I mean, I don't even know
what I'd say anymore.
"Hi, Vincey,
I know you're probably out
keepin' West Hollywood safe by
beatin' up gay-bashers right now,
but when you get a minute,
can you give me a call?"
Hey, you better watch out,
or he might come after you next.
Javi, I'm serious.
I am really worried about Vincey.
You want to worry about something,
worry about my shoulder.
All right, I saw your shoulder,
there's nothin' there.
Where?
Right here.
I don't see anything.
Right there.
There's nothing.
There's nothing there. Come on.
Ls a blotch.
It a freckle, man.
The tiniest freckle in the world.
I think I would know it if I had
a freckle on my shoulder, Buzz.
People get freckles
all the time, man.
You went riding last week without
your shirt in the park, remember?
Could have happened then.
Ls cancer.
Ls starting.
Nothing is starting, Javi.
Come on, man.
Besides, we both agreed if you
came down with any real illnesses,
- we'd investigate them.
- Okay then, feel my glands.
They're swollen.
Your glands are not swollen.
You didn't feel them.
They're not swollen.
I can feel them.
If you could not feel them,
they would not be there.
I'm calling Dr. Mellgard.
And this time you're not invited.
Not after that last episode.
It was just too Norma Rae for me.
- But Javi, man, look...
- But nothing, Buzz.
He is still my doctor.
And he's a respected doctor.
Besides, I don't want him pissed
off at me.
Especially when my pants are down
and his fingers are up my butt.
Fingers?
Ls only supposed to be one.
Sweetie?
I'll be right out.
You got a moment?
Honey, I'm really late for work.
This won't take long.
- Fuck!
- Exactly. "hat the fuck is this?
- Are you going through my things?
- Don't even try that approach.
Let me dry off, okay?
What, so you were gonna
just leave without tellin' me?
"Honey, I'm goin' to the store for
ex-lax," and then never come back?
We've talked about this before,
Tara.
This isn't something new.
Ls a ticket to the Middle East!
I can't stay here!
- What about yourjob?
- The one you're making me late for?
Right, is my fault.
I'm making you late for work.
You can't just wander off.
- You're not a kid anymore.
- Don't tell me what I cannot do.
You want to settle down, I don't.
I've said that from the start.
Yeah, well talk is one thing,
but this,
this is sayin' you'd rather
wander around the war capitals
of the world than stay with me.
Like there's no violence in L.A.
Can't you just stop for a second
and think what you're givin' up?
You think I haven't?
No, I don't think you have.
'Cause I'll tell you one thing
you're not gonna find out there,
in Cairo or anywhere else,
and thas me.
It would be different
if you were a scientist
and wanted to explore
the rainforests,
or you were a businessman
and wanted to open an office
in Beijing.
That would be something
totally different.
But you're so vague about it.
Ls not like you're running
towards something but runnin' away.
I think by the time
you realise that
and come back to get what you
left behind, ill be too late.
I know you don't want to hear this,
but I love you, Gus.
And don't you think
I love you too?
I don't know.
Do you?
Yeah, of course I love you, Tara.
But I can't stay.
If what we've gos not strong
enough to last till I come back,
then thas something
I just gotta risk.
But I've never left California.
I only did community college.
I can't say why I gotta do this.
But that night when Vincey
did that shit,
I kept thinking I've lived such
a totally sheltered life.
That all this shis happening
to all these people,
but everything that happens to me
is through you and people I know.
I was having this totally
fucking bizarre experience,
but then I realised that
I wasn't having any experience.
That I was just watching.
Not that I want to be doing
what Vincey did,
but I gotta start
doing something on my own.
But is gotta be out there.
And is gotta be on my own.
Thas the best way I can put it.
Baby, youjust gotta let him go.
- What else can you do?
- I could break both his legs,
so he'd have to cancel
his stupid trip.
Got any brandy to go in this?
- Tara, is 9 in the morning.
- Yeah, so? Whas your point?
We should be drinking
Bloody Marys.
Ls hard for me to believe
Gus would pull this crap on me,
but is even harder to believe
that Sarina hasn't called you yet.
Thas gonna happen sooner
or later.
You don't know anything for sure,
so les not jump to conclusions.
Tell me what happened.
And start from the beginning...
- Robin?
- Darling?
Sorry to bother you at this hour,
but I have to talk to Sarina.
Baby, is telephone...
telephone.
Hello? 0
Thank God you're there!
You have to come over right away.
Megan, whas wrong?
Just, please, just come.
I need you.
What is it?
Ls... is... Mr. Mittens.
Whas happened?
He's... he's not moving!
Megan probably poisoned the cat
to get Sarina over there.
Did you take him to the vet?
You're the first one I called.
Here.
Thank you.
I'll be right there.
You did what?
Her car's in the shop,
so I told her to take my truck.
"Hat are you, nuts?
Since when is Megan so helpless?
She's acting like a little girl.
If I can't trust Sarina,
then I don't...
ls not a matter of trusting Sarina.
Ls a matter of separating
the sheep from the wolf.
Speaking of wolves, where the hell
is that stupid Jared?
How come he couldn't drive her
over there?
He's out of town on business.
But he'll be back on Monday.
So what happened?
You broke a finger?
You can't pick up a phone
and call poor Robin here?
I been puttin' all kinds
of sick ideas in her head.
I'm sorry.
One kiss.
Okay, look.
"E were driving around all night,
trying to find a stupid vet.
And then when we did, they had
to pump Mr. Mittens' stomach,
and then hook him up to an I.V.
And then we couldn't find
a pay phone.
- In L.A.?
- No, a pay phone that worked.
We lost track of time...
I'm sorry, baby.
- How sorry?
- Really sorry.
Really sorry?
I guess I'm not needed
around here anymore.
I'll just go somewhere else
to be miserable.
Bye.
I'm glad you didn't get
your stomach pumped.
Bye.
- Bye.
- Bye!
Hello, Vincey, is me, Tara.
Guess what.
Javi and Buzz just had
a huge fight.
According to Javi, it was more
dramatic than "Gone With The Wind."
So, let me tell you exactly
how he told me,
but you have to swear
not to tell anybody.
Get ready for this.
Ls gonna be a real shocker.
They are arguing about H-l-V.
Big surprise, right?
Buzz pulled another Larry Kramer
with Javi's doctor.
So Javi's all...
I won't bet my life on it.
There are too many big brains
that say that HIV does matter.
And then Buzz is all...
I know this shit scares you.
And thas when Javi goes...
I can't live on that kind of
rollercoaster.
And they are going back and forth,
back and forth.
And finally Javi says...
HIV is killing me!
Of course,
he's as healthy as a horse.
He's got more T-cells than
bad outfits and thas a lot.
But he was pushed over
the edge, poor dear.
Like Faye Dunaway in "Mommy
Dearest" without the lipstick.
And then not to be outdone,
Buzz is Elizabeth Taylor in
"Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf"
Only his hair was
little bit different.
You know how Javi loves
being the drama queen.
So, he's all, "I'm leaving.
Goodbye."
And then Buzz is all, "No, no,
you're not. I'm leaving."
Of course neither one of them
is going anywhere
because they just thrive
on this kind of interaction.
But finally Javi does leave.
He storms right out the door.
- And Buzz says...
- Where you going? Ls your house.
I do hope they make up because,
well, they are kind of
cute together.
Anyhow, take care, honey,
I'll talk to you later.
You okay?
Ls Buzz.
Yeah, what about him?
I left him just now.
You asked.
- I didn't say anything.
- You didn't have to.
I think Buzz is okay.
What happened?
I don't want Buzz sticking around
out of sympathy for me.
Well, Buzz seems like
he's really into you.
And you seem like
you're really into Tara.
But you're leaving anyway.
Thas fucked up, isn't it?
Ahh, yeah...
but you're gonna pull a Terminator.
You'll be back.
Yeah, sure, eventually.
Question is will she take me back?
Thas something I gotta risk.
Something you should think about
before you fuck up a good thing.
So she's still not talking
to you, huh?
- You know how she is.
- Yeah.
Better watch yourself.
I think you should do something
to make it up to her.
I didn't do nothing wrong.
I've been telling her for months
that I'm going, and now I am.
Now see, thas the difference
between you and me.
When I screw something up
with someone...
I try to make it up to them
in some way.
You know, like, bake 'em
a good dessert,
buy some flowers.
You know, something.
And at that moment,
I knew,
I knew that that was gonna be
the best fuckin'breakfast ever.
Hi, Vincey, this is Tara.
I know you're still...
workin' through things but I thought
I'd give you the weekly update on
whas going on.
You have to swear not to
tell anybody. Of course,
you're not talkin'to anyone,
so who you gonna tell?
Dwight and Diego, they broke up!
No, I'm just kidding.
And me and Gus are having
lots and lots of sex.
Though I don't have to tell you
that because we always do.
But he's shooting good ones.
Anyhow, enough about me.
You're dying to hear about
Megan and Sarina and Robin, so...
So there I was,
outside of Sarina's,
dressed in my best Norma Kamali.
I usually wore a blouse
underneath, but not that night.
I had on my newest, sexiest bra
which kept slipping down.
If I was going to be stalk,
I ought to look my best.
- Hi there.
- Hi.
- Could we talk a minute?
- Sure.
Do I get a hug hello?
You look... good.
You think so?
I'mjust coming from work, and...
But you,
you look great.
So, whas up?
Do you think we could go
somewhere to talk?
No. I can't.
I'm meeting Robin here in
a few minutes to go out to dinner.
Right. Of course.
How is she?
She's fine.
And the two of you?
"Ell...
as you've probably heard,
Jared and I,
well, it just didn't work out.
Yeah, I was sorry to hear that.
So, you know, well,
I was just thinking, I mean,
I just wanted you to know that,
I think we,
you and me,
had some really,
had something really good.
And I just wanted to
tell you that,
because life goes on
and sometimes you don't,
or I don't say thank you,
when I had something good.
It was good.
It was a big part of our lives.
It was, right?
So, any chance of, I mean,
God, I can't believe I'm coming
right out and saying this,
but, do you really love Robin?
Because if not,
I really think we could still
salvage what,
maybe something.
I never stopped loving you, Sari.
We had our problems. Who doesn't?
We were so good together.
And my parents...
think we should buy that house,
like we used to talk about.
They even want to give us
the down-payment.
Anyway, I know I'm getting
ahead of myself.
And I know Robin
is a terrific person,
but honestly,
Sari, could you ever love her
like you loved me?
Honestly?
Honestly.
I never stopped loving you
either, Meg.
But I see now,
we never had a relationship
kind of love.
Ls not at all like
what I have with Robin.
No one can turn heads like you,
Megan. You are beautiful,
charming, successful, witty.
All the things we all want to be.
But it has nothing to do with love.
"Hen I'm in Robin's arms at night,
I feel, I feel something
I never felt with you.
I can't explain it.
But I feel
more real and stronger
than anything I've ever known.
I know you're going to find
someone,
because you have so much to offer.
I have to go now.
Sarina,
if it doesn't work out.
Just remember,
I'm always here for you, okay?
I love you.
Fuckin' lesbians.
Well,
okay,
Buzz bought me this camera and
suggested I keep a journal
as a way of expressing
how I feel about HIV...
So, so...
les see...
Okay,
thas enough about HIV.
At home, things have never been
better between Buzz and I.
Ls scary how we slid from
dating right into domestic bliss.
When I used to dream about
a relationship with someone,
it was never quite like this.
And yet,
now I can't imagine my life with
anyone else or in another way.
Although we try to do something
positive for the community.
Like Dwight and Diego do.
Well, maybe not exactly
like they do.
We all went over to Tara's
for Gus's good-bye dinner.
Megan brought this new boyfriend.
And, as it turned out,
Dwight and Diego weren't
mad at anyone.
They'd gone on some fabulous
gay Christian retreat
to re-evaluate their lives,
then got really busy with work
when they got back.
In fact, they were in a hurry
that day I saw them.
Ls funny how we misinterpret
looks and actions.
When I did bring up Vincey,
things got uncomfortable.
But then, Dwight spoke up.
Guys. Guys.
Okay, guys.
Diego and I talked
about this at length,
and you know we don't like to
force our beliefs onto anyone,
but we were wondering if maybe
it would help the healing process
for Vincey as well as for us,
if we all took a moment
and said a prayer.
- Non-denominational, of course.
- For him.
Now before you say no,
because we know how this makes
some of you feel uncomfortable,
we just want you to
consider the fact that
- though we understand his anger...
- We do not condone his actions.
"E thought this might be a way
to acknowledge what happened...
- as a group...
- And move on from there.
So, can we give it a shot?
Maybe?
Nobody could think of a reason
fast enough why we shouldn't,
but as weird as it was,
it did offer a sort of closure
to the whole deal.
Pray God in heaven,
looking down upon us...
- Great, white bird...
- We'd like to talk about Vincey.
We want you to take him
under your wing.
We'd love it.
"Ith all our hearts.
"Hatever you can do
to keep him safe and dry,
I hope he's wearing shoes.
Okay, that was great.
Can I open my presents now?
I think it was
a very lovely prayer-thingy.
And I think we should all toast
Dwight and Diego
because they are not only
fabulously good-Iooking,
but they're amazingly spiritual
at the same time.
That night at Tara's
was the last time I saw my brother
before he went on his trip.
And then, about six months later,
I'm watching TV.
Thank you for being on my show
"Fags On Line", Vincent.
Oh, my God.
- Call me Vincey.
- How could we not know this?
Everyone else does.
And you can call me Mar-shaw.
Accent on the "shaw."
Now, a lot of queers have
criticised your on-line series
as being too political.
Too preachy.
As co-creator and head writer,
how do you respond to this?
I can take that criticism.
I'm a big man.
I go to the gym.
- Hello?
- Turn on channel 3 right now!
- What?
- Channel 3! Right now!
To give that new prospective...
Oh my God!
...we did a story line
about the gay-basher
who winds up getting raped
and beaten by his intended victim.
- I gotta call Diego and Dwight.
- Okay, bye.
And you really have to wonder
why politicians get upset...
- Turn it up.
- When all that gay people want
are the same rights as
everybody else, not special ones.
Yes, we're watching it.
I think that we're all brought up
with such stupid
- myths about sex and love.
- Megan just called us.
- We were about to call you.
- These lies cause a ton of damage.
Some people are meant to be
in relationships,
some are meant to be single.
Ls not a big deal.
So now, what about you?
Where do you fit into all this?
Relationship?
Not relationship?
Love's a tricky thing, Marcia.
Ls like, no one knows
when or even if is ever
gonna show up.
- Amen.
- But I tell you what.
I think that I'm finally
at a time in my life.
- You go boy.
- Lf it does come my way,
I'll be able to recognise it.
3 years ago, I never woulïvee
dreamed I'd sit at my computer
writing stories
and sending them over the phone
lines into other people's houses.
So maybe love now will look
differently.
Who knows?
How enlightened
Shaka Buto of you.
- That is so clear.
- Shaka Buto?
Vincent,
you've just been a pleasure.
God bless cable.
Thanks for being on "Fags On Line."
We'll see you all later.
As dramatic as I know I am,
I promised myself
I wasn't going to make a
big deal about this baby.
In fact, I haven't even
told Gus about it. Not yet.
I'm gonna wait until
after the baby is born.
Even then, is gotta be
handled very carefully.
I don't it to seem like a
desperate ploy to lure him back.
I'm gonna wait until later.
I haven't told my mother, brother
or anybody yet.
I'm gonna wait until
after the baby's born.
'Cause I know how
people in general
have a much easier time lovin'
cute little babies
than they do lovin'
unwed pregnant women.
So we're just gonna wait.
But in the meantime,
I'vee had all my tests.
I've had my ultrasound test,
my APPtest,
my blood test, my urine test.
All the tests.
I've had them all and
everything's normal.
So there's really nothin'
extraordinary about this baby.
EXcept that, is mine.
Ls my baby.
And this baby's gonna have
all the love in the world.
Isn't it rude when people don't
return other people's calls?
Don't you think is rude
to sneak up on me like that?
I almost killed you, you moron.
Yeah, is a gun.
- Ls loaded.
- My God.
Not that I'm not happy to see you.
Hey, baby.
How come you didn't tell me
you were gonna be on TV?
'Cause I didn't think
public access counted.
You're Mr. Big Shot now,
are you?
No, I've been working hard on this.
I'm flying to New York tonight.
The backers are excited. They can't
believe is going so well.
- Backers? You have backers?
- Yeah.
"The backers can't believe
is going so well."
"I'm leaving for New York."
"Public Access doesn't count."
What about your friends?
We're going to miss you.
- Have you talked to anyone else?
- No, not yet.
- Why not?
- Well, when I come back...
I just wanted to see you
before I left.
Oh, sweety.
- I missed you so much.
- I missed you too.
He wanted to see
how huge I'd gotten.
- Tara, are you all right?
- Yeah. No, I'm okay.
I'm fine.
I'm...
just tired.
You look pale.
- Ok, where does it hurt.
- Somethin' s wrong.
Take a deep breath now.
Take a deep breath.
Everything's fine. Because we're
all here and thas a good thing.
- Oh God!
- No, I'm gonna go get my truck!
Oh, no... my water broke!
I'll call the hospital.
"E'll help you up.
I'm gonna pack.
Ls only seven months.
So he's early? It just means
he's not gay. We'll still love him.
Hold on, little baby.
"E're almost there.
Somethin's wrong.
No, no. You're going to be fine.
Healthy premature babies
are born every day. All right?
- You change your mind about Gus?
- No, don't tell him.
- He should be here for you, Tar.
- No, I'll tell him.
I lost the baby.
Thas what they told me.
Like it was an umbrella
or a ball game or somethin'.
I didn't allow the doctors
to put me under.
I was gonna do everythin'
within my power
to make sure this child lived.
But his lungs
just weren't fully developed yet.
There was nothin'in the tests
that coulïvee told us that.
It was just, you know,
one of those things.
The doctors all said
that they were surprised
the pregnancy lasted
as long as it had.
They let me hold him,
my little son.
He was really tiny!
And when I was holding him,
he gasped like a tiny whimper.
I heard a nurse in the hall say
that was nature's way of
weeding out the weak.
That it was Goïs will.
I wished I had one ounce
of strength left in my body
so I could get out of bed,
slap that nurse silly,
and tell her it was Goïs will.
Look who's here.
I was in New York when I got the
call about the memorial service.
I took the next flight home.
When those ashes flew back
into our faces,
I was certain it meant something,
but just what, I still haven't
figured out yet.
And so our lives go on.
Although I know they can never
be exactly the same.
Javi still has HIV.
I still... did what I did.
And Tara and Gus still
lost the baby.
But just thinking about
that baby's life
and how it never even got started,
the strangest thought
occurred to me.
I thought about how
that life began with sex,
and how sex
sometimes leads to life,
sometimes to death,
sometimes to love.
And then I thought
about my friends.
'Cause every day,
people are born and people die.
And in between we find ridiculous
and important things
to keep us busy.
Like love and sex,
although not necessarily
in that order.
Those people who can find them
both with the same person
should count ourselves among
the lucky ones.
As for the others,
like me,
I've got plenty of love.
I'vee got my friends.
And you know what?
That is something to cherish
in this amazingly brutal,
crazy, but totally
wonderful world.