You can go.
This is Radio Uganda.
Today, November 7, 1972, is the day
in which the people of Uganda...
... are witnessing the end of one chapter
in this country's history...
... and the beginning of another.
Today, the last of the Asians who have
been forced to leave the country...
... will have done so
in order to pave the way...
... for the indigenous people of Uganda
to control the economy.
You give an interview on BBC...
...say that Amin was evil.
Are you mad?
What about Kinnu?
What about Mina?
- Do you ever think of them?
- What should I have done?
Remain silent?
- That is the coward's way.
- Don't talk to me about cowards!
That's what you are.
You're not leaving
because you're scared to leave.
- You are scared of leaving Uganda.
- Why should I go?
Why should I go?
Okelo, this is my home.
Not anymore, Jay.
Africa is for Africans.
Black Africans.
I'll be leaving today.
Thank God you're back.
Where did they take you?
Did they hurt you?
Speak to me, Jay. Where's Okelo?
Gone home, I suppose.
I just can't think about the house,
what to pack. I just want to go.
- Where are we going, Papa?
- Mina, go to sleep.
- But sleep's not coming.
- No one's going anywhere.
- Now, go back to bed.
- Beta.
We are leaving very soon.
Are we going where Masuma went?
Maybe.
- She said there's snow. Will there be?
- Yes.
Is Okelo chachu coming with us?
- Take whatever you want from the house.
- Thank you.
Bye. Bye.
When are we coming back home?
I don't know.
Papa?
Are you crying?
You said that big people don't cry.
Why do we have to go, Papa?
Last day. Last day.
Kinnu.
Okelo.
The car.
I'll sell this.
Mina, come.
- What's this? You're taking it with you?
- Can't you come with us?
Be a good girl. Look after your parents
and you'd better not forget your Swahili!
But who will speak Swahili
with me over there?
I'll see you soon, okay?
Okelo Uncle...
Thank you.
You. Out of the bus.
You stay here. Bring your bags.
- What's in your bag?
- Nothing. Just clothes.
Open.
- What's this?
- Music.
Show me.
My shoes are Japanese
My pants are English
My red hat is Russian
But my heart, it's all Indian
You can go.
Mama.
Mina.
East African Airways announces the
departure of flight EC 786 to London.
Passengers holding
boarding passes...
... are requested to proceed
to the aircraft. Thank you.
- Mama, pee is coming.
- No. No. Not now, beta, we're late.
- It's coming so badly, Papa.
- You can't do it here. Now, wait.
I did it.
Last call for East African Airways
flight EC 786 to London.
Passengers are requested to proceed
to the aircraft immediately. Thanks.
Please, bagger, checkout three.
Bagger, checkout three.
Sale on aisle five.
Mina.
Toilet paper's on sale. Shall I get some?
Aren't we late? I thought
you wanted milk for the wedding.
Is this enough?
Yes, it's enough.
- Good afternoon.
- Afternoon.
Twenty-five gallons of milk,
10 buttermilk.
Holy cow. You opening a dairy?
I was just trying to be friendly.
- Why you going so fast?
- I'll get a ticket if I go any slower.
Drive slowly, Mina.
Do you wanna drive?
- Look, there's an accident.
- It's gonna be all over town tomorrow.
- Damn it! Didn't you see me?
- Hold on, I saw you.
Where did you get a driving license, boy,
Sears and Roebuck?
You stopped in the middle of the road,
this woman ran into me...
- lf you hadn't just stopped...
- What's going on here?
- My truck stalled.
- No, your truck stopped in the road!
- And you tailgated...
- Keep your voice down!
Your license.
- Does anybody need a ride?
- I'm not finished.
Is it against the law
for my truck to stall?
- It is to stop in the middle of the road.
- Lf you're barreling...
- What is he talking about?
- Step back.
Told him I'm not afraid.
- What's he saying?
- He's saying everything is fine.
- Get that black guy's name for insurance.
- I told you, drive slowly.
Didn't I tell you to drive slowly?
What will Anil say?
I'm really sorry.
I think I need your name
and address for the insurance.
- You all right?
- Yeah. Here's mine.
- Thanks.
- All right.
I'm telling you, it's not my fault.
I ain't finished with you yet,
young lady.
"Honorable Sirs: This is in reference
to my lawsuit, number 2089...
...filed in the high court at Kampala,
dated 30 December 1985...
...for restoration of my property.
I was born in Uganda
and Uganda has been my home...
...a country to which I had the
utmost loyalty and love...
...until I was forcibly...
...and illegally expelled...
...by General Idi Amin."
Suing the mad government
of a mad country.
It's going to drive you mad.
For five years they haven't replied.
- But you carry on like a stuck record.
- Kinnu, it's a new regime.
I know it's a new regime.
So what? Every year it's new.
- But nothing...
- Kinnu, Mina had an accident.
- What happened, beta?
- What did you do to my car?
- What did you do to my car, Mina?
- Was anyone hurt?
No one was hurt.
- How did it happen?
- Thank God nobody was hurt.
What's happened has happened.
No use crying over spilt milk.
Who is going to pay for this?
Does money grow on trees over here?
Maybe in your fertile Uganda
it used to grow on trees, but not here.
Can't feed his own family
and lecturing about spilt milk.
My father can feed us just fine,
you wanker.
- What did you say?
- Shut your mouth.
Why should I shut my mouth?
Hey, my man, I need my money.
Forty bucks.
Y'all gonna need this
for the insurance.
See, Napkin, last week I even got
Chanda's name on the license plate.
Anilbhai, stop thinking of the car.
From whose pocket is this all
going to come?
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye, bye-bye.
- You have other problems.
- What?
In this country,
all they know is how to sue.
You get me?
You know about whiplash?
He'll say, "When she hit my car,
my neck got a...
And my spine is damaged forever...
...and so I am suing you
for just one million dollars."
- Then what will you do?
- Hey, Pontiac, stop scaring him.
- Anil, give me that fellow's card.
- Sure.
Your debt is our bread and butter.
This fellow cleans my carpets.
- Mine too. So what?
- So I'll fix it.
- Don't worry.
- You speak to him? Please.
Tomorrow. Now, smile.
I want to see you smile.
It's your wedding day, man, come on.
Enjoy!
- Okay?
- All right.
Beautiful.
Must you check, Kinnu?
It's not Mina's wedding after all.
- I knew it. Go change your slippers.
- Why?
- Is he gonna check out my feet also?
- Mina.
Face it, Ma, you got a darkie daughter.
Harry's mother doesn't like darkies.
Who needs Harry hero-types
in our family?
Want her to be a 30-year-old spinster
running a liquor store?
Why not? You can have a chain.
Go change your slippers.
The things I do for you, Ma.
Really, you never say anything to her.
You forget she's a girl.
Can girls behave the way she does?
Spoil her. Spoil her.
When she sits on our head,
it'll be your responsibility.
Kinnu.
The accident wasn't her fault.
Man, tell us what happened.
We was in this room
filled with computers and shit.
So I go on over to check them out,
you know, start fooling around with them.
- Start typing, "Kill the crackers."
- Oh, man.
And all this other stuff, right?
And then I couldn't erase it.
D-Money nearly lynched me.
- That's messed up, man.
- Yo, Dex, man. Dex.
There's big brother.
You better haul ass.
Okay, y'all, peace.
Dex's messed up
his brother's shit, man.
- Hey, D-Money.
- Why I always got to come get you?
Why I always got to come get you
off the street corner, man?
Daddy wants you home, maybe fix him
something to eat before he get off of work.
That's why I don't take you
on the job with me.
- I can't depend on you. Come on.
- I was getting ready to go.
- Go by the employment office?
- Yeah.
- And?
- I went down...
...and they tell me I'm coming
in there too much.
They tell me veterans come first.
Those crackers always got
some excuse...
That's what I'm talking about.
You always got some excuse.
You can stand out here on the corner
with these crackheads...
...but when it's about getting a job,
you got an excuse.
- You can wear these big-ass...
- Hey!
- Can I get something for y'all?
- No, thank you.
- Gentlemen, did you ring?
- No.
Anything else I can get for you, sir?
Ma'am?
Could you put our bread
in a doggy bag, please?
Certainly, ma'am.
- I'll go inside and wait for my father.
- All right, Demetrius. Take care.
All right.
That's Grace's son.
You know, Mrs. Sanders' Grace?
He's the good one.
We helped him start his own business.
Clancy, bless his heart.
He spoke to the bank.
You know how they are with references.
Sorry I'm late, Dad.
It don't make no difference.
Thought those two was
never gonna get up and leave.
Sat there all night
and forgot to leave a tip.
I don't know why you're so stubborn,
working for them slave wages.
What you want me to do?
Sit at home and catch flies?
What you know about
slave wages, anyway?
- Guess who called me tonight?
- Who?
- Alicia.
- Oh, yeah?
Sure was good
to hear her voice again.
I invited her to stop by on Sunday.
Daddy, what you do that for?
What happened between you
and her is your business.
But she always been
a part of this family.
She always will be,
so long as I'm alive.
Yes, sir.
- Hi, Mina.
- Hi, Harry.
- How are you doing?
- Fine.
That's the mother. Owns a liquor shop.
Can you imagine?
The father's a complete screw-loose.
Spends all his time suing the
government of Uganda for his property.
The mother has her eyes on Harry.
- But we're trying to get Harry for Namita.
- You think this one has a chance?
You can be dark and have money,
or you can be fair and have no money.
But you can't be dark
and have no money...
...and expect to get Harry Patel.
Brothers, sisters and friends.
On this happy occasion
of my only son's wedding reception...
...I would like to say a few words.
Hear, hear! Three cheers for Anil.
Thank you. Thank you.
But what I wish to say is
more serious and that is...
...even though we are
10,000 miles away from India...
...we should not forget our roots,
our culture...
...our tradition and our gods.
So please join me in singing a prayer.
What is this? Behave yourself.
Wake up. Everyone's singing.
Wanna go out when this is over?
Okay, let me tell my mother, though.
I have to get out of these clothes.
Ma, Harry's asked me to go out.
They're going out.
You wouldn't believe the racket.
It's 10:00. Customers are complaining.
- So you better come right on over.
- Send them back to the reservation.
How often I gotta tell you?
They're not that kind of Indian.
- This place?
- It's the only place open in your town.
- Wanna give it a shot?
- Sure.
Excuse me, two beers, please.
Michelob.
- Cheers.
- Tadice.
- Hi, girl. What are you doing here?
Just hanging out.
Harry, Tadice.
Tadice, Harry.
- Tadice. Pleasure.
- We worked together at the motel.
"You are needing room?"
- Never mind us. Wanna dance?
- Me?
- Hi.
- Hey, how you doing?
We met this afternoon. The accident.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- How's your van?
- All right. And the car's all right?
- Not really.
- Yeah.
Excuse me.
What's up, Rabbit?
Back from the city of Jackson...
... let's welcome home
our very own Alicia LeShay.
We saw your face in the magazine.
We're all proud of you, sugar.
Sylvester Artiste III,
record producer.
How you doing?
Hey, with this lady by my side,
I feel like a king.
Rabbit and me used to be
the talk of the town.
- You seen my advertisement?
- Yeah.
Now I'm gonna cut a record.
And you?
Yeah, I'm doing all right.
We got some new machines...
...we're working with deep shags.
Everything's going all right.
Matter of fact, I'm feeling...
Rashida, girl, how you doing?
You look fabulous.
Like to dance?
Mina, I'm leaving.
Come on, Mina, you can't leave already.
D-Money will take you home.
- Yeah, yeah. Where you stay?
- At the Monte Cristo off the 82.
- You sure you wanna leave?
- Yes.
I'll stay if you don't mind, huh?
Tyrone, this here's...
Mina.
Mina, Mina... You got the...
Are you from around here?
Yeah.
- You Mexican?
- No.
I used to live in L.A. Plenty of Mexicans
there looking as pretty as you do.
I'm Indian.
Oh, come on, now.
You ain't no Indian.
Yes, I am.
What's a girl like you
doing in Mississippi?
Punishing yourself?
- You about ready to go?
- She just got here.
Why don't you stay
and I'll take you home?
I'll see you in the morning, Tyrone.
Come on.
What?
So you clean carpets?
Yeah.
I got my own business.
Motels?
Motels, offices, homes...
Indian motels?
Yeah, some.
Mostly they clean
their own carpets, though.
Yeah, I know.
That's where I live.
In a motel.
Work there too.
I'm gonna give you one of my cards here.
You might want to...
You already gave me one.
I did?
This morning.
The accident.
Oh, yeah, okay. Yeah.
- I'll walk you in.
- I'll be fine.
- Really.
- You sure?
All right.
Oh, listen, I didn't mean
to butt in on your man.
He's not my man.
Well, maybe I'll give
you a call sometime.
- Listen to me.
- Okay, okay.
If you don't spend,
how will money come in?
There must be crossventilation.
If money is not important,
then why are you wasting your time...
...suing the government of Uganda
for your property?
Money comes...
...money goes.
- Right, Pontiac?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Meet our Jaybhai.
In Uganda, you're the champion
defender of blacks...
...but the same blacks kicked him out.
Right, Jaybhai?
- Cruelty has no color.
- Principles, Pontiac.
Principles.
Jaybhai? Hey, Jaybhai,
who are you phoning?
- Hmm?
- Kampala.
To tell the person who is
living in my house to get out!
- Had a good time?
- Ma.
Where did you go?
Dancing.
I keep telling you...
...go out more.
Meet people.
You should've seen his mother's face
when you left.
Are you going out again?
Did he say anything?
Ma.
What happened with Okelo and Papa?
How did that come into your head?
I mean, why doesn't Papa
ever write to him...
...or talk about him?
- Is Harry Patel a good dancer?
- Yeah.
Like him?
No.
It doesn't happen in a day, you know.
Happened with Pa and you.
With this attitude...
...you'll never find anyone.
You say that Indian was ripe for plucking
and you ain't do nothing?
She did look pretty good, though.
T-Bone, what you think?
All a man got on his mind is
just getting in a woman's pants?
- That ain't all he's got on his mind.
- You got a leash on your mind.
She don't want you no more.
She got a geri-curl head,
wigwam boy from Jackson.
Sylvester Artiste III,
record producer.
You need a geri-curl, boy.
- You gonna make me late again?
- Pa, she ain't going nowhere.
- Good morning, Tyrone.
- Pop, how you doing?
Oh, Lord...
...grant peace to every living creature
under the sun.
Hey, fellows.
I want you to try something special.
Relax. Sit down.
Your people are very good
at sports, no?
Kareem Abdul-Jabbar.
Freddy Brown from downtown.
- Hector "Macho Man" Camacho.
- Macho ain't black. He's Mexican?
- He's Puerto Rican.
- Puerto Rican.
Black, brown, yellow, Mexican,
Puerto Rican, all the same.
As long as you're not white,
it means you are colored.
- Isn't that so?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I guess.
A girl had an accident
with your van yesterday. Correct?
But no damage was done
to your person or to your van. Correct?
- That's right.
- Thank God.
The person whose car she was driving
is my very good friend.
- Also Indian. You get me?
- No.
He is worried...
...because in this country,
people are suing all the time.
Yeah, I got you now.
Yeah, this is good tea.
I didn't mean to laugh.
You tell your friend he ain't got
nothing to worry about.
I told him. I told him not to worry.
You are a good man.
All us people of color
must stick together.
That's right.
Because you and your brothers,
you all done all right by us.
And me and my brothers,
we gonna do all right by y'all.
United we stand.
Divided we fall.
That's right. Right on, brother.
Power to the people.
What a brother.
"Power to the people."
Anil.
I spoke to him. It's all okay.
All right.
- Hello.
- Is that Demetrius?
- Yes, ma'am. Who's this?
- Mina.
Oh, Mina, hey.
What's up?
I just wanted to say thanks.
You know, the other night?
Thanks for dropping me home.
- Yeah, okay. Bye.
- Wait a minute, hold on, now. Relax.
Relax. Wait a minute.
I ain't gonna sue.
- What?
- Hello?
Yeah, I'm here.
Look, what you doing
Sunday afternoon?
Sunday...
Nothing much.
Would you come to my house
and have dinner with me and my family?
I'd love to.
Mina.
My father always used to say:
"They can take everything from you...
...but they can't take
away your education."
Papa, please.
Mina...
...you are too intelligent to waste
your life cleaning bathrooms.
It makes me feel
I failed you as a father.
Look, Pa, there's nothing wrong
with cleaning bathrooms.
When you win your case...
...and you get your money...
...l'll think about college.
Okay?
Sure is hot today, man.
Give me that.
Give me that wrench.
- Shit, look at this carburetor.
- Hi.
- What's up, Jay?
- Hey, Skillet.
How's the lawsuit?
Those niggers paid up yet?
Oh, yeah.
So as long as I can see those
dimples today, I'm doing just fine.
Go on, now.
Go drink your beer.
See you, Skillet.
All right.
Jaymini.
Anil phoned me again.
Same old complaint.
We must talk to Mina.
She's so rude to him all the time,
and I owe him so much money still.
What?
Where did this come from?
It's always been here.
- How long you been in Mississippi?
- Three years.
- And before that? India?
- No, before that I was in England.
- And before that I was in Africa.
- Yeah?
- I've never been to India.
- Never been to India?
- No.
- You kidding.
No, I'm not.
I'm a mix Masala.
"Mix Masala," huh?
What's that? One of them
kind of, religious thing or...?
- What?
- No.
It's a bunch of hot spices.
You hot and spicy, huh?
Yeah, mix Masala.
That's what I'm gonna call you.
I told you. It's the Mexican...
I mean, that Indian girl.
Damn.
Everybody, this is Mina.
She's from England
and India and Africa.
Anywhere else you're from?
- I'm his father. Williben.
- Nice to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
- Meet the family.
- Go on.
- Dexter, you turned that chicken over?
- Yeah, Money.
- This is my sister Rose.
- Mina.
- Hello.
- She tough, watch out for her.
- Don't pay him any mind.
- This is Dexter, my youngest son.
- Hi.
- You're from Africa?
- I was born there and then...
Tyrone.
- You remember me.
- What's going on?
- Bring the food.
- It's coming, Granddaddy.
- Coming!
We waiting on Alicia.
If I say I'm going to dinner
for someone's birthday...
...l'll be sure to be on time.
Alicia's busy, Aunt Rose.
She's moving up in the world.
I never did like that girl. Anybody
change their name to LeShay...
- You got a mean old mouth.
- I say the truth like I see it.
Where's the food?
While they blew money up their noses,
Eddie had his head on his shoulders.
- Eddie Murphy.
- That's why I ain't going back to L.A.
I'm biding my time here
in Greenwood...
...until I learn how to handle success.
You understand?
I'm hanging around here too.
You know, until I get myself situated.
I'll go see if they need help
in the kitchen.
You need any help with that help?
Because I'm right here. Yeah.
Man, just looking at her
make me break into a sweat.
Don't sweat all over the chicken.
I can't wait to see Alicia's face
when she see her.
When Alicia comes back to you,
you can pass Mina to me.
Like she a bag of groceries
or something?
You so righteous,
you should've been a preacher.
I tell you what,
you should go out with Alicia.
I tell you something,
I already been out with her.
He's about the nicest man
a girl could ever ask for.
- We're just friends.
- Did I say any different?
He was all set
to go to Jackson State.
When his mama died, he didn't
wanna leave his daddy alone...
...because that's the kind
of boy he is.
Now, I made a vow to Grace
that I would look after her boy.
And I've been like a mother
to him ever since.
Doing so well now,
with his own business...
...makes me right proud of him.
It's not easy, you know?
Sometimes, no matter
how hard you work...
...things have a way of going wrong.
That's when you gotta know how
to make them right. Know what I mean?
Lord...
...bless this gathering...
...and remember
our dear departed Grace.
Amen. Let's eat.
- Granddaddy.
- Did you say you were from Indianola?
- No. India.
- You have to yell. He don't hear good.
- India.
- Indiana?
India.
Where're the biscuits?
What's Africa like?
It's not like Shaka Zulu is it?
Some places.
You know, they got cities too.
- We used to live in Kampala.
- Isn't that where Idi Amin is from?
Y'all hush with all the questions.
Let the girl eat her food.
I'm going to Africa one day
to see Nelson Mandela.
Then I can say
I saw somebody for sure!
Who gonna pay for the ticket?
Welfare?
Young lady, tell me.
How come they got Indians in Africa?
The British brought them
to build the railway.
Like slaves.
I guess.
That's how my grandfather came.
Then the railway was finished
and he stayed on.
- How come you left?
- Dexter, let her eat her food.
- I'm just asking a question.
- Just let her eat.
What's wrong with asking
how come she left?
There ain't nothing wrong with asking
why she left, just let her eat.
It's time for the cake!
Happy birthday, Uncle Williben.
Come on, now. Help me blow it out.
I used to know someone in Indianola.
She don't know that person,
because she's from India.
- What did you get, Uncle Williben?
- Beautiful.
- Look at it.
- That's from all of us, Dad.
- For when I retire, huh?
- And the sooner the better.
Ruining your health
for old Mrs. Morgan...
...who don't say hello
when she pass me on the street.
Happy birthday.
Well, Mina's gotta go,
so we gonna head on out.