- What?
- Yo, dog, I ain't going.
I'm getting on that bus.
Now that means
you are getting on that bus.
We look stupid!
Oh, now you want to be
all embarrassed.
You should've
thought about that before.
Dog, I ain't going.
Call me dog again and see if I don't
knock you flat on your ass.
Now, I'm getting on that bus and you
are going right along with me.
I am your father.
You are my son.
So let's get on the bus, okay?
Walk.
Gary...
...stop looking at me like that.
Shelly, are we cool...
No, we're not cool, and we're not
finished either.
You'll feed Kaya for me?
I'll feed him, walk him and watch him
crap! I'm looking forward to it.
You make it sound like I'm
running off with another woman.
You expect me to get wet like you're
doing something incredible?
This whole thing is sexist and
exclusionary.
Yes!
How would you feel if the march
was only for dark-skinned brothers?
How can Farrakhan call a march for
dark-skinned brothers...
...when Farrakhan's about your
complexion, with straight hair?
Gonna kiss me? Kiss me goodbye?
I'm late for work.
I love you anyway.
Remember to watch CNN.
We're not done talking.
I know we're not.
I'll call from Arkansas.
Looks like they're boarding.
Welcome aboard, welcome aboard.
I'd have hated
being on your plantation.
Runaway slave wouldn't have
stood a chance against you.
Court order says I have to keep my son
tethered for 72 hours.
But it's cool.
We're working it out, right?
All right.
Welcome aboard the Spotted Owl.
We're ready to ride into history.
Step right up on in.
Come on. Anybody else going to the
Million Man March, get on the bus!
- How you feeling?
- Okay, Pop. You?
Never felt better in my life!
Then give me some of what you got.
How you doing?
Welcome aboard.
Black power, brothers!
Black power.
Sounds like he's stuck in the '60s.
- Got it?
- Yeah, I got it, thank you.
Thank you very much.
My name...
...is Jeremiah Washington.
Jamal.
Glad to meet you, Jamal.
Not much legroom, is there?
I'll have to stretch these bones
every chance I get.
Ain't that the truth?
Them fools back at the barbershop...
...they asked me what I hoped to
accomplish by going to the march.
These black men, nagging at me...
What'd you say?
I said I'd be first in line
at the revolution...
...while they'd be
bringing up the rear.
And by the time I return
from Washington...
...my behind's gonna be
20 years younger.
Fountain of youth, huh?
The Miracle at the Mall,
that's what I'm looking for.
And that's what I'll get.
Craig, how's it going?
- Let's roll it.
- We ready to roll, peoples.
If you're going to the Slauson
swap meet, the Brentwood mansion...
...or the La Brea Tar Pits,
your black ass is on the wrong bus.
This bad boy is going
to Washington, DC...
...for the Million Man March!
- I'm George, this is Craig.
- Say, fellas.
We'll get you to and from the march
safely, in six days.
- We hope.
- There are some rules we must observe.
One, and this is for you, Pop.
No drinking alcohol while on this bus.
Two, no smoking.
And three...
...most important, and this
I ain't bullshitting about...
...no using or possessing
illegal substances.
There's a bathroom in the back.
I trust that none of you men
are women.
If you are, you're some of the
ugliest broads I ever seen in my life.
Flush the toilet after you use it.
Try not to piss on the seat.
You two gonna have
a problem with that.
He sounds like my mother.
For the next 6 days, I am your mother.
Don't make me use my belt.
Mr. Driver?
With your permission, sir,
I think we ought to ask...
...that the Creator
should travel with us.
I got no problem with that.
Any objections?
The floor is yours, Pop.
Bow your heads.
Father God...
...we come to You as pilgrims on a bus
that's bound for glory.
We're not perfect, Lord,
but we seek perfection.
We're not guilt-free,
but we ask for Your forgiveness.
We know You was with Moses
when he parted the Red Sea...
...and freed the slaves.
We know You was with Noah...
...when the rain came down
40 days and 40 nights.
You was with Malcolm in Mecca...
...with Martin when he went
to the mountaintop.
And we're asking You, dear God,
to be with us now...
...on this historic journey to
fellowship...
...with one million black men.
And if there's anything, Lord,
that we need and we pray for...
Hot damn!
Thought y'all was gonna jet
without a brother!
My horoscope said the moon
was aligned for me.
Hey, we're in the middle
of a prayer here.
Oh, oh. My bad.
Y'all go ahead.
And if anything, dear Lord,
that we do need and pray for...
...is that after this trip...
...each and every one of us will
be a better man than he was before.
Amen.
You got a ticket?
You better have a ticket.
I made the bus.
What's up?
- Hey, Ben Vereen!
- Ben Vereen's not on the bus.
Let me ask you...
...what would a bus trip be
without James Brown?
Like O.J. without a white girl.
Be a sorry-ass trip.
That's all I needed to hear! Hit me!
Ready?
Papa don't take no mess
Papa is the man
Who can understand
How a man's got to do
Whatever he can
Hit me!
What's up, dog?
I done told you about that "dog" shit.
Don't let me have to take care of you
out here in front of these brothers.
Now turn that mess down.
It's too loud, Junior.
Let me ask you...
...you don't like to be called "dog."
Well, you know, "Dad"...
..."Daddy"...
..."Sir" would be nice.
Take your pick.
Then I should have the right
not to be called Junior.
That's cool. That's cool.
What do you like? Evan?
Hell, no!
Then what?
Smooth.
My homies call me Smooth.
Your homies call you Smooth.
I ain't your homie, okay?
You must be out of your damn mind.
Ain't no way I'm calling my son Smooth.
All of a sudden, I'm your son again?
But I'm the one out of his mind?
You're a Bruins fan, huh?
Yeah, 1995 NCAA champs.
Can't argue with that.
You down with the Bruins?
I went to SC.
Flip Carter. What's happening?
X.
X? Like in, what,
"X marks the spot"?
No...
...just X.
I've heard some trippy names
in my life: Ezekial, Cadillac...
...even a brother named Porcupine.
But even if she's in labor
with a bottle in one hand...
...a big fat blunt in the other...
...no mother would name her
son a letter of the alphabet.
You're saying your mama named you...
...Flip?
Phillip. Flip's my stage name.
I'm what you call a thespian.
My real name's Xavier.
- Xavier Moore.
- That I can get with.
What up, black?
What's up?
I'm doing well. I made the bus.
It's all good now.
Had trouble waking up?
Please, I get up with the roosters.
I had an early audition.
You a singer?
I'm an actor.
You ever been in any movies?
- See Boyz N the Hood?
- You were in that?
Almost.
At the last minute they gave it to...
...to Ice Cube.
You believe that?
He's a rapper, not an actor.
They hired a rapper to act.
I can't get behind that.
It's okay, though, because
I just went up for a role opposite...
...Denzel.
That's on the q.t.
What is this, CNN?
Excuse me.
Film school. I'm doing a documentary
for my thesis project.
Gary.
Gary what?
Gary Rivers.
How come you're going to the march?
The march. How come you're going?
I guess if the brothers are getting
together, talking about things...
...working things out,
I want to be there.
Where are you from?
Pasadena.
No, where are you from?
Monterey, originally.
Right.
I didn't know black people lived there.
We got a handful.
If you don't mind my asking...
...are you mulatto, or just
light-skinned?
You mean biracial?
Biracial?
So that's a yes.
I consider myself black.
If you're raised by at least one
black parent, I guess you're down.
Many brothers were raised
by one parent.
My mother's white.
- No disrespect.
- What's with your pop?
What?
Your father. What's up
with your father?
My father was a black man.
He was a cop. He got murdered.
Must've tripped you out.
Yeah, it tripped me out.
Really tripped me out. Just like
having to watch a rapper act.
This brother, man...
- Excuse me.
- Shoot on this side.
I'm sorry.
Mind if I ask something?
Why quit now?
Was it a brother
that killed your father?
- What kind of question is that?
- I'm just wondering.
Yes, a brother killed my father.
Did you get it?
Did you get it, X?
Yeah. Yeah, I got it.
Kyle, you can't just blink your eyes
and expect me to go away.
I know you can hear me.
- Should I just keep talking...
- What's your beef?
You think if you pretend to sleep,
I'll forget we were talking?
You always think I'm playing you.
I'm not accusing you.
- I'm asking for clarification.
- I said all I have to say.
You can't just wake up one morning
and say you need space...
...and expect it to be case closed.
- After all we've been through?
- Keep your voice down!
I forgot.
We can't let your macho ass
out of the closet.
What do you want me to say?
Anything.
That it's another man, or a woman.
That you're confused about
your sexuality. Anything.
Look, Randall, I need space.
- That's it.
- Not good enough.
If I knew you were gonna trip
on me, I'd have made you stay home.
You've got a lot of nerve.
You are not the reason I came on
this trip, you pompous bastard.
Good. Then you won't mind
if I change my seat.
I do mind. I mind that you're not
man enough to admit you love me.
- Hold up!
- What?!
- Cool, Dad.
- Oh, Lord.
We're going to the march
with a bunch of homos!
Sissy.
Tell me I didn't just hear
what I think I did.
What?
He said:
"You're not man enough to admit
that you love me," to him.
So?
So?!
We have faggots on the bus.
Gays have no role in our community?
I'm talking about the faggots
we got on this bus.
How else would they get there?
Skip.
Damn straight.
It's no biggie to me.
You bend down
and grab your ankles too?
No, I ain't gay, all right?
I still don't see what the problem is.
Ask them why they're going.
Look, bro. You know what? I will.
The Bible says it's an abomination.
Still...
...sometimes I ask myself
what would I do if...
...one of them...
...was my son?
Or worse, still...
...what if I was the one
that was born that way?
What's your lady's name?
- Jindai.
- Oh, she is pretty!
How long you been together?
We been talking for about two years.
Two long years? Two short years?
Two short years.
I met her one day
when I was crossing the street.
Don't tell me you
met this beautiful young lady...
...and you did the "daddy-cool" thing.
In my unenlightened days...
...big booty would catch my eye.
You could say I had "big booty radar."
Son, you ain't in love.
You're in lust.
No, sir. No, sir.
Far beyond that now.
Since we've been together,
we've never really been together.
You kidding me?
No.
We're of the faith.
Living clean, you know?
No shame in that.
Shabuya, sha, sha, shabuya
Roll call
My name is Mike
Representing New York
I'm not a Muslim
Still don't eat pork
Roll call
Don't call me Evan
'Cause I'm on the move
Don't call me Junior
But you can call me Smooth
My name is Evan
Evan Senior
They got my son
On a misdemeanor
My name is Gary
I'm down with Shelly
She's got the butter
I got the jelly
My name is X
And I'm a Bruin
And blah, blah, blah
My name's Jamal
My mind is free
We need more love
And unity
My name is Pop
We're at the top
Now all this shabuya
Has got to stop
Mike, how come you're going
to the march?
I'm thinking this
could be Black Monday.
What do you mean?
This could be a setup.
This could be a conspiracy.
We could be on our way to getting
done, like the trains into Dachau.
- You saying it's a plot?
- It could be, man.
Think of all the planes and cars
filled with black men going to DC.
Thousands, right? Thousands.
If I'm a crazy white man
in the government...
...and want to kill a million black
men, just hit one button, and boom?
When and where would I do it?
At the Million Man March.
The next day, when we're all dead,
who'll fight our battle?
Nothing but black women left.
Some "holocalyptical" shit going on.
That's what I'm saying.
- Jay, you going for the same reason?
- No, I'm going to the march for myself.
It's time for us to be responsible,
get out of the beggar mentality...
...to say, "Look out for a brother."
We need to start looking out
for ourselves.
This is a strong black businessman.
- You have a business?
- Yes, I have my own business.
Ask him what.
I've been in business 7 years.
- What kind of business?
- I have a black bubblegum company.
- What's it called?
- Yo Bubba.
How's business?
It's blowing up.
I just don't understand.
Got the girl at private school
her whole life...
...Sunday school,
church every Sunday...
How she gonna come home
with a bun in the oven?
16 frigging years old.
What about the punk got her pregnant?
He's 16 too.
Says he gonna quit school,
get a job and rent an apartment.
Ain't said nothing about no marriage.
I tell you, if Farrakhan
has a way to handle this...
...I'd be all ears.
Right now, I want to kill that boy.
Craig! Watch out!
- Everybody okay?
- Call Jacoby & Meyers!
- Can't you drive?
- This isn't a Bronco, is it?
Damn, the engine just cut off.
Is everybody all right?
Damn.
What do you think?
We'll never get out of the ditch.
Now don't be so negative.
Okay, Little Orphan Annie,
the sun'll come out tomorrow.
Haven't you heard the expression
"There's strength in numbers"?
I've been on many ditched buses. I
won't let nothing like that stop me.
Fellas?
I need every able-bodied man
off the bus now! Come on!
- Come on, everybody!
- Gonna mess up my shoes!
We got a little problem.
Get on down there.
Come on.
Everybody!
Ready? One...
...two...
...three!
We can't do it.
Can't?
What do you mean, can't?
Look there. When Hannibal
crossed the Alps...
- Who's Hannibal?
- Who's the Alps?
...and saw that he was outnumbered 10-
to-1 by the Roman army, he didn't say:
"Let's go home. We can't do it."
He said, "Get your ass
back on that elephant...
...and stomp them Roman bastards!"
There ain't no such words
as "We can't do it."
Let me use 3 other words:
Too damn heavy.
I can't believe you're so shiftless...
...and lazy that you'll just give up.
Oh, he's going to get all
plantation on us now.
"I'm gonna to do it, boss!"
The way you look, I can't blame him.
I thought slavery was over.
It doesn't concern you.
Maybe it does.
Tell us what it's all about.
No, I'm telling you to back off.
That's what I'm telling you.
Hey, everybody, the man's got
a court order. I seen it.
I want to see it.
- Who are you, Richard Roundtree?
- That's all right.
I'd like to see it too.
Okay, now, does this
meet with your approval?
Good...
...because I'm gonna
say this one time...
...okay?
Now, this boy right here
has got one father. One.
And that's me.
If you're trying to find
somewhere to stick your noses...
...I got several places I would
love to tell you about.
But whatever you do...
...make sure that it ain't
in my business.
You see, brothers? That's just
what I'm talking about.
The devil don't want the black man
to have atonement.
Right, Pop?
Right.
But God wants us at that march.
It's our mission.
So, on 3...
...I want you strong, black African
Mandinka Zulu goddamn warriors...
...to lift this damn bus out of that
stupid ditch, and let's be on our way!
To whose tribe
do you belong to anyway?
Shaka Zulu's or Clarence Thomas'?
Shaka Zulu's!
Put your back into it! You're all
Mandinka warriors! Lift the bus!
Come on, do it for me!
Pull it up! Go! Go! Pull! Pull!
Come on!
Pull, y'all! That's right, baby!
That's right.
You didn't believe me!
You didn't want to!
Did you see that?
Give me my $10.
Now what?
The devil's kicking
our Mandinkan asses.
Wait. Remember Hannibal, now.
We ain't getting our ass kicked.
We'll get out of this ditch.
You know what this is? A plot.
It's a plot, man!
What's going on?
I was putting its pedal to the metal.
The axle must be busted.
Shit.
Let me call base.
- They want me to stay with the bus.
- You know those idiots.
But I'll miss the march.
You know the rules.
What can I do about it?
This is a bitch.
Who's taking my place?
They didn't say. They'll just
send us another bus.
We got another bus coming.
- When?
- I don't know.
We won't get stranded on no desert.
Why don't y'all take your shit out?
Gentlemen, please!
Which way? You going back to L.A.?
Out on the road
And the bus broke down
Well, it won't be too long
Till I see Farrakhan
You go, Jay. Take it away.
- And it won't be long
- Till what?
Till we're 1 million strong
Well, I was out on the road
And the bus broke down
About 20 of us was
Out on the road
And the bus broke down
Well, I think
They're trying to stop us
But we still DC bound
You guys, here comes...
Hey, here comes the bus!
Y'all didn't believe me.
What's up?
Craig, George, what's all this?
They're going to the march.
The Farrakhan thing? You're kidding.
I'm kidding. They're the
Harlem Globetrotters.
They said a trip to the Capitol.
I should've known.
I guess so. Come on, brothers!
- This is our ride.
- And he's white, fellas.
He gets to go to the march,
I get to stay.
You're kidding, right?
We can't go to no march
with a white boy driving.
What about all that Mandinka stuff?
Used to be we always
had to chauffeur the white man.
This time, he's chauffeuring us.
Right, Pop?
Right.
Come on!
You got anything to stow,
leave it with me.
What's up, Reuben Kinkaid?
You looking for a recording contract,
you come to the wrong place.
What's up?
- Gary.
- Rick.
Not scared or anything, are you?
Of course not. Why, should I be?
Damn right.
They got guns and knives.
I'll be with you guys in spirit!
Freedom now!
We're just getting going, y'all.
Yeah, one million strong.
I can't believe this.
Writing a letter?
This is a prayer I thought I might say
when we arrived at the march...
...thanking the Lord
for all that this means to me.
If we arrive.
White boy driving us to the Million
Man March, that's gotta be a bad omen.
What's the deal
with Kunta Kinte there?
Brother said for us to stay
out of his business.
I don't care what some judge said, no
way I'd handcuff my son like that.
You?
That I cannot say.
No kids?
Oh, yeah, I had...
...two kids.
But not anymore.
That's all over now.
No family at all?
Not anymore.
Jeremiah's strictly on his own.
How do you feel?
Pardon?
You're on a bus...
...with 20 black men.
How do you feel?
Black, white, all the same to me.
I like to think of myself
as colorblind.
Colorblind?
So you didn't notice at all that
everyone on this bus is black but you?
So-called black men,
descendants of slaves.
Well, we're all
brothers under the skin, right?
Now we're brothers just because
you're on the black bus?
Look, I never wore a white sheet
over my head. I'm Jewish.
God forbid we think a Jew
could be a bigot.
My parents were for civil rights.
Blacks came to our house...
Are you getting this? They actually
had blacks at their house.
I didn't mean it like that.
Oh, spare us.
Only two things came out of
the civil rights movement.
One: Black people got a few crumbs.
And two: Condescending whites
could say they struggled with us.
But it didn't end with
the March on Washington.
We're still catching hell.
My people know about catching hell.
My parents did their part.
Their part to make a difference,
or to appear liberal?
Jews made a difference
in the movement.
As soon as they got what they wanted,
they abandoned it.
I don't see black people
marching for Jews...
...Hispanics or Asians.
Why do you expect whites
to solve all your problems?
We didn't create our problems.
White people did.
You think we asked for slavery?
We asked for the Holocaust?
Six million Jews died.
Doesn't mean we're gonna forget
Nazis, Arabs...
...black anti-Semites...
Do you know how many blacks died
in the slave trade? Over 60 million.
I didn't kill them, nor did
my parents. Don't blame us.
Yeah, it's our fault.
After 400 years of slavery
and oppression...
...we're just supposed
to fix everything ourselves?
Damn right, we are.
Who else will do it?
Hey, Spike Lee Jr., are you
paying me for this movie?
Then I quit. Get that camera
out of my face.
Your name is what? Randall, right?
And correct me if I'm mistaken,
but you are a homosexual?
- Yes.
- And he's Jewish.
That makes both of you
minorities on this bus.
Which shows you know nothing about
the civil rights movement...
...because it was about
bringing people together.
So we can stop insulting each other
and deal with the real issue...
...the real oppressor.
I've known him for 5 years.
All he's trying to do is do his job.
Just help us get to the march.
That's all he's doing.
A reasonable man like you
can understand that.
So why don't you cut him some slack?
I don't have a problem with you.
Good.
Thanks, George. I appreciate that.
Yeah, Rick. Listen...
...as long as you do your share of the
driving, I have no problem with you.
You're okay in my book, pal.
Yo, dog!
What, man?
I gotta use the restroom.
What?
Piss. The bathroom!
If you don't mind,
I'd love to go by myself.
Thanks.
What's happening?
So they liked me?
Yeah, yeah, count on that.
I got my fingers and toes crossed.
Bye. Bye.
Oh, boy!
Did you get it?
They're gonna make the decision this
weekend, but it looks like I got it.
Big role?
They throw me up on that screen, I'll
blow up too large. People be like:
"Denzel who?"
You know what I'm saying?
I hope it works out.
Then I can say I knew you when.
- "The fool on the bus."
- Right on.
Go on your way
to the Million Man March, 1995.
Say...
...what do you think he's thinking?
Mighty whitey, driving the bus.
Right now he's probably thinking
about kicking his boss's ass.
You don't have a problem with him.
You got no problem with him
because you share a white thing.
You know what I mean.
I already told you,
I consider myself black.
Hang on. No disrespect, brother.
I didn't...
A person is white,
doesn't mean I dislike him.
And just because a person is black
does not mean I like him.
I consider myself black,
just like Bob Marley.
- I'm not talking about him.
- He was mulatto. I'm black.
No disrespect, partner, but I could
consider myself 6'4" and ugly.
The fact remains that I'm 6 foot and
too cute for the English vocabulary.
Wait a minute, Mr. Hollywood.
The man is black.
Just let him be.
He's also white!
If this was slavery,
would ole massa care?
He'd be a slave like the rest of us.
He'd be a house slave
in the big house.
While we'd be talking about grits...
...he'd eat potatoes.
He'd have the breast of chicken.
Our women would be blistered
from picking cotton.
His would be bathed, smelling good.
And 9 times out of 10,
the honey he'd hit skins with...
...she'd be a white girl.
Hold it just a minute.
About the grits:
Grits was for the white folks
up in the big house.
Slaves were lucky to get corn mush.
As for hitting the skins
with a white girl...
...a black man could get lynched for
just thinking that thought.
- Pop, you know what I mean.
- You are wrong.
Look, my lady's not white.
But you would never
understand that, would you?
What's your problem, really?
Do you want a white woman?
- That's it.
- Is that it?
Please, please!
"Player" is written all over me.
I done tagged all kinds of freaks,
black, white...
- Blondes, cripples, crazies.
...Chinese, Mexican.
Why do you insist on
calling women freaks?
I love my woman, okay? I respect her.
She's not a freak. She's a queen.
I bang queens too.
Oh, sorry. I get it.
You're on that henpecked trip.
I don't cheat on her. It doesn't make
me a henpeck. It makes me honest.
I wish I could see
how noble you'd be...
...if you had as many drawers
thrown in your face as I do.
Delusions of grandeur.
What's that you said?
Well...
...your constant references
to your sexual prowess...
...are nothing if not
overcompensatory...
...and lead me to think that you're a
misogynist who is very insecure.
"Overly-compensatory."
Nobody asked you, Harriet Tubman,
Alice Walker, Angela Davis...
...or whatever sister
you think you are.
Randall Royal, if you don't mind.
Well, "Randall Royal,
if you don't mind"...
...just because I like pussy,
I like the way it feels...
...I like the way it smells...
...and, on occasion,
like the way it tastes...
...don't make me insecure.
Can you even say the word?
- Pussy.
- I'm looking at one.
Come on. Pussy.
- You want to back off?
- Come on, faggot.
Leave him alone!
Stand by your man!
Oh, no, my bad, because actually
you're the man of the relationship.
You made your point. Leave him alone.
He wasn't bothering you.
He was.
Just the fact that we got
two faggots on the bus...
...bothers me.
I won't be too many
more of your "faggots."
Leave him alone.
Mr. Chain Gang in the mix.
"The Defiant Ones."
What's your sign, old man?
"All deliveries in the rear?"
Yo, dog, don't even trip.
"Yo, dog, don't even trip."
Sit down, clown.
Don't trip, dog.
Y'all so serious, brothers.
But a lot of gays think that
Farrakhan is homophobic.
He called for a day of atonement.
Perhaps the minister
will atone for his homophobia.
When I go down the street,
white women clutch their purses...
...cross the street like they
would for a straight brother.
I'm going because I'm a black man.
My sexuality doesn't change that.
- Evan Junior.
- Smooth.
Okay, Smooth.
Tell me how come you're going
to the march.
Because he's making me.
He's making you go?
Otherwise you wouldn't be
going at all?
Hell, no.
I don't even want to go.
Tell him why.
I'd rather be with my homies.
I got things to do.
That's why I'm taking him. The homies
are just killing each other.
I want to take my son
to this historic event.
I want him to see...
...a million black men doing something
positive for the country.
I served enough for this country.
Ten years in the Marines, fought
in the Persian Gulf...
...I even took a bullet.
"Friendly fire" from two homophobic
assholes who suspected that I was gay.
When I woke up, they were laughing
and talking about how...
...they killed two birds
with one stone.
One nigger, one faggot.
You care about blacks?
Yeah, I mean, I'm black myself...
You care about other blacks?
Do you steal from black people?
Man...
Steal? I ain't stole from nobody.
Okay, do you take what isn't yours...
...even from black people?
- Lf it's just lying around the house?
- Yeah, sure, if it's there.
Right. But you say you care
about black people.
- Don't think I have a right to go?
- I didn't say that.
I just want to know what you think
the gay man's role is...
...in the black community.
What's yours?
Why do you say that
stealing's not wrong?
I didn't say it wasn't wrong.
I'm saying the way I got it,
it wasn't really wrong.
Because I ain't hurt nobody.
Right, so you're saying...
...if you take someone's stuff
and don't hurt anyone, it's okay.
You're taking it the wrong way.
I ain't taking nobody's stuff.
It was there.
The money was there, you know?
Nobody was there.
You'd leave money if you saw it?
If it wasn't mine.
Yeah, okay, that's what you say.
Don't know, man.
- Are we going to eat?
- I think I'm getting a hangnail.
It gives me great pleasure
to welcome you to the Little Rock...
...rest area.
Who are you supposed to be?
The welcoming committee
for all the fine sisters.
Oh, please!
You don't recognize me, do you?
I'm an actor.
You played on an episode of Martin!
You were the janitor!
He's famous. You're funny.
Sorry we didn't recognize you.
We've been driving.
- Where are you from?
- Dallas.
I've heard Dallas has fine honeys.
Wait a minute.
Aren't you the only two black
cheerleaders on the Dallas Cowboys?
Well, what do you know?
Is he bothering you?
- You scared me.
- Sorry.
Hopefully Minister Farrakhan will
teach him not to bother ladies.
Are you going to the march?
Yes, it's time for the brothers
to work it out.
No, wait a minute. No!
How do you brothers propose to work
things out without the sisters?
I've heard this argument.
She's got a point.
It's not right to exclude women.
Especially after all the things
our sisters have done for us.
So why are you going?
Someone's gotta raise the
consciousness of these lost brothers.
There are certain questions
which are specific to manhood.
Such as, how can we be better
husbands, sons, fathers and...
...Iovers?
You can start by not trying to put us
womenfolk in our place.
Leave the sisters at home
while you work it out? Please!
Personally, I'm glad to see
the brothers showing some unity.
Thank you.
That's not unity!
What we need is some solidarity.
You cannot name...
...one struggle in black America...
...in which the sisters were not
an active force, can you?
I can. Can you?
It's not about excluding sisters.
It's about trying
to gain your respect and keep it.
By the way, my name is Gary.
- Gina.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm Jamilia.
- You too.
You know, I wish we could go to DC.
Why don't you? I could
help you drive. Follow our bus.
Gentlemen, thank you very much...
...but we do have somewhere
we need to be.
That's too bad.
In that case,
slide me those digits...
...so when it's over I can
run it all down for you.
You don't quit, do you?
This one right here,
can this one be trusted?
I just met the brother.
- What about you? Can we trust you?
- Me?
There's no one more trustworthy
than good old Gary.
Just ask his girlfriend.
My, my.
No, he's right. Ask her.
She'll tell you I'm very...
Trustworthy?
Very trustworthy. Exactly.
Let's go.
Well, you know what?
It's been stimulating.
Nice to meet you.
Bye, brothers! God bless!
Keep up the good work!
God bless!
One love, all right?
Hey, watch CNN, all right? CNN.
Get out of here.
You poured salt on my rap.
- Swing and a miss.
- He's out!
You're crazy.
- You're crazy.
- Tripping ain't easy.
You're still crazy.
Look at Flip! Brother's jealous!
Mr. "I don't cheat on my girlfriend."
I don't.
Please, please, please! You was
salivating all over her.
Oh, come on, James Brown.
You're crazy.
Pop, are you hearing this?!
- I'm hearing this.
- You tell me.
What man ain't gonna try to get
something on the side if he can?
Some men wouldn't.
Name one. Better yet, how about you?
You ever cheat?
Maybe I did, when I was a youth.
So, Jeremiah was a bullfrog.
And no friend of mine.
"Maybe I did in my youth." That's a
yes. How about you?
I never cheated on my wife.
Technicality!
There was a time I was
on this bus with 20 nymphos.
I had to fight them all.
But, no, I'm serious.
Let me think about it.
You ain't got to think about it.
I never cheated on my girlfriend.
I like Cathy a lot.
- How old are you?
- 19.
You got plenty of time.
Brother Jamal over there...
...he didn't ever cheat
on his girlfriend.
Course not. He prays 5 times a day!
Get him to pray for music, since
James Brown's on the other bus.
You want music...
...music you got.
We got music that goes
way back yonder.
Is this it?
Now I want to introduce you
to my pride and joy.
This is my djembe drum.
What's up, man?
The drum is the mother of all music.
Tell them, Pop!
I tell you what I'm gonna do.
I am gonna use this djembe drum...
...to take all you brothers back
to the motherland.
I see a ship
It's a big ship
Ain't no slave ship
I don't see no chains
I don't see no shackles
It's a going-home ship
I cross the ocean
Get off the beaches
I walk in the sand
I step in the grass
Say hello to the python
And the baobab tree
I walk in the jungle
I see the monkey
I see the chimpanzee
I cross the river
I see the crocodile
I come to my village
I see the chief
I see all the elders
I see the warriors
I see the women and the children
I see the fires
I smell the cooking
Hear the singing and drumming
And dance all the dances
I cross the compound
And there at the end
In a little rise
I see home
Jeremiah sees home
And they're glad to see me
Pop! Pop!
Get your ass on the bus.
Memphis.
Listen to your mother.
You should listen to your mother.
That's not how I was raised.
That doesn't matter.
What's happening?
Not much, I guess.
Not much is better than nothing.
Can we get some menus?
Sandy, get them some menus.
Let's get something to eat,
then I'll drive for a while.
I need a favor, George.
- You can't drive the whole way.
- That's not it.
Base calls, tell them I got sick.
Why?
I'm not coming back.
Shit!
What the hell you mean?
I can't do it.
Stop bullshitting me. You're just
trying to go to Graceland.
I'd be safer there.
Meaning what?
Think we'd put you in boiling water
and eat you for supper?
You already have
the African drums in there.
That's the epitome
of cultural disrespect.
I could come back with something...
...anti-Semitic...
Or I could whip your ass.
Which would you prefer?
I'm sorry.
All right, here it is.
Maybe I am a little prejudiced,
but no more than you are.
Want me to stay and prove I'm liberal?
I don't have to prove
anything to anybody.
I think affirmative action
has been fucked up.
I think O.J. is a cold-blooded murderer
who slaughtered two innocent people.
There it is.
And I bet you wish there were
more white players in the NBA.
Let's just get it out
in the open, huh?
I bet you'd like to call me a nigger.
Or, what do you call it?
A shvartzer, whatever it is?
I'll allow you to say it.
I never called anybody that
in my life.
But this bus is going to the Farrakhan
march, and I can't be part of that.
This is not just Farrakhan's march.
He called Judaism a gutter religion.
He said Hitler was a great man.
I wouldn't expect you to drive a bus
to a Ku Klux Klan rally.
So now you're comparing this
to a Klan rally.
Either you'll kick my ass, you'll
cover for me or I'll get fired.
But no way am I getting my
white ass back in that bus.
So what's it gonna be?
If you feel that way,
you shouldn't get back on the bus.
I'll cover for you, Rick.
See you in L.A.
Thanks, George.
Is there a problem?
Sorry, I just never seen this many
people in here before.
Where are y'all from?
L.A.
Long way from Los Angeles.
- We're going to the Million Man March.
- No kidding?
- Guess where these fellas are headed?
- Where?
The Million Man March.
No fooling?
That's what they said.
Farrakhan is the new
black leader, huh?
The new black leader?
Like Martin Luther King was.
You could say that.
Not really.
But he's one of our leaders.
The only one that could pull this off.
What about that stuff they say?
About him thinking the white man
is the devil, that true?
- Yep.
- No.
Not really.
Actually, Farrakhan...
...is pro-black.
That doesn't mean he's anti-white
or anything else.
- I assume you feel the same way?
- Oh, yeah.
- I'm Rodney.
- Evan.
- This here's Mitch.
- How you doing, Mitch?
I'm Smooth.
Evan Junior.
Just Smooth.
What's with the handcuffs?
It's personal.
I can talk for myself.
It's a court order.
Judge mandated that I be
in the custody of my father.
A judge?
It was either community service
and this for 72 hours...
...or me serving a one-year sentence.
So, what'd you do?
I stole something from a grocery.
Like a candy bar or something?
No, like money out of
the cash register.
Damn!
It wasn't at gunpoint or nothing...
But it was still a boneheaded
thing to do. You know better.
How do you know what I know?
I know your mother taught you
better than that, okay?
Yeah, put it off on Moms.
We'll talk later.