On the freeways it's looking
good! No major traf...
BACKFIELD IN MOTION
You touch it again and
you lose the finger.
It's not too late to turn back.
Forget it.
God. I'm going to be wearing
overalls and picking my teeth
with straw.
Hey,  I've seen Hee-Haw.
And now you're gonna live it.
Hee-Haw.
So honey,
where do you think our house is?
Here! Here it is!
AHHHHHHHHH!
I knew you'd like it.
Dish patrol,  they're here.
Just showed up in some old car.
Honey,  you should see
what's she's wearing.
Isn't it exciting.
Our little community
is growing every day.
Think she's nice?
Are you going over?
Are you kidding?
I've been cooking all day.
What are you bringing?
What do you think?
Are you moving in?
Ahhhh,  yeah.
I live up the street.
Great. Well,  I'm kinda busy so...
Look. This wasn't my idea,
alright. You know,
my mother sent me down here and
stuff like that. Joe Dooley.
Tim Seaver.
You play football?
I haven't had much time lately.
Why?
Welcome to Deerview.
We're glad you're here.
Wow.
All this from a can of tuna?
Right here.
No,  you gotta go up higher.
That's too high. Take it down.
A little big more,  a little big
more,  a little big more.
There,  I like it there.
Straighten it out. That's good.
That's good.
Yoo-hoo! Hi.
Everyone around here is weird.
Oh,  they're just trying to be
friendly. They're not my friends.
My friends live five hundred
miles away. Did you ever see away.
Did you ever see Invasion Of
The Body Snatchers?
They were friendly too.
Nice friendly pods.
Yeah. Well,  they do have that
certain game show contestant
glow about them.
You sure you don't want any help?
No. If your dad can do it,
I can do it too.
Alls I have to do is stick
this right in here.
Aces,  Nanc.
Shut up.
Hi. Hi. How are you? Hello!
What is that?
Some people call it lunch.
I don't know. It's a concept.
You haven't made lunch
since I was ten.
Is that a casserole sandwich?
It's tuna,  isn't it?
Is that what you're wearing?
Bag the earring. Let's go.
You won't tell?
Mrs. Seaver?
Yeah. No,  I mean go. It's Nancy.
The company said you'd be here
and here you are.
Oh,  I'm Shelia Evans.
Hi.
Welcome.
Thank you.
I'll get us some coffee.
Great.
Oh,  oh. Come here.
This is your office.
Oh,  I see they gave me
the executive suite.
And which hemisphere is that,
Christine?
Ah,  the southern?
Oh,  Hi. You must be Tim.
Class,  this is Tim Seaver,
our new student.
Everyone make him feel welcome.
So ah,  you're from L.A.?
Yeah.
Have you been with the company long?
Well rounding it out roughly a
week. The company sent me right
here right after the training
course. This is the first job
I've had in like fifteen
or sixteen years.
Wow!
How long have you been here?
Ah,  seven years.
Whoa.
Yeah. But I'm-I'm just a
receptionists. Um,  anyway,  ah,
I went through the multiple
listing and I typed up everything
that's on the market.
Now that includes things that
are in escrow. And I also noted
how long each house has
been for sale.
Man,  this must be a typo,  478 days?
Oh yeah,  sorry.
That should be 578 days.
Hi. I'm Laurie. This is Sally.
Hi.
We're not interrupting are we?
Well,  I...
Good.
Your house is lovely. Just lovely.
Well,  I was thinking about
painting the living room black.
What do you think?
I was kidding. Just kidding.
Well,  I hope you don't think we're
too pushy dropping in like this.
Shelia's told us so much about
you. Well,  not so much.
We know you're from Los Angeles.
Your son goes to Deerview.
You're a widow. But it's the
little things that make a
neighborhood. You know,
like what kind of hobbies you
have,  the kind of food you eat,
that that's any of our business.
No. Of course not.
Kitchen? I'm real thirsty.
So ah,  Laurie's the shy one,  right?
Yeah.
Mrs. Hill across the street's
widow too. You meet her yet?
Oh yeah. We did that widow
secret handshake thing.
You're kidding again,  right?
You caught me with my pants down.
Oh,  we came here for another
reason,  didn't we?
To invite Nancy to the pep really.
Oh that's right.
You do like football,  don't you?
Hmm... you see,
our sons play junior varsity.
Well,  to be honest with you
football's not my thing.
Oh really? And what is?
Well,  if you're talking serious
entertainment value then I'd have
to say access cable. You know,
it's on all the time.
You want to know my favorite.
Okay. It's that Priestess Of Love
Show. I swear to God,
this broad sits there and
She tells you four hundred ways
how to 'boink' your man,  you know.
She's got this really bazaar green
eye shadow on and this tub-top thing.
You can't help but love her.
So,  you'll let us know. Oh,
we would love for you to come.
Well,  thank you. Um,  Listen,
I've got to get some homeowners
insurance. Where would I go?
Huh. Only one agent in town.
Ann Badowski.
We could add flood,  tornado,
infestation and,  of course,
mysterious disappearance coverage.
Oh,  for those unexpected UFO
visitations. Well,  whatever you
got I want it on the economy size
see,  because I'm kinda living on
a limited budget.
You know,  we should rethink that
earthquake insurance.
A 7.5 snaker could annihilate
your home.
Well,  I like annihilation,
you know. It's like my favorite
form of destruction.
Alright,  then. Who do we want to
name as beneficiary?
Um...
We do know the meaning
of beneficiary?
Yes,  'we',  I do. I happen to be
one. My husband died about
a year ago.
Me too. I'm single,  I mean.
Divorced. Kids?
A son.
Deerview High?
Yeah.
Mine too. Boy,  are you lucky
you came in here today.
I did happen to mention that I'm
president of the PTA,  didn't I?
Now,  here is a schedule of our
activities. You'll note the
asterisks. Those are the combine
meetings with the Booster Club,
which I'm also the president.
Yooo,  save me!
Do you have to walk so close?
Yes. So,  this is what Hell is like.
Later.
Oh,  there she is.
Hi!
Oh,  you made it.
Yeah. Hi.
So,  what do you think?
Well,  it's beyond anything
I ever imagined.
I am hot. Anybody else hot?
I think Angie's pregnant again.
Hi,  Darleen!
Are you listening to me?
Little beads of have sweat
dripping down my back.
Okay,  we get the point.
There are our boys.
Oh.
Mine's the blond. Andy.
My Derek's next to him.
Boz is the one with the string stuff.
Boz,  stop it!
How proud you all must be.
Yeah.
G - O... Go!
De-vil's Go!
Go - Go - G - O - De-vil's Go!
Go - Go...
Joe,  who's that girl over there?
The one next from last.
Oh,  that's my sister,  Betsy.
Pitiful,  ain't it?
Thank you,  girls. Thank you.
Let's hear it for the Deerview
Cheerleaders!
And now without further ado,
I'd like to present to you your
coach. Coach Jimmy Cox.
Thank you,  Principal Marsh. Well,
here we are. Another season.
Another championship season.
Boy,  football's kind of a big deal
around here,  isn't it?
The biggest.
We've got a bunch of touch,  smart,
good boys. With your help...
heck,  we could do anything.
Football isn't just a sport,
it's life itself. The fumbles,
the interceptions,  the touchdowns,
we live 'em day to day. I am...
Nuts.
...reminded of a quote from
an old coach of mine...
...Jimmy,  the man who said winning
isn't everything was a weinie.
On a scale of one to ten
how hurt can he get?
Coach Cox can answer all your
questions. There's your boy over
there at the boockers
Hi,  Timmy.
Hey,  Jimmy! Jimmy!
Yes.
This is Mrs. Seaver. Tim's mom.
How do you do?
Hi.
Now,  she's a little concerned
about the ah...
Yeah,  I just want to know if he's
going to play he's not going to
get ripped into thousands
of pieces,  is he?
Now,  I can assure you that
Coach Cox plays a safe game.
Ah,  excuse me,  Howard.
I play the way we need to play.
I know that but...
You wouldn't want to tell how
to run this team,  would ya?
Of course not.
Good.
Ah,  maybe this isn't a good time.
No,  no,  no. Don't go running off.
Actually,  we've been like this
for years. We used to play
against each other.
Oh,  you played football?
You didn't tell you about '76?
I guess it never came up.
See,  it was County Championship
game 1976. Howie here is this big
deal player. Collage scouts come
to see him play. Where were they
from again?
USC.
Yeah,  yeah,  yeah. Anyway,
Howster's QB at Deerview.
Me,  defensive end,  Lincoln High.
I knew there's only way we're going
to win that game. Get in the 1st
half. Deerview's third and goal
at the seventh. I knew Howie was
going to fake left,  so,
he faked left and who do you
think he found on his right?
You?
Oh! It was beautiful.
Sacked and out! Of course,  ah,
I never meant to break your leg
like that. But we won the game.
And that's all that's important.
You bet. Oh,  excuse me.
Thank you for sharing.
I feel much better now.
Me too.
Touch down,  Devils score.
Touch down... six more...
Devils score.
Hey Dooley,  Coach wants to see
you. It's about the fathers
and sons game.
Oh yeah,  right.
I forgot about that.
Yeah,  my dad's already starting
to do sit-ups and stuff.
Well,  they have to.
They're so old. See ya.
I thought you were at the
Dooley's. Guess I was wrong.
Are you okay?
Just tired.
Did you do your homework?
Yep.
Geometry?
I said yes!
Well,  do you want to make
an ice cream run?
No.
No?!
You know the echo's getting
worse in here! Hey!
What's going on?
Nothing.
Well,  something's bugging you.
Why? Because I don't want ice cream?
Is it school?
Why are you doing this?
Is it your friends?
Stop!
I'm just trying to figure out
what's wrong?
You want to know what's wrong?
What's right? We move from home.
I hate my English teacher.
You ask me four thousand questions
a day and there's a fathers
ons//football game coming up.
Oh,  Tim.
You want to help? Give me back our
old life. My old friends.
Give me back my bad!
I wish I could.
You all know how important the
fathers/sons game is to the school
as a found-raiser. So,
I hope all your fathers out there
are getting into shape so you can
beat the sons this year.
Mr. Harris assures me that his
broken ankle is healed and he's
ready to go full steam ahead.
Any of you moms out there who
want to bake for the bake sale,
the sign up sheet's up here.
Let me emphasis that you can not
over do on the brownies.
You know how our men are.
They love their chocolate.
You know baking is something
that any of us can do.
Even us single gals.
So,  without further ado,
I'd like to introduce the man
who's going to lead your sons
to another glorious game,
Coach Jimmy Cox.
What'd I miss?
The bake sale.
Hey,  what's with the jacket?
What? Is it too much?
Well,  not to Annie Oakly.
Tttt.
Thank you,  Mrs. Badowski. So,
we're all looking forward to that
game,  aren't we dads?
You men know we play for fun.
For laughs. Hey,  with nine guys
on the side you get plenty of
rest for substitutions.
But seriously there is that fund
raising side of things. Ah,  ladies,
like Ann said,  we need your help
too. Baking,  the car wash,
ticker sales... Ah,  volunteer?
Mrs. Badowski has sign up
sheets for ya.
I don't bake.
Oh. So,  what do you want?
I wanna play.
I'd like a shot at being
in the fathers/sons game.
I'm sorry,  that's just not possible.
Why?
Well,  it just isn't,  alright?
No,  it's not alright!
My son doesn't have a father and
I want to play. I mean,
I know I'm new to this town and
everything. I just don't get you
people. I mean,  geez,
especially you women.
This is the best you can do?
A bake sale? Don't you remember
like fighting for equal rights?
Equal rights?
Don't let these men push you
around. I want to roll in the dirt.
I want to have some fun.
I want to play football.
Come on,  sit down!
Harry!
Mrs. Steamer!
Seaver!
Mrs. Seaver,  we'd love to have
you play but let's be practical.
It's too dangerous. Look at Mr.
Evans here. Put pads and a helmet
on him. What happens if he
accidently falls on you?
Not a pretty picture,  is it?
No. No,  it's not.
You know you are absolutely right.
Let's lose the dads and what about
a mothers/sons game?!!!
Sign the tardy sheet and
you'll have to bring a note
from your mother.
Okay. Okay.
Sorry. Car trouble.
Mrs. Seaver.
Well,  I would like to continue
our discussion about the mothers
and sons football game.
There is no game.
Well,  in that case,  do the words
sexual discrimination suit mean
anything to you?
Wait a minute! How'd we go from a
football game to a sex suit?!
I'm sure Mrs. Seaver didn't mean...
Can I interject here?
I think I know Nancy better than
anyone else in the room. Single,
alone. I know what it's like to
stand on the sidelines of life.
Even though we can't play Nancy,
we can still cheer the others on.
Well,  I don't want to cheer.
And I don't want to patronized.
I just want to play football.
And if you have a problem with
that,  well,  I'm really sorry but
I'm not going to give up.
Howard? Howard?
Yeah.
You're boy's VP,
tell her how the boys will react.
They'll hate it... at first,
then they'll love the idea of
creaming their moms.
Great. Just great,  Peterman.
Maybe you'd like to coach them.
They're about your speed.
Would you give us a minute,  Mrs.
Seaver? Perhaps Mr. Peterman could
show you our trophy case.
Well,  I suppose I should thank you
for standing up for me.
You don't have to.
Yeah,  you're damn right.
Especially since I know you
weren't trying to help me.
I wasn't?
You were just trying to
get at Coach Cox.
Maybe a little.
Maybe a lot.
Lady,  I take it where ever
I can get it.
No! No,  no,  no!
She's only asking to play against
her son. You can still have
the Varsity fathers
ons game.
It's humiliating! It's un-American!
Look,  you have nothing to worry
about. In order to pull this
thing off she's got to recruit
enough mothers to play.
And you can take it from me there
are not nine mothers in this
town who will do this.
Do you think they'll go for it?
Not a chance.
Mrs. Seaver? You've got two weeks.
If you can't get a team of nine
organized by then I never want to
hear about this again.
Deal!
You guys want one of these?
They're Blue Hawaiis. Oh,  okay.
They're good.
Nancy!
Oh,  Hi,  Joe.
Say hello to camera.
Hello. Hello.
Our lovely hostess.
Good. Good stuff.
Yuck!
Why don't Nancy invite her?
She didn't.
Are you implying I might have
let the word get out? Really.
Let's get this over with.
Hi.
Ahola.
I brought you some cupcakes.
Oh,  that's very very sweet.
Well,  what do you think?
Oh,  it's very festive.
I love what you're wearing,
Shelia. It's very Don't Ho of you.
Thanks.
I'm trying to organize this
mothers and sons football game
thing,  you know.
Hey,  hey,  don't even think
about it. Shelia.
I heard you. We all heard you.
He probably has hair
on his back too.
Hey,  I've been meaning to talk to
the two of you about this mothers
football game...
No.
No really,
don't beat around the bush.
I knew there was an ulterior
motive for this Trader Vic food fest.
Think she'll pull this off?
Actually,  you know what?
I kind of hopes she does.
What are you talking about?
Remember last year's game?
I was so sore afterwards I had
to have the kids tie
my shoes for a week.
Here we go.
What is this?
Teriyaki surprise.
Surprise?
Just eat it. Open your mouth,
shove it in and eat it.
Forget it,  Mr. Harris.
My mom is a total whimp.
He calls them like he sees them.
Joanne,  this is Nancy.
Nancy,  this is Joanne.
Hi,  Joanne,  nice to meet you.
Oh,  I've been meaning to call you.
I work at the aerobic studio
down the street from you.
I thought maybe we could
have lunch or something.
I'm tell you they're not real.
You know I'm glad you brought up
this aerobics thing see,
because I'm trying to put together
this mothers and sons football...
Nancy! Darling,  you're running a
little low on the Ramaki.
Oh and how very thoughtful of you
to point that out to me,  Ann.
Mmm... really different tasting.
What gives it that unusual flavor?
Prunes.
Shelia,  you will be singing the
school fight song at the
fathers
ons football game, //won't you?
I really hadn't planned on...
Oh,  you must. With your voice.
Besides it just won't be a
fathers
ons game without you.
If there is a fathers
ons game.
Oh,  there will be. Oh,  excuse me.
Talk about your basic damage,
Seaver. Your mom is totally weird.
You're mom isn't?
I know what you're doing,  Ann.
What do you mean?
Right. Well,  hey,  you like to be
helpful,  don't ya? Not that I want
to take you away from all of your
socializing or anything but,
could you do me a really big
favor? I've got a couple of
pineapples sitting out in the
kitchen. Could you cut them up
and put them on this plate here?
Oh,  you're such an angle,
thank you so much.
Nancy,  thank you. Great party.
Thank you for coming.
Yeah,  I've got some great shots.
Yeah,  I want you to make me a copy.
I'll come over and play it for you.
Not that I have a VCR or anything.
I'll get you one. Alright come on,
Julie's in the car. Come on!
Bye ladies. Oh,  Laurie,  dearest.
I've notice that you have not
signed up for the bake sale.
Remember,  'nothing says loving
like something from the over. '
Call me. Tootles!
I don't believe it.
She actually thinks I'm going to
be inspired from a quote from
the pillsbury Dough Boy.
You know my son thinks I'm a whimp?
My husband won't let me do anything?
Aren't we tired of being
pushed around?
I want to toll in the dirt!
I want to have some fun!
I want to kick some butt!
Is this some sexual problem?
No. I am not a whimp.
We want to play football.
Are you serious?
Well,  what do we have to lose?
Our kids and husbands
don't respect us.
Well,  that's true.
Besides we all hate baking.
Great!
Yeah,  I'm as coordinated as an ox.
Yeah,  me too. But I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna show those little pigs.
Nancy,  Hi!
Hi!
Look,  if anyone sings the Rocky
theme I'm outta here.
Hey,  boys.
Oh look,  there's Howard.
Really? Look,  keep going.
I'll be back.
I need a wind machine. Okay.
You think it's funny?
Ah,  yeah.
Well,  listen,  Mr. I was A Football
Hero,  how about putting some
of your expertise where
your mouth is.
You're asking for my help?
I am flattered.
Course,  I'll still be the coach,
you know. But you can help with
the strategy.
You mean how to pass and how to
catch? And how to tackle.
Ah,  exactly.
I'll think about it.
I'll be fun you know.
Out there on the grid iron.
Running those plays.
I said I'd think about it.
Thinking's good.
I can except thinking.
She's going to ruin everything.
Seaver's mom comes to town.
She's going to blow it.
Am I in your way,  Seaver?
You got a problem,  Badowski?
Me? Naw. I was just explaining
to them what 'macho' meant.
'Macho' as in manly.
As in Seaver's mom.
Excuse me?
Coach!
I bet she likes chewing tobacco
and tracker pulls.
Don't do nothing,  Joey.
Shouldn't we do something?!
Stay outta this.
Break it up! Break it up!
Break it up.
Ever hit anyone before?
Hurts don't it?
Felt great.
Badowski must have said something
pretty awful to make you go that wild.
Yeah. Something.
Something about your mom?
Lucky guess. I'm also guessing that
right now the earth would open
up and swallow her whole.
Keep that on there.
You and Coach Cox don't get along,
huh. Nancy told me how Cox
broke your leg.
Coach Cox and I aren't the issue
and neither is Badowski.
Let's get back to the part
about your mom.
It's like she's becoming this
different person.
She's always been a little cranked
but ever since we moved here.
It's like this Mothers
ons//football game. I mean she never
would have done that before.
Why can't she just leave things
alone? Just don't make her
come get me,  alright?
I have to,  Tim.
What? Is that part of the Vice
Principal's code of honor?
Give her a chance.
Please.
You won't let it happen again?
Least not this year?
I swear.
Alright. Get outta here.
It's over 24 hundred square feet
and the very best part about the
whole house is backyard here.
I mean,  talk about low maintenance.
Can I go back there?
Sure. Have a party.
What are the neighbors like?
Oh,  they couldn't be nicer.
Oh! Nice doggy! Nice doggy!
His bark is much worse than his bite.
Oh.
Oh yeah. Right there. It feels good.
Hmm...
Oh yeah. Right there. Oh,  Nancy! Hi!
Howard was just showing me how
to get rid of my headaches.
Wow,  I can't wait to see what
you do for hemorrhoides.
Oh lis... oh,  I better get home.
See you.
I'll see you. Ah,  your messages
are on the desk,  Nanc. Bye!
Tim got in a fight at the game.
A fight?
He's fine.
What was it about?
I don't know.
Well,  why didn't you call me?
Because he asked me not to.
Well you still should have.
I mean isn't that part of the
Vice Principal's code of honor?
That's what he said. Look,
Tim is having a little bit of
trouble adjusting and I think that
the Moms/Sons football game is
like setting him up as a target.
Oh,  yeah,  yeah.
I forgot. You got your PH. D
in Child Psychology.
Right. Like it's hard to figure
out that your mom playing football
is embarrassing.
Well,  it wouldn't be if we weren't
so bad. I mean,  if we could get
some help... if you'd help coach.
Whoa,  I know where this is going.
Well,  if you don't want to do it
for us then you should do it
for yourself. Think of the
satisfaction you'd get by beating
Jimmy Cox. By totally seeing him
humiliated in front of all those
people,  you know.
Losing to a bunch of women.
Losing to you. You can almost
taste it,  can't you Howard?
Revenge is sweet. I'm telling you.
It's very very sweet.
Where's my fork?
Mom,  I'm starving!
Coming right up!
You're such a brat.
Potatoes,  please. Potatoes.
Pass the pess.
Here we go. It's an even trade.
So Joe,  what'd you get on that
history test the other day.
You know the one you had on Monday?
The day after Sunday.
Oh yeah. I got a
A 'B'?
A 'D'.
Next time try harder. Okay?
Okay.
You're so lucky. I just don't get
it. I mean,  why do you like
hanging here?
I don't know. I guess I like you.
All of you.
How many bathrooms at your house?
These places are all the same.
Okay. So,  three bathrooms and
only two people.
Want to trade families?
Believe me you wouldn't want to.
Oh yeah,  because if you lived here
it would mean like you're a
brother. To bad too.
We couldn't become friends.
We have potential.
Faith,  honey! Paper towels!
Paper towels coming right up.
Hut,  hut!
Hike! Hey,  next time keep your
head up. That big can on the
right almost juked you.
Is this like a thing with you?
How do you know where I live?
And where I work?
Privileges of membership.
School records.
Or invasion of privacy.
I burn,  do not chop.
Hey,  how's Tim doing?
He's not speaking to me.
Not that it's any of your business.
Boy,  if you act like that
I'll change my mind again.
About what?
About helping you out.
Like you said. Revenge is sweet.
I knew I couldn't be wrong about
you! We're like two peas
in podsville.
You want to run that by me again?
Yeah. We're alike,  you and me.
Trouble makers.
You actually thought something
nice about me? Must be my smile.
Women are really into smiles and
I got a pretty into smiles and
got a pretty damn good one.
No coffee stains or nothing.
Just a little overbite.
Chicks dig that.
Well you know if was shopping for
a horse teeth might really be
an issue but I just want you to
show us how to throw a ball.
She says as she stares at my dimples.
Can we get down to it?
Hey,  anytime.
I'm talking about playing.
So am I.
Football! Would you stop it?!
Okay. Alright. You've got about
a week to put a team together
before Mrs. Marsh's deadline.
And then there's the game itself.
No,  I don't have a week.
We have a week.
Remember we're in this together
right up to your dimples.
Give me some coffee.
Well,  how are we going to
recruit these women?
Well,  if you're going to go
hunting you've got to go
where the prey is.
You mean we have to find a place
where these athletic type
moms hang out?
Hm-huh. Exactly.
Feel the burn. Feel the burn.
One,  two,  three,  four. Breathe in,
breath out. Breathe in.
And elbows up.
Squeeze the beachball!
Squeeze the beachball! Squeeze!
Squeeze! Squeeze! Squeeze!
Squeeze! Visualize that you are
firm! Visualize that you are firm!
Visualize! Visualize! Firm!
Firm! Firm!
Visualize that you are firm!
Great.
I told you they weren't real.
Okay now,  I want you to try and
tackle. Now if you can't don't
worry about it. Just try to keep
your hands on me and hold onto me.
Don't let me run by you. Ready? Okay.
Bag weighed how much?
Good! Good. Very good. Hey,
do you think we're ready for our
workout? You know,
tackling and all that.
We need a quarterback.
Yeah,  by tomorrow. Listen,
I got to go pick up Tim.
You think they'd mind if
we knocked off early?
Hey,  you guys mind if we
knock off early tonight?
Yeah!
I think they can handle it.
Can I get a ride home?
Nancy,  How,  come on in.
Pull up a chair.
Make yourself at home.
Mom,  we need more bread!
Coming right up!
Okay,  Nancy,  present your team.
Alright. Joanne Nelson,  center.
Faith Dooley,  quarterback.
MaryAnn Turner,  tackle.
Laurie Harris,  wide receiver.
Sally Ramos,  wide receiver.
Shelia Evans,  running back.
Diane Anderson,  tackle.
Carol Foster,  end.
Alright,  knock me down!
Hit me hard! Low! Get down lower!
Hot me hard! Hit me hard! Okay,
atop! Stop! Alrgith,  Laurie,
knock him down! Come on! Get him!
Okay Faith,  let's see some
defense. Okay,  Shelia. Okay,
Sally! Okay now,  Nancy!
I think you're starting to get it.
Call a coroner,  we're dead.
Come on.
Ahhh... even my hair hurts.
Come on,  let's get up!
Come on everybody,  let's run a
play! Get up,  gals!
Alright! Let's go.
Let's go! Alright! Sally!
Do a fly pattern to the left.
Shelia,  ten yard button hook.
Nancy,  two second delay and then
Faith will pop it to ya over the
middle. Alright,  let's go!
Okay. Just give me one second
of your time. Okay,  Sally?!
Yeah.
Run really far out and head
for the library.
Oh. Okay.
Shelia you run to where it says
20 on the ground and then stop.
Hut one! Hut two!
They're alright.
They haven't done anything yet.
They're here,  aren't they?
Hey,  Seaver. That your mom out
there? The one in charge?
Yeah.
That's my mom.
Offensive/defensive tackle.
Mine's the tightend.
Too bad we're going to kill 'em.
Hut one. Hey two.
Get your butts over here!
I've decided to take over
coaching you runts for
this mothers/sons thing.
But coach,
what about the varsity team?
Priority,  son. Some things are
just more important.
Alright,  let's do it again!
Alright! Alright,  line up.
Let's go!
Hi. I know it's late but I forgot
to give you your playbook.
Oh,  thanks.
Right. Well...
Goodnight.
Hey,  good practice today.
Well,  yeah. Nice. Earrings,  I mean.
My husband gave them to me.
Your husband?
Yeah,  you know. The dead one.
Eric.
You never talk about him.
Well,  it's not that easy.
You know. It's like talking about
this whole other life.
I wasn't always the town
subversive. I wasn't always a
single parent. Hell,
I single parent. Hell,
I couldn't even find the mayonnaise
in the market. I had to ask every
single time. Look,
it's not your problem.
Man,  I was hoping you were
going to say that.
You are such a sensitive guy,
aren't ya?
What I meant was... I think you're
blowing it way out of proportion.
Don't be so hard on yourself
and on everybody else.
Yeah,  thanks. Well,  I guess I'll
figure out my life some day,  huh.
Maybe you already have.
Well,  it's late.
I should go in.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay. Goodnight.
Bye.
Hey,  I heard you're coaching
the sons now.
You heard right.
That your play book?
Yeah.
This is mine.
You know what they say,  Jimbo...
size doesn't matter.
It's what you do with it that counts.
Alright ladies,  let's get up now.
Let's work on some blocking.
We'll start out with the offensive
line. Now line up.
Go ahead and line up and run a
play. Let's see how you do.
Okay,  ready? Hut one! Hut two!
Okay,  that's it. Alright.
Nancy,  come here. Listen,
that's real good but there's a
couple of things we've got to do
a little bit different.
I'm gonna be you this play,
alright. You did a good job.
I want you to watch me.
Listen,  each of us has a man
across from us,  right?
Right.
Keep that men from out away from
the quarterback. Keep her outta
there no matter what.
Go ahead and play.
Hut one! Hut two!
Okay,  that's great!
That's great. See?
I felt great.
So honey,
is Howard getting cuter or what?
Oh Howard's definitely
getting cuter.
Would you look at my hands.
I mean,  I used to have fingernails.
And what is the deal with this rash?
Bra burn.
Is that like jock itch?
What is jock itch?
It's really gross.
You really want to know?
No!
So Nanc,
what do you think of Howard?
Oooooh!
Whoo-whoo-whoo!
Oh,  what do I think of him or what
do I want the whole town to know?
Excuse me,  guys,
but I am not a gossips.
No but what about like,
a big blabber mouth?
Or maybe busy body?
Or chatterbox?
You forgot yenta.
Oh wow,  they look great.
They don't move. I mean,
they move but... they don't jiggle.
Well,  they sort of jiggle but
it's like a uni-jiggle.
Was I right or was I right. Whoo!
Goodnight.
Does this make any sense to you?
Ahh... yeah,
it's the Statue Of Liberty play.
Oh. Of course.
You know what these are,  right?
Hugs and kisses? Oh,  I know.
It's the offensive and
defensive alinements.
Right. So your quarterback drops
back like he's gonna...
she's gonna make a pass...
You know your birthday's
coming up next week.
I thought you wanted to
talk about this play.
What should we do?
Ignore it.
I was in labor for 47 hours.
This is not a day I ignore.
You owe me. Besides,  remember how
your dad used be no birthdays.
Could we not do this,  please.
Well,  I just thought we'd do
something special. You know you
could invite anybody you want.
Joe. Betsy. For example.
I don't want anything.
Okay,  so no parades and no
fireworks. It'll just be me and
you. I know.
I'll make you some tuna casserole.
No.
Some Ramaki.
No!
You know I love you,  honey.
I know.
Alright,  ladies. When I call off
your names you come up and I'll
give you your jerseys.
And after that Mr. Brooks will get
you the rest of your gear.
Foster,  72.
Yeah. Alright. Anderson,  75.
Oh,  sorry I'm late.
Here are the comps you wanted.
Oh,  why didn't you give
them to the client.
Oh,  you're the agent.
You could be.
Oh,  I couldn't. Harry wouldn't
want me to be out of the house...
Forget about him. We're talking
about you now and your life.
I'm afraid.
Oh what?
Of failing. I mean,  what would
people think if I don't do well?
Who cares? You've gotta over that.
You know,  you can't go living
your life based on what other
people think. There's always gonna
be people who like you and people
who don't. You just have to be
yourself and take it from there.
Seaver,  89!
I appreciate the fact
that you know what...
you could have said...
Mrs. Seaver?
Do you think that... What?
Telephone. It's over there.
Alright,  thanks.
See you later,  Nanc.
Hello. Oh,  Hi,  Maryann.
Where are you? No.
No,  you're right.
Chicken pox is much more serious
when you're an adult.
You just feel better okay. Bye.
You heard.
I happened to be standing there.
Right.
So,  football game's off.
Well,  Nancy,  can't you get someone
to take Maryann's place?
You know I have already asked
every mom in this town.
Every mom? I beg your pardon you
have not asked me.
Of course,  no one every asks me
to do anything. Ever!
Not a cup of coffee.
Not a party. Not a-a lunch.
Ann.
All I do is work.
Work,  work,  work,  work.
And what do I get in return?
Zero,  zilch,  nada.
I just want people to like me.
Why don't they like me?
Well,  could it be you've got a
tendency to overdo everything.
Charge of everything.
The PTA,  Quail Fan Club.
Well,  you're lucky.
Your husband died.
Gee,  I knew I was looking at
this whole thing the wrong way.
I don't mean it like that.
My husband walked out on me.
Do you know how many hours I
filled up wondering what I did
wrong. I wasn't sexy enough.
I wasn't funny enough.
I wasn't pretty enough.
I wasn't smart enough.
I wasn't enough. It's funny,
isn't it? I've been trying so
hard to get everyone accept me
I made everyone hate me.
Nobody hates you,  Ann.
You just kind of wear us all out.
Well,  maybe it's time you put some
of that energy to some good use.
Actually it would be but it's not.
It's perfect.
Ah ladies! Excuse me. And Howard.
Okay,  I've got good news and bad
news. First the bad news.
Um,  Maryann had the chicken pox.
Are you serious?
That means we don't have a team.
No. See,  you're always jumping
to the wrong conclusions.
The good news is I got
us a replacement.
Alright!
Great. That's great,  Ann.
Okay,  you guys.
Nancy,  thank you so much.
It was so much fun.
What to have lunch with us?
No,  I've got to go home and
make dinner for the kids.
Okay,  see ya.
Okay. Bye-bye.
You need a ride?
Boy,  you really like to cook,
don't you?
Hey,  I like to eat.
Yeah but Chinese is really hard.
Not once you get the hang of it.
Why?
Well,  all the chopping takes about...
How come you're not married?
Go ahead,  ask me something personal.
Hey,  you're blushing.
Go sit out there.
Oh,  so now it all makes sense.
What does?
Why you never got married and
why you became Vice-principal
instead of Principal. Why you let
Coach Cox push you around.
Hey,  I like being Vice-principal.
That accident sure changed your
life,  didn't it?
No,  it just just your life and
your whole future.
It wasn't that big a deal.
Tttt.
How do you know?
I guess I don't.
I'm sorry. It's just that I've
heard that I've heard that
I could been a contender' talk
my whole adult life.
And you wanna know a secret?
I wasn't that good.
What about the scout and
the scholarship?
Pipe dreams. That injury got me
off the hook. With my family,
with my school.
With this whole damn town.
I didn't let anyone down.
I didn't disappoint anyone.
I broke my leg. End of story.
No more hero.
I got to just be a guy.
And a very good Vice-principal.
Yeah.
So now that you know my deepest
darkest secrets maybe you'll go
out with me sometime.
Out? You mean like a date?
Because,  I mean,  if it's like a
date date kind of thing,  oh man,
I really... I don't think so.
But then if it's just like a
friend. Get together,
no pressure kind of thing.
Then,  you know,
I-I think that's okay.
Fine. Hey,  if it makes you
feel any better you can pay.
Okay. No,  wait.
Hey,  thanks for the ride.
Can we go back to the part
about where I pay?
Goodnight,  Nanc.
Goodnight.
Hut one! Hut one!
Go,  go,  go!
I see your mom plays better
than you do.
Ha-ha.
Alright. Good job!
You know,  Coach,
they're not that bad.
Maybe you'd like to play with 'em,
Dooley.
Hut one! Hut two!
Whoo!
Good job. Alright,  here we go.
Get back on the line now.
So,  we'll face it.
It's not the Taj Mahal but they,
it's a steal. All you have to do
is use a little bit of imagination.
Okay,  like this ugly wall back
here. That's ugly right?
It is ugly.
So you could just get somebody to
paint like a mural on it.
You know,  I was thinking something
very early Grand Canyon.
What do you think?
Grand Canyon will work.
Why don't you go out there and
take a look. Oh. But before you do.
Listen. Trust me.
You are going to need this.
Hi,  Tim.
Bets.
Yeah?
Ah,  nothing. Are you going home?
That usually happens after school.
Right. Right,  that makes sense.
Glad I could help out.
Um,  see,  I was wondering since we
live so close to each other.
I thought maybe I could sort of
walk you home or walk home with
you or we could walk together.
I'd like that.
Wanna go?
Are we going to go to your
house now or what?
Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah,  yeah.
Yeah. Sure.
Hi,  Nancy. Come on in. So,
Nancy,  can you stay?
No. And neither can Tim.
Mrs. Dooley bought a cake.
Let's go.
It's just a party.
This isn't your family!
Come on Tim,  you come home with me.
No.
No,  I want you to come here.
Who do you think you are to treat
me like this?! Oh,
you don't want to talk. Fine!
Cause I've got stuff to say anyway.
Number one! I don't want you
eating at the Dooley's anymore!
This your home,  you get the
picture! And I don't want you
to ignore me like I'm some sort
of leper or something.
I am your mother!!
And it is not a take it or leave
it proposition. You owe me some
respect. And finally,
if you ever pull the kind of crap
that you pulled over there tonight...
I got it,  alright. Now lay off!
Now,  I'm not going to pretend like
everything's back to normal again
because it isn't! And it hasn't
been ever since your dad died!
Oh,  I'm not going to talk about this.
You need to talk about it!
No we don't!
You have to!
I can't!
Because it hurts! Alright?!
It hurts too much.
I didn't ever get to say good-bye.
Don't you think I know?
Don't you think I'm feeling
everything that you're feeling?
One day the man I've lived
with for 15 years leaves for work
and the next thing I know some
drunk driver makes a wrong turn
and I'm at the hospital collecting
his watch and his ring and his
wallet in some plastic bag.
It will never be the same.
We're not the same.
I can't be mom and dad.
And you can't go over to the
Dooley's hoping they'll adopt you.
I know. I love you,  Mom.
I know you do. I love you too.
Nancy?
Can we still do something
for my birthday?
Yeah,  well,
I thought of a few things.
But,  what do you want to do?
I am dying for some Mexican food.
Ever since we left L.A.
There's that little place right
outside of town.
Let's go. Okay,  hold on a minute.
I'll go get my purse.
I'll be right back.
Okay ladies,  let's talk about
some penalties. Nanc,  up.
First of all,  clipping.
Clipping is blocking from behind.
You can't do that.
Second of all,  off sides.
Crossing the line of scrimmage
before the ball is hiked.
You can't do that either.
Now my personal favorite...
holding. You try and run by me.
Okay.
That's holding.
Okay. You better quit before you
get to illegal use of the hands.
And now for a little defense.
Stripping the ball.
Sometimes when you tackle someone
you just don't want to tackle
them you want to get the ball
loose. Cause a fumble.
Give me that ball.
Let's do this in slow motion.
You come at me. Slow motion.
I'll strip the ball. Watch me.
Aaah,  okay.
A very effective move.
You going out?
With Betsy.
Like on a date?
Maybe. You? Howard?
Maybe.
Tim! Hey,  Tim,  do you wanna a
ride?! No! Too geeky? No. No,
you look just like...
you look very handsome.
You look okay too.
Yeah.
You mean for someone my size.
No,  I don't. Short and beautiful
like the perfect day.
That's what dad always said.
Well,  he meant big and difficult.
You know your dad never cared
about my size or what I said or
who I ticked off and,  in fact,
I ticked off and,  in fact,
I think he loved me because of
those things. You know that I
really loved him too,  right?
Is this some weird way of working
up a mom/son talk about Howard?
No. Well,  yeah,  maybe. I mean,
even it's not Howard it could be
some guy. And I just want to make
sure that you're okay about all
this. Well,  what do you think your
dad would think about this game
on Saturday?
Same as always.
Mom's doing a Lucy Ricardo.
He never said that.
Sure he did. All the time.
Come on. I don't believe it!
Lucy? He was Lucy.
Now are you sure that you're okay
about Mr. Peterman,  you know,
Howard and me?
Nanc,  I heard what you said.
Lighten up. It's okay.
Wreck him.
What happened to dinner?
Movie? Bowling?
Well,  I just want to be
ready for Saturday.
You're ready.
It's not like it's the Superbowl.
I don't want to blow it.
You won't.
How come you're always doing all
this positive thinking stuff?
It's an ugly job but
someone's gotta do it.
I can think positive.
Right.
I can!
Like?
Okay,  like... this place.
I'm starting to like here.
This town? Your home?
Yeah... my home. That sound cool,
doesn't it? My home. My town.
Your town.
You know um,  Eric,  my husband,
he was really a great guy.
I really loved him.
Everybody really loved him.
And what could be better than
being Mrs. Great Guy. But this...
I did this. I moved here.
I made new friends.
I'm raising my son al hell,
I even got a job.
Nobody told me how to do it.
I did it all by myself.
Me. Me. Me.
Pretty gutsy.
You're damn straight it was gutsy.
I mean,  I miss Eric and
everything but I never would have
had the guts to do anything
like this before.
Probably not.
You know what I'm finding out though?
What?
It's just like,  you solve one
problem and then another one comes
along. There's never really any
end to it. There's never time
either. But,  you know what the
beauty of it is?
At least now when I make a mistake
I know it is mine.
You're on a roll.
You're happening.
You're the queen bee. Head honcho.
Big cheese. Top dog.
You've got it all figured out,
don't you?
Yeah.
Me,  me,  me and a little bit more
me and that's all you need.
That's all I need too.
Well,  did anybody ever tell you
you do have a really cute smile?
It's the overbite,  right?
Yeah. Chicks dig that. Howard.
Damn kids.
D-d-d-e-v... I-i...
How's it go?
Will you just calm down.
Hold your breath.
My breath or my breast?
Feels like my last mammogram.
OH! Are you suppose to do that?
This is killing me.
I can't believe guys do this
all the time. Ahh...
Anybody have any mascara?
Wait a minute.
Need some help?
Yeah. Ah! Ah! Ahhh!
Hey... hey,  this looks pretty good.
Hey Nanc,  I saw you last night
working out.
So now I suppose the whole
town knows,  right?
Well actually ah,
I haven't said a word to anyone.
You haven't?
Hey,  it's nobody else's business,
right?
Right.
Okay,  ladies,  huddle up! Look,
the game's gonna start in a
couple of minutes.
Oh goodie,  our first pep talk.
I know you worked hard and you
deserve to win but if you don't
it doesn't matter. We're still
gonna go out for pizza and beer
afterwards anyway.
And anyway winning is not important.
It's how you play the game.
No. It's believing in yourself
that counts.
So let's go out and have some fun.
And now I think your coach might
have a few words of inspiration.
Yeah,  okay. Okay. Well,
I do have one announcement.
Right now,  as of this moment,
I'm quitting as coach.
What?
Because...
Aaah...
You know you've been calling the
shots all along anyway so this
just kind of makes it official.
But forget that crap he said
about winning's not important.
Let's get out there and show them
we're a bunch of tough mothers!
Moth-ers! Moth-ers!
What are we gonna do?
Kill 'em!
I can't hear you!
Kill'em!
This is getting kind of sick.
Devils do it... gotta get get get
to it! Devils do it...
gotta get get get to it!
Devils do it...
gotta get get get to it.
We're the mothers,
we're the mothers rah-rah-rah!
we're the mothers sis-boom-ba!
Ricka-racka firecracker,
rah-rah-rah! We're the mothers,
we're the mothers sis-boom ba!
Man,  hey look mean.
Look,  the jiggle up and down.
Good luck to ya.
Yeah. Play your best.
That's my earring.
They're pierced,  Mom,  not clip on.
You pierced your ear?!
You are dead fish!
It's meat,  Mom. Not fish.
Meat,  fish...
I don't care what it is!
That is ridiculous.
You look like a complete pinhead.
Earring!
I'll never do it again. Mom!
Hey,  nice going,  Ace.
Hey,  it wasn't my idea to pierce
all their ears. They thought it'd
raise team spirit.
Oh man. Hey,  Howard,
we've gotta do something.
Well,  let's get everyone lined up
for the National Anthem.
That'll make them stand still.
No can do.
Shelia's suppose to sing.
What am I suppose to tell her.
She's never seen a boy in and
earring. It's not just
your grandmother.
We need a volunteer.
Me? Sing? The National Anthem?
I don't think so.
Go,  go,  go Moms,  go!
We are set for the first annual
Mothers/Sons football game!
We're set for the kick-off.
The Moms are kicking off to the
Sons. And oh,  look,  kicking off is
none other than my lovely and
intelligent wife,  Faith Dooley.
Faith,  honey,  wave to the camera!
Hi! Alright,  alright.
She's busy. We'll get her later.
Alright,  the ball is picked up ah,
33. Derek Ramos. Oooh,
he's got daylight. The fitty,
the forty,  the thirty,  the twenty,
the ten! He's going to go all
the way,  folds! Touchdown!
Touchdown Sons! And they take a
quick lead six to nothing!
YES!
Ahh. Ahh.
They got one. We get the ball
next. We're still gonna win.
Don't worry about it.
Come on now,  you're okay!
That's alright!
Sorry.
I got it. Alright.
Hut. Hut.
Oh,  I'm so sorry.
You okay,  Mrs. Dooley?
Hey,  Faith. Get over center!
Take the hike from center,  Faith!
Hut! Hut!
Oooh,  intercepted by Fred Badowski.
Way to go,  Freddy!
One,  two,  three.
Come on. One two,  ready go.
Ready,  set. Hut,  hut-hut. Hut-hut!
What'd I do?
Joey's throwing you off
with his count.
Oh.
Don't move before you see
the ball leave the ground.
Okay.
And you're hitting me too high.
Get low.
Okay. Thank you.
Ready set! Hut! Hut-hut!
Hut-hut! Hut-hut.
That's the way to do it,  Mom.
Great job.
Thanks,  honey.
Set. Hut-hut.
Alright. Beautiful move by Tim
Seaver. Really faked his mom out.
Put her in the popcorn machine.
Left her in the mud hole.
And Nancy is down on the field.
You okay?
How'd you get so fast?
I've got motivation.
From Coach Cox?
No. From you.
Well,  whatever I said... I lied!
Oooh,  no good.
Just off to the left. Alright,
that makes it 13 to nothing,  Sons.
Ocme on everybody! Cookies!
Brownies! Get over here!
Now remember what we worked on
the last couple of weeks?
The basics. Don't let them run
the quarter and if it's a pass
get your hands up in the air.
Now,  you can do that,  right?
Right.
Right!
Let's go then! Come on!
Hut! Hut!
Go,  Moms! Hit 'em again!
How's that for motivation?
You guys don't have a pray.
You want me to tell dad how you
broke the CD player?
No.
Then shut up!
Ready,  set... hut! Hut!
That's for the 'B+' in Algebra.
What?
It should have an 'A'. By the way,
don't you ever call me a whimp again.
M-O-M-! MOMS!
Yeah!
Hey,  Ann. He wants you to carry.
I can't carry.
Yes,  you can.
On two. Ready,  break!
Go!
Nancy!
What?
What do I do?
Well,  you stand there...
get the ball and then you run.
Right. Stand there...
get the ball... run.
Run play! Run play!
Go Mom,  go!
I'm running. I'm running.
I'm running.
Hit her low.
Okay. I got her.
Ladies and gentlemen,
she's carrying two young men
towards the goal line!
I'm running. I'm running.
Go! Go!
Alright! Alright!
Why to go,  Mom!
It's up... and it's good! Alright!
And the score is The Son,
13 and The Moms,  7!
Oh,  you guys are doing great!
Alright,  team spirit. I love it!
We are not... I repeat NOT,
gonna to lose to a bunch of
mothers. Do you hear me?!
Come on,  Coach,  it's just a game.
It is not!! It's about honor!
Our honor! See women can be smart.
They can play tennis.
They can be president of the whole
U.S. of A!
But they cannot play football!!
Do I make myself clear?!!
Come on you guys.
Do you have any idea what these
boys are going to be like for the
whole rest of the year if they
beat us here today?
We gotta do it!
Maybe the coach has got a point.
Do you have any idea
what it'll be like
living with them if they win?
Nancy's right,  you know.
We owe it to ourselves to win.
Hell,  we owe it to Nancy.
She's the one who's done all
this and made us believe that
we can do it.
So,  are we going to let her down?
No.
Are we?
NO!
Nancy!
Nancy! Nancy! Nancy!
Let's get 'em!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Let's go out there and
blast the little suckers!
Yeah!
Let's go! Let's go!
Hey,  Tim. Think your Dad's watching?
On the fitty.
I bet he's proud.
Of both of us.
MOM!
Cotcha.
Hey,  let go! Let go!
Let me up! Let me up!
Yeah!
Ready,  set,  hut!
Alright,  they used up their last
time out. We got one left. Save it.
Now,  they're probably gonna run
the ball at us. We need a turnover.
Okay. We did talk about this,
right? Turnovers?
Stripping the ball!
Alright,  in here!
Let's go!
Get out there. Come on! Alright!
Break!
Set! Hut! Hut!
These moms have really done
themselves proud but,
basically they're just running
on fumes at this point.
Again,  the score's 16-13.
It looks like this will be the
last play of the game.
Wait a minute! Fumble!
And the mom's have recovered!
Call time out! Call time out!
Time!
What do we do?
Defense - Defense!
Okay. Here's the play.
Should we let'em tie?
We could lay back on our backs
and die and they still wouldn't
make that kick.
Okay guys,  ready.
BREAK!
Block that kick! Block that kick!
Block that kick!
Get in there and block it!
Block that kick! Block that kick!
Block that kick!
Hut!
Statue if Liberty play.
The old Statue of Liberty!
Statue of Liberty play!
Alright! Alright!
Get'em!
NANCY!
Keep moving! Keep moving!
Alright!
Ah,  you're not thinking...
I've been thinking about it for days.
Here?
Right here.
You're crazy.
And that's why you like me.