[Crowd cheering]
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
prepare yourselves for the match
you have all been waiting for.
[Announcer]
Tonight's main event:
The Royal Reptile
Rumble!
Thank you! Thank you!
Tonight, fighting
out of the blue corner...
at a fearsome 6 feet,
240 pounds:
The dreaded Python!
[Crowd booing]
And in the red corner,
standing at a towering 6'4",
weighing in at
a monstrous 265 pounds...
Will there be anything else,
Mr. Broddick?
Box of Raisinets.
You love him!
The Boa!
I want a good, clean fight.
No kicking, biting or kneeing.
[Bell dings]
- What was that for?
- Fun.
We are here to celebrate,
aren't we?
[Ringing]
Hold on to that thought.
Broddick.
- It's Ramon.
- Who?
- Ah, Ramon!
Como estas, mi amigo?
So what's the ETA on our guest
from Southeast Asia?
- It's loaded. We're leaving.
- I knew I could count on you.
Call me if you have
any problems.
Just remember
this delivery is COD.
A generous compensation
will be awaiting you
and your associates
upon your arrival.
Good.
Patronizing prick.
Stupid cunt.
Did you tell the hack
I said hi?
Believe it or not,
the "hack" has our package,
and it's en route
as we speak.
You still haven't told me
what the package is.
It wouldn't be much of a surprise
if I told you, would it?
Let's move out.
We have a problem back here.
It's awake.
[Man] All right.
Pull it over.
I said Raisinets.
[Creature growling]
What the fuck?
- It's awake.
- It's been shot up with 2,000 cc's of tranq.
It's awake now.
[Creature snarling]
I don't think it's supposed to do that
if it's sleeping.
No, it's not.
This is supposed
to be your job.
- You're going to open it?
- You are. Hit the blue button.
- But...
- The blue button.
Is that thing awake?
The blue button
opens the side panel
just enough to help give this thing sweet
dreams for the rest of the trip.
Blue button.
Come on!
[Screams]
[Beeping]
Oy! These are $500 seats!
We're the ones paying
for the view here!
Get back in your yard and play.
[Snarling]
[Roaring]
- What are you doing?
- What do you think we brought this for?
You see those bullets doing anything?
This will.
Where's the dynamite?
It's right... It's right here.
[Bell rings]
Yeah!
Yesl
[hissing]
Broddick!
- Run out of hot water?
- No!
I just got attacked by
a fucking anaconda in there.
Lucky for you, the bite of
a common garter snake is non-lethal.
You shit.
You know I hate snakes.
Hence, I was merely trying to condition you
for this weekend's hunt.
You're kidding me.
That's what Ramon flew in
from overseas... a snake?
Not just a snake, baby.
This one is a real monster.
And it's all ours.
Unless, of course, you're too afraid.
In which case, the boys and I
will have all the fun.
I said that I hated snakes.
- I never said I was afraid of them.
- That's my girl.
[Squeaking]
Oh!
- Where were we?
- [Phone rings]
[Sighs]
Talk to me, Ramon.
This is Clover Trucking.
You leased one of our trucks.
Is there a problem?
We haven't heard
from the drivers,
and they aren't
answering our pages.
- Why the hell not?
- I don't know.
I can connect you
to the shift supervisor.
- They've lost the trucks.
- Told you Ramon was a hack.
Fat fuck!
Do you realize how much money
I spent for this weekend?
The gentlemen I've invited
are extremely wealthy
and extremely
well-connected.
They are flying out here for the sole purpose
of hunting a giant snake.
What am I supposed to do now?
Offer them an Easter egg hunt?
[TV]...in rural Pennsylvania.
According to local police,
the two vehicles
and the remains of five bodies
were found by state police
earlier this morning.
County officials have
yet to determine whether the accident...
Do you want me to call the boys
and tell them the hunt is off?
No.
Just tell them we're
simply rescheduling
the date and location.
...the contents
of the vehicles.
Sources tell us of huge crates
filled with high-yield explosives,
automatic weapons
and what appears to be
a gigantic pet cage.
For this reporter,
we may be in the beginning
of an appearance by AI-Qaida
in the middle of the heartland
of middle America.
For Channel 15 Action News,
I'm Kent Humphries.
And we're out.
"Inaction News"
is more like it.
AI-Qaida? It looks more
like a big car wreck.
That's why you are
where you are
and I am
where I am, Louis.
Really?
I thought maybe it was
because I am the cameraman
and you are
the reporter, Kent.
[Chuckles]
That's us.
Start rolling.
Rolling, rolling, rolling.
Kent Humphries,
Channel 15 Action News.
So, is the government officially
deeming this an accident,
a multiple homicide
or possibly an AI-Qaida
terrorist operation?
AI-Qaida?
- Yes.
- I wouldn't know. I just got here.
Certainly this is an interesting
position to be in, Agent...
Sharpe.
Now if you don't mind.
Is the government willing to say
anything about the vehicle's contents?
Or about who the men were
and what they were doing?
And any possible connection
to any AI-Qaida
terrorist operation?
I wouldn't know.
I just got here.
So there you have...
So there you have it,
ladies and gentlemen.
You heard it here first
on Channel 15 Action News.
A possible terrorist operation foiled.
Five men in the prime of their lives,
struck down in this
senseless tragedy.
What were their names?
What were they doing?
Why were they here?
Kent Humphries, Action News.
[Siren wailing]
Outstanding.
Agent Sharpe,
what do you think of this?
Do we tag this
as body number six?
I think it's what's left of bodies
two, three, four and five.
- What's that?
- Scale.
Found it in the case.
That's a big scale.
It's a big case.
What is that?
I thought you shut off number 6.
I did.
What the hell?
Aaah!
Carl!
Carl! Carl!
[Screaming]
Carl!
Carl! Carl!
[Screaming]
[Carl groans]
[Roaring]
[Screams]
Agent Sharpe! Agent Sharpe!
Would you mind putting
my evidence back?
Sorry. I found this
in the back of the truck.
Where exactly does that lead?
That's one of the access tunnels
to the Philadelphia
water treatment plant.
Thank you, Deputy.
You should clean up. You got
a piece of liver on your chin.
Right.
Maybe I should.
Looks like it's some sort
of tranquilizer dart.
But for what?
I'm not sure yet.
But whatever it is, it woke up.
Agent Sharpe, I just got a call
from the treatment plant.
Apparently,
they were just attacked.
Attacked by what?
They said a giant snake.
Call the plant back.
Tell them I want
this entrance sealed,
all main lines
connected to it turned off,
the facility itself evacuated.
Are you asking me
to have them turn off
the only major source of water
for this half of the state?
I'm ordering, not asking.
I don't mind telling you
that people in this state
get a little upset
when their toilets don't flush
and the sinks are dry.
I see.
We'll need maps and diagrams
of every aqueduct, pipe and tunnel,
all ways leading in and out of that system.
If that thing's down there, I'm not about to let it
back out,
not until we can call in
some serious firepower.
Call in two reserve units.
Have the highway patrol lock off
all traffic within five miles.
Then I want everything we've got
on the Larson project.
That was a CIA project gone bad.
A couple big snakes
got loose in Russia
and wiped out the entire team.
- Just get me the file.
- Right.
And get me Monica Bonds.
[Woman]
I don't work out.
Two minutes isn't bad,
but I can beat it.
Tyler here's half fish.
Yeah? I bet I can take him.
I don't think so, cupcake.
I got 50 bucks
that says I can.
I'll take that action.
- Make that two.
- This'll be sweet.
Tyler was in Navy Seal school,
before he got discharged.
Really?
I've done a little
Navy ordnance
and mine-sweeping myself.
- You searched for mines?
- Yep.
- With Navy divers?
- Nope.
Dolphins.
[Girls cheering]
[Guys cheering]
Thirty seconds!
We only have 30 seconds!
Come on, buddy.
Speak to me. Are you all right?
Here. I know CPR.
I don't know what you did to him down there.
Just stay back.
You all right? You okay?
Did I win?
Bro, you got spanked by a chick.
Thank you. Thank you.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Thank you.
Monica Bonds?
Who's asking?
Agent Sharpe wants to see you.
There's a car waiting to take you to the airport.
- How are things at the institute?
- Great.
We got three new dolphins
coming in next month.
Working hard and making some real progress.
I can see that.
I didn't have time to put a full ensemble
together.
I appreciate you coming here
on such short notice.
With you, Alan, it's always short notice.
What are we doing
out here in the backcountry?
Your boys told me
to pack for Philadelphia.
How well does your equipment work out of the
water?
Why do I get the feeling
you're about to ask me
for four years of research?
Haven't had a chance to field-test it
out of the water yet, but
the sensor pads were designed
for wet or dry applications.
It should work fine.
Well, you're about
to get your field test,
compliments of Uncle Sam.
What kind of doctor is he?
Dr. Emmett is one of the world's leading
herpetologists.
That's kind of creepy.
You haven't even met the man.
In my book, people who
play with snakes are creepy.
It's locked. Maybe there's another entrance.
Emmett?
He's probably got the whole crazy, bug-eyed,
Christopher Lloyd, Jeff Goldblum
mad scientist thing going on.
Pasty skin, doesn't see the sun much.
Definitely has social interaction issues.
Agent Sharpe?
Yeah. No.
He's...
Alan Sharpe,
Federal Bureau of Investigation.
And this is Monica Bonds with
the Miami Aquatic Research Institute.
Hi.
Pleased to meet you.
Please come in.
Thank you.
[Beeping]
Impressive lab.
It used to be.
I'm working out of pocket
for the moment.
The place requires constant funding.
I know the feeling.
Doesn't it bother you,
working with these things?
I mean, one bite and you're history.
Snakes are like other creatures.
Respect them, and they'll respect you.
You have to know what you're doing,
especially with the poisonous kind,
like the one you're tapping there.
[Hisses]
I understand you've grown
a rather large snake
here on the premises.
She's a constrictor...
a Scarlet Queen boa.
May we see her?
Mm.
[Buzzer sounding]
Follow me.
[Beeping]
You need all this for a snake?
You might want to stay close.
It's a little smaller than I imagined.
This isn't Betty.
This is Betty's lunch.
You feed snakes to snakes?
I inject the food snakes
with a dose of venom extract,
which is then digested
by the Scarlet boa.
- Won't that kill her?
- Doses are minute.
Absorbed into her bloodstream
before she knows they're there.
Her system then works
to create an antibody
which I can then harvest.
Betty is the largest
constrictor on the reserve,
probably the largest
Scarlet boa on the planet.
And she produces a vast amount
of antibody for my research.
You're creating
an antivenom.
Trying to, anyway.
It's all extremely
interesting, Doctor,
but hardly
the reason I came.
Where's the boa?
[Chuckles]
She's standing on him.
Shit!
Aaah!
[Shrieks]
[Roaring]
Outstanding.
This is big.
And big is nice.
Well, color me
officially curious.
Assuming we didn't come
all the way out here
just to see some gigantic snake,
I'm dying to know
what kind of situation
could possibly require the use
of his boa and my implants.
Doctor Emmett,
how well would your boa perform
in an uncontrolled environment?
Well, I wouldn't know.
She's the first of her kind
to be born and raised entirely in captivity.
- Would she hunt?
- Absolutely.
Snakes, no matter how they're raised,
have the instinct to hunt.
It's a matter of survival.
In that case,
I'd like to use your boa
to help me find this.
Here comes the party.
[Tires squealing]
My good friend Tex from Lubbock.
Mr. Foley...
our military's greatest sniper.
Try not to stare so hard, Eve.
[Tires squealing]
- Mr. Danner and...
- His son James.
Wife took the truck.
Good old family get-together.
I thought there was one more.
There is.
Littlefield,
master huntsman.
Gentlemen,
glad to see you all could make it
to our little... safari.
[Broddick]
I apologize once again
for the last- minute
change in venue.
Luckily, rearranging one's travel plans
becomes a lot easier
when one has access to their own jet.
A series of unfortunate events
has somewhat complicated
the hunt I promised
to deliver to you.
However, being that
I am a man of my word,
I've decided to do one better.
That's why I'm going
to deliver you to the hunt.
Babe, would you do the honors?
I'm sorry. Would anyone else
care for a drink?
We are fully stocked here,
so choose your poison.
An ashtray and a beer.
Make it two.
I'll have a Sprite, please.
Can I have a cold one,
too, actually?
Uh-huh.
- And for you, Mr. Foley?
- Surprise me.
Since this is my first time
hunting this particular predator,
I thought it only fitting
that I invite those associates
who would truly appreciate
the experience.
And I assure you
this is a once-in-a-lifetime, gentlemen,
an experience that will
truly separate the men...
from the beasts.
We are hunting
one of the most cunning predators on this
planet.
We are the knights
that are going to slay the dragon.
If you take a look inside the expedition
dossiers my beautiful associate Eve
has prepared, you'll see I've taken the liberty
of mapping out a few routes.
We will be landing outside Philadelphia
in approximately two hours.
Eyes on your own paper.
From there we shall depart
for the hunt at 7:00 a.m.
So, you're telling us
that this thing is on the loose
and that you
are going to find it?
Exactly.
The only thing that
you need to concern yourselves with,
gentlemen, is your aim
and how you like your snake...
belt, boot or wallet.
Well, in that case,
gentlemen,
ma'am,
to the hunt.
To the hunt.
[Sharpe] The Philadelphia
water treatment plant
won't let me go after this python
by spraying poisons or chemicals
near the water supply.
I'm not about to send armed men blindly down
there so they can become snake bait.
But with your expertise and boa
and your equipment,
I believe we can successfully locate
and eliminate that python.
Using my implants,
we can track the boa
as it tracks the python
and see every move she makes?
- Exactly.
- Let me get this straight.
You want to attach that to my boa
and use it to hunt down
the python that this belongs to?
That's the stupidest idea
I've ever heard.
Is it? The Navy trains seals
and dolphins to sweep for mines.
The Army uses dogs for security
and tactical engagement.
It's a hell of a leap from dogs
and dolphins to wild reptiles.
It's not as great a leap as you think.
The CIA has been conducting
extensive tests
on the potential
combat and covert ops
applications with specimens like yours.
Why doesn't the CIA
use its own specimens?
Their point man on the project
was forced to take
an unfortunate "leave of absence"
during a mission in Russia.
The project's dead.
So we're the best you got, huh?
Yes.
I guess the question now is
whether that stuff's actually going to work.
I've been successfully
using the implants
on bottle-nosed dolphins for months.
With the digital microcam,
audio sensors,
and GPS monitor in this unit,
we can practically monitor
your boa's every move.
And I've called in
military reinforcement
to back up our operation.
Most snakes are territorial,
especially the big constrictors.
Your point being?
Take two scorpions,
put 'em in a box,
they're both going to want
to own that box.
They'll fight till
one of them dies.
So your boa will
attack that python?
If she picks up the scent,
she'll attack, theoretically.
Then what?
After the boa's done her job,
she'll be returned to the lab.
After she's been
immobilized, of course.
- Immobilized how?
- That you'll have to let me look into.
We better move.
It's almost dark,
and, unlike most snakes,
the constrictors
are corpuscular.
Sorry, I must've skipped
biology class that day.
They're mostly active
at dusk and dawn.
Your python is
already out of the tunnel.
Impossible. I've got three teams
working with local authorities,
shutting off every inch of pipeline
and tunnel in the area.
Agent Sharpe, judging by
the size of that scale,
we're talking about
an 80 to 100 foot reticulated python.
If it wants out, it's getting out.
[Roaring]
[Roaring continues]
~~ [rock music on stereo]
[Thumping]
- What was that?
- What?
No, I heard something.
All right. Touch my car again,
and I'll kick your ass.
Yeah.
No, no, no, wait. Wait.
Relax.
Let Lester take over.
Who?
Lester. You know...
You named your dick Lester?
Well, not me.
Actually Candace did.
One night we were...
Okay. No.
Total mood killer.
You know, I liked it better
when it was just you
and me
and Lester.
Mmm.
[Snarling]
Aaah!
Mmm.
Brian, don't stop.
Oh!
[Slurping]
Oh! Oh!
Give it to me, Brian.
Aaah!
Good. Keep me posted.
Tracking's good.
[Sharpe]
Is that the immobilizer?
Stun spike.
Hit the remote, she gets 80,000 volts.
Should knock her out.
Can she survive that much voltage?
Worry about her surviving your equipment.
We're only surgically attaching
the contacts and sensor pads.
She won't even know they're there.
I promise.
All right.
How's she doing?
Her heart rate's not where it should be.
Breathing's shallow.
Implanting that equipment took a lot out of her.
She lost a lot of blood.
Is there anything we can do?
Just wait and see.
Workers at a local
water treatment plant
just a few miles from here
were killed today in what
government officials are deeming
an "accident."
But it is the opinion of this reporter
that there is something more pungent
than the fetid smell of stale humidity
in the air tonight,
and that's the stench
of government half-truths.
In a time when lies can cause war
and wars create deception,
we need something more than... facts.
We need something more than
government stories about
"accidents."
We need the truth.
This is Kent Humphries,
Channel 15 Action News.
[Clicking button]
Ohhh...
- Wanna take it again?
- Weren't you rolling?
Yes. It's just that...
I thought you were...
It was a little,
you know... big.
A little much.
Hard-hitting journalism is always "big."
That's what real news is, Louis...
sensationalism in its purest state.
Well, Kent, I'm not sure
how this "routine" works.
I am creating my own signature
journalistic style, Louis.
Dan Rather
has a signature style.
Walter Cronkite
had a signature style.
But this...
makes you look
like a schmuck.
Really?
You know something, Louis?
You are frigging fired.
Not again.
As of now.
You can't fire me.
I can this time.
You've crossed... the line.
[Cell phone beeping]
No reception?
What the hell do I pay
these idiots $200 a month for?
$200?
Maybe you should
get a better plan.
You know what?
I'm going to keep walking until I find a signal.
Then I'm calling Jack Dauner at the station,
and I'm going to have you fired.
Do you understand me?
I'm just trying to help you
be a better reporter.
Your next gig will be
cable access, Louis.
Besides, Jack hates you
much more than I do.
[Phone beeping]
Kent Humphries
for Jack Dauner, please.
Hello?
[Static, beeps]
Goddamn it!
[Heavy breathing, rustling]
Louis?
[Snarling]
So, did you finally get a signal?
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
So, tell me more about your antivenom.
It's a universal antivenom, hopefully.
Most are created to counteract
the toxins of a specific species.
So, consequently,
a large number of victims
die needlessly every year,
because they can't help identify the snake that
bit them.
The situation's much worse
in Africa and South America,
regions with large concentrations
of poisonous snakes
but which lack the financial means
to have the antivenoms on hand.
Seems like someone
would have to have
some pretty strong
personal reasons
to devote their life
to such a cause like that.
Well, if I can help save one life,
it'd be worth it, right?
[Rapid beeping]
[Snake moaning]
Metabolics are up.
Vitals holding.
She's coming back.
[Sharpe] Cops just found
what was left of
a couple of necking teenagers
in their car.
We also got word about
a missing news reporter.
You were right.
The python got out.
How much longer will this take?
We're done with the procedure...
Good. Let's get
this show on the road.
She's still recovering.
She hasn't gotten used to the equipment yet.
Look, at this point, I'd settle for her
just finding the python.
- We'll take care of the rest.
- You mean "kill."
That was pretty much the plan.
It's attitudes like yours that are the reason
why people are so scared of snakes.
Instead of trying to understand them and
study them, they beat them with a stick.
I don't have time to stand here
and argue reptile rights with you.
In case you haven't been paying attention,
that thing is killing people.
How do I know your trigger-happy grunts
aren't going to shoot Betty?
I'm running short
on options and patience!
If you've got another solution,
I suggest you offer it.
Instead of shooting
to kill, use this.
Megaketamine.
It's an animal tranquilizer.
It'll save the life of the python and my boa.
We don't even have to
use the stun spike.
I've got two of these.
Two or three doses, they'll sleep for hours.
You were the one that said
the CIA was interested in studying giant
snakes.
I'd imagine they wouldn't mind
their own guinea pig to play with.
All right.
We'll make every effort
to capture this thing alive.
But if it comes down to a choice
between saving human lives
and saving that snake,
I'm siding with my own species.
Now, this is
a beautiful day to hunt
and... kill something.
Easy there, good friend.
First, let's check out the scenery.
Open it up.
All right, driver.
Hold for my signal.
Quick review.
Those tunnels down there go for miles.
We could spend the next 12 hours
trying to find where
that thing went topside.
All we can do is deploy your boa
and hope it picks up the python's trail.
Agent Sharpe,
you're going to love this.
Trucking company finally gave
us a name on those vehicles.
Broddick.
Founder and sole owner
of Broddick Casinos
and notorious
big game hunter.
Notorious, indeed.
Lock and load, boys.
We're in python country.
[Sharpe] Fish and Game department has a
file
two inches thick on this guy.
He sponsors weekend hunting parties
for rich gun nuts
with nothing better to do
than shoot game
in controlled conditions.
That's his python down there.
That at least answers the question
of who'd be dumb enough to let
a giant python out of its cage.
Let's hope two wrongs
do make a right.
Strike force team stand by
until I give the all clear.
- Ready to kick some ass, sir.
- Outstanding.
Open her up!
[Door beeping]
Talk to me, Doc.
What's she doing?
It's got to be a reaction
to those implants.
Elevated cardio and metabolic rates.
I never should've let you
talk me into this.
Me? My equipment is perfectly safe.
Your equipment is killing her.
There she goes.
Microcam and audio plugs are up
We're broadcasting full picture and sound.
GPS puts her out about...
400 feet ahead of us.
We can see everything she does.
Congratulations, Monica.
I couldn't have done it without
the doctor's help... and Betty's.
Your equipment is incredible.
The equipment...
Audiovisual thermal retrieval unit.
Yeah, that.
Thanks, Doc.
[Sharpe] Enough patting
each other on the back here.
Pack your gear and let's get ready to track this
python.
Let's move out.
Clear!
[Tracking device beeping]
Boa's about a hundred
yards ahead of us.
Let's move out.
Maintain a minimal distance
of 50 yards at all times.
Remember, the name
of the game here
is control and containment.
Shoot only
if you have to.
We want to take
this python alive.
Seal us in!
She's moving faster
and breaking off to the west.
Your boa seems to be
doing her job.
If the scent's out there,
she'll find it.
Shit! We just lost the link.
Hold up!
I'm not getting a visual.
Where did your snake go, Doc?
I'm not sure. She could've picked up
the scent already, unless...
This...
This general area
is under where it attacked
the teenagers and the reporter.
Pythons change their feeding ground after
each kill.
So if the workers were attacked
in the main service tunnel,
it may have staked out
this adjacent area.
How do we know the python
will return to these tunnels?
We don't. Another hour, the sun's
going to be pretty strong out there.
It'll seek out the coolest place possible.
Let's just hope when it does,
it comes back down here.
Yeah.
[Typing, beeping]
Keep your eyes peeled.
Okay, we'll split up here.
Dad? Dad.
Dad!
I told you to do that back at the plane.
Or you'll have to wear
a catheter like your old man.
This ain't one of
your dumb-ass video games.
Make sure you wait
until you get a kill shot.
Yeah, I'll remember.
Oh.
God, I hate you.
You travel light.
I don't believe in wasting bullets.
One?
I never needed more.
I did a Google search
on pythons last night.
Apparently, when they squeeze you,
they can feel your heart beat.
The faster your heart beats,
the tighter they squeeze you.
Just remember what I told you.
Show no fear.
[Birds squawking]
Broddick, hold up.
We've got movement back here.
Stay put.
We'll circle back and flank you.
Eve, what's your position?
We're on your left, babe.
I've got you.
Possible sighting behind us.
Push ahead of me 50 yards.
Stagger the line. Wait for my signal.
Copy that. Let's do it.
There it is, boy!
Go get it!
What are we
waiting for?
Broddick's signal.
Oh.
Guy like that has it all...
his own casinos,
a tasty biscuit like her,
and now first shot
at killing that snake.
And we're just going to sit back
and let him take it.
Fuck that.
Damn it.
Okay, AV link's back.
Finally. Let's move out.
Move out.
[Emmett]
Where is she?
I can't tell. Damn it!
I lost the signal again.
Shouldn't we wait for them?
And stay here all day till Blondie
gets her Game Boy to work right?
Let's find this thing,
tag it, bag it and get
the hell out of here.
These retaining walls are between us and the
boa,
but it's not on the GPS.
They're disrupting the signal.
Has anyone seen our soldiers?
Broddick, we have a problem.
Foley just went AWOL.
Tex took off after him.
Amateurs.
Foley!
Fuck.
Foley, come back!
Aaaah!
What happened?
Mr. Foley, what happened?
Where is Tex?
I don't know.
When I got back, he was gone.
I have two very simple rules
here on this hunt.
Number one:
Never leave your team.
Number two:
Stay the fuck away
from my girlfriend.
Who's firing?
My boy's got him on the run!
[Yelling]
Shoot to kill, boy, not to wound!
Let him have it!
I've been waiting 15 years to use this!
Fire in the hole!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
Congratulations, James.
I'm sure this will look wonderful stuffed and
mounted
on the wall of your father's den.
- It'll look great above the fireplace.
- Shut up.
Now that we've completely
lost our tactical edge...
[rustling]
Whoa!
It's just me, boys.
I think I found where our snake went.
If I were a disgusting 80-foot reptile,
those tunnels are
exactly the kind of place
I'd go to wait out the sun and find a drink.
Then that's where we're going.
Tunnel maps are in the van.
Let's fall back
and reload for round two.
Dad!
[Sharpe]
Repeat: Halt current position.
Please respond.
Interference must be messing
with the radio frequency.
That or those jar heads decided
to play hero and ignore me.
AV signal's back.
Betty's really on the move.
She must be
hunting something down.
Work, you $10 million piece of...
Wait. GPS is picking up two more signals,
both inside the plant perimeter.
One's moving faster than the other.
She found the python.
Unless she found your soldiers.
Soldiers, read me!
Repeatl We've lost contactl
So, Rock, Paper, Scissors?
[Distant hissing]
I don't see anything.
I sure in hell hear it.
[Distant hissing]
Now where?
Uh, uh...
- Which way did they go, Monica?
- I don't know. It's scrambled.
- Get that stun spike ready.
- AV's back.
Oh, God. Betty's right on top of them.
Light her up, Doc.
This is a one-shot deal.
I spike her now, she's out for hours,
if she survives the voltage.
- Excuse me?
- [Banging]
[Screams]
[Monica] Now left.
No, right!
Where the hell are we going?
[Snake roaring]
[Gunfire]
Look!
They're sitting ducks in there.
- Emmett, pull the trigger!
- Shoot the pipes.
What?
[Screeching]
[Screeching continues]
[Yells]
[Screaming]
Give me your radio.
Soldiers, listen to me.
Constrictors use heat to see.
They rely on thermal differences.
Shoot the pipes.
A burst of heat or cold can disrupt their vision...
- Shoot the pipes?
- Shoot the pipes!
Use the heat
and the steam for cover.
[Soldier] We're clear, but we lost
Hoffman and Montgomery.
Copy that. The two of you continue until you
reach the surface exit. [sighs]
I gotta hand it to you, Doc.
That was some quick thinking under pressure.
You saved two men's lives...
and our spike.
Let's keep moving.
Damn it.
Mmm.
You having fun yet?
I'd be having more fun
if we could ditch the weekend warriors.
- This damn thing is stickin'.
- Here. Use mine.
What are you gonna use?
I think it's time to turn up
the heat a little.
Ooh!
We got one hour of daylight left, if we're lucky.
Hot enough for you?
No. Why don't you do me a favor
and kick it up a few notches, pops?
You boys like
your meat extra crispy?
- Got to get me one of those.
- Oh, man!
Whoa.
No, no, no.
- May I ask you a question?
- Sure.
Why dolphins?
- Why do I work with them, you mean?
- Uh-huh.
Well, they're intelligent, social.
They interact well with humans.
Guess it makes it
a little easier to get to know 'em.
So, what about you?
Why snakes?
Well, they're intelligent.
They're, uh,
pretty independent.
Occasionally known to have bad tempers,
and not particularly social.
They keep their distance...
from humans especially.
[Chuckles]
You all right?
Yeah. Just a little pissed.
Want to take five?
Good plan.
Truth is, if you
really want to know,
I lost someone very close
to a snakebite.
When I was six,
I traveled with my family
through South America.
We were staying in this village
outside of Buenos Aires.
One night, my little sister
goes to get a drink of water,
steps on a pit viper that was curled up
under the bathroom sink.
The village doctor couldn't figure out
which antivenom to administer.
By the time my dad did the 15-mile drive
to the nearest hospital,
she was already...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I guess I figured that,
working on the antivenom,
I'd learn something about them.
- How's that working out for you?
- I don't know.
For starters, I've learned that I gotta
get out of the lab more often.
[Sharpe] I hate to interrupt getting-to-know-you
time, but could we keep moving?
Betty's sitting tight,
[tracker beeping]
But there's another signal
moving toward her.
It must be the python.
What's the location?
I don't know.
I think she's in some sort of service tunnel or...
Diversion tunnel.
Look.
She's in one of these two passages
located underneath the main pipe tunnel.
- They're connected by this link.
- Part of some overflow system.
- If we could seal off that level...
- Both snakes would be contained.
But who's going to volunteer
to be trapped in those tunnels
while trying to locate and sedate
two super-sized reptiles?
We don't have to send anybody in.
We flush them out.
How?
We flood the system. We force them
to go where we want them to go.
The sublevels both drain
into this underground reservoir here.
Your men could go in
and bat cleanup with tranquilizers.
All right.
Kosnetova, you there?
Listen up.
I need sublevel diversion tunnels 1 and 2
sealed off immediately
and all teams mobilized
to the reservoir junction 27B
in preparation
for target recovery.
I need it all yesterday.
We don't have a second to spare. Copy?
I'm on it. Out.
Boys and girls,
time to move.
Let's trap this rat.
We've got AV back.
It's weak, but it's...
- Damn!
- What?
- I don't think you want to see this.
- What is it?
Looks like the python's
trying to get busy with your boa.
[Growling]
She's the only species
of boa that lays eggs.
I've tried to get her to mate, unsuccessfully.
Nothing's worked.
It looks like she's putting up
one hell of a fight now.
- Ew, is that his...
- Vestigial hind leg.
The male python uses them
like spurs during mating. Oh, that.
[Snakes growling]
I'll go check it out.
Mr. Danner, you and James
go with him.
Maintain radio contact at all times.
Oh, and, Mr. Danner, you're in charge.
[Monica] Looks like the boa's on the run.
Damn it. We need her to keep
that python interested
long enough for that sublevel
to be sealed off.
He's still interested.
The python's following her.
I can't believe I'm condoning the use of
my snake in laying a man-trap.
We've got company. GPS is picking up
three more signals in tunnel 2.
Kosnetova, come in.
We're getting multiple signals in the tunnels.
You send somebody down here?
Kosnetova, do you copy?
Whoever it is,
we gotta get them out.
In three minutes, that tunnel's going to be filled
with several thousand gallons of water.
Then there's still time.
Stand back, boy.
I'm in charge. [groans]
Anyone else get the feeling
that we're completely lost?
Give it a rest.
[Growling]
[Pipes creaking, water running]
Where?
[Alarm blaring]
- Here, here!
- I got this.
[Alarm blaring]
You know, that can't be good.
Someone's coming.
Or something.
One shot, one kill.
Nothing more,
nothing less.
Good night,
[whispers]
My love.
[Monica screams]
[Coughs]
[Monica sobbing]
Outstanding.
Sharpe! Sharpe!
Holy shit, Foley.
Whoops.
- He's dead.
- Who the hell are you people?
- Which one of you is Broddick?
- He's upstairs. He's in charge.
Save it.
[Snake growling]
[Yelling]
[Growling]
You got a gun in your hand,
you idiot! Use it!
Dad!
[Yelling]
That's right.
Open wide, you son of a bitch!
We've got to get out of here.
Come on!
[Yelling]
[Steam hissing]
Hold up.
Give me some more light over here.
Baby, look at this.
I'd say your snake didn't come here to drink.
She came here to nest.
Yeah?
Well, there's only one problem.
The snake I ordered wasn't female.
[Hissing]
- These must be the water tanks.
- There's dozens of rooms like this.
- Shit!
- What is it?
I forgot the bag
and the monitor and...
[snake growling]
Doesn't matter.
Let's go!
There's no way out of here!
- You know how to swim, don't you?
- What? Wait!
Oh, shit!
[Broddick]
Okay, baby.
Let's put the egg back
where we found it, shall we?
[Hissing, growling]
Aah!
Eve!
[Grunting]
[Yelling]
[Clicking]
[Snake growling]
Stay with me, baby.
Be right there.
[Moaning]
[Gasping]
[No audible dialogue]
I'll get her for you.
[Coughing]
That... That was amazing.
You should see me do it
out of the water sometime.
- I'll be right back.
- Where...
There's a grate about 60 feet that way.
- I think it leads to a different room.
- Let's go for a swim.
Okay.
Where's the hell's the cavalry?
Well, I'd say we either
go after the python
and your boa without
any radio or tracking support
or we call it a day
and get the fuck out of here.
Your call, Doc.
- Who the hell are you?
- I was about to ask you the same question.
Broddick.
- Have we met?
- Nope.
Asshole! Do you have
any idea what you've done?
Whatever it is, I'm sure it's nothing
compared to what I'm about to do to you
if you don't get the fuck out of my way!
Let him go.
I said, let him go.
Mr. Broddick, you're under arrest for poaching
and illegal animal importing.
Take him away.
You all right?
Then let's go. Come on.
[Snake snarling]
We went to 27B.
Nobody was home.
- We've been following you ever since.
- Sharpe's dead.
We know.
We found his body in the reservoir.
You didn't happen to find the AV monitor
down there too, did you?
No. But we've got
your laptop equipment
up and running at
our camp in Philadelphia.
We'll be there
in 10 minutes.
Asshole.
[Laughing, shouting]
It's not a toy, huh?
[Beeping]
And we're back in business.
Well, sort of.
I've got GPS and audio.
Visual's basically a bust.
Implants must be damaged.
- Location?
- About four blocks east of us.
What's it doing
all the way over there?
- Probably checking on her brood.
- What are you talking about?
Oh, don't you know?
We stumbled into her nest.
Broke one of her eggs
accidentally.
That's why that bitch reptile
killed my girl.
- Can you play it back on the video feed?
- Sure. Give me a sec.
I got it.
[Whirring]
Okay, slower. Stop.
There. Now zoom in.
The only species
of a boa to lay eggs?
There's no way he could impregnate her
and then she lay eggs within an hour.
No. She must have
already been pregnant.
That's why she was fighting off the python.
She was defending her nest.
Either that, or she's just
got good taste in men.
Oh, no.
Why is she letting him eat her eggs?
What's wrong with her?
She must be too injured to fight.
When was this recorded?
Fifteen, 20 minutes ago.
Look.
- At least we know she's all right.
- And she's after the python.
Your snake has
a sense of vengeance?
That's what we're
about to find out.
I wonder if you officially
made her shit list, Broddick.
Mclntyre.
Well, just don't stand there!
- Stop! Stop!
- Fuck off.
[Whooping]
I should've known
she was pregnant.
It must've been a combination
of the food snakes and the growth hormone.
Or maybe it was just nature's way of letting you
know you're doing all right.
[Rhythmic beating]
- What is that?
- Whatever it is, it's live.
- Sounds like machinery.
- It's music.
I thought you secured a five-mile perimeter.
~~ [heavy drumbeats]
~~ [techno]
See you on the other side of here.
[Screaming]
[Snake slurping]
Watch it!
[Woman screams]
Oh, my God!
[Shouting, screaming]
[Shouting continues]
Everybody move forward.
[Screaming, shouting]
[Growling]
[Together]
Oh, shit!
[Shouting, screaming]
[Screaming, shouting]
Die, you slithering piece of shit!
Welcome to my barbecue.
[Screams]
No!
[Yelling]
[Soldiers yelling, groaning]
We have a madman loose
with a flamethrower.
I need more men ASAP.
[Growling]
Monica!
Fucking thing!
Here's the plan: Run!
- Good plan.
- We're in trouble. The gun's out there.
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
[Hissing, screeching]
[Growling]
Hello, bitch.
Remember me?
[Yelling]
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
[Snakes snarling]
[Spits]
I hope you fucking
choke on me, bitch!
[Yelling]
Okay, come on.
[Horn blowing]
Whoa!
[Screaming]
It's too late.
Sorry, Betty.
[Screams]
[Horn blowing]
I killed her.
No, you saved her life.
She's gone.
So, what if we can't find her?
We know where her nest is.
We'll find her.
- What?
- You and me.
We make a pretty good team.
And Betty makes three.
- Ready?
- Ready.
Subtitled by J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank - CA