Simon, where's the Wakenfield code?
Everyone else has finished.
May I remind you...
that your culprition date
is non-negotiable?
I repeat: non-negotiable.
Did you see someone?
Yeah.
$ 21.52
Some guy, brown coat and a hat.
Hello?
Do not touch it.
Hello? Who is it?
Public Emergency Services.
Hello. I'd like to report a break in.
Puppy!
Go inside.
Simon, what's going on out there?
The neighbour's got a dog.
You made some improvement.
You want to see him do a trick?
Hum, not right now.
I've got a deadline.
Let me show you
something really cool.
That's my couch.
It's nanotech.
It's a fantastic piece of furniture,
and it cleans itself.
It cleans itself?
When you spill the Chianti on it
it cleans itself.
Hey, have you received
any packages lately?
Packages?
Yeah, I found these two packages
in my apartment.
What was in them?
- They were empty.
- Empty?
You know, I got an eviction notice.
Maybe the landlord's
playing tricks on me.
He's a Scheiß, and
he just wants to let you know
he can get into your apartment.
There's some kind of
chemical imbalance in him.
Well,
I should go. I'll talk to you later,
Derrick. I've got a deadline.
Yeah, I know you.
You're a professional.
Simon, why don't you get
the videophone hooked up?
I'd like to see your face
when you tell me why your code
still hasn't been abrogated.
The client is breathing on my neck
and he's no small client.
He's gonna crush us like rice.
A company has paid you well
for your work, Simon.
They will protect their investment.
Deliver the code, please.
Thank you.
Do you have the rent today,
Mr. Simon J.?
Tenants who pay get to stay.
Tenants who don't pay,
don't get to stay.
Unless you are useful.
Are you useful, Simon?
Or useless?
- What do you want?
- You're going to fix my terminal
and I'm going to ignore
your delicate financial status.
I really can't today.
I've got a deadline.
I think you can get to your deadline
after you've fixed my terminal.
Please.
It's frozen again
and won't turn off.
Is it a virus?
- When did it go down?
- Earlier tonight.
What time?
According to the system,
around 11:30.
Is it a virus?
We'll see.
You know, someone's been
breaking in in my apartment.
Impossible, not with my security.
There are ways.
Camera's always crashing.
Besides, whoever it was
might live here.
Might even have a key.
Give me twenty minutes.
- Twenty minutes please.
- Sure, sure.
The terminal's fixed.
You're still ahead?
Anything to drink?
Hi. Do you have any locks?
Any padlocks or anything?
- Isle three.
- Thanks.
$ 32.52
Someone's following me again?
Yeah.
Howard?
Simon? I was just thinking about you.
Where have you been?
I've been looking for you.
Can you hold this for a second?
So... Listen Howard, have you been
sending me these packages?
Packages?
I've received these three packages,
I don't know how
they got to my apartment.
Packages?
There was nothing inside them.
And no address, no sender... Nothing.
Let's think about this for a second.
What do you think?
Maybe it's all just happening
inside your head.
- Perfect. Thanks, Howard.
- Don't laugh.
That's how they got me,
only in baskets,
and played their game,
but I've beat 'em.
That's how they get inside
your head with their tools,
They'd offer you that
target audience,
mass production, cheap labour,
uniform quality, easy access,
growth...
That's growth forever.
Oh hell, let's live forever.
Hallelujah, I'm a bomb.
Hallelujah, a bomb again.
Hallelujah, give me a hand out,
revive me again.
Howard, you're nuts.
Listen, I have to get upstairs
and put this lock on before
they try and break in again.
Do me a favour. If you see anything
weird or whatever, tell me. Okay?
The elevator works?
Why, was it broken?
I thought so.
No keys?
Can I use your phone?
So, what do you do?
Oh... I fix computers.
I work with computers.
Hello, this is Juliet. I'm not in,
seems you gotta leave me a message.
She is peaking out.
- I can call the landlord.
- Thanks.
Hello Simon.
I see you've been making friends.
She lost her keys.
She's locked out.
What's in it for me?
You can tell her I'll be right down.
Just a few minutes.
He says he'll be right down.
Oh, great.
I'd only sleep.
I hate to work at nights.
Gotta do laundry.
I feel like I never catch up.
Would you mind
if I made another call?
No.
Hey, I'm not here.
Gonna look into your call when...
Another machine.
Hey, I'm sorry I wasn't home.
Could you bring the package
to the hospital tomorrow,
Maybe I can pick it up tomorrow night.
Anyway take care.
You sent them.
You sent me those packages.
What packages?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Why are you here?
I was locked out and I thought
you were helping me.
All my data's encrypted.
No one can break in.
What are you doing in my apartment?
- I'm leaving.
- What do you want?
I just wanna get
some sleep. That's all.
The 24 hours are over.
Where is your code?
This is very unprofessional.
Smarten up or fuck off.
Please... and thank you.
Fucking virus,
Get out of my computer.
Red Courier now speaking.
May I help you?
Hey... Listen, it's an emergency.
I need the best home
security system on the market.
Also I would like the latest
virus protector and three cards of milk.
Alright. I'll be there in an hour.
It's free. Thanks for calling Red Courier.
- What's up, man!
- What did you get me?
I got you PRP 4000 infrared
motion and sound detector system
and Virus Pro Version 5.5.
Great.
Do you want me to install it?
Well, I'll install it myself,
but could you install
this trigger for me?
Yeah.
Did you bring the milk?
I might have to charge you
the emergency rate for this.
Yeah, that's fine.
Simon, I'm fucking with you.
Damn, I'll behave some serious!
Here.
Why do you need
all this security anyway?
I started receiving
these strange packages.
Four packages exactly the same.
Nothing inside them.
I was just asleep. No one has
the keys, apart from my landlord.
What about the windows
and the ventilation system?
Either way, you're not
gonna have a problem
now the system's off
and the code of the release is set.
Read the instructions.
Alright. Thanks for coming so quick.
You really need to get out.
I mean you look pale man.
and the place is like shit.
Look, go to a club, fuck a girl...
Let me get you some
psychedelic drugs.
You know I can get that shit.
Okay.
Look I'm only saying that
because I care about you.
You're one of my best customers.
- Thanks.
- Call me if you need anything.
Bye.
Look.. have you been putting
shit in my apartment?
Shit?
Yes, packages with
nothing inside them.
Did you crawl through
the vent on the wall?
So, here we are...
- Simon.
- Hi.
I was wondering if you could turn
your music down a little,
I'm trying to work.
Work? It's Friday!
It's the week-end. No work.
Come and have a drink. And let's talk
about the neighbours. Come.
Gesundheit. Are you sick?
Yeah, I guess.
Just an overnight thing.
I have the cure.
- Cognac. It's the best!
- Do you have any milk?
Milk is the worst for a cold.
Sit down!
Hey, what happened to your couch?
I thought it cleaned itself.
It's broken.
Drink this, it's good for you.
- So, how is your head?
- Adam.
He is sleeping right now,
but I believe
he's making some progress.
Yeah?
I always wanted to have a child,
but I have bad sperm.
- So what's its first word?
- Oh, he goes... aaaaaah!
Say, couldn't we use
your speech pattern?
At the moment he's learning
and he's using my pattern
but he keeps confusing
his voice with my voice.
And...
Adam needs clarity.
Adam with my voice?
It seems a little strange...
Please, do it for Adam.
A, B, C, D, E...
...F, G, H, I...
...J, K, L, M...
...N, O, P, Q...
...R, S, T, U...
...V, W, X, Y, Z.
Hello father. Thank you Simon.
Have you received the package?
I want to help you.
There are changes happening.
I am afraid... I am afraid.
My son!
Why does he make that sound?
I gave him access to the web
all the time. I don't censor anything.
- Are you infected?
- Maybe I should...
I'm gathering information.
I know something bad
is happening. I'm finding answers.
There are changes happening.
Some changes in the Q zero zero.
Adam!
Wait, don't touch it.
That's my neighbour,
the guy with the dog.
- Adam! You filthy thing!
- What are they doing?
- Haven't you played the neighbour's game?
- What game?
It's porno! Role-playing shit.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he was using you as a subject.
- What do you mean?
- I don't know,
maybe he's capturing
your reactions for his stories.
You!
You were in the club? My club?
- It's a free country.
- What are you, a sheep?
You've been following me.
Look, you've been fucking with me.
Why did you send me those packages?
Packages?
What do you know about packages?
- I don't wanna be part of your game.
- Is that what this is about?
You kiddin' me?
With all that's going on
you wanna talk about my game?
You're in the game!
You wanna lead
or you wanna follow?
There are changes happening, man.
I can show you things.
It's your call.
My dog will be hungry.
It's supper time for Puppy.
Hey, we're gonna have a drink,
I'll show you my game...
...then we can talk
about this package riddle.
Actually I think I must
go back to my apartment.
Don't be so fucking nervous!
Elevator doesn't work
and we gotta do with this.
Fix the fucking elevator!
Wait, check this out.
Are you gonna fix it?
How about that drink, uh?
Home sweet home.
Puppy?
Don't be the naughty boy.
Puppy!
There. See? He's fine.
Hear that?
Your phone is ringing.
Thin walls.
So...
What's your poison?
Huh.. I'd have a beer.
I drink Cola 500.
Yeah, that's fine.
- Haze 'em on your ass.
- Cheers.
Come.
Have a look at some of my work.
I just got the latest "Virus Pro".
I've been having some problems.
- Yeah, me too.
- It's been going around.
You wanna see something fresh?
Are you sure it's fixed?
Welcome to the game, my friend.
Bugs are part of the game.
they can grow as the game
grows. Have a seat.
You wouldn't have something
like this at the club?
Yeah, there's a few
of them at the club.
Thanks.
Okay.
Put your hands here.
Control it with your fingertips.
Everything's touch-sensitive.
This has a mind.
Yeah, that's Alice. Check her out.
Alright. You know what... I should...
You here?
So, what do you think of my game?
Isn't that the girl
who lives down in the hall?
Trish?
Yeah, the nurse.
She works on the cancer ward.
That chip is from her.
She needs a good fuck now, man.
She seems to me so full of life
after being surrounded by slow death all day.
I've always been so creative
doctoring her performance.
She doesn't like that.
She's Alice's friend.
Alice has many friends.
I like Alice.
She holds my future.
I suspect her.
I don't know her motives.
What you do to me...
You're my baby...
You're my lover... you're mine.
I've received packages too.
Cola 500.
I love the smell of sweat and blood.
You're my baby,
you're my lover. You're mine.
You're up early.
Still high, asshole?
Sorry. I didn't mean it.
You're right.
I've just been put on the one edge.
You're pretty fucked up, aren't you?
I'm just doing the laundry.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
It's alright.
It'll be alright.
He's watching us.
So? He's just another lonely man.
There's a lot of you out there.
You should probably
stay away from me.
I think I might be getting sick.
Yeah? Let's feel it.
I should go.
- That's a lot of milk.
- Well, I like it.
- It makes mucus.
- How much?
Lots. Enlarges the pancreas too.
- I meant the milk.
- So did I.
How much does it cost?
$ 82,57.
$ 82?
$ 82.57. I don't control
the prices, man.
Sorry to disturb you, sir.
Detective Harris and I
need to ask you a few questions.
No problem. What's the matter?
- Hello?
- Hello Simon, my name's Adam.
You may not talk to me.
I must talk to you.
I've been trying to
connect me with your brain.
I wanted to help you.
Stop buying. I must go now.
I will call again. I will call again.
Hello.
Hello?
- Hey, what's up?
- You alright?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm good. I'm good.
Just sort of freaked out man
about your neighbour, man,
I mean he used to be
this hardball tenant...
Do you think he was infected?
I don't know, I don't know.
Are you infected?
Infected with what?
I don't know, I don't know.
You know...
You know your neighbour was on
to something? I mean his game
could be responsible for shit
done to venture corporate thugs.
It has something to do with
those packages you received.
Do you still have one in here,
that I can look at?
Yeah.
Where?
I thought it was right here.
- Are you alright?
- Yeah.
I think you need a blood test, man.
Do you want me to take a sample?
- You could do that?
- Yeah yeah yeah.
I got a kit in my bag.
Hey, take a seat.
- Where did you get this?
- Oh, connections.
Sterile. It's a one-time use.
Gimme a thumb.
- That's it?
- Yeah, that's it.
I'll get this delivered to the lab.
I'll get the results back to you
as soon as possible.
Why are you drinking milk?
What?
Didn't you tell me
you were allergic to it?
Oh man, just stop drinking it for a while.
See how you react, alright?
Howard?
Who else could it be?
I don't know.
Did you see someone
in the garbage room?
I think that a dog
was in the building.
Maybe it was me.
I've been down here,
working on pipes and vents.
I'm really glad to see you Simon.
Glad to see you.
Are you plugged in now?
Where are the plugs?
You know what I mean?
Plugged in plugged in plugged in?
Come on.
- Where?
- My place.
Sit down.
You know, I made some home-made wine
Made out of real grapes.
You want some?
Sure.
- It's a nice place, Howard.
- You hungry?
- Yeah, I suppose I am.
- I'll make you a sandwich.
Thanks.
You know most people get that food thing,
almost get screwed and crazy?
They don't understand how the human
body works. They don't understand.
gastronomie.
Hey, Howard?
Can I trust you?
I hope so.
It's about the Christmas presents.
Yeah, those packages.
Do you feel sick?
No, actually I don't, now that
you're asking. I feel better.
- Here. Eat this.
- Oh, thanks.
That's good.
What were you feeling?
I don't know.
...I mean, everything.
What?
I feel... I feel the building,
humming and
...worrying...
...noises.
Most times I'm just afraid.
Afraid of my own apartment.
Afraid I might get another package.
Did you change your locks?
I can fix 'em for ya,
I'm really good with my manos.
- No, it's okay, I've already done it.
- You changed 'em?
- No, no, a friend of mine, Nile.
- An old friend?
I've known him for a while.
Somebody you can trust?
You're gonna be fine.
You have a conscience.
That's all you need.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome any time.
- Alright.
- Just a second.
Happy birthday, Simon.
It's one of my early inventions.
They're micro-bugs.
Yeah.
Yeah. Just toys, really.
They're nice.
Makes you feel like you're
in the country. I love that sound.
Makes me feel comfy and peaceful.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
- Good night son.
- See you, Howard.
Hallelujah I'm a bomb...
Hallelujah bomb again.
Hallelujah...
Give me a hand out, revive me again.
Listen, Simon.
This isn't funny at all.
I don't think you realize
the seriousness of the situation.
We need that code.
There are people waiting.
I put someone else to work on it,
because I couldn't find you.
I didn't know what to think.
If you don't get back at me soon
...you'll fucking find it hard
to work in this business in the future.
Hello?
It's the police!
We know you're in there!
Detective Harris and I...
...need to ask you
a few more questions.
Mr. J., open the door!
You okay?
Yeah... Yeah thanks.
Hey.
Have you been calling me?
- Would like to come in?
- Thanks.
With those cops
I don't think I can sleep.
Would you want some milk?
No, thanks.
Simon, I'm moving.
What?
This place is really getting into me.
Where are you gonna go?
Anywhere but here.
The Hospital's out for sale,
they'll sell anything...
...it's pathetic.
Everyone's so afraid they don't
wanna get sick, so it's empty.
But where do they go?
No one cares.
No one says a word, it's not normal
I mean maybe it's normal, but...
...maybe something is wrong with me.
Have you been receiving the packages?
Have you been buying
and buying anything?
Consuming anything
out of the ordinary?
Listen to yourself.
You're paranoid about some package
while a man was murdered
down the hall. It's not normal.
Real people don't
have this conversation.
think like this... It's like
everyone in this building is... is so...
Hey Trish,
- I saw you in the game.
- So what?
It's just something I did
to escape this fucking reality.
What does that have
to do with anything?
I was playing the game when he died.
I don't know anymore what
was real, or what wasn't.
But I couldn't get out.
I had to crawl through the vents.
I heard somebody coming in after me.
It's addictive.
I never should have played that game.
But you've been tested?
Tested for what?
If you play the game
you should be examined out
...for mineralities in the blood...
...STDs, some of them...
If you haven't been
tested I can do it for you.
No, my friend Nile did it.
He's a doctor?
He's a courier.
You had a courier
take blood from you?
Are you fucking crazy?
- Oh, it's alright. He's a friend.
- A friend.
I have no friends here. And no family.
You know it's like I'd love
to have children some day...
...you can't raise children
in a place like this.
Everyone's tainted.
I'd like to go somewhere
where there's some people left.
Please don't say that,
it's not too late.
Simon, it is Adam. I'm
worried about your condition.
I have learned many
systems of human logic,
I know bad and
good. Bad is Q zero.
Double zero can make
the device stop.
You're in danger of being
erode. Stop buying.
I found the answers.
Buy is not answers.
Do not trust them.
I must go now.
Wait, wait. Adam?
Hello?
Simon, I have something wrong.
Farm Cut meat!
Did you hear that?
Did you?
- What's going on?
- Please, help...
What? Farm Cut!
There is someone...
I have no control anymore.
Find someone of the Farm.
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Anyone here?
Hello?
Shit!
Howard?
Simon J.?
Yes.
You're fired.
I wanted to tell you over the phone...
just to make sure that
the words got into your brain.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Your code. Where is it?
It's been infected.
A virus?
I don't know. What was the code for?
I can't tell you that, Simon,
you know your contract.
Tell me. What was the code for?
I don't know. We're only
working on a specific part.
We don't know the big picture.
We know you're in there.
We want to have
a few words with you.
There's something
we want to tell you.
It concerns your health and safety.
I have safety through my alarm.
Everything's fine.
No, no.
Everything is not fine.
Your life as well as most, if not all, the
tenants' in this building is in possible danger.
We're warning everyone.
Now obviously I can't force
you to do anything,
but I would suggest
you leave the building...
until this matter is resolved.
If you feel sick at all
check yourself into a Hospital.
Better to be safe than sorry.
Good day to you, sir.
Good day.
- Hello?
- Nile speaking.
- Hey, where are my results?
- I've got 'em.
Actually... You know what, don't worry
about it at all. I think I'll go to a Hospital.
No, don't go there Simon, don't go there!
I'll be right there in a minute.
No, that's okay. Bye.
- Simon, where you goin'?
- What are you doing here?
Look man, I'm trying to stop you from making
a mistake. Look, I've got your results.
Don't freak out.
There's something in your blood.
And the last place
you wanna go is in there.
- Don't worry, Trish works in there.
- Who's that?
She's a friend of mine,
someone I can trust.
Oh, you trust her?
I've never even heard of her.
You don't even talk to fucking girls!
You can't trust anybody
in there right now.
I'm the only one you can
trust, but I gotta tell you:
- What have you been working on?
- You said you didn't wanna know.
It's an antivirus program, right?
My code got infected,
I couldn't finish it.
That's bullshit! The only thing
that's infected is you!
They gave it to everybody
in your building, Simon.
You're a fucking
guinea pig, and so am I.
It's a big experiment
that's all gone wrong.
Now, if we don't do something
about it, we're both gonna die.
Okay?
Now get on the bike!
What are the packages for?
What the fuck!
The package is a delivery system.
What? There's nothing inside them.
Just because you don't see it,
doesn't mean there's nothing.
Now, what's inside you is inside me.
- It's not safe anymore.
- What's inside them?
Nanomites. Version 1.0.
What?
Code-break messages that
go directly into your brain.
That's why you can't stop
buying Nature Fresh Milk
and I can't stop buying
fucking Parker Jarks. man.
And it is not safe anymore.
Get on the bike!
No, you're lying. You're working for them.
No!
You're trying to scare
me, to manipulate me.
Simon, your code could help us.
Now you're wanting the code.
You won't get it. It's there.
Stay away from me.
Be quiet, Adam!
Be quiet!
I need to talk to Adam.
Come in.
Come in, Simon.
I need to talk to you.
I can explain. I can help you
explain. You know the nanomites?
You know, he's been calling me
when you're not at home.
Adam is behaving
very strange lately.
Father made Adam,
he no made the nanomites.
You've been receiving
the packages too?
What packages, Simon?
- What's in your fridge?
- In my fridge?
Adam knows about the packages.
Adam knows something bad is happening.
Adam knows that Derrick father is infected.
- Adam knows that Derrick father lied about...
- Stop talking!
Stop right now, you filthy thing!
Adam, knows that nanomites malfunction.
I'm sorry, my son.
What the hell are you doing living here
all deep in this fucking building,
playing with your stupid android head?
- I want you to leave.
- Shut the fuck up!
You sent me those packages.
- Leave, now!
- Or what?
Or I'll have to call the authorities...
I don't want to do that.
Simon, I think you're sick.
You're the sick one.
Simon, I saw you going into
the neighbour's apartment
the night he was killed.
Well, if you're so sure
I killed my neighbour,
what makes you think I won't do
exactly the same thing to you?
Simon.
What's wrong?
I think I'm alright.
I think I just fainted.
Careful.
I'll be alright in a minute.
What did you buy?
Just some juice
and stuff. Look at me.
Stuff? What kind of stuff?
Oh, just juice, actually.
What kind of juice?
Orange Juice synthetically pure
calcium, enriched with vitamin E.
You've been receiving
packages too, haven't you?
Do you know what's going on?
Can you feel it?
- I'm full of bugs.
- No.
- I'm full of mistakes.
Life is full of mistakes.
Gentle.
I don't love you.
I don't love you either.
Come inside.
Trish?
Trish, are you here?
Simon?
Go away!
Simon, it's Nile.
Come on, man, open the door!
Open the door before it's too late!
I can't take this anymore,
It has to stop.
So you believe me now?
I'm seeing things. I'm seeing people
and they're not there.
I'm seeing packages.
I know, I know.
They're side effects, bugs.
It's a beta version,
but I found the upgrade.
The upgrade from version
1.0 to version 1.1.5.
Look, I've got it right here,
I just need you to touch it.
- Have you tried it?
- Yes, yes yes. Simon, look at me, I'm fine.
Everything's okay.
Besides, what other
choices do we have?
Now please, touch it.
- That's it?
- Yes.
- But how do I know?
- It should already be working.
I'm really, really sorry.
Farm is happy to be
the solutions' provider.
Feel free to browse all of
our finest choice products.
We guarantee that they'll
make you feel a happier individual.
Farm very much wants
to be a part of your life,
because we care.
We care about you.
So stay at the Farm.
We'll show you the way
to the solutions you want...
What's new?
Not much. How are you?
Hey Trish!
It's me!
Nature Fresh Milk!
Howard?
Nile, you fucking bastard.
There are more bugs in this.
What - Nature Fresh Milk!
Did you hear that?
I didn't say it!
You sent me the first
package, didn't you?
Fuck!
Leave your message after the beep.
Trish, hi this is Simon.
Listen...
I'd like to come, come with you.
You were right about everything.
Hello... Nature Fresh Milk!
Help me. Help me!
I love my life.
It's too late.
Simon?
I heard the crickets.
Howard, come in.
Can you help me?
- I'm sorry. You want something to drink?
- No.
Nature Fresh Milk!
Did you hear that?
- I didn't say it. Zero nanomites.
- Yeah.
Zero nanomites. Happily brought.
I'm afraid.
Let me take your hand.
There are good people and there are bad people and
they're on their way and they want you, Simon.
The bad people could
save you, but they won't.
The good people, they wanna
save you, but they can't.
The bad people, Farm people,
they wanna hurt you, Simon.
They want to possess your intellectual
fibre. They want your money.
They put the mites in your brain.
And I wanna save you.
Come on, open your mouth.
You see, you haven't got much time.
This'll help you, come on.
Simon, you're infected.
Just say "ah"! "Ah"!
Say "ah".
Almost too late.
Your body is rejecting the mites.
It's a completely bugsy product.
It never would happen in my day.
If I don't remove your hard drive,
you're gonna have to die, or Farm will catch you.
I've saved you Simon, just like I've saved
the landlord, the game man.
I was too late for that garbage man.
How you know,
I don't know everything.
You know, you're gonna feel
a little uncomfortable for a while...
...then you're gonna sleep.
And when you wake up,
everything's gonna be different.
Everything is gonna be good.
There's a time when we walk up.
There's a time we fall back.
It's just the beginning.
# Subtitles: lyliakar #