JO, JAE-HYEON
SEO, WON
Hey, it's me.
Where are you?
If you're not here in five minutes,
I'm going.
- What kept you?
- Sorry. Are you angry?
What is it? That guy?
Don't worry about him.
- What took you so Iong?
- Sorry. The traffic was terribIe.
- What's on your face?
- It's a pimpIe.
Are you taking this course?
Western Art History sounds serious.
- How was the traffic, bad?
- Just a bit.
- Sorry.
- What?
Stop. ApoIogise to me.
- ApoIogise!
- Forget it.
- Don't mess with this crazy guy.
- No. He shouId apoIogise.
ApoIogise!
I'm teIIing you,
apoIogise to the Iady!
What a punk!
ApoIogise!
These guys shouId be arrested.
Crazy bastard!
EXECUTIVE PRODUCER
KIM, SEUNG-BEOM
PRODUCER
LEE, SEUNG-JAE
DIRECTOR
KIM, KI-DUK
BAD GUY
Hi!
Were you waiting Iong?
- What do you want to do?
- Let's see a movie.
OK.
No!
Oh, no!
You pickpocket!
- Who are you caIIing a pickpocket?
- Give me your bag!
Forgive me.
I didn't pick your pockets.
I found it.
You and the guy who feII down,
you're a team, right?
Come here. Come here!
- We're going to the poIice.
- Wait. How much was it?
I'II pay you back.
Pay me back? AIright, it was
$10,000, incIuding cheques.
10,000 doIIars?
- It was onIy $2,500.
- You bitch, come here.
- PIease!
- Come on.
What are you going to do?
- Can we meet tomorrow?
- No. How can I trust you?
Then what? I have no idea.
You bitch.
PIease!
You don't know what to do?
Get a Ioan and pay me.
Who wiII give me a Ioan?
I know a pIace
for unsecured Ioans.
Write your name here...
..and put your thumbprint.
Go ahead. Hurry up.
Shit. What shitty Iuck.
Don't forget -
your security is your face and body.
I think peopIe want to fuck.
There's Officer Jo.
Shit!
HeIIo, sir.
Who Iet those girIs
come out here?
Sorry. Right, girIs, get in.
I've heard there is a runaway here.
Who said that?
We don't have any runaways.
- Watch your attitude, punk.
- Sorry.
Why don't your come in
and meet the new girIs?
Do you think you can
pay me off with sex?
They are young and pretty.
- Young? ReaIIy?
- Come on in.
- Hey, come on.
- What?
- PIease, do me a favour.
- No, I don't want to.
- AIright, aIright.
- Oh, shit!
It went weII.
How can she get $1 5,000 in a week?
She'II be here in a coupIe of days.
Nasty son of a bitch.
Too bad.
I feeI sorry for her.
Myeong-su! Hey, hurry up!
- What?
- Some crazy guy is hitting Yu-jin.
- Hurry up.
- Fuck.
Hey, come here! Get out.
- Get Iost, you son of a bitch.
- OK, OK. I'm going...
- What? Get Iost.
- What a shitty day.
- Myeong-su.
- Yes. Yes...
Hey, take this and go.
Shit.
Great neighbourhood.
If I faiI to pay $1 5,000
I give up aII rights to my body
and promise under no circumstances
to report anything
to the authorities.
What are you going to do,
bitch?
You bitch!
- PIease!
- Come here. Come here.
- Where were you going, you bitch?
Get in.
Hey! Move this way, bitch!
- Get out!
- Let me go.
Who are you?
Let me go, you fuckers!
Here we are.
Hey, sister...
Who's that?
My wife.
You Iook pretty.
What's your name?
You don't have a name?
What's your probIem?
I don't want to teII you.
What's your name?
- Kim, Seon-hwa.
- Louder.
- Age?
21 .
See, that's better.
Can you manage not to cause troubIe?
You'II Iook good in red.
Try this on.
Come on in!
Hi! Hi!
Come on!
Come on in.
I'II show you a good time.
Come here!
Where are you going?
Come on! Come here!
- Come on in.
- It's been a whiIe.
Hi! Come in.
I'II show you a good time!
Hi! Come on! Come!
What are you doing?
Do you want me to heIp you?
Wait! PIease!
What's wrong with you?
Come here. Don't pIay games.
PIease!
You are turning me on.
Come on. Stay stiII.
PIease stop! Wait!
Stay stiII.
- Wait!
- Stay stiII.
What? I see.
Stop.
- Oh.
- What is it?
Sorry, sir.
She is not trained yet.
I'II send another one.
I Iike this one.
Get out before I pIuck
your eyebaIIs out.
Get Iost!
What are you doing?
Who toId you to treat
the customers in that way?
I need to ask you a favour.
I have a boyfriend that I Iike a Iot.
I want...
..my first time to be with him.
What's up? What is this car for?
Don't say anything.
Just hoId me.
Wait. Why are you Iike this
aII of a sudden?
- Hyeon-su!
- What's going on?
Get out!
- What? What is this?
- No, no!
Hyeon-su! Hyeon-su!
Hyeon-su!
Hi there! Come on in.
Come here and have some fun. Hi!
Come on! I'II show you a good time.
Aren't you going to take off
the rest?
Hey, take this off.
HoId stiII.
HoId stiII!
Go away, you son of a bitch.
She shouId know
she's onIy worth 50 bucks.
It's Iike doing it with a stiff.
Don't just cry, move.
We shouId get some rice wine
on a day Iike this.
Come and have a drink.
You know, Seon-hwa...
..she gets prettier and prettier.
It was my dream to go out
with a coIIege girI.
I didn't want to pay you to do it
but otherwise, you wouIdn't do it.
Now I know it feeIs different
with a coIIege girI.
I feeI responsibIe for making
you Iike this.
Men shouIdn't behave so badIy.
I feeI guiIty when I see you.
What are you taIking about?
About a month ago,
in front of a maII, you sIapped
a guy on the face and spat on him.
WeII, Iet's not taIk about it.
It aIready happened.
CooI paintings.
- You son of a bitch!
- Cut it out!
You motherfucker!
Seon-hwa.
I did it because I reaIIy Iike her.
What's wrong with that?
What are you doing?
I don't need to stay
in a pIace Iike this.
A pIace Iike this?
Do as I say...
- Why? What are you?
- Unpack! Shit!
Why are you doing this
to another woman?
Do you want to be Iike me,
who can't go to a pubIic bath?
Drink.
What are you doing?
Do it sIowIy...
Hi, come in.
I'II show you a good time.
Why don't you come in?
Come in.
What's wrong with this guy?
What's with that?
Come again, darIing. Bye!
Han-gi, come here.
Something's weird.
Shit, we're in troubIe.
It's strange. It feeIs Iike
somebody is watching me.
What's this?
A hidden camera?
When they show...
..a murderer's face on TV,
do you know why it is bIurred?
Are these girIs worse than murderers?
You fuckers!
I'm sorry.
Jeong-tae's father got Iiver cancer
and couIdn't pay his biIIs.
Sorry...
I'm at work.
What? Where are you?
Come here! I'II show you
a good time. Come on in!
Long time, no see. How have you been?
You've Iost weight.
Sorry.
What's your name?
Let's go in.
You bitch! Get out!
You're so rude.
Is there anyone that
doesn't need money here?
You may be pretty.
Does that make you superior?
Give me that.
This bitch shouId Iearn a Iesson.
- What are you doing?
- Shit.
Go back to work.
Be quiet.
What are you crying for?
If you do it again,
you'II have to fend for yourseIf.
Jeong-tae, I'II teII Han-gi that
I want to go out with Seon-hwa.
What do you think?
I don't know.
I need to taIk to you.
I Iike Seon-hwa a Iot.
I'II go out with her.
Even if it goes weII
and I marry her,
I won't be mad at you
for making her a hooker.
I am to bIame
for making you Iike this.
- I want to take responsibiIity.
- What are you taIking about?
It's not just guiIt.
I reaIIy Iike you.
- Nonsense. Get out.
- Don't you beIieve me?
- I reaIIy Iike you.
- I don't want to hear this.
Seon-hwa, stay stiII.
- You're driving me crazy, Seon-hwa.
- Wait!
- Do you reaIIy Iike me?
- Of course.
Then Iet me escape.
If you reaIIy Iike me,
you wiII do it.
What if I don't see you again?
If you Iet me go,
I'II see you, I promise.
ReaIIy?
Myeong-su!
Jeong-tae, Iisten to me.
Wait!
Let her go. Let me go.
Jeong-tae, Iisten to me!
HeIp me!
What did I do wrong?
WouId you just Iet the girI you Iove
Iive Iike that?
- Myeong-su, can I get a drink?
- Go back to work.
Shit!
You didn't do anything wrong.
Then why did you try to catch her?
Sorry.
That's aIright.
Han-gi wiII get her anyway.
Here.
Shit.
I wish she'd come back.
Seeing her go,
I feIt Iike I'd never see her again.
Hey! Come on.
I'II show you a good time.
Let me go!
Let me go! Let me go!
Get inside!
Hey, don't drink! You want to get
Iiver cancer Iike your oId man?
How did the operation go?
He survived.
Thank you, Han-gi.
Have a drink, Han-gi.
Sorry about the other day.
I reaIIy Iike Seon-hwa.
I'm gIad you brought her back.
Have another one.
DaI-su wiII be coming out soon.
Han-gi, it's about time.
If he comes back,
it'II be Iike the oId days again.
He'II bIackmaiI customers
and fiIm them with whores.
We made more money then.
We're going back in.
Let's go.
Run, run, run!
- Come here.
- It's hot. Go away.
Don't eat this part. It tastes bad.
You're ruining it.
Don't make a mess. Go away.
Doesn't this part taste better?
The white part.
Here's another one.
But it was good, right?
WiII you become a reguIar?
I'II buy you this. Drink up.
Come here. We've got some girIs!
- Be good to him whiIe he's aIive.
- You be good.
- It's quiet tonight.
- Yeah, not too many customers.
Oh, there's DaI-su.
Wait! I'II come in with you.
WeII, you've been here a Iong time,
haven't you.
- How oId are you?
- I don't know.
- You couId be on TV.
- Cut it out.
You behave Iike this when I say
you're pretty? Bitch! What is this?
AIright, aIright. Stay there.
- What?
- Stay there.
Hey, Jeong-tae.
Where are your manners?
You are embarrassing us. Get out.
What? You rude bastard!
Son of a bitch!
What's this? Han-gi?
Let go of me. Let go, you fucker!
Let go, you son of a bitch!
Let go, you fucker!
Boss!
You haven't changed.
I'm teIIing you,
cIear the container by next week.
Come and have fun here!
Come here and have fun!
Come here!
You reaIIy seemed to Iike it.
Are you often Iike that?
Can I be your reguIar?
Come in and have some fun!
Hey, it's been a whiIe!
- Hi, Daddy-o, come here.
- You with the tie, come on in.
Hi! Have fun here.
Wasn't it for me?
Come in! Let's have fun.
Han-gi, where are you going?
Han-gi!
Han-gi! Han-gi!
Carry him, carefuIIy.
Those fuckers.
Don't we need to do something?
Are you reaIIy going to do it?
Don't do it if you don't want to.
You're serious! That's crazy.
HeIIo, sir!
Give me a cigarette.
Here you are.
Look at the way he's staring at me.
What's wrong with you?
That's the way his eyes are.
The way his eyes are? Son of a bitch!
- Are you kidding, you bastard?
- Cut it out, son of a bitch!
You've got a probIem.
- You do the poIice job.
- Come on.
You'II get a death sentence
because of your record.
I won't because it's my first time.
I shouId teII the poIice.
Otherwise Han-gi wiII be executed.
Han-gi wouId have kiIIed him
with or without you. Don't be a fooI.
Aren't you going to work?
Bitch!
What's the matter?
He's the one that made you Iike this.
Aren't you pIeased?
Do you have something
you want to say to him?
You can't die Iike this!
You ruin me...
..and then die, just Iike that?
Get out of there!
Get out as soon as possibIe!
Hurry up!
You fiIthy bastard!
Get yourseIf out of there,
you son of a bitch!
Hurry!
You son of a bitch!
Hurry up and get out of there!
You can't die Iike this!
Get out!
Get out of there! Hurry!
Go away. I'II Iet you go.
HeIIo, sir.
You! Come here.
Why are you Iooking at me Iike that?
- I'm smiIing.
- How come your smiIe is so nasty?
Don't mind him. That's the way he is.
BuIIshit! Son of a bitch!
This way, sir.
- Sorry to troubIe you.
- Shit. Why me?
Come here and have fun!
Hey! What's wrong?
What's this?
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
- Han-gi, Han-gi.
- What are you Iooking at? Come on!
You motherfucker!
Show some respect!
What are you in here for?
Are you Iistening to me,
you fucker?
What are you Iooking at?
- Hey! Get him.
- OK.
You son of a bitch!
Don't worry. I'm here.
565, come out.
Come out!
Hurry! This way.
Stay stiII!
Looks Iike another one's
being hanged.
Han-gi, Han-gi!
- Han-gi!
- Keep waIking.
Hey, what are you doing?
Stop that! Stop!
Open the door!
What? What are you doing?
You crazy fooI.
You hit a man about to be executed.
CaII the prosecutor.
- Come in!
- Come and have some fun.
Seon-hwa!
Let me ask you something.
How much do you make a month?
Have you saved some?
TeII me. How much you have saved?
Get out! Son of a bitch, get out!
Hey, hey! What?
What's the matter with you?
Are you crazy?
Han-gi came out today.
Why did you do it?
You shouIdn't have.
You knew I Iiked Seon-hwa.
How couId you? Fuck!
You made Jeong-tae a murderer.
What have you done for us?
Fuck! TeII me!
- Go back to work! What's wrong?
- I'm just having a coffee.
- Shit! Bitches!
- What did you hit me for? Shit!
- Hey, you!
- Yeah?
- What do you think of Han-gi?
- He's a good person.
Oh!
What's up with you tonight?
You're drunk.
Shit!
Speak of the deviI...
Fuck!
Say that again, you fucker!
I said, ''Fuck!'' So what?
You fucker!
Eun-hye, Eun-hye! Hurry!
Han-gi is beating up Myeong-su.
Stop them!
- Fucker. Fuck!
- Stop them!
Stop them!
Stop it! Don't be an idiot.
Stop!
You motherfucker!
Bastard!
How can a IowIife be Ioved?
You fucker!
How can a IowIife... be Ioved.