Presented by
CJ Entertainment / FILMZ
Presented by CJ Entertainment
A Film by Doo Sa Boo Film
The time is 1636
right after the Manchu war
China's Army was stationed
in Korea and started to interfere
In Korea's affairs, which made
the people's lives miserable
At this time of disorder, there were
fools living by their own rules
Blood would be all over
everywhere they went
Shame less fools doing anything
for money...
There is no way to find out the truth
about these people
But, people call them
the 'Romantic Warriors'
I took a pity on the poor little thing
Kim Min-jong
and made her my concubine
Choi Sung-guk / Jin Jae-yeong
That ungrateful whore ran away
with another man
I want them captured a live
at all costs
You'll get 5,000 more
Associate Producer - Je Jeong-hun
Oh, gods of the Mountains
the Moon
and the waters
Let us be rid of these demons
Producers - Heo Tae-gu
Yun Je-gyun
Let the evil spirit be exorcised
from this woman
God of heaven and earth!
Let us be rid of these demons
Not there...
Produced by Lee Ji-seung
Who the hell is out there?
Who are these punks?
Oh, no!!
- Ah!
- Oh, no! Oh my, my...
One stroke could mean ten thousand
Ten thousand strokes, one!
Screenplay and Directed
by Yun Je-gyun
Got any problem with it, punk?
ROMANTIC WARRIORS
You scoundre is
Do you have any idea who I am?
Where are you taking me?
You want a piece of me?
Hold your trap, bitch!
You SOB's!
I can see you don't know me
Do you know
the Hong Kil-dong brotherhood?
You have no freaking idea who
Brother Kuk-jeon is either
You no-name good
for nothing bastards
Today is your last day
What the hell
are you looking at?
I think we're lost
Yo-yee
Can't you stay with us again?
- I'll talk to my Dad...
- Giving this to me for real?
Like it was before
Sure this is from China?
- I don't have any parents
- Did you stea I this like last time?
Tell me you didn't steal it
like the last time
Yo-yee
Dal-rae
Say 'One' and an old lady
Lifts her cane
Say 'Two' and a bean-curd seller
rings his bell
On three...
- That's not it
- Dad?
- Ho hum!
- What's wrong?
I told you
not to hang around
Get lost!
I took pity on you
as an orphan and fed you
But you dared
to leave us?
You idiot
thank your stars
You got lucky
because of Lady Fei Fei
A job well done, boys
Big Brother
we aren't beggars
This just isn't enough...
So... you're running
your mouths
to be treated like professiona is
Nonsense!
Five coins aren't enough?
I get the same
boneheads!
I even send money home
and get to save the rest
Brother
don't worry
Lower your gaze!
Shut your mouths!
Knew it was mine
Told you to stay still
Pang!
You fool!
Fei Fei doesn't
talk about me?
No
- Not even a bit?
- No
I know she does
you fool
Get something
tasty to eat
After I become rich...
we can live together happily
little sister
Say 'One' and an old lady
lifts her cane
Say 'Two' and a bean-curd seller
rings his bell
Say 'Three' and a bride
looks at her mirror
Say 'Four' and women
wash clothes by the stream
Shit!
This is driving me up the wall!
Hey, you two!
What the heck
Master, Master?
Master!
Master, Master
Master
Master!
Master...
Oh, Not bad!
All right
Way to go...
How many tear drops
so far?
Sister, 999 drops
Good job
One more guy tomorrow
and we are done?
Bingo!
It'll be one thousand drops then
Finally ascending
to the Nirvana tomorrow?
Wow! Narvana!
Narvana!
Sister, it's Nirvana
Repeat after me, Nir!
Nir!
Vana!
Nirvana!
Narvana!
Say rice!
Lice!
Rice!
You don't do anything right
so do as you please
Bitch!
Master, Master
Hello
Shit, you stupid whore!
You give me the creeps
Get a grip!
No human be ng will avenge
a ghost's grievance these days
Wait for that and you'll be stuck
in this lousy world
For real?
Do I look that scared?
Tell us something
we don't know
Don't stop now
Come on!
Move it!
Assassin, assassin
assassin
It's time to teach you boys
the Ultimate Swordsmanship
The Ultimate Swordsmanship
You guys are to use it against the
enemies with high inner karma
Remember you
first need to break
their inner balance
Break what?
Inner balance!
Why not say
inner stupidity
Watch this
Watch
Kawabanga!
Abracabadra!
What kind of
freaking exorcism is that?
Why don't we switch
our day jobs?
No matter how good you are
if you lose inner balance
you lose
- Two!
- Three!
Von!
You short-tongued freak
Get your hand ready!
It's three this time
- Listen to me morons
- Shut up, you all!
- Shut it before I rip up
- I'm a possessed shaman
that big mouth of yours!
- Quiet
- Two...
One
Damn!
I told you, asshole
- Damn
- Frustrating
Do something
A friend of mine got himself a house
after listening to me
Pity me stuck here with dumbass
assassins
who can't even win this game
What are you mumbling about?
What do you know about this game!
I don't
That's not what I mean you moron
What are you doing
in front of a noble lady?
Going to violate me
with the knife?
Dream on
Old lady
What the...
What?
What kind of
an idiotic assassin
loses his sword?
Beware of ghosts SOBs
They're so full of
grievances
If you aren't careful
they'll eat you alive
I don't think
this is the way?
You morons get lost on the paths
you trave I every day?
That's why
ninjas eat you for lunch
Even the cook looks down
on me now
What the hell
are you looking at?
This is not the way
Let's go
Are you two going out?
Why don't you guys
try to make out here then
What are you looking at?
Lose the attitude
you SOB's
Damn those wolves
Yo-yee
do you know
why I rarely draw my sword?
I don't want to know
you moron
It was exactly
10 years ago
Soldiers revolted in the royal court
Princess Jeong-rin and I
who were to get married
We're now on the run
I was a top warrior
and her bodyguard
We ran away as far as
Ji-ri San
But I had to face
the 17 best assassins of the nation
in one last stand-off
Damn it...
Princess Rin
I decided then...
I understood
what her last words were
I 'll never draw
my sword in vain again
Rin!
Big Brother!
Yo-yee, Yo-yee!
Don't cry on me
Yo-yee!
Brother!
Dumb and dumber
putting on a show
Can't believe
I'm their hostage
Let it go
you bastards
One more to go
and not even
a cock roach
is in sight
Who peed here?
Not me
Look at the color
Oh, finally, Our meal is here
Looks juicy
Oh my!
Look at my enchanting body
I didn't know
- Look at my body
- Who's gonna rub my back?
Someone might want me as
their concubine
Look at my enchanting body~
What is that funny thing
on your head?
What's underneath?
Take it out
Darn it!
Told you to take it out
you wimp
It' s really nothing...
This guy is retarded
That panty hasn't been washed
for long time
Enjoy the aroma?
Give it back
Get it now?
That was great
A job well done, girls
No
we gotta thank you
Well said
Glad that you know
So we're going to
Heaven tomorrow?
Heaven, baby!
Where's the tear gourd?
Gave it to you yesterday
It's on top of the altar
Are you out of your mind?
You wenches
Something always goes wrong
at the end
What's that?
Looks like liquor
Liquor?
Watch out what you touch
you idiots
Can't help it
These retards don't grow on me
Give me a sip
You pilfering thieves with no morals
This liquor tastes drab
You sons of bitches!
Stop right there
you dirty bastards!
Oh my rotten luck
You scoundre Is!
Done with running
you wimps?
What's going on?
You lowly ghost!
Do you know
who I am?
Do you have any idea
what you just drank?
No
we couldn't possibly...
Who told you to talk
back to me?
What shall
I do with you?
What did I tell you
You idiots?
Told you
not to touch it
What are you
looking at?
I didn't touch
a single drop
Get rid of him first
Hold it
Could you...
hold it for few days?
I have the rest to collect...
Playing games with me?
On second thought, go on
Stop this nonsense!
Talk about your loud
and filthy mouth
Who are you calling
bitch
Do I look like a chopped
liver to you?
Tell me about it
Are you going to hit me now?
I'm a ghost
not a human
Oh well...
you're right
Knew you would
you retard
Stupid bitch
You've been around the block
haven't you?
I had some fun
because I could, you barf face
Yeah, I could've been
a surrogate mother
Let it go, you hag
- Would you if you were me?
- This bitch is insane
How dare she
Hit her before she gets to you
Swipe her legs
Pull out her hair
Let go, you wench
Who's laughing now?
Told you to watch it
Today is your lucky day
shorty
She must' ve been
a school bully
girls!
Those worthless scums
Drank what we gathered
for the last 3 years
in one fell swoop
No freaking way for us
to ascend to heaven now
What's gotten into everyone?
Listen to me, kiddo
You take care of this guy
and we ascend to the Paradise
If you don't
that gorilla over there
He's gonna get it
Got it?
To-ryong!
Sa-ryong!
Can't you read?
To-ryong means worm
you fools
Might as well move
and start over
Found a clean house nearby
with a good price
You don't know between
earthworm and snake
Did you even
go to kindergarten?
And you call yourself
an assassin?
Everyone is driving me nuts
Hurry up!
Our thanks to the
ladies and gentleman
who have graced us
their presence today...
Today' s special event!
Mademoiselle Luscious!
Gung-ye!
Welcome gentlemen
Full of juicy girls today
Your usual?
Premium liquor
with calamari
Will do!
Is Sa-ryong here?
Sa-ryong?
He's a regular
and in a VIP room
What shall I tell him?
Never mind
Cheers!
Irregular payments
and we know
these aren't permanent
positions either
You guys b, b... bitch
and mo, mo... moan
- Told you I didn't want to be in on
it -You are the one who started it
W... when?
What are you looking at?
Big Brother
I'm innocent
Handsome hunks waiting to
get acquainted
- Come on!
- Let go of my hand!
Little girl!
You go home now
Gung-ye!
She's a hottie! Get her
Get lost, you scums!
Ouch, ouch!
Watch it, you scum!
Abracadabra
Oh, yes
Oh, my God. Oh...
Oh... Oh...
Ouch, it hurts
Yo-yee
Yo-yee!
Hey!
Big Brother, run!
Ado Ado
Hori Hori!
Ommami Bemi Ommami Bemi...
It doesn't work
Run for you life
moron!
You call this swordsmanship?
Got some zits in your balls?
Want me to scratch them for you?
Stupid fools...
We sent a bunch of posers
and pretenders to avenge us
- They can't do anything right
- You call yourself a man?
We've sent them to
avenge us...
- But they can't do nothing
- I should've known
- But where's the ball?
- They were imbeciles
- Should have known...
- If they got that SOB
we would have ascended
to the heavens
- Idiots
- Tell me about it...
- What the hell were they doing?
- You guys are
- Animals! Animals
- They probably did this all day
Look at us now...
- What are we going to do?
- I'm going to move
Those idiots were
our last hope
This is all you do
after running away?
I'm disappointed
How about Dal-rae?
No parents now
and she has only you
Why don't we teach...
the Supernatural Swordsmanship
to them?
Not much time you know
Those Chinese bastards are
about to return to
their country too
These fools don't
even know the basics
Instructors to the front!
Fall in!
Go get her!
Get down!
What are you doing?
Go get her!
Oh my head
Lunge!
Okay...
Can't hear you
Hey, guys!
Are you gonna do it
right or not?
Slice in the air!
Okay!
Not bad!
Ya!
Do you know why
I rarely draw my sword?
Aga in?
I know! Don't tell me
It was exactly
10 years ago