Don't come here...
Give way! Give way!
Give way!
It's a very lucky omen, sir.
All troubles turn out blissful.
But you should be careful with your health.
Fine. Pay for it. Extra two hundred.
Three hundred. Thank you.
You've got a bamboo stick
of a very bad omen for Hong Kong.
Leave it for him!
Does it mean in the coming year, Hong Kong...
It shouldn't be the case. The fortune-teller's said...
Hong Kong's in the deepest of the valley...
If we work in unity,
we can definitely get out of the valley.
You look tired. You didn't sleep well?
I got many patients last night. I worked until ten.
Don't fag next time. Is it worth doing
something harmful to your health?
They were nearly finished. Just get the jobs done.
Play tennis this morning? How can I beat you?
Daily exercise's good to health.
No. I'm exhausted after working.
I'd rather sleep than tennis.
I've kept an eye on you. You always put
one and a half sachets of sugar into coffee.
Don't you think it's wasteful to
leave the sugar unused?
My parents have diabetes.
So I can't eat too much sugar.
And it's also wasteful if you
force yourself to eat. Right.
But now there's artificial sweetener.
Don't you know there're many people starved?
The resource allocation's always uneven.
OK, even I don't waste this sachet of sugar, it won't
fall into the hands of the starved people, right?
Both have a point.
Nothing changed, doctor.
Still I have bad cough...
Bad cough?
I've told you. Mr. Kan has bronchiolitis.
We've prescribed a nebuliser as a treatment.
Let's check the status.
This is Mr. Kan's X-ray film.
The image shows contraction of bronchi.
It could be emphysema.
But as he still has bronchiolitis,
we still prescribe a nebuliser.
For emphysema, we can prescribe ventolin or
ß-agonist. Also a large dose of vitamins.
Clear?
When patients try a nebuliser,
it's easy for the treachea to have allergy.
Cos the treachea encounter allergen like
nebulisers; allergy and cough occur easily.
So we must be cautious with the dosage.
Before the patients adapt to the medicine,
we can't use a large dosage.
Raise your head, Mr. Kan. Right...
Breath slowly... right...
Breath slowly
We go there.
Hong Kong reported the first case
of atypical pneumonia.
Morning, mum. Morning, dad.
Morning.
It's still early. Sleep for a while. I call you.
I'm a new comer. I don't want to be late for work.
Do you adapt to the new environment?
That's fine. The colleagues are nice.
You work like machines.
I've been on placement in the college.
I can handle it. Don't worry.
Viola.
The anchor's said in the hospital you worked
there's a patient with atypical pneumonia.
Really? Yes
Such a big trouble.
It's said that this disease spread
rapidly in Guangdong. Yeah.
You must be careful, Viola.
If the patients have bad cough,
try to avoid them.
Mum if all the nurses avoid the patients,
who looks after them?
It's only a job.
You should think of your safety.
The facilities in hospital are sufficient, dad.
Don't worry.
Gotta go to work.
Enough?
I go. Bye. Be careful!
Remember my words.
The rabbits and monkeys fight.
Don't fight. Let's kiss the kids first.
Then it rushes to your side...
Then rushes to your side...
Then to your side...
Go to bed after taking sweets.
Listen to the nurses.
Well.
Are you sick, Dr. Li?
It's alright. I have fever.
I bring some medicine for you.
No, thanks. I've already taken some.
Go back and take a rest.
No, I'll be OK after a break.
There're so many patients.
We only work, not risk our lives.
Let me take a break. I'll be fine soon.
Don't force yourself.
What's the problem? Still have headache?
It's the same. Still got headache.
Viola.
Viola. Yeah.
Give her a pain-killing injection.
Better today?
It's nearly the same.
Take medicine as per instructions.
You'll be fine.
Viola.
Viola. Yeah.
What's the matter, Dr. Chen?
This patient's prescription: The same
as it did last time. OK. Sorry, Dr. Chen.
When I was a novice, I also had a
heart like you. Later... you'll understand.
Why? We're medical workers.
Shouldn't we try our best to help every patient?
Yes! We make it.
We work nine hours a day.
But we have over a hundred patients.
How much time can we spend on each patient?
Just five minutes.
Dr. Li...
Dr. Li!
Dr. Li faints.
What's happening?
He has high fever.
Move him to the bed.
Look out. Go.
Dr. Li fainted this morning.
He has high fever.
Rapid test confirms that
he has atypical pneumonia.
For this reason, all medical workers
who had close contact with Dr. Li
must do chest x-ray immediately. We haven't
known the ways of spreading the disease.
All medical workers must
take the preventive measures.
Wear masks and gloves
when contact the patients
to prevent the spread of virus in the hospital.
Any problems? No...
Meeting adjourned.
For the details, I'll issue you a memo.
Dr. Chen, are you tired?
No... nothing.
How's Dr. Li going on?
Well, he's fine.
I saw him during lunchtime.
The CXR film shows his lungs look good.
That's great.
What's the result, Dr. Liu?
Don't worry. Both of you are negative.
But the medical students led by Dr. Li...
they all have positive test result.
And several doctors and nurses of 8A ward...
are confirmed to be SARS infection.
It seems that this disease's highly infectious.
It is. So I've requested hostel to self-quarantine.
You know, we face so many
SARS patients every day.
T's very risky. And it's
easy to spread to the family.
I think you should also request hostel.
Dr. Chen, please come to ICU.
Haven't seen pneumonia spread so
quickly like this. Why does it go like this?
It's much more horrible than expected.
Doctor... I’m very sick.
All pneumonia patients're very sick.
Rest and will get well soon.
I wanna leave...
Let me go, doctor!
Mr. Kan!
Mr. Kan, what's up?
Press him!
It's OK...
Dr. Chen!
Dr. Chen, Come!
Calm down!
Mr. Kan, don't move.
Press him. Help me!
Lie down! Lie down first!
Lie down first.
Press him! Mr. Kan!
No, don't do that.
Mr. Kan...
Lie down first. Calm down.
Lie down...
It's alright. Don't worry.
Why are there so many medical
workers infected by SARS?
It's probably because they had
close contact with the SARS patients.
So they contracted the disease. Does
it mean the preventive measures aren't enough?
These are individual cases.
The hospitals have sufficient facilities.
In good condition. Disease under control.
And they're likely to recover.
I say again: The hygienic facilities and
precautions in hospitals are sufficient.
The disease doesn't spread in
the community. Thank you.
Mr. Lau...
Viola
Mum
What's the matter?
Why don't you let us approach you?
Nothing. Just for the SARS virus spreads through
close contacts with sick people within one metre.
You contracted?
No... But if I infected SARS,
I'd spread the disease to you.
What's the life in these days?
I'll take care of myself. Don't worry.
Can I? Now the medical
workers are also contracted.
What's happening?
It's life-threatening to be
a nurse. You can't go home.
Don't do this job,
Viola. Resign, OK?
No, mum. Don't weep.
I stay in the hospital...
just because it's safe.
Hospital's not a safe place.
Don't fool me. It's a highly risky place!
Your colleagues haven't get well.
Some are even in ICU.
I can't bear this. You know,
even the phone ring gives me scare.
I don't know how to... face it.
Listen to me: Resign.
Don't you know...
you're the only daughter in the family?
If you have any accident, what
should we do? What should we do?
Mum, don't be like this...
Honey, let me talk to her.
Viola, listen to me. Resign now.
No. If all nurses resign,
who takes care of the patients?
Sorry, dad.
Sorry, mum.
Viola... I’ve made some soup for you.
I put it here. Bring it back and eat.
Thank you, mum.
Remember to eat them all.
Remember: Take care
of yourself. Remember!
Got it.
Bye.
You can't get in...
Dad! Dad!
Let me see him...
Mrs. Kan, calm down please.
Please... please let me see him.
Let me see his corpse.
Sorry, Mrs. Kan.
All the patients dying of SARS...
Their body must be sealed and
cremated immediately. You can't approach it!
Why? Why it goes like this?
It's the last chance to see him.
Why can't I take a look at him?
You still have humanity?
It's inhumane... Mum, don't...
Mrs. Kan, this is regulation.
We can't help you, sorry.
It's inhumane
Let me take a look at him. I see...
Keep an eye on her.
Mum.
Mr. Lau's confirmed
to be SARS infection.
CY, you should understand there're still
many SARS patients in our hospital.
And many co-workers have contracted. So we
don't have enough workers to perform the duties.
I think we'd better talk
about your request later.
I understand, so I want to
transfer to another hospital.
Why?
At first, it was Dr. Li.
Then it went to Dr. Liu.
And Mr. Lau, who said the facilities
were sufficient, also contracted SARS.
How can you tell us
to perform the duties?
Don't worry. We can
put the disease under control.
No! No... We've lost the
control over the epidemic.
In the morning, Dr. Li was
fine and I chatted with him.
In the afternoon, he was sent
to ICU and incubated.
I see. But the patients
need us to treat for the disease.
We treat the patients, right? Several
medical workers take care of one SARS patient.
Then they all contract. Is it worth doing?
How could we calculate?
If so, it's hard to do the calculations.
Yeah, it is. Today I infected SARS;
you treated me and you contracted.
Tomorrow it's my turn to treat you and you
contracted... I don't know. Can't make it clear.
If we go on like this,
all of us will die!
I'm medical practitioner,
not Aussie battler.
Do me a favour, please. My parents brought
me up and supported me to study medicine.
I can't let them down.
Do me a favour. Before I died,
I also want a last chance to see them.
Please.
I want to tell you: Medical workers
have their own responsibility.
I know but I just want a transfer.
But we're actually short of staff.
Well. If you turn down
my request, I resign.
Sigh... I gotta make some manpower
arrangement first. Talk to you later, OK?
Dr. Chen, are you OK?
Anything wrong with me?
You look bad.
I just lost temper in the Chief's office.
It's alright. Go work now.
Ms. Tam, do you get a thermometer?
Yes, here you are.
Oh you have fever.
Really?
Thanks.
Dr. Chen...
Dr. Chen faints! Nursing Officer!
Let me help you.
Drink some water.
Thanks.
Dr. Chen, you'll get well soon.
I wanted to transfer to another
hospital. But it's too late.
We medical workers
shouldn't worry too much.
You don't fear?
What's the matter?
Actually...
my parents worry about me very much...
They told me to resign.
What do you think?
I wanna be a nurse just for helping patients.
If I resign right off,
it seems that I flee from the battle field.
Your parents brought you up,
they don't want you suffer.
Me too.
Lf... they all contracted the disease,
you'd feel sorry, wouldn't you?
But isn't it too selfish?
Listen to me...
Don't hesitate...
I don't want...
you'd be the next patient.
Nursing officer, what's the matter?
Dr. Chen's suddenly in critical condition.
Check blood pressure!
Hold on, Dr. Chen.
We're here. You'll be fine.
What's his BP?
BP 70 over 50, pulse 140.
Check again!
BP 66 over 45, pulse150.
Vital signs?
He's getting weaker.
Tube!
Again.
Gonna flatline!
Paddles!
Dr. Chen, hold on.
Clear!
Dr. Chen.
Hold on.
What should we do?
Clear!
Dr. Chen...
The Hospital Authority invites
two Guangdong Chinese Medicine professors
to introduce new treatment for SARS
OK. We integrate the western and Chinese
medicines as alternative clinical treatment
to cure SARS and prevent
the spread of the disease.
Yes, Chinese medical
practitioners have much
experience in this treatment and
we got many formulas.
Sweet pea, mum's coming home.
Be a good girl. Listen to dad.
I wish every patient and colleague
recover and reunite with the family soon.
Sorry, mum; sorry dad.
I haven't resigned
cos I think...
every patient needs our care.
Each medical worker is vital in this battle.
But I promise you: I'll take care of
myself. And come back to have dinner with you.
First of all, I thank my colleagues.
When I was deadly ill,
they were great... they
faced me... and saved me.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be here.
My colleagues and I do... try our best to
treat every patient for the disease.
And we shall overcome SARS.
Doctors, I back you up!
Hip, hip, hurray!
Several suspected SARS
patients admitted, doctor.
Bro, you come to see me?
Yeah, open the door. Quick.
I gotta go to the toilet.
News headline Today new SARS cases
at Amok Garden are confirmed again.
Two victims live in Block E. One is
twenty-nine and the other is thirty-five.
And a 4-member family also contracted
the disease. Martin, what're you doing?
I... have a meeting. How about you?
I don't tell you.
Have you bought my birthday present?
Your birthday's our love anniversary.
I won't forget. Really?
Then I wait for your present.
And you make the schedule of
the events. Alright. I've made it.
We'll see the night scenery of Victoria Harbour
while we enjoy the candle-light dinner.
Do you like French cuisine?
Who tell you to let me know before
my birthday? No surprise for my birthday.
Have you had dinner? Or we...
Sorry. I gotta work overtime.
I can't eat dinner with you.
I'm busy. Call you later.
Bye.
Martin... Hello...
Morning.
Wendy, please come in.
Put on the mask, please.
Sit down. Thanks.
Take some precautions...
It's routine.
Never mind.
Well... You're granted
a ten-day holiday.
Effective immediately...
You may take a break.
Please don't mind this arrangement.
You know... the SARS epidemic's serious.
And you live in Amok Garden.
To allow our colleagues to work lightly,
we hope you take a leave.
Man will take over your work.
We don't discriminate
against you... I know. Thanks.
Thanks for your cooperation.
You may transfer your work to Man.
Have a nice holiday.
What's the matter?
Give way. Disinfection.
Martin, I'm on vacation.
What happens?
Boss said I live in Amok Garden. They fear...
I spread the virus, so they granted me a holiday.
They did?
Yes.
I'm on holiday for
ten days. Let's travel.
Travel? You're kidding! How can I
take a leave to travel with you?
Don't let me down, Martin.
Ten days! How can I kill the time alone?
I call you later. That's it.
Wait. Hello? Martin...
It's a bit much!
I'm not available right now.
Please leave your message.
Don't press it, Mike. There're a lot of germs!
Follow me: Press the button with a toothpick.
Got it?
Yeah, use toothpick.
Ms. Li, you're sick?
Gotta go far away from us.
Right. You'll spread the disease to others.
Or wear more masks. Such a wicked person.
Or call an ambulance to
send you to hospital. Such a fart!
I don't take this lift.
Give way!
Henry!
Faggot! The toothpick is
used to press the buttons, not bite.
Rinse your mouth after getting into the flat,
OK? Brush your teeth and rinse with disinfectant.
What's the matter? Hello. I come to inform
you... the Government has decided
to move all E block residents
to the quarantine camp.
Please pack your luggage.
We'll inform you later.
How many days?
Ten days.
Ten days?
Oh, where're the crotchet hooks?
Please... please give way.
Sorry... please give way.
Sorry. Please.
Give way...
Aunt Sun.
Don't worry.
The residents committee organises
a 10-day tour for us.
Fresh air in the camp site.
Good for morning exercise.
Hi I live on the nineteenth floor.
My name's Henry. What's your name?
Wendy.
The number you dialled is temporarily
disconnected. Please try again later.
Welcome to this...
ten-day 'compul-luxry tour'.
We'll live in the five-star camps. With
beautiful scenery and peaceful environment.
No one answer you even
you shout, I guarantee.
And there's a special audio system. How special?
You'll hear your neighbour with this system.
If you're bored, you may listen to your
neighbour. Enjoy the holiday here, OK?
Be happy!
Sorry. I got a call.
Hello? Speaking. I'm on the way
to the quarantine camp.
OK. I'll take care of myself.
Call you every morning, OK?
OK... talk to you later. Bye.
There's no sheet.
Only a mattress provided. But it's wet.
How can we sleep? Right!
Where's the toilet? Let's have a look.
Let's go.
No TV?
Poor facilities. Really poor!
Have you brought playing card?
No.
Go see if the neighbours
bring the mahjong. Let's go.
Morning!
Morning! Morning! Breakfast time!
VCD for amusement!
Thanks...
Wash hands before
eating. C'mon.
What's the matter? I haven't brought
the charger. Our model is the same.
Have you got an extra
battery? I've only got one.
Forget it.
Well... you take my
battery first. Thanks.
And I recharge yours.
I'll return you later. Thanks.
Welcome.
Have you had breakfast?
Or I give you a ride to canteen.
Hurry!
Why so hurry?
Take more water.
Two bottles more.
Take it.
What? How can you
put the mask in this way?
It doesn't matter.
You should put it in the bag.
I don't really care.
Martin... answer the call. I'm not available
right now. Please leave your message.
Hurry. Answer...
What's that? Glutinous rice dumpling?
You think we're beggars. I don't eat it!
Even beggars don't eat this kind of things!
What the hell place is!
No desk for my son to do the homework.
No TV. Like a prison.
I can't sleep if I don't watch TV.
Lunch time.
Haven't seen you in the canteen.
Sorry. I'm looking for the
woollen thread. What's the matter?
Nothing. Haven't seen you in
the canteen. So I come see you.
I lose appetite.
Can you help me to do something?
What's that?
Do something happy.
Sit down.
Why do you bring so many things? Stay
here for ten days. Without amusement, it's boring.
What do you want?
Come here.
Draw something on the masks.
Sit down. I tell you.
Draw something on the masks?
If we write some encouraging words
or draw pictures on the masks,
the kids and elderly will find it funny
to wear masks. They won't be so bored.
Let's try. C'mon.
What're you doing? Just make
a set of mahjong to Aunt Sun.
She told me she's extremely bored.
These are mahjong?
This is character four.
This is one dot.
Let's try. Make more.
Quick...
I'm not available right now.
Please leave your message.
Hurry. It's your turn...
Go. Next... yeah.
Good!
What's wrong?
Nothing. It's raining.
Well... it's only raining. Don't be so miserable.
Like you? Always laugh?
Of course, it's happy in the sunny days. But
you don't need to be desolate in the rainy days.
Look at them.
There're two sides of a coin.
It's you who choose to be happy or sad.
Things doesn't change no matter you're
happy or not. So I must choose 'happy'.
Remember.
Coming!
What's wrong?
Stomachache.
Are you OK?
Watch out!
Get up. Lean on the wall.
Did you eat something dirty?
Should I send you to the doctor?
No.
Haven't reached you nor seen
you in the canteen. Are you OK?
Nothing. I've taken some drugs.
Where's my cell phone?
Cell phone?
Here it is.
Today's my birthday.
It's the fifth day...
He hasn't called me.
Does he see me as his girlfriend?
Don't be like this.
Maybe he's too busy. Don't weep.
Night scenery, French cuisine...
All are fake.
Don't weep.
It's unlucky to weep on the birthday.
Don't weep. Be good...
I've made...
I've made you some birthday presents. I don't
want them! You see. So many presents.
Take away...
Take some. No...
I don't want them.
Go away.
Please come in.
You bring me here for what?
It must be something good.
Here's canteen. Anything good?
Wait a minute. You'll know soon.
Henry, where're you?
Don't play the game!
Henry!
Come out.
Ma'am.
What're you doing?
This way.
Martin's sick, so he can't speak to you. But
he's reserved a table in this French restaurant
as remedy of missing your birthday.
Look. It's beautiful.
Sea view and moonlight.
It's a romantic.
Please try our house wine.
Well try the appetizer first.
It's Foie Gras Saute.
Isn't it a luncheon meat?
Don't see it with contempt.
It's much more rare than Foie Gras in the camp.
I used a whole set of VCD to trade.
Let me have a try. Just one minute.
Let me tell you what the main course is.
Fine.
Salmon in French style.
Salmon? It's canned tuna. Where do you get it?
From Aunt Sun. I played mahjong for
eight round with her. You must cheat her.
No, I lost the games on purpose. Lf not,
would she give me her private canned tuna?
Let me try it. Wait.
I tell you what's the dessert.
It must be...
It's souffle.
It's easy. I used a gameboy to trade.
Enjoy them.
I'm the chef. Don't worry.
Henry, can I take my doll away?
I go to bed now.
I can't sleep without it.
Sorry... it’s my fault. Sorry.
Go to bed now.
Go back.
Sorry.
It's OK without a imitated Martin.
I imitate Martin.
Happy Birthday, Wendy.
No. Be the real you.
Then... Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Eat them.
Try the carrots. They're fresh.
I haven't cooked them.
It's me who cut the cucumbers. You're
so attentive. You must be a good boyfriend.
I haven't got a girlfriend.
You mean the lady talked to me on the phone?
It's my mum. She runs a
restaurant in Shenzhen.
I buy you dinner after
leaving the camp. Sounds great.
Hello. Sunshine on your ankle.
You just wake up?
Yeah. I call you immediately.
Well, see you in the
canteen thirty minutes later. Bye.
Morning, mum.
News about the atypical pneumonia.
Today 56 new SARS cases are confirmed.
The total number of the cases is 604.
And 6 new cases of death are reported today.
The age is between 25 and 58.
Only one case is resident of Amok Garden.
Poor! The young guy also
infected with the disease...
Yeah. I just think only the
elderly will contract
Now even the young guys can't
resist the disease. Yeah. Who's so poor?
Ma'am, you can't get in!
Where's Henry?
Ma'am, you can't come in!
Where's Henry? Please get out!
What's the matter? He was sent to the
hospital this morning. What happens?
He had high fever last night. The officers
suspected that he has atypical pneumonia.
He's under observation for SARS.
Henry...
Sunshine on your ankle.
Are you OK?
I worry about you.
I really worry about you...
It's you who gave me the helping hand.
When I fell down, you gave me the helping hand.
I'm afraid I can't see you again.
I'm afraid I can't see you any more.
Silly girl. I just contract
atypical pneumonia.
But I'm young. It'll be OK.
You forget what I said? There're two
sides of a coin. Don't weep, OK?
Don't weep, silly girl.
It's you who're silly.
It's two o'clock...
Who can see the sun?
It is?
I used to call you when I woke up.
I haven't check the time.
Don't weep. You leave the
quarantine camp tomorrow. Free again.
I miss you...
I really miss you.
It's me, Martin.
What's the matter, Wendy?
I got something to talk with you.
Let's have lunch.
Lunch?
Aren't you under quarantine?
The quarantine period's over.
I'm at home.
Then you should take a rest first. And...
we meet next week, OK?
You don't want to see me again?
Alright. Let me talk to you now.
I don't want to be your girlfriend.
We break up.
Wendy can you stop losing temper?
What do you want?
I mean it.
Don't call me any more. Bye.
Wendy!
Morning, Henry.
You're at home, Wendy?
I'm at the bus stop outside the hospital.
You can see me if you come out.
I leave the camp. How about you? When'll
you be discharge? Dunno. I'll try my best.
Hurry up. You promise to bring
me to your mum's restaurant.
I can make it.
Can you promise me
one more thing? What?
Promise me:
Call me every morning.
Alright.
But you also promise me one thing:
Don't weep again.
With you,
I won't weep again.
OK. I promise you.
When the sunshine's on your ankle,
I call you.
Well. Go back and
I call you tomorrow.
Bye. Bye.
Bro Hung, congratulation.
Wish you good business! Cheers!
My business is always fine. Please
be seated... Don't get into a fuss.
Try my Boston aerobic lobsters.
The lobsters spring like the aerobic dancers.
For vegetarian, try ambrosia.
In Greek mythology, gods
eat nothing but this stuff. You needn't
go to Mt Olympus now. Taste it here.
Bro Hung, isn't it a bit of hype?
No!
You know. Wanna earn your bread?
You have to bluff, sham and hype up.
Hype comes last.
That's not much of a hype.
Yes. Bro Hung,
what comes next to your mind?
Listen, I'll open a tourist agency next week.
I'll treat you guys to the global tour!
Thanks!
You're welcome... Once my dream
comes true at the end of the year,
You'll be grateful.
What's your dream?
I'd like to...
open a funeral home.
Terrific...
It's the so-called through-train service.
Eat and play,
dead or alive, all on me.
That's too good to be true, Bro Hung. My mom
has got leukaemia and was sent to the hospital.
A leukaemia patient cannot
last so long. Your mom...
Bro. I know you're with this
guy when I can't see you home.
Ling, you're here?
You're drunk. Go home.
What're you doing, dude?
Sell weeds again?
A dime a dozen, can you earn a living? Can
you make a good living with the chicken feed?
You even give out banlangen tea for free?
Do you know what business is?
Let me show you.
Seeing the outbreak of SARS,
I made the banlangen tea for the neighbors.
Wanna marry him?
Why not marry the guy opposite?
Look down, the one with long hair.
Not the gold-haired one.
Very long and tangled hair... The guy
with eight pouches... I mean the beggar.
Bro, don't go too far!
Pong, leave him alone.
It's OK. He's drunk.
Would you see him home?
Call you later.
I go now.
Bye. No need to see me home!
See your banlangen tea.
Goodbye.
Still mad at me?
You really went too far.
Am I wrong? Selling
herbs makes no money.
You think you're someone? If you haven't
won the Mark Six, we're no more than hawkers.
We've been poor. So, I don't
want you to suffer anymore.
Pong's a nice guy. I'm happy with
him. Don't poke your nose into my affairs.
You'll suffer if you turn a deaf ear
to my warning. Go now!
Hello.
Would you like to dine... with my boss? Do me
a favor, please. My boss wants to dine with you.
Would you... Don't give me
a hard time. I'm just a small potato.
You know life is hard.
Say yes please. I'll call my boss.
Thanks.
Mr Lam, what does SARS
to do with your business?
I sell no pig lung. What does it to do
with me? I'll open more branches!
But the business of karaoke lounge is slumping.
The turnover of your competitors drops by 70%%% .
They are planning to
close down their business.
They close their business, not mine.
I'll take over their shops.
But the turnover of your karaoke
lounges slumps by 90%%% .
Who said that?
Slump? Impossible.
Why I've never heard of that?
The newspapers said that.
Which one? Impossible!
Jackie Chan...
Are the reporters right?
Yes.
Why not told me before?
I've told you long ago.
Where?
At the restaurant last week.
Restaurant? I can hear nothing when drunk.
Why not told me when I fall asleep?
No, boss. You were not drunk.
You were talking on phone.
Talking on phone?
No business at all now?
We've got business, but it drops by 90%%% .
Some branches drop by 80%%% .
We've got business then.
I think SARS will be over soon.
Yet... We gotta...
take action to deal with SARS.
Let's begin with the pay cut.
Let me jot it down.
But... boss, how do you cut the pay? The more
the turnover drops, the more pay to be cut.
The turnover drops by 90%%% . Cut the pay
by 90%%% . Then, sack the workers.
Who will be sacked?
Sack the grumblers first.
Then, sack those who work for less than
three months. Sack the pregnant women.
Sack the ugly ones.
Sack the ugly ones?
And sack the tall ones.
Boss, only a few staff
will be left in our company.
Why so many staff? Poor business
needs fewer staff. I like it quiet... Quiet...
Have you called Ling for me?
You haven't called her?
Yes, I have.
But she doesn't reply.
I'll treat her to a meal of abalone mushroom.
Why doesn't she reply? What's wrong?
Boss, what abalone?
Abalone mushroom,
have you seen that?
Never.
Is it a bit of hype?
Not abalone. It's mushroom.
Mushroom?
Someone treated me to a meal of caviar.
It turns out to be sesame paste!
So I treat her to a meal
of abalone mushroom.
What time is it?
One o'clock.
Day or night?
Day.
Not a soul in the daytime?
Manager, come over here!
Boss, would you like something
to eat? Bullshit. You see.
Boss, SARS is raging now.
Everyone fears to be infected when dining out.
What's with you?
SARS, I fear to be infected.
You've scared away all my diners!
Take it off!
Boss, we gotta get some gimmicks.
How?
What are you doing?
Racking my brains.
You can take my post if you can make it.
You needn't be a manager anymore.
Get out of my face.
Boss, let's try one dollar meal.
50%% % discount for the senior.
Buy garoupa, get lobster free.
You can only make it with something special.
But...
Think something to do with my business.
Like...
Clients of our travel agency...
enjoy their meals here for free on the trip.
Can they enjoy their meals here on the trip
outside? So, that wouldn't cost me a dime.
The gimmick of boss, I got it.
Or the customers of our karaoke lounge...
dine here for free at midnight. We close
at 11 o'clock. No dinners offered at midnight.
Awesome...
Dine here at seven thirty evening,
get five matinee tickets of that
day free. As souvenirs only.
OK... Any more? For the cinema,
I'd like to suggest...
that... for the two thirty matinee,
buy one cinema ticket, get one airline ticket free.
I'll be broke. You won't.
The ticket is to Shenzhen.
There's no flight to Shenzhen.
The tickets'll not take effect until there's one.
Terrific!
Such gimmicks are cruel.
Damn the guy who
thought up those gimmicks.
Boss, those're your own ideas.
How much is the turnover?
Five grand odd.
Five grand odd?
It was fifty grand odd for a branch before.
Only tenth now. Which one? Close it down.
Not one. The sum of eight
branches is five grand odd.
Eight branches? Too bad.
Too bad.
Close down all branches.
That's even worse.
The sum of severance payment for eight
branches... is more than that for opening them.
Or...
In the name of renovation,
tell the staff to go home.
Reinstate them when we restart our business.
I've told them. They said...
they're no fool.
Sharing my troubles is caring.
They said you never share with them your money.
Who's that cocky?
Everyone.
Let me talk with you.
Didn't you wanna be a boss?
Let me sell all eight branches to you.
No kidding, boss.
Can you last with five grand a day?
Come up with something.
Tell them to move our branches.
Move to Amok Garden.
See if they dare to work there.
Sack the absentees.
Boss, moving to Amok Garden costs a lot.
The banks trust me. Borrow from them.
No problems then.
Mr Lam, you're our long-term client.
We know you do very big business.
But SARS is affecting the economy.
The banks are prudent in making loans.
And all your business is affected by SARS.
All belongs to the troubled industries.
What's more, all your
properties are under mortgage.
You haven't pay off
your mortgage payments.
Your request for loan...
Save your breath!
I don't want to spend money
spilling kerosene on your door!
OK... Don't be mad, sir.
I see you out...
Check us out later, sir. Sorry...
Hello. Wait.
Boss, Auntie Silly's calling you.
Auntie Silly, what's up?
Hung, something's wrong with my son.
Who?
Henry.
What?
SARS!
Congratulation.
What...
You can save your grub for your son.
You know, studying in university costs you a lot.
You can save a lot now. And there's a
saying goes/SARS brings you riches.
The government'll pay for your loss.
No, I wanna borrow money from you.
I'm poorer than you.
How can I lend you money? That's that.
Boss...
What boss?
Mr Lam!
Bro Hung!
What's your hurry?
You wanna escape me?
That's not the case. The dishes're not
enough. So I tell them to bring in more.
American steak, African antelope...
Save it. Pay my bills.
Seafood bill.
We sell no seafood for long.
Where comes the bill?
What's this? So fresh.
And more...
Fee for renovation.
You've never paid me a dime.
I did pay you.
I've given the money to the manager.
How about the red wine bill?
I warn you... Stop your show.
Pay me off now.
Or we'll stay here for good!
And if you don't pay off your debts,
we'll have breakfast, lunch and dinner
here. I take the meals as interest, OK?
Got it?
Go ahead!
Gulp!
Bro Hung.
I've counted it.
You sell your properties off cheap...
together with the severance payment...
There's 15 million left.
It's OK. I can turn
a new leaf with the money.
No. You have 15 million left to pay.
Can't you speak it straight?
Boss, have you thought of
applying for bankruptcy?
I'll have no face if I go bankrupt.
If Ling learns that...
Oh, Ling has made you a reply.
What did she tell you?
She tell you to go to hell.
Actually,
she made a good suggestion.
I fear no death, but who
looks after my sis then?
I.
Go to hell.
No, boss. My death
won't help, but yours will.
You're insured. Lf you die,
the insurance company will pay your sister.
But that's not for
the case of suicide.
Accident insurance doesn't cover
suicidal cases. But life insurance does.
Is this the best way out?
According to this book,
The maximum fatality is five. It's got four.
The torture of it is only one.
Highly recommended?
Yes, you've got the right place.
Make sure you jump from over twenty meters
high, nothing's around your landing spot,
the ground's hard concrete. And no man,
no tree on the ground. Do you know why?
If you jump and hit someone, you gotta
pay him. The insurance will not pay your sister,
But the one hit by you.
Which part of my
body hits the ground best?
Boss, the head makes the best hit. You
can see nothing when you land on head.
If you land on feet,
seeing your height, your leg
bones'll poke into
your body and you'll die a mess.
Boss...
Boss, wait a minute.
You... haven't pay me the wage.
I've forgotten that. I'm going to pay you.
And the bonus. Can you do me a favor?
Yes.
Push me down, OK?
Damn it! Why all the hurry?
Help me up!
Sorry, boss. Let me help you!
And try another suicidal method.
Bro Hung, how about charcoal burning?
According to my information,
The torture is only three.
If you has a good setting,
no one ever find you,
it is very likely you can make it.
There's little torture for charcoal burning.
You'll got a headache at the beginning...
feel a bit tired,
then, you'll feel sick...
and worn-out.
And then, your body temperature'll drop...
You'll become incontinent and go into spasm.
Then, your breath'll die away...
And then... you die.
So, all that matters is before you kill yourself,
take a dump.
Boss.
Where's the charcoal?
Nil.
Nil? What's eating you?
Today is Easter. Everyone has
barbecue in the suburb.
The charcoal is sold out.
So I've got no charcoal.
Only you can mess up such...
Don't be disappointed.
According to the survey,
85%% % of people who burn the
charcoal fail to kill themselves.
They become cabbages
coz their brains lack oxygen.
Paralyzed and staying at the hospital,
they need caring. This'll affect your sister.
And since you lie all the time,
your back muscles will decay,
bleed and breed the worms,
This'll affect the medical staff.
What's more, if your corners of mouth decay,
You can't brush your teeth. Your mouth stinks.
Ling'll not come see you.
You have only yourself to blame.
And more, you can't go to
the toilet by yourself.
You shit here and there. I gotta buy
diapers for you. This'll affect me.
OK...
You dare not jump nor bump.
You may...
What makes the insurance and the
government pays? SARS, give it a try? Boss?
It’ll be cool if you're the first one to be infected.
It'll be striking as soon as the press covers you.
Officials' attendance at your
funeral makes you a big time.
Wait!
SARS? All wearing facemasks? I'm alright.
Fear to press it? Let me help you, which floor?
Thanks.
What's with you?
Fear? Hong Kong people
gotta have faith in Hong Kong.
See.
I don't wanna. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I've had too much last night.
Take a bird's nest weight loss pill before I go out.
Remember to wear a facemask.
Bro.
How're you feeling?
I've forgotten that.
Bro, why you turn the facemask over?
Just the same.
You don't need to wear a facemask at home.
I should wear it at home.
It does no harm to infect someone outside.
But it'll be no good to infect you.
Bro! What's up?
Stay there, take off your shoes.
Why?
You bring in many germs, so dirty.
Take the shoes off and put them outside.
Outside.
I'm in a hurry, take off your clothes and
wash them. There're many germs, you know?
Talk to you later, bye.
I'm sorry, Ling.
I don't know you're here.
Hurry, Pong said there're many people
queuing at the shop. Bro, I go now.
Wear your facemask! You gotta
change clothes. Be ware of the germs.
Don't put the shoes inside.
Who said SARS is
highly infectious? Nonsense.
Twenty cases of SARS added to the list.
Among them four are medical staff.
They're suspected to be infected by the
SARS patients. Hospital Authority is reinforcing...
Sir... where do you want to go?
I'd like to see the patient.
Who?
My friend.
You're not allowed to see
your friend here. My relative...
What's his name?
I don't know all the names of my relatives.
I can't recall the names of some relatives.
Now's critical period. I won't let
you in unless you know the name.
Tom, check if any.
No Tom.
Dick?
No Dick.
Harry, there must be a Harry!
Stop messing around, sir.
If you go on like that,
I'll call the security guard.
We're fellows.
What fellows?
That's... I donated a few hundreds in the charity
show... for the performance of Michael Jackson.
So we're fellows.
I think he'll be grateful.
Go back and check it out.
How dare you! I've paid you!
Get out of here.
Your salary... I’ve paid you.
Check the name first.
Or I'll call the security guard.
Mike, how are you?
Any SARS at your home?
Coke only.
I mean atypical pneumonia.
Nutty?
Nutty? SARS is everywhere!
You're nutty as a fruitcake!
Uncle Keith! I'm Hung.
Your birthday? What a
coincidence. Happy birthday!
Nothing special. I'd like to ask...
Any SARS patients at your home?
Goddam?
Maybe there're SARS patients at your home.
Wow, Auntie Silly.
Auntie Silly, I'm Hung.
Yes, Hung Lam...
Nothing special, haven't you said your son...
Yes... that SARS...
Have he died? No...
Is he fine?
At hospital? Not yet go home? Fine! No...
I wish he get well.
Staying at hospital? Sorry, I've forgotten...
What's the name of your son?
Sir...
Have you checked it?
Yes, L...
Lee, Henry Lee!
Bed no.10 on eighth floor, right?
I can't see him without his name.
But I've got it now. Why?
He's a SARS patient,
living in isolation ward.
He's a SARS patient.
He'll die soon. So I...
Except medical staff, no one is allowed to
access him. The truth is I studied medicine before.
I'm a vet. Is it OK? Sorry.
For the safety of others, I'd like to...
request you to leave here.
No! I really in a hurry...
Life and death, let me in!
Sorry, sir. Please leave.
Or I'll call the security guard.
A security guard can't help you.
I get someone beats you.
I know someone, you know...
If you mess around, I'll call the police!
The one without the tube... Is he
serious? I don't care. Suck him.
Doctor, what're you doing?
I see the patient is breathing hard.
So I do the artificial respiration for him.
Artificial respiration?
He's dead.
We're going to wrap him.
Dead?
Really?
Shit.
I come here for SARS,
but I suck a corpse.
This world is ridiculous.
You can die of a rupture...
So dangerous!
I'd never eat a bad egg again.
Sis, what are you doing? Here's
Super Oxide Dismutase package. Bro.
Specially For you.
I drink red wine every day, why this?
Have you got it wrong?
This one is different.
Alcohol is bad for your liver.
This one does no harm to liver?
SOD has the function of red wine,
but not the damage of it.
What's more, you'll sleep
well with this. You see,
your face is yellow coz you
always work overnight.
SOD'll bleach your face.
Above all, it strengthens your immunity.
You know, the outbreak of SARS
is scary. I hope you well.
Quick, drink it. Remember to
drink it every day. Drink it now.
You take me as a guinea pig? Wonders'll
never cease. I do that for your goodness.
Bro, I've washed all filters in the morning.
And, I installed many air-cleaners at home.
The clearer the air, the happier we live.
Yes, I've told the administration office...
to check the drain pipes in this building more.
You know, if the drain pipes burst without
repairing, the outcome can be very serious.
Just like Amok Garden... what a disaster.
Bro, where're you going?
Going to hell!
No... going to help my friends.
My friends are in trouble.
Bro!
Bro Hung...
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
Come out.
Here's very dirty.
How come you're so silly? Bro!
Banlangen prevents SARS, get one.
Thanks.
Ever since herbal treatment's
introduced, most SARS
patients recovered.
The outcome is remarkable.
The combination of Chinese and
Western methods to cure SARS
reduced the fatality in
Guangdong to 6%% % only.
Bankruptcy is no big deal.
Do you need to die?
If you die, what'll I do?
What'll your sister do?
Not if Pong and I arrived,
you're done. Pong.
I'd rather suffer...
by myself. I don't want you to suffer.
When you get the insurance...
You don't need to suffer anymore.
What does the insurance mean to me
if you die? Have you seen me as your sister?
Bro Hung...
Have you sacked your workers?
Not yet.
That's good. Because...
Other than this drugstore,
my dad left me... a workshop...
which makes face masks
and medical instruments.
The fact is...
SARS is raging now.
The orders of my workshop rise and
I need a lot of helpers.
I've thought it over.
I can't use all your workers.
You may save some of them to help
you. Once the situation goes better,
the business of my workshop'll drop. That of
your restaurant and karaoke lounge'll rise.
You can reinstate your workers, OK?
You solve the problem of workers, but...
I owe a lot of money. I've thought
it over also, see if it works.
No harm to try. I've got more
prepayment as my business rise.
If you need money,
I can lend you.
I have nothing to do with you,
why do you help me?
I've never got such motive.
I help you, Bro Hung, in fact...
I want you to agree to the marriage...
I got it. OK...
That means we are relatives now.
You must help me then.
It's solved. Come up with
something for my business.
I must solve the problem of rent. The news
said the developers are planning to cut the rent.
Talk to them.
You talk to them?
Bro Hung, remember Ling's a negotiator?
Yes.
Oh, yes. A negotiator specializes
in dissuading suicide.
That's right, Ling. You may talk with
Bro more. He wanted to kill himself.
Let's go.
Why are your hands so hot?
Bro, you have fever!
Very hot!
Pong, where's the toilet?
I've got stomach ache.
Special news roundup.
Who declares to lift the
travel advisory on Hong Kong.
The clinical test was
proved to be 100%% % successful.
The government earmarked money
for the research of vaccine.
All SARS patients recovered and
were discharged,
except for one special case.
The medical staff suspected this patient
had taken in many immune enhancing food.
His cells is extraordinarily strong.
But at the same time,
he inhaled many SARS viruses. Therefore,
the cells are fighting against the viruses
His condition greatly fluctuates...