My son, our family owes
a lot to the cyclo taxi.
We work hard, day and night.
Eating and sleeping in the street.
Pedaling all the time.
Some mornings, the backaches
nail you to the bed.
I don't know where it all leads.
This has been my life.
When I die,
I'll have nothing to leave you.
If you can, see if you can find
something more worthy.
You're late!
Look again and see if I'm right.
"The People's committee makes loans"
"in line with the policy."
"of fighting poverty."
Where is it? Show me.
CYCLO
- How old are you?
- Eighteen.
Parents’ occupation?
We're very poor.
Answer me, your parents?
My mother died in childbirth.
My father too, an accident...
How did he die?
A truck...he died instantly,
with two passengers.
At Hang Xanh intersection, right?
Yes.
Who's left?
My grandfather, my sisters.
They study in the morning
and work in the afternoon.
What do they do?
The eldest delivers water to the market,
the little one shines shoes.
And your grandfather?
He repairs tires.
Who rents you the cyclo taxi?
The boss lady, in Cholon.
- Her name?
- I don't know.
- How much per day?
- 5,000 dongs.
And the deposit?
200,000 dongs.
Okay, we'll consider your file.
- We'll let you know.
- Yes.
These days it hurts.
When I piss. What about you?
Me too. It burns.
You've got to drink, it helps.
It makes you sweat, wears you out.
A doctor warned me,
take anything to build muscles.
You end up impotent.
Nonsense.
Yeah, right! Who can afford a doctor?
Better to see a butcher.
Shoe shine, sir, shoe shine?
- You free, kid?
- Yes.
Number 8, Le Loi Street.
How dare you steal our clients?
It's her...
This is our turf.
If you want to live, get lost!
- Beat it, you're on our turf!
- Go away.
Yes, you're my little fish.
So, how much?
It's a good day, 26,000.
5,000 for you, 21,000 for me.
No problem?
The thugs took a passenger from me.
Careful, each turf has its gang.
You hungry? Want to eat?
Wai!
Wash him, give him something to eat.
Go with him.
He was born that way,
He must be your age.
Take care of your tooth.
You see, I told you.
Okay, that's enough, get out.
Come on Grandpa, it's late.
Yes, let's go home.
- Bring tobacco for grandfather.
- Yes.
Is your shoulder better?
It gets worse everyday.
Do you have any balm left?
Hardly any.
I'll bring some back for you.
Grandfather, take the scale,
they send us by mistake
and change jobs, it'll be easier.
See how it's done.
Someone comes, you wipe.
You invite him, 1,000 dongs per person.
We shouldn't. The scale isn't ours.
Yes, we can, we've waited long enough.
No one has claimed it.
Your shoulder's hurting.
You can't keep pumping tires.
Let's wait awhile.
"On the old riverbanks.
Leaves and flowers fade"
"The sun dies, icy, shuddering"
"Hesitant, I cross the hamlet"
"My childhood, I remember you"
"l remember your graceful silhouette"
"You gazed at me, radiant, tender"
"l remember the sun was setting"
"on your ivory cheeks
your rippling hair"
Put him to bed.
Tomorrow. I'll come see
if you're dead or not.
Get up, little brother.
Go wash up.
"lf l, the Heron, die by boiling"
"May it be in clear water"
"To ease my children's suffering"
Follow them.
And not a word, to anyone.
"Bom has a fan made of palm leaves"
"The rich man says, I'll trade you"
"Three cows and nine buffalo"
"l don't want your buffalo"
"I'll give you a pond full of fish"
"l don't want your fish"
"I'll give you a raft of precious wood"
"l don't want your wood"
"I'll give you a bird..."
Tomorrow, come to the icehouse.
I'll tell you what to do.
Go now, and be discreet.
What's the matter?
- Who is it?
- Why?
He stole my cyclo.
Don't be stupid,
he works for the boss lady.
Let's go!
Wait here.
Don't go out.
Except to eat.
And don't lock the door.
Close your mouth, it stinks.
- Do you have any money?
- No.
We stayed up all night again.
Let's go to sleep.
- Can I sleep here?
- Another time.
I don't want to do it.
I came, because you wanted me to.
I called, no one answered.
Can I come in?
Don't touch her.
It's her first time.
Would you like to pee?
You want to piss?
Peepee, you get it?
Understand?
Go on, pee!
Drink...go on, drink!
Drink and pee.
Pee, please! Drink again!
Again, drink up!
That's enough! Piss!
And do it standing up!
I brought you two friends.
People are singing your praises.
You're a Samaritan.
You tried to save a drowning man?
The boss is happy.
She sent you this reward.
Damn, you're disgusting.
She wants to see you, for another job.
What? What did you say?
I don't dare.
I didn't ask your opinion!
You dare refuse?
What does he want? Say it again!
Open your mouth!
This is a taste.
Next time, it'll be straight. Sabotage!
250 tons of moldy rice.
Do you know who did it?
Imagine yourself in the headlines?
That's a life sentence!
Nameless river.
I was born sobbing
blue sky, vast earth.
Black stream water.
I grow with the months, the years,
with no one to watch over me.
Nameless man.
Nameless is the river.
Colorless the flower.
Perfume. Without a voice.
O river! O passerby!
In the closed cycle
of the months, the years.
I can't forget my debt to my roots.
And I wander through worlds
towards my land...
His father won't let me work.
I'm bored.
I'm going in circles.
So I busy myself with small tasks.
Is Papa well?
He just came home.
When he leaves, I feel so alone.
You're thin.
When he was little, his nose bled.
Does it still happen?
Yes. Sometimes.
I'll show you a photo.
He's still here?
What are you looking for?
He's our son. Please, speak to him.
He came with his whore?
Please.
I don't want to see him.
He was five years old.
- Stay and eat with us.
- Mama...
No, no, he won't let me.
We were starving...
No rice...
People dying everywhere.
We loved each other deeply. At 16, or 17.
We drank alcohol. To forget our hunger.
A bit of shrimp paste.
On the end of the nail. And we drank...
It lasted a year...
then the child was born.
He came out backwards.
Too late...almost dead.
The doctor said "Abnormal".
The father left us.
Coward. He was a coward.
Why coward...
He was only 17.
Younger than his son is now.
And then...
How much for a bottle of gasoline?
5,000
And this?
10,000.
Not bad! And all alone!
You're a real pro!
No cop can catch me.
I know all the shortcuts.
Sure, you're a cyclo driver.
You like skirts?
Women's underwear?
That's all there was.
You sure you're a guy?
Show me.
That's my gift. Take it. For real.
I want to join the gang.
- What did he say?
- What did you just say?
I got a shock too.
Which gang were you talking about?
I want to be like you.
Take him to Mr.Lullaby!
Look at my hands? See?
In 1956.
I was 17, a bullet cut the nerve
my hand stiffened up.
And look at this...
A bullet, through the neck.
It came out the back.
How it is?
And then this, here.
Guess which hole is bigger?
in '57,
a bullet shattered my shin.
You know why I'm telling you all this?
I know what you're
thinking faced with death.
I understand you so well.
"Autumn wind blows.
Sleep my child, sleep"
"The night is long"
"I'll watch over you"
"Until the end of the night.
I'll watch over you."
Listen carefully to
the art of syncopation.
"Sleep, my child, my beloved"
"my little one"
Keep it as a souvenir.
Take it!
Ah, for an iced tea!
- Waiter! An iced tea!
- Yes.
Why don't you love me as much as them?