Presented by
The Doppelganger Production Committee
YAKUSHO Koji
Hey...
NAGASAKU Hiromi
Takashi
What are you doing here?
I just finished work
Want a ride?
Yusuke Santamaria
Call if you're going to be late
EMOTO Akira
DOPPELGANGER
As you can see, violent waves
are pounding
the beach here on the Kii Peninsula
As we heard earlier...
What?
Welcome back
How'd you get back?
What do you mean, how?
Weren't you just at
Home lmprovements
Home lmprovements?
Are you crazy?
What?
Oh, no, did I mistake
someone else for you?
How embarrassing
Takashi, can you get the phone?
I've got my hands full here.
Yes, hello?
Nishimori Police here
ls this Nagai Takashi's residence?
Yes, it is
And you are...
I'm Takashi's sister
I see. You'd better come
straight to the Chuo Hospital
Um, um...
Did something happen to Takashi?
He just passed away
What?
The investigating officer
believes it was a suicide
Oh, you have the wrong person
Takashi's here at home
But,
we got your number
from his student lD
Please wait a minute
I'll put him on the line
Takashi, will you come here?
There's a strange phone call
Takashi?
Oh, no...
At Medical Cytech Corp.,
we continue to develop
visionary medical equipment
through unique ideas and
constant technical innovation
For individuals suffering
paralysis after a spinal cord injury,
were developing
the Artificial Human Body Chair
A simple sensor around the neck,
communicates your every wish
The ultimate nursing care robot
Its radical flexibility even
lets you chase a tennis ball
A little reading when you're bored...
Shut that damned thing off
Yes
I'm sorry
Maybe my will's too weak
Maybe so
Takano, adjust the sensors
Yes
What are you doing. Aoki?
Record that data
Yes
Don't you think we should try
simplifying the information stream?
What?
I mean, the human will
is fairly complex
We've known that all along
Well, yes
The product's useless unless
it obeys commands universally
That's why it makes sense
to try simplifying it
I thought the point was to rep icate
the complexity of human behavior
Get with it
Yes
Say, Hayasaki
Didn't you once say you wanted
to develop a new pacemaker?
Yeah
Got any?
Good ideas?
Nope
Oh, right
Get to the point
What?
That project would be easier
to allocate funds for
Since when were you
my enemy?
What?
We're all on your side
You have no enemies
in this corporation
We a l ive off that b ood pressure
instrument of yours
Don't talk about the ancient past
Sorry
I'l get the funding
Keep on working
Try not to be such a perfectionist
Do you need that data?
No, I don't!
Who needs a useless log of failures
- Here you are
- Thanks
We all work too hard
You're right
Can I ask you something?
Sure, what?
Do you be ieve in paranormal
phenomenon, Hayasaki san?
No, I don't
That stuff on TV, right?
The brother of a friend of mine,
ki led himself recent y
Huh
And according to his sister,
he died because he'd
seen his doppelganger
Doppelganger?
Like a double
They say if you see it, you die
But,
some psychologists claim
to have similar cases
When people see
their exact double
I imagine her brother
was in denial
That he was burdened
with some terrible pressure
What's your opinion?
My opinion?
Sorry, I'm not interested
Hey there
Key please
Hey, it's gone
Didn't you take it?
- No, no, I didn't
- What?
Yeah, I'm much better now
What?
I haven't touched his room
I can't just throw away his things
Yeah, more or less
I'm fine
Don't worry
Yeah, yeah...
Thanks
I'l call you
Yeah, bye, now
The President wants to
promote you to management
What do you say?
I think it's a nice way of
kicking you out of research
Isn't it about time
you considered taking it easy?
A management position
isn't so bad, you know
Murakami, I'll never work
for anyone but myself
When you don't need me, fire me
Tell that to the President
All right, I will
It's just...
For you to continue your research,
we need a little ritual. You understand
No, no way
That machine isn't ready yet
Don't be so stubborn
It's your duty to report on your work
I'll write up a report
But I won't unveil the machine
I told you, it's just for the executives
A hoop to jump through
lf you have to show it to them,
just take it! Leave me out of it
I'll go make some coffee
Yeah
Are you OK?
Is it Murakami san?
No, that's not it
Recently I've been...
You've been what?
Someone's been stalking me
Sta king?
Wow, that's a drag
Is it a woman?
Or a man?
- Oh, thanks
- Sure
Listen, Takano
Remember that...
Who was it?
The person you know
whose brother killed himself?
Yeah
How's she been, since?
She said things had settled down
Huh...
And her brother?
I mean that, the...
Doppel... ganger?
But her brother's dead
Oh, right, right, right
That's right
Silly me
Maybe I'm cracking up...
- Welcome
- Anyone joining you?
- Oh, no
Call me when you're ready
The same
What?
Like I said, the same
The same as what, sir?
What's that?
- Coffee
- That, then
Right away
Thank you
You're really stuck, aren't you?
Get out
This is my house
Huh?
I'll call the police
Like you're such a hotshot
Who are you?
Me? I'm you
I'm Hayasaki Michio
I'm Hayasaki Michio, too
What kind of nonsense is this?
Just hurry up and disappear
What do you mean? I turned up
here because fe t sorry for you
I'm overworked
I'm losing my mind
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm hallucinating
Man, you're uptight
I'm offering
to help you accomplish
what you can't do on your own
Hard to dream up
a better partner
I still hear him
You all right?
The figment's saying something
I can't listen
That's just it
This inflexibility of yours
has been dragging you down
Why the hell do I have to
listen to me lecturing myself?
You've got big plans, remember?
I have no intention of
discussing them with you
Neither do I
Get out
All right
And...
stop driving around in my car
I had to walk home
because of you
And you.
stop calling me a sta ker
Everything's ready.
Hayasaki san
Right
Let's begin
Are you OK?
Yeah
We pulled it off
Pulled what off?
That's not an artificial body
The way Murakami applauded
How tota ly humiliating
Can I say something,
Hayasaki san?
I think you need to consider
Murakami san's fee ings
You're a genius, Hayasaki san
No one knows that better
than Murakami san
In addition, you're
in a slump right now
Get to the point
We're all hoping,
all us employees are
That you'll come up with
another amazing invention
That's why
Murakami san and I are trying,
somehow, to pull you out of your slump
I'm hardly much use,
so it's not for me to say
But I'm incredibly proud
to be working with you
Let's work hard
And meet their expectations
They only think of themse ves
A heavy load, huh?
Their expectations
Yeah...
What are you staring at?
The budget's up 150%
No complaints, right ?
Right
Now you get to buy that
super computer you wanted
OK, right?
Sign off on it
When we perform that ritual
for our President next month,
let's give him a real nice shock
Leave everything to me
Hayasaki
You did this
Do you hate my way of
doing things so much?
You're incomprehensible
Hi, Takano?
No, no, forget it
I've been fired
No, no, it's fine I've been fired
Yeah, that's right
It's strange
I'm kind of relieved
Actually, I'd hit my limit
I see, he's still here?
He is
The doppelganger?
I don't know
But he's there
In my house
Even now
And what's this other brother
of yours doing at home?
Writing a novel
A novel?
Yes, the deadline for
the Newcomer's Award
that magazine sponsors
is coming up
Takashi always dreamed
of winning it
I see
But the Takashi I knew
was never that way
He was a slacker,
weak-willed.
totally dependent on me
Frank y, I'm happier
with the new Takashi
- But...
- My brother
probably met his ideaI self
and wound up facing
his own limitations
That's why I think
he killed himself
How are things with you?
I'm sorry. I wasn't istening
What?
Oh...
How are things with you?
Oh, my situation
is hardly that serious
I see
In that case,
you'll get used to it
You have no choice
Hey, lazybones
Off we go
This is hardly the time to
brood over the past
That's exactly the thing
that's holding you back
Hey!
Hey, off we go!
Hey
Off we go
Hey, c'mon, we're going
Hey
Hey, hey
Hold on now
OK, here we go
No
Why not?
I don't have a c ue
what's going on anymore
What'll we do with you?
Stop whining
No, no, no, no!
I can't do it alone
Leave me alone!
Hey
- Hayasaki san
- You still working?
Yes
What brings you here?
Not to worry
Shall I help you?
Huh?
Takano...
I'm sorry
It's all my fault
It's an honor to be of service
OK, OK, OK, stop
- Thanks
- Oh, no
- Make up some story for Murakami
- Yes
Here
Excuse me
I'll remember you...
for the rest of my life
Me, too
Takano
Yes?
What the hell have you done!
What?
To Takano,
by the door back there
Nothing
Liar!
I only did what you wanted to
I knew you did it
Did what?
I'll leave your lunch here
Don't bother me
My brother's gone
Really?
He's totally different
He doesn't seem
to need me anymore
Huh...
He's someone else
He's not Takashi
Even though he looks the same
Of course he is
What am I supposed to do?
ls Takashi finally, really dead?
Or will have to keep dealing
with that completely different,
other Takashi forever?
That's a tough one
Yes, it is
But, you know
I think the doppe ganger and
the self are entirely distinct
Oh, that's right, you said so, too
That he was a different person
So...
It's like having a twin,
or a chance resemb ance, so...
So...
So... right
I think it means your brother's
finally really dead
You think so?
Yeah
Awful
It's too awful
That's not what I meant
What did I do to deserve this?
I'm starting...
to not give a damn anymore
Sorry
Leave everything to me
OK?
What the fuck!
Hey! Get off!
- Move!
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry, sorry
Excuse me, I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
You, again
This thing's pretty handy
Don't touch my machine
Hey. hey, hey
Don't eat that crap
Look, I brought you
some yummy stuff
Wow, looks good
Did you do something bad?
Don't be such a wimp
I'm going to wind up
responsible for everything
The cops?
Why do you think like that?
It's just the opposite
Whatever you do,
as long as I get caught,
you're safe
Can't you even figure that out?
Not that I really care
Just get out of here
I've got a ton to do
AlI right, that's the way
OK, then
I'll be off
You are pleased, right?
What are you?
I was told to come here
What?
Your brother hired me
Wow, so this is
the artificial whatever
Pretty tacky
Shut up
Put that stuff over here
So, what do I do?
Sit here
For real?
Yeah, it's for real, real
You're an emp oyee. No back-talk
Try grabbing this
What?
Here goes...
Go
Grab it
You fuckin' around?
I am not
I can't grab it
Your wil 's too weak
Get out of there
Start over
You look exact y like him
Your brother
What?
It creeps me out
Like you're his double
Don't say that
Ever again, got that?
Lift both arms
Good
That's good, good, good
OK, now slowly try
raising them to your sides
Good
OK, lower them
Hey
Huh?
You can do it
Why'd you take 'em off
They're cool
Shut up
Whatever
Everything groovy?
Yeah, we l
Welcome
I'm not staying
Hey, you in a rush?
Yeah
Huh
Hey, Kimishima working out?
Kimishima?
Oh, oh, oh, him
Yeah, not bad
He wasn't easy to find
Just dumb enough not to find us alarming
Just get it over with
I'm busy
What's with the attitude!
- What?
- I'm bustin' my ass, too
Oh, I'm sorry
I'm always grateful
Fine. then
In that case
What?
It's time I...
Going so soon?
We can't be seen together
Let me know when
you need something
There's an equipment manufacturer
in Niigata, caIled MediCon Industries
Yeah?
I need to access their
confidential progress reports
Can you get those?
I can get 'em
I've heard they once tried
to develop something similar
Huh
I need more details
- Sure
- As soon as possible
I know that
I'm counting on you
Man, you are an asshole
There we go
Watch your step
All kinds of stuff lying around
Wow, this is...
So?
Yeah
What else do you need?
I worked here 3 years
I can get you anything