Take this I'll call you up
next time.
Thanks.
I'm fainting.
The building would collapse,
they're supported only by glass.
Judge,
count me in if you have other deals.
Forget it.
- Do you know it.
- You son-of-the-bitch.
Boy,
don't leave any traces in the car.
Don't blow it.
- Don't worry.
- Don't make mistake.
Let's go...
What's the word on his back?
Foul word.
Get the whore...
What's the hell going on?
Stand straight. Turn right.
Good morning.
Mo, you've signed it.
Yes. How can I forget?
Times have changed,
the new boss don't like this.
Don't say that I doublecross you
when you blew it.
If I didn't blew it,
you won't be the one doublecross me.
How can you say that!
I'm just giving you some advice.
Sergeant,
the whole section will be doomed,
if this was discovered.
You've signed it last week.
Shut up,
I don't need your advice.
Don't say that I didn't warn you.
The new Inspector Lo is straight.
He's notorious for scolding people.
I've heard of him
when I was being trained.
As long as I make no mistake,
he's got nothing to do with me.
How dare you,
you're new and you won't learn.
Good morning, Inspector Lo.
- Where's the occurrence book?
- Over there.
Why would it go over there.
Who's on duty today?
Me, sir.
Where's the guys?
Team 6 is in court today.
Team 3 and 5 is out,
the others are in.
District Sergeant Cheung
signed 5 min ago, where's he now?
- He just went out for work.
- Work!
Where did your inspector go?
I've been here for a week,
I've never seen this person.
I must see him in 15 minutes.
Fetch him here.
Did you hear me?
Yes, sir
No discipline at all.
Goodbye, Sir
What's go funny? Go to work.
Chiu, you talked too much this time.
What are we going to do?
Who told you
to flatter the boss wrongly.
I didn't tell you to take this up,
this is your own fault.
Kong,
only you know Boss's telephone number.
Please tell him the message. Please.
Sergeant, please beg him,
it's not my business.
Help me.
I'm only helping
the district Sergeant.
- Not you.
- Yes!
It's Kong, where are you?
I'm making love.
The new CI tell you to go back
to the station.
Return quickly.
Return, he must be crazy.
That new guy wants you back
in 15 minutes.
I have things to do,
we talk when I come back.
You show up at last?
Damn your mother,
why did you stop the car
so suddenly.
How can you pull over
in the middle of the road?
It's my fault.
- Move it aside. Hurry up.
- Sorry.
Hurry up or I'll beat you up.
What're you guys up to?
Damn.
Drive it away immediately.
You're trying to murder people!
Is that truck yours?
Yes, so what?
- I want to talk to you.
- You're crazy!
I've to arrest you.
- Go and check what is doing.
- O.K.
Don't be so polite, swear at me.
You're policeman.
You can park anywhere.
- Stand still and have an eye on him.
- Okay.
- Hold it.
- He's running that way. Go after him.
You...
Why did you hit me!
Run faster.
Don't stop. Good.
Get up and keep on running.
You're faster than my car.
But you're still slower
than my bullet.
Little brat, you want to run?
Run back the same way
as what you just did.
Run.
What a Lucrative return?
Check how many bikes are there?
There's a few boxes of spare parts.
Give me the total amount.
- For you!
- Of course.
Check the owner
of the pulling truck afterwards.
- Yes.
- Sir.
District sergeant, come here.
I didn't know you were a cop,
I'm so sorry.
If you don't swear at my mother,
you're good citizen.
You said I am a good citizen?
How did you catch those 3 robbers?
- These 3 convicts...
- Sir.
Should I be awarded
with the "good citizen" prize?
If no, I'll give you one myself.
These 3 convicts stole that truck.
I flew down to catch them.
Inspector Lo.
What happened?
District Sergeant is smart,
he caught 3 guys by himself.
And retrieved the truckload
of Yamaha motorbikes!
He's over there.
- What's your number?
- 105663
- What department?
- 1st team of criminal investigation.
Boss, this new boss.
How are you, sir?
Sir...
The convicts said
they have to examine their wound.
Forget about him,
fix him up for me first.
- Ok.
- Thanks, sir.
This is stolen as well,
what should we do about it?
Find the car owner.
You're Cheung.
Lo sir.
Return to the station immediately,
and write a detail report for me.
- Wong sir.
- Reporters want to talk to you.
- Tell them to wait.
- Yes sir.
Go right away.
Yes, sir.
What should we do now?
Wait in the car.
Inspector Lo was in a rage
this morning.
He knew you didn't come to work
for a whole week.
But I was working outside?
I have been in the field
for over ten years.
I've seen enough fierce bosses!
But he's really ferocious.
- Lock him back first.
- Yes, sir.
Do something. Don't just stand here.
Sir, you didn't write down
my address.
Inspector Lo.
Why are you writing here.
Is this your office?
What impudence. Sit down.
I am used to standing around, sir.
My report today.
What is this?
Is this a child's composition.
Rewrite it.
I've spent two hours
to write this up.
You can understand it.
I've read over your file.
You've been working for over 10 years,
and received many complaints.
Sir, it's true.
But many commanders
have commended me.
Didn't you read it?
Really?
It's over here, this pile.
Do you know what it means?
I know all the 28 alphabets.
But it's more difficult
if they're stringed.
Cheung, don't be impudent.
And be over confident.
And treat your superiors rudely.
Inspector Lo,
I've always respected my superiors.
And I'm always responsible.
I haven't seen you for whole week.
Is that being responsible?
I've been watching those few convicts
for the whole week.
Can I catch robbers
if I sit in the station?
What are you implying?
This unit is under my supervision,
you must listen to what I say.
From now on.
You sign for attendance everyday,
understand?
No problem.
Take it.
If you're finished,
then I'll write up my report again.
See you tomorrow.
Concise, fluent and accurate.
If he can't understand this,
it's hard to explain.
District Sergeant,
What did CI commend you?
Damn you,
it took a whole week
to catch those convicts.
Now he wants to boot me.
He's a hard boss to work with.
He must have some abilities.
It's not easy to be a inspector.
Stop flattering, okay?
Even if he 'boot' me,
you're not qualified
to take my place.
- Put it down.
- Yes, sir.
When you award
the "good citizen" prize for me?
I will contact you when it's ready,
be patient.
Thanks.
Boss, the report.
I want to complain about him.
You hit me without any reason.
- Shut up,
- you don't have the right to complain.
I was being complained many times
anyway.
I got the permission to hit you!
Remember, I'm Cheung.
Lock him in the cell, no bail.
YES, SIR...
Follow me.
Sir.
- What's so funny?
- Sit down.
What are you writing?
Check.
Why don't you write in Chinese.
What is this L stands for?
What is this stands for?
Location.
Why didn't you write
the Chinese word.
Copy it again.
What is it?
Boss, I can't read scribbles.
Do I have to write in English.
For your reference,
let me sign it after you copied it.
Yes, sir...
I know all the alphabets,
and about a hundred Chinese characters.
I still am an officer.
You're so brilliant,
district Sergeant.
Of course, how is my office?
Very big.
I don't come back often.
You've been playing at the station
all the afternoon,
go home now.
I'm going now.
Don't forget my price.
Sure.
Let's go and relax.
Judge, what's the background
of this old man?
He owns these two buildings.
Take a shower.
Judge.
Chicken. Where are you going?
Going to whorehouse.
Go to the pier immediately.
O.K. I'm coming.
Room checking,
present your ID cards.
My penis has retreated.
- How is that guaimui.
- It's good!
- Bull!
- Judge!
Smut you must be cooled.
Better than taking medicine.
Of course, it's fun.
Brother, don't wander around.
The stuff will arrive tomorrow,
we'll start tonight
for some capital.
Chicken ravage
Bill's gambling joint.
Not enough!
Fix him.
Judge, what do you think?
It'd be the easiest,
fastest and safest deal.
Just like drawing cash
if everything goes smooth.
With those millions of dollars,
we can get as many women as we want.
Remember, do in next week.
Tonight we must be on our toes!
See you tonight.
I've lost all of it,
but I'll get it back in the next round.
L, M, N, O, P, Q, R, S,
T, U, V, W, X, T, Z, Z.
There's 29 alphabets,
there couldn't be one more.
I don't have a talent for English.
Don't waste time.
You come here...
I'll go out and patrol,
you will take care of this place.
You...
What are you afraid of?
Just pretend you don't know.
Call me if anything happen,
I'll be here in 15 min!
That is. Cheer up.
Boss, but.
Who?
Yes, Judge?
Get me a car.
Okay, when?
Quick, I'll see you
at the old place in 20 min.
No problem, don't be late.
C.R.B.
I'm District Sergeant 105663,
please check.
Function 60 Delta Fox 5654,
it's a private car.
It's silver in color,
check if it's a stolen car.
Wait a minute.
Damn you mother-fucker!
What did you say?
I'm sorry,
I'll not scolding your mother.
Repeat the license number.
Delta Fox 5654.
The owner is Mrs. Johnstone.
Her address is at 66 Repulse Bay.
Judge.
- Take it.
- It's great.
Judge, take me with you.
Next time. Alright, bye.
- The car is not reported stolen.
- Thank.
Smartass, what do you want?
Straighten up!
Don't go! Watch it...
You'll regret if you run again!
- Why should I regret!
- Stand straight.
- What is it?
Why should I.
I tell you to stand straight.
Crazy.
Don't go. Mother fucker.
- What are you doing
- Why didn't you stand straight.
- Let me go.
- A nutcase. You don't listen to me.
Stand straight for what?
I'll break your skull.
Let me go!
Let me go, or I'll beat you up.
Let me go.
Psycho, I'll stamp you.
Don't move!
Don't move, or I'll shoot.
I won't move...
Don't play tricks.
I dare not to...
Stand aside.
Don't be impulsive,
you may misfire it.
- Lock yourself.
- No problem.
Lock the handle. Quick.
Lock myself, okay.
I shouldn't have done it that way.
- Chicken.
- Speaking!
- What time?
- Around 1 o'clock.
No problem.
Go. Alright, I go.
Go.
Chang sir,
what time you arrested him?
One missed.
And cropped out again.
Chang sir, I say that
what time you arrested him.
- Half past twelve.
- Thanks.
You'll be punished.
Where's the car?
Come with me, if you lose.
What can do for you?
How about it?
Please, come in.
How much you lose?
About 250 thousand.
Where you got the money?
Please come in!
Please...
Brother.
How many do you want to change.
All of it.
Boss.
Don't move!
Crouch down,
how dare you come to gamble.
How a lot of money!
Kill.
Get down, don't breath!
You came out if you know
the second shot is no bullet,
Go.
Why don't you fight back?
Chicken, we can go now.
Just now a rich man
give us a thousand dollars.
Don't move.
This car was theirs.
What is going on?
The joint was ravaged.
If I become unproductive,
you would be suffered.
I'll help you.
Where did you steal that car?
Did you see me stealing it, sir?
DF5456, 5546.
Be careful of
what you are accusing me for.
Do you think I'm stupid.
I have all the records
at the radio station.
Your want to trick me?
Don't trick me. Go.
Don't walk around.
He molested me
when I was walking along the street.
She said you molested her.
No. I'm not.
When she rushed to me,
I pushed her away.
You've asked me for the whole night.
What's happening?
D. Sergeant, he is a school master.
The girl said he molested her.
He said you bump into him yourself.
Of course he'll say that.
He didn't admit he molested her.
What a pretentious beast.
I saw you with Saboman.
Are you his disciple.
What Saboman,
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't pretend to be stupid.
You can't pick the guy's pocket,
so you trick him.
What pickpockets?
Don't blame for nothing.
He's molested me,
why did you question me instead.
What is the matter?
Inspector Lo.
I don't know what this guy
is talking about?
- Shut up,
- What do you want?
- Stop the nonsense.
- He's asking me.
Sit down.
Don't I have a right to talk?
Not bullshitting.
Lo sir, I suspect this girl is
from the pickpocket organizations.
When they blew it,
they blame the guy for raping.
Who is in charge of this case?
Chiu.
- Don't nonsense.
- It's me, sir.
I really didn't do anything
like that.
Speak when you're questioned only!
Why are you here then?
I caught the car thief.
Don't bullshitting.
I didn't steal any car.
What car did he steal?
That car was driven away.
I was walking on the street,
he hit me and accused me
for car-stealing.
How can you do that?
Don't you have better things to do?
- Come over.
- Stand straight.
Chiu.
Inspector Lo, I'm all ears?
Someone was wounded.
Check out the case at the location?
Yes.
- Kam.
- Inspector Lo.
Lock him up
and go to court tomorrow.
- Yes, sir.
- Lighten up.
I thought I could off duty.
Come here.
You've got the wrong guy.
You're too optimistic,
- take him down as well.
- Mo, yes.
- Bring him along.
- Yes, sir.
You've got to be careful.
This guy is very tricky.
Don't mess around, brother.
Quick, we'll meet in court.
- What is the matter?
- Inspector Chan.
How's that going?
Inspector Cheung.
The gambling joint is being robbed.
- Is that right.
- What are you doing here?
Inspector Lo said
I should have more overtime allowance.
The case was handed
to the homicide section.
Two dead, one seriously wounded.
That bad? The big boss is here too.
Don't disturb him.
DELTA FOX 5654
Sir, is this a stolen car?
Right, the owner is Mrs. Johnstone.
Right.
What?
Something was detected
in the stolen car.
Could be.
Did you have the midnight snack yet?
Since the homicide section
had took up the case,
we can go home earlier.
Are you the one who decide
when to call off the investigation?
Stand straight beside the car.
This is order.
Go. Chiu.
Damn, he only listen
when I speak in English.
It makes me mad.
Many superiors are here,
don't say the wrong words.
Please take a look.
There are so many superiors here.
We don't have right to say anything.
I'm going. Bye.
Calling for more people?
This way.
Where's the goods?
What's the price?
$20,000, including your watch.
Damn, fool.
Don't move!
What're you doing?
Don't play tricks,
give me the watch.
Here.
One is not enough,
is there anymore goods?
Yes, bring the long one.
- Okay.
- Quick.
Good.
How much?
$40,000 for one.
Chicken, give them the money.
Yes.
I'll pay you more for the guns
your men are holding.
Give it to us.
$200,000, come over...
Give them all, sell them all.
We'll sell them the bullets as well.
Put them all here.
Great, give me the money.
Give it to him.
Hide it first.
I'm rich. This is for you.
- This is for you.
- How about me?
Okay, you're great.
This is for you.
All included.
What's this supposed to mean?
You hid one. I'll kill you.
Damn, you don't keep your word.
I'll pay you still.
Don't play tricks.
I've been on the streets for decades.
Now you're in Hong Kong.
You're far behind. Go.
- Good morning.
Come in.
Good morning, Inspector Lo.
How's the case last night?
Gambling den robbery.
Two dead and one seriously injured.
Department of criminal investigation
has already taken over the case.
Do you have any idea who did it?
The owner of that joint is Bill.
I think he knows who did it.
But they won't talk.
Any other traces?
The car the robbers left.
It's the same
as the one I caught last night.
I suspect the two cases are related.
Good, then put the kid in the files.
And charge him for car stealing,
robbery and murder.
Inspector Lo, how'd you do this.
Put all the blame on him.
I don't mean it that way.
I mean, that kid was caught
and put into the cell.
In a different location.
Have a thorough check.
Don't take the wrong person.
Cheung, we're serve the law.
We don't judge
whether he's guilty or not.
The judge do that, not you.
Not you. Is it clear?
Very clear, Inspector Lo.
- Is it alright?
- Get out.
He's guilty alright,
but wrongly charged.
Let me out.
You're all dead, right?
- Don't let me go.
- Shut up.
Don't go away. I haven't finished.
Let me out, I'll sue you.
Damn you.
Let that monkey out.
I've to ask him something. Thanks.
God, my wrist.
What am I charged for?
You can't jailed me
for more than 48 hours.
You're up to your neck
and still mouthing?
Don't bluff me.
You can't do that in court,
you need evidence.
Right, see if the judge trust you
or me.
I'm frightened, really.
Someone is committing suicide,
open the gate.
Someone is committing suicide!
Stand here, kid.
Quick, come here and help.
Take him down first.
Call the ambulance.
- What is wrong?
- Tell D.O. A prisoner hanged himself.
The suspect hanged himself.
Why did he commit suicide?
He's O.K.
He's alive. It's alright.
- Quick...
- Come here.
- You hold it.
- Quick.
What's going on?
I didn't molest her!
- Inspector Lo.
- Inspector Lo is here. Step aside...
What are you doing?
The prisoner hanged himself.
Hanged?
You said you're innocent.
Now you're so afraid
to be convicted that you rather die.
Why didn't he die?
Inspector Lo, just let him die.
The school kids will be saved then.
Right! He's better dead than alive.
Then there'll be no appeals?
As the motto says:
You can't trust a cop.
What did you say? Why are you here?
I told him to record the statement.
Inspector Lo,
I have the file on that guy.
He's unemployed
He's probably involved in the robbery.
- Don't just wag your tongue.
- Okay...
Is it your turn to talk?
Lock him in.
Yes sir...
I want to see my lawyer first.
- Go!
- Don't push?
Give me his statement now.
Thanks.
I'm not more lucky than you,
Walk.
You won't admit to car stealing?
What a stupid question.
Come here...
Why did you give me food?
I don't want to send you
to the hospital.
You should co-operate afterward.
Dirty trick again.
Your boss is quite trash!
What are you talking about?
Inspector sir,
he dares to frame anyone for anything.
How dare you insult
the Royal police.
He almost killed that old man
as well.
And you were scolded.
It's your business.
Don't talk so much, it will be worse
if I want to incriminate.
You won't.
Do you know what I'll accuse you of?
Maybe attacking your penis.
Don't be so scared to shit here.
I'm charging you for car stealing,
robbery and murder.
You're worse than your boss.
Don't look at me like that.
I found the car you stole.
That car was proved to be used
for the robbery.
Two died and one wounded.
But I was taken here
when I got out of the car.
How can I rob
when I'm locked in the cell?
So you admitted you stole the car.
Yes, I won't be hanged for that.
Say it! Give the car to whom?
It is good for you.
Don't bluff, I don't know anything.
I've expected
that you won't confess.
You should have a bright future,
in Stanley prison.
Bring up that chair.
Come on, help me.
Don't touch me, you're diseased.
Don't touch me.
- D. Sergeant.
- What are you doing?
Got nothing else to do.
No...
Come with me to a drive.
Take him out.
Tell me clearly,
what's happening now?
Alright.
Where are you going?
- Quick!
- Where are we going?
Why should I tell you?
Do I have to report to you.
Come here.
I gave him the car here last night.
They live on the top floor,
I don't know which flat.
Take me up.
Boss, forgive me.
You want to take my life, don't you?
If he's really up there,
I'll be dead for sure.
Are you bargaining with a cop?
What do you want from me?
Just let me go up alone first.
And check what's going on,
then I'll report to you.
If we let you go, I'll be a moron.
Alright, let you go.
Open it...
This brat's got some idea.
D. Sergeant, this guy is tricking us.
Go up.
Wait here for me.
- Don't play tricks on me!
- Ok.
I wonder what's he up to.
Watch the end of the street,
you watch the corner,
- I'll follow him.
- Yes sir.
Should I tell Inspector Lo about it.
Do you want to shoe shine again.
You're right.
Did you bet on horses?
I've finished dinner.
What's a answer.
Quick...
Do you have your dinner?
Where did you go last night.
Don't bow out, go, charge.
Not this one,
quick...
Judge.
Who is it?
Me, boss, don't shoot.
What are you doing here?
To look for you guys.
Come up first.
You scared me.
Thanks.
- I almost killed you.
- Never mind.
Bull, why did you shoot.
I pulled the trigger by mistake.
You saw all the cops
at the racing stadium.
You're very well informed.
What news?
They're going to deal with you.
I deliberately come here
to inform the two bosses.
I'm not afraid even
if an army came up!
- Afraid of them.
- Of course.
Wait for me outside.
Bull, even the kid knew about it.
Don't think about it,
we'll take it as it comes.
No, We can't stay here any longer.
We'd better leave.
With so many guns,
we can go anywhere.
Go away, they have machine guns.
Follow me.
What are you doing here?
Judge, get me a car.
What car, can't we take the taxi.
It's coming, what can we do now,
the D. Sergeant not here.
Just wait.
Let's go.
- Run.
- Actually I...
Stop mumbling.
Excuse me.
Step aside.
So you appeared finally.
You're the judge,
my nickname is Dummy.
How dare you.
How's that going?
They've got so many people.
My mother.
Mother...
Run.
Help, Boy.
I'm the judge, come out.
Mother.
Come out.
It's enough, let's go.
Don't go out, he has machine guns.
Don't fool around.
Give me that.
Stop, listen to me...
I've got nothing to do with that.
How can you bargain with the cop
when holding a gun.
Now you're involved.
How many shots did you fire?
I can find, that out later anyway.
Where did you get the gun from.
After stealing a car,
robbed and killed,
now you're involved in the massacre.
What else would you be doing?
I don't know,
I've only stole a car.
Sir, I want to tell you something.
I want to tell you something too.
Wait for me in my office.
Yes, Sir.
- Chiu.
- Yes.
Take him down to the cell,
I'll charge him myself.
Yes, Sir.
Do you think you're Rambo.
You didn't tell me with something
so important happening.
Do you want to frame me.
If I knew they have
that much ammunition,
I will inform you.
Alright, what's your relationship
with that kid?
How dare you let him out
to kill people.
I don't know how you're promoted
to D. Sergeant.
I'm promoted for my ten years
of service.
We're in
the criminal investigation department.
I know the kid didn't kill anyone,
so I took him out to help
in the investigation. Sir.
What are you yelling for?
I was afraid that you can't hear me.
You.
You're not on this case anymore.
From now on, you will stay
at the station, get out.
Thanks for your recommendation, sir.
D. Sergeant.
What did Inspector Lo say?
He took away my case.
What.
I was the one who caught the guy.
Now he will be accused of murder.
I know he is innocent.
You can't fight with the P.I.
I wouldn't care.
I don't feel ashamed for that.
I have no regrets.
What the hell. I won't die.
- Don't follow me.
- Yes sir.