Hurry up...
We're not playing chess here
Exactly
Alright, what's the rush?
Got any flower?
Of course
Hurry
Fine... I won't play next time
Come on
Having fun here
Four East
Hold on...
Four East?
Yes
Thirteen Orphans
Look, the 4 different winds,
the 3 different dragons
three different singles
three different nines
128 dollars each, please
Thirteen Orphans
Pay up...
So strange... I had a good hand! Look
Just pay up, no excuse
Look, it's a good hand
I want one, four and seven dots
Guess, it's one dot
I can't believe it
Another one
Eight, seven...
You'll win for sure
Six pairs and a half
Same here
Alright
You too?
Can't believe it
So?
You'll see
What's the big deal?
Open
Look closely
Seven, eight, nine, ten, jack,
a straight flush
So unlucky
Don't believe it!
It's strange
Better than mine
Come on
Hurry up...
Discard one card
Hurry
It's your turn
Not 4, it's 3
Leave one if you pass
Pass
Me too
Pass, three
Three again? So many of three
No? Pass
Pass
Three, one, one, three
Three, six
Six, two
Pass
Two, five
Five, five
Five, three
Pass again
Don't keep passing
Yes, look at him
Pass
Me too
What's the big deal?
I've passed the fifth one
Three, two
Two, two
Two, four
Four, six
Then...
Six, one
One
One, two
Open
Fine, eight for me
Eight, double
Twenty, thirty, forty eight, ninety six
Thanks
This is bad news for you
One hundred and ninety two dollars
That's all, split it
Check this out
How much would this be worth?
I don't run a pawn shop here
Fine, I'll go to one
Hurry
Fifty dollars, I'll gamble again
Hey, watch it
It's you. Where are you going?
What's the rush?
Where're you going?
I've been very unlucky
I'm going to gamble again
Just can't believe I won't win
Believe it
Your forehead is dark, a sign of bad luck
Take a break
I don't believe I'm that unlucky
I've got fifty dollars
You want to bet?
Alright
What should we bet on here?
I've got an idea
I'm listening
It's easy
Just answer 'yes' to whatever I ask
You must be quick though
You'll lose if you say 'no'
That's it?
Yes
Fine, let's have a trial
Listen up
Has your wife gone off with another man?
What kind of question is that?
Yes or no?
Yes
Take it, can't believe you
For money's sake
Another 10 dollars
10 dollars
Are those men your fathers?
I've got so many fathers?
Yes or no?
Yes
Good boy
Buy a milk bottle with it
I'm telling you
If all my fathers are as nice as you...
I'll be rich; another ten
No, I've lost twenty dollars
Wait. One more time
Fine, but the stakes will be higher
Fine
Seventy dollars
Clean your ear wax
Is all this money mine?
No, I've got some too
You lose, you said 'no'
I'm so stupid. Should have said 'yes'
Come on
Place your bets
One, two, five, total eight, small
All small win
How come you win every time?
Of course.
I've offered my respects to the Gods
Is it working?
I get what I ask for
Just follow my lead
Excuse me
So many notes
Can I borrow a hundred?
No way, you still haven't paid your debts
Get lost, I'm trying to gamble here
Place your bets
Mister, please place my 200
on the upper gate
Upper gate
Two hundred on upper gate
Fine
Two hundred dollars? Are you sure?
Yes
I'll take my chances
You'll lose
Come on
Hold on
Place your bets
Ten again
Look
So?
You'll see
Oh, shit
Seven
I must be unlucky
Banker opens
Three, four, all win
You've it
So do you
You're unlucky
What have you got?
Nine, win
I knew I would win
Here you go
Hey, I placed two hundred dollars,
how come?
I'm doing this according to
the money on the table
You placed one hundred,
I'll give you another 100
I told him to place two hundred
Crazy
What's wrong with you?
I gave you two hundred
Two hundred? One hundred only
Give me back the money
You crook
You took my money
& wish to pocket it, huh?
Give me back my money
Give me the money back
What's going on?
The woman says
he has siphoned off her 100 quid
I told him to place two hundred
Fine, shut up
Give her two hundred, and send her away
Why would I take your money?
You, come over
Come here
Brother Nine, give me a chance
Kid, you've got some nerve
Look at all these IOU notes
What do you want here?
You want me to break your ribs?
Or have your legs amputed?
Tell me
I've been very unlucky
I've pawned everything
...except my wife
I've seen her before.
Quite a figure she's got
That's what everyone says
Get your wife to sleep with me
tomorrow night
Then I'll let you off
No way
I'd say no even if she agrees
Beat him up
Brother Nine, you should know
Women always ask for a show
I've got to give her some incentive
Lend me two hundred
to get her some trinkets
Don't try anything funny
Relax, I'll make sure she sleeps with you
Thanks, Brother
Two hundred dollars, that's a good deal
Cheers
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to my wife
This beer is the best, dear
Drink some more
I thought the only thing
you remember is gambling
You still remember my birthday?
I've come to my senses
You, my wife, are most dear to me
Let's have another drink
No
It's your birthday
You must drink some more
Good
Stop it
Darling
We are in public
Let's not go home tonight
Where are we going then?
To a love motel
How much?
Interesting? So pretty
So many mirrors
Come here
So?
Don't worry, it's all set
Come over when I turn off the light
So pretty
Strip
Let me help you
Wait a minute
It's fun
Come here, darling
I want to take a bath first
Come on
You look gorgeous, darling
OK
Wow! You're amazing
Smells weird
Damn you
Get in
Sit down
Damn it
Turn your head
Let me teach you a lesson
You piece of shit
I've met a hot babe lately
And look what happened
I can't do anything now
Brother Nine, it could have worked out
You should have told me
about your body odor
Then I could have done...
No excuses
You've got two choices
First, you kill yourself
Second, let my staff to kill you
However that'd be a terrible death
So?
Is there a third option?
Yes, cut it off
Brother Nine, if you cut it
Then I'll become an eunuch
I'd rather kill myself
Fine, within 24 hours...
I want to read about your suicide
in the headlines
Or you'll be torn into pieces
within 48 hours
Think it over
Where are you going, honey?
You heartless fellow
You set up a trap for me
to sleep with some guy
I will divorce you
Honey, I had no choice
ltjust happened
Please forgive me
Cry all you want
Even if you cry yourself to death
I won't fall for your tricks
Crocodile tears
Leave me your number
Then I can call you sometime
...for tea
Call 999 or 110, you shit
999 or 110?
Easy to remember
Wait, honey
Kramer vs. Kramer
Me against the Jaws this time
Good bye Mahjong, pai gow, solitaire
Bye, honey
When unluckly even a tree
tends to bully you
Discard it
I'll pick another tree
My friend...
Be careful...
Please, don't do it
Don't try to save me
Sit down
I must die
I'll pick another tree
Thank God
You thought I care about you?
I just want to save the tree
This is government property
If you break it, then I'll be in trouble
Did you break this?
Yes or no?
Let's go to the police station
I've already charged you...
for destroying trees in the park
Do you have money for bail?
No, I'm broke
How about this?
Call your relatives to bail you out
I've got none. Even my wife has left me
I'll trust you for now
You can bail yourself out;
report to court on time
Sign here
Go
This is the most powerful type
of rat poison
Careful, one could die
Really?
How much?
Three dollars
Hey, what about my ecstasy pills?
I've paid you
Lower your voice
I sell these items secretly
Quiet
Hurry
Pay up
Ah Mei, where are you going?
For dinner
Your boyfriend's nice
Yes
I think so too
Let's call him
Go on then
Alright
For you
Go
Let's go
It's me
Pay up
Fine, talk to you later
Here you go
So many coins!
This is the wrong one
What's wrong with you?
Yes
Let's return it
What's this?
He must have taken the wrong packet
Such a drag, we're in a rush
Fine, take this
Goodbye, Hong Kong
My eyes to donate to
the Japanese blind man
My kidney for a friend who needs it badly
My blood for the vampire
So stupid
My teeth for a toothless guy
Signed, Cai Tou
You...
A flasher... nuts
Salute
Left, right, left, right
What are you doing?
Maybe I should cut it off
Cut it into pieces
Cut up your clothes
You want to flash again?
Left, right, left, right
Attention
Turn to the left
Right turn
Turn to the back
Stand still
Get set, ready
Don't run, stop
I'll shoot
Go... go... go
Thanks
Thanks everyone
Stand still
Let me borrow this
Try again
Crazy
Got you
Sir
Sir, this guy is a streaker
You again? What's your problem?
Sir, look at my thigh
Am I Miss Hong Kong material?
Put it down
Do you have any idea
...what day is it today?
Your god mother's birthday?
My god father's birthday?
Wedding anniversary of them both?
No
Today is my unlucky day
You've been here twice,
what's the matter with you?
Nothing, sir
Sir, why isn't he...
wearing any pants?
PC1331
Yes, sir?
Get a piece a cloth for him
Yes, sir
Thanks
Listen, now I must charge you...
for indecent behavior in public
You have no money
And you said you have no relatives
Put him in the cell for a night
Go to court in the morning
Go
Sir
What?
Just speak up
I have no relatives
But I have a friend
I'll call him to bail me
Go on then, don't try anything funny
Brother Nine, you are so mean
If you want to collect my debt
See me in hell
Here I go
Damn it, I stepped out
for less than a minute
And someone broke my wind shield
LPG Gas can? Asshole
I will kill you if I see you
What now? I'm still alive?
Must be the robbers who dropped it
Hey, whaddya know!
Reckon it ain't my time to die yet
I struck gold
Spiritual tablet of my beloved daughter
Liu Ah Cui
Born on 7th Feb., 1958
Died on 2nd May, 1980
She's only 20 something
I thought it's made of gold
Such an unlucky thing
Who are you looking for?
You
Me? Do I know you?
I know you
Did you pick up...
a bag in the alley earlier?
No
What about this picture? Is this you?
Come in
So what?
What are you going to do?
I picked it on the street
Don't worry
I'm not here to collect the jewelry
And I've got more to offer
There's no free lunch in this world
That's for sure
Listen, my name is Liu San
This belongs to my daughter, Ah Cui
She was captured by the gangs
while entering...
Hong Kong illegally;
got tied up, raped and killed
Her body was dumped in the wild
I've watched that in the news
Listen well
She's my only daughter
After she's dead
I don't want her to be alone
Don't want her to be a wandering ghost
I must help her to find a husband
So that she won't be lonely
And what's that got to do with me?
Go advertise in the classifieds
It concerns you now that
you've picked up the bag
If you promise to marry her
I'll give everything to you
You haven't got a lot in here
I deserve more
for marrying a piece of wood
If you marry my daughter
...I'll be very generous
I'll give you a flat
which is already worth a few hundred grand
Below the peak,
across the Governor's house
Right of Queen Mary Hospital;
left of funeral home
Left, right, above, below
Where exactly is it?
Next to Kowloon Funeral parlor,
No. 2 Maple street
Has good vibes.
All in the neighborhood became rich
999 sq. Feet including the parking space
Let me think about it
That will be around a million
Old man, don't trick me
If you agree, we can go to a lawyer now
Deal
Master, your son-in-law
Please
The groom & bride, bow to heaven and earth
First bow, second bow
Please take a seat, bride's father
Please drink this, from the groom
Dad, please have some tea
Please
Have some tea, dear
Groom, please serve the tea
to your mother-in-law
Mom, please have some tea
Please
This is from my wife
Thanks
This is from me
Thanks, master
Groom, go have a drink
with the bridesmaids
Ladies
I'm here to raise a toast to you
Ladies, we don't have a big feast
I'm not a good host
Please help yourselves
Groom, bride,
please go to the bridal chamber
Good night
Thanks
Good night, master
From this day on
You are Ah Cui's husband now
In order for you to get along well
I must tell you about her habits
She's hot-tempered, knows Judo
You must treat her well
She likes to eat instant noodles
with fried eggs
You must cook for her every day
She likes a San Miguel before dinner
And a Guinness stout afterwards
That's good for health
She's lazy
She reads in bed and often leaves
...the light on at night
Electricity is expensive
Here's a switch
Clap once and the lights will turn off
Clap twice and it's on
Interesting. Where did you get it?
Lane Crawford
Well then, I won't bother you two
I'll drop by to see you sometime
Good night
You must be nuts
Made me marry a ghost!
Made me toast with a ghost. This is crazy
I am only in this for the money
Sick of your sight
Stay in here
Better turn in soon
Is this place haunted?
So it's you
You stupid dog
Didn't expect a dog here
Fine, since you're here before me...
You can live here
You just scared me a while back
Silly me. There are no ghosts on earth
Scared myself
Romeo and Juliet,
a pair of star crossed lovers
Hey, what's that terrible singing?
They won't be separated...
Won't be separated
Fine, stop it
You sound terrible
Sorry?
I told you to stop
What? This is Hong Kong
I can do whatever I like
Sing whatever I like
Listen
I come from the hills, carrying an orchid
I can dance too, look
A ball on the left, a ball on the right
I'm playing ping pong
Damn it
I'll show you
Go on, sing
You threw a tennis ball at me
See if you'll keep singing
Shake! From head to toes
Shake! Johnson's Baby Powder
Shake, shake, shake
Use Johnson's Baby Powder
Shake
You will feel like a baby
all through the day
It's great
Shake
Hey, Doggie?
What? I'm busy tonight
I've a date
I'm going to the disco with Ah Zhu
Hello
Miss Air Hostess
You must be busy
flying all around the places
Mister
You still haven't paid
the cleaning charges
Fine... 30 dollars, is it?
Thank you
Who is it?
It's me, Cai Tou
Hello, darling
Oh, Ah Zhu, look at you
You are sexy
...and hot
Let's go out for dancing, huh?
My daddy might lecture me
We'll play at home
Tell me whether you love me or not
Don't lie to me
I'm happy besides you
You have great legs
Let's go to the disco
Ah Zhu, let's go
Let's go
Why did you hit me?
Why?
You! We were married yesterday
And you're cheating on me
Listen, I'm here for you
That means you are looking for me
I...
She is she, I'm me
She's a slut, I'm Joan of Arc
We're not the same
What happened to your voice, who are you?
Your wife
Get back home now
Beat you up
Ah Zhu, it's me, Cai Tou
Get out, go home
Damn it
I don't believe this
It's only instant noodles...
not Shark's fin soup; big deal
Romeo and Juliet
Star Crossed lovers
Wishing to be in love forever
Stop it
Never will be apart
We...
I'm prepared
I've got a racket to block you
What do you say now?
I...
Are you serious, Cai Tou?
The ghost is so powerful?
I'm not kidding
It's scary
If that ghost...
really died a terrible death
like on the news
I'm sure she will haunt you forever
So unlucky
I'd have divorced her
...but I'm in it for the money
Don't worry
I'll think of something
It's simple
What?
Give me a thousand
I'll find you a psychic
And she can talk to the ghost
Are you kidding?
She can talk to the ghost?
I'm serious
Just pay up
Fine
Only one?
How much do you need?
An extra one, at least
The gods, the guards of hell
Liu Ah Cui, the illegal immigrant
who died earlier
Her husband Cai Tou
would like to have a chat with her
Come up here now
What's she doing?
Shut up
What's happening?
She's got possessed
Possessed?
Give me back my life
Where are you from, woman ghost?
I was an illegal immigrant
Why can't you rest in peace?
I've had a tough life
While I was trying to sneak
over the border
I got captured by a gang
They robbed my money
Raped me and then killed me
Barbwired my hands
and put my body in a carton
I died terribly
Why did you try to sneak over the border?
I wanted to look for Teresa Tang
Is she crazy?
For a pop singer?
Teresa Tang has lots of fans
You've come to the wrong place
Teresa Tang is not in Hong Kong
Go look for her elsewhere
Please leave my client alone
No, I can't
I must get my
Hong Kong identity card first
The decree of special pardon
doesn't apply now
You can't get the HKID card
Where can I go then?
No. 1 Pine Street
Give her some money and it might work
Go ask her
Ask her if she'll leave if we pay...
My friend, he said...
Would you leave if I pay you?
Yes
Open a bank account for me
Fixed savings or current account?
Even ghost asks for money
Exactly
I'll kill you if you won't pay
Let go of me...
You stepped on my toes
Who switched on the light? It's over
What now?
Turn it off...
You lied?
Asshole, you lied to me
Give me back my money
It's only a thousand
Think of it as helping a friend
Who's your friend? Pay up
I've spent it already
I've hired a crew, go
Listen
Don't trust anyone, idiot
Damn it
I don't want to see you again
My friend...
I ain't called
the Great Spiritual Master for nothing
Sit down
I'm the Great Spiritual Master
If there's something wrong...
Also...
Family problems
Possessed by ghosts, come to me
How do you know that?
Have a seat, my friend
You don't look so good
You're being haunted
A series of love problems
If I don't help...
You'll die tonight
Don't bluff
My friend
You didn't heed good advice.
Your time is up
What a shame!
I'll really die?
Yes, for sure
You can help?
Certainly
Are you for real?
I got duped yesterday
Don't worry, you can pay after the job
I won't take your money if it doesn't work
Don't bluff
I'll show you
Fine
The incense goes to the underworld
Here I'm calling the great exorcists
The Four Heavenly Kings
Assist me to expel the ghost
I'm here to capture the spirit
Only the spirit
The spirit of Ah Cui
Bless this rice
I'm here to capture the spirit
Heavenly gods
This is urgent
One, two, three, four
Five, six, seven, eight
Liu Ah Cui, I must capture you
Ding, ding, ding
I must capture Liu Ah Cui
You can turn on the lights now
I've caught the ghost
Miss Liu, please forgive my rudeness
Mister, the ghost you told me to catch
...isn't a wandering ghost
She's the master of the house here
I can't catch her
She's kicking me out
Sorry, I'm off now
Master
You rotten man
Piece of shit
Lowlife
What?
You found an exorcist?
You think it's that simple?
You are possessed
Shut up
Sit down
You know who I am?
I'm your wife
Trying to dump me so soon?
You wish
Even if you're a ghost...
you should be reasonable
Reasonable?
We got married
You take me...
for a promiscuous woman?
Do you know what you're doing?
I married you
Good that you know
You eat and spend my money
You heartless man
You found an exorcist?
Dear, do you know that...
I've got to tend to my physical needs
You're like smoke
You have nothing for me
I sleep with the pillow every night
You want me to be a monk?
Not exactly
What then?
Don't you worry
You'll get lucky tonight
It's 1 a. M
Is she coming or not?
The exorcist lied
Time to sleep
Miss Air Hostess
You're back?
I'm here to serve you
My dear husband
You got possessed
Good, you're welcome here every night
Open
Come scrub my back, dear
Let me do it
The world of a real man full of vigour
Macho
Ladies and gentlemen
The plane has entered the eye
of the typhoon
We'll experience some turbulence
Please fasten your seat belts, thanks
Serious turbulence
There he goes again
Freeze
Don't worry, I'll take care of it
You've been my companion for so many years
Who would thought that you'd leave me
Now I'm all alone
Poor thing
The beautiful Shangri-La
Lovely Shangri-La
I'm deeply in love
Deeply in love
The beautiful Shangri-La
Lovely Shangri-La
I'm deeply in love
The women of Alishan are pretty
The men of Alishan are strong
Ah... ah...
The women of Alishan are pretty
The men of Alishan are strong
Let's see what
Freddy's weather forecast is
Sorry
Sorry? Should have said something
I'm all soaked
Miss Air Hostess
Oh, it's you
No garbage today
Bye
Don't you recognize me?
We've just met
I'm your wife
What? She's on you? You...
Get in
Let's begin
Please leave me alone, dear
Please leave me alone...
We haven't started yet
No, I want you now
Help...
Stop it, dear
Lie down...
No...
I want you
Dear
Please leave me alone this time
Strip
Let me help you
No, dear
Don't go
What are you doing?
Strip, hurry
Let go of me...
Stop it
I'll knock you out
Don't worry
Let me show you some colors
It's all over
It's spring time
The flowers are blossoming
Careful, the paint is still wet
I know
The daffodils are blooming
So are the peonies
Here again
You've been walking in and out
of the toilet
Is your kidney alright?
So what if it isn't?
None of your business
I'm concerned
I'm more concerned about you
Are you a squint since birth?
Peeped at my sister in the shower
when I was little
That's what happened
Lucky you didn't go blind!
Quit the chit-chat
Get back to work
Why are you blocking the way?
Don't worry
If you think my eyes aren't working
...you're wrong
Look at the yellow...
the red and the black
The stains have ruined the wall
With my eyes
...and one brush
The yellow's gone
The red's gone, and the black's gone
All gone
Now the wall's clean
That's the power I wield
You know?
Fine, get back to work
I'm done talking to you
Don't look down on me
Let me get dolled up a bit
The nails, too
Who is it?
Me
What now?
I'm hot, open up
Who's hot?
I want you
Oh no, she's on him
Not again
What now?
I can't take this anymore
Hurry, I can't wait
I'm doing a number one
I'm in a hurry
Come on
It's over
Hurry
I want you
Here you go
I don't want this, I want yours
Help
Give it to me
Don't you run away
Wait, I want you
Let me kiss you
Kiss me, dear
I want you, come back
Stinks
Are you sick of me now?
You're a man
I'm your wife, what are you talking about?
No, you got possessed, that's all
I'm not, I'm your wife
No, you're not
I'm serious
I'm your legal wife
Legal? Wait
What do you want?
I want to take a leak
Hey, don't try to sneak away
Come here
Don't come down here
No, I can't catch you
It's dangerous
It will break
Don't worry. It won't
Sorry
It's over
If you want to visit tonight, dear
...you better possess the air hostess
Not the garbage woman, or the painter
Then it will be a bitch next
I won't be able to take it
Please be considerate
...or I'll die
Click the chopsticks twice if you agree
Yes?
Great, you're so cute
Here she comes
It's open
I'm going to have a good time tonight
Let me fix the room first
The hen marries to the pig
He's no good
If you've eaten something bad
...you'll go to the toilet
Toilet paper
Brother Nine, it's you
You sure have guts.
I told you to kill yourself
And you're living a good life here
I'm now an eunuch because of you
How can you make it up to me?
I'll fix it for you
Fix it? I won't be here if I can fix it
I'll pay you then
That's easy for you to say
Tell him what he owes me
Asshole
He owes $2,400,000
You heard him
I owe you a thousand
How come? $2,400,000?
What currency is that? Japanese Yen?
I still haven't charged you
for my operation fees
You think I'm the Hong Kong Bank?
Brother
Please don't
It's not funny, don't
That will kill me
I want you to be like me
Not a complete man
for the rest of your life
Help
Don't move
Take it out
Sure
Help
Please don't
Don't move
Why do you sound so strange?
It's me, what?
Take it out and I'll cut it off
Cut it
Let me cut it
Let go of me...
Cut it
What are you doing?
What? Let go of me
Cut it
Don't come near me
I'll cut off yours
Take away the knife
You'll know what it's like
Come on
Your turn
What are you doing?
I got you
Come on
Are you alright, boss?
Got you
Help me, boss
Don't worry, don't let go of him
Pass it
Trying to scare, huh!
Bloody freak, you played a trick on me
Trying to get yourself killed?
Hello, let's fight
Thank you
What are you doing?
Judo, karate
Thanks, two more moves
Power toss
I'll do it myself
Not enough?
That's it
This place is haunted
Don't ever come back here
Yes
Go...
Thank you
Did you just move in?
You want to check my ID card?
Merciful Buddha
Place your bets
One, three, four, total eight, small
I win
Look, I told you it's gonna be small
Seven times in a row, strange
Play another round
I've used up all my money
Two hundred dollars
There's a seat
Whose is this?
Mine. C'mon, pay up
I'll win for sure this time
Here I go
What are you doing? Robbing?
Give it to me
Help, robbery
Robbery... Help!
Got some nerve!
Return it
I'll kill you
Help
Robbery
Give it back to me
I'll kill you
You loser
You steal from an old lady
Don't let me see you again
Are you alright, old lady?
I'm fine
Scared me
You are a good man
Robs an old lady? That's too much
Let me help you up
Don't move
So you're a robber too
Don't move, or I'll kill you
You are broke
What have we got here?
Don't try anything funny
...or I'll shoot
Unzip now
I'm not wearing any underwear
I'll count to three
Then I'll shoot
One...
Two...
Great! I'm rich
Stop nagging, kid
Or you're dead
Give me back my gold
Let's go
Sure
Dear, I'm on a losing streak
Got robbed by an old lady
If you don't help me...
this flat will soon be gone
Then you won't have a place to live
We're a married couple
Help me to win, okay?
There's no point to keep talking
Click the chopsticks twice if you agree
Thanks, dear
Place your bets
I'm going to start, dear
Shit
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm
Look at this fool
He bet on three sixes
So stupid
You are the fools
if you don't follow my lead
No thanks
Open
Double sixes, one five,
seventeen total, big
Only two sixes?
My wife is lying again
Damn it
How could you do this to me?
You said you'd help
Darling. Calm down
Don't you 'darling' me
I want a divorce
I want a separation
I want to... sleep with you
I don't get it, dear
Sometimes you're a shrewd
Now you're sweet as honey
Of course. That's how women are
Listen
I went with you to the casino today
But I couldn't go inside
Why not?
There's a Bodhisattva statue at the door
A statue?
It protects the place
Then how can you get in?
Get a oilpaper umbrella
Put my spiritual tablet
inside the umbrella
Then I can go in
Is that so?
Just do it
What's with the umbrella? It's not raining
I just bought this
Got anything you shouldn't have?
No, look
Put it over there
Dear Gods
Please help me win
You...
Darling, I'm here
Remember to bet on 3- sixes every time
Got it
Three sixes?
Yes
You're cute
Why did you pinch me? Are you nuts?
Never mind...
Place your bets
200 dollars on three sixes;
you'll lose for sure
Did you see the banker?
His face is green
Shut up
I've lost so much I'm turning green
Big
Open
Three sixes
Neither big nor small
What happened to your voice?
Nothing. Caught a cold last night
This is unbelievable
You should have followed me
I don't believe it
You're very lucky
You're blushing...
you're about to win a lot
Helps us out with a good tip
Be generous
I haven't seen three sixes for a long time
Here's 10,000
Here's 20,000
Thanks...
Thanks
Place your bets
The same
Three sixes still?
Fine, I'll follow. A dollar
Open
Three sixes
He bets four hundred
Struck gold
Should have followed him
So unbelievable
He's won a lot
Zhang, change the banker
Move away, Cai
Ming, come here
Boss, the chair's wet
It's something wicked
Wait
This table is closed temporarily
Please move to another table
That's not fair
Darling, you've 90,000 dollars now.
Enough?
Are you nuts? I'm on a roll
It's difficult to bring you in
Honey, what are they doing?
I don't know, just go with the flow
Darling
What? Darling?
I'm a man
Who are you calling 'darling'?
I'll try to win some more
Sister, there's a gambler outside
...who's on a winning streak
Two rounds of three sixes
He's won 90,000 already
Go take a look
Don't worry
Cinnabar
Kill
Place your bets
Honey, this woman is powerful
Try to possess her
Hurry... place your bets
Go on
This is blocked
Place your bets on other combinations
That's the rule
Let us bet on it
No
Open
I'm not scared of anything,
leave me alone!
Fine
Open
So strange!
That didn't count
Take the money
Another round
You're good, bitch
You could handle me
Paper money for the dead
It's been very evil today
That's right
What's next?
The dice will pile up again
No way
I bet you five hundred dollars
Fine
Kill
Place your bets
Three sixes
Open
Oh, piled up again. Take the money back
So wicked
Pay up
Never guessed!
Well?
I'll stop now
The bitch is good
The guy is so wicked
Be careful
OK?
Don't worry, boss
I'll put up a good fight
Fine, again
Amazing
There will be a good show
Hex versus witchcraft
Place your bets
Three sixes
Open
One
Six...
You don't need to work tomorrow
The money
My friend, I'm impressed
You're on a roll
I've lost so much to you
I hope you won't come here again
Take the money
Thanks
Close the table for today
Boss, it's been very evil today
Look, something's wrong with your mouth
Wicked
I smile when I see you
You're gorgeous
So happy to be with you
It's late
Where's my wife?
What's this? Let me take a look
I struck gold
How come?
It's late, dad. What are you doing here?
I'm not here for you
My daughter has changed her mind
She likes the muscular type
Then I don't have a wife anymore?
Don't worry, my daughter
has taken care of that
Look
You
I'm so in love with you
Can you believe my luck?