That’s very nice. Perfect.
I love it.
Look at that.
The detail!
I like it.
-How much is there here?
-Four million dollars.
It’s totally flawless.
-Are you okay, dove?
-I gotta go to the bathroom.
Jesus Christ!
Go with her and make sure
she doesn’t have the kid here.
Keep you foreign feet off
my coffee table.
-You think this is a brothel?
-It looks like one.
Who is this guy?
This is no way to
do business.
You bring your pregnant woman
and this foreign termite.
That’s right.
You’re just a wet back.
No, I’m not. I flew first class
from Moscow.
I even have a green card.
Fuck you and
whoever gave it you.
-I love the noises you make.
-You’re heavy.
-Your gun jammed me in the tit.
-It wasn’t my gun, baby.
You’re something. First you put
your feet on my table...
then wipe spit
on my $10,000 chair.
You’re the problem.
You come here and take
jobs from real Americans.
We should put armies
on the borders...
so every time a shit like you
tries to cross, we shoot them.
Everybody relax.
We’re here to do business.
-Immigration issues aside.
-Are you okay in there?
-I’ll pay 20 cents per dollar.
-Fifty.
-0ne minute.
-Twenty five.
-Forty.
-Thirty.
0kay. But you take them all.
Tomorrow at noon.
-You okay, dove?
-Let’s go.
Get her out of here before
she drops the kid in my room.
Come back tomorrow and leave
the communist scum at home.
-Get the fuck out of here.
-Move it.
-Let’s go.
-Russian wanna be.
Time to make the donuts.
Check that.
Come on.
What the...
-Watch out.
-Shit.
It’s crawling with cops.
It’s okay. We’ll lay low.
Everything will be fine.
Sweet dreams, big guy.
The signal! I love you, Attilla.
Let’s go.
-What are you staring at?
-Don’t touch that.
-It was looking at me.
-Come on.
The whole place is wired.
-Everything’s okay.
-Nice work. Watch the door.
Let’s find the cash.
-Where are you going?
-I’ll kill our host.
The cash is this way.
Leave him alone.
-Don’t say what I can do.
-We’re killing nobody.
Give me the axe.
Let go!
What are you talking...
Give me the axe.
-Cops. At the gate!
-We triggered the alarm.
Come on, let’s go.
0ut back.
Let’s go.
It’s locked.
-I’ll break the door.
-Not that!
This way, through the roof.
-They’ll get us out there.
-I’ll tie them up.
-Taylor, no!
-Go, go.
Get her out of here.
-Tell Megan I’m sorry.
-Come on.
Shit.
-I’m unarmed.
-There he is, guys.
Get your hands up.
Check inside.
We got him!
Hands behind your head.
Cuff him.
You’re going down, son.
Let’s go.
Good morning.
My name’s Jose.
Good morning, sir.
My name is Jose.
Glad to meet you.
My name is Taylor.
Good morning.
My name is Jose.
My name is...
My name.
This is the place.
Paige.
You’re out early!
I missed you.
You lied. You said you were
well. When did you move in here?
It’ll get better.
Don’t worry.
My God.
-Megan!
-Daddy!
You’re huge.
Unbelievable!
I brought you a card game
with little animals on it.
Thanks...
but I don’t use these anymore.
I use big kids cards,
these are for little kids.
These are what I use.
Cool. Let’s play inside.
-Come back.
-Just a minute.
Come here.
-Come here.
-I’ve got to brush.
-Enough cards, kids. Come in.
-0ne more, Mrs Monty.
I’ll stick.
You’ve got sixteen.
And I have a face card.
You’ve lost.
You need to hit.
371 days, 23 hours
and 17 minutes.
-Wanna smoke?
-I gave up on the inside.
Do I double now?
If you want me
to take all your money.
-Thanks for taking care of her.
-We got along.
-We gotta get out of here.
-0pen Plan?
View of the dump?
I’m serious.
This isn’t what I want for us.
I thought about you both
so much.
Come in you two.
Megan, go on home.
I see your dad’s back.
It was a surprise. I guess they
shut the oil platform down.
If he worked on oil rigs
you wouldn’t live here.
You’re talking too much.
Get in.
Come on, sis.
Let’s go play them horses.
I dreamed of escape
but I stayed...
Did the time and
kept quiet.
Card shark, what’s up?
Since the oil platform closed,
what ‘re you going to do?
-Make us some money.
-How?
My buddy can get me a job
driving ambulances.
Come here.
Come on.
Get over here now.
Come on. Move it.
Hurry up.
Go! Go!
I’m happy we teamed up.
I’ve so much confidence in you.
You’re always in control.
Hey man, what’s up.
I’m happy for you.
See what I’m saying?
The jar, the top of the jar.
Like this.
You can do this, this...
but not this.
Partners.
Not partners.
-0kay?
-0kay.
This music is making soup
out of my brains.
I need sleep and I haven’t slept
for three days.
Learn to flow.
Flow.
Check it out.
Mark, over there.
There’s an ambulance.
Look Judd, steering wheel.
Street.
And don’t call me Mark.
Partners use first names.
Let’s go.
Coming through.
-Where the hell are you going?
-Heart attack.
-There’s no heart attack here.
-Someone called in.
No one called here.
-The third time this week.
-Not my problem.
-Nobody called.
-I’m betting this race.
What are you doing?
Get back here.
Move the stretcher.
It’s clogging up the place.
-I’ll wait up there with it.
-Fine. Let’s go.
Get in line
like the rest of us.
-I got to get back to work.
-I don’t believe this.
You’re not a good partner
unless you can prioritize.
-Prioritize?
-What to see and hear.
Like opera.
Let it in. What are you willing
to do to be a partner?
Can you?
-You may learn about yourself.
-Yeah, like how to kill myself.
Go!
A fat guy sings about the sex
he’d have if he weren’t so fat.
Expand my horizons!
-It’s so depressing.
-It’s a tragedy.
Tosca is my favorite.
-She’s in love with a painter.
-Nice.
-Avaradossi.
-Really nice.
Who’s killed by the betrayal
of the evil, wicked officer.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Get in line like everybody else.
Get in line.
-We’re all waiting.
-Back of the line, okay?
I’ve no problem with you.
We’re on the same team.
I put them down.
You patch them up.
Whatever.
Can I get through? Sorry, I’m
not in line just need to get by.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Don’t worry about it.
Hi, boss man.
-Daddy, could you fire me up?
-My pleasure.
Meet me at the door.
-Hi, big daddy.
-You sure are pretty.
-Thank you.
-Let me light your fire.
Great race, fine cigar,
pretty woman.
What else can go right?
Stay here.
I’ll get you a drink.
Get the fuck down now!
-Alright.
-I said down!
Thank you. Now stay down or
talk to my Uzi.
Hit the floor.
-Did you hear something?
-Will you listen? Focus.
Who’s then murdered
by Tosca’s own hand...
who in turn...
commits suicide.
Here’s the deal,
you compulsive freaks!
No one moves, no heroes
and no one gets hurt.
Did you hear?
-Get the fuck down.
-Wanna do it?
-Get down.
-What’s this?
-How’s Yellow?
-I’m good.
Pink, we’re good to go!
Listen, Mark.
What’s wrong with you?
No speaking.
Go!
We’re out of here.
Baby, behind you.
-I’ve got to go.
-I’m down.
Go!
Stay down!
-Code three.
-Call it in.
Get back. Come on,
stand back.
Eddie.
Get over here.
-Ma’am? Check her pulse.
-Go check the perimeter.
Ma’am? Stand back.
-Can you see this?
-Her pulse is weak.
-She’s losing a lot of blood.
-Will she live?
Think before you shoot.
Let’s get her outta here.
-You, get the stretcher.
-Hurry up and get it.
You don’t know what to see.
You don’t know what to hear.
You don’t see.
You don’t hear.
Fuck.
Fuck!
Get out of the way.
Move back.
Jesus Christ!
Let’s go!
Pull that lever.
Pick her up.
1...2...3...
-FBl.
-What’s happening?
They’re shooting up the place.
They’re in the cage.
All right, out of the way.
FBl.
-0ut of the way, FBl.
-What’s this?
She was gonna rob the place.
We gotta get her to a hospital
or she’s gonna die.
You stay with them.
Let them through.
Coming through!
-Did they get the money?
-They got the money.
Took the surveillance chip.
Left not a trace. Smart as hell.
0fficer, I saw it all.
She was in bright pink...
The black cop shot the girl.
Where?
-Mind your business.
-Jump in.
-I need you as a witness.
-Get in!
Get out of my way.
What’s wrong with these people?
Will she live? Die? Who shot her?
Shit!
I got a surprise for you.
Let’s see the money!
Hurry up.
Shit, that’s a lot of money.
-Am I good or what?
-How much is there?
0ne point nine million.
-What?
-Two million dollars!
I’m finally gonna finish my CD.
They said we’d never amount
to nothing.
My rap will be ready!
You went down hard.
You okay?
-I’m great.
-The look on his face.
The perve had his hands
all over me.
-We got two million bucks.
-US$200 dinners, US$500 suits...
US$1000 hookers.
I got this from the 0TB.
Thief.
Marry me.
Get me pregnant.
My skins gonna be dark
as Rock’s.
Not on your best day,
white boy.
-When he goes, me and you?
-Get lost.
She knows your just my
little brother. Fuck off.
In God we trust.
Absolutely.
-I love you too, Rock.
-Smoke that.
I love you, baby.
-Kill the lights.
I’m serious.
What the fuck is that?
-They’re marked.
-Shit.
What is this, Taylor?
What’s going on?
The money’s part of
a Fed operation.
I want my cut.
-Wanna get cut?
-Lay off him.
-Get off me.
-Everybody chill out.
I’m not going to prison.
-I wanna get my cut.
-Shut the fuck up.
They’re all marked.
We can’t pass them.
-We’ll have to clean them.
-Where’re we gonna clean them?
A guy I worked with before,
but it’s gonna cost. Heavy.
-Real heavy.
-Shit.
Is Nikita around?
Nikita, it’s for you.
Good morning.
My name is Jose.
-I sell oranges.
-This is a prayer meeting.
-I say my name is Jose.
-Jose, fuck off.
-Goodbye.
-We’re in a meeting.
You’re back from Siberia.
I knew you’d come to see me.
I appreciate what you did.
I have a surprise for you,
I’ve been planning for a year.
-Do I need more surprises?
-I timed it perfectly.
-Where can we talk?
-Here.
Anything you have to say
can be said in front of them.
My Russian brothers. After what
Russia did for my Cuba.
I need to clean two million
marked bills.
Not the big money.
They’ll want a rise.
Back to work.
Come in here.
The Karamazov Brothers.
They can hear this.
Two million?
-Why didn’t you include me?
-You know why.
But you trust me
to clean your money.
Trust has nothing to
do with it.
Every time I want
to do something...
0ne minute, okay? Please.
Remember him?
The one with the big mouth.
0pen your mouth.
0pen like it was.
This is your surprise.
But you’re the one
who wanted to kill him.
You get me!
It’s not your surprise,
it’s everyone’s surprise.
Today’s my birthday. I want
to share the cake with everyone.
Remember me? You called me
wetback in my face, remember?
-I’m sorry.
-It’s too late.
Who’s a wetback? See this?
It’s an American passport.
Who the fuck is a wetback?
Wetback?
No problem. I’ll dry you off.
You’re still wet. No problem.
Look at this fucking suit.
The sleeve is shrinking.
See here? Dry clean only.
And I launder his suit!
I could lose my business.
What am I gonna do?
Alteration. No problem.
It will look like new.
Your sleeve is gonna fit
in no time.
What are you doing?
Russian handshake.
I’m famous for this.
Care for a souvenir?
Take one, put in the fireplace.
See you around.
-I give you dime on the dollar.
-It’s thirty across the boarder.
We’re talking
a lot of money!
That’s the deal.
Take it or leave it.
Let’s shake on it.
Bring me the big one.
He has big hands.
-Thirty cents on the buck.
-What? That price?
Not bad for money marked
by the FBl.
Thirty on the buck? I got
a quarter of two mill coming.
There’s five of us. Don’t count
Virginia and me as one.
-Why not? You’re fucking her.
-And she’s loving it.
-Shut up!
-There’s five even slices.
At thirty cents? I worked
too hard for 150 grand.
$125 grand.
-Fuck that!
-No, it’s a good deal.
-I’m in. When?
-At least another day.
-What do I do until then?
-The usual. Whack off.
-Stay out of trouble.
-Who holds the money?
I’m going nowhere
until I get my cut.
He’ll spend it,
they’ll catch us.
-Shut up.
-The money will stay together.
I’ll hold it, 0K?
-That’s a great idea.
-We should hide it.
In a bus station,
in one of the lockers.
Good idea.
-Is that what we’ll do?
-Not exactly.
Bus station?
My name is Jose.
I sell oranges for money.
What do you want?
Give me your money.
Come on.
My name is Jose.
I sell oranges for money.
Son of a bitch!
The package stays in a P0 box
until we can get it out.
-We need a fake I.D.
-I got it.
We’ll use mine.
-I don’t get it.
-What a surprise.
I’ll rent a P0 box
and mail this package.
He’ll mail it to his fake l.D.
and wait to get it out.
You will get it?
Can anybody get it?
Will you rip off a post office?
This place is open 24 hours!
Thousands of packages, people,
are you gonna kill everybody?
Taylor has the only key?
I don’t trust you with
the only key. Do you, guys?
You got a better idea?
Camp out and watch the place
for the next 20 hours.
Bring your vaseline and spend
the night staking out.
Exactly what I’ll do.
-Will you mail to this office?
-Writing a fucking book?
Just mail it.
-I’m watching you.
-I’m watching you, too.
Nobody’s gonna camp
out here, 0K?
We’ll meet here
tomorrow at noon. Got it?
Stay invisible until then.
-Not exactly how I thought.
-Not exactly.
-Twelve o’clock tomorrow.
-Geez.
Wake up.
-Wake up.
-Paige, let her sleep.
What’s wrong?
Did you get the money?
Two million.
I had it in my hands.
What do you mean?
Did you get it or not?
I got it.
-Where is it?
-Hidden.
Why?
It’s marked. FBI money,
we can’t spend it.
Let me guess.
You’ve seen Nikita.
How much do we get?
Thirty percent.
Works out to $125 grand.
Jesus!
Nikita, the FBl...
All this for $125 grand?
You know where it is?
Let’s go get all of it.
-What about the others?
-What about them?
They’d take it if they could.
You can’t trust them,
let’s get it for us.
-I can’t do that.
-Why not?
You told me to pack my bags.
I’m ready to go, let’s go!
I thought you would get us
out of here. Nothing even works.
-I can’t stay anymore.
-It’s 0K, we can stay longer.
That’s what I get for
wiping your nose last year.
I understand.
You have your daughter.
You two together...
I don’t fit in here.
You should fix that faucet.
What are you doing here?
I’ve hired another girl.
I’m not here to work.
A vodka, straight up, no ice.
You don’t look good.
What’s wrong?
I’m fine. Make it double.
Are you working
the day shift?
A little early for vodka.
It’s not your fucking
business, is it?
It’s for you.
Hello?
What did you do at school?
I did Math,
but that’s just boring.
I always hated Math.
What did you do
when you were away?
I thought about you,
Paige, about life in general.
Ever think about mommy?
All the time.
She was a beautiful lady.
I miss her everyday.
Paige took good care of me.
But she’s so young.
I’m glad you like her.
Do you want a soda?
-Two sodas.
-Sure.
Sorry I couldn’t be there
for you.
It’s 0K, I’m not stupid.
I know you were in jail.
And I know you want us out
of the trailer park.
I’m afraid of
how you will do it.
-What are you talking about?
-Come on, daddy.
I know you’re up to something.
I just don’t know what.
-You can’t do that.
-Why not? ‘Cause it’s stealing?
Let’s get aseat.
Right here.
Listen, I want you
to know something.
I can’t live like this.
I’m afraid you go back to jail.
My daddy being a thief!
I don’t want money you stole.
Promise you won’t go back.
-Listen...
-Promise me.
-I promise.
-Thank you.
Megan!
Come on over!
Sweety, go play with
Darone and Arie, 0K?
0K, dad.
0utside. Now!
I told you to stay away.
I got a kid.
Relax, I told no one
where you live...
and that you have a kid.
-What do you want?
-My money.
I started cutting my CD
and now I’m broke.
My producers are getting itchy
and they’re gonna fuck me up.
-I need my money today.
-Tomorrow you’ll have plenty.
I need you to get out of here.
Please.
Hi, Dad.
Sorry about that.
I told him to stay away.
But he came anyway.
Soon they’ll all be here.
God!
-What’s wrong?
-I have a bad feeling about it.
Can we get out of here?
Take off and forget about this.
You wanted all the cash and
now you want to take off?
It’s too dangerous.
-Let’s drop it.
-I’m right in the middle of it.
Give me one more day.
Let’s do it.
I wanna pick up this package.
-No, the one by your feet.
-Relax, ass mouth.
Down there!
Let’s go to your place.
Let’s go.
I love what you did with
the place. It’s like grandma’s.
Virginia decorated it.
-Your bunny collection!
-I like my bunnies.
-What the fuck is that?
-Relax, it’s the cleaner.
I bring detergent.
-So fresh, so clean.
-Looks good.
0f course it’s good.
Everything is always good.
What is this? Planning to track
your two million?
You come back later
and rip me off?
In case you get greedy
and decide to rip me off.
No need for this, we’re friends,
we have trust.
Look at this. Everyone!
Man, woman, black, white...
so much diversity! Unity!
What is it
that keep us together?
The money.
The magic word.
Fuck! What is this shit?
No cash, no nothing!
That’s why I hate
fucking with you.
What are you trying to pull?
What’s going on?
Who fucking took it?
You did!
What were you doing
at the post office?
I saw you there.
-Are you saying it’s my fault?
-Yes! Where is the money?
I’m confused, and when
I’m confused people get hurt!
-What is going on?
-What is that?
-Are you playing games?
-Let me see.
-What is this?
-Butch.
-He pulled his gun on me.
-You shot my ear!
-I want my money.
-Did you see this?
Were you planning to
to fuck off with her?
You!
-I want some answers now.
-Don’t touch me.
I leave here with two million
or with your head.
-Expecting a call?
-Are you expecting a call?
-It’s one of his whores.
-Answer the damn phone!
Fuck.
Hello.
It’s for you.
Be smart.
I’m listening.
I’m on my way.
What are you doing?
Don’t shoot.
He knows where the money is.
-Give me the fucking hand.
-Fuck you! I’ll get out of here.
-Come on!
-Go!
He shoot me. He shoot me.
When I get Taylor, he’s dead.
Steals my gun and pulls this!
Leave me alone.
-Don’t touch me, you cheap...
-Shut up!
You fucking bitch!
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
-We’re losing him.
-I’m not losing him!
Would you relax?
We’ll go to his house!
And where’s that?
Where the fuck does he live?
Rock knows.
I don’t know. He contacted me,
same as you. Don’t give me that!
Don’t lose him.
Watch out!
Fucker! Pull over!
-Fuck.
-Shit.
Look out, Eddie.
Fuck.
We should be after the other guy
with the real money.
You fucked up,
you can’t do shit right.
Come on.
Move this asshole!
Go around him! Around him!
If we don’t get the money,
we’re all dead!
Taylor, you’re dead,
you hear me?
You earned a free alteration
in my shop.
-Three times in a row.
-Megan!
-Can you hear me?
-I don’t know how...
but I know you’re doing it.
My friend will take you
to your daddy now.
Great.
Or not.
I know what you’re thinking.
Don’t think it.
Hundreds of hotel rooms here.
She could be anywhere.
A very smart daughter you got.
She is very smart.
She won every hand.
-Are you gonna say anything?
-If you hurt her, I’ll kill you.
-Relax, we’re gonna be friends.
-Who the hell are you?
You don’t remember me?
Mark Cornell?
-FBl.
-That’s right.
You were at the OTB.
What do you want?
Your talent.
When you stole my money,
everything became clear to me.
What do you mean, your money?
I was gonna launder it a bit
and make money on the side.
And then you steal it!
You ruined my life.
The worst thing became
the best thing! We’re partners.
You’re kidding me.
No, never more serious.
I was tracking you down...
your name came up under
the smart guys. You’re good.
You’re perfect.
I know you smoke...
so I got you some, they’re
on the counter, help yourself.
-I don’t do that anymore.
-You quit?
I know they’re killers.
-How did you do it? The patch?
-What the hell do you want?
Every night, a boat comes into
the docks...
with the Atlantic City
casinos’ profits.
It’s gonna be six million
totally untraceable.
I deliver you the money,
and I get my kid back?
You’re a good thief.
I respect you.
It’s the beginning of a long
and prosperous future together.
You kidnapped my daughter.
I can’t see a bright future.
That’s just a formality.
Prove yourself trustworthy and
she’ll be with you on Saturday.
It’s up to you,
but this is perfect.
I’ve got the contacts, can’t get
busted. Secure information.
You do the heist, I set up
the gigs, split it 50/50.
You will be able to buy her
whatever she wants.
-50/50 is fair, isn’t it?
-I can’t do this job alone.
-Your crew? Whatever you want.
-They won’t do it.
The stuff in the envelope
will help convince them.
Is this money from the heist?
-How did you get it back?
-It’s what I do. Surveillance.
I’m not gonna take it.
It’s too risky.
Listen...
just give me back my kid.
You don’t need her, you got me.
I’m gonna do the job. I can’t
do it unless I know she’s safe.
I’ll be in touch.
Stay with the money.
Stupid.
Stupid, stupid.
What do you think you’re doing?
Get Megan on the phone.
Put her on the phone.
Here.
-What are you doing?
-What am I doing?
I’m being a nice guy and
letting you say goodbye to her.
Don’t do that, you don’t have
to kill her. I’ll do the job.
-Please.
-Hang on.
You start
a partnership like this?
-I’m sorry.
-Are you?
Very, very sorry.
I’m disappointed.
Call you back.
I went to pick up Megan
from school, she wasn’t there.
-She’s missing.
-I know.
Are you okay?
Tell me nothing
is gonna happen to her.
Tell me.
0k, let’s go!
0ver here.
My God.
You scared the shit out
of me. Do you want a beer?
Got it all figured out?
How are you doing?
-Just great.
-You look worried.
You got a plan?
And the guys with the guns?
You got enough guys?
And your crew?
-Maybe you’re not so smart.
-I got it all figured out.
Megan asks about you
all the time.
A said you’re on a trip,
working hard...
but might be away
for a long time.
I can’t forget about you trying
to follow me at the hotel.
That wasn’t smart.
And I have to trust you.
I can’t be up all night
thinking about this.
I’m no good without sleep.
I could do anything like...
What are you like?
-Not good.
-I’m like a mush.
Like... Like a mush man.
Sleep easy.
-This won’t be a problem.
-Great. I feel better already.
My man, Taylor.
Here’s the next time and place.
Smoke?
Wanna get a beer? No, I can’t.
There’s no one watching Megan.
-Any message?
-Just tell her I love her.
I’ll tell her you said hi.
She better be there,
you son of a bitch.
It’s Taylor.
I need you, my friend.
In my contingency plan.
I know your price.
Jesus.
Paige?
-Are you hurt?
-He thought we had the money.
You did this?
He attacked me,
and I screamed...
no one heard me
so I started swinging...
Get yourself cleaned up.
We’re out of here now!
Come on.
Hurry up.
Jesus!
You scared the hell out of me.
Why are you up so early?
What’s that?
Just a little trash, that’s all.
-Sorry for the noise last night.
-I heard no noise.
What are you doing?
Going somewhere?
We’ll take a short vacation.
We’ll be back soon.
Paige! Get in the car!
-We gotta go! Come on.
-Why?
-What?
-Nikita.
There he is
and here we are.
My fucking shoulder.
Congratulations, Taylor.
You’ll get a cheap laundry...
and a quick alteration.
-Where?
-This is it.
Hold on.
Watch out for the lake!
Come on!
What are you doing?
Let’s get out of here!
You fucking stupid!
You mother fucker.
Answer the phone.
-You got a good driver.
-Do you think it’s funny?
Relax, I’ll make this up to you.
You’ll get the two million.
I need you to be
my contingency plan.
-Your contingency plan?
-I’ll be in touch.
I’m gonna cut
your balls off.
Thanks for finally calling.
-Did you bring my money?
-Where’s our money?
I brought you a message and
I want to give you your gun.
-Where is my two mill?
-What the fuck is this mess?
FBI guys, on their own.
They tracked us down.
Why?
They were laundering money
and we screwed it up.
Remember the counter boss?
He had a heart attack.
The autopsy connected
the death to the robbery.
What does it mean?
A report hasn’t been filed.
We aren’t wanted for murder.
-Yet.
-What?
-Felony murder rule.
-They want us to pull a job.
-Six million.
-No fucking way.
This is bullshit, brother.
Let’s take off.
Let’s run to Mexico.
We’ll get married.
-I want my fucking money.
-Listen...
These are dirty FBI guys.
If we don’t do this...
they’ll track us down
one by one.
I’m not gonna get arrested.
They might not want
to arrest you.
Holy shit.
It’s Rock.
My God.
We get one shot,
let’s get it right.
Butch, go to the empty repair
shop by the docks...
and get me a cheap arc welder.
This is the last of my cash.
Virginia, buy a sexy outfit.
-Short skirt.
-Shorter than usual?
I’ll meet you at the post office
around eleven.
-I’ll tell you the rest there.
-And what do I do?
Do what you normally do.
Whack off.
-I’m serious. What do I do?
-Do what you normally do.
What do you think
of his story?
Is he telling the truth?
Those FBI guys?
I think he’s lying.
It’s dangerous. I don’t want
them to know you two exist.
Hand me my vest.
Who gives a shit?
We’re gonna jack that money
and give it to the Feds?
I don’t think so. We’re gonna
keep it for ourselves.
Just me and you,
me and you.
-Me and you.
-Six million dollars!
Who’s the little brother now?
Who’s the little brother?
Wait here,
I’ll be back soon.
Be careful.
Let’s go, boys.
-Evening, ma’am.
-Thank the Lord it’s the 5-0.
Howdy y’all?
How did I end up
at the water again?
You have to move your car
out of the way.
0k, but could you tell me
where I can find Hershey.
I don’t know where it is.
You have to move your car.
-I will, but...
-You have to move your car.
Watch out!
We gotta help them.
Give me your hand.
Butch, is that you?
Yeah, baby, it’s your Butch.
Look at you.
Look a little surprised.
You were expecting Eddie?
Double-crossing bitch.
Suck on it.
At least your brother
could deliver.
The only testosterone you had
was from the steroids you take.
-I said to stay at the motel.
-She is like my daughter too.
I can’t sit around and wait
for something to happen.
How did you find me?
A boat rental receit
in your wallet.
Catch.
Thanks.
Thanks for saving me.
I told you
you couldn’t trust them.
How about you?
What do you mean?
The old lady didn’t hear
anything the night Rock died.
-Tell me what happened.
-Cornell’s guy killed Rock.
-Why did you lie?
-I didn’t know what to do.
Cornell said that if I didn’t
show him where the money was...
he was gonna send you to jail.
I had to work with him.
So Rock told you which P0 box
and you told Cornell?
I figured that
he would leave us alone.
I was stupid to think
he would go away.
You’ve never been stupid.
You’re saying I’m into this
for the money?
I don’t know
what to think anymore.
Take the wheel.
I screwed up and I can
make it up. I know how.
There’s his boat. You hide
and I take the money onboard.
I’m not gonna let you get
near this money!
Move. Go on.
-You have to trust me.
-Right.
Wave to your daddy.
-Ahoy, there!
-Daddy!
Daddy!
It’s 0K, sweetie.
Are you alright?
Move her back inside.
Let me go.
Daddy!
Daddy, help!
Give me a hand. I got
the money. Where’s my daughter?
-Leave the money. You come up.
-We had a deal.
Now we got a new one.
We don’t have all night.
Stay in the boat,
I’ll be there in a minute.
Go in the back
and take a look-see.
Daddy.
Daddy, help me!
It’s 0K, I’m gonna
get you out of there.
Actually it’s not.
There’s enough explosive
to blow up a battleship.
And this remote gives me 90 secs
to enjoy the fireworks.
-Jesus.
-Did you check the money?
I hate boats.
-Don’t do this.
-You’re doing it.
I like you.
I can’t trust you.
And I got a new partner
I can trust.
What the fuck is this?
-It’s the contingency plan.
-You little shit.
Daddy!
Shoot him.
You don’t believe it,
but I waited for you.
Do you think I’d work
with a lunatic like this?
Lunatic?
-What is it with you two?
-Give me the remote.
Don’t make me shoot you.
I was looking forward
to working with you.
Shoot him.
Shoot him!
Blanks. Do you think
I’d give you a loaded gun?
Do I look like an idiot?
Get away from the boat! Swim!
-Don’t!
-Daddy!
Stay away from that thing.
Don’t touch it.
-Help me!
-Maybe I ran over with your girlfriend.
-Cornell, give me the key.
-I don’t think so.
Don’t bother trying to break in.
The cabin’s secured.
Come on,
pull on the door.
Pull, alright?
You can do this.
Just pull on the door.
-Give me one of those things.
-I knew you couldn’t quit.
Careful,
those things are killers.
It’s late to worry
about my health.
-You’re right.
-What’s that?
These things are killers.
Daddy!
Find something there to help me
jimmy this lock.
Go on, keep looking.
Anything you can find.
Don’t touch the bomb! Jesus!
Anything on you?
ln your purse?
Look, quick!
-My cards.
-Slip them through here.
Through the door.
Daddy, hurry!
Let’s go!
Daddy!
-Sweetie, are you 0K?
-I’m really so cold.
We’re gonna get out of here.
-0ver here.
-What are you doing?
Right here!
Damn you, Taylor.
I’ll keep you above water.
Just kick your feet.
-Here we go.
-Be careful.
Grab her hands.
Pull her up. That’s it.
-Wrap her up in this.
-You’re all right.
Taylor, over here.
There’s Atilla.
Head over to him.
-Take me.
-You got him?
Now you got me.
Work me over, baby.
I’ll keep track of you.
I didn’t know...
He said you sent him
to pick me up.
It’s all right.
I’m sorry I got you
involved in this.
Nice.
Very nice.
What is this?
Where’s the money?
-This is shredded paper.
-No sweat, it’s safe.
-You couldn’t be near the money.
-I almost took off!
But you didn’t.
You came back for us.
I know it’s heartbreaking,
but that’s my price.
-That’s your cut.
-Come on, baby.
Pile on another bundle.
You know the shit’s wet.
And so are you.
You bet I am.
You got me all horny.
-Come here and warm me up.
-You little shit.
Throw on another for him.
-That’s it.
-Thanks, sweetie.
You feel good.
Thank God.
-Now we’re square. Thanks.
-Absolutely.
So long’s right.
Look at this money!
So much!
What are we gonna do?
-What are you doing?
-Stolen money.
-We could have kept some.
-We gotta let it go.
We could have used that.
It nearly cost me
everything I care about.
I promised her.
We’re gonna be 0K.
Jesus! Who the fuck are you?
The contingency plan.
I see you have the two mill.
Two million? No.
Your suit is wet,
that’s a big problem.
I happen to be
in the laundry business.
We’ll make quick alteration.
No problem.
Jesus Christ!
Do you want one?
Here.
Lighter.
Do you know why I love you?
-Why?
-You bring out the best in me.
Do you have any idea...
what we’re gonna do in Canada?
What are we gonna do?
Tell me.
Come on, Daddy.
I gotta make us some money.
Fast.
Good morning.
My name is Jose.
Fucking Mexican.
Dicks...
my name is Jose
and I kill people for money.
Jose, there’s no need
to kill us. We are friends.
Friends?
Good.
Then I kill you for nothing.