Yo! Pat, don't you like us no more?
Fucking punk.
I trusted you dog.
Fucking shouldn't have.
I never fucking trusted you.
I trusted you.
Motherfucker.
Yo! Motherfucker's still smiling dog.
Yo!! You want us to dump the body?
No. Leave the Motherfucker
to die right there.
Go get my table ready!
I gotta go get my shit.
My brother always used to tell me
that he was smart.
I never believed him,
whatever, not with your grades,
I told him
I'm not book smart,
I'm a different kind of smart
It's like a special gift,
he used to say.
I'd laugh at him.
He's always bragging.
He'd tell me that
he'd notice things about people.
He'd notice the way they would act.
And the shit they say
Hey kid, don't let them wet my car
He figured that
it would come in handy someday.
Songkran; the Thai New Year,
used to be a lot more about tradition.
My grandma said that back in Thailand...
the whole water ritual
was very important.
I don't know
what ritual she's talking about.
All I know is that it's
just one big water fight.
To bad for that kid, Yo!
He gonna lose his car right now.
Papa's gonna have to send money
for another car.
Check this out.
Watch it punk.
Yo! Yo! Man I thought
he fucked you up already.
Chill man. Don't worry about it!
Come on. Let's go. Let's go!
Yo!! What's the nicest car
you see all in here?
What?
Say in the last 20 mins. Man.
What man?
I don't fucking know Man.
Fool you don't even know
which car it is?
Na Man.
Oh! Fuck Man.
Yo! Chill out man don't worry about it.
Yo! Quit your scratching already Khan.
Where am I supposed take that
car again, I forgot?
You forgot!
Calm down man.
Why don't you have a coke and a smile...
and let Charlie take care
of businessman I got this.
Main Street.
The warehouse
you were at just the other day.
Main Street, you got it?
Do you remember what car it is
or did you forget that shit too?
The one with all the fucking
sticker on it, man.
Yo, like that one.
Yo, stop you scratching already Khan,
fucken driving me crazy dog.
Man shut the fuck up, man.
If that Motherfucker finds out
you're a dead man.
Shit then I gotta move out of here.
Fool you said you
were going to borrow the car.
Then why did you go steal one then?
Come with you man damn why did I.
Man, what fucking car do you think
we're going to use?
Your mama's car?
Man, my mom's car is alright man.
Did you say you fucking
wanted money Khan?
Yo! After tonight
we'll be filthy fucking rich dog.
Yo! We're better be man, be better be.
Don't worry about that guys man,
they won't even know
what fucking hit them.
Stop! It's the red light!
Should we tighten the safety belt?
What's up dog? I know this isn't your ride.
Shit you know we got next though, right?
Make sure it's all their
cause will be back for it.
Shut the fuck up
and give me the money,
let your driving do the talking.
All show you who's the bitch
when I come back for my money.
Let me get out of the car man
maybe it would be lighter.
Good luck Man.
Come on fucken Khun.
Yo! 5.0
Damn fucken Pat you fuck me up man.
What the fuck am I gonna do now?
It's not just my money man.
Fuck my bad Khan,
I guess you win some,
and lose some, man.
Shit I guess so man.
Fuck, while you know
I got your back dog.
Yo, I got your back.
Yo! Yo! Yo!
Hey! Get up lazy.
Gotta go help dad at the restaurant.
That was start man,
but you gotta finish.
Don't move. I gotta go finish something.
So hey Billy, you can't pay your debts...
but you can buy all
this fucking food, huh.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Oh, no.
You owe me money.
Till I get paid nobody eats.
Shit!
Shit this ain't mine, it's customer's.
Shit I owe you money
How much 50- 60, What?
Make it 100 now Motherfucker.
Now that's how you finish.
Let's go, we got to talk man.
Pat, Pat where are you going, Pat?
Ok and then,
How about Pad Thai,
Ice coffee for you?
Ok. Ok. That's good.
Hi, Mom come in. Let me help you.
Did you see Pat? He's not here.
If I saw him do you think
I'll be pushing this?
He's useless.
I bring you some water later.
Ploy put everything in the van,
Pat's not coming.
Today you have to help grandma, okay?
Keep a look out, ok?
Grandma's eyes are bad.
Be careful, grandma!
That's my boy Charlie...
you might want to think twice
about fucking with him.
What the fuck are you doing here man?
Get the fuck out of my gym.
Look fool!
What, you mean him?
Fucking you!
So what, is this what you have
to talk to me about?
You talk like a gangster dog,
your uncle must have taught you well.
What uncle?
Yo, I heard some what happened to him
that's fucked up.
So, I didn't know him.
Yo, you sick of the Restaurant,
yet or what?
I guess it's fine for now.
Doesn't seem it's fine for now,
it seems you want to move
onto something else, Yo.
Guess will see then, right.
So, how's Pearl? How's she?
Don't know, I haven't seen her.
Well, the next time you see her
tell her I send my love, alright?
Man you know I ain't gonna tell her that.
Why not?
Cause she be fucking pissed
if she knows I was here.
What, you ain't wanna be here
or what, Motherfucker?
I didn't say that, did I?
You got a smart mother fucking
mouth, watch it.
Hi, my girl.
Doing your homework?
Did Pat help out today?
Ploy, you didn't hear what I said?
No, he didn't, but we were fine...
grandma just hit the curb twice
and that's it.
Shit... Pat's useless.
What did he do all day?
Lucky grandma's helping
us out or else we'll be in trouble.
Help me unpack dinner.
Yo, get your shit
out of my fucking way man,
his F.O.B. Don't understand a word I say.
Motherfucker.
Yo, tomorrow night I got a table
at Thailand Plaza. Be there!
Alright man, I'll be there.
I need to talk to my brother.
Alright yo, what happened to my money?
Yo. I ain't got it and you heard her.
Get lost.
My bad, yo.
Alright man one love.
Keep it buzz'en.
Who was that?
You know who that was.
What are you doing, hanging out
with that punk?
Nothing, none of your business, really.
What do you mean nothing
you want me to tell dad...
you're hanging around
with that wanna be gangster?
Yo, tell dad what you want
I don't give a shit no more.
What are you looking at?
Business, what business?
Your business is to help
out at the restaurant and Than temple,
that's it ok?
Don't you know
we're having a tough time?
Don't you see everyone's helping out?
You don't do shit.
What are you thinking?
You wanna be like hector down there
or you want to end up
dead like your uncle.
Have some respect,
I'm your father god damn it. Respect.
Daddy.
Fuck you look at F.O.B.
Daddy. Did you get tax papers yet?
Henry has time to help you now.
Oh now he has time to look at them.
While you know it's tax season...
and it's the busiest time of the year.
While I don't have any papers ready.
Why not, you can't avoid this
the IRS people...
they're serious people
they're ready to take everything.
I don't owe them any thing.
Yes, you do.
Look, Henry has time to help you now.
Maybe I don't need his help.
Henry's a great lawyer!
Daddy... Are you still mad at me?
I don't get it why you move out with Henry.
What am I gonna tell people...
when they ask about you?
I know this ain't Thailand,
but I can't accepted.
At least he should ask me first.
I'm gonna go help grandma close up.
Excuse me, is my dish ready?
Hurry up and eat your food.
We close in 10 mins.
Goldie, I'm here.
That's great, sit down.
Motherfucker you best get that
look off your face...
before I shove this Singha right up your ass.
Shut up, Charlie.
Yo, ready to do some work
for me kid?
Ah ya, Goldie.
Good, see I have some concerns...
about mother fucking
Armenians like that...
selling dope on my streets.
Yo, Pat what you think we should...
Where the fuck did he?
Now what the fuck is he doing?
Bitch.
You shit! Now that's what I'm talking about.
Get outta car.
Uh... I thought you were my brother.
How did you ever get that scare?
Pardon me, sir?
You speak Thai pretty good.
I speak Thai at home everyday.
Sir, you just moved from Thailand?
I came from somewhere else.
What's your name, sir?
I'm Ploy. I live upstairs.
I'm Dan and please stop calling me sir.
You already know which room I live in.
Uh, do you speak English?
Accent not so good.
See! That what you get.
They watch out.
Be gentle with my vegetables, son.
Yes.
Oh! You're that,
Good, then please help me carry my bags.
Ok, I'm going to give all
these papers to Henry...
and he'll take a look at them next week...
and he'll be able to tell
how much we have to pay.
Payment?
Henry said he was going to fight the case.
But this is the IRS
you have to pay you owe tax, ok?
If you don't pay they will take every thing.
Do you understand?
Pearl, your dad is hard headed
but don't raised your voice.
Dan?
Here is my nephew Pearl
Can I help you?
This is Dan, he just moved in.
He's even helped me with the bags.
Thank you, why don't you stay for dinner.
May be next time. Thank you anyway.
Thanks again.
You've been doing good dog.
Yo, man.
Yo, I had a feeling about you,
but you done better than
I ever expected. Keep it up, yo.
You walk with me today...
you walk with me tomorrow
and that's my word.
Alright, yo.
Dan, are you there?
Dan?
(Grandma)
Just wanted me to bring you this.
You meet her today, right.
Are you okay?
Please, tell grandma that I said thank you.
Eat up, dog.
We got a lot head of us tonight, man.
Oh ya, what's your plan man.
You'll see.
Someone's busted.
Ain't that the fucking F.O.B.
From your building, dog.
Yo, that looks like him.
He says he comes from Thailand.
I'll take care of this.
Do you know why they stop you?
I have no license.
I just moved here.
You on the run.
OK, I give you a break...
this time next you won't be so lucky,
understand?
Everyone needs to get back in line guys.
What's up Hollywood, good to see you.
Good to see you, Goldie.
My boy Pat's wise guy in training.
Please, Goldie.
For real, don't be surprised
when you see this kid come up, man.
Well, see, baby.
Jules in?
Yo, he's inside brother.
Can we get at him?
Yo, go ahead.
Thank you, man.
Get inside bitch,
before I kick you to the curb.
Get - Go ahead.
Man, come on?
Hey! Kid.
What's up man?
Everything cool?
What's up, G?
What happened
with that shit I gave you to do?
It's alright man, take care of it.
What the fuck is wrong with him?
That motherfucker's just stoned.
Don't worry about him, dog.
That motherfucker's always stoned.
Yo, Pat, let's go man.
You need me boss?
No, just wait here. I'll be back.
Besides your two seconds away
from losing 530 dollars - Fuck.
Show me man.
That shit don't count.
Yes, it does.
No, it doesn't.
So where and the fuck you been?
You the one that had me waiting.
So I heard business has been pretty
good there, Goldie tooth.
Pretty good -
thanks to my new boy Pat here.
So you are the new bad Motherfucker.
Yo, this is Jules man
he knows your uncle back in Thailand.
Oh yes Chan,
he was one crazy Motherfucker
that who you took after.
I didn't really know my uncle.
From all the shit you been up to...
you must know something about him.
It's in the blood baby,
it's in the blood.
So what's this my bonus?
Employ of the month right here.
He needs a little Pun man, hook it up.
Alright then
so what do you have in mind partner.
Do you like them short, tall...
or you like one with big titts
or perhaps those little pointy ones?
I like'em blond.
Pat the bad Motherfucker.
I know exactly the girl - K.C.
Good shit.
Dope man.
I'm finally getting super pure
products again.
I can see that.
But it's going to cost you.
You jacking prices up on me again.
The price of production has gone up.
What can I say?
Your cost goes up so I pay for it.
If you don't like it,
get it from somewhere else.
You're biting me.
How old are you any way?
Old enough.
You're so beautiful.
Say it again.
So beautiful and sweetly cool.
What are you doing?
It's not in.
Oh my god, is this your first time?
Ya.
So beautiful sweetly,
so beautiful.
Say it again.
Henry and I will stop by tomorrow
with a paper work.
All right, then.
You know Henry did a really good job.
Henry said two years of payment
and you'll be done.
What, did you say two years?
I thought we were going to help dad.
While he's just paying
half of what he owes.
What only half.
Come on man that's bullshit.
Pat, you don't know
shit shut the hell up.
Ok, that's enough...
I got enough headache now if papa knew.
Man, I really thought
we were going to help dad, man...
you and fucking
Henry's full of shit, man.
I'm fuck'en out of here.
Why you smoking shit?
If Papa knew -
you know you'd be in big trouble.
Just give me that -
Your such a dork sometimes.
I got another one.
Thank you lord.
What do you want?
What is your problem?
You know dad is having
a rough time right now.
IRS is trying to take everything away.
At least Pearl's trying to help.
Look, she's not the only one
trying to help.
What do you do?
You don't even go to work any more.
Just don't worry about it, ok.
I mean you don't even talk
to me any more.
Look, I'm sorry about that, ok.
But it will all be over soon.
I got it all figured out now.
Got what figured out?
What can you do?
You just don't need to know
right now, ok.
Is this about Goldie?
You know, he's not a good person.
Do you want to end up like Uncle Chan?
Look, you know I'm not like Uncle Chan.
Come here.
No, get off me.
Look Ploy, I don't need you
worry right now, ok?
I just don't need it.
So I'll need you to sign the bottom
of these papers, please.
Dad, this is an agreement
that you have to pay for IRS annually.
Dad, sign it.
Henry thank you for all of the work
that you did,
But...
But what?
But I think I will take care of it by myself.
He did everything for you.
How can you do this?
He's been doing this all week.
I pay for your time.
That's not the point,
Dad.
That is the point.
Somebody have to pay.
Don't look at me like that -
I'll wait in the car.
Dan?
My grandma invites you for dinner.
I just went to your room
but you weren't there.
I figured you would be here.
Please tell her I said thanks and
I'll see you then.
Where my soup, Ploy?
She made the soup herself.
So, how long have you been here?
I was in San Francisco for
the last 2 years before I move here.
Oh! Yeah... what were you doing there?
I worked in a restaurant.
Really, that's good.
He's probably just a dish washer.
You got a social?
Have you got a work permit?
No, sir.
So, where do you work now?
I haven't got a chance to got a job.
I suppose I should get one soon.
Welcome to work
with me if you want a job.
We're about to need help.
Shit man.
Can you drive?
Yes.
Fuck this, I'm out of here.
Say Pat.
So Dan would you come to work with me?
Yes.
Henry, I'm really sorry about my dad...
he can get really stubborn sometimes.
Really, that must be where you got it from.
I knew he was going to pull
something today.
Look, I know he'll come around.
He just needs some time that's all.
What, your kidding right?
Henry, he knows he has to deal with this.
Then he has to deal with this on his
own. I'm done it's over.
You have to help him, he's my father,
If you don't help him the IRS
they'll take everything, the restaurant.
No way.
What took you so damn long?
You've been doing this for an hour.
Why are you doing it so small for.
Pat! It's his first day
stop nagging, show him.
Come here, come here.
Get off my sight!
Just go take care of the garbage.
Hi! Pearl.
Have you eaten yet?
I can cook you something.
No, thanks. This is your paper work,
keep it good because...
You gonna need.
I'm sorry, don't be mad at me.
I was wasted you and Henry's time.
Try some other's way.
Up to you dad, because I've done my part.
Here? What's that guy doing?
I hire him to help me here.
He said he used to work
in a restaurant before.
Has he got a work permit?
How are you gonna pay for him?
Come on, he's that just like us.
How can you do this?
You already got a problem with IRS
Want more problem with then?
Up to you, you know it's against the laws.
I don't know. Up to you.
Hey gorgeous, haven't see for ages.
What do you want,
better yet get the fuck out.
Relax I ain't here to eat.
If your not here to eat
how can I help you?
You can't help me.
Yo, Pat let's go, dog.
Look at your ass -
you know K. Cs' been asking about you.
She's over at the pad
with the other girls.
Hey man, let's just be out then.
Pat get back here.
Listen to dad, Pat.
I say we be out, dog.
What the fuck you looking
at Motherfucker.
Yo, fuck him man, he's just a fucking
F.O.B. Let's just be out.
Who the hell are you?
Yo, I say we be out, dog.
Don't be a stranger, give me a call.
See? That's why I need help
from a new guy.
You like that, baby?
Bitches, out.
Out!
Fuck, what's your problem?
I'll be waiting in the bed room
there's a Jacuzzi in there to.
Out!
Asshole!
Are you ready, dog?
I was fucking ready man.
Why you gotta cut me off like that?
I'm not talking about that fucking whore...
that you think is your girlfriend, dog.
I'm talking about you ready to walk
with me for tomorrow?
What you got in mind?
That Motherfucker Jules...
he should never have disrespected
me like that.
I made that Motherfucker way
too much money, man.
Yo, man.
Stick with that Motherfucker
and this is as good as it gets.
While it's not good enough.
I hear you, man.
It's time for a change
for tomorrow, yo.
Hey, I'm waiting.
Go fuck your whore, dog
and not a word of this.
What?
Nothing.
You don't know how beautiful you are...
That's sweet.
But you know I'm paid
for so don't waste your breath.
Paid for.
Baby I ruined Goldie's surprise, didn't I?
But, but I thought
he said you were asking for me.
I was baby, I was I told him I wasn't
going to come if you weren't here.
But he paid for you...
how much do you get
for an afternoon pool party?
Fuck you,
you don't pay my rent Motherfucker.
K.C., I didn't mean like that.
Nobody takes care of me.
I want to take care of you.
You still ain't paid me
for the two times I been with you...
and now you want to take care of me -
please.
Just tell me how much I need.
You can't afford me.
But I'll be real soon.
Yo, what you got in mind, baby?
You'll see.
Pat Thai, please.
Yes, sir.
What would you like to have, sir?
Number 33.
What can I get you?
Have you seen my dad?
He's on his way.
Excuse me, can we order now?
Let me take care of this.
I'll be right back. Sorry.
You lies to my dad...
that you worked in a restaurant before.
I can tell by the way you work
that you never done it before.
Why did you work here?
It seems your dad need here.
I don't get it.
I've been trying to help him.
But he's never seen my thought.
Maybe your dad need other kind of help.
Pearl, isn't it?
I thought... l'd like to move back
to our house for a little while.
Just saw a smile from your dad today.
Why do you always stick
you nose on somebody else business.
Seem like your dad must love you a lot.
Yeah, he loved me.
But it's hard to stay under.
Because he always say being Thai,
you have to be a certain way.
Specially the lady.
Being Thai lady couldn't do this,
couldn't do that anything!
But why doesn't he took the fact if us
being in America.
American are so much lay back.
That's the Thai Traditional.
Anyone who understands
would be proud of being Thai.
So why are you here?
If I have a choice, I wouldn't be here.
How about your family,
don't you miss them?
They're so far away form you.
I'm not that far away from them.
I'm done for a day. I gotta go.
Man, what are you doing with my bike?
I said what are you doing with my bike?
Kick his ass.
So did you really think that shit
wasn't going to change that.
I would be busted my ass out on
the streets making you money?
Shit you got off to a good start G,
but you ain't gonna finish.
Time is up - you through -
It's my world now, dog.
What do you think, man?
What don't you just shoot him
in the head?
Motherfucker's always getting
shoot in the head.
It's to easy, man...
see if I'm gonna shoot a Motherfucker...
I want to see him die.
See you shoot a Motherfucker
in the head til he's dead,
he didn't fell it.
I'm going to hell, dog
there's no doubt in my mind,
so when I kill Jules ass,
I want to see that Motherfucker suffer.
I been making that Motherfucker
money for years.
Now that Motherfucker gonna jack
prices up on me.
That's the last straw.
You know what we gotta do.
Yo man, I got it.
This is some serious shit.
You freeze up of fuck up you gone die.
Look man, you give me the signal
I'm clock'en...
Jules' bodyguard
then you got him all to yourself.
On my signal.
That's right.
I'm gonna shoot those
Motherfuckers in the head man.
I don't want to see them die
or nothing, yo.
I want them dead as soon as possible.
Yeah.
What the fuck happened to your ass?
That bastard with the sport bike
from the other night.
He broke down in front of the gym...
tried to take his bike
didn't work out to while.
But boss you know me,
old Charlie's going to take care of business.
Motherfucker's just got lucky, that's all.
Was this Motherfucker by himself?
Yo, but Charlie got fucked up though.
You know, Jack I been meaning to ask
you something.
Where were you when
I was getting my ass kicked?
Yo, I was waiting to see if the shit
got out of hand.
Out of hand,
out of hand the shit don't get more
out of hand then this shit man.
Shut the fuck up man.
What this fucking F.O.B. Did this?
You gotta be kidding me.
Yo, smart ass.
I don't see you fuck'en take him on.
Well, it looks like he took
you on pretty good.
Motherfucker I had it with your shit man.
Hey, (Unclear) we got to go get this
motherfucker alright.
Yo, make no mistake.
I'm gonna get this motherfucker.
Then your ass is next.
Hi, Pad Thai?
Hi! Grandma.
I thought you forgot me.
Go help Dan back there.
All right.
Yo, you know your ass is marked right
motherfucker.
Man you fuck'en F.O.B. You don't even no
who your fuck'en with
Who the hell do you
think you are, Bruce Lee?
He's my Idol.
Fool!
I don't give a fuck if you work
for my father or not.
Hey, what's the problem?
Where's Grandma's noodles?
You'd better watch your fuck'en back,
they're coming for you.
Got a problem with my brother?
What is F.O.B.?
I got to apologize for my brother.
F.O.B. Is Fresh on the boat
The refugee that just off the boat.
So, what the problem with Pat?
Nothing, just his friend
that got problem with me.
Gol-d?
Not him, maybe some other boys.
They're all in the same gang.
I'm warning you, stay away from him!
You seems to hate that man.
How do you know?
I could tell by the way you look at him.
Doesn't your brother know.
Of course, he doesn't care.
He doesn't even know that Gol-d used him.
Opp...
Dindan... Dan.
What's wrong?
Must be him.
Must be who?
She was 9- month- pregnancy...
When officer Dindan's wife was killed
got murder in her own home.
The killer was never found.
To investigated...
And discovered the killer
Chan the drug lord.
The investigation took 4 years.
Dan is that officer.
The fuck'en place is empty, dog.
Yo, I thought you said me was going
to be here.
Probably sent him to the Restaurant man.
Yo, Jack!
What's up?
Charlie's line can't understand.
Ah, pretty.
Motherfucker.
Fucker - you'd better know your fucking role,
cause Goldie ain't here
and your fresh out of friends.
You better quit this shit Charlie,
you're going to get hurt.
Yo, Charlie we ain't got time for this shit.
Next time.
Oh baby, Oh.
Like that uh, that kid didn't never
make you feel that good right.
Never honey, not even close.
So his little ass told
you whom he loved you, uh.
Man when you told him
your plan with Jules,
he thought he was going
to take over the world.
Little Motherfuckers almost
as ambitious as I am.
Shit, but not as fucking ruthless.
So you sure it's only going to be Tommy's
ass there that day?
Ya, as far as I know.
What the fuck you mean
as far as I know,
is he going to be the only
Motherfucker there or not?
Yes, yes -
It's collection day that day -
all the other guys
are out collecting payments.
It's the same thing every month.
Hey, you know I love you,
you crazy bitch, right?
I love you too.
I love this time of the day.
The sunset makes me calm
and be myself again.
Then it was Pat and Ploy.
You know about my past.
I just found out a few days ago.
I know every thing ever
since I met your dad.
My dad is a good man.
He's not like uncle Chan.
We never got to meet uncle Chan.
The only one who's like uncle Chan is Pat.
Pat, why did you do that for?
What?
I saw you Pat, I saw you driving away.
I ain't got time for this.
Were you going to kill Dan
is that why you were up there?
Pat you don't even know uncle Chan.
What about uncle Chan?
Dan was the one who killed him -
he was an old police in Thailand.
What, how do you know this?
Isn't that, Isn't that
why you where up there?
Look Dan fucked up some of my friends...
and he had it coming
that's why we broke into his apartment.
How, how do you know
he killed uncle Chan?
Ploy tells me.
I think Pat's like that...
Because the people
that he hang out with.
I try to warn him about Gol-d.
Yeah, that guy just
like your uncle Chan.
By the time I found out it was too late.
I made a wrong decision.
By going out with him.
I was a fool for believing him.
And one day I saw the real him.
I try to fight him.
I never told anymore before.
I want each man
at the corner of the house.
Two out front is that fucking, you clear that?
Yo, what's up dog,
what's up with all the muscle and shit?
Sit your ass down Motherfucker
I have got some good news for you.
What the fucks going on here, man?
Goldie, I need you to take care
of someone for me.
Yo, you know I don't be trying
to fuck around like that no more.
Goldie but this is different...
the fucker...
that works for your father's restaurant...
he's the cop
who killed your uncle in Thailand.
Son of a Bitch!
How long have you known this?
Just found out - why do you think
I have all these men here.
He's just one Motherfucker though, yo.
Goldie, this guy's
way to fucking dangerous,
that's why I need you to do this.
I'll take care of this.
Yo, what?
He fuck'en killed my uncle,
I want to take him out.
Ya, Happy New Year to you Charlie.
Son of a Bitch!
Hey, Sweetie.
Hey, Pat.
Yo, Pat comes over here.
Looks like they don't
wish you a Happy Thai New Year, yo.
I don't fuck'en need there luck.
Man, it's been two days...
why ain't that mother fuck'en
F.O. B floating in the sea?
Times got to be right,
you know what I mean.
Times right now make
it happen dog tonight.
I got it, man.
Then we'll take care of Jules ass.
Bring me a proof, dog.
That's a pretty sharp knife.
Officer Dindan.
Want to hear what I got to say first.
No!
Let's go.
What the fuck is that shit?
We ain't robbing a Bank.
Gangster, dog.
Jack your watching entirely
too much television.
Come on, man.
Look, I'm serious man...
after this you and I got to have a long
time to talk,
but business first make sure
you're together.
Yo, Charlie get the fuck in here man.
Hay! Dan.
Meet Jack.
Get you back Motherfucker.
My dog, I love the way you say hello.
Hello.
Talk to me.
He took off on his motorcycle
And his sister.
Bring them back here now.
Come through the back
and wait for my word.
I'll take care of it.
We're taken them back
to the warehouse.
Hey, I want well locked,
loaded and ready to go.
Bring that fucking pig in.
Take the motherfucking bag
off his head - on my word.
Where do you want me baby?
Just stay right there,
shut the fuck up, cause right now.
I got to think how I'm going
to handle this Motherfucker.
Yo, who the fuck is that man?
Oh, this motherfucker, he's a friend.
Actually, he ain't no friend,
his ass is dead, yo.
But fuck this motherfucker is that
other motherfucker dead?
I brought you his bike man.
I don't give a fuck
about his bike is he dead?
Ya, he's dead I told you
I'd take care of that shit.
Bitch shut the fuck up alright -
so he's dead.
That's what I said...
I got you the proof you wanted
what the fucks up, dog?
Nothing, fucking everything.
I'm curious dog.
How're you fucking kill him dog, man.
Bang, Bang right in the back of the head.
So this Motherfucker
just let you roll up on him...
and fucking blast his fucking head off?
Like I said man,
he wasn't fucking shit.
Motherfucker didn't put up a fight?
No, man. He did even
know what hit him.
Pat, you're a bad Motherfucker.
You're a bad some, bitch.
Fuck, fuck, why can't shit go the way
I fucking plan it.
You know what
I hate more than anything?
No, dog. What's that man?
I hate when motherfuckers
take me for granted...
like that motherfucker right there.
Hey, Jules thought shit wasn't never
going to change.
Thought, I'd be busting my ass
on the street making you money.
No, it's all coming to and end.
You had a good run G...
good start but you ain't going to finish.
Throw time is up.
It's my world now.
I wanted to wait for you dog,
but I couldn't resist
KC new her just wanted to get them -
sold Jules' ass out in a heart beat...
couldn't wait to see his ass go down.
Goldie.
What's gonna take to sell me out?
What are you talking about?
I love you.
Is that right.
You know that.
You love him,
Ya, that's right.
She sold your ass out to, dog.
Told her you loved her and
gonna take care of her.
I did, man.
How you gonna take care of this trick?
You know, I can't afford her.
Not unless you had some fucking
extra money coming in.
I trusted you Motherfucker,
I trusted you...
after all I fucking did for you,
you gonna shit on me...
so you fuck'in killed Dan.
Come on, Goldie. I told you I did.
So why the fuck is Charlie and Jack...
on their way back
with that Motherfucker.
Ya, that's right,
I sent them to after your ass...
make sure you get that shit done.
Any minute now...
I can't no more you just gonna have
to trust me Motherfucker.
Grab that bitch...
you can die with the mother fuck'en
love of your life.
You asshole.
Get that Motherfucker go.
I want that Motherfucker dead.
Keep your hand up young lady.
Get them up.
Any visual on the gun?
No. No visual on the gun?
I shot him, I shot him.
Drop the gun.
I shot him, I shot him!
No, I shot him.
I shot him.
Of course, I feel bad for what I did.
I killed the person
and there's no excuse for that.
But I did what I had to do
to protect my family.
They understand that.
My brother wasn't a bad person.
He just made bad decisions.
He wanted to help my father
with his tax problem...
and he did it the only way
he thought he could.
Everybody said they didn't see anything.
No one would step up
and testify against me.
And everybody's fingerprints on the gun,
the police couldn't find
a case against me.
We have to look out for each other
in these crazy streets.
We're family.
Even Dan
Dan says: You stole my vest
Dan saved my brother...
even though my uncle
caused him harm.
We are so grateful to him
Although the doctor's say
that Pat will never be able to walk again
At least he's still alive.
My father's problem with the IRS
turned out to be a mistake...
and the case eventually dismissed.
It was such a relief.
All of us Thai people living
in Los Angeles
We're all out here trying to survive.
Trying to make a living.
Trying to hang on to our roots.
Those are the thing
we have to hold on too
Because that's all we have.
I've already been in here for
the past three months and now.
I'm finally going home.