Take a break guys.
Grab a cup of coffee.
Let's go!
This is going to Section 3.
Section 3? But...
I said Section 3!
But it says in the papers...
There is a mistake in the papers.
But lieutenant Melnikov said...
We got around 200 ton
of nuclear weapons here.
Less than half has been disarmed.
Continue.
Go!
Barabanov?
Yes.
There will be 12 men on the slegdecrew.
All has been handpicked by my people.
They've promised stable weather. It will
take them ten days to reach the border.
Ten days? Very well.
That will give the President
enough time to panic.
The President?
Yes
He plays an important role
though he doesn't know it himself.
The leading role for once.
Barabanov!
Eat.
Great!
How do we find them?
There's a shitload here.
Take this one. Check
every single one of them.
What is the password?
I don't know.
Come over here. I found them.
Cheers for Åke and Anna.
Next time it might be your turn?
Perhaps. I haven't dared to ask.
Excuse me.
I think this dance is mine.
Hey, Tessie.
Did I say something wrong?
A very nervous person enters the room.
He is not Åke's cousin from Åbo.
Then he says a few things to you guys from OP5.
What is this? A wedding or a conspiration?
Answer!
He, who was here, works for
a organization, called ClA.
You are under suspicion for being a spy.
Oh no.
You are caught.
What if I confess?
Doesn't matter.
Punishment is the same.
Do I get a last wish?
Yes. You have 20 minutes.
OPERATIONAL HEADQUARTER
OP 5
Hello!
Per Molander, Prime minister's...
ID card...
I'm here twice a week.
They're awating me.
That much rush there is not.
Please be seated.
We will only need 4 people
besides Stålhandske and myself.
You... you...
... you and you.
You are on reserve.
Please leave the room now.
Someone wishes to smuggle a nuclear
weapon from Russia and through Sweden.
We are to find and eliminate
them inside Russia.
This is Top-Secret. You will meet
well trained and equipped resistance.
So it's combat rediness,
as soon as we hit the ground. Questions?
We will assume they have heatseeking devices.
Wear snowsuit till we have established contact.
And after that reflectionsuit.
If I do not wish to be seen,
I will not be seen.
I just need to know,
where the hell they are.
THE RUSSIAN TUNDRA
We will camp here.
The area has been secured.
Good.
Find him, but quickly.
Get him back.
Who is in charge?
Damnit!
What's your name?
Kolja! Kolja Mordavin!
Good, Kolja. Now tell me,
who will have the missile.
I do not know! I do not know!
You are gonna turn over a nuclear
missile to the first guy you meet?
It seems a bit too easy, right?
Think, Kolja, think.
The password is Washington. That's all.
I know nothing else!
Execute them all.
Do as your order tells you!
Shit! Damnit!
Collect all personal belongings,
which is not burnable.
No, I do not wish to die.
Please don't. Please?
They were all carrying 50.000 dollars.
What to do with the money?
Burn them.
What?
He's dead.
I fell through the ice with
the bastard... and lost my skies.
Good. And the body?
It was impossible to get him out
The stream must have taken
him several kilometers away.
It was a nuclear missile.
You scare me.
A russian produced SS20,
1,5 megaton, completely intact.
So why did the "terrorists" have
nothing to defend themselves with?
They were dragging a nuclear weapon and
a fortune, but not a weapon.
You did a good job. The missile
has been located and secured.
Fine.
Then we can all sleep safely tonight.
Have you not been home?
Do you need anything?
This.
No sign of anyone waiting,
on the mentioned meeting spot.
It was never intended, for the
missile to cross the border.
How do I get in? You just
need to have your head with you.
What does he mean by that?
You said he loved toys,
but that is too much.
In Carls case that border
is fine as hair.
We don't know what to do,
with these rooms.
Carl says he wishes,
to keep them as they are.
He has secret plans properly.
They are beautiful. I'm considering
to begin working from home.
Anna asks all the time.
Have you told Tessie anything?
Concerning what?
The trip. What did you say?
The truth: Lots of snow, fucking cold,
tons of meetings, and then we went home.
Did she believe it?
No, she is too smart for that.
It doesn't look good at all
for you, Carl.
It is your turn.
I'm going now.
Yes.
Great Britain attacks...
Nothern Europe.
Well damn it,
it's a conspiracy.
You are somewhat paranoid.
Your damn right I am.
Why you want to play?
You loose and get mad.
I don't get...
I'm focused!
Statistically I should win soon.
Statistically you should be dead.
LULEAA, NOTHERN SWEDEN
It was homicide.
The chemical test showed
no signs of alcohol or drugs.
But instead a noticeably
high concentration of syccinykolin.
Sushi... say what?
Syccinykolin.
It's another word for curare.
The russian border guards has faxed.
We can exclude everyone,
except maybe Matti Leppinen.
Finish passport, resident of Murmansk.
He crossed the border to Finland
same day as Holma was killed.
Two days later he buys a one-way
airplane ticket from Göteborg to Murmansk.
The 20th.
Yes.
What happend?
I can't say.
Was is this circus I
was going here for?
I just heard it myself. Congratulations.
I hope you have a good reason.
You are to see a weird request.
I can't accept the medal.
It causes only problems to refuse.
Come. I want to show you this.
I haven't been able to forget
what you said when you returned.
Rune Jansson.
Give me the http address.
You are permitted to go up there
and find out what it is.
Unusual to kill with curare.
Perhaps not.
No, but it is out here in the country.
I read,
that KGB used it as a gimmick.
This thing with curare, that is.
Alright.
We have calculated the size, value,
and origin of the cargo.
What has been smuggled out of
Russia that is to kill for?
Caviar, weapons?
But the combination of caviar
and curare doesn't sound likely.
Weapons then?
Yes. But it's pure speculation.
But that is what you got to do, in
such a situation -- speculate.
Of course.
So we'll keep doing that.
Answer following:
Is it possible, that russian nuclear
weapons are smuggled through Sweden?
Unlikely.
But not impossible?
No, but as said unlikely.
But what could it then be?
They have hardly smuggled
cloudberry from Tjernobyl.
Was that all?
Yes.
Just one more thing...
We have arrested a suspect.
He's a well-known smuggler up here.
He lacks an alibi
and is under suspicion.
He has told an amazing story,
I think you should hear.
It's him!
That's the man from the tundra!
He can provide me with an alibi! So
talk with him! It's me, Juha!
Ask him! He saved my life!
I didn't kill anyone!
Shut up! Get him down!
Fucked up assholes!
What the hell is this? What?
Would you care to tell me
what is going on here?
I got to talk with him in private.
You may participate in the interrogation.
but you can't takeover the
interrogetion of my suspects.
He's mainsuspect in a homicidecase.
He has persistantly claimed to have met
a swedish parachute soldier
on the russian tundra.
Five minutes ago it sounded like
the world's most incredible story.
Now I'm not so damn
certain no more.
Are here all the documents?
He's a homicide suspect!
Not any more. There's his alibi.
Is this some kind of fucking trick?
I can guarantee you he was not in
Sweden, when the murder was committed.
Okay, okay. Then I'll release the prisoner.
Arrest him again.
For what?
According to paragraph 2 in 2. chapter
in the State Secret Act
everything he's done in the last
30 days are of national security.
LULEAA LUFTHAVN
You know what your charges are.
An intern investigation decides,
if it leads to prosecution or not.
Was there any doubt of
the operations nature?
No. I made a decision, which
in the situation seemed correct.
You admit insubordination?
Is that term correct?
I made a decision, that I in the
same situation would make again.
With that decision
you threat national security.
In addition to that you place your
commander and the groups life in danger.
You must have known that.
Or what?
So? Or what?!
Yes, I was aware of that.
Still you lead the man escape.
A terrorist with information
of our actions.
Terrorist? The man smuggles
fox fur, damn it! An amateur!
Why didn't you execute the man,
as you were ordered?
From now on I will only answer
questions from Hamilton.
Wont he show me enough respect
to hear my explanation in the same room
Can he not show me that respect
then you can go to hell!
Give him his dismissal.
One thing you shall know:
As leader of the organistation
it's still my call
who leaves and who stays.
Is that clear?
Yes, of course. Sorry.
There's another missile.
It was taken out of Russia and
on through Sweden.
The left behind truck in Luleaa...
There was radioactivity in the hold.
The truck driver was killed with curare.
The Dollars in the glove compartement was
from same serie as Juha Saaronen's.
So the truck driver and
the episode on the tundra
are connected.
They origin from the same source.
All traces lead back to Russia.
To Murmansk, to Severomorsk.
But now I don't dare to trust the CIA.
I need information
straight from Russia.
From one who I trust and
who trusts me.
You admit insubordination?
Is that term correct?
I made a decision, that I, in that
same situation would make again.
same situation would make again...
Hi.
Where the hell have you been?
At work.
Right till now?
Yes.
When did you start to
work till 10:30pm? Uh?
Why dont you pick up your celluar?
Relax. What happened?
You have to answer when I call.
I worry. Don't you understand that?
Anna called today.
Can you say what happened?
No.
What is Åke charged of?
I can't say.
You know that. But...
Anna spoke about insubordination.
So talk to her, if it...
I'm asking you!
What happened in Russia?
This is insane.
You don't sleep at night.
You are like a maniac.
Who do you really work for?
Carl!
I love you.
And I love you. You know that.
Yeah...
I guess that's what I wanted to say.
Was that it?
Yes.
Aren't you gonna ask anything else?
Like what?
Like why I dont sleep at night.
You are not interested.....
You're gonna tell me if I ask?
No.
No, uh?
It has nothing with this to do!
What is it then related to?
You asking.
Are you bringing Rune Jansson
with you to Murmansk?
No, he's bringing me.
He's to investigate the murder of Lasse
Holma. Officially I'm his assistant.
MURMANSK, RUSSIA
Am I to listen to this story?
Of course.
I've got a hunch, you're telling the
Russians one story and me another.
Bingo!
You say you talk Swedish?
Yes.
I'm chief of police
Rune Jansson from Luleaa.
I've been counting on recording
this conversation on tape.
If just the shit works.
Sorry.
You're under suspicion for assitance
in the murder of Lasse Holma.
What do you have to say to that?
It wasn't me.
You confessed it to
my Russian colleagues.
Those sons of bitches are crazy!
The homicide was in Sweden. The
question is, where you should be tried.
Here in Murmansk or in Haparanda.
If you are tried in Sweden,
you'll be sentenced to life.
And if you brush your teeth every
night, it'll be 7~8 years.
Here in Murmansk you'll get a
bullet. Got it?
Yes.
You where there when Holma was killed?
You know what happened?
It wasn't me.
It was Ilja.
Ilja Aleksandrov. He killed him.
Samuel Ulfsson, please.
Ulfsson here.
I'm straight from the interrogation.
Just as we thought it was one missile.
It was loaded to Amalthea in
Varberg, nationality is unknown.
Probably Libyan.
I'll call you back.
We have traced Amalthea to Rotterdam.
She has changed identity
and disappeared.
Does Carl know of this development?
I haven't called him.
Good, I will.
Grab his briefcase!
Look at me, you motherfucker!
Go to Hell!
Get him in the building. Now!
This way.
You rat.
Major Barabanov, You speak english.
The Swedes have some questions.
I'm a KGB officer.
Mr. Aleksandrov or Barabanov...
Go to Hell!
I dont think, this is working.
Yes, it works. Relax.
See...
Hello, Mr. General.
Oh, Hello!
Yes... I've heard, you have taken...
what's his name? Aleksandrov.
Yes, after a Finn's description.
Has he helped you with
the investigation?
Not the Finn, Aleksandrov.
Yes, quite a bit.
I see. Perhaps you'd like,
for us to take care of him?
Thank you, Mr. General. It's friendly
of you. But there is no need for that.
Let me know, if I can help.
Thanks.
I've got evidence!
Get him to the car. Quickly.
Good Evening.
Okay?
May I...? Thank You.
Good Evening.
Everything alright?
Where the hell have you been?
Been? Me?
Damn Idiot!
Don't be so haughty!
You want names?!
Fellinskij! Japasvilij!
Glusjenko! Rotenko!
You wanted names! You got them.
They have completely left you out.
They let you rot here and take
all the money you earned them!
Excuse me?
He likes your apartment.
I'm a KGB officer.
You have no right to interrogate me!
Okay.
Okay, Mr. Major. Go.
Go, go.
Get out!
Go, I tell you!
Go on I said!
What if I tell?
Tell them everything?
Could you tell me
where to find Mordavins office?
Down there and to the left? Thanks.
What's wrong?
Get a hold of the coroner too.
He died of a heart attack.
Have a look at this.
Oh my god.
They wont pay to
anyone but Hawkins.
Only Hawkins can wind up deal.
The swedes have him.
We have to send someone else.
No. It's only the american
who knows where the tritium is.
You have Barabanov
to thank for that stupidity.
It must be Hawkins.
Damn it.
Make sure that he gets the bomb.
Very well. And Hamilton?
Hamilton should have been killed
several years ago.
Any problems?
He's one hot-headed little bastard.
It's absurd letting Hawkins
dictate us the conditions.
I think
we should meet all his demands.
In that far out belief he can stay
and enjoy the lovely Swedish house.
Meanwhile the CIA locate the missile
and disarm it.
The government agrees Carl. As the situation
is at the moment, it's all about...
Sam?
Hello? Can you...?
Carl?
I can't... Can you hear me?
Fix it.
What's going on?
What the hell is going on?
Who are you?!
What do we do now, Sam?
What's the next move?
It's no longer our problem.
USA has taken over.
6. fleet has set course towards Libya.
CIA is tailing Hawkins
and expect to find the bomb.
That's what USA have been hoping for.
Bombing Libya to pieces in their
hunt for a nuclear missile.
And if they get a direct hit...
For Sweden the case is closed.
Go home and sleep.
That's an order.
There has been put a lid on, right?
Nobody can hear about it.
Ulfsson!
600. Russian, who after a weak start
came 3rd after Torrence and Ottey.
I can't keep up.
It's going to fast.
You take it.
No. Forget it.
No, I'm taking it.
It's Stenhamra.
Hey, Åke. It has been a while.
It's Åke.
Could he call you back?
Yes. Yes.
Okay. Give my regards to Anna.
Okay. Bye bye.
What was it about?
Hawkins escaped the CIA in London.
What else did he say?
If you want to talk to him, call him.
For gods sake... Anna can
forgive him. I can forgive him.
An intire World can,
but not his best friend.
What do you forgive?
I don't know.
No, but it sounds great.
What can't you forgive him for?
Something you will
never be able to understand.
I can't explain it,
but it's...
It's an entire other world.
Another universe. Something
you can't even begin to grasp.
How do you know?
What could he have done that's so...
... unforgiveable, that you would
let it destroy our love?
I gave an order,
for 12 men to be executed.
Before we burned the bodies
we cut them up with a chainsaw.
I cut them up with a chainsaw.
It's best parting the limbs from
the body. They burn better that way.
Nothing kept me back.
One of... the bodies I cut up...
... was... He...
Strange enough he was alive. He was
trembling. The entire body was quivering.
I had to get out my gun. I didn't
know where the heck it was.
I dropped it in the snow.
It was sticky from the blod.
Then I put a bullet through his brains.
Officially it was an assignment
that never took place.
We had to eliminate
a terroristgroup inside Russia.
We couldn't leave any clues.
No witnesses.
Åke knew about it too.
Everything was planned. Gone through
every little detail.
But still...
... he lets one of them run.
By that he threatened not only me, but
the entire group. He broked a deal...
... and put everyone in danger.
The problem is, how do I
convince anyone that...
... it was wrong letting one live.
That it was a failure to disobey an order.
Who are you Carl?
Who would do that? Can't you grasp,
that such a man would explode?
I don't know them and don't
know if they deserve...
Who would deserve something like that?
It's totally uncomprehensible.
We were given an order.
If one of your superiors,
told you to murder me...
... would you then do it?
What are you doing, Carl?
Excuse me?
Orders from the highest place.
Your leaving for Tunis.
Yes sir... Tunis.
I don't know whether to be irritated
or impressed? Why are you doing it?
Therapy.
Good.
Oh yes, there was one more thing.
This means you'll be working
closely together with USA.
You know, PLO shoots the head of me,
if they think that.
Then make sure they don't think that.
All contact with USA is through me.
Untill the bomb is located.
After that you're on your own.
"You"?
What?
You said "You".
Yes, you're not going alone.
And it's not up for discussion.
Sam?
Therapy.
Good luck.
He wants to know if we can help.
Else anything can happen.
Can we trust him?
No.
Excuse me? No.
May I call you back? Exactly.
Yes?
I've gone through the equipment.
Everything is as we wanted, except
these transmitters, I found.
Good.
PLO has accepted.
It's tommorrow morning at 05.00.
From here we cross the desert to the base,
where the bomb is... There!
What the hell is this?
Hey! Hold on.
I'm allergic.
To horses, yes. These are
camels. You'll take the white thing.
Carl, take a look at these.
This can only mean one thing.
Stop! On the ground!
Sorry, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
They forced me to it.
They're gonna kill me.
I trusted you!
Sorry. Sorry.
Please forgive me.
That's Carl.
No it has to be Åke.
No Åke is in the back.
The one with the lover.
71 or 82?
Take the 82.
Oh, it's third time this week!
Stop it, Brännström!
I didn't know you were here, I'm sorry!
I'm going home now.
Yes... Sorry.
The light is on out there.
Check the gate. It's probably the fox.
Ulfsson.
The alarm has gone off out on Stenhamra.
Everything is clear. False Alarm.
Again?
I think, I applied for five
different jobs at once.
It was probably more... I guess
I'm longing for one at all...
Wake up. It's bedtime.
I didn't hear the last part.
This is their camp.
We go in when the night comes.
This is where the bomb is.
It has to be disarmed.
Gør nøjagtig, hvad de siger, Tessie.
Jeg elsker dig.
Anna er her også, Carl.
I can handle it.
Are you sure?
Else I wouldn't say so.
Wouldn't you?
What the hell do you mean?!
You know damn well what I mean!
Yes there.
Yes, Ulfsson here.
Yes.
It's me, Sam.
Listen like you've never listened before, Sam.
15 minutes... nu!
After him!
Everything alright?
Yes damnit.
You've got four minutes.
Nothing is right.
Hawkins must have modified the bomb.
That counts for you also.
Not with that hand! Get out of here now!
It's an order!
Didn't you hear what I said?
You know I never obey orders.
Danish Subtitles by Rosa Reenberg
Translated by B**e* for Team EPiC