Recent newspaper headlines have
planted questions in our minds.
Will Gen. Su****** be Thailand's
next Prime Minister?
The nation is up in arms
as he prepares...
...to sacrifice his honour
for the nation
and break his pre-election
promise not to seek office
and to return the nation
to democracy.
After general elections,
the five majority parties:
Sama***, Cha** Th**, Social *****,
Thai Citi*** and Ras***don
...backed Gen. Su*****da as
the nation's 19th Prime Minister.
Hundreds of students and civilians
have gathered...
...in front of Parliament
to protest.
Protein, Carbohydrates, Fat,
Minerals and Vitamins.
Smelling Salts, Cold Chaser,
Headache Easer.
Monkey Silver Ball Brand
Smelling Salts.
In the recording studio.
It's not the sound of
forest floods.
Weighing 114 pounds.
SAYEW
Sayew
A copy of "You and I", please.
This is a hot issue.
You'd be out of luck
if I didn't save you one.
Wow! What a hunk!
These two, please.
Star Soccer's 15. Sayew's now 35.
50 Baht total.
Do you want a bag?
Yes. Yes, please.
Real Sex Encounters.
My name is Tao. I'm from Sukhothai
but moved to Bangkok to go to University.
I live with my Aunt who runs a
restaurant in our apartment building.
Whenever I'm free, I help wash
dishes and deliver food.
The restaurant is a centre of sorts
that has let me meet a variety...
...of people.
Daeng is a night angel, renting
a room down the hall.
She's the hottest thing to
a country boy like me.
The sexy sway of her sweet slabby
ass sets my heart on fire.
Her bountiful breasts
beg for my attention.
Their quivering bounce simply
leaves me breathless.
One day, she ordered food as usual.
It was my job to deliver it.
When she opened the door,
she was in her nightie.
And beneath that,
she was completely naked.
Can you imagine my excitement?
She didn't shy away as my staring eyes
took in her luscious body.
The hunger in my eyes
begged her to ask.
Would you like to know
what I do for a living?
I don't know.
I avoided the question.
I didn't ask if you knew
but if you want to know.
I nodded my head
but averted my gaze.
She was silent
but smiled seductively...
and pulled me into her arms
and kissed me on the lips.
I shuddered.
She laughed with glee.
There you go. That's my job.
I was surprised and tried to run
but she laughed and pulled me back.
Don't be scared. I won't bite.
But this is my first time.
Everyone has a first time.
That night she schooled me
in the sutras of sex...
...how to love and
kiss like an exper...
Tao, your Aunt needs
you to deliver food.
Okay.
Wet Dreams
These are Sayew's editorial suites.
Sayew is the kind of mag that stirs
the tiger in your loins.
This here is...What's his name?
Fuck it.
Here's Seed. Our layout designer.
He's cut and pasted until
his hands are stuck.
And Knorr Not Nor, owner of
7 serials. Each one a classic.
He's also our photo editor.
These aren't censored yet.
They're off limits.
Not even a peek?
This is Kajorn. The old hand here.
Tao, come here.
He's everyone's mentor
and designs the cover.
There's also Dr. Porn...
...who writes his sex help
column from home.
Our staff may be small but
we're a brilliant bunch.
I'm not a baby anymore.
We have it all. Be it fashion,
factual entertainment...
...foreign and domestic news.
Our best column prints sex stories
submitted by our readers.
But the bulk of them are trash.
Literary drivel.
That's why Hia hired me, Tao,
as his star writer.
Hia Kung Fu. Everyone calls him that.
He's been a porn dog for decades.
Tao, this ain't cutting it.
Why's that?
It's just like all the rest.
That's the problem. Don't you get
what our readers want?
They want more details down to
the pubes.
So they can get off.
Graphic sex.
The kinkier the better.
Long stories short on sex
like yours are getting old.
It was cool before.
It even gave our magazine class.
But let's be straight.
Right now our sales suck...
and my backers called me in.
If you can't raise the heat in your
stories, I'll have to drop you.
But I'll give you a break.
The onus is on you.
You've got to produce what
the market demands.
But my writing's graphic.
My hand trembles just from typing.
Your writing? Graphic?
This is graphic.
Our new writer Young Stallion.
His stories are so graphic they've...
...turned our readers blissfully pale.
"Life is Short, So Enjoy the Ride"
And I thrust ferociously into her.
Where's the art in that? This is
crude and lacks literary style.
That's my point.
You write like a girl.
Think like a man
or give it up, girl.
Save your stories
for trashy romances.
Tits and ass.
Men blow buckets from them.
Hia, red alert! We're about to shoot
and our tits are gone.
Stallion was chatting her up
and then she was gone.
I forgot about these two.
On the left is Pai, our photographer
who loves country music.
On the right is Mah,
our giant stylist.
She has a pimply back
but thinks she's a star.
What the hell!
That rack'o'tits ain't no pussycat.
How'd she disappear?
These two work and
fight all day long.
I'm done with this month's serial.
Same story again.
Go change the title.
Our readers will catch on.
Seed used this just last month.
Here's the next cover.
Excellent. In big bold type.
Big bold type.
Wide Forehead, Sexy Hips,
Dynamite Dimensions 34-24-35.
Shtir Your Desire.
Tao, "Shtir"?
Is there such a word?
Here we go again, mixing
and matching words.
Who cares?
Shtir Your Desire To Sizzles.
But somehow they always catch on.
Tag a few 'S's to the end of that.
That's grammatically incorrect.
Grammatically incorrect.
Then quadruple them, damn it.
Where could she have gone?
Now I have to paint
your nipples again!
Not again.
Make sure your fun doesn't
affect other's work.
I was prepping her for the shoot.
Keeping them pert.
Tao, come and meet Young Stallion.
This is Tao, my niece.
This is Young Stallion.
Our hot new writer.
You two chat. I'll be back.
Young Tao, Hia's favourite niece.
Your reputation precedes you.
I'm honoured by your presence.
I guess I'm the only honoured
one here.
I've read your stories.
They're just pussy perfect cute.
- Black ass baboon!
Think you're shit hot?
You've met your match.
That was a compliment.
Just holler if you need any help.
I'm always open.
You're almost done with
school aren't you?
Your Aunt will kill me
if you flunk because...
...you've been writing porn for me.
She won't find out now.
I've been writing for years.
If I stop now I'll be broke.
Don't you worry about my degree.
I'll pass for sure.
This won't pass.
Categorizing romance doesn't
prove anything.
If your work doesn't improve
you won't graduate.
What's up? Why the long face?
Life sucks.
Here's something to cheer you up.
The last one was hotter.
No. Saengrawi was the hottest.
Do you remember that
accident 2 years ago?
You guys are useless.
Tits this, ass that.
Women are gentle,
beautiful and pure.
Act like gentlemen, women like that.
As if you're such a man.
Mui, how's it going?
Shove over.
What's wrong? Stressed out?
Here, I'll give you a back rub.
The report I have due
is so difficult.
I don't really understand it.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'll write it for you.
Hey, isn't that the guy
who sent flowers to Mui?
Where?
- Over there.
Looks like a monkey.
He doesn't stand a chance.
Right, Mui?
I don't have any change.
Come get it inside.
Does she live alone?
Her husband works in another
province. He's rarely here.
Phan. Help me out. I'm lonely.
Who would've thought
a motorcycle driver like me...
would lay an oyster this rich.
She rapidly ripped off our clothes.
And swallowed me whole like
a sex starved bitch.
Have some sausage.
Your Aunt gave me too much.
Tao, Hia's here.
What the hell! Even your hankie's
a monk's saffron.
Hi, everyone. Food smells good.
Aad came from Lampang
and brought these for you.
Is Tao any use at your
amulet magazine?
She's a hard-working girl.
Don't you worry.
I've got to run, though.
Business calls.
Tao, take Uncle Wang his food
and two packs of water.
Jon, give me a hand so
I can make one trip.
Okay.
Uncle Wang's on the fifth floor,
right?
Who says? He's on the 6th.
So forgetful.
He lives next to that room, Tao.
Oh...that room.
Here's your ice.
What's wrong? Is it your thesis?
I'm sick of work. I can't keep up.
And I still have to deliver food.
I know what you mean.
I feel pressed for time, too.
You? Pressed for time?
Don't make me laugh.
Is the water heavy?
No sweat. When I was a monk
I had it harder.
Uncle Wang. Your food's here.
Tao, come in.
Just put it on the table.
Jon, perfect timing. Tell me what
this Buddhist term means.
The sweltering heat hasn't deterred
the thousands of protestors...
from crowding the streets from
Parliament to the Royal Grounds.
But it means the kids no longer
have a place to fly their kites.
Day Six and Chalard Vorachard's
hunger strike is ongoing.
You sure learnt a thing
or two as a monk.
Talk, schmalk. I'm yawning.
Pay me first. 75 Baht.
Tao, can you see
if there are any vacancies?
Why? You gonna move?
I can't stand the racket from next
door anymore.
They're at it all night.
I can't finish my mantras.
C'mon. I know you like it.
I just want to live in peace.
Fine. I'll check for you.
Do his neighbours drink all night?
You're better off not knowing.
Why?
Who lives there?
I don't know.
What a hottie!
That's your type?
Not bad.
You know a hottie like her?
I've never seen her before.
Her name is Koi. She's my neighbour.
Pong's sister-in-law.
She's still in school.
But I feel sorry for him.
He's been jobless for months.
His wife has to support him.
Not graphic enough.
You're a fool.
This isn't a fairy tale.
You're about to be wed
and you don't have a clue.
That night, I came back to my room.
I heard someone bathing.
If it was my wife
we could get down and dirty.
But then I heard another sound.
Like someone eating spicy food.
I knew then it wasn't my wife
but her sister, Koi.
Suddenly I noticed light flitting
through a small hole.
So I took a peek.
What appeared before my eyes
was Koi's white and voluptuous body.
Koi, who disdains me for being
jobless and classless,
...leading her sister
through hardship.
Her naked curves caused my staff of
fire to rise and burn the door down.
Slave of My Desire
by Tao Dindaeng
You're a genius.
You finished it so quick.
Piece of cake.
I don't know what
I'd do without you.
No sweat.
There's no problem I can't solve.
It's still not there.
You don't get it.
Tell me something.
Have you ever?
Come in.
We're all here.
Let's start the meeting then.
I have something to show you.
Here.
Is this really her?
Of course.
Straight from acting to porn.
It is her. Wow!
These photos suck.
Who's gonna cast
her in movies now?
You want me to take
photos like this?
I can't afford anything this glossy.
But who can afford the cover price?
Everyone, I guess.
They're all sold out.
I had to fight for the last issue.
Now, take a look at these.
We're in dire straights gentlemen.
The new cop won't take a bribe.
Crummy mags like these are
flooding our market.
Nevertheless,
we must maintain our standards...
...and not stoop to their level.
And yet,
we can't afford to spend more.
We must find a new way to sate
our readers' desires.
We've got to spice things up
with some new columns.
Any suggestions?
How about a gay experience column?
I can write that, Hia.
I can't stomach it.
Let's stick to normal human
behaviour. Any other ideas?
Why don't we sell these?
I shaped it myself.
What the hell is it?
It's called The Void, sir.
Seems risky.
Let's concentrate on our
columns first? Anyone else?
How about publishing amateur nudes.
Here are some samples.
We've got a big following
among housewives.
Let them strut their stuff.
Not too shabby. Good idea.
It provides release for
both genders...
and fits perfectly with
our magazines concept.
Are we going to cut Dr. Porn's
Sex Advice Column?
No way. It stays, no matter what.
It serves a social role.
Don't forget our magazine maintains
the fabric of Thai society.
Don't follow fads blindly
and forget our roots.
Now get back to work and remember.
Sayew serves Thai people's pleasure.
For Thai people's pleasure.
Now you see the problems we face.
You have one more chance.
But if you fail, that's it.
I'm telling you, this tape's
shit hot. A sexpert like me was amazed.
As for neophytes,
this will blow their mind.
There was the wheelbarrow
and arching doe.
Dr. Porn's Sex Advice.
Dr. Porn. I'm a big fan
of your column.
That's why I need your advice.
I've got a big crush on this girl.
Her name is Toy.
I'm serious about her,
but I'm afraid of rejection.
I'm very shy.
My question is this. Is there
a drug I can use to arouse her?
How much will it cost?
If we had sex, then
I'm sure she'd be mine.
Can you solve my problem?
Problems I can solve,
but rape I won't condone.
Drugs won't make her love you.
The best thing is to woo her.
Women love gentlemen.
My measurements are 40-23-38.
I'm 172 cm. tall...
...and weigh 46 kg.
I'm also fair-skinned.
I'm comfortable with my body.
Everyone stares as I walk by,
which is proof of my beauty.
What should I do to become
a nude model?
Your measurements are stupendous.
I'm only a 37.
Send me shots that flaunt
your face and figure.
A swimsuit shot would be great
as the editor is keen on you.
You'll be the next cover girl.
Dear Dr. Porn.
Can a girl get pregnant if she has
sex 1 to 7 days after her period?
And if she was on the rag?
What then?
What if I wore a condom?
Is there a risk then?
Please tell me all the risks.
Sex during her period isn't risky
but might be bad for the girl.
And if the condom didn't
break, your risk is low.
But are you sure you slipped
it on right?
Dear Dr. Porn.
I'm a single woman. My problem is...
One of my co-workers keeps
flirting with me.
He's very sweet.
love love love love love love love
He says he loves me even
though he's married.
Late at night, when we're alone,
he tries to feel me up.
Sometimes I get aroused.
I'm afraid I'll give in one day.
I never wanted to be a mistress.
What should I do?
Girls never win by messing
with married men.
And these men are horny bastards,
unsatisfied with one woman.
I'd steer clear of trouble.
There are so many other men
out there for you.
Dear Dr. Porn. I'm in love with
a certain woman.
But I'm only a salesman so
I don't dare approach her.
Right now,
my heart's about to burst.
She gives sex advice.
Her initials are P.
I've followed her column
from the start.
As time passes, my passion grows.
Judging from her writing,
she must be sexy.
I'd like to be with her.
Do you think I stand a chance,
sexy Doctor?
I'll patiently await your answer.
Love, Anonymous.
Dear Anonymous.
Your sexing...oops,
vexing problem.
Uncle Porn. Do you ever get lonely?
Where would I find the time
with all my work?
Have you ever had writer's block?
Having trouble writing, are we?
Our job is to fuel
people's fantasies.
But sometimes...
We must fantasize ourselves.
- Doctor's licence revoked...
by Medical Board.
- Like my sexy doctor persona.
Must we have experienced
what we fantasize about?
Be patient.
Experience takes time
and shouldn't be rushed.
Tell me, have you ever read
our magazine?
Give it a read. How can you write
without understanding...
...who it's for and what it's about?
And remember,
we create ready-made experiences.
Ready-made experiences?
That's right.
All types of pornography
are ready-made experiences.
Masturbation.
I'd like one ticket.
25 Baht.
Let's get a room.
Okay.
What the heck!
What a rip-off! No tits and ass
and the scenes were swapped.
Who cares? No one's here to
watch the film.
Just my luck.
Sticky floors and no tits.
Come to watch a porno, have we?
What? No! I came to buy noodles but
the store was closed.
I'm only teasing.
Where're you headed?
Home. What's it to you?
Hia told me that we live close by.
Let me be your ride.
I'm fine. I have feet.
I guess you're scared to straddle
my bike!
You wish. I just don't need a ride.
Fine, have it your way.
I don't like to force people.
Hold on. I've changed my mind.
I'm too lazy to wait for the bus.
I knew you'd give in. Hop on.
C'mon, just straddle it.
You drive like a maniac!
This is nothing! Grip me tight.
Can't you drive any slower?
Life in the slow lane
just ain't fun. You only live once.
You might as well push the limits.
Stop. You'll miss the turn.
What do you think you're doing?
Try that again and I'll sock you one.
Such soft breasts.
Let go. I said let go.
Can't you hear me?
You take life too seriously.
Go out and enjoy yourself.
Or time may find your heart cold.
Beware your cold heart, vampire.
Toodle-loo!
Wise ass!
Protests against the military
dictator are heating up...
with thousands more people
descending on the capital.
Tao, give the manager my old key.
Is your new room quieter?
Much better. I can pray in peace.
Around 1pm, a gunfight
broke out between police...
...and a gang robbing a gold shop.
And they can scream to
their heart's content.
The police, led by Black Hand,
shot dead three thieves.
Once again, Black Hand lays down
the law with his gun.
Murder, schmurder!
Switch over to the soaps.
Why? It's the news.
But there's never any good news.
One bullet is all it takes!
That's my hero.
Hey!
Are you mental?
That shirt's perfectly good.
I hear it's all the rage.
I see. You wanna be
kool and the gang, huh?
Are you trying to impress a chick?
Chicks don't dig dudes like you.
I guess you're right.
You're such a wimp.
One word and you cave in.
But you're right. No one digs me.
You're so lame.
Treat it as a challenge.
If you need tips to hook a girl,
just ask me.
To get a girl,
you've gotta give it your all.
This hasn't improved.
You ignored my comments.
You need to understand
how romances use language...
...to manipulate
the reader's fantasies.
Are you listening?
Stick to your thesis...
...the relationship between
Thai literature and Thai life.
If not, you won't pass
your thesis defence.
The professor stroked my ripped
and ready body.
She breathed in my ear:
"For this, I'll grant you an A".
She peeled off
her nightingale wings...
...and lay down on the table
allowing me to examine her.
If you perform OT
like this every night,
...you'll definitely get your bonus.
Aside from pork buns,
...her hot buns were included
with the combo meal.
She cleaned my entire body
from head to toe.
She slapped cuffs on me and
handed me a hot sex ticket.
She provided hot
after sales service straight...
...to bed without
charging sales tax.
Her cooking was spicy
but her sex was even spicier.
What a loser! The original version
was much better.
You hate every version
but watch them every night.
Aren't you sick of the plot?
Who cares?
When you're beat and broke,
anything's better than reality.
This guy is all talk, no action.
Why doesn't he just rape her
and get it over with?
Are you endorsing immoral behaviour?
Of course not.
We just shouldn't be inhibited.
We should go out and
get what we want.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Seems risky.
There's a live show in there.
We'd be idiots to pass it up.
Or are you chicken?
It's not that.
I'll go myself then.
Why don't I climb first?
This room looks empty.
It's not. They only come at night.
There's nothing here.
Look!
Ssh! Quiet, Tao.
A whole handful.
What's this?
It vibrates.
I see. A foot massager.
It feels good. Give it a try.
I'll pass.
Where should we hide?
I'm cramped.
Give me some room.
I can't. I'm against the wall.
I'm bored. Where are they?
It's 1 a.m. They're not coming.
Let's leave, Tao.
Tao, they're here.
You make me so hot.
It's Black Hand.
Honey.
Like what you see?
You can sniff me now. I'm all bare.
Catch me if you can. Hurry.
Catch me.
I've got you now.
Good boy.
You can run but you can't hide.
Come and get it.
It just won't wake up.
Don't get upset.
Let's try something else.
Turn over. Here's your favourite toy.
It's no use. Nothing can help.
It's okay. Hush now.
We've tried everything.
All because of the bomb
in that damned war.
I've got nothing left.
Be still, love.
I'm the Black Hand. A hero.
Where will I put my face?
My wife left me. I'm not a man.
But you've still got me. Be still.
We can just hold each other.
Premature Ejaculation.
Hello. Who's this?
Tao, is that you?
What?
The story's not finished?
Which one?
Don't worry, Tao.
Take your time. Gotta go.
No rush. Take your time. Bye.
The position of the Prime Minister
to defend Buddhism from its enemies.
By assembling data on
trends in Thai fiction,
I found that 86% of romances
crossed class boundaries.
50% of the time, the man is wealthy
and the woman is poor.
Wikanda.
Wikanda! What is the point
of all this data?
That different authors have
different writing styles?
- What connects all the numbers?
- What is their social role?
Fuck. I'm dogged with bad luck.
I need a monk's blessings.
It'll work out. Remain calm
and you'll see clearly.
What do you know?
My life's a mess right now.
Like how?
My thesis was scuppered.
I might not graduate.
Deal with one thing at a time.
Fix it and move on to the next.
The magazine I write for
might be shut down.
Don't worry. I'm sure it'll survive.
And my hero, Black Hand,
turned out to be a dud.
Nonsense. I think it's great.
Even though his wife left him.
...he still has someone
who loves him.
How romantic.
Damn it! Why are you so upbeat?
Why didn't you stay a monk?
Why'd you enrol in university?
The Science Major gently places
his hand on her thigh...
...and strokes her
to arousal.
She unconsciously spreads
her legs wide.
But she fails to see the steering
wheel turning into a short-time motel.
The Science major, of honest face
but crooked heart,
...tricks innocent Mui into
this dubious situation.
I understand now. Men and women
are opposite poles.
Mui!
How did you find me?
The other day I saw
you in that guy's car.
What were you up to?
Nothing. We bumped into each
other so he invited me to dinner.
After that he dropped me home.
What did you think we did?
I thought...I thought...
Mui lay on the plush bed in
the motel room.
Her clothes in disarray revealed
her soft, full breasts...
increasing my desire to strip her
naked and revel in her taut flesh.
What are you doing? Stop it.
Don't be scared.
This is your first time, right?
I'll make it special.
I'm scared.
Don't be.
Try it once and you'll love it.
You're jealous, aren't you?
What's wrong?
How come it's so soft and slimy?
That wasn't so hot!
Damn, maybe I'm not.
Dyke Gets Dicked
by Young Stallion
And a tomboy like Oh got
her first dose of cock.
Who's the owner?
Not me.
Then who?
He's abroad.
What's this?
Shots of my wife I took for fun.
The Armed Forces Supreme
Command released...
...the National Peace-Keeping
Council's Mandate...
...forbidding citizens from joining
the political protests...
...and disturbing public peace.
Hia's been arrested.
You can't all see him at once.
What's wrong? He's right there.
But this is...
Hia Kung Fu, how are you?
We'll get you out.
Hia's gone into hiding.
Greetings, gentlemen.
I apologize for running off.
But this time the cops
mean business.
At least I've arranged a fall guy.
I've taken a beating with
the last few issues.
Sometimes ideals go against market
forces and even the law.
It pains me to quit publishing
Sayew, even though...
...it's just print on paper.
I know we're all proud of it and
the joy it provides our readers.
Though the magazine is shut down,
I'll return.
May everyone go his or
her separate way for now.
Vaya con dios.
Is this really it?
Every party has its end.
It's time to face reality. Right?
Does everyone have
somewhere to go?
I'm sticking to porn.
Cherry Poppin' needs a writer.
Are you sure?
It's wilder than Animal Planet.
That's a bad idea.
It's challenging and exciting to me.
When will you settle down?
You should plan your future.
Life without plans.
This is my future.
It's your life. Let's split up then.
What should I do?
You should study
so you can graduate.
Your thesis won't write itself.
Haven't you been helping
at Hia's magazine lately?
You need to work harder.
Look at Hia. He started with nothing
and now he's well to do.
Or Jon. He's an orphan
but he's worked hard...
...for his scholarship.
He'll go far.
You should finish school
and lead a normal life.
Get married and teach.
Does it have to be that way?
What if I don't want to be
a teacher?
If you don't become a teacher,
what will you be?
Losing It.
Where are you going?
Dropping off work for Hia.
I thought Sayew was busted?
You heard about that?
Going to see that grease ball?
I'll go with you.
What for?
He seems dangerous.
Danger's good.
It makes life pulsate.
Are you bored?
Just enjoy things as they are.
I'm not like you.
I can't stand being boring like you!
What are you doing here?
Returning the porno.
Come in a sec.
I'd be a rude host if my guests
stayed in the hallway.
Or are you scared?
I'm not scared.
A cup of coffee?
Be back in a jiff. I'm out of cream.
"The Young Girl On Fire"
Innocent Joy hesitantly crossed...
FAMOUS DOCTOR DRUGS
PATIENTS FOR SEX
LOPPED OFF PENIS
MOTEL BROTHEL RAID
FINDS 11 YEAR OLD
Do you take sugar?
Two spoons. Two.
Innocent Joy hesitantly crossed
the point of no return.
He stirs the tasteless sex potion
into her cold orange juice.
She takes a big gulp knowing...
...it will plunge her into a dark
world she's never experienced.
Her vision begins to cloud.
The world becomes fuzzy.
She loses motor control.
Her surroundings begin to spin.
Her head throbs.
Her heavy lids slowly roll down
over her eyes.
She sinks into a deep darkness.
When Joy regains consciousness,
...she finds herself lying
in a strange room.
The walls are a deep red.
The lights are dim.
There's a mirror on the ceiling.
As her eyes adjust, she sees
her reflection in the mirror.
She's wearing an S&M suit.
She's scared to death!
Here's some steaming hot coffee.
Sorry for the wait.
Can I work at Cherry Poppin' too?
I don't think so. Failing to finish
a porno doesn't qualify.
This is the real deal, baby.
Stop.
My life isn't for you. You have
another life waiting for you.
My name is Tao. I'm a country girl
but I moved to Bangkok...
...where I live with my Aunt.
I'm twenty years old.
I'm just an ordinary girl who enjoys
making up stories...
...to spice up all our boring lives.
I've never accepted a mundane life.
...the reality of an uneventful
life as a woman.
Www...
One day, a certain man
made me realize...
...that the mundane holds
a loving warmth.
Jon.
But that realization may
have come too late.
His loving gaze made
my heart beat fast.
I could sense his
true feelings...
...the care he's always
lavished upon me.
Tao, why are you sitting in the dark?
I'm bored. Let's watch the soaps?
Damn. It's over.
In the refreshing rain,
...we enjoyed a long and deep kiss
and swore never to part.
The End
Day Dreams
That night I found my true self.
I wrote a novel and that novel
changed my life.
I became a best-selling
romance novelist.
Hia Kung Fu is back.
After going into hiding, who
would've thought that "The Void",
...would make him rich enough
to return.
He met Pol Sopong,
a talented nude photographer.
They enjoyed a glorious comeback
as NIGHT-TRIP.
Hia expanded into a publishing group
that publishes my books as well.
He maintains the same old ideals.
But he's adapted them to
his readers' changing tastes.
Hey, Tao. I sold the movie rights for
your book, "True Love".
He even has plans to host
a website "motel69.net"...
...to meet his readers' needs.
Sex has become a social norm.
But sexual confusion still remains.
For some, like myself,
it's a passing phase.
But for others,
it's a life-long commitment.
Next month, we're getting married.
And some people still quest for
ever more exciting lives.
As for myself,
I discovered excitement...
...and adventure in everyday life.
But there are still times when I get
bored and dream of running away.
SEXY
SASSY
DARARAI SUPERSPY
Sometimes I forget how lucky I am.
I have a job...
...that I love and which pays me to dream.
And a loving family to boot.
The End
So picture perfect.
Could it all be a dream?