I looked up all the documents from
before you were adopted.
Before you were adopted,
you were reported as an orphan.
I went to the neighborhood and asked around.
Luckily, there was a woman who remembered you.
Thank you very much.
I'll never forget your help.
Hey, you bitch!
Where the hell do you think you're going?
Pay up...
Let go, you bitch!
Why you, bitch!
You're stealing a zipper that's only a dollar?
Is this the way you sew on a zipper?
Of course, this is the way!
How else, bitch?
She's the one I told you about!
Ugh...dumb, fat bitch...huh.
Scratching a person's face like this.
Hello.
This is the man I told you about.
Then...this is...Jin-woo?
Yes.
I wanted to see you because
there's something you should know.
Sit, sit here.
I was hoping to have this time with you some day.
It's a long story...
Today, commentator Bang speaks
about the Kwangjoo incident.
Hello. This is Young-jin Bang
Today, I'd like to talk about
the military that has entered Kwangjoo.
The difficulties the military had
in stabilizing the crisis is well known.
The military under martial law worked hard
to bring it under control.
It is well understood that it was
hard for the military to protect
the innocent majority of Kwangjoo
who are citizens of this country.
Thus the army acted cautiously.
We will not forget their endeavors.
The Martial Law headquarters released
its report on the Kwangjoo riot today.
According to the report,
there were 33 main instigators,
30 who attacked the prisons,
33 looters who also set fires,
174 who left the main party,
10 who spread rumors,
and 74 who participated in demonstrations or riot
"The river is flowing...Underneath
the Third Han Bridge..."
Hey
Did you see the guy who moved
into the second floor?
He looks real elegant
His fingers are white and really long
What good are pretty hands, you fool
Look at Kyung-chul. He easily makes
10 bucks a day.
Ugh...whatever. Who cares if he's a good worker
You crazy bitch!
Then what's great about pretty hands?
What's he gonna use them for
You haven't got a clue...A fool,
that's what you are.
Ki-ok, all you do is curse
Stop it.
It's irritating.
Huh! Am I wrong?
It's not like his thing is pretty.
Who cares about his hands, right?
Ki-ok! You do know something, don't you?
You go, girl!
Ugh...I'm sick of this neighborhood
I've gotta get out of here.
So let's get out together, okay?
They say the discomfort index is high today.
But I can't tell.
Just like I don't know about pleasure,
I don't know about discomfort either.
I'm just used to this space.
I couldn't take such humid weather before.
But once you get used to it,
it feels comfortable.
That's life for me.
The fact that there's nothing for me
to do is also comfortable.
I just have to live.
It's okay to just feel alive every now and then
So many fucking bills.
And no one who cares. Damnit...
You should've told me before if it fell out
You gotta take care of these things right away
I fixed it good now.
When are you going to paint this?
Soon.
Damnit! Get over here!
Oh...at it again, those crazyfools.
Hurry, it's your move
Why are you so slow
What kind of move is that
Who says you're a great player,huh?
Move your 'cha, cha,'...
What do you mean 'cha?' I win if I do this
Give it, give it
The girls at the teahouse in front
they smoke really cool.
How
Look at you..
But where do you hide your ciggies?
My cigarettes?
Wo
Plan on working at a match factory
Let me see.
What the hell...
Damnit! I stepped on shit! Fuck
What's the ring for
You know. It's Detective Im's son's first birthday
He has all the luck
Gets promoted..
You know what
I think I'm gonna get my job back soon
They know I took the fall for them
that I didn't do it.
Just wait a little.
They said they'd call me back
Our troubles are over
We'll live like we used to
I'm confident
Just be patient
We'll get out of this shitty neighborhood...
"Who said love was beautiful..."
"Rather, rather...Put me to sleep with
your empty hands."
I went to a friend's house yesterday
His sister was sleeping
I put my hands under her skirt
Crazy bastard
Who the hell
I'll kill you
You! It was you, right? Stupid bastard
Look! Look! Crazy bastard...Damnit..
Shit
Who put this..
Wait till I get my hands on you..
Fresh cabbages
Fresh cabbages from Kangwon
If I catch the bastard,
I'll stick his head in the can.
What kind of sick pig peeks at that?
Exactly.
Hey, are you talking to us
Mr. Park, I beg you,
change the bathroom door.
Why me
Plus, today's a holiday.
Why'd you come here?
Why don't you go use your own bathroom...
I won't mention names but there's a pric
who's ruining the neighborhood
You can't even take a dump
in our own neighborhood.
When I catch him, I'll fuck his life up good
What? Fuck his life up?
Don't talk like that, Ki-ok
Fuck up his life cause he saw her take a dump
Is that a thing to say
I'm not being mean.
That's how the world is today.
Say the wrong thing and they'll tear you apart
Peeking into the bathroom,
that's a crime! A big one!
I'm...I'm... Young-mi
What was that in the papers a few days back
Immoral behavior?
The thing that they're trying to set an example with?
That's it! Immoral behavior!
Set an example.
What? What? What'd you say
Well, you know...l don't wanna be
to mean living in the same neighborhood.
But there's a bastard who doesn't seem to get it
And if that's the case,
you're part of the problem, too.
Boy, you're so smart, aren't you
I don't get a word you said.
What? Set what
Set an example!
You don't need to get it all.
If you don't want to be dragged of
and tortured then watch out.
It's a scary world right now
Let's go. Peeking into the bathroom...
What? What? Torture?
Man...She's so full of herself...
These mosquitoes are driving me crazy
Why aren't you sleeping? Come here
I'm gonna steam some yams
Don't pee there. Go overthere
"My love who has left me"
"if I could only meet him today..."
"With my tired lips, I can tell you all about it."
Where is everybody
"...I've lived, unaware of the world."
How far are you going to follow me
Wanna go see the circus?
I happen to have two tickets.
No thanks
Can I see your place?
No!
Oh...how about tomorrow night at 8
Okay
"The river is flowing..."
Cut it out
"I'm so...fucking embarrassed."
Hey! What is that
Do we always gotta listen to country
Let's get some culture.
Crazy bastard. Do you even know the title
You making fun of me
It was as popular as Paul Anka, Diana
Do you even know that
"I'm so...fucking embarrassed."
Sure, no matter what you spit out
no bitch here can understand you.
We have nothing to do with English
except for 'thank you.'
What
I'm telling you it's something like Diana
Are you crazy? Hey
Polka Inca, Diamond, whatever
what the hell are you throwing at me
Damnit... Hey! Pick that up! Pick it up
Well...you were laughing at me...That's why..
I'm out of here
Hey! Where are you going
What are the torture camps doing?
Not taking that one...
What did you say? Bitch...
You brat, you out of your mind
We've a big load to send out in two days
Did you even do your job
Kyung-chul.
Yes.
Is this a dance hall
What are you doing
Stop being full of yourself and
undo these stitches, will ya?
I'm sorry. It's just that..
...you're so beautiful.
It was you the last time too, wasn't it?
You always look so lonely
Why doesn't your husband look at you
How do you know that
Overthere
I'm sorry I couldn't make it last time
I had to work overtime.
Do you work in the factory out front
I'm just a low-level worker right now
but one day, I'll have my own store
I have a savings account, too. In a few years,
I'll have enough.
I'm different from the people around here
Some thread here...
What are you doing?
It must've gotten there at work. I had to do a lot today
Do I have any on my back
Yes...
Could you take them off?.
Sure