Tales of Terror
I'm home.
Hello?
I'm back.
Hello? It's daddy.
Yes, I'm late.
Are you studying hard?
Say what?
None of my business?
That's interesting.
You learned that from TV?
Hello? Can you get mom?
Hello?
You're busy?
How come you are...
What are you doing this Late?
What the...
Hello?
Hello...
Yes, I got cut off.
I was going to tell your
Mom about this first, but...
I've got some news.
Guess what!
I might make it back to the head office.
Isn't that great?
It's time to go home
after three lonely years.
Oops, hello?
Why the answering machine?
It doesn't make sense.
Something's wrong with mom and the
kids.
I guess I can't blame them.
They've been left alone without
the man of the house.
The ideal husband and father
suddenly gone for work.
It's been three years.
They could become a little crazy.
Even I've been talking to myself lately.
Everything is going to be just fine now.
I'm going home!
Daddy's going home soon!
We're gonna be happy!
Sorry. I'll be quiet.
He is insane.
The kid next door must be insane.
No music. Not even the TV.
And he complains when I talk at night.
I live quietly here all by myself.
AII alone...
No...
No, I'm not alone.
Where are you?
Where are you tonight?
I'm not alone.
I'm not alone at all.
Mom and the kids are weird somehow.
I'm all right.
I'm not alone.
I am not alone at all.
I'm all right.
Daddy's going home soon.
Just wait.
I'm going home soon.
That kid next door is insane!
It's going to be just fine.
I'll be home soon.
I'm not alone.
I'II be home.
It's gonna be fine.
He's insane!
The kid next door is insane!
I'm fine.
You are insane!
Tales of Terror
It's cold.
Are the fish biting?
No way. Moron.
No, uh...
Not at all.
Raccoon dogs and foxes
that take human form...
...aren't just the stuff
of tales from long ago.
There's always a chance that you'll
run across them, even now in your daily
life.
That was odd...
Might as well call it a day.
What in the name of...
Dancing all night...
Words are just...
Ouch!
Dancing...
Ow!
Look at that!
Fox or raccoon or
whatever, just knock it off!
Is hitting people with
stones all you got, huh?
I'm not afraid at all!
Is this all you got?
Morons!
Maybe it was my singing...
Is this serious?
I apologize. I'm sorry!
Help me, mom!
Tales of Terror
Whether you accept it
or not, it does exist.
What does the visitor that
comes at 2:00 want to tell you?
I think there's a ghost in my room.
What? You're joking.
You were just dreaming.
I wake up the same time
every night sweating.
Well, that's probably...
What?
Puberty.
Oh, Honey.
You're going to be Late for work!
It might be there.
What?
It started last summer, right?
How can you tell?
You suddenly become
quiet at exactly 2:00.
That went on for a week.
Cut it out!
You're scaring me!
Tales of Terror
What did you just say?
Well, I'm quitting the job.
Finally.
Yes, finally. It's gone to the limit.
Haven't you transferred?
Yes, but that didn't
change anything at all.
Everybody is so lazy!
That means I have to cover their work.
But they get paid better than me.
I can't take that anymore.
I understand.
See?
Then, after that?
I don't know that yet.
Getting married?
No way!
How about your boyfriend?
Marriage is another matter.
It's not that I don't like him.
You see, I spent a lot of time thinking
about married Life.
It's not what I really want.
I understand.
You see?
Actually, my boyfriend proposed to me.
Really? Will you say yes?
Well, I don't think so.
I know.
I never thought of marrying him.
But, he was serious about it from the
start.
I see.
He should've told me first.
Would you have dated him if he did?
Maybe not.
You're mean!
Yes, I'm mean.
Do trains run this Late?
I wonder.
Are we out in the country?
It's just some special
occasion, I guess.
She's Late!
We'll run out of snacks
before she gets back.
I'm getting bored.
Are you going home?
No, I'm bored of that too.
I just want to go somewhere.
Sounds good.
Just anywhere.
Forget everything.
And go somewhere!
Again!
How can she Live here?
Have you been waiting?
You're late!
Sorry.
I couldn't find any
drinks around the area.
I hate rural places.
Shut up!
Trains run this Late.
Trains?
Yes, trains.
There are no trains here.
There was one just now.
There's a river on one side.
You walked from the station.
The trains don't come this way.
Changing the subject...
I'm thinking of moving
back to my home town.
I don't Like my job.
I just broke up.
It's bitter.
Maybe I should go back
and just take it easy.
But my father will set me
up for marriage, I'm sure.
I don't Like the custom
of arranged marriages.
It just doesn't feel right.
Are you with me?
Tales of Terror
Tetsuya killed himself.
The Last time I saw
him was six months ago.
What do you mean, ''quitting work?''
I've just had enough.
I'll find some other job.
A part time job at a
coffee shop or whatever.
Anything would be fine.
But I believed in you. I ignored
my parents to be here with you.
You said that we'd marry
once we got settled down.
This is not fair.
I just can't go on.
I'm finished!
Tetsuya!
Why?
What happened to you?
You've never talked Like this before.
Come on, you can do it
for me! I'm begging you.
Hang in there!
Stop it!
Tetsuya!
Tetsuya.
When he walked out, I had no way of
knowing that he had acute depression.
It was only much later that I Learned
that encouraging him made it worse.
''Hang in there'' is the
Last thing to say to someone Like that.
But on that day, I don't know
how many times I said that to him.
Tetsuya?
That's you, isn't it?
Tetsuya, I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
AII those things I said...
Please forgive me!
Tetsuya...
Tetsuya?
Tetsuya!
Tetsuya, stop it!
Stop it. Tetsuya, stop it!
Stop it!
Please, oh God! Stop it!
I was wrong. Forgive me, Tetsuya!
Please!
That's when I knew
he had hanged himself.
Tales of Terror
Are you serious?
Seriously? No way!
That guy is stupid.
I just got to the hospital.
I'm so annoyed with Yamada.
He's been on paid vacation
for two weeks straight.
I'd understand if he was dying, but
why do I have to come get his mother?
She's not even dead yet.
Yeah, Leukemia.
The disease where blood turns white.
No! My boss told me to come here.
He said I'm the closest
to him, so I should go.
What?
To be honest, we drew straws and I lost.
He's so creepy sometimes.
He lives with his Mom,
just the two of them.
It's Like he's saying ''I'm a virgin!''
Right?
His mother should die soon,
so he can be on his own.
Ah, found it.
lne Yamada
Ine Yamada? That's her name?
Cell phone use is prohibited
on hospital premises.
Excuse me.
Wake up!
Mama!
You promised you would
go to Disneyland with me!
You promised to cook for me again!
Mama!
Mom, I'II sing our favorite song.
I am the yolk of the egg!
Excuse me...
Yamada?
Yamada!
Suzuki.
This is from the company.
What is it?
A melon.
I thought it was a bomb.
Mama...
Mama!
No! Mama!
No!
Mama!
What the hell is going on?
Mama! My Mama!
Mama!
Please wake up!
Say something!
Mama!
Take care of him.
Yamada...
Mama!
Please, say something!
Did she just...
Tales of Terror
I'm next!
Let's switch places.
Let's play.
Let's play!
Let's play
What's your name?
Come on! Let's play!
Hey! Wait!
Don't be scared! Let's play together!
Please wait!
You were just watching
from the window, right?
You want to play with us, right?
Let's play!
I'm going out to play.
Wait a minute.
Who are you always playing with?
Akemi Takayama.
Where does she Live?
On the 5th floor of
this building. Room 502.
Really? When did she move here?
See, she's calling me
again so I gotta go.
Nobody is calling you.
What?
See! I didn't come outside, she Left.
Eiko, come here for a second.
Nobody Lives here.
That's not true, because...
Because why?
I always write her
letters saying ''Let's Play''
And then she always comes
to our door to meet me.
This has been empty for two years.
Eiko!
You messed it up.
Let's play!
Tales of Terror
We're here!
That's the end of the trip.
Well, you go ahead and...
It was after a horror video shooting.
Because there weren't enough rooms,
two of us had to stay in a different motel.
I sensed that something
was going to happen.
I don't Like this creaking noise.
Yoko, don't you feel anything?
Nothing.
This is just a regular motel.
Are there any other guests?
Yoko.
Yoko, wake up.
Someone is there.
Wake up!
Yoko!
Open the door!
I'm in pain.
Open it!
I'm in pain...
Don't.
Don't open it!
I'm in pain.
I'm in pain...
Open it.
Tales of Terror
Etsuko, I have a favor to ask of you.
What's wrong?
Can you come to my house?
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Is there...
...a bug flying around?
Come in.
Do you feel anything?
No.
Does your husband ever say so?
He doesn't really care about it.
But...
When I'm home alone...
Don't worry about it too much.
I see.
Okay, thank you.
I know how to get home from here.
Thanks for everything.
See you.
Kaori?
Etsuko?
What did you keep in the garden?
Garden?
What's with it?
You'd better leave the house soon.
Murders occurred in that house.
The corpses were fed to a beast.
Is there a bug flying around?
Tales of Terror
Yaeko! Are you ready yet?
Sorry, I'II be right there.
She said that, but what
if she never comes?
Sorry, I'm Late.
Tsugumi, be a good girl
and take care of the house.
Okay, let's go.
Tsugumi.
Don't open the altar today, Okay?
Hurry up. Let's go!
Wait a minute.
Would you Like some juice?
Okay.
Have we ever played together before?
What's your name?
Stop it! It hurts.
Let me go!
Stop! You're hurting me!
What are you doing?
Let me go!
Where's mommy?
You opened it!
Tales of Terror
This is a story about me
house sitting for my aunt.
I wanted to take care of my Aunt's dog
Chippy, so I decided to take the job.
What?
What is this?
Who's there?
Is anybody there?
Chippy is being a bad doggie.
Who are you?
Was that a dream?
Is this a dream, too?
Who are you?
Was this a dream, too?
This is just a dream!
Stop it!
No!
Was everything a dream?
AII right! It was just a dream!
What is this?
Oh, you were the one licking me.
You scared me!
Tales of Terror
Is this recording?
The red light is on.
It should be recording.
Oh yeah.
My name is Shiro Tobe.
I am in the 8th grade.
This is my house.
This is my mother.
Don't record me!
Introduce yourself, Mom.
Hurry!
I am Shiro's mother, Mitsuko.
Don't get too close or I will look fat!
The band-aid on her forehead
is where she got bit by a bug.
Stop it!
Dad is working overtime
tonight, so Mom is a Little sad.
A Little.
Okay, that's enough.
Get out!
This is a plant.
Here we have a shoe horn.
This is the slipper rack.
The electrical outlet...
What else is interesting?
How about the stairs?
This is my older sister.
Are you taping me?
Can't you see?
I can't believe you!
Oh, it's okay.
I'm still taping you.
Don't be mad.
My feet.
And my big toe.
And my butt.
The Hulk!
This is boring.
Here is my leg hair.
I don't have that much.
How about my nose hair?
My legs Look skinny from this angle.
The Hulk!
This is the foyer.
Mom, someone is at the door!
I'm coming.
I told you not to tape me.
Stop it!
Dad? Did you forget your keys?
No one is here.
Hey!
You're being stupid.
Dad, you failed your mission.
Shot down!
Maybe my timing was off.
Or I should say ''Bahhhh!''
Are you recording right now?
You recorded that?
What? Don't tape me.
Introduce yourself, Dad.
I'm a Little embarrassed.
I am Shiro's father Takao, 44 years old.
Too formal?
You don't have to be serious.
That's a really small camera.
Yep.
Actually, they really love each other.
Mom, someone is at the door!
What?
Someone is here!
Who would come at this time?
You asked someone to
do this, didn't you?
I wouldn't do that...
What's going on?
This is outrageous at this hour
I'II talk to them.
Who's there?
No one is there.
This is strange.
What the heck?
HEY!
What?
Lock it.
Tales of Terror
It has been two weeks since
the strange incidents started.
It's happening again.
At the exact same time.
I'II tape it.
Shiro!
Just Leave it alone.
Okay.
We figured out it always
lasts for ten minutes.
Dad just ignores it now.
But, one night...
What?
What's wrong?
Suddenly, all of these...
What?
What's going on?
Dad!
This is really out of the ordinary.
After a couple of days,
this guy came to our house.
This way, please.
Thank you for coming.
What's the problem?
Is there an intersection nearby?
Um...
Yes, there is, but what does that mean?
Many people died there, right?
And this house...
...could be a passageway for the dead.
Wow, that's scary...
Well, Let’s go inside.
Um...
How Long have all of
you been living here?
A Little over a year.
How can you put up with it?
I did some research, but couldn’t
find any related complaints.
I see.
I thought so.
Are you ok?
I'm fine.
Hey... There are scientists
who research these incidents.
Scientists?
Have you seen a film called
''The Legend Of Hell House''?
No.
What's that about?
Tales of Terror
Yes. It has been 3 months
since the first poltergeist.
There are scientists who
research these incidents.
Scientists?
Have you seen a film called
''The Legend Of Hell House''?
No.
What's that about?
It says that people constantly
generate electromagnetic energy.
Sometimes, that energy
gathers in one place.
This energy can cause
individuals to hallucinate.
This is called the ''Poltergeist
Phenomena''.
Evidence suggests this phenomena
is caused by these energy fields.
These energy fields can
cause people to feel scared.
We decided to depend on the scientists.
We found reactions in this Living
room, but mostly in the foyer.
Yes.
Exactly.
At 10:15 pm, the phenomena began.
Yes.
According to our data,
the nearby power plant...
...increases power
for maintenance checks.
This happens at 10:15.
I see.
So, this is not a poltergeist?
Right. There is no such thing as ghosts.
We will prove this to you.
Now, we are ready.
Let's begin.
They took their time, and got rid
off all the electromagnetic energy.
They were Like exterminators.
They looked so professional.
Yeah.
It's clear now.
There are no problems now.
I don't know what to say..
Thank you so much.
There will be no more poltergeists
in this house from now on.
Like he said, all the
poltergeists were gone.
For just one month.
What's that?
What about the kids?
Are you guys okay?
What's this noise?
It's so loud!
Downstairs!
From that point on, we
stopped Living there.
We couldn’t take it anymore.
That night, we went to
a hotel in our pajamas.
I can't forget those ghosts, even now.
We don't know what happened
to the house after that.
I don't even want to
get close to that house.
That's right.
I haven't gone near that house again.
I don't want to remember.
I wonder what happened to that house.
Does someone Live there now?
Tales of Terror
Even now, I don't know what it was.
I was hiking up the price of land.
Right. No problem.
They're old, they don't
have much time Left.
They are rich for country yokels.
Huh?
Hello?
What the heck?
Out of Service Area
I hate the countryside.
After a while, sleepiness overcame me.
This is not good.
I should stop and take a rest.
When I was thinking about it...
I found myself in a bathtub.
What?
Hi.
I-I'm not a burglar.
It's okay.
By bike? By car?
The car.
What?
If you came by car,
it's there by the field.
The field?
I'm sorry to come in uninvited.
Don't feel bad about it,
it happens occasionally.
Occasionally?
I started to feel sleepy...
However, unconsciously,
I parked my car here...
...went to that house...
...opened the door, went
inside and got in the bathtub.
That's ridiculous.
That doesn't make sense.
This can't happen.
You found it, right?
Your car.
Yes.
Excuse me, Ma'am?
What the heck happened?
You don't Live here, do you?
Right.
Um, my name is Narimoto.
Sometimes this happens to
people from out of town.
Sometimes?
I don't know why, but it only happens
when I take the water out of the tub.
Right before I open the door to wash
the bathtub, they regain consciousness.
People on bikes would appear holding
the handlebars and on their knees.
That's why I asked if
you came by bike or car.
What on earth?
I think it's the fox.
There is a myth that any outsiders trying
to harm this town are cursed by a fox.
That's stupid!
In this day and age, we
can send people to the moon.
Doesn't this ring any bells?
Tales of Terror
Let me ask you again.
At 1 :40 AM, you were going
towards Tokyo on Route 222...
...and a young lady appeared
running towards your car.
Is that correct?
Yes.
I was returning from a business
trip and it was getting Late.
The road was so windy.
I don't think I was going that fast.
And there was a girl?
I was so frightened, I closed my eyes.
When I opened them, she was gone.
And you walked all the way here?
Boss?
Mr. Naito.
I don't think you are lying.
But on the police report...
...I will write that you mistook
a small animal for a person.
That caused you to hit the brake.
Is that Okay?
Mr. Naito?
Is there anything wrong?
Nothing, please write what you said...
Tales of Terror
I married into a very traditional
Japanese family in the countryside.
You seem to be adapting well
to this way of Life.
AII you need now is a child of your own.
Yes.
These beads...
Takashi gave this to me as a gift.
I see.
Takashi did.
The only wish my mother-in-law
has is to see is her grandchild's face.
My husband works at a foreign firm,
and is often away for more than a month.
Then, one night...
I knew my menstruation was near.
Since I moved into this
house, I would dream about fog...
...right before I would menstruate.
What's happening?
Who are you?
You're pregnant!
Pregnant!
No, I'm not.
Give me your unborn child!
There is no child inside me.
The successor of this
family is inside you!
No, it is not.
Give it to me!
Don't play games with me.
How do you know I'm
pregnant, when I don't?
Why do you want my baby?
I assumed it was a
dream, so I was not timid.
If you want to kill
me, go ahead and do it!
Those beads mean nothing!
What's wrong?
What are you doing here?
I heard a Loud voice
coming from this room.
Then it sounded Like someone
was shuffling across pebbles.
What happened here?
You are sweating...
I had a dream.
A creepy looking samurai came
and asked me for my unborn child.
Did you see the samurai's family crest?
Family crest?
Yes, his family crest.
I didn't see a crest on his back.
Etsuko.
Don't ever lose these beads.
Okay.
After 3 months, I became pregnant
and successfully gave birth.
I never told you this but...
What?
This family's first born has
always been a miscarriage.
Takashi is my second child.
So, you too...
Is that samurai our ancestor?
I'm not sure.
This sounds strange but...
...when I gave birth to Takashi,
these beads came out from inside of me.
I gave this to Takashi as an amulet.
This actually protected you.
It was the same crest as...
Tales of Terror
Hello, this is Nakasago.
Please, excuse my previous behavior.
Yes.
Regarding the loan...
Could you reconsider?
Please...
Yes.
Hello, this is Nakasago.
Hello?
Shiori?
Are you all right?
Dad!
What's wrong?
Shiori.
Dad!
What happened to you?
Hey, Shiori!
Dad!
Shiori!