Hello, I'm Pado.
I chose that name 'cause
I want to live like a strong wave.
When I was young, I saw
a young girl with straight hair.
She had beautiful eyes.
My heart beat, and I fell in love.
Don't give me a hard time.
I really liked her.
Haa haa, you're pretty.
What's your name?
It's Bada? Then I'll be Pado.
These days, nobody cares.
The withered soul
of the exhausted rose.
Come into by arms.
Hold out your arms.
I don't have anything
to soothe you.
Get lost. Don't babble on,
just get lost.
Get lost, you stupid fool.
Loving someone isn't a sin.
Tell me now.
Produced by Zzam Entertainment
Kim Han
Cha Soyoung Kim Yerim
Jung Hyunsuk Yoo Min
Lee Yongho Kim Youngmin
Written and directed by Bong Mandae
Beautiful Pado and Bada
Video Room
Bada, I love you
Fuck you. Get lost.
Get lost. Fuck you...
- What's up?
- Hey.
What do you want?
- What are you doing!
- Get lost, fuck you.
- What are you doing tonight?
- Just hanging out.
- Hey!
- What! You surprised me.
You should be studying
for your college exams.
Why do you keep going
to the video rooms?
Hey, where are you going?
We're getting together tonight.
Those guys?
- What's that?
- What do you think?
Good-for-nothings? Hey!
What is that?
Just keep up with your
studies, okay?
Where are you going?
You just get to your studying.
Hey, if you suck well,
I'll give you a tip.
Really?
What's a good suck?
Don't use your three front teeth.
Use your gums and
then take it in deep.
- Oh, is that so?
- Yeah, that's the best.
If I do well, is there more than a tip?
- Of course.
- Is that so?
- But...
- What?
Your dick's not that great.
Hey, what do you mean?
It's been certified.
Really?
Hey, my ass isn't too clean.
Shit, it's been a while.
Fuck, you're a total sex machine.
Shit, yeah.
God, you're awesome.
Hey, still at it?
Give him some extra service
so I can get free meals.
Hurry up and finish it up.
I like you so much.
Really?
Grab me harder.
- Aren't you overdoing it?
- Nope.
- I'd like to see you come.
- Shit, just go on.
Hey, mister.
How much is a second round?
You want a second round?
Well, you know how it is these days.
It's about 15 grand.
Of course, a used one
only costs about 80 bucks.
I like your sense of humor.
It's my area of specialty.
Oh, she's taken.
She's expensive.
Damn, money, money.
I like your style.
Haa haa, you're pretty.
What's your name?
It's Bada? Then I'll be Pado.
Yo yo yo yo, I really liked her.
Tell me now!
Thank you. I'll give it my best.
Bada, I love you!
Haven't seen you in a while.
I hear you've been studying hard.
I think I am.
Rumor has it you're dating
the gas delivery guy.
Here.
I'll get you money whenever I can.
I want news of my mom
as soon as possible.
You're close with the American soldiers.
You interested in working with me?
No.
I found a black dude, too.
You wanted to ride one.
Forget it.
You know the unit out front?
They love our video.
They're going crazy trying
to meet an Oriental chick.
- So why did you come?
- To inhale some bond.
I think I'll get a job.
Come and learn how
to shave at my store.
I don't want to.
Don't act so elegant.
I didn't want to say this,
but you don't have any skills.
And it's not like you have
a good education.
I won't tell your sister,
just think about it.
A customer told me today.
If you fuck American soldiers,
you can learn English and earn dollars.
Should I test this ring?
What is that?
This? It's a ring.
I'm gonna show you the
time of your life tonight.
It's almost time for my
sister to come back.
Yeah?
Hey, look at this. Do you see this?
Wanna do it?
How much did you pay?
This?
You know me, I didn't pay for it.
I bought it with a tip.
I'll turn off the light.
- Now what?
- Hold still.
That hurts.
Mother fucking assholes.
Hey, what the fuck are you doing!
Who do you think you are?
I'm the gas delivery boy.
What are you gonna
achieve by staring at me?
Goddamn.
I paid taxes to have this road paved.
I threw tofu on that road,
got a problem?
You mother fucker.
I'm talking to you.
If you keep up that attitude
you won't last long.
Fucker.
You fucking asshole. Goddamnit!
You want to try that
Hong Kong kiss again?
Hey, when did you start seeing
that fucker behind my back?
Who are you to tell me what to do?
What are you, my mom or dad?
That money you gave me?
Take it back.
I don't need your sympathy.
Are you rich, moron?
Hey!
Go ahead, hit me.
You can't even hit me.
Ooh, you little...
What are you getting worked up for?
Goddamn. Fine, forget it.
What have you ever done for me?
You didn't do shit.
If I was treated that way,
I'd at least give my body.
Now I see the truth.
Is that why you were so nice to me?
Is that what the money was for?
Stupid fool.
Do you really wanna do it with me?
You're a sex man? Yes.
Really? Yes, okay.
Tell me, hair. Hair, hair, hair.
Lots of hair means lots of sex.
No hair means bad luck.
Who says so? You ever do it?
You ever eat one? No hair?
What are you doing?
Bada, I really wanted to do it with you.
You know how I feel, don't you?
I don't care if you're not a virgin.
I won't leave you.
It's my first.
Fuck, yeah right.
There aren't any virgins.
Just look at me.
I'll kill you if you do a messy job.
Is it okay?
Forget it. I'm gonna kill you.
What am I gonna do.
Here, wipe my face.
It's all yours anyway.
Still, wipe it.
There isn't any. It's clean.
- Really?
- Is it sticky?
Isn't it sticky here?
It looks like it would be.
Hey, why do you have
such a big butt?
Hey, I'm a glamour girl.
You call this glamour?
This is glamour?
- Hey, don't hit me.
- Quiet.
Can't I smack you?
- It hurts.
- What hurts?
It hasn't even gone in yet.
It hurts 'cause you're
about to put it in.
It's yours.
Here.
Hey, I could massage you with this.
I could rub this all over your body.
I don't want a massage.
That tickles.
Stop running away.
Hold still.
That tickles.
Hold on, I'll touch you up front.
Don't.
- Why?
- It tickles, stop.
Really, stop. That tickles.
Is it good if it tickles?
No, it tickles.
- It doesn't feel good?
- No, it tickles.
- Oh, it came undone.
- I undid it.
Why?
So I can look at your breasts.
Ow, that hurts.
Hold on.
Quit now.
I'm being gentle.
You're not.
I'll be gentle.
Don't make me hurt.
Okay.
It doesn't look like it'll
hurt, it'll go right in.
- What?
- It hurts.
Just be patient.
Why?
Just a minute.
Lift your arms.
Why do you have your clothes on.
- Come on.
- Why?
- It's cold.
- You're cold?
I'll make you sweat.
Are you embarrassed?
I'll take it off for you.
That tickles.
Where? Down below? Or your tits?
- Here.
- Your nipple?
Does that tickle?
Hold on a sec.
Doesn't it feel good
when you do it together?
Oh, you're sweating. You poor thing.
I like it.
- Hey.
- What?
I can feel it coming. I'm gonna come.
Go ahead.
No, I'm gonna make it last.
- Just do it.
- No, I want it to last.
Let's take a break.
- Come on.
- Doesn't it feel good?
- No.
- Really?
Hurry up and finish it.
Why?
I want to keep it inside.
Fine, suit yourself.
You want it, don't you?
Pado, ow.
What?
My legs are gonna rip apart. Hold on.
Don't hit me.
My legs.
Want me to bite you again?
That tickles.
Don't hit me.
Hey, stop going down there.
You keep pushing me.
I'm going to fall off.
I'm holding you.
Doesn't that feel good?
Now what?
Hold on.
Hey, slow down. Slowly.
Why?
Slow down.
Why did you do that?
Hold on.
You know what?
All those videos are
all a bunch of bull.
You know they just keep
going on and on.
We only did it for about 5 minutes.
Yeah, it's all bull.
And you were so dry.
It wasn't wet.
I thought I was gonna die.
So, you didn't like it?
Of course I did.
Hey, should I check and
see if you're a virgin?
- Forget it.
- Come on.
Am I?
You lied, didn't you?
No.
Yes, you did.
I can't lie.
So, why doesn't it show?
That's possible.
It's okay.
Look at all those movies.
Nobody ever tells a girl
to get lost 'cause
she's not a virgin.
Real men don't say stuff like that.
Only good-for-nothings do.
You're a good-for-nothing.
No, I'm not.
You're the good-for-nothing.
- No, I'm not.
- Yeah, you are.
- Sure you are.
So, are you gonna leave me?
Hey, I'm not your mom.
Don't talk about her.
Okay.
- Hey, I have to go.
- Why?
My boss is gonna throw a fit.
Why is he always on your case?
He's really driving me
crazy these days.
- I'm gonna shower.
- Yeah, go ahead.
Hey, throw that away.
Hey, this is made in the USA.
It smells. Just throw it away.
Hey, where are my socks?
- Socks?
- Yeah.
Aren't you wearing them?
- I can't find them.
- You took them off?
It must be there somewhere.
- I'll be back.
- Okay.
Wow, this is great.
Special forces.
When I was a staff sergeant,
first class men beat me up real bad.
So I lose it once in a while.
You weren't a first class
man, were you?
A pardon is really good
from a national perspective.
What's your relation with her?
Didn't she tell you?
No, I heard about you
for the first time today.
Will you all leave?
Hey, let's eat.
- We don't have any gas.
- Order some.
Hey, I want to get rid
of all this prison dust.
You got a problem?
Just leave, Bada will be home soon.
Now that you mention it,
what is she doing?
Bitch doesn't even show when I'm here.
I'm being treated like dirt.
What's the use of getting out?
It's prison here, too.
Hey! Go order some gas.
I'll do that. Gas...
Water should be water.
Who ordered gas?
Let's go party.
Hey, shithead.
What the...
Don't you remember me? Tofu?
You crazy ass. You followed me here?
Goddamn.
Isn't it a small world?
Meeting you here.
Yeah, I like your eyes.
Come on, let's go.
Hand over 100,000 won.
What?
To pay for gas, humiliation
and cleaning by bike.
Mother fuckers.
Hand it over before let this explode.
Goddamn.
Let's just split it in half.
Goddamn, I don't have
the time or money.
You jack off or whatever.
Just pay for half of the meter.
I'll give you 36,000 won.
Let's wash the car 3 times.
There's a car wash right there.
Let's go on in, come on.
Come on. Oh, yeah.
When mother goes to
gather oysters...
It's me, you know where
we played that doll game?
Be there by 7.
You're dead if you're late.
See you then.
Look, aren't you going
to play a video?
Not this, you know,
men and women making love.
What? Enforcement? Bullshit.
Turn it on before I report
you for letting minors in.
You've gotten so pretty.
You're studying?
- Give it to me.
- The original?
Not yet. I'm not threatening you.
You didn't mind before.
What's your problem?
Give me the tape.
Your mom's really good
with the black dude.
I enjoyed watching the tape.
She made it for a whore
to get to the States.
Son-of-a-bitch.
I know where your mom is.
- She's on an island.
- What island?
An island that gets big
when you touch it.
By the way, you wanna fuck me?
You and me are both kids of a whore.
Let's block off all the holes.
Close them all up.
Cover you asshole, too.
What are you doing?
Come here and see.
Your sister's got a great pussy.
Should I bond off yours, too?
Crazy ass. Get out. Get out of here.
Did you ever see a fist go in?
I just put it in.
See? This went in.
Should I try yours?
You've totally lost it.
Just proves you're a whore's son.
Right, I'm a whore's son
And you're a whore's daughter.
I'll lick yours, too. Come here.
When did you get here?
Don't go about so late.
I got a lot of free meals thanks to you.
I've become a totally
new person. See?
How's your studying?
Get your hands off. Don't touch her.
What's your problem? Don't overdo it.
Do you know how
shocked she was last time?
Didn't you have enough in prison?
Leave her alone.
Go way!
Disappear from our sight.
Fine, I'll go. I'm going.
I'm leaving, bitch!
Goddamn. Have a good life.
Hey, gas!
Hey, you're an awesome rider.
Hey, when I was a staff officer,
I was in the mobile bike unit.
Staff officers don't ride bikes.
Forget that.
Aren't you making any deliveries?
Fuck, I was fired.
What's that?
I can't look like I'm not working.
My boss didn't like
the way my eyes looked.
I didn't have enough
of an education either.
What a strange mother fucker.
What does gas delivery
have to do with that?
Character and education...
Those kind of people ask for more.
Those mother fuckers.
That can't be the reason.
Hello, I'm Pado.
Is the title 'Blackman'?
Yes.
Go ahead.
God doesn't rule the world.
Hoodlums do.
Headbands and crew cuts.
Get this. Fucking get out of here.
Short hair, black ties, black cars.
We should die our hair, too.
Get down.
Stop. You call that a rap?
It's a hoodlum theme song.
You know how to beat box?
No.
Send the next person in.
Is it your job to put
young people down?
You don't like kids with
dyed hair and raised bikes?
Does a judge look at
the world like that?
The world is like this
'cause of people like you
driving around in foreign cars,
you mother fucker!
Asshole. Have you ever
taken the muffler off?
Go away, if you're done
with your business.
Any ramen noodles?
Then leave after you eat.
You got gimchi, too?
Okay.
- Bring some chopsticks.
- Okay.
I'll sleep here today.
Oh, that was good.
I want to succeed.
I want to live in style.
Hey, go ahead then.
Who's stopping you?
Man man man.
That's life. Man man man.
Some have rich parents.
Man man man.
My life sucks. Man man man.
It's trash. Man man man.
Life is a blackhole. Man man man.
Hey, that's good. It's great.
Do you know what
the song's about?
That was a song?
I got an idea.
Do you have a manager?
Are you kidding?
You know that guy we saw last time?
"Thank you for the nice meal, sir."
He owns a barber shop.
He has some customers that
go on stage at night.
Want me to introduce you?
No, that's embarrassing.
Why? It makes good money.
You've got possibilities.
What, you don't like him?
He's a famous rapper.
You ever hear about people
dancing to rap
in an American soldiers' cabaret?
The Yankees like to mambo,
jitterbug and tango.
I guess this won't work.
Who's going to employ him?
He's perfect for fast food deliveries.
You son-of-a-bitch. What did you say?
Hey, you should be patient.
Goddamn. And is this a proper place...
Hey, what's your problem?
Things were going fine.
Goddamn, how embarrassing.
Hey, I had an idea
as an ex-staff officer.
How about making
a video tape of you?
Record you rapping and
then send the tape to people.
- That's a great idea.
- Isn't it?
Right.
But, we don't have a camera.
Don't worry.
Cameras are everywhere downtown.
Hey, are you a fashion designer?
Go back to your shop
and cut some hair.
Your job's done.
And don't tell my sister I'm here.
Okay. By the way,
she said she'll report you.
So be careful.
What did I do?
I only touched her like this.
I heard all about it.
You loosened your belt, too.
And, why do you keep yelling at me?
I heard it from Nami.
Hey, I'm going to leave.
Goddamn, what about the camera?
Where can we get one?
At the grocery.
A disposable?
Yeah.
Go cut some hair.
You're always yelling at me.
A disposable?
How much is a disposable?
How much is it?
Goddamn.
It's me. Can you come out tonight?
Goddamn, are you coming or not?
Hey, who is that with you?
I hear a guy's voice.
Oh, the TV?
Hey, and, you know?
You know that guy at the club?
No, the one that makes videos.
Yeah, Jjangga.
He's got a camera, doesn't he? Yeah.
Can you borrow his camera?
I'll ask him.
Yeah, no, I'll call you back.
Okay.
That tickles.
Did you wash your socks?
Why?
It has a strange odor.
But I like it.
Oh, really.
Your mustache hurts.
Stop it, I know you like it.
You like it? I know you like it.
Your breasts have gotten bigger.
I know you like it. You like it?
Goddamn, that hurts.
I'm gonna do it 'til my legs give.
God, I look like a frog.
Who cares?
Forget how you look. It feels good.
Why are you wearing army boots?
You'll be wearing enough
of them in the army.
They're great for kicking.
Goddamn, why are you spitting on it?
Hey, this isn't American.
Look, K-O-, Korea.
Look, Made in U.S.A.
Where? U.S.A.?
So why does it have Korean writing?
How do I know?
You're gonna succeed.
That'll be good.
Hi.
Bada!
What's your problem?
Hey, talk to me.
That guy in there is my brother.
Really?
So what?
Hey, Bada!
Pado, I think I'll move overseas.
Where?
Texas.
I want to go to Manhattan.
They make dates at 10 at night.
It's not in style there to make
dates at 7 like we do.
That's why I like
Manhattan songs, too.
- You know that song?
- What?
Kiss and Say Goodbye.
Well, I think so.
I have to make a confession.
My mom's a whore.
An international callgirl.
Surprised?
I don't care.
It's no big deal.
One more thing.
He's not my real brother,
but that guy that was with you,
he raped me.
Can you still date me?
Now that you're shocked,
let me tell you one more.
I know where my mom is.
She's in Texas.
Not the U.S. Texas,
the Texas in Korea.
Hey! Why did you like me if
you're gonna leave like that?
You think I dated you for sex?
I used this camera before.
Hey, look at this camera.
It's a really good camera.
Didn't you see during the
Sydney Olympics?
People were filming everywhere.
S-O-N-Y. Sony.
The Japanese know a good thing.
They make good products.
What's the problem?
You're her step-brother.
How could you?
You call yourself a brother?
Get out. Get out now,
you mother fucker!
That was a mistake.
It was fun.
This is a present.
Should we move far away?
Why?
I met your brother today.
- Did he talk about me?
- Yes.
You know what?
What?
Nothing.
Gee. That's okay. Don't tell me.
Secrets should be kept secret.
- You know what?
- What?
I think I'll move far
away with my sister.
I searched for my mom so much.
I saw the tape of her.
She was in a motel room
with a black man.
The face on the screen
was definitely my mom.
What's shocking is that it
was my brother who filmed it.
Hello, I'm Pado.
I chose that name 'cause I
want to live like a strong wave.
I made this for my girlfriend.
I'm quite a rapper for a
high school dropout.
I'll do a rap.
Actually...
I borrowed this camera
from my girlfriend.
Goddamn. The battery's dead.
What's this?
Hey! Jjangga!
What's the problem with you.
Goddamn, mother fucker.
Where did you shoot this?
What are you thinking
about, you son-of-a-bitch?
Where's Bada? Where is she?
Where's Bada? Tell me!
Now!
I think I'll move overseas.