Presented by
TUBE Entertainment
a MIR Film Production
Executive Producer
Seung-Bum KIM
Executive Producers
Sung-Jun MOON
Remember me? Bishop Martin...
Who the hell are you?
I've been wondering that myself too...
What on earth I am
TUBE
After all, everything disappears...
and...
... all that's left are memories
Producer
Keun-Chan YNNG
The only thing in the world that's mine,
I need to find the owner of those memories,
Find a way into his heart,
... and
Iove him...
Written and Directed by
Woon-Hak BNEK
Every 30 minutes!
- It should be more often
- That's enough. Just go
- Kiss!
- You're late. Hurry and go!
You're talking to your husband!
You're talking to someone older!
Now go to work.
What's that?
I'm going!
Good morning!
- Good morning!
- Hey! Be on time
If the new groom says good morning,
it's good.
Did your wife let you sleep?
What do you think?
If you're jealous, people,
just say so.
2nd mike open, sir
Which train is approaching Jamsil Bridge?
2890, sir!
- Reduce speed to below 10km/h!
- Yes, sir!
Tell all trains approaching
there to slow down.
It's under construction.
That bridge isn't in good shape
at all, got that?
All sections, start PPM!
C sector is flooded again, sir!!
Flood Control Team, move out!
Your nose needs flood control, too!
I envy you, new husband
Wow, you must have really exerted
yourself, last night. I envy you!
That's all I got today.
Fuck that. You're killing me.
You think I'm a beggar?
Damn it.
I'll get in shit because of you.
It's better to fucking get
everything worked out now.
Do you want to die?
No.
Then move your hand.
I said I'll pay the money back.
Just tell them to hold on it
for a little longer.
Stupid bitch...
I told you two things I hate most.
Money and being called stupid.
You ever heard of my traditional medicine?
Please eat something!
Okay? Eat!
Oh fuck!
Fuck, fuck, you fuckers!
Whoever, if show his shoulders
I can see his wallet...
his idea...
his life...
And he has very lonely sholders
too much
Trains 6036, 6042,
hold your positions!
- Track 63 ATS standby!
- Standby!
6036 EMR hold. Emergency stop!
Dammit!, subway!
Lets it go!
Oh god! Oh god!
Fuck!
Fuck you, asshole!
You're fucking psycho!
Goddamn it, you fuck! Fuck!
Stop fucking saying
Fuck you hurt
Fuck, what... I... Fuck
Hey, he wants you...
If you need an account of apology,
I'll fax you one
What a nuts!
Sir! You've got to do something
about him, this time.
- you still alive?
- Thanks to you, sir.
You may not realize this because
so many trains have stopped for you
but sometimes, you know,
there's a train that nobody can stop...
Please be careful.
Sounds good to me...
Good, my ass.
Hey, deep shit!
Okay, let me go, you fuck!
If it's what the people want and need
I am ready to run for president.
Did you say "Rhodes Team"?
I've never heard of such a thing.
It's a fanciful conspiracy theory.
I think the Bishop has it, sir.
Get rid of them both.
Don't you need a light?
My bag. That was you, wasn't it?
That wasn't a bag
It's a trash bag.
Your heart's probably the same.
Full of dust and cobwebs.
Don't worry, I'll send it home
just the way it is.
I'm a cop.
- Don't make mistakes like that.
- It wasn't a mistake.
If you ever need a light, tell me.
Police regulations! Look them up!!
Where does it say jump on the tracks
to catch a freakin' suspect?
Where does it say make the suspect
piss in his pants, you lunatic...
Let's talk about yesterday.
I understand you chasing T
outside of your jurisdiction.
I understand that, I do.
But if you didn't get him,
you should haul your ass back here.
Not go break someone's nose.
Do you know who those people are?
They're the special team from
Police Headquarters.
They've gone ballistic
because you made them lose T.
Now, Headquarter has a war
If you got kicked out of there
you should be laying low.
Stop interfering in my work, boy.
Next time we meet,
one of us dies.
- That's a deal!
- Remember
today's promise!!
You're still obsessing about
that nasty bastard?
You have your obsession, too.
Well, drinking was the only thing
I can do better than you.
There are things you should forget.
You're hopeless.
Bravo!!
Nobody gets close to me.
Such a fool...
Life's not that complicated.
APB on T!
This comes from the top.
All available men here
are to work on this.
Catch him and you get promoted.
No,no. A double promotion
By the way
the Mayor's photo up on the subway...
HQ will take care of security
So we just need one man
to follow them for 30 minutes.
Who wants to go?
That's Detective Jay's job...
Anyone but him.
If the people from HQ see him,
they'll chew his ass off.
All right, all right. Forget it.
Go to your positions.
Are you working with mouths?
Move your asses! Now!
Hey Detective Jay!
I can't stand the sight of you.
You'd better really watch it today.
Another screw-up, and that's it.
Aren't you sick of getting crap
from an old fart like me?
Try to be good, okay?
Please have some peace, ok?
You promise, huh?
You know I can't make promises.
Jay! You know it's classified
Orders from the Police Chief
Come on, give me a break
Be rash sometimes
My neck is on the line!
Hey, put more men over there!
People will probably crowd in here.
So keep them under control
Is it clear?
- I have a question, sir!
- What?
What is it?
This is a top security operation.
Don't we get guns, sir?
What guns?
Use the water gun in your crotch
if you need to!
I have a question, sir!
What now?!
Where's our Detective Jay, sir?
What's this?
It goes to Chun Maintenance Yard.
Mr. Park.
We need to cut the power for a while.
I'll shut it all down except for
the front car. Hurry up and fix it!
Okay then, be careful.
Take the subway, not the bus.
It's cooler.[br]It's a love-time.
- you too, right?
- Yeh.
Sangho, I love you.
Me, too, baby.
You can't just say "Me, too."
That's not enough.
Is it so embarrassing to say
that you love me?
That's the best of times.
Give it a year...
He'll probably get tired of it.
Sir!
Train 7 103's driver is on the line.
D3 7 103 pulling out.
T is up to something.
There must be a target.
Crosscheck with the victims
from the last incident again.
Thanks for your trouble
Forget about T,
and just do your job.
150,000 policemen in this country.
Even without you,
someone's bound to catch him.
Can you spare a cigarette?
I don't need a light.
It's an emergency situation
You might as well smoke one
Promises and laws are even more
important in times of emergency.
Hello.
This is Kay.
Are you done?
Well...
Can you hurry it up?
I've got an appointment.
You're not leaving quietly this time.
I wasn't planning to.
Who are you?
Jay and Kay...
Interesting...
Hello?
Hello, hello?
Get off at the next stop!
What would you like to ask
of the Mayor?
I'd like to see cultural events
in subways and better facilities.
Things will improve from now on.
You can count on that.
Oh no, move it! Shit!
There's nothing to do while I'm moving?
This is too cruel.
Yeah, I'm heartless. So why don't
you run off with that Sammy girl?
- Are you sure? I can really go?
- Yeah, go on. Why not?
Fuck this.
Come on, asshole!
Slow down!!
Or we'll all die!!
All die
Sir!! 7 103's brake systems are all
being switched to manual.
Red alert, all tracks on 37!
Attention all trains on 37!!
No. 7 103, reduce speed!! 7 103!
You're risking a collision!
7 103, reduce speed!
7 103, can't you hear me?
Reduce speed! You're in danger of colliding with
the train in front. Reduce speed!
Slow down!
Come in, 7 103! Collision alert!
Reduce your speed!
If you don't stop...
I run this train from now on.
If you try to stop the train
by cutting the main power,
you'll see what 1 ton of explosives can do.
Call the police.
T on APB is here.
Slowly...
Dammit, move slowly...
Fuck slowly
shit, fucking slowly
Oh, fuck!
Check all the positions of trains
ahead of 7 103!
7315,7 427...
- Stay here!
- I'm going...
- I need to get something back from them.
- It's dangerous, stay here!
Then you stay here, too...
I told you it's dangerous.
Yeah, it's dangerous.
That's why I can't let you go alone.
Get the track controller ready.
Kay, are you there listening?
I'll give you exactly 2 minutes
to get here.
After that, a bag will explode
in one of the cars.
If you want everybody alive
you'd better hurry.
Now, you have 1 minute
50 seconds left.
1 minute 40 seconds.
No!
Kay, don't go!
Kay!!
My name sounds nice
when you say it.
Don't worry. I won't die...
Don't go... Kay.
No!!
30 seconds.
20 seconds.
10 seconds.
Your time's up. Kay!!
It's you again, Jay.
Your girlfriend screwed up my plans.
Watch me kill her
just like you killed Mun!
No! Let her go!
I'm the one you want.
The subway's not a bad place
for an ending to each other.
Impressive!
Welcome aboard, novice.
Anytime.
Come and stop me.
I run, and
you stop me!
There's no way to stop it from here?
Remote controls were switched off
from inside of Train 7 103
so they'll work only in places
with external braking systems.
Sir! It's a transmission from 7 103.
Who's in charge over there?
I'm the Central Department Chief
Let's talk with me.
No need to talk. Just listen.
In 30 minutes,summon all the press
and live broadcasters...
And the Ex-Prime Minister, Song ll-Kwon!
Anything getting in my way will not be tolerated.
Do not attempt anything foolish
and keep the deadline.
You have 30 minutes!!
Arrogant prick!
Get the SWAT team ready.
This is the Main Control Center.
This is Detective Jay.
Huh? Jay!
Hey, where Are you now?
The rear control room, sir.
The T situation is serious.
SWAT team is getting ready to move in.
Anyway,
Get as close to him as you can
and tell us what's going on.
You know? Kind of like a reporter...
He got away last time
because of you, right?
Don't screw things up.
Just wait for orders!
Don't you think things will worse?
Don't say that!
Can we make it alive?
I'd say 70:30.
70% we make it?
No, 70% we die.
Ah, shit, man...
Clear Track 37 first.
Can the trains in front
keep their distance?
For 8 more minutes, yes.
All right, ATS station to remote!
Determine possible ATS position
for the train 7 103!
Power team, track team,
all standby until then!
Close tracks in all directions!!
Fuck, fuck.
Asshole
Dammit
You motherfucker. Hey, you
son of a bitch, let me go.
Where're you going? Hey Jay!
Detective Choi
Detec...
Fucker! You
fucking son-of-a-
Fuck. Fuck, shit.
Fuck
Cramp, cramp!!
Right. This sort of tragedy will sell well.
My face will mean death to one old man.
make sure you record every single thing.
Yes, sir!
Don't you dare to be stupid!
You think you'll make it out alive
if you jump out of here?
I'm very sorry, sir...
Time's up.
Are they ready?
Are the old man and the press there?
I asked you if they were there.
They're on their way.
Could you give us more time?
Is that so?
Mr. T! Mr. T!!
What are you doing?
I'm the Mayor!
What do you want?
If you don't want to see any more tragedy,
remember that Song is the only one
who can put a stop to this.
You now have 30 more minutes.
- is The anti-terrorism unit in place?
- Yes, sir!
Tell them to get ready and
alert everyone of the operation