(rhythmic, melancholy melody
plays quietly )
( wind whistling )
( melody builds slowly )
( melody crescendos
and continues )
( melody continues )
( water splashing gently )
MAN:
Ain't got all day.
BOY:
Dad, I can't.
Ain't got all day, boy.
( feet stumbling )
( gasping )
Come on, boy.
Help...!
( gasps )
You can do it.
Come on...
Let me see you
move your arms.
Kick your legs.
You can do it.
( water bubbling )
DAD ( muffled ):
Come on!
You're not trying!
Nobody's gonna make
it easy for you!
It's up to you!
QUOYLE:
I used to imagine
that I'd been given
to the wrong family at birth
and that somewhere
in the world
my real people longed for me.
From where my father stood
my failure to dog-paddle
was only the first
of many failures.
Failure to speak clearly.
Failure to sit up straight.
Failure to make friends
every time we moved
to another dreary upstate town.
In me, my father recognized
a failed life--
his own.
When I got admitted
to the junior college
my father figured
it was a clerical error.
When I dropped out
a year later
he wasn't surprised.
Quoyle!
Job not stimulating
enough for you?
No. I mean, yes.
I mean...
This is the best work
I've ever had.
( machinery clanking )
( bell rings )
QUOYLE:
I stumbled into adulthood
learning to separate
my feelings from my life...
counting on nothing.
( man and woman arguing )
I got used to being invisible.
Until... someone noticed me.
( muffled yelling )
( wipers sound like heartbeat )
I'm sick of this shit!
( loud argument continues
indistinctly )
Where you going, Petal?
Let's go.
Wake up! Go!
( pounding )
( tires squeal )
What's your name?
Quoyle.
Are you all right?
I'm starving, Quoyle.
Aren't you?
I sell burglar alarms.
Really?
That-that must be
interesting work.
I'm an ink setter.
I work for
the Poughkeepsie News.
You haven't touched
your food.
Oh.
( anxious sigh )
So, what do you think?
You want to marry
me, don't you?
Huh?
It's 8:05.
I think I'm gonna fuck you
by 10:00.
What do you think of that?
( passionate breathing )
( breathing slows and echoes )
( echoing slows, dreamlike )
( passionate moaning )
( both gasping )
Oh, my God.
That was the
biggest one yet.
( exhausted sigh )
Yeah... I'm always hungry
after I get laid.
I guess 'cause I... I burn up
so many calories.
You live in a
dump, Quoyle.
( weakly ):
I love you.
( baby voice ):
Oh...
( weakly):
I love you.
( gasping breaths )
( baby voice ):
Nibble, nibble
Little mouse.
What'd the
doctor say?
If I end up with stretch marks,
sue his ass.
Yeah, but, Petal, Petal,
is everything okay?
QUOYLE:
Petal? Petal?
( splashing )
Petal, you're the only
woman I've ever loved.
You're-you're the only one.
Mm-hmm-- how do you make
an Alabama Slamma?
Where are you, sweetheart?
Alabama, that's the point.
Look, look up the recipe.
It's on the fridge
where I keep the Mr. Boston.
If you come home,
I'll make one for you.
( baby whimpers )
Oh, Christ, never mind.
I'll have a vodka.
( baby cries )
Oh, oh, it's okay,
Bunny, honey.
Oh, I know...
( TV playing )
( man yelling outside )
( woman and man laughing )
MAN:
All right, baby.
( Petal laughs )
( announcer speaking Spanish )
( Petal laughing sensually )
( loud thud, crowd cheers )
( laughter echoing,
referee's whistle blows )
( grunts )
Has your friend gone?
( laughing ):
My "friend."
( sighs )
Oh, shit.
( heavy sigh )
Don't do that!
Don't touch me.
( sighing )
Stop doing stuff--
creeping around, cleaning up.
Look...
it's no good.
Find yourself
a girlfriend.
I don't want a girlfriend;
I want you.
Your funeral.
Listen, you going
to be home for dinner?
Don't expect me.
-Bunny's missed you, and...
-Hey, Petal.
Hey, Bunny Rabbit.
Petal's got to run.
BUNNY:
That's so pretty.
( popping tab )
Here. So's that.
Thanks.
Beautiful.
( beads clatter)
Oh, shit!
( Petal sighs )
Sorry.
That's okay.
( machinery clanking )
( beep )
Hi, this message
is for Daniel Smith
confirming your appointment
with Dr. Davis today at noon.
( beeps )
Quoyle?
This is your father.
Lost your home number.
It's time for your mother and l
to put an end to it.
I left instructions
with the undertaker--
Dayton & Sons.
Told them to notify my sister,
Agnis Hamm.
Not much of a life.
Nobody gave me nothing.
Other men would've given up
and turned into bums
but I didn't.
I went without
so you could have advantages.
Not that you done anything
with them.
( beep and click )
What, were they sick
or something?
PETAL:
Oh, come on.
They must've left something.
What's their house worth?
QUOYLE:
No, Petal,
the bank is taking it.
There's nothing left.
There were medical bills,
and funeral costs, and...
It's all gone, honey.
You wanna marry me,
don't you?
I won't have
to go to school?
It's an adventure.
Who goes to school
when they're on an adventure?
Is Daddy coming?
No. Daddy is boring.
Daddy's boring?
Mm-hmm. That's right.
You're a very clever girl.
( TV playing )
There's Frank.
Come on, he's waitin'.
Hey, big guy!
Good-bye.
Hey, hey, hey!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What about my pay?!
( radio blaring )
( tires screeching )
What about my pay?
You owe me for three weeks.
QUOYLE:
Yes, Quoyle.
Q-U-O-Y-L-E.
Quoyle.
She didn't leave me
a message or anything--
a note somewhere?
Only for you to pay me.
What? Uh, yeah, Bunny.
Bunny. Yes, that's,
that's her name.
( fading out ):
She's, uh, six years old.
And Petal. Petal, yes...
( knocking )
Agnis Hamm.
Half-sister
of Guy Quoyle.
I'm your aunt.
This is a really bad time.
So I heard.
I'm here to visit
his ashes.
No, I mean this is
a really, really bad time.
QUOYLE:
She's never done anything
like this.
I mean, she's
walked out before
but she's never,
never taken Bunny.
I don't understand.
The potato chips
won't do you any good.
-Drink your tea.
-Huh?
Tea's a good drink.
Keep you going.
Do you think maybe you could
stick around for awhile?
Sorry, just passing through.
On my way to Newfoundland,
where our people come from.
You ever been there, nephew?
Only I want to say
farewell to Guy first
if you'll tell me
where he is.
Oh. Uh, sorry.
He's the one
on the left.
( phone ringing )
Petal, hello!
Is that you? Hello?
MAN ( over phone ):
Mr. Quoyle?
Oh. Uh, yes, it is.
This is Investigator Danzig
from the New York State Police.
Oh, Jesus, have you found 'em?
-Yes, sir.
-Yeah?
( loud bang )
Ow! Jesus!
Goddamn it!
Hang on a second.
Hello?
-Yes, sir, I'm still here.
-Are you...?
Oh, thank God.
Hello.
Can you hear me?
That's not a problem.
Yeah. Uh, how's Bunny?
You know what
I think she's gonna
be all right.
Oh, Jesus, good.
And, and Petal?
Mr. Quoyle
we'll talk about that
when we get there.
Uh-huh. You're gonna,
you're gonna bring her here?
Yes, sir.
Okay. And you have
the address?
Yes, we do.
Oh, good.
And Petal?
Relax, sir, we'll be
there as soon as we can.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
They're gonna bring Petal;
they're gonna bring Bunny.
They found 'em.
The cop said he's
got something
to tell me about Petal.
I hope she didn't get
in any trouble.
She's got such a temper on her.
There's just no telling
what she...
( motor rumbling )
DANZIG:
The convertible went over
a guardrail in Jersey.
Fortunately, your daughter was
no longer traveling
with Mrs. Quoyle and, uh,
and her male companion.
She was mercifully
killed on impact
I can promise you.
Look, uh, there is
something else.
Seems she sold your daughter
to a black market adoption
outfit for $6,000.
There was even a receipt,
if you can imagine.
That's how we tracked her.
Daddy!
Hi, sweetheart.
BUNNY:
Who's that?
That's your
great-aunt Agnis.
Where's Petal?
Mommy!
Mommy?
Maybe I could stay
just a day or two.
"Your loved one has
not left your heart
"or your thoughts
but is sleeping
peacefully."
She's sleeping?
Yes. Peacefully.
-( groans )
-In heaven.
With the angels.
( sighs )
If I was asleep,
I'd wake up.
Why are you so scared,
Daddy?
( Quoyle weeping )
What do I do?
AGNIS:
It takes a year, nephew--
a full turn ofthe calendar,
to get over losing someone.
That's a true sayin'.
The move'll help. You'll see.
What place on earth could be
better than...
the place your people
came from?
Smell that clean
northern sea?
I'm not a water person.
At least the girl is.
QUOYLE:
I hope we're doing
the right thing, Aunt.
AGNIS:
I thought I'd never
come back here.
But the older you get
there's an ache, a pull...
something you've
got to figure out.
Like you're a piece
in a puzzle.
It takes some time to get used
to the rock 'neath you.
It's a place like no other.
The people who came here
came by accident.
Those that stayed learned
strange things can happen--
omens and restless spirits...
magic.
We Quoyles,
we left it 50 year ago.
Hard times.
( sighs )
We're nearly there.
Quoyle Point.
Named after us. You.
Well, I don't understand.
It's May, there's so much snow.
Up here, forget everything
you thought you knew
about the weather.
I was born in that house.
( seagulls calling )
( waves roaring )
AGNIS:
Empty 44 years--
Look at that roofline.
Straight as a ruler.
( doorknob rattling )
( water dripping )
( gulls calling )
Look.
QUOYLE:
I wonder who that is.
It's your grandfather,
Sian Quoyle.
Died before I was born.
Died young-- 12 year old.
Twelve?
Then he couldn't have been
my grandfather.
You don't know Newfoundlanders.
Who's this?
It's my father and...
and you.
I never did care for that hat.
( coughs )
Oh!
My Lord, the table!
The blessed table!
( chuckles )
There's no way we can live here.
It's all fixable.
We'll get a carpenter.
Oh, well, it might be cheaper
if we just build
a whole new house
on the Riviera.
Only I wasn't born
( rain pouring )
( wind howling )
( rattling and creaking )
( wind whistling )
Daddy?
What?
Why did you wake me up?
I wanted to see
if you were asleep.
( water bubbling and swirling )
( no audio )
( door squeaking open
and closed )
Are these cables so the house
won't blow away?
So far so good.
They say it
rocked in storms like
a big rocking chair.
Made the women sick,
so they lashed it down.
QUOYLE:
They're moaning.
The house is sad.
What?
You should let it loose.
( laughs )
QUOYLE:
I'm here to apply for a job.
Come on in.
Listen here...
Listen here, my son.
I'm going to need
clarification on this.
I got Doris Koontz down as
runner-up in "Cakes and Muffins"
but her entry is listed
as "Strawberry
Rhubarb Cobbler"
which I believe ought
to be under "Pies."
Name's Tert Card--
managing editor, rewrite man,
and snow shoveller.
You'll have to do
without the boss.
Himself, Jack Buggit, has
called in sick, as per usual.
Which is why I am occupying
his office, Billy Pretty
and no bones about it.
Come in.
Name?
Uh, Quoyle.
I just got here yesterday
from New York...
Ah, you're a Quoyle, are you?
Well, I should've
seen that right off.
Sit down.
Prior experience
as a journalist?
Washington Post?
London Times?
Oh, oh, no,
I'm not a journalist.
I'm an ink setter.
( phone rings )
I had that position...
Gammy Bird.
JACK:
Are you in my office, Tert?
No, no, no, Jack.
I'm just conducting a job
interview here at my desk.
Job interview?
Yeah, there's a Mr. Quoyle here.
Says he's
an ink setter.
The fella's a Quoyle, you say?
And no mistake.
Hmm.
Have him
meet me at the dock in, uh
one hour.
That bronchitis of yours
cleared up already?
Much better.
Thanks for your concern.
Okay, Jack.
Quoyle!
Over here.
Step lively.
Uh... hello there, Mr. Buggit.
The man at the...
The name's Jack.
Come on, get in.
I'm not a water person.
All Quoyles
is water people.
Boats is in your blood.
That's why
I'm hiring you.
I need somebody to cover
the shipping news.
You'll get a list
from the harbormaster--
what ships go in
to Killick-Claw...
But, Mr. Buggit,
I-I-I'm an ink setter.
Pay attention, me old son.
I don't need no ink setter,
I need a reporter.
And you'll do
Local car wrecks.
Take the picture,
write the story.
We run a front-page photo
of a car wreck every week
whether or not
we actually have a car wreck.
Now, there's a knack
for taking photos
that make you
feel something.
If there's a dark
patch on the ground
it reads blood whether it's
motor oil or Diet Coke.
And you want
something human, uh
a child's mitten, a purse
a baseball cap
lying in the road.
See, that's what makes it human.
That's what makes
the reader feel.
Jack, I'm, I'm no reporter.
Jesus Sweet Christ.
You think any of them tomcods
knew how to write
when I hired them?
I get a feeling
about people
that's all.
( urinating )
Welcome home, Guy.
QUOYLE:
I can't do it.
I mean, even
if I knew
the first thing about writing,
which I don't, I...
Car crashes--
I can't cover those.
Why not?
You know why not.
We face up to the things
we're afraid of
because we can't go around them.
Car wrecks are
a fact of life
up here.
Come winter, a drive
into town'll be
damn near impossible.
We'll buy
us a boat.
Look, I already told you,
I'm not a water person.
They dragged it here.
What, honey?
The house.
They dragged it here.
You must've had a dream,
sweetheart.
Who told you about that?
A long time ago,
on Gaze Island
the old Quoyles couldn't make
a go of it there
so they lashed the house with
ropes and they dragged it.
Yeah, they
dragged it.
Across the ice,
clear to the mainland.
Right here.
( rope creaking )
( wind whistling )
( driving Celtic drums )
( rumbling and creaking )
( strained groaning )
( drums stop )
( house cables gently moaning )
QUOYLE:
This is from the "News
of Your Neighbors" column.
"The pole on the corner of Main
and West Streets
"has a sign on it that says
"it's illegal to place anything
on that pole.
"We see the postman
has landed in the clink
"for throwing the mail in
Killick-Claw Harbor.
"He said he had too much
to deliver
"and the folks could just take
a dip and help themselves.
Guess it helps
if you can swim."
This is professional stuff.
How am I supposed to write this?
BUNNY:
You can't.
You'll get it wrong.
Here now, miss! Don't you talk
to your father like that!
Course he can do it.
Petal says
Dad never gets anything right.
Yeah, well, it'll work out.
( banging)
( staticky radio
transmission )
Hello.
You must be Quoyle.
B. Beaufield Nutbeem.
I head up the Foreign
News Department.
Steals every story off
that goddamn shortwave.
Which Tert takes the
liberty of rewriting
in his own
mystical tongue.
Only to save you from charges
of plagiarism, Nutbeem.
NUTBEEM:
Ah, Mr. Billy Pretty
an old fish dog
and local landmark.
Edits the
Home News Page--
poems, baby photos,
household tips.
There's your desk, Quoyle.
Is there, um, a computer?
Well, do you see one?
No, I just...
I see everyone else...
Keen powers of observation.
I can see why Jack snatched you
off the job market.
( phone rings )
( chair squeaks )
TERT:
Gammy Bird.
Uh-huh.
Right on to it.
Well, Quoyle, you
lead a charmed life.
Two minutes on the job
and you got
your first car wreck.
FIREMAN:
As far as I can tell,
the site is really fresh
about 10, 15 minutes,
uh, at the most.
You got two victims--
one male, one female.
Not one vital sign between them
so we're gonna wait
till the police come now.
Uh, the rate of speed
we estimate at 65
so there's
nothing unlawful here.
There's not a whole lot
you can do, right
when a moose decides
to get in your way.
BILLY:
That's for sure.
Uh... the driver
most likely
had his chest crushed
before the car hit the water,
so at least that's a mercy.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah. Well, there's that,
and the-- and the moose
you know,
which is a gift really
when you think about it--
out of season
Like that--
a moose that size.
BILLY:
Oh, Lord, yes.
Billy, I suppose
we could split it
four ways, right?
( shutter clicks )
How much could you fit
in the station wagon there?
I'll take
the hind quarter.
I know we're
gonna want to use
some of those recipes from
the "Home Page," you know?
( retching )
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's new, is he?
New fella.
BILLY:
There you go.
It's wrecks like that
that sells papers.
Oh, Jack knows his readers.
Now, mind you, there's more
people down under these waters
than are killed
on the roads.
You'll want to get yourself
a nice little boat before long.
Something that fits
the water.
I just don't want
to think about a boat right...
Wh-Who's that?
Why?
Oh, I... I was just curious.
I've seen her around.
She's very tall.
I... I mean
she... she's got good posture.
She seems very...
her stride
is different.
It was grief that caused her boy
to be not right.
She was carrying him when
her husband was drowned at sea.
Like I was saying,
there's more life
Lost that way.
How's your car wreck coming,
Quoyle?
If I wanted War and Peace
I would have hired
William Bloody Shakespeare.
( sighs )
"The policeman ate breakfast
at the Codcake Diner
before he arrived
at the accident scene"?
Yes?
Your spelling is fine
and I've seen
plenty worse grammar.
But-but finding
the center of your story--
the beating heart of it--
that's what makes
a reporter.
Now, you'll have to start
by making up some headlines.
You know?
Short, punchy,
dramatic headlines.
Now, have a look.
What do you see?
Tell me the headline.
Horizon Fills
with Dark Clouds.
Imminent Storm
Threatens Village.
But what if no
storm comes?
Village Spared
from Deadly Storm.
( seagulls calling )
( waves rolling in )
AGNIS:
How was your first day?
What's all this?
Nephew, we can't fix up
the house proper
on a journalist's wages,
so I've un-retired.
From what?
Boat upholstery.
All us Quoyles have
a feeling for boats.
QUOYLE:
Who-who's this?
That's Dennis Buggit,
master carpenter.
Ah, only till I gets
me lobster license.
I'm a fisherman
in me soul.
QUOYLE:
Buggit, huh?
You-you wouldn't
be related
to my boss
down at the Gammy Bird?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, yeah.
My dad.
Tomorrow I'll run two-by-fours
under your second story.
Oh, and, uh, I was you
I wouldn't sleep in
your upstairs tonight
unless you want to wake up
downstairs with a thud.
( chuckling ):
Yeah.
Yes, boy.
( wind rushing )
( snoring )
( snoring continues )
( screams )
What? What?
What is it? What is it?
A ghost.
The window.
A skinny ghost,
and a white dog.
I-I didn't dream it.
Don't say I did.
I won't, I won't,
sweetheart, okay.
There's a ghost there...
Okay, okay, shh, okay.
Okay, shh...
Okay...
( whispers ):
Okay. Shh.
( children shouting
indistinctly )
Oh, excuse me?
This is our first day
at school.
-I don't like these kids.
-Bunny.
-Um, she's in the after-school--
-They're boring!
Boring, boring, boring!
Bunny, that's enough.
I'm sorry. She's-she's not
usually like this.
Not usually
Like what?
I hate going to new places
where I don't know anybody.
I don't know anybody.
( giggles )
What's wrong with him?
Bunny, that is...
There is nothing wrong
with him, all right?
This is Herry.
When he was being born
he didn't get enough air
to breathe
and that makes him a little
slower than most people.
What's your name?
Bunny.
A bunny rabbit.
That's what
my mother calls me.
Is Mommy at
work now?
No, she's asleep
with the angels.
I am a bunny rabbit.
Oh, you certainly are.
( Bunny laughs )
Boing, boing, boing, boing...
Whi-Which of those women
are in charge here?
Neither of them.
They're just moms.
Oh, 'cause somebody
really ought to be paying
more attention to them.
I mean, look at that.
There's scissors
on the ground.
I mean,
somebody really ought
to be supervising them,
don't you think?
Yeah.
Better get back to work.
Supervising and all.
I'm Wavey Prowse.
I run the place.
They are having
entirely too much fun
aren't they?
It's a constant problem
around here.
( children laughing
and shouting )
Headline:
Bumbling Dad
Humiliated at Day Care.
NUTBEEM:
Quoyle!
C'mon over, Quoyle!
COOK:
Order's up now.
Come and get it.
WAITRESS:
Aye, sir.
Hey.
Hmm.
You've been to
the harbormaster's.
Yeah, boats in,
boats out.
Not exactly the
stuff of legends.
Sometimes there's a
story behind the story.
WAITRESS:
What can I do you for then?
Oh, um, I'll have, uh,
what-whatever they're having.
What are you having?
Squid burger.
It's good.
All right, then.
You want some fries with that?
Okay.
All right, then, be back.
Have you got yourself
a boat yet, Quoyle?
-No.
-You ought to get Alvin Yark
to build you one.
Or you could buy
Nutbeem's.
I built a Chinese junk.
Sailed it up from Brazil.
Unfortunately, I missed
Manhattan by a mile or two
and got stranded here when I
shipwrecked by Gaze Island.
I've almost finished
my repairs.
I'll be sailing
away soon.
She's ugly, and...
the only thing
I've ever loved.
( mock weeping )
Eh, your story tugs
at me bladder.
Excuse me.
Um, what is it
between those two?
First thing:
you'll have to understand
about the curse.
Jack Buggit's father,
his grandfather
his great-grandfather
all died at sea.
Second thing:
Jack is... sensitive.
Especially about the sea.
"Sensitive."
It's what they call
people around here
who, um, "know" things.
So, Dennis is
forbidden the sea.
But being free
Newfie and 21, he goes, anyway.
What? And that's enough...?
Death storm.
A massive wave cracks
her steel hull amidships
a one-inch crack
from starboard to port.
Men go in the water.
Dennis is lost.
After about a week
they come to Jack and tell him
the search is to be called off.
Jack stands like a stone.
Then he turns-- quick,
the way he does-- and says...
"He's alive...
and I know where."
So, off he goes, out to sea
on his own, in just a skiff
and finds Dennis.
Can you imagine
the odds?
Finds him.
Both arms broken,
99% dead.
The boy comes to.
And Jack says to him,
"If you ever step foot
in a boat again,
I'll drown you myself."
And do you know
what Dennis said?
( whispers ):
Say it fast.
He said...
"All fishing licenses
are spoken for.
I'd appreciate it
if you gave me yours."
Jack looked in his eyes
and they never spoke again.
JACK:
Quoyle... you got
the "Shipping News"
written up yet?
Oh, yes.
( clears throat )
There's nothing here.
Boats in, boats out.
What else is there?
If I knew, I'd write it myself.
I took a chance on you, Quoyle.
Don't let me down.
( door closes )
( man shouting indistinctly )
MAN:
Go get the aspirin now!
Oh, shut up!
I had as much to drink
Last night as you did!
Excuse me.
Do I know you?
I'm a... I-I work
for the local paper.
I do the-the
"Shipping News."
I was just...
Is this your boat?
That's a boat.
This is a Botterjacht.
She was built for Hitler.
He was the original owner.
Really?
I-I just wanted to ask you
a-a couple of questions.
The finest Botterjacht
ever built in Holland.
Tell him what happened
in Hurricane Bob.
And she's incredibly heavy.
40 tons of solid oak.
Tell him!
She broke free of her moorings
and pounded six boats--
expensive ones-- to rubble.
Wham!
Now tell him who let
our insurance lapse.
Wham!
Oh, it took six
very expensive lawyers
to weasel us out of it.
Jesus! An inch
from bankruptcy.
Moral of the story?
When you marry a tour guide
confine his authority
to mixing the drinks.
Did I come at a bad time?
Yeah. Ten years ago
would've been better.
( windshield wipers
squeaking dully )
Wife Fires Artillery
on Hitler's Boat.
Hello.
Hi.
You guys need a ride?
Thanks, but, uh,
Herry likes to walk.
Oh. Well, it's a nice day
for a walk.
Mr. Quoyle...
About the other day?
I'm sorry we got off
on the wrong foot.
No, that's, that's all right.
I-I was way off base.
I-I admire anybody
that works with kids.
That's the hardest job
in the world, you know?
I'm-I'm a journalist, myself.
Really?
Have you seen
our local paper?
Strictly fish wrap.
( wipers squeaking louder)
What?
I'm the new reporter there.
Oy... uh... oh...
no, I'm-I'm sure...
that'll be, uh...
( sniffs )
Good luck to you.
Oh, thank you
very much.
It was nice
to see you again.
Nice to see you.
Bye, Herry.
Bye.
Dennis?
( pounding )
Bunny.
W-What are you doing?
She's boring.
Boring.
How was Bunny
when you picked her up
from day care?
All right.
A little snotty.
What's that?
Robert Burns.
Someone gave that to you.
Someone
that you're missing.
Six year ago today.
Leukemia.
We weren't married
but that's a
technicality.
( keys clacking loudly )
( shortwave playing
indistinctly )
That your boat?
Yeah,
I just bought her.
One question remains: why?
Well, she's
a speedboat.
JACK:
It's a shit boat.
Wallowing, cockeyed bastard.
It'll sink in a bathtub.
Makes you cry
to look at her.
Just a coffin, boy.
Let me know when
you're serious.
I'll take you
down to see
Alvin Yark.
He'll make you up a
sweet little Rodney.
You don't have the sense
God gave a doughnut, do you?
I'm going home.
The best you can
do is bury it
some dark night.
What in hell
a name's this?
"Hitler's Barge."
Uh, that's, uh,
a vessel in port.
It goes with
the "Shipping News."
So, what about
the motorcycle accident?
Oh, I'm still working on that
but I think
this is a better story.
What do you mean?
You didn't do
the one
that Jack wanted you to do?
You did one
that he don't know you did?
Well, this is worse
than your boat.
Jack even
sniffs this
he'll cut you up
for lobster bait.
I think I'll run it.
...and he crawled off the grass
onto a branch
and he made a cocoon,
which is like a house
except it's for
a caterpillar...
Hey, Bunny.
Shh.
I'm reading.
He thinks I know how.
( kids laughing )
( grunts )
Oh, oh... no, no...
( yelling )
( kids laughing and screaming )
( groaning )
Go on, get the pig.
( yelling )
( kids laughing )
See you tomorrow.
Oh, bye, Sarah.
Bye, Patrick.
PATRICK:
Bye.
Hey, can you hold these rods
together for me?
You have to hold them flush
against each other.
Okay.
Thanks.
Be careful, honey.
I want to see
if it can fly.
Well, not in the
house, sweetheart.
Throw it up in the air,
high as you can
Okay.
and count
till it comes down.
( imitating engine noise )
One, two, three, four, five.
Hey. Have you been
to flight school?
Not really.
No? Oh, my.
( Bunny imitating engine )
QUOYLE:
Aunt?
Hey, guess what?
Just keep it down.
This is my assistant,
Mavis Bangs.
-Oh, hello.
-How are you?
Did you read my article
on the Hitler boat?
( scoffing )
What?
Silver and Bennett Melville
were clients of mine.
They pulled anchor last night
without paying a penny
for all the work
we did for them.
The buggers.
Now, you find out
where they're to
we'll give you the Pulitzer.
What, you make juju beads
out of lobster feelers?
Oh, that's pretty
remarkable, missus.
Now, where do
you export these?
Haiti?
Oh, well...
um, I'll tell you what.
I'll-I'll, uh,
do my best.
I'll try to get you
a bit of ink
in the next edition,
how's that?
Well, you know,
these things
take some time to work out,
you know?
Card?
Hold on.
( grunts )
If you're going to Shanghai me
office, Tert
you best conceal
the evidence.
Oh, no, Jack...
Nah.
This, uh, Hitler boat...
you assign it?
Nope, sir.
It wasn't my idea.
Get me Quoyle.
Quoyle... he wants you.
Mr. Buggit, it was what you said
to me in the...
Have a seat.
I got four phone calls
Last night
about the Hitler boat--
four.
People enjoyed it.
Mrs. Buggit liked it.
Of course,
you don't know
nothing about boats,
but that's entertaining, too.
So, listen here, me old son,
I'm giving you a weekly column.
A story about a different boat
every week.
Human stuff.
Who owned the boat,
who lived and died on her
who drowned
who was saved,
who lost his fortune
who had
his heart broke.
You follow?
Tert!
Jack?
Order this boy
a new computer.
And buy him a real one,
not one of them Japan clones.
You got that?
Uh-huh.
Oh, Mr. Buggit
I-I-I don't know what to say.
Did I not tell you?
My name is Jack.
Jack.
IBM, please.
Get back to your
work, Quoyle.
I... B... M.
( stifled snickers )
Lumbering Idiot Stuns Crowd...
for a Change.
WAVEY:
Herry Prowse!
Look how well
your kite is doing.
Are you making it dance
with your thoughts?
Your kite is doing so much
better than Mr. Quoyle's.
( kids laughing )
Do you think
Bunny's strange--
I mean, mentally?
The skinny ghost
with the white dog?
She told you about that?
Maybe she's sensitive.
The way some folks are
around here.
And what about
the necklaces?
Do you know how many
of those she makes?
I mean... and I found her
bashing her baby doll's
brains out with a hammer.
A baby doll
doesn't have brains.
It's a toy.
Do you know she's...
saving a room for her mother?
Did she tell you that?
( softly ):
Yeah.
Is she strange, that's all?
Is she okay?
If-if you had to take a guess.
That little girl's
the only friend my son ever had.
So she's strange, you bet.
BUNNY:
It crashed!
( kids laughing )
All right.
There you go.
( seagulls calling )
( labored breathing )
Do you know
how he died?
My husband?
It was a calm night
when Herold took the boat out.
There was no sign
of any storm.
Storms can be sudden
around here.
He wasn't the only one
whose boat went down.
It was four years ago...
and it's yesterday.
HERRY:
Look how high
we're up.
BUNNY:
Uh-huh.
Beat you to
the car.
( kids laughing )
Did I blow it
or can you still
be my friend?
Your friend? Sure.
( Bunny humming )
Is this yours?
( yawning ):
The ghost brought it.
Then he ran away.
The skinny ghost
with the white dog?
Don't say I dreamt it.
( sighs )
BILLY:
Ah, you're getting
the hang of it.
Now, coax her a wee bit
to starboard.
Attaboy. You're a Quoyle--
there's seawater in your veins.
( groaning )
How are things
with your girl?
Oh, Bunny's just still
adjusting, I think.
Oh, I was talking
about Wavey Prowse.
Sorry... sorry!
Whoa!
-Jesus!
-Sorry.
I... Wavey and I
are just friends.
Fine. Don't have
to drown me over it.
This is where
I grew up.
That's my poor old
father there.
And that's where
your house stood.
Before they dragged it
across the ice.
Yes, sir.
Before they was driven away.
Driven away by what?
You never knew?
Ah, well.
It's neither
here nor there, right?
The point is, they made
a new place for theirselves.
No, by what?
Driven away by what?
Oh, that's old stuff, boy.
It's in my blood.
You ought to be
able to tell me.
Well, they come to Gaze Island
centuries ago, they did.
The old Quoyles was rackers.
They were, they were pirates,
sort of like.
You see them cairns?
Fires used to burn in them
to guide the ships at sea,
like lighthouses.
Now, the Quoyles
would move the fires
to fool the ships.
They'd lure them
into the rocks
so the Quoyles could grab
their loot.
Oh, they was a savage lot,
the old Quoyles.
Then they went too far one day,
they... nailed a man to a tree
and they cut
off his nose
to draw the nippers
and the flies
that-that ate him alive.
And that's when the Quoyles was
given their walking papers.
Jesus.
Now, there's still an old Quoyle
down in one of these coves
somewhere.
They say he slept with his wife
after she was dead.
Anything else I should know?
That about covers it.
( buoy bell ringing )
BILLY:
[m] When the knitting pins,
you is abreast [m]
[m] Hold the tiller
to the west... [m]
[m] Behind the pins
you must steer... [m]
[m] Till the old man's shoe...
does appear. [m]
( Celtic drums fade up )
( woman screaming )
( men yelling )
( men shouting indistinctly )
MAN:
Pull, pull!
( shouting angrily )
( drums stop )
( gasps )
AGNIS:
Show me that necklace.
See, if you make
the loops bigger
you don't have
to make so many.
BUNNY:
Okay.
Good morning.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Where's that chair from?
Excuse me?
The chair
that you're sitting in.
Where's it from;
where'd you get it?
It's not from
around here, right?
It's foreign,
it's exotic.
I don't want pirate's loot
in this home.
Billy Pretty told me
all about it.
It's a good thing
somebody finally did.
I don't believe in dwelling
in the past.
No? Then what
are we doing here?
Making a future.
Well, well, well
if it ain't the second coming
of the Quoyles.
Taking a long
and hearty meal break
I can't help but noticing.
Hope you've got a good idea
for your next story, Quoyle.
I'd hate for Jack to think
that it was just
beginner's luck.
Let the man digest, Tert.
Mind you,
if I was the esteemed author
of the "Shipping News" column
I'd pick up
the McGonigle oil field story.
Petro-dollars;
a golden flood of jobs.
You write a story
about that
I'll put it right there
on the front page.
Thank you
for stopping by, Tert.
Yeah, thanks, Tert.
Aw, gee...
What was that
all about?
Oh, uh, he owns Mobil Oil.
Ten shares.
WAVEY:
What about your column?
What about it?
You said you'd
read it to me.
Yeah, I will,
once the game is done.
( horn blowing )
"There's a 1904 photo hung
in the Killick-Claw library...
"eight schooners heading out
to the fishing grounds
"their sails are white
and beautiful.
"But nowadays you're just
as likely to see
"a big black shape
of an oil tanker
"Like the ruptured Golden Goose.
"Last week it leaked
14,000 tons of crude
"onto the seabirds, fish
and boats at Cape Despot.
"There will be more
and more tankers.
"They will get old and corroded
and their tanks will split.
"And there will be less fish,
and less fishermen.
"Nobody hangs a picture
of an oil tanker
on their wall, do they?"
What do you think?
I think when Tert Card sees it,
he'll stay up nights
thinking of cheap shots
to pay you back.
I think he won't stop
until you're fired.
I think I haven't been so proud
of a friend...
since I don't know when.
( switch clicks )
( water bubbling )
( door squeaking )
Uh, what do you think?
Pretty impressive, huh?
Like I said, nobody
hangs one of those.
Well... your column's
front page stuff.
Only now it's more
a caption, is all.
"More than 3,000 tankers
proudly ride...
the world's seas."
"Even the biggest
take advantage
of Newfoundland's deep water
ports and refineries."
Spelled it all perfect
so as not to embarrass you.
"Oil and Newfoundland
go together
"like ham and eggs
and like ham and eggs, they'll
nourish us in the coming years."
Even put
your name on it.
"Let's all hang a picture
of an oil tanker on our wall."
Man of your principles...
I understand the only honorable
course is resignation.
( crumples paper)
And if you're off
to see Jack Buggit
you're going
to have to swim.
For I runs the Gammy Bird,
every inch of it--
which he'd have
to do without me.
And if you think he's going
to choose you over fishing
then you're dumber
than a doughnut.
If that's possible.
Jack?
For Christ
sakes, Quoyle
cut your motor!
All right,
what's the emergency?
Can't it wait
till I'm done fishing?
It's about my column.
Card, he printed it
not the way I wrote it.
Well, so?
You disapprove
how Card runs my newspaper
enough to lose your job?
Yes or no?
Yes.
( shortwave radio
playing quietly )
( door opens )
So, this is what
Jack and I think:
we want to run Quoyle's
wrong-headed oil spills story
because controversy sells papers
and papers sells ads.
But the oil tanker picture
stays.
( groans )
( laughter)
You should have seen
Tert's face.
Yeah?
Oh, it was
a beautiful thing.
That's all right,
I've seen it.
( chuckles )
-Oh, it's great.
-Mm-hmm.
Let's see
what the special is.
How do you feel
about ordering to go?
You ever had that
before?
No, what is it?
Seal-flipper pie.
Yeah, it's made
from, like
the knuckle part
of the flipper.
The slimy cartilage part.
Yeah, it's good, though.
I mean, it's
a good choice
if you like
that sort of thing.
I... you know,
I'm really not
all that hungry.
I just wanted, you know,
to come and sit.
I had a big lunch today.
Yeah.
They say you're not
a real Newfoundlander
till you've had a piece
of seal-flipper pie.
That's what they say?
Yeah, that's right.
Mmm, good.
That's surprising.
( laughs ):
I never eat it, myself.
You never eat this?
This is horrible.
Here, I got you some
real food-- look.
( both laughing )
( lilting melody playing )
( engine revs )
( gasps )
( grunting and gasping )
( gasping )
( motor clanks dully )
( yells in pain )
( gasping )
( melancholy music playing )
( music continues )
( buoy bell clangs
in distance )
( motor chugging )
( motor throttles back )
JACK:
Christ.
I knew somebody
was out here.
( groans )
Oh, for Christ's sake.
( shuddering )
He's still burning off
the fever.
Any feeling yet?
Little tingles.
You're lucky.
I'm fine.
I'll be ready to get
right back in that water
in another 20, 30 years.
Do you know how close
you were to dying?
I'll get my uncle, Alvin Yark,
to build you a proper boat
and learn how to use it, okay?
Okay.
Good.
MAVIS:
Were the eyes open or closed?
I don't know.
Just said it was
an disembodied head.
What'd the police have
to say about it?
Still working on it.
A little late to return the head
to its owner, though.
( snorts )
Hello, nephew.
Police bulletin:
"Mrs. Silver Melville
was arrested early today
"in Lanai, Hawaii,
for the murder of her husband
socialite and raconteur
Mr. Bayonet Melville."
'He pushed me once too often,'
Mrs. Melville confessed
'so I finally pushed back."'
Good for you, my dear.
Well, he probably
deserved it.
-Hey.
Don't get your hopes up.
You're the first man
who ever cooked for me.
You got a lot
of leeway.
How are they?
They're both asleep
in Bunny's bed.
Should we trust them?
-( Wavey laughing )
-I can do this.
You just don't think...
Oh, no.
No, I know. Here...
let me do that,
all right?
There you go.
-Can you feel that...
-Yeah.
through your bandage?
What?
Your husband, he never...
he never cooked you a meal?
Why are we talking
about my husband?
Because I understand.
You said "It's four years
ago and it's yesterday."
( heavy sigh )
I understand that.
My husband's not who
we're talking about, right?
I'll go get Herry.
He wouldn't like
waking up in a strange bed.
( dog barks )
( mysterious theme playing )
( wind whistling eerily )
( rattling and creaking )
( mysterious theme continues )
-Hey!
-Huh?!
Who are you?
( barking )
( growling )
( muttering )
I tied magic in these knots
to protect you
from the house.
No good ever come
from the old place.
Never, never... never.
You... you have no...
business in the
Quoyle house.
I get you
out of there.
But I am a Quoyle.
A Quoyle?!
I was a Quoyle
before you was anything.
( clearing throat )
Leave the house.
Tell, uh...
Agnis hello from...
Cousin Nolan.
( muttering )
You know why
Agnis come back?
To show she ain't afraid
of the place no more.
'Cause I know what she's done.
I know.
She got rid of the baby
she was carrying.
What could she do? What?
She was only 12
and it was her own brother
that done it to her.
( girl laughing )
( laughs )
No...
No! No! No!
Please! No!
No! Please!
( shrieks )
( kettle whistles )
Does that belong
to you?
Sorry.
There's still hot water
in the kettle
if you want some tea.
I've started looking for a place
for me and Bunny.
You sure you're going
to be okay at your shop?
I said I would,
didn't I?
I think
Silver Melville was right
to chop her husband's head off.
He probably deserved it.
I think more women
should do what she did.
Maybe some should have done it
to their own brother...
my father.
Cousin Nolan dropped by
last night.
( dishes clatter)
I always thought if anyone
knew, I'd be turned to stone.
Shit!
Here.
Tea's a good drink.
It'll keep you going.
When someone hurts you
that much...
how do you...?
Does it ever go away?
Is it possible?
( sits mug on table )
AGNIS:
Her name was Irene.
The love of my life.
You look happy.
So, yeah, it is possible.
QUOYLE:
Agnis tells me we got to move
for the winter.
It'll be a three-hour drive
from here to the Point.
All the ice...
Me and Bunny,
we're going to have to find
a room in town somewhere.
I'll have the usual,
please, Annie. Thank you.
Well, if it's a place
to stay you need
you can have
my trailer.
Timing's perfect.
What are you talking about?
My boat's ready.
If I stay here
any longer
I might begin
to like the place.
I'm throwing myself
a farewell party on Saturday.
Departure to
follow Sunday.
The rootless traitor.
Regrets soon after,
no doubt.
( boisterous din )
( bottles breaking )
( laughter)
Quoyle of the North!
Quoyle of the North.
Have you and Wavey
done the dirty yet?
( slurred ):
Shh! She's the grieving widow.
Grieving for
Herold Prowse.
Oh, that's a good one.
Let me tell you
something
about old Herold Prowse.
It's like a party game
in town--
to look at babies
and see if they look
like Herold.
Hey...
Hey!
Everyone!
To Nutbeem!
ALL:
We all loves
our fucking Nutbeem, huh?!
( all cheer)
Lets us keep him here then!
Got your chainsaw,
Neddie?
( all cheer)
( chainsaw buzzes )
ALL:
Nutbeem!
Hoh-oh-oh!
( chainsaw buzzing )
( blows echoing )
( woman screaming )
( grunting )
( bird hooting )
( accordion playing
in distance )
( grunts )
( accordion grows louder )
( pounding )
What's wrong?
( slurring ):
I'm a Quoyle.
I'm one of the Quoyles
pirates and looters
and murderers.
My father raped
his little sister
and then he taught me
how to swim.
Stop that.
Jesus, you smell
like a brewery.
Stop it.
Go on, Herry. Go on.
( whimpering )
Stop it!
Herry.
Sorry, Herry.
( sobbing gasps )
( voice breaking ):
I'm sorry, Petal.
I'm so sorry.
( sniffles )
I meant Wavey.
Good. I feel much better.
When were you going to tell me
about your fucked-up marriage?
[m] [m]
I'm scrambling eggs.
Are you going
to be able to eat?
No.
Listen, I'm...
Maybe I should just go.
You forget where
the door is?
( door closes )
( pan clattering )
He ran off to Winnipeg
with some little bitch.
She was barely
out of high school.
Is that fucked up enough
for you?
Herold...
my husband,
he didn't die.
Not that he didn't
deserve to.
He left me when I was
eight months pregnant;
no good to him in bed.
So I took his 15-footer
out into the bay
cracked the hull with
a hatchet and sunk her
and pretended
he was drowned
and played the grieving widow
and packed my bags
to leave town.
But then a funny thing happened.
All these folk I grew up with
they put their hearts
around me and Herry
so we wouldn't be alone.
And I just
couldn't leave.
I'm sorry, Wavey.
You're always sorry.
( crying softly )
( footsteps approaching )
You're looking dishy,
Quoyle.
I'm afraid my offer
to let you stay in my trailer
will have to be retracted.
Sorry about that.
And your boat.
I'm some disgusted
with the human race.
I never would have
made it anyway.
Storms would have
blown me to bits.
You boys saved my life,
I imagine.
I've gathered up my savings,
and I'm flying back to Brazil
where the water is
swimming-pool green.
You and Bunny can stay
with the wife and me.
To Brazil.
Brazil.
NUTBEEM:
QUOYLE:
Brazil.
BUNNY:
We can stay with Aunt Agnis
over at her shop.
Barely enough room
there for myself.
You'll like it at
Dennis' house, sweetie.
No, I won't.
Hi, Quoyle. Hi, Bunny.
Welcome, weary travelers.
Our home's your home.
BUNNY:
-No, it's not.
-Come on in.
QUOYLE:
-Bunny...
-Come on in, sweetie.
I made a big
seal-flipper pie.
BUNNY:
What's that?
BEETY:
Weather light. Storm coming.
DENNIS:
Big one.
( distant thunder rumbling )
( thunder rumbling )
The house... the house...
house...
( gasps )
( panting )
( thunder crashing )
( reading softly )
( thunder rumbling )
[m] [m]
I...
What is it, Quoyle?
What?
( thunder crashes )
( door creaks open )
( closes door )
( thunder crashes )
( thunder rumbling )
[m] [m]
( Celtic drums )
( wind howling )
It's gone.
What?
The green house is gone.
I didn't dream it.
Don't say I did.
( phone ringing )
Yeah?
Oh, hi, Mom.
Some storm, eh?
What?
Oh.
Yes. Yes, of course.
BUNNY:
What's a wake?
QUOYLE:
It's to say good-bye.
BUNNY:
Mr. Buggit is sleeping
with the angels.
MAN 1 :
He was a hard man,
but he was fair.
MAN 2:
Another one
for the Buggit Curse.
QUOYLE:
Dennis...
Yeah, I'm still looking
for my dad's Navy medal.
I found it.
Don't you worry.
It's going to be
all right.
Thank you.
Mom.
What?
( gasps softly):
Good...
I found it...
in his desk at the office.
Would you write something for
the Gammy Bird about Jack?
Yes, I'll try.
BILLY:
Jack is...
Jack is all right now.
You all know...
we are only passing by.
We walk over these stones
a few times.
Our boats...
sail for a little while
on the waves
and then they have to sink.
Jack knew that
better than anyone.
Right, Jack?
( whispering ):
Yes, boy.
( gulps )
( screams )
( others screaming )
( screaming continues )
( screaming )
He's awake!
Jack...
Get a doctor!
Oh, Jack... oh, Jack...
( coughing )
Oh, Jack...
No, no...
JACK:
Come here, son.
I beat the curse.
The fishing license is yours.
( siren chirps )
Sweetheart, you ready?
I want to have a wake for Petal.
Why didn't we have
a wake?
Why didn't we wake her up?
It worked for him.
Honey, Mr. Buggit
wasn't really...
It's more like
he was in a coma.
From the cold water.
It's like he
was sleeping.
-Petal was asleep.
-No, honey...
You said she was asleep
with the angels.
I know. Honey, I know
what I said, honey.
You said! You said!
-I know, but she's not sleeping.
-You said! You said!
-Honey, honey, listen to me.
-You said!
I know what I said.
Listen to me.
I just... I was too scared
to tell you the truth.
Petal is dead.
And you know that.
I know you know it.
It's okay.
Is it because of me?
What?
That she drove away.
Well, why would you
say that?
Because...
because I'm boring.
( crying )
Oh...
No, honey, it's not
because of you.
And you are anything
but boring.
Come here.
You just come here.
Hon...
You believe me, don't you?
You still don't
believe me, do you?
About the house.
I told you so.
It's all right.
Worse things have happened.
To both of us.
Maybe one day we'll build
a summerhouse out here.
Summer...
BUNNY:
Do they have summer here?
AGNIS:
Oh, you'll know it's summer when
the partridge berries are out.
WAVEY:
And we can make
partridge berry duff
and sweet berry okie.
Will you show me how?
I will, yeah.
I will.
QUOYLE:
There are still so many things
I don't know.
If a piece ofknotted string
can unleash the wind
and if a drowned man
can awaken...
then I believe
a broken man can heal.
Headline:
Deadly Storm Takes House.
Leaves... Excellent View.