Over here, Mr. Addison.
-Any sign of Geiger?
-No, sir.
Keep looking.
He's out there. Somewhere.
What the hell?
Jesus!
-Slow down!
-l can't!
We're clear, Geiger.
Stand back.
-Mind over matter, baby.
-Loose cash only. Go!
Right.
-Elias!
-Hands up! Don't move!
-l said hands up!
-So you did.
Elias!
-Adrian, get in!
-We can't leave him here!
There's no time. Adrian, he's dead.
Come on!
Martin Elias. Been a prime suspect
on our watch list since 1977.
-Ancient history, Mr. Addison.
-Well, it was. Until this morning.
Elias was shot robbing
an armored car in Los Angeles.
He's currently in LAPD custody
undergoing surgery.
A division that's been closed down
for more than 20 years.
There's still fallout, sir.
We believe Elias is a part of
a larger group.
Possibly rogue. Headed by this man,
Adrian Geiger.
Also on the list, and probably
the most dangerous.
Look, the 70's are over,
Mr. Addison.
We're a little too busy tracking
down black market nukes to worry...
about all things Roswell,
if you catch my drift.
-Sir. Sir?
-What is it?
lf these people become active...
they can pose a threat
more dangerous.
And we believe this Elias
is a key to finding them.
Weren't you supposed
to retire last year, Ray?
l like to finish
what l start, sir.
Well, maybe it's time
to finish. Period.
He didn't believe you,
did he?
We need someone
to infiltrate them.
Somebody on the inside.
An expert
in this particular field.
Friction. Friction is the enemy
of all motion.
No matter where we move, friction
is pulling us the other way.
We move right, it pulls us left.
Forward, pulls us back. Questions?
-This is a physics class, right?
-Right.
That's why nature gave us friction
to stop things from moving.
Like you.
You call that a lecture?
What's next, illegal street races
to demonstrate acceleration?
-That's not a bad idea.
-l didn't know you were a runner.
No? Maybe you could
run over to my place later.
Teach me more about friction.
l miss you.
People don't stop seeing each
other when it's going so great.
We were great,
you know?
l know.
lt's not you.
Then what is it?
lt's me. l...
l can't...
You can't? What?
Well, l can.
So watch your step.
Hi, Sarah. How are you?
Will that be all, sir?
''Sir'' my ass, bitch!
You think l'm stupid?
-You know that guy!
-Take it all. Whatever you want.
l told you what l want! l want you
to open that fucking ATM machine!
-l can't! lt's not ours!
-Open it, bitch!
Put your hands up!
And put it on the end of this gun!
Put it on there!
l'm gonna give you 3 seconds!
Hey! Look at me!
One!
Two!
Look at me! Look at me when
l blow your fucking head off!
-Three!
-No!
Professor,
did you see that?
l wasn't here.
Professor, where are you going?
We have to call the police!
lt's black.
lt's a flip-phone.
lt's got a little blue trim
around the edge. Check, please?
Now, there's something
you don't see everyday.
Are you guys FBl?
Yeah. Agents Ripps and Mclntyre.
lt says here you lost control of
vehicle right before the robbery.
l didn't lose control of nothing.
l'm the best driver they've got.
They made me write that
for the insurance.
So what happened out here,
Earl?
This is off the record.
First l thought
we hit something.
And then, well, the truck
just started driving itself.
-Driving itself?
-You mean the gas pedal got stuck?
No, l mean, after we stopped,
it started going sideways.
Like...
Frogger.
The arcade game.
We were going sideways
like a crab.
What's with this guy
and shellfish?
A frog's an amphibian.
Damn thing had
a mind of its own.
A truck with a mind of its own.
That's a new one.
Just don't tell my wife.
Bad enough she wants GPS.
You're gonna think l'm nuts.
You drink lime juice for breakfast.
How much worse can it get?
But l actually believe him.
Sounds like sabotage.
They followed the truck, flipped it
somehow, then hit it.
How do you flip
a seven-ton truck?
Beats me.
Homeless guy confirmed the truck
flipped and that Elvis was driving.
ldeal spot. Light traffic.
cuts down on witnesses.
Security camera?
Out of commission.
Agent Ripps?
Real sorry l didn't recognize you
before. Would you mind?
You look different than on TV.
Better, l mean.
Oh, for Christ's Sake...
Any word on our suspect?
You mean Elias? He's at St. Mary's.
Recovery room 320.
Should l call ahead and let them
know you're on your way?
-That would be great.
-Sure. Sure thing.
Jordan.
-You should get your own website.
-Don't start, Frank.
No, seriously. We could post
likes and dislikes...
photos, favorite hiking trails...
Coming up next, details
on the mysterious armored...
car robbery in South Central
Los Angeles this morning.
Police and FBl are still
on the scene at this hour...
and we will bring you
a live update in 30 seconds.
Let me guess.
Spring cleaning?
l heard you missed first class,
so l figured you were probably...
What's going on?
Something's come up
. l'm leaving.
What do you mean?
For good?
You can't be serious.
l mean, what about your classes?
The semester doesn't even end
for another 2 weeks.
Yeah, l talked to the Dean.
Someone's gonna fill in for me.
The kids. You're the main reason
half of them are in the program.
-When were you gonna tell them?
-Before l left.
When were you gonna tell me?
l was gonna call you.
Don't.
Obviously l was just
fooling myself...
thinking that
we were anything.
l'll tell them you say goodbye.
Brooke...
wait.
Wait for what, huh?
For the past year l've been trying
to get you to open up to me...
for you to tell me something.
Anything about yourself.
And you know what? The only thing
l really know is...
that l don't really
know you at all.
Police say no money was taken
in the bold daylight robbery.
The wounded suspect, Martin Elias,
underwent surgery at...
St Mary's Hospital and is said to be
in guarded condition at this hour.
And then she offers me
head right there on the freeway.
She said her husband's gonna kill
her if she gets another ticket.
Well, l guess the jerk wouldn't mind
if she went down on the LAPD.
-Where's Elias?
-They moved him.
They what?
Don't look at us. These 2 Feds
showed up with a warrant.
Said they were transferring
the suspect out.
Doctor said they shouldn't
move him, but they moved him.
-And you just let them take him.
-We had no choice. They were FBl.
From what office?
This office. LA, l mean.
Dipshit,
we're from the LA office.
-Something you don't see everyday.
-What?
-This is bogus.
-l've seen these. lt's legitimate.
See the watermark?
The crest is reversed.
lt's supposed to be signed by the
Regional Bureau chief. Who's that?
Of course you don't. That's why my
6-year-old niece could've signed it.
You would have thought
it was official.
Lighten up, sweetie. The cameras
aren't rolling anymore.
Your 15 minutes of fame
are over.
Well, l've got news for you.
This suspect ends up dead...
your 15 minutes of fame
are just starting.
l'm gonna make sure your face ends
up on TV, magazine, newspaper...
post office and PTA newsletter
in this city.
That light enough for ya?
Sweetie?
-PTA newsletter?
-l was on a roll.
Hold up, kid.
Before you go off all half-cocked,
let's call the bureau...
put out an APB
on our mystery feds.
-You think that's our best move?
-Unless you got a better one.
Well, it seems to me this wasn't
amateur night at the lmprov.
These guys knew what they were
doing. Had a top-shelf forgery.
Meaning?
Maybe we should look one more
time before crossing the street.
Dig up more on this guy Elias. Find
out what's really going on there.
You plan on using a shovel?
Or your customary sledgehammer?
You think l was
too harsh back there?
To act impulsively is heartfelt.
But never head-felt.
You're creeping me out, Frank.
When did you get so soft?
l started Tai Chi.
-Try it. lt takes away the stress.
-l like stress.
Hello, Martin.
Wow, you don't look good.
Addison.
You still breathing, man?
Christ, you must be over
a hundred by now.
-Turn 95 next week.
-l'll bet.
Hey, would you do me the favor
of removing the goggles?
l'd like to see
what a cold war relic looks like.
l'm sorry, l can't do that.
You know what they say.
''What you can't see
can't hurt me.''
l guess you know
why l'm here.
Let me guess.
You decided to stop killing
for the government...
and you've become
a paramedic.
Not quite.
Where is he?
Where is who, man?
They're recruiting again,
aren't they? Where can l find him?
Nowhere, man.
Everywhere.
Just kill me.
Frears.
Meet my new associate,
Agent Frears.
He's a quick learner.
Pleased to meet you, man.
Now, l'm gonna ask you
one more time.
Where can l find Adrian Geiger?
Good evening, Professor.
Running again, are we?
Do l know you?
No, not formally.
But we know you.
My name is Addison.
l'm with the Pentagon.
Specifically, a special division
designed with one thing in mind.
To keep track of people
with your unique abilities.
l don't know who you think l am,
but you got the wrong guy.
That was quite a feat
you performed the other night.
What are you talking about?
People describe it as intense
static electricity...
coursing through your veins.
Your muscles get taut.
The hair all over your body
stands up.
Your vision becomes
tunneled.
An ordinary person is able to move
an object without even touching it.
Sound familiar?
lt's time to stop running. Denying
who you are and what you can do.
What do you want?
We want your help.
For the last 20 years l've been
tracking down a group of criminals...
who possess the same gift as you.
Their leader is Adrian Geiger.
-You'll be tracking him down.
-l'll be tracking down?
l'm a Physics teacher.
l'm not one of your agents.
l know you're not.
But my agents tried
to infiltrate the group...
to check out the scope
of their operation.
They tried and failed,
l take it.
Look, we're not trying to
infiltrate the mob here.
This group only trusts people
who can do what they do.
So, if they ask you to move
something with your mind...
there better not be
any fucking strings attached.
Half of my agents tried,
and they were all murdered.
l don't want to be next.
l can't help you.
l'm sorry.
Do you know
what would happen...
if the world knew what you did
in that store the other night?
ln one hour, it would turn you into
a goddamn global phenomenon.
Your life would never
be the same.
l'm asking you to use your gift
to stop them from abusing theirs.
Nice meeting you.
Frears.
Okay, l'm in.
What do l do?
Go 12 miles on Canyon Lake Road
until it dead-ends.
-That's where it's going down.
-How do l find them?
Our source said that they use
a code word: ''Raze''.
-Then the recruiter finds you.
-And if he doesn't?
Pray he does.
Three-fifty.
l'm looking for someone.
You mustn't be
looking too hard.
-This someone got a name?
-Raze.
l'll ask around.
Come back later.
-Do you come here often?
-Do l what?
-Come here often?
-All the time.
Never would have guessed.
Hawk!
-Can l borrow your cell phone?
-Fuck off, Tristen.
Last time you called
some ex-boyfriend in London.
-Want to help me out?
-Long distance?
Local.
2 minutes. l swear.
-Oh, damn.
-Where are you going?
-Hey, what are you doing?
-There's no signal.
l love this song.
l got this thing for first-timers.
l like to break them in.
Who said it's my first time?
l just have this feeling.
What's going on?
Your wallet and your car keys.
Now.
You're kidding, right?
-Better do what l say.
-Great.
Lure some asshole out here...
and take all his shit.
Works every time.
You rich white boys think you can
just come out her and roll with us.
Hawk, put the gun away.
You'd be surprised how long
it takes to find a body out here.
-Wait.
-We're done waiting.
-Back up.
-You're not gonna shoot me.
You heard me.
Back up.
We don't need bullets.
l told you he had it in him.
l felt it the first time l saw him.
What's this?
lt's your ticket
to the promised land.
Bottoms up.
lt's a long ride.
Come on!
LAPD!
Search around.
We've got nothing
here.
Are we sure Elias
lives here?
Positive. Landlord recognized
his mugshot from the news.
Said Elias came and went
like a ghost.
-Looks like he was moving out.
-Or planning a quick getaway.
What ya got?
A book on telekinesis.
Seems our pal Elias was quite
interested in the subject matter.
-What's telekinesis?
-You move things with your mind.
-Like bending spoons?
-Yeah, spoons, forks, whatever.
Only silverware?
l don't know. lt's all bullshit smoke
and mirrors anyway.
Now there's something
you don't see everyday.
What did l tell you, Josh? You're
not gonna learn anything that way.
Now put down the remote control
and do it right.
Well done.
Now the tank.
Good.
Morning.
How's your head?
We call that
a recruitment cocktail.
Young man's got quite a talent,
don't you think?
Show him what else you can do,
Josh.
Good try, Josh.
Go inside, Josh.
So you're the new stray
they brought in.
-Don't look like much to me.
-Go easy, Lincoln.
What would you have done...
if l didn't stop that
from hitting you?
Anybody can move something
when it's that close.
How about something
more distant?
Hell, Adrian,
that's too far.
You're the only one
who can reach that.
Humor me.
Merely tip it over.
Don't think you can move it.
Know you can move it.
He's gonna blow.
What are you laughing at?
That's enough, Lincoln.
Let's give the man a chance.
Go on.
Show us what you can do.
No, l can't.
That's not good enough.
You can try and fail,
but you will try.
This should be good.
Don't mean shit.
Okay, listen to this.
''Some researchers believe primitive
man may've had telekinetic ability.
But as we developed,
we lost the capacity...
to access
that part of our brain.''
Rumor has it that the government
did experiments in the '70's...
to see if it was possible
to re-access that ability.
Was that before or after
aliens assassinated Kennedy?
Come on, Ripps. Don't tell me
you're taking this shit seriously.
A truck with a mind of its own?
Utensils in the ceiling? None of
this strikes you as out there?
Hey, the world's
full of weird shit.
lt all started
with those blue M&M's.
Okay, what do you want to do?
Check and see if there's unusual
robberies in the area. lf there are...
We call in
Mulder and Skully.
l'm watching them as we speak.
Yes, Agents Mclntyre and Ripps.
He's a career Fed,
veteran field agent.
Smart, but definitely
won't cross the line.
Ripps, on the other hand...
-she could be a problem.
-Then make sure she isn't.
What about the tracer
on the professor?
Signal's weak, but l expect to
have that fixed within the hour.
Good.
Let me know when you do.
Welcome to our camp.
lt's a temporary safe haven
for those with the gift.
A place where they can hone
their skills away from ...
the judgment and persecution
of the outside world.
You showed an abundance
of talent back there.
But you hesitated to use it.
Why?
-l don't know.
-l can help you with that.
But first you must realize what
you have is a gift, not a curse.
Come. l want to show you
something.
You already met Tristen.
She spoke highly
of your abilities.
She must be
easily impressed.
She's rather discriminating
of the company she keeps.
A lot more than you,
l'm afraid.
This was found
in your wallet and disabled.
Who sent you?
Let me clarify your situation. The
only reason you're still alive...
is because Tristen sensed
something special in you.
As it happens,
l feel it too.
But have no doubt.
You lie to us, you won't leave
this room alive.
So, who sent you?
You want a name? Or should
l just say the government?
lt's Addison, isn't it?
-You know him?
-He's been after us for years.
Trying to track us down.
But you're the first
he's sent who has the gift.
How did he convince you?
Blackmail?
The man's losing his touch
in his old age.
He said you were murderers.
-That we're murderers?
-This is no game.
We're fighting for our survival. The
man isn't out to catch criminals.
He's trying to erase a mistake.
Addison ran a program
back in the '70's.
He recruited telekinetics
and trained them as weapons.
The program was called
''Momentum.''
You were a part of it?
l'm the only part left.
When they realized
how powerful we'd become...
they decided to terminate
the project and everyone in it.
l've spent every day since
on the run.
Trying to help those with the gift.
Trying to protect them.
Addison sees our kind
as a threat.
He won't stop until he finds us
and wipes us all out.
What Adrian said?
lt's all true.
We live in fear
every single day.
Hiding, moving from place to place
so no one finds us.
Must be hard
for you to believe.
No, not really.
You know, for the longest time
l thought l was the only one.
l never thought l'd find
anyone like me.
l know.
Most of us have spent our lives
thinking that we're outcasts.
That we don't fit in.
When did you first know?
That l had the gift?
l was 13.
These girls were teasing me...
and l broke their noses
without touching them.
l got suspended for a week.
l've read that it comes on
for most kids during puberty.
Did for me.
Well, l've had it
for as long as l can remember.
Every time l slipped up, my parents
would just pack up and move us.
After a while l just became
an expert at hiding it.
You don't have
to hide it anymore.
Geiger has a plan for us.
He thinks you're here
for a reason.
So do l.
No hands.
Wait up!
-2 minutes.
-We won't need that long.
Hold it!
Time?
-45 seconds.
-Let's do it.
Hundred G easy.
Maybe 2.
Yeah. Right.
l'll tell him.
He's gone.
Took his car and split.
Son of a bitch.
l knew we couldn't trust him.
We have to find him.
-Don't bother.
-But Adrian...
Addison's using him. The minute
he gets back there, he's dead.
What if he gives away
our location?
-He won't.
-How the hell do you know?
Because he's one of us.
We can't take that risk.
He's right. We've got to get back
and prepare to move out.
We can trust him.
Guard didn't get a good look
at them...
but he thinks they were in and out
in under 2 minutes.
They cracked this door
in under 2?
lmpossible.
Not this week.
These were ripped
open from the inside.
Just like the armored car.
Agent Ripps?
What's this?
Robbery homicide sent it over. They
thought you should have a look.
-Now there's something...
-you don't see every day.
Would you look at that?
We got a name on this guy?
Clerk said he's a teacher over at
Westlake. Professor Zach Shefford.
Looks like we're going back
to school.
This is Ripps.
What?
Wait a minute.
We're right in the middle...
No, of course not.
Yes, sir.
-They're pulling us off.
-What?
Somebody's pulling rank.
-l'm gonna make one more stop.
-Here we go.
Professor Shefford?
Agents Ripps and Zach.
Can we have a word?
No, l'm sorry, Agent Ripps.
l've never seen him before.
Jordan. He was arrested in that
armored car heist the other day.
Don't take this the wrong way, but
shouldn't you be questioning him?
We were going to.
He's kind of missing.
Did you tell him
about the ESP thing?
We found some books in this
guy's apartment on telekinesis.
-Know anything about the subject?
-Not really, no.
-But you must've read about it.
-A little bit, yeah.
How does it work?
lt doesn't. lt's
a hypothetical phenomenon.
How's it work
hypothetically?
lf l remember right the most common
theory is that someone...
makes a connection with an object
on a cellular level...
and moves it.
Have you ever seen someone
move something without touching it?
No. l can't say l have.
Okay.
Well, l guess that's it, then.
Thank you for your time, Professor.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
What about something big?
Like an armored car?
lt wouldn't be possible to connect
with it on a cellular level...
and flip it over?
Would it?
That would be impossible.
That's what l figured.
Thanks again.
So, what do you think?
Never having met him before
and knowing almost nothing...
about him, l'd say
he's lying out his ass.
You're just upset
because he didn't recognize you.
-You said this was the last stop.
-lt still is.
Just give me a few more hours.
lf l'm wrong, we'll walk.
l hate stakeouts.
My ass gets numb.
Gravity's a bitch.
TlTLE
Put that down.
Can you imagine how proud they'd
be if they could see you now?
What are you doing here?
You had me worried there
for awhile.
Thought you were
changing teams.
l'm not on a team.
Oh, l've got news for you.
Everybody's on a team.
You just pick a side and hope
you pick the right one.
The right one?
There is no right one.
You want to expose me?
Go for it. l've been through worse.
-You found them, didn't you?
-Didn't tell me about the project.
You didn't need to know.
You're not trying to arrest them,
you're trying to wipe them out.
l am trying
to protect this nation.
Nobody with that kind of power
can be trusted.
Especially a fanatic
like Geiger.
Now think about it,
Professor.
Today, robbery.
Tomorrow, terrorism.
What's to prevent a foreign gov from
paying them to turn against us?
You should have thought about that
before you trained them.
We hadn't planned on creating
a weapon that can do what they can.
Geiger's got people all over
this country waiting for orders.
Don't walk away.
Not now.
Good night.
The others want to know
why we're not moving out.
They're not coming.
How do you know?
l know.
lf you're wrong, this could be
the end of everything.
lt's just the beginning.
Christ.
-You scared the hell out of me.
-Sorry.
l saw your light on.
l didn't think l'd see you again.
Well, you were wrong.
l just wanted you to know that if
you ever need to talk, l'll be here.
Besides, what would you
do without me?
-Who are these guys?
-Addison sent them.
Which means
you didn't sell us out.
-l knew it.
-What?
You're with us.
-l'm not with anyone.
-We need you, Zach.
Your strength.
Addison says Geiger
has sleeper cells in place.
That he's gonna use people
like us to start a war.
ls that true?
What's he gonna do?
-Preserve our kind.
-How far is he gonna go?
He's out of control.
He's tired of living in fear.
We all are.
-There's got to be another way.
-There isn't.
-Now there's something you don't...
-Start the damn car, Frank.
-How many are there?
-Just your boy so far.
l got to tell you, my gut says
we should bring in some backup.
Sure, if you want to lose our jobs.
We're not exactly on the clock.
Let's just wait and see.
Company.
Leave him to me.
Addison's got Tristen.
Now ya know what it feels like. The
fear that comes with being hunted.
Addison tried to kill you,
didn't he?
He's killed
dozens of innocents.
And he'll keep killing.
Driving us towards extinction.
He created a weapon.
The most dangerous of all.
One that thinks and breathes
and feels.
But now they're afraid of what it
can do so they want to destroy it.
They used you, Zach.
Turned you against your own kind.
Time has come
to make a choice.
Unless you want to try your luck
with Addison alone.
ls what Addison said
about you true?
We're nomads.
Always on the move.
Always seeking sanctuary.
Your parents, they were nomads too,
weren't they?
Always on the run. Never staying
in one place too long.
They were smart to do that.
They did that for your protection
and theirs.
Running is a hard way to live.
You spent your whole life
hiding your gift.
Fearing it.
-The time has come to embrace it.
-What could you hope to accomplish?
To be recognized.
Others may fear or revere us.
That's a choice
that l'll leave up to them.
But l promise you, we will be
a power to be reckoned with.
At what expense?
Why don't you just make it public?
Go to the goddamned press.
And what? Take center stage
in a 3-ring media circus? No.
No, when we rise up,
we'll make the news.
What about Tristen?
Don't worry about Tristen.
Super-size them.
Frank...
This is bad. Right?
You could say that.
Good morning, agents.
That's one
fucking bright light.
ls that a halogen bulb
you got in there?
Why were you doing
trespassing on private property?
Our car broke down. lt's a good
thing you came along when you did.
lf you uncuff us, we can avoid
charging you with kidnapping.
Of course.
Neat trick.
Can you pull a bunny
out of your ass too?
What the fuck?
lt's of the utmost importance
that l find out what you know.
We don't know anything.
Except you'll have a big power bill
if you don't turn that light off.
Have it your way.
May l see your fingers,
Agent Mclntyre?
Any specific finger
you have in mind?
Now, then.
You were saying...
Goddamn it, stop it.
We don't know anything.
We'll soon find out.
That was very impressive
last night.
Looks like
we underestimated you.
Where is she?
lsla Vista. Where we trained him.
This is your chance to be a hero.
l'm proposing a trade.
Geiger for the girl.
He won't go for it.
-Sure he will.
-Why would he?
Because we're talking about
his daughter.
Your friend's thumb
is gonna be next.
Why don't you do him
a favor and start talking?
We were investigating
an armored car robbery.
-Who sent you?
-Nobody. Just following Shefford.
-l don't believe you.
-Believe what you want, asshole.
Because in 5 minutes this place is
gonna be swarming with FBl.
5 minutes? Then we have no more
time to waste. Lincoln?
Who the fuck are you?
We're in motion.
Good, round everybody up.
Let's get out of here.
Adrian, how many
people have to die?
As many as necessary.
They were sent to kill us.
One person wants you dead.
One.
He says he'll hand over Tristen
in exchange for you.
Where?
-The place where he trained you.
-Bullshit. Don't believe him.
Goddamnit, Adrian.
She's alive.
Adrian, it's a trap.
l know.
What about her?
Finish what you started.
-lt's okay. Come with me.
-Not a chance.
-She's not a part of this.
-But you are.
Lights out, asshole.
Get the car before
anyone sees you. Go ahead.
Agent Ripps.
Clearance code 5512.
Okay, Agent Ripps.
Standby for repatch.
Repatch?
Josh, where's Geiger?
He left with Hawk.
Are we leaving again?
Yeah. Time to go.
Come on, Josh.
We're leaving.
Zach, come on!
Get in!
Thank you for what
you did back there.
l'm sorry about your partner.
l called for backup. They should
be here any minute.
What?
What did you do that for?
-These people are dangerous.
-Yeah, they're dangerous.
You've got to call them off before
more of your agents end up dead.
Shit. Where the hell are they?
What are you doing?
Making you listen to me.
l know what Geiger's planning.
l know where he's going.
Forget it We're waiting
here for help.
l'm the only chance
you've got
Send your people in there against
them, it's gonna be World War 3.
Never underestimate
the government.
You can say that again.
Those aren't your agents.
Those are Addison's guys.
We've got to get out of here.
Let's go.
-Jordan, you can't help them.
-l have to try.
-lt's too late.
-Not too late.
-Addison killed them all.
-You saw it yourself. They're gone.
They're gone.
And you'll be next.
ls that what you want?
l'll tell you everything.
But we gotta go. Now.
Affirmative, sir.
The site's been neutralized.
Cleanup crew is on its way.
This time tomorrow, no one
will know it was even there.
Well done. What about Geiger?
Most likely on his way to you.
Good.
Project Momentum.
How could they cover up...
something
that big all these years?
Like you said. Never
underestimate the government.
lf you're not part of that group,
what were you doing out there?
That's a good question.
Geiger and Addison,
they're like 2 time bombs...
just waiting to go off.
Can you stop them?
l'll give
base command a call.
This is where it all began.
Where they trained us.
So this is it?
Brings back memories,
doesn't it?
l would not do that
if l were you.
You might get 2 or 3 of us.
But rest assured:
she will die in the process.
Welcome back, Adrian.
Place hasn't been the same
since you left.
You mean since you tried
to kill us.
Attention. This is not a drill.
All personnel please
evacuate the facility immediately.
This is not a drill.
Smart. Clear out the base. Make
sure no one sees what we can do.
Or is it what you're
about to do?
Just like old times,
right, Ray?
Close up shop,
pretend we never existed?
You're a threat to the security
of the nation.
l am what you made me.
We dedicated our lives to this
country and you tried to execute us.
You became too dangerous.
No, Ray.
You took our ability
and made it dangerous.
And then you turned against us.
What did you expect us to do? We
were forced to protect ourselves.
Self-preservation
is not an excuse for murder.
For once, we agree.
That's not possible.
We've come a long way
since we were together.
We're through being targets. Our
turn to show the world who we are.
The real battle's
about to begin.
She's gonna take my place.
Because no one in this room
is gonna walk out alive.
Fire.
We were once ready to die
to protect our country.
-Now it's your turn.
-Doesn't make any difference.
Wherever you may go, wherever
you may hide, we'll find you.
-We'll hunt you down like animals.
-You'll never find us all.
We'll grow in numbers, gaining
strength, learning, prospering.
Sounds like a fucking disease.
Not a disease. Just a natural
step in our evolution.
One which you were dumb
enough to make lethal.
They're gone.
Everyone's dead.
They wiped out
the whole camp.
He didn't leave anything to chance,
did you, Mr. Addison?
Goddamn you!
ls this how you'll be recognized?
By starting a war you can't win?
Can't afford not to win.
l can't let you do that.
You should never have come.
Prepare to be moved.
lf this is not your fight,
don't try to stop me.
l'm gonna stop you.
Take him out.
l can't reach him.
He's too far.
Focus.
Don't think about doing it.
Know you can do it.
Don't let them win.
Come on. We've got to get out of
here. We've got to go right now.
Where are we gonna go?
Who the hell's gonna believe us?
Yes, sir. l was working undercover
with Addison on this.
l'm sorry to report he's dead.
Along with my partner,
Frank Mclntyre.
You have my condolences,
Agent Ripps.
-You're sure this Geiger is gone?
-Positive, sir.
l think you can officially
close the book on this.
What about
this Zach Shefford?
He was at the farmhouse, sir.
He must be dead too.
Very well. You've done
a great service, Agent.
We'll need to debrief you
as soon as possible.
Give me your location. l can have
units there in 10 minutes.
lt's done. They're coming
for me. You have to go.
l don't know what to say.
Don't say shit.
Just get out of here.
Change your name. You won't have
to look over your shoulder anymore.
What about you?
Don't worry about me.
l'm blessed.
Remember?
Breaking news from San Diego...
where a train has derailed
after a bizarre bridge collapse.
At least 15 people are confirmed
dead at this hour.
Witnesses report
a horrifying scene...
as the bridge
fell into the river...
seemingly ripped apart
by some unseen force.
We take you live now where
Stacy Mitchens is on the scene.
Zach, wait!
Zach! Wait!
Wait!
What is this?
lt's Geiger's daughter. She wants
revenge her father's death.
-What do you mean?
-She's picking up where he left off.
Well, you have to go after her.
You have to stop her.
No. l'm done.
You wanted a reason? You wanted
a reason you were given this gift.
Well, this is it.
You're the only one
who can stop her.
Federal agents!
ldentify yourself!
Jordan Ripps!
TlTLE