- That's not the Girl Scout salute.
- Oh.
- Wrong hand, Peterson.
- Oh, well, okay.
So I was never a Girl Scout,
but I'm telling you the truth, Brackett.
I swear.
Okay, so tell me.
What's LDF?
"LDF is a genetically engineered hormone
for dairy cows. It could be the fir..."
Somebody's trying to kill us
over a cow hormone?
"Could be the first commercial success
of genetic engineering...
that directly affects food
for humans."
"Milk Hormone Stirs Fear."
Okay, now we're talkin'.
"LDF milk tests will be reviewed
by State's Agricultural
Committee Chairwoman...
Gayle Robbins."
Bingo!
- You wanna know about LDF?
- Yeah.
You've come to
the right place.
- In English, Sam, please.
- Okay, here's the deal.
Normally it takes a calf two years to
mature into a milk-producing cow, right?
So, Chess figured, why wait
that long taking care of a calf?
It's not making you any money.
So they invent this hormone LDF. They
shoot that stuff into a newborn calf.
Nine months later, you got
yourself a full-grown,
milk-producing, moneymaking...
- Franken-cow.
- That's exactly what I thought at first.
But then from what we hear the cows
are healthy, and the tests show...
I hates these tours!
And the tests show that the milk's,
uh, pure. So, there you go.
Say, what kind of profits can
Chess make on a thing like this?
Thing?
This thing, my boy, could revolutionize
the entire worldwide dairy industry.
Potentially the biggest moneymaker
that a chemical company has seen...
- since NutraSweet.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- So, how much can they make?
Oh, somewhere in the neighbourhood
of a billion dollars a year.
- Oh, nice neighbourhood.
- Yeah. I wouldn't mind
living there myself.
Oh, hi.
You got out early.
One of the advantages
of being chairperson.
You get to adjourn the meetings.
- How'd that school board thing work out?
- Oh, nothing to worry about.
- Uh, these are friends
of mine from Chicago.
- Oh, hi. Gayle Robbins.
- Peter Brackett from the Chronicle.
- Yes.
- And this is Sabrina, uh...
- Peterson.
Of the Globe.
Sorry.
Yes. It's nice to meet you.
Sam, are we having a press conference?
No, no, no. They're just doing
some research on LDF, that's all.
- Really?
- Yep.
- What do you think?
We were just gonna ask you
that same question,
being the head of the committee.
Uh, it really doesn't behove
the Senator to render an opinion
on that matter...
- Sam!
- All right, go ahead and render.
Give me a buzz after the FD A completes
its review. We'll talk then.
- Ready, Senator?
- Sam.
I know, Pete. You got like a thousand
questions, right? Okay, okay.
Look, I got a, an hour here.
Okay? What do you say I take
both of you to dinner, huh?
On the house?
Two New Yorks, rare.
And one steamed vegetable plate,
no salt, no oil, no butter.
Thank you.
So, you started to say that during
Vietnam, Chess manufactured...
Oh, you know, just things like
napalm, Agent Orange, you know?
All that wonderful stuff.
And then the war ended and
their profits really dried up.
For a while, it looked like the
company was on its last legs.
And then, along comes
the genetic revolution.
And boy,
things really heated up for them.
LDF could put them right back on top.
- What's the Chess family like?
- Oh, boy.
Well, the old man's
a real zealot, you know?
He's kinda like a Ross Perot wannabe.
His kid, Willy, kind of runs things now.
I don't know too much about him.
I think he went to Yale,
and then straight to work for Daddy.
- Did you know him at Yale?
- Uh-uh, uh-uh.
No, I think he's younger than me. How
did you remember that I went to Yale?
That is incredible.
You've got such an amazing memory.
I can't remember my own name.
It's possible that I met him
at school, but I doubt it.
I don't even think he graduated.
What year would he have been
if he had graduated?
I don't know.
Let me think. Uh...
- What year did you graduate?
- Me? '73. No, '74.
So that would make him class of
'76, '77, something like that.
You know, Gayle's met him a few times.
He's supposed to be a nice guy.
Not exactly a rocket scientist,
but he...
What's going on here exactly, guys?
I mean, why are you
so interested in LDF, huh?
Oh, Peterson here is
a big milk drinker. That's all.
Oh, well, it d...
It does a body good.
Sorry. C'mon, you're not
gonna tell me?
It's gotta be somethin' big if
both the Globe and the Chronicle
are in bed together on it.
I wouldn't say we're exactly
in bed together.
Cheque, please.
Oh. Okay, now.
In case you have any more questions...
or if you finally decide
to tell me what you've
actually got up your sleeve...
- here's my card, Pete.
It's got my direct dial on it.
- Oh, thanks, Sam.
- Where are you parked?
- In the lot over there.
Oh, perfect.
We're gonna pass by...
- the best frozen yogurt joint
in the entire state.
- Yeah?
It's on Peterson.
- Look out!
- Sam!
Move!
Sam, are you okay?
What the hell
was that all about?
Medwick, it's me.
Just checking in.
Listen, I've put together a
"just the facts, ma'am" kind of thing...
and wanted to
run it by you, okay?
- They know you're there?
- Uh, no.
- I guess so far
they don't know we're here.
- You're lucky.
Yeah, real lucky.
So, here's what we know:
Beekman was the head researcher
on LDF.
He retires mysteriously,
then dies a week later.
His son boards a train with something
in his briefcase that his dad sent him.
The train crashes, the son dies,
and the briefcase is stolen.
The kid who stole it is murdered,
but before he dies he writes
the initials "LD" on his palm.
LD means LDF, and LDF means
a billion dollars a year.
So you tell me.
All this adds up to...
Good morning, everyone,
and welcome to Chess Chemical.
Our first stop on today's tour
will be the Chess Family
Science Discovery Centre.
Now, as we walk in pairs
down the Biology of Tomorrow corridor...
I'd like to point out some of the
everyday products created here at Chess.
For example, the cold medicine
that I forgot to take this morning...
as well as the disposable diapers
I used for my little one last night.
Now, as we continue on...
Extension 307 is a 72-year-old
cafeteria worker named Sadie.
Hair net,
orthopaedic shoes.
Are you sure?
Maybe it was 3-0-something else.
No, no, no. I'm positive.
Here, look.
Well, do you wanna get out of here,
or take a stroll down
the Biology of Tomorrow corridor?
Rule number one of
investigative reporting, Peterson,
is find out what you're up against.
- Let's stroll.
- What's rule number two?
Stay clear of all surveillance cameras
when visiting the lair of the enemy.
Thanks.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
- Wilson Chess.
- Sabrina Peterson.
- And Mr Peterson?
- Actually, the name's Brackett.
Peter Brackett,
the writer.
Of course. Well, what brings you
to this neck of the woods?
I'm doin' a little research
on a new novel, Wilson.
You're kidding?
What, here at Chess?
- Mm-hmm.
- What's the new one about?
It's a murder mystery set against
the backdrop of a chemical company.
Sounds intriguing, but I'm always
a sucker for a good murder yarn.
- Aren't you, Miss Peterson?
- As long as the bad guy gets
it in the end, I'm happy.
W-Well, have fun.
And don't forget to change
the names to protect the innocent.
So much for rule number three:
Avoid insulting...
the men who may be trying
to kill you.
- Oh, uh, I was just looking for
you, sir. Here, look at this.
- Hello.
- It's fine.
- You look very nice today.
- Thank you.
- Check this one out.
- We missed you for lunch. It was...
...right through to
the research farm behind me...
where scientists are fine-tuning
Mother Nature with such innovative...
products for the future as the
Livestock Development Factor, LDF.
Now, if you'll come with me,
I'd like to show you a film...
that highlights some of the exciting
things we're doing here at Chess.
Don't worry, parents.
It's G-rated.
- Hey, where'd you guys go on your break?
- We looked for you.
- We did.
- Oh, I had to go to the lab.
Rule number four: Get close to someone
who's close to the enemy.
How am I supposed
to calm down?
You promised me this was going
to be taken care of...
and now they are here
in my building.
Ernesto, I can't
handle this any more.
Just make it happen.
- You want us to pick you up
at Ruby's tonight?
- Oh, I'll meet you there.
It's better if we take our own cars,
in case one of us gets lucky.
You mean, in case
there's a miracle, right?
You never know.
Well, what do you know?
Huh.
Evans, this is great. This is good.
You got any leads on 'im?
- Pete, I'm looking for
some more information on...
- Come in.
- Hello? Mr Brackett?
- Hi.
Mr Brackett, we haven't come up
with anything yet, but when we do...
Yeah, okay. Well, stay on it
and I'll check with you later.
Yeah.
Interesting news.
It seems Willy Chess
did go to Yale.
- Who's Ernesto Vargas?
- Well, that's the interesting news.
The reason Sam was confused about
whether or not Chess graduated...
- is because he was expelled.
- For?
Burning down
the English Department.
Somethin' about a problem
with one of his professors.
Young Willy and his cohort,
this South American kid Vargas...
they decided to torch the place
for revenge, and they were
caught and properly booted out.
A fire back then,
a fire at Beekman's.
A South American friend,
a South American assassin.
- Where's Vargas now?
- Evans can't seem to get a line on him.
- Maybe Sam could help.
- Yeah. Good idea.
Good idea.
You don't know
what I did with his, uh...
Thank you.
By the way, I dressed like this
because I figured this is the way...
you're supposed to dress
at these pickup places...
and I didn't want
to stand out or anything.
Yeah. No chance of anyone
noticing you, Peterson.
- That's good thinking.
- Sam Smotherman's office.
- Hi. Is he in?
- Who's calling, please?
- Peter Brackett.
- Just a minute.
By the way, Peterson, that reminds me.
We never did finish
that other discussion.
- What other discussion?
- Pete, hello.
Sam, how ya doin'?
Well, I'm all right,
believe it or not.
Well, I knew you'd recover. Listen,
can you check on an old Yalie for me?
A name came up. We can't seem
to get a lead on the guy.
I'm sorry. Just one second.
Sure. Who is he?
Well, he was at Yale
the same time as Willy Chess.
- His name is, uh, Ernesto Vargas.
- Bargas?
No, no, no.
Vargas with a "V" like Victor.
Oh, Vargas. That doesn't sound familiar,
but I'll check him out.
All right.
Well, look, I'm gonna be in and out,
so if you come up with anything...
like where he is or how we can reach
him, call my office, ask for Evans.
Yeah, I'll make a deal with you,
though. I find this Vargas guy...
then you're gonna clue me in
on what you're workin' on?
If he finds Vargas, will we clue
him in on what we're working on?
No.
You got it, buddy! Thanks a lot.
I'll see ya later.
Rule number five, Peterson:
Always humour those who can help you.
Now, what other conversation
did you want to finish?
Oh, the one about me
wanting to get you in the sack.
Oh, that. Well, forget it.
I didn't really think...
No, no, no, Peterson.
This is important.
I want you to know that I see you
strictly as a fellow newspaperman.
I mean that sincerely.
I see you as nothing else,
and I never will.
You have my word on it.
- I do?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, thanks.
That makes me feel really good.
I appreciate it.
I, I, I, I do. Thanks.
You're welcome, kid.
There's gonna be
a heartache tonight
A heartache tonight
I know
Gonna be a heartache tonight
The moon shinin' bright
Kim, introduce me.
Michael, this is Robin.
Robin, this is Michael.
- Hi.
- Robin's thinking of moving here.
Do it. We need more cute babes
in this town.
Yeah, right. Like there aren't
already four babes to every man.
- Kim, look who's here.
- Dixon, what are you doing here?
- Didn't your wife just have a baby?
- I'm celebrating!
- Yeah, right.
- Dance?
- Sure.
That's the other problem.
Small town, big chemical company.
Everybody knows
everything about...
Whoa, daddy!
Look what just walked in.
Somebody's gonna hurt someone
Before the night is through
Who? The guy
with the black suit?
Somebody's gonna come undone
There's nothin' we can do
You don't think he's like
off-the-charts hot?
I don't know that I'd go right to
off-the-charts. You think so?
I know so.
I also know I haven't been laid
in more months than I care to admit.
- Hi.
- How ya doin'?
- Ooh, great now.
Good.
- Can I buy you a drink?
- Absolutely.
- I'll have what the lady's having.
- Comin' right up.
I'm fine, thank you.
I don't like you
- I'm David.
- I'm horny.
Seems that I'm always
- Thinkin' of you
- Oh!
Ohh-ohh-ohh
You treat me badly
I love you madly
You've really got a hold on me
Really got a hold on me
You really got a hold on me
Baby, I love you
And all I want you to do
Is just hold me
Hold me
- Hold
- Do you wanna dance?
- I'd love to.
- Wh...
Tighter, honey
Tighter
Ohhh
I don't wanna leave you
Don't wanna stay here
Don't wanna spend
Another day here
Ooh, I wanna split now
But I just can't quit now
You've really got a hold on me
- Really got a hold on me
- You got me
- You really got a hold on me
Hey, Peterson.
I'm sorry.
I lost track of time.
No problem.
I'm sure you were...
I mean,
I imagine you were...
Not that I was sitting here imagining
anything, because I wasn't.
- What time is it?
- It's a little after 4:00.
I see. Fine.
So, um, it's late, so let's
just go, okay, Brackett?
And, by the way, do you mind
if I drive, because...
Just because I'm the woman
doesn't always mean I wanna be
the passenger, okay?
Peterson,
I didn't sleep with her.
Excuse me. Did I ask you
if you slept with anybody?
No, no, no, no, no.
I just wanted you to know.
Look, Brackett, however you choose to
get your information is your business.
Did you lift her security pass
is all I wanna know.
- Well, I couldn't. She was all over me.
- Oh.
By the way, for the record,
not sleeping with her...
was maybe some of
the hardest work I've ever done.
- Do I look like your roommate?
I don't wanna hear this.
- You're right. I apologize.
Now, please, sit down.
Let me buy you a cup of coffee.
I'm tired of sitting,
and I'm not thirsty.
Peterson,
I've got us a lead.
This is Kim's surprise party
last year.
The man with the grey hair
is Beekman.
There's our friend Willy. And next to
him in the glasses is Alexander Hervey.
Uh, who's Alexander Hervey?
He's a research scientist at Chess.
He and Beekman created LDF together.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- So where has he been during all this?
- Boulder City, Nevada.
- Nevada?
Mm-hmm.
- You want some coffee?
- Not really. No.
Well, okay, yeah. No.
Uh, yes. Half a cup.
Doughnut?
Oh, no, thanks.
I try not to eat after 11:00.
It's bad for your metabolism
to eat when your body's inactive.
Plus I try to avoid saturated fats,
but you go ahead.
So, what's in Nevada?
Hervey and Beekman worked on LDF
for ten years.
At the end of the day,
LDF was a big hit and they were heroes.
Hervey was promoted and made the head
of a research facility outside of Vegas.
- So he's sitting pretty.
- He was, but a couple of months ago...
he had a stroke, so he's pretty
much out of commission now.
But the interesting thing is, Kim heard
Beekman was also offered a promotion...
but he turned it down.
So he turns down a promotion,
quits his job...
and suddenly dies?
Look, I realize that we're only
investigating together...
and we're trying to avoid coming
to any actual conclusions out loud.
- However?
- However, it seems to me...
- that something wasn't kosher with LDF.
- Mm-hmm.
And Willy must've gone to
Beekman and Hervey and offered
them promotions if they'd...
- Fake the test results?
- Is that what you think, Brackett?
- Is that what you think, Peterson?
- I asked you first.
- Yes.
- Me, too.
I think Hervey went along
with the plan, but Beekman refused.
So he leaves Chess and takes
the real test results with him.
- And just in case,
sends a copy to his son.
- Exactly.
Willy finds out, panics,
and calls in his old friend Vargas.
You've turned into
a hell of a Hardy Boy, Peterson.
Besides the fact that these people
are trying to kill us...
how about the fact that they're
contaminating the country's milk supply?
Milk! Is nothing sacred?
Let's go!
Gimme the keys, Peterson.
You can drive next time.
What was that all about?
That guy was what? Tell me.
I don't know. Like, he was there then he
was gone. I don't know. I got spooked.
Well, it's okay.
I'm dead anyway.
Yes, you are.
You two have somethin'
that doesn't belong to you,
and I've been asked to take it back.
Peterson, do you have somethin'
that doesn't belong to you?
- No. Do you?
- Mmm. Sorry, we don't have it.
Stay in this lane, boyfriend,
and keep it at 60.
So what's the plan?
Take us to some remote place, kill us
and make it look like an accident?
- Sounds good to me.
- Well, guess what?
Since I'm the designated driver,
screw your plan.
What are you doing?
Slow the car down,
or I'll smoke you right now!
Go ahead!
That's it!
Pull over!
Brackett!
Put your seat belt on,
Peterson.
What are you, crazy?
- You're welcome.
- Should I search him?
- Is he dead?
- I don't think so.
Then I wouldn't.
I think we took
the wrong turn.
Jeez! Oh!
Perhaps this is
a blessing in disguise.
- At least nobody knows where we are.
- Including us.
So, are we gonna go see
this Hervey character or what?
Yeah. Sure.
Which way's Nevada?
What do you think that guy meant
when he asked...
if we had something
that didn't belong to us?
I don't know. Maybe Beekman's
test results weren't in the briefcase.
But if we had them, why would we
still be on the story?
Better question is, if they weren't
in the briefcase, where are they?
You aren't suggesting
I have them.
Oh, I hadn't thought of that.
Do you?
- Wanna frisk me?
- No, not tonight, dear.
I have a headache.
Oops. I'm sorry.
You sure you don't want
some sunscreen, Brackett?
- It's paba-free.
- I'm fine, thank you.
One out of every six Americans
gets skin cancer before the age of 65.
You blonds have to be
especially careful.
Peterson, do me a favour.
Quit givin' me advice.
First, I shouldn't eat bacon,
then saturated fat.
If I'd eaten that saturated fat, I
wouldn't be starving to death right now.
Fine.
Don't wear sunscreen.
You know, I was just thinking.
You know where I'd be today
if it weren't for you?
- No, tell me.
- At the Beverly Hills Hotel...
on my book tour, lounging around
the pool, giving interviews,
gazing at starlets.
You're not even embarrassed
to say that, are you?
Embarrassed?
What do you think? I'd rather
be traipsing through poison ivy...
wearing a shirt on my head,
looking for hidden test results?
You think they're hidden?
You're actually having fun
on this story, aren't you?
You're not? I mean, I understand
your saying you're not,
but you're really not?
Peterson, do I look like a man
having fun?
A man lounging around
the Beverly Hills Hotel
ogling starlets...
looks to me like a man
not having fun.
And furthermore, I think
you owe me an apology.
In my opinion, meeting me was the best
thing that ever happened to you.
You could've quit this story
anytime you wanted, and you didn't...
because you and I both know
this is the story of our lives.
No matter what you say, I know
you'd rather be an ace reporter...
than a second-rate
novelist.
What is that?
What is what?
- Don't turn around. I'm getting out.
- Yeah?
I didn't think you'd be back so fast.
Don't turn.
I won't.
- What's that?
- What?
- Uh-oh.
- She's naked.
- What?
- She's butt naked!
Honey,
we've been rescued.
What are you doing?
Don't do this to me, please.
Was I hearing things, or did you
call me a second-rate novelist?
I was, I was kidding.
I, I never even read your book.
- I, I'm sure it's quite brilliant.
- Uh-huh.
- Oh! What are you doing? Walk backwards.
- You never read it, huh?
Boys! Hi, boys! Look!
A double-spotted platypus.
They're very rare.
You're missing it.
When they said be prepared, I bet you
boys didn't expect anything like this.
Only in our dreams.
Are you sure you never
read my book, Peterson?
- Okay, stop. I, I read it.
I'm, I'm reading it.
- And?
It's cute.
Very cute.
I, I expected more,
to tell you the truth, but...
These nature walks are really
educational, huh, guys?
Hey, I got a great idea!
Does anybody have a camera?
- Come on, you look great!
- I can't believe I let you
talk me into this shirt!
I mean, we look like
Roy Rogers and Dale Evans!
I mean, look at us.
Brackett, they found us.
Let's get outta here.
- Stop!
- Get out of the way.
- Stop! Stop!
Go!
Move 'em out!
Come on, Peterson!
This way! This way!
Brackett, through here.
Ooh!
We don't see
many of those any more.
Congratulations.
Right this way.
- You kids next?
- Us?
- Yes! Yes! Yes, we are. We're next.
- Isn't this rather sudden?
Come, come, come.
Don't be shy.
My name is Ray. I'll be conducting
the service this evening.
Please take a position
in front of the podium...
and I'll acquaint you with the
accoutrement we have at our disposal.
We have flowers,
fresh or silk.
We have rings, veil, tux,
yarmulke, if you so desire.
- Music, prerecorded or live...
- We'll take the works.
Yes. The works, Sandra.
Spare no expense on such
a marvellous and holy occasion.
That's a 42,
and it looks like a winner.
Please place this
on the apex of the skull.
Very good.
Would you folks prefer the...
long or the abridged service
this evening?
Uh, just do us a favour.
Just go through the motions. Uh...
- Just start.
- Just start? Why don't we just start?
Sandra, if you will.
I'll need your names.
- Peterson.
- Brackett.
Peterson, you and Brackett
have decided to unite your love.
May you cherish
this sacred moment...
forever.
Rings.
As I ask Brackett...
do you take Peterson
to be your wedded wife...
promising to cherish
and protect her...
be it in good fortune
and adversity?
- Is he here?
- Yes!
Yes? And do you take Brackett
to be your wedded husband...
promising to cherish
and protect him...
be it in good fortune
and adversity?
- If he comes any closer,
we're out the rear exit.
- Okay.
Okay. And so,
by the powers vested in me...
by the great state
of Nevada...
I pronounce you
husband and wife.
Mazel tov.
I'm coming up empty
on this guy Vargas.
And your friend Sam
called twice.
He said that he can't find
anybody who knew him at Yale.
Oh, how's Peterson?
Is she still driving you crazy?
More than you can imagine.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
- Anything?
- Not yet.
- You hungry?
- Yeah, a little.
Thanks.
To the bravest girl
I ever met.
Why? Because I've managed
to stay alive?
Oh, no, no!
Because you married me.
Am I really looking
at a heart-shaped turkey burger?
You know, if anyone told me two weeks
ago I'd be married to Peter Brackett...
Oh, no, no, no, no. Don't worry.
I already checked.
We can have it annulled
in the morning.
Oh, you did?
Good.
Well, a 12-hour marriage.
Even shorter than my first one.
Peterson,
you were married before?
You find that so hard
to imagine?
No, no. I'm just sort of particular
about who my wives have been married to.
- Who was he?
- Name's O'Connor.
Of Peterson, Peterson
and O'Connor.
He's extremely close
with my parents.
- Well, you've been married
before, right?
- I tried it briefly.
- Didn't like it?
- No, actually it was my wife
who had the complaint.
She said I was never home. She said
I loved newspapering more than her...
She said she'd never mean as much to you
as the story you were working on.
- She said she was jealous of the boys...
- In the city room.
- Yeah!
- Funny.
- Yeah.
She's now married to a brilliant CPA
with an amazing sweater collection.
- Bet he's home every night.
- Like clockwork.
- That's what they like.
- Regularity.
Yeah.
You know, Brackett...
some guys...
might try to take advantage of
a situation like this, but not you.
No, no.
I know this is
the one area...
- where I can completely trust you.
- Mm-hmm.
So, which side of the heart
do you want?
- We're sleeping in shifts. Remember?
- Yeah, right. I forgot.
- Um, you want to take the first shift?
- No, no, you go ahead.
Mmm.
Tell me something,
Brackett.
What is it about me
you don't like?
I'm not pretty enough?
Not tall enough?
Too tall?
Too smart?
Not smart enough?
Wrong colour hair?
Talk too much?
Really, what is it?
I've never had this effect
on a man before.
You would be surprised,
but...
most men are actually
somewhat attracted to me.
I know you think I'm trouble,
and you curse the day you met me...
but off the record, I don't feel
that way about you...
at all.
Off the record, Peterson...
I don't feel that way
about you, either...
at all.
You don't?
First time I ever kissed
a newspaperman.
I like it.
This doesn't change anything.
I'm still the Globe, and you're still...
The Chronicle.
I know, Sabrina, I know.
- We're still...
- Competitors.
Thank you
for calling me Sabrina.
- Hello?
- This is Mrs Hervey.
If you want to see my husband,
please come now.
This is exactly the sort of thing that
would've driven my ex-husband crazy.
Your current husband's not
too thrilled about it, either.
- Well...
- Yeah.
Oh, hey, don't forget
your wallet.
Shall we?
Sure.
My husband's home now because
there's nothing more they
can do for him at the hospital.
But some days
he's not all that bad.
Alex, the reporters from Chicago
are here to see you.
Alex?
Alex.
Alex, they've come
such a long way to see you.
You wanted to talk to my husband
about, um, Darryl Beekman, didn't you?
Mm-hmm. Yes, we were wondering why,
a-after the success of LDF...
that your husband
was given a promotion...
but Dr Beekman chose
to leave the company?
Were you wondering, Mr Brackett,
or do you think you know?
We think we know. We just need
someone to tell us if we're right.
Did your husband ever say
anything about Dr Beekman...
about disagreements
between them?
Never.
I-I'm sorry. I w... I was hoping
Alex could talk to you.
I sensed
that he wanted to.
Uh, uh, excuse me. Can I use
your restroom for a second?
- Down the hall.
- Oh, thank you.
I'm sorry you had to come
such a long way.
I really appreciate you calling us,
Mrs Hervey. Thank you.
Maybe we should wait
until Mr Brackett gets back.
No, no, that's okay.
Uh, I really don't know
what it is, but...
I thought it was strange,
because in 30 years...
I've never seen Alex bring
anything home from work.
You can take it, but I'm afraid it's
not much use to anyone outside of Chess.
Thank you.
This is Captain Riley. Just to let
you know that we're ahead of schedule...
and we'll be arriving in Chicago
in just a little under an hour.
The temperature is a breezy
34 degrees with clear skies.
- Sorry.
- No problem.
Complimentary champagne
for the bride and groom?
I can always spot the newlyweds
on our Vegas flights.
Of course with you two,
who couldn't?
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
So, what should
we drink to?
- Our annulment?
- Perfect!
Because, truthfully, Brackett,
there's not a man in the world
I'd rather annul than you.
Truthfully, Peterson, I wouldn't
believe anything you ever said...
that started with
the word "truthfully."
Well, I guess it's time
to put an end to the charade.
Yeah. Gimbel's marries Macy's.
We wouldn't want that to get around.
- May I?
- Mmm.
Will you do something for me,
Peterson, for old times' sake?
What?
Kiss me goodbye.
Back now, 7:30 on this, uh,
Monday morning, October the 14th.
I'm Bryant Gumbel here in Studio 3B.
Katie Couric's up on Capitol...
What happened
to October 13th?
Let's go.
Uh, I'm here
for the 4:00 tour.
...in beautiful
Spring Creek, Wisconsin.
Our first stop
on today's tour...
is going to be the Chess Family
Science Discovery Centre.
Now, as we walk in pairs down
the Biology of Tomorrow corridor...
Right this way, sir.
How are you folks today?
I'd like to point out a few of the
everyday products created here at Chess.
For example, the cold medicine
which I forgot to take this morning.
- Hi.
- Milk, a staple for the entire family.
And just one of the products
Chess Chemical is working to improve...
- for the 21st century.
- You know, you look very familiar.
Have we met before?
No. Actually this is my first
visit to the Twilight Zone.
- Why'd you double-cross me, Peterson?
- Just following the Golden Rule.
But I thought we were partners,
five-oh, five-oh.
That must explain why you took
Kim's security pass.
- Oh, Peterson, I was gonna...
- "I was gonna tell you."
You can't even be honest
about being dishonest.
I was gonna tell you, Peterson.
I took it as a backup.
- I never thought we'd be here again.
- Yeah, mm-hmm.
- Look, I gotta go.
- Peterson, listen.
It's not safe for you
to be here alone.
Now, you probably don't wanna be
reminded of this...
but I did take an oath to protect you
till death do us part.
Game's over, Brackett,
and you lose.
I've got the disk.
I've got the security pass.
Actually, I have the disk.
Actually, that's blank.
I've got the disk.
I've got my own security pass.
And I've got the authority
to have you thrown out of here.
Sabrina. Honey, come on.
After all
we've been through!
Just do in your heart what you know
I would do if I was in your position.
Okay.
Sam, stop!
I don't want to hear.
I'm not interested in Vargas any more.
I'm off the story.
- Peterson, too?
- No, no, no. She's still on it.
You know, the girl is nuts!
- She went undercover
as a Chess tour guide.
- You're kidding!
I'm serious.
She got a job there.
Pete, look, look, there's more
I wanna tell you, okay?
No, Sam, don't tempt me!
I'm not gonna get killed on a story
where I don't even get the girl.
I'm goin' back on my book tour.
I'll be in Seattle by dinner.
In a few hours, this whole thing
will be a distant memory.
Okay, don't worry about it, buddy.
And good luck on the tour.
Thanks for everything, man.
You need to have a little chat
with your personnel director.
Sabrina Peterson's
working at Chess.
Oh, Jesus.
He ain't gonna help us.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
We hope you have enjoyed
your tour, and remember,
no matter where you may live...
Chess Chemical is your neighbour,
striving for a better tomorrow today.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Does this plane have a phone?
Straight ahead on the
cabin wall, but you really need
to stay in your seat, sir.
- We're about to take off.
- Okay, thanks.
- What city, please?
- Uh, Madison. The number
of the capitol building.
- That's 555-4331.
- Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we'll be taking off momentarily.
Flight attendants,
please prepare for departure.
- Good evening. State Capitol.
- Yeah, Sam Smotherman.
Mr Smotherman.
That's extension 307.
Keep it movin'.
Keep comin'.
Fine. Hold it right there.
Okay.
- How you doin', Jack?
- Okay, Bob. How are you?
Jesus! God!
What are these...
Oh, Jesus!
Too bad. But a definite "A"
for effort, Peterson.
Or should I call you Brackett,
Mrs Brackett? Hmm?
I don't really care what
you call me, Smotherman.
Or should I call you
Ernesto, Mr Vargas?
Oh, darn!
I wanted to be the one
to tell you.
You did!
A cop once told me...
"Always look for the lie; that's when
the story begins to unravel."
When I asked you
what year you graduated,
you gave me two different years.
I wondered why, so I looked
you up in your yearbook.
Funny thing was, you weren't in it,
not under the name Smotherman, anyway.
We were hoping you had what
we were looking for, but...
since you don't have it,
and we don't have it...
we can assume
it didn't survive the crash.
So now the only evidence
to destroy is you.
Oh, and your husband,
of course.
Fortunately,
we know exactly where he is.
- What's going on, Ted?
- Oh, Mr Chess, I didn't know
anyone was in here.
We've got an alert
down at the loading dock.
- Go back to your station.
I'll deal with it.
- Yes, sir.
Get out there.
See what's going on.
How'd you get involved
in this, Sam?
Willy wanted to get rid of Beekman, and
he thought you could get the job done?
- Something like that.
- But you botched the fire in college.
- What made him think
you'd get it right this time?
- I was the only bad guy he knew.
Did he pay you to hook up
with Senator Robbins?
Think I could afford
steak dinners if he didn't?
Do me a favour, Peterson.
Sit down.
Stay with her,
and watch her.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
It seems...
It seems we've got a traffic jam
in the parking lot.
I'm in no rush. As long as
we've got a couple of minutes...
What?
You want an interview?
Why not? Give a dying girl
her last wish.
Why'd you do it, Willy? Why not just
admit LDF was a flop and move on?
For ten years, Beekman and Hervey
promised me they'd iron out the kinks.
A hundred million dollars later,
they apologized, said they were wrong.
By then it was too late.
I mortgaged our company's future
in this thing. It had to fly!
What were these kinks,
exactly?
Well, let's put it this way. You can't
put a label on a carton of milk:
"This product has been known
to cause cancer in laboratory animals."
- And Beekman was gonna blow the whistle.
- Can you imagine?
The guy screws up and then
he tries to bite the hand that
feeds him? Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
All right, that's it. I've had it.
Just get her out. Now!
- Willy, let's go.
- Where's he gonna take me, Sam?
- At least tell me how
he's gonna do it, huh?
- No comment.
Another train crash?
Another fire?
Hey, maybe I'll get it the
old-fashioned way like Danny Brown.
Come on, Sam,
you're the organ grinder here!
Tell me how this ape's gonna do it.
- Why not just show her, Mando?
- Brackett!
Brackett.
You got her? Just get her.
Stop shooting!
Lock the gates.
Don't let anyone in.
Peterson, I thought
you were one of them!
It's okay.
I'm all right. I'm fine.
What'd you come back for,
Brackett, me or the story?
- Mostly you, Peterson.
- Mostly me?
He's on the third tier!
Nice try, Mando.
Drop the gun.
Why? Are you going to shoot me
with your finger, Brackett?
There's only one way
to find out.
Any time you want to jump in,
Peterson.
- Thank you!
- You're welcome.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, Jesus!
My mother always said, you want
the job done right, do it yourself.
Whoa. Whoa.
- Peterson!
- Self-defense classes.
A must for a woman in the '90s.
Uh-huh.
- Stay there or I'll shoot.
- I don't think so.
Think again.
Mrs Brackett,
you had it all the time.
Uh-uh-uh.
Don't touch.
Hey, Pete, do you mind
if I kill your wife?
As a matter of fact, I do.
Hang on, Peterson!
Grab on!
I got it! I got it.
Atta girl.
"As Vargas shouted
his final command...
the Thin Man's eyes
measured Peterson for a coffin.
She turned, a breath away from
the barrel of his.22 automatic."
Poetry, sweetheart.
Absolute poetry!
Look who's talking. "The cold metal tip
of the pistol brushed against my hair.
I looked up at the assassin. His eyes
were empty as two holes in a mask."
Honey, I got goose bumps!
You ever think
of writing a novel?
And give up the newspaper game?
Never.
Okay!
Well, I might give it a try again.
Here's my idea.
- Mmm.
- Male, female reporters
solve mystery...
- fight,
- Mm-hmm.
- make up, fall in love...
save the day,
go on a honeymoon.
Sounds like a best-seller
to me.
- Darling.
- Yes, my love?
You didn't really mean it when
you said our scoundrel days
were behind us, did you?
They are for me
if they are for you.
All right. I promise
to go straight if you do.
I do.
Then I do too.
Brackett, get this!
- Two guys with.38s coming right
out of that, uh, that bank.
- Peterson.
Peterson, sweetheart.
We're on our honeymoon.
Sorry, baby.
It slipped my mind.
Let me refresh
your memory.
Uh-uh.