After his appalling first round,
he won't survive the cut.
What on earth are they
going on about?
Ted Ray's just broken
the course scoring record.
By Jove,
Ray's tied for second!
Mr. Ouimet?
One question, sir!
Francis!
Hey! I thought you'd
gone back to college!
I thought you quit playing!
- I guess I changed my mind, huh?
That's wonderful!
- Yeah.
It's great to see you.
Can you come tomorrow?
I have to leave tomorrow!
- Come back tomorrow!
Are you his caddie?
Give this to him, would you?
For luck.
Dames. Who needs 'em?
Fine play today, Mr. Ouimet.
Thank you, sir. You too.
It's mostly dumb luck, though.
On my part.
Not on your part.
You don't need luck.
I need luck.
Well, good luck, then.
Thank you, sir.
I cleaned 'em good.
Wiped the grips too.
You did just fine
out there today.
You too, Francis.
You gonna be able to skip
school again tomorrow?
Let 'em try and stop me.
All right,
well, you get home safe.
Hey, don't you worry about me.
I'll meet you right here.
Early bird gets the worm.
Deal.
All I can say, ladies,
is that when the day began,
I scarcely imagined
that I'd find myself
tied for the lead with
the immortal Harry Vardon,
and two strokes ahead of
the ever-so-capable Ted Ray.
Ah. Speak of the devil,
and up he pops.
Excuse me, ladies.
I'll be with you presently.
I simply adore Americans.
The exuberance,
such charming naiveté.
How do you find them, Ted?
I should imagine
you feel right at home.
They clasp all manner of the huddled,
yearning masses to their bosoms.
Even the lowly golf professional.
You know, I can foresee a day,
given their democratic standards,
when they invite your kind
into their clubhouses.
Well,
how could they resist?
Two poor lads from Jersey,
up from nothing.
Working-class heroes
to the great unwashed.
When all Jersey's ever given us
are potatoes and dairy cows...
Don't look over there.
Sorry, Harry.
I couldn't contain myself.
Neither could he.
He shouldn't have
brought Jersey into it.
My God. My nose.
Do I look all right?
Quite frankly, Mr. Reid,
it's an improvement.
So, did you really
see the President?
He waved at me.
No.
Yes, he did. President Taft.
- Can you believe Francis?
Why don't I sleep
downstairs tonight?
No. You sleep upstairs.
You'll need your sleep for tomorrow.
- I'm OK.
Oh! Arthur.
So, they call you Mr. Ouimet.
The others,
it just says their names.
Well, Father,
they're professionals.
I'm an amateur.
Let's have some dessert.
No, wait, wait. Sit, sit.
They're all talking
about you now.
It say here that if you win,
you get no money.
The others make money,
you get nothing.
What does that prove?
They don't even pay you!
What kind of work is that?
Arthur.
- What?
I'll fix you a plate.
Come on, you! Pull!
Morning, Harry.
Dreadful English weather.
How'd you sleep?
- Like a baby.
Woke up every two hours and cried.
Hey, Francis!
I had a dream last night
that you shot a 72!
Yeah? It won't be easy
in a nor'easter.
You've played this course
in weather like this.
You're right.
It's a good day for a 72.
Okeydokey,
pipe and smokey.
If the Brits beat us, they'll say
it was a fluke I ever won it.
They'll say it's their game,
and we're not good enough.
This is our Open.
Yes. Marvelous.
Ouimet. Ouimet.
O- U-I-M-E-T.
He's only one stroke behind Vardon
and Ray after three rounds.
Move it!
Put your backs into it now!
Go a little deeper there!
There we go.
Not here. Over there.
Watch that end go through!
And move on down!
- Yes, sir!
Thank you.
Ray needs that putt
for the lead.
I don't want to hear how
anyone else is doing.
We play our own game.
Where do we stand?
You'd still have to par the last
five holes to tie Ted for the lead.
Dreadful conditions, Harry.
No one would blame you
if you came...
Thank you, Bernard.
He's done for in there.
No chance he catches him now.
Whoa!
What's got into you, old thing?
You had to go
and get me angry.
Oh, yes. My mistake.
When I par this one,
we'll have to go at it
again tomorrow.
A playoff? What a bother.
Yes, but there it is.
Never seen you smoke
on the job before.
Should've started
four holes earlier.
Ah, all square again.
Not a chance
this stripling bears up.
Probably not.
Let 'em look.
We're tied, and you're
the one still playing.
Might as well get out of this
beastly New England weather
and raise a glass
to British victory.
What's that carrying
his bag, a Pygmy?
We need two strokes.
One here, one at the 16th...
Francis, don't think so much.
You can't play 'em all at once.
You gotta take 'em
one at a time.
One at a time, two down.
Two down, six to play.
I can get one here
and another on 16.
That girl wanted me
to give you this.
What girl?
- Sarah.
Sarah gave you this?
Just put it on.
Don't get all sloppy over it.
To England.
What the hell was that?
It's not over yet.
Well, well.
Look who's back.
Nice.
- Nice shot!
Let us through.
It's Ouimet's mother.
What's happenin'?
He hit it stone dead at 16.
He's only down one.
What does that mean?
Is it good?
If he makes this, it's a playoff.
Dear me, it's almost beyond
one's ability to calculate.
Ah, don't mind if I do.
He can't keep this up.
It's impossible.
I'll be damned.
Yeah!
Oh, Francis!
There will be
an 18-hole playoff tomorrow
between Vardon, Ray
and Mr. Ouimet
to decide the Championship.
That boy's a gift
from the gods.
They're printing 'round
the clock at home.
Cripes! Imagine what
they're selling here.
Should have bought one of these
rags when I had the chance.
It's a bold charge,
but he's spent his powder.
It's a two-man game now,
my lads.
An all-English final.
Well, we'll see.
Come on, Harry.
It's inconceivable.
The man's a bloody amateur.
When was the last time
you were beaten...
Have you ever been
beaten, man-to-man,
in your entire career
by an amateur?
Amateurs do not win Opens.
Hell, the last one
who won it back home
was 40 years ago,
and he was a gentleman.
This one's nothing of the kind.
He's a peasant. Common clay.
He'll fold like an accordion.
I need my rest.
If he couldn't hit the ball
a country mile, he'd be digging ditches.
Where are you going, Harry?
Sit down with me.
Eat with me.
Enjoy yourself.
I came here to win a trophy.
On the face of it, Ted Ray
or I should carry it off.
Not for you, not for England,
but for bloody pride at being
the best. That's why we do this.
And if Mr. Ouimet wins tomorrow,
it's because he's the best,
because of who he is.
Not who his father was,
not how much money he's got,
because of who he bloody is!
And I'll thank you
to remember that.
And I'll thank you to show the respect
a gentleman gives as a matter of course.
Good night.
Do you want him to fail?
Is that the only satisfaction
you can take from what he's doin'?
You think I want him
to break his heart?
What will you do,
Mary, when he fails?
How will you help him then?
All you ever do
is encourage him.
That's right.
I do encourage him.
He has a God-given talent,
and this is his one chance
to give a voice to it.
He's just tryin'
to make you proud.
"It seems impossible to believe
that this untested boy
could hope to beat
two seasoned champions. "
One David against two Goliaths.
He'll have to face
Vardon and Ray alone,
with a night to sleep
on the incredible situation
in which he so shockingly
finds himself.
Although, I suspect,
from the unearthly calm
he showed today,
he will sleep
better than most.
I am not certain I believe
Ouimet can win,
but I have given up
all attempts at prophecy.
I will start tomorrow's round
with an open mind.
It should be
the greatest game ever played.
Young man.
We've been talking this over.
Talking what over?
The members feel you need as much
help as you can get out there today.
What kind of help?
- According to the rules,
your caddie is the only person
who can give you advice.
You need someone with you today
who really knows our course.
Exactly.
- Eddie's doin' a great job for me.
For God's sake, Ouimet!
This is the U.S. Open,
not some junior
club championship.
You told Eddie this
before talking to me?
Oh, you can't reason
with a boy like that.
We'll take up a collection
for him and pay him handsomely.
I understand
his family could use it.
Don't let 'em do it, Francis!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Is it true? You know
I can't pay you, Eddie.
I wouldn't do it for ten bucks.
I wouldn't do it for a hundred!
Hey, listen.
You think I'd replace you?
But they said you'd want to.
Who cares what they said?
Who cares?
This is me and you.
We're a team. OK?
They don't get a vote in this.
All right?
I'll meet you outside.
Don't ever talk to my caddie again.
Mr. Ouimet will play first.
Mr. Darwin will act as honorary
marker and keep your scores.
Gentlemen, it's time.
Here he comes!
- Good luck, son!
Come on, young man!
- Come on, Ouimet!
Come on, Francis!
Come on!
Give us a strong show, son.
Five for you there?
- That's right.
You can do it, Francis.
What?
- Wha... Sorry.
Did I say something?
That was big.
They're human.
What's that?
I can play these guys, Eddie.
Yeah? Who said you couldn't?
Oooh!
Maybe they're not human.
This is where he fell
apart the last time.
That was yesterday.
Sarah!
What are you doing here?
You're supposed to be in school.
Don't be ridiculous, Father.
He's not cracking, Harry.
The thought
occurred to me.
"An all-English final. "
Quiet, please.
Stymied.
What are you doin'?
- I'll show you.
Come on, now. Finish him.
Let's see if he cracks now.
Fore right!
He's dead in those trees.
Mid iron.
Done in by the monarch
of the forest.
Down to you, old thing.
I'm done.
Pity. It's a great match.
That's the spirit, Harry.
Come on, Ouimet.
Where you going with that?
Gonna cut the corner.
- There's a bunker down there.
If he's over it,
he's a chip away.
We don't know he's over it.
It's a trick.
This is
our chance, Francis.
Run it in there,
just like yesterday.
My God. Francis has
a one-stroke lead with one to play.
Hold the line, please.
Hold the line!
Take your time.
Let me have that towel, Eddie.
Well done.
You need this for 72.
You can do it.
Read it, roll it and hole it.
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Thank you! Thank you!
You did it!
- Thank you!
Look, Eddie, we did it!
We did it!
No! No! I can't take it!
Pass the hat for Eddie!
Pass the hat for Eddie! Here!
Pass the hat for...
Well played, Mr. Ouimet.
That was a great game.
I enjoyed it.
So did I.
Yes, you did.
Congratulations on your success.
You deserve it.
Thank you.
We'll play again sometime.
Look at this thing.
It's a whopper.
- Isn't that something?
They let you take it
home with ya?
Nobody's tried to stop me.
Well, they'd have to get past me.
You know somethin', Eddie?
You and I are gonna be
great friends.
You said it, Francis.