BALL
& Chain
Hey, you got a safety pin?
Why would I have a safety pin?
Oh, good God.
This is easy as hell.
Ready? One, two, three.
It's gone, ladies. Where'd it go?
That was so cool.
- Yeah, I know.
Hey, listen. I'm having
a party this weekend.
Yeah?
- Yeah. You should come.
Hey, I need a pin. Somebody have a pin?
Please?
What am I supposed to do with this?
It's all I got.
People, people, people!
It's show time!
Relax, Ameet.
- It happens to the best of us.
It didn't happen to you, so shut up.
Oh, hey, Ameet, look.
I found a safety pin.
You want it?
- It's not that funny, big boy.
Don't count on me for tomorrow.
Bobby's big day, huh?
I think it's pathetic.
I'd lose my pants any day not
to have to go through that.
Ruby Chandra, huh?
Yeah, why?
Poor you.
What's that supposed to mean?
You never exactly met her, have you?
No. That's kind of the point.
What? What's wrong with her?
What's wrong with her?
She's fine, man. I don't know.
In a unique kind of way.
Go see what she looks like.
No.
Come on, Ameet, help a brother out.
Please?
Okay.
Hi, Auntie.
- Hi, Ameet. How are you?
Hi, Uncle. How are you?
Hi.
This is Ruby's mother.
This is Saima.
Isn't she beautiful?
Well?
Bobby? It's time.
Hi.
Whew.
Hey.
Oh, hell no!
No!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
No.
Sorry.
Whoa, whoa! What the hell are you doing?
Did you see that thing?
She's a wildebeest!
Do you hear that shit? I can't
live with that the rest of my life.
You got to go back and apologize.
- What?
I'm not saying you should marry her,
but you can't leave her like this.
Watch me.
I'm sorry. I'll talk with him.
What the hell is going on?
I got this under control.
You can just turn around.
I don't think so.
That's my best friend down
there crying like a baby.
Wildebeest!
- Would you please leave?
Good idea.
I'm supposed to be Sleeping Beauty!
Hey, roll me out of here.
- No.
Please? Please?
- No. No.
Please?
- Shut up.
Can you believe it?
- No.
Cheers.
You idiot!
Saima, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to--
Ameet, this is the ladies' room.
Is there anything I can do to help?
Yeah. Get out.
Are you sure there's nothing I can do?
Get out!
What's the matter with you?
- Mom.
It's just a spilled drink.
- Did Ameet do this?
It was an accident.
On behalf of my son,
please accept my apologies.
That's all right.
- That boy.
I don't know how he can survive
without a woman in his life.
What?
Okay, okay.
Yeah, hi. Okay, okay.
Momm!
Aah! Ow!
Hurts?
- Yes!
So we got married.
I didn't get a honey moon, of course.
I got a nurse.
Hi, honey.
Hi, honey!
Yeah, hi.
- Hold this.
Oh!
All right.
Oh.
Thank you.
- Poor baby.
Little chips for my honey.
You want some more of this?
Thank you.
My baby.
I can't believe Bobby
got trapped like that.
See ya.
- Where are you going?
Out.
Don't be late.
Where are you going?
- Out.
You should concentra te on your studies.
It's Friday night.
After so much hard
work. You are in medical.
Why you want to ruin that opportunity?
Papa, it's just one night.
Hey, you work now.
Tomorrow we are taking
dinner with some friends.
You also come. It'll be your layer time.
You enjoy then.
But, Papa, what about Dave?
Is he also taking dinner tomorrow?
God bless you, God.
Oh, God.
Damn!
Why are you always in heat?
Because I know what I want, girl.
Look at that ass.
Hey!
- Aah!
Hey, Saima.
What's with her?
What happened to you?
Hurricane Ameet.
Huh?
Where is everybody?
Hey.
No.
What's your problem?
You are.
Take it easy.
I would if you'd stay away from me.
Why can't you just leave me alone?
Can't you see, I can't stand you.
I don't want you around me,
and I'm sick of you
spilling shit all over me.
What?
Drink?
I found out where everyone went.
They left.
What?
I can't find them, and
their cars are gone.
Great. And how am I
supposed to get home?
You...
I...
Tomorrow you're coming with us.
You're going to take dinne
r at a friend's place.
You be ready.
Come on, Deep.
You gotta play better
D if you want to win.
Play defense with your
feet, not like Bobby.
I wish Bobby could play with us.
He will... soon.
- When?
Four to six months.
Why does he have to be married anyway?
I don't know. It was
just his time, I guess.
Does he love Ruby?
- It's complicated, Deep.
Love is just a part of it.
- What is love?
Well, um, love is...
Love is when two people
care for each other so much
that they'd be willing to
do anything for the other.
Is that how Bobby feel s about Ruby?
Well, not yet, but he will... soon.
When are you goi ng to get married?
Ohh! Oh, God!
Ameet, are you okay?
What happened?
- No!
Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
I guess our parents hit
it off at the wedding.
So, Ameet...
I hear you are doing computer science.
Good profession.
Huh, Saima?
You know, Saima is doing medical.
I'm an intern.
Yes, yes, medical.
And...
Mom, I'm gonna go to my room.
Excuse me.
Saima, why don't you go
see if Ameet needs anything?
Mm-hmm.
Go, go.
She is quite something.
I told you so.
Come in.
What do you want?
Papa wanted to know
if you needed anything.
Is it me, or are your parents
acting kind of strange?
Yeah, actually they have
been acting kind of funny.
What's with them, huh?
I mean, I didn't know our
parents knew each other,
and then Papa sends me in
here to check on you and...
They'd never allow me to be
alone with a guy unless...
Oh, my God!
Ow.
Where are you going?
I'm leaving.
That didn't exactly work for Bobby,
and I don't think it's going to work
for you, not in your predicament.
Shit.
I'm not ready to get married.
- You? What about me?
I can't get married.
Not now and not to you.
Yeah!
Hey, what's wrong with marrying me?
Okay, wait.
There has got to be an
easy way out of this.
Our parents are reasonable people.
We'll just explain to them that
we're not ready to get married.
How old are you?
26. Why?
I'm 25. That's not going to work.
My father already
thinks I'm an old maid.
Well, we have to try something.
Okay. Okay.
Calm.
Reasonable.
Rational.
Calm.
Reasonable.
Rational.
This is an excellent match.
You are both getting good education.
Dad, we don't want to get married.
We're not ready.
I did not want to get married.
I was not ready.
Huh? -
Mm-hmm.
But it-- it all worked
out for the best.
But we don't love each other.
Forget about love. We
don't even like each other.
Why are you worrying about love?
I did not have any love
when I married your mother.
Ask her. Did I have?
No. But you will learn it.
You guys don't care about passion
or desire or any of that, do you?
You are thinking of romance, sho-mance.
You are seeing films and
all. It is not like that.
Hey.
- Hmm?
Please explain to them.
- Let me tell you.
It's very simple. You get married.
You will have your home.
- Correct.
You will be together.
Then you will have children and family
and love will come.
Don't worry, it'll come.
- Maybe 40 years.
It'll come automatically. Look at us.
It came after 27 years , but it came.
27, 45-- What is
the difference?
Yeah, I know, I know.
That's it.
You see?
So we're sitting in
his living room, right?
And his father is like bald
and I think he drinks too much
because he's got me
pinned in from this side
and my father comes
in-- - You're lying.
I can't do this.
Then let them know you won't.
I can't do that.
Run away. I've got some money saved up.
I can drop you o ff at the
bus stati on and you could--
I can't do that either. It...
It doesn't work that way.
How does it work, Saima?
They've always looked out for me,
and I know I'm going to get out of this,
but I just don't want to...
I don't want to upset them.
I just don't know how.
I don't understand.
It's not funny.
Hey, it happens to
the best of us, Ameet.
What do I do?
I am the last person you should ask.
Can I get you anything, Ameet?
Thank you, no.
By the way, congratulations.
Thanks.
So how are you guys getting along?
Well, it's really weird.
But she's nice.
You'll know soon enough.
Where are you going?
To the hospital.
Good, good. Go.
Saima.
I'm only wanting to give
you a secure future, beta.
Yeah, I know, Papa.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, Josh. How you doing?
I'm doing great.
- Great to see you.
I need to talk to you about something.
- Okay.
I'll catch you a little
later. I'm in a rush.
Okay, I'll see ya.
- See ya.
What took you so long?
Hey, don't snap at me.
We're not married yet.
If that's what you think it all about,
then I definitely don't want to be with you.
What is that supposed to mean? It's not
like you have any idea what it's all about.
It's about love, cooperation!
Shh!
Working together to live a better life.
It's about raising kids and teaching
them what's right and what's wrong.
It's about trusting someon e
with your innermost secrets.
It's about passion and fire and
emotion that you can just run away with.
That's what I think a
marriage is all about.
Aah! Aah!
Oww! Oh, God!Oh!
Are you okay?
- Shh!
I'm fine.
- Shh. Shh.
- Shh.
Owie!
Ow!
Feel any better?
I'm okay.
I'm, I'âm... Yeah.
- Huh?
Yeah. Oh, yeah. I'm... I'm peachy.
So, do you have a plan?
Huh?
- A plan.
Uh, yeah.
Of course I do.
A toast to the happy couple.
Let us celebrate this union.
Not only a union between two people,
but a union between two families.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
It is my greatest pleasure
to have Saima join our family.
Welcome.
I also would like to say a few words.
I just want to take this
opportunity to thank you all
for setting me up with
this wonderful woman.
She's smart...
witty...
and, oh, so hot.
What do you think you're doing?
What? You are my woman.
The hell I am!
How wonderful. A lovers' quarrel.
Lovers'  quarrel.
What? No.
It is not funny.
- Yes, it is.
No.
I can't even have Bobby and the
rest of my friends over anymore.
And I can forget about a bachelor party.
It's over. Totally over.
Oh, no.
By the way, what was the
deal with that glass of wine?
Payback.
Fair enough.
At least I got a kiss first.
Oh, I'd say you got
a bit more than that.
You liked it.
- Nah.
Did you?
Dream on.
So what do we do now?
About the kiss?
No, about getting out of this, jerk.
I don't know.
Hey. What's up, yo?
Hey, sweetie.
You're looking better there, tough guy.
Yeah, I got a smaller cast
so I can use crutches now.
What happened to your face?
We'll talk about it later.
Uh-huh. -
Long story.
Your mole.
I had it removed.
Oh, you look beautiful.
Thanks.
Ready?
- Okay. Ready?
One and go!
Thank you.
That's awesome, guys.
Isn't he great?
- That was great.
Are you thirsty?
I'm thirsty. Margarita time!
Oogie boogie boogie!
So, how's married life treating you?
You know, it's actually not so bad.
She's kind of okay now that
I'm getting to know her.
Really.
I got to admit, I didn't think
you guys were a good match.
Well, it was weird,
but... he's opening up.
So it's all working out.
No, I didn't say that.
She still does a lot of stuff
that really pisses me off,
but I'm assuming I do the same thing.
That's great.
So it's working out?
Yeah!
It's all right.
Get out.
- No.
I just never expected you
to say anything like that.
It's been like a week now.
- I know, I know.
I've seen him naked now.
Hey, baby.
Hey.
How's it going?
Hey, man.
What's your problem?
Nothing.
Just thought the lady might
want to hang with a real man.
Thanks for the offer, but
I'm already with a real man.
Really?
- Really?
Yeah, really.
Well, when you change your
mind, I'll be over there.
Eww!
Drink?
What?
- Nothing.
Nothing.
I didn't ask.
- Oh.
Hey, listen.
What?
I meant to ask you.
Are you seeing someone?
Why?
Just curious.
Well...
Actually...
- What? You are?
No. Are you?
No, no.
No.
Hey.
You know, my dad u
sed to tell me stories
about these Indian princes
and how they'd ride to
their weddings on elephants.
I always dreamed I'd go to
my wedding on an elephant.
Like a prince?
Yeah.
You think it's silly?
No.
I think it's romantic.
Hey, guys.
Peanut?
What's up?
- You work here?
Yeah, part-time.
Monty here is gonna be a veterinarian.
Really?
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, he didn't want to, but
he figured it was the only way.
to stay close to his girlfriend
in the gorilla exhibit.
Oh, ha ha ha.
This guy, huh?
Yeah, listen, I actually got to
get back to her. She's lonely.
Cool. Say hi to wifey.
- See you guys at the party.
When are you going to
find me a nice girl?
Ameet.
I was wondering. if
it is possible for us
to broadcast the wedding
on this, um, Internet...
so our relatives in India
may share in our joy.
Sure, we can do that. No problem.
No problem? Excellent. Excellent.
You know, this Internet.
Well, actually, there is one problem.
What is that?
May I have your attention, please?
I'd like to take this
opportunity to say a few words.
I just want to tell all of you
how blessed I am
that Saima and I will be together.
She really has brought out
the passion in my heart.
Saima has shown me
what it really means
to be true to myself.
As a result,
I would like to announce
that, with Saima's blessing,
I'm quitting my job to pursue my dream.
I gotta dance!
Go, Ameet! Go, Ameet! Go, Ameet!
What are you doing, son?
This is a total disgrace.
I tell you, this marri
age cannot happen.
My daughter will nev
er marry some dreamer.
Papa?
- Don't worry.
We're just leaving this place. Come on!
Come, come. Don't
even look at him. Come!
Shit.
Hey.
You were great last night.
Yeah?
Well, my parents weren't too pleased.
I'm sorry.
- That's all right.
They'll deal with it.
What's this?
Yeah.
I thought we'd celebrate our breakup.
Come on.
Okay.
This one time, a couple years ago,
I went out camping with the guys.
We found this spot way out,
right by this beautiful lake.
Anyway, everybody was all
passed out from drinking
the night before.
So...
I decided to go for a swim.
You know,
right there,
at that moment,
in the cool water with
not a care in the world,
I felt something.
Something I...
never felt before...
or since.
This... right here...
This is the closest I'll
ever get to that feeling.
To us.
Or... not to us.
Whoa!
I can't believe we got away with that.
You were good.
Whoo!
Oh, my.
Ameet!
Ameet. Ameet?
Huh?
What are you doing?
Saima!
Saima.
Coming.
Come. Sit here.
Listen, I don't want you to
worry about that awful fellow.
Ameet? He's not awful at all.
Do not say his name. I will
not hear it in this house.
I'll find a new husband for you to love.
No dreamers for you. Not at all.
I'll get an upstanding fellow.
Doctor. Maybe... engineer.
Trust me.
I will take care of everything.
I will.
But, Papa.
Good morning, Auntie.
Shoo!
You...
You are not welcome in this house.
But I
was--
I'm warning you. You
just go away from here!
But I was just--
- Just you go!
But I was--
You shitty fellow, yaar. Go!
Go inside!
Go inside.
Hey, Ameet, can I play?
Sure.
Nice shot, Deep.
Thanks.
Ameet, are you okay?
No, not really.
Why not?
Do you remember when I
told you what love is?
Yeah.
I was wrong.
Well, not really. Let's
just say I was a little off.
Oh, you mean like your jump shot.
Yeah, like my jump shot.
Then what is love?
Well, do you know how good you feel
when you do something right?
Like when I beat the bad
guys in my video games?
Yeah, a little like that.
Imagine feeling a hundred
times as good as that.
all day long.
Wow.
I know.
Pretty incredible, huh?
When you meet some one who
makes you feel as good as that,
then you'll know what love is.
Hey.
How are you?
Saima...
we can make it through this.
We just...
I just need to know
you want to be with me.
Of course I do.
Of course, but--
But what?
Papa's lining up men for me to meet.
There's got to be a
way. We could just--
He won't even let me talk about you.
Come here.
What's this?
Open it.
There's more.
Hmm.
I understand you are an engineer.
Uh-huh.
And then I got my second PhD
in electro nuclear physics.
"Hello. My name... is... Shili."
Can she cook?
Uh-huh.
"Uh-huh." That's all?
"Women find me... exciting."
You?
How about some tandoori food?
You don't diet?
Sorry about that.
Uh-huh.
I like tandoori food.
- Next!
And degenerative chemical manipulation.
Um, can she cook?
You live here in town?
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
Yes?
Yes. Hello?
Eating so much.
Eh?
Huh?
God.
"You... can... not... lose.
"I... am... the...
total... package."
Package?
What a package.
We don't deal in packages.
Carry on.
I don't know.
I'm not impressed. Not
a winner in the lot.
Cancel, cancel, cancel.
Stupid.
God, send me some husband material,
not animals, okay?
Send me someone good.
Some... some eligible...
Namaste.
- Namaste.
Asshole.
No, um, Ashol.
Ashol.
- Yes.
A computer programmer.
Yes, sir, I'm a computer programmer.
I have recently started my
own Web site design business.
Oh.
And, uh, why do you want to get married?
Well, I feel it's the
right time in my life
to start to work with someone
and build a life together.
Fine.
And, uh, what abou t your family?
Unfortunately, both
my parents have passed.
I'm an only child.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Would you like to meet Saima?
Sure. I'd love to.
Saima!
Come here.
Come, come, come, come.
Saima.
Ashol, Saima.
I would like for you to
sit and talk with him.
Come, sit.
Come. Sit.
And let me know when you are done, okay?
We're done.
- Ah, Saima!
Please, beta.
You know, Saima...
You're lookin' good, babe.
What are you doing here?
Looking for a wife.
Well, you've come to the wrong place.
I don't think so.
In fact, I think I've hit the jackpot.
Oh, nice ass.
Oh, the things I'm
going to do with that.
Oh!
Oh, yes.
Got to love that ass.
True happiness comes
when you love your wife,
you love your home and
keep your values intact.
Hmm?
Sir, I'm honored to have your
daughter's hand in marriage.
And I promise to devote myself to
providing her with a secure life.
I'm sure, I'm sure.
God bless you.
Okay.
Good night.
My dream boy. I got him.
Got him.
Ashol, my future
son-in-law.
But he's creepy.
What creepy-sheepy?
Such a nice fellow.
But, Papa, doesn't my
happines mean anything to you?
This is for your happiness only.
Did you hear the things he said?
Saima, where are you going?
I'm going to the library.
You really think I'm some fool?
I know you have been meeting
that fellow. I know it!
So you're not going out to study.
You're going to study at home.
But I-- - At
home, that's all.
Up.
Where's Saima's mom? I'm so confused.
Where has she kept my tea?
Saima's mom, where's my tea?
Ow!
Sorry.
What-- What are
you doing here?
I missed you.
Drop the dupatta.
You're crazy.
Yeah.
Saima?
Papa?
Saima, did you hear anything?
Like what?
Some... scraping?
No.
No?
I can't sleep now.
Can you go downstairs
and make me some cha?
Papa, why don't you take your medicine?
Okay, beta. I'll do that.
I'm old. My bones are weak.
But that's okay. You don't worry.
I'll make my tea.
No, Papa, I'll make it for you.
You'll make
it? - Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Some scraping...
Shh.
- But--
What's up?
Uhh.
Where's Ameet?
What happened?
Your father...
came after me.
Had to hide.
Aha!
Hey!
What?
Bye.
Stay away from my daughter!
Yourafka!
Stupid fellow.
Damn.
Did you see those things?
You know, you should get a boob job.
What? What's wrong?
Why are you doing this?
- Doing what?
Marrying me.
You know I don't love you,
and you know I never will.
me. You will grow to love
You can only resist
my charm for so long.
I can resist you forever.
Asshole.
Listen, you little bitch.
We're getting married.
If I say you get a boob
job, then you get a boob job.
You do what I say. Get it?
Ma'am, are you all right?
I'm fine.
- Bathroom's this way.
How do I get out of here?
Is there a back door?
- That's off-limits.
Where is it?
Ameet! Ameet!
Saima.
What's wrong?
He's awful!
Figured you'd go running back.
- You want a piece of me?
Just in case you don't understand...
Hey!
What are you doing? Wait! No!
Oh...
Are you okay?
- I'll live.
I can't believe this is happening.
What else could go wrong?
Well, um, I don't know
how to tell you this,
but they decided to move the wedding up.
What? When? Where?
Well, they already had the banquet
hall  reserved for you and Saima,
so they just kind of figured
they'd go ahead and use it.
But that's tomorrow.
- I know.
I'm helping Nadi with
the Internet broadcast.
It's her mother.
Oh, so you're helping them now?
Yeah. It's my wife's best friend.
What about your best friend?
Ameet, wait a minute.
Yeah, that's right. You
will come on time, huh?
That's very, very important.
Yeah. Of course, food is arranged.
Everything's arranged.
-Good, good, good.
Dev, see if Mom is ready or not.
Listen, that holy man
should come on time.
Yeah, yeah, he's very busy.
Just a minut e. Yeah, yeah.
Papa, please.
Is there any way for me to speak to Saima's
mother? Because you are confusing me.
Come, come.
Come.
Ah.
Now, tell me.
What is it?
Please. Don't make me do this.
Saima, it is all for the best.
But I don't love Ashol.
Beta, love will come.
Why do you kee p saying that?
Look at Ruby and Bobby.
Are they not happy and in love?
That's different.
How? How is it different?
Ruby wasn't in love with someone
else when she married Bobby.
Saima.
Saima, you're too young
to know what love is.
Ashol is a fine young man.
And he will give you security.
No, he won't.
There's something's creepy about him.
I don't trust him.
He'll take good care of you.
Didn't he take care of you
when that fool attacked?
But that's just it.
Ameet didn't
atta-- - Shh!
Go get ready. This
is your big day, okay?
Bobby, get dressed!
In a minute, honey.
Bobby, the wedding sta
rts in less than an hour.
I have to make sure the Internet
telecast works before we go.
Just give me a minute.
- Okay.
ted. Good. Let me check the search
engine to see if it'’’s lis
Okay, Saima's name comes up fine, and...
What's this?
What?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Call-- Call Ameet.
I'll get ready.
It's busy. -
Well, try-- Aah!
Bobby?
Ashol, my son!
I really welcome you to my family.
I welcome you.
A real welcome!
Ameet.
Do you love Saima?
Yes.
Then go and do something about it, son.
If she makes you happy,
she makes us happy.
Ameet!
Call Bobby on his cell phone.
He has something to tell you.
Bobby, we're gonna miss
the wedding!  Hurry up!
Coming!
Come on, Bobby! I'm
going to go start the car.
No! Don't start the car!
I'll be right there!
- All right! Hurry!
I'm hurrying, I'm hurrying!
Come on, Bobby! Don't do this to me!
Yeah, that's my baby!
Where have you been, man?
Just go.
Hi. How are you?
Fine. Very good.
Okay, ready, gentlemen?
We are starting the ceremony.
Here.
Beta, what's wrong?
I can't do this.
Saima, stop this nonsense.
I'm sorry, Papa. I love
you, but I love Ameet.
I can't do this.
Saima!
Just hear me out for one minute.
I don't need to spend the
rest of my life with you
to fall in love with you.
I don't even need to be
with you for a little while
to find out that you're kind of okay.
All I know is I spent most of my life
prophesizing about love.
And now I know what it is.
I feel what it is,
and I can't let go of that.
I won't.
Let me take care of this.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome.
If you could please turn your attention
to the screen in front of
you, that would be wonderful.
Thank you.
That's--
This is Ashol.
I'm your fantasy man.
Oh, my God.
This is Ashol.
Do you like what you see?
For as little as 19.95 a month,
you could see all of me.
What a perv, man.
- Ohh!
Come to papa. Who's your daddy?
Don't believe it, sir! They put
my face on somebody else's body.
Hey, asshole!
Yes!
- Yeah!
I'm sorry. I did not know.
Go. Go ahead.
Honey...
- What?
Come, come.
Nice ride.
My princess.
You know what's scary?
What?
I love you.
Now, what about you two?