I tell you,James, There's no
virtue if there's no immorality.
I met a waitress last night.
Big--I mean big
ol' butt on her.
A waitress with a big butt
doesn't seem so uncommon.
Perfectly uncommon.
Like 20 pounds of sunshine
in a 10-pound bag. MMM !
How's your wife?
Oh,she good.
The girls ?
They great.
Trip the alarm,will ya?
It's time to do this,baby
girl. Andele vamanos!
It's all clear.
Eight minutes. Not bad.
Gung-ho bastards.
Must be rookies. Ha ha.
Sid Vicious, Ottis Redding
Tim Bukelley and Karen Cochran.
Overdose,plane crash, overdose
and underdose.
Ten minutes forty.
The Battle of Chalons.
451 A.D.
Attila's defeat by Aetius.
Duck!
It's another false alarm.
Let's get out of here.
26 minutes
We've officially cried wolf
You know Mother Teresa
didn't believe in God.
No?
No
Watch your feet.
You're kidding, right?
Mother Teresa did not believe in God.
You can't say that !
She definitely questioned his existence
in some of her letters.
Are you guilt-reading again?
Listen
After she heard Jesus' voice
on the train to Darjeeling--
Allegedly.And if so,
she never heard from him again.
Well,I can see how she could doubt.
But not to believe ? I don't buy it.
Maybe she was faking it.
Faking it ?
Because we all know how much
fun it is to work with lepers.
Can we work now ?
Oh,I'm done.
Yeah,baby! Done a
trick. Done a trick,baby.
That's right,yeah. We did
it,baby. Who's the man now,huh?
Police! Freeze!
Put the gun down!
Put the gun down or I will kill him!
Get back!
I'll kill him.
I'll kill him right here.
Put it down,Lutha.
Put the gun down.
You bitch !
The Bloc Team Present To You Heist
How we doing,Bill?
Pretty good.
I got some of those self-help
tapes. You know, Personal Power.
I'm hoping it'll help me
with some of my weight issues.
You know,everybody
says "do more cardio,"
but my knees
just can't--
I meant how are we doing here?
Oh. Multiple alarms.
Hollywood division
responded three times.
Then logged it as an alarm malfunction
Good police work there,huh?
Anyway,uh,last alarm went off at 3:00.
Guy opened up at 9:00.
Point of entry-- the
sledgehammered door.
Point
of exit--
The sledgehammered door.
Bingo.
You got a list of the stolen items ?
Uh,item. Singular.
The owner... Gave us a picture.
It's an Incan talisman.
That means good luck charm.
Actually,a talisman is,
uh,used to ward off evil spirits
Just saying it didn't work, is all.
Anyway,it's valued at about eight grand.
What they didn't take was the
bracelet that was sitting next to it.
Which cost over 80.
Good work on the safe too.
Immaculate.
We're never going to solve this one.
A good cop would.
Right.
Keep  your enemies close.
How's it going,baby?
Never call me baby.
The name's Lola.
I'm Ricky. You hurt my upper lip. -I'm
here for the job. Not dinner and a movie.
I'm here for the job
Not dinner and a movie.
Look at this guy.
I ain't working with no mothball. -Ooh.
How's it going,baby?
I'm Lola.
They call me Pops.
Shall we ?
He hurts my lower lip.
Who are you ?
Who am I ?
I'm Gatsby. I'm freakin' Spartacus.
But my name,for your purposes, is James.
Never Jimmy.
Never Jim and never,ever,Jimbo.
James.
Hi,James. Where's the pisser?
Long  bus ride.
You're all here
because you are the
very best at what you do.
That being said, this job
is going to be dangerous.
Possibly  deadly.
But extremely lucrative.
How much we talking about,Mick?
Half a billion.
With a B ?
Yeah.
Welcome to Rodeo Drive.
Quite possibly
The most expensive three-block stretch
in the world.
Anything worth stealing can be found
right here.
It is also home to three of the
most exclusive jewelry stores
in the world.
So which one we gonna hit ?
All of them.
Whoa,whoa. Hold on,Mick.
I'm as horny as the next
guy for half a billion.
But how in the hell do you
plan on pulling this off?
Not how.When.
When ?
Tomorrow.
You're insane.
No. We go during Academy Awards week.
When the most expensive
jewelry on the planet
will be moving through these stores.
So where do we start ?
We'll need some working capital.
Ooh,a bank ?
No,dummy. We're going to take out
a small business loan.
Yes. A bank.
I'm just saying, your people
don't make good quarterbackss
What?
Your people. They don't
make good quarterbacks.
Now you're an idiot and a racist.
Vick,McNabb,
Culpepper,McNair--
How would you feel if I said
all Irish people were drunks ?
Well,we have to be, to
put up with the blacks.
What did you say?
Oh,I'm sorry. African Americans.
Billy--they want us
in the briefing room.
Good.
I think I made my point here.
Last night's jewelry store
robbery had no witnesses,
no prints,
no physical evidence.
I've asked Metro to surveil
a couple of stores...
-So did you call that girl?
-Yeah. She give you a wrong number? Yeah.
Is there something you
want to share,Detective ?
Maybe. Can I take my pants off
Hey! Wanna go two out of three?
Then shut your mouth and listen.
As detectives, you all suck,
okay ??
Got the job, got lazy,
and figured you could what?
Phone it in until your
pensions kicked in?
Well,that's done. Over.
Because bottom line is,
I'm not going anywhere.
So you better hurry up and
get serious about your jobs.
Otherwise I will kick your
asses straight out of RHD.
All right. That's all.
Evans and O'Brien.
Stay for a second.
Yes, Detective?
I'm making a partner change.
I want you working with O'Brien.
No. With him ? No.
Yes.
Let's see if we can get some better
chemistry going on in this division.
You know what? I want to go on record
as being strongly opposed
to this move,all right?
He's, he's lazy. He's
obnoxious. He's fat. He's racist.
I'm standing right here.
Request a transfer if you don't like it.
Now come on. Let's get to work.
This is just like Lethal Weapon.
Except I actually do hate you.
Who you supposed to be, Mel Gibson? Eh.
Pizza. -How you
doing,it's 17-- -Whoa,man!
Why you rob banks,Mick?
Because that's where the money is.
Grander scale.
Like instead of being a fireman
or a shortstop ?
Why not be a fireman ?
I don't like the hats.
Point the camera that way.
Four eyes in the sky
Two guards. One Social
Security,one in diapers.
Bulletproof glass.
Bullet resistant acrylic.
Only an inch and a quarter thick.
Everybody is cutting corners.
Ultimately how I turned out is
probably a product of my childhood
and my inability to believe in systems.
So...
You've given this some thought.
Sure.
Once I saw how things worked,
or didn't work,
the absurdity
of it all--
I guess I'm talking
about consciousness here--
robbing faceless, hegemonic
corporations seemed,
in a strange way, the right thing to do.
I'm speaking just for me.
Can you get the vault from here ?
I'm on it.
Have you ever tried a
non-authoritarian collective
like a Kibbutz ?
I  have.
It doesn't work for me.
Oh,no. Look over there.
I think it's time to leave.
What?
Why?
Well,it's a little warm  for a
giant parka. Don't you think ?
You saying
he's here--
Well,it looks that way.
Unbelievable. He going to
rob this joint before us?
That ain't right. Look,I'm
going to say something to him.
Let's not get caught up in this drama.
That's just rude,is all that is.
You're not calling this in.
Oh,hell yeah.
There's a bank robbery
happening right now.
California Financial at the
corner of Ventura and Reed. Hurry.
You're very competitive.
this is a robbery !
Everybody down !
I said everybody down !
You know,you really made
it more difficult on him
by calling it in.
Well,he should have
been more well-mannered.
Besides,we can get some
nice tactical footage
of our police friends in action.
Hey,hurry up,man!
Stop right there!
Now! I said stop!
Drop the bags! I said,drop the bags.
Drop the bags! I said,keep them up.
Well,that's that.
Let's get out of here.
Damn amateurs. Spoiling
it For everybody.
You know, I'm sick of these fools.
Maybe I shouldn't call it in.
This is awful.
Looks like a miniature golf course.
Hey,I got something over here.
You got something ?
Write this down.
Remaining eye, unresponsive.
Oh that's sick,man. I
ain't writing that down.
Why would this guy blow himself up?
What do you got, Doug?
Radio detonator.
Someone could have set it off by remote.
Cell phone,even.
He definitely did not
trigger it himself.
This  kid was no bank robber.
He was a hostage.
Mm-hmm. Thanks
You guys....
We're changing the file log.
From suicide to homicide.
Somebody else triggered the bomb
Yeah.
Find out who.
So,you hungry ?
Grab a bite ?
Tacos,maybe.
Man,you just finished picking an eyeballoff
the street. How can you even think about food?
Focus.
You--you-- not right
in the head,man.
Hi,it's me. Sorry I'm late.
Hi., She's in the other room.
She had a good day.
Great.
See you tomorrow. Thanks.
You've gotten more beautiful again.
I know you ?
You know me.
I'm your husband.
Of course you are George.
George was your first husband.
He died.
I'm Robert.
It was a lovely funeral.
Blue violets are my favorite flower.
I know.
Robert !!
When did you get here ?
Just now.
You haven't been getting into trouble.
No.
No trouble.
You know,for me, it's
not about the money.
It's about--
the thrill.
For me it's the money.
That's what I meant.
Like,the thrill of the money.
Like seeing it lying out on
the table in front of you.
Spread out,spilling out.
That is thrilling.
You're in it or the thrill,right?
Kind of
a thrill-seeker?
I'm actually quite calculating
That's what I meant. You
calculate your thrills.
You're thrilled by the money.
Like me.
So.....
I'm right.
You're an idiot.
Do you like music ?
'Cause I have made....
a perfect mix...
for this heist.
Great., A moron with a soundtrack.
It's okay.
I have extras.
I work out. Three times a week.
You should try four.
Okay. Set up the equipment in the trunk.
When ?
Now !!
Did you get it? ?
Got it
Did you see her naked ?
Yeah. We took a shower together.
Oh,that is so hot.
Let's see what this lady cop is into.
Visa
Mastercard
Driver's license.
I gotta get this back.
Start the car and keep it running.
I think I love you.
Excuse me.
Is that yours ?
It looked like it fell
out of your locker.
Thanks.
Sure. Have a good one.
What do we have on the cop ?
Pretty dull.
Mostly credit card debt.
Health club,restaurants.
A bit of a shoe whore.
I did find something.
Dancing lessons.
I'm going to check it out tonight.
Oh,I  got it.
You think it's smart to
show your face this early?
I said I got it.
Fine.
Chin up.
Uh,ma'am?
Ma'am.
I got to tell you, that was real slick.
I'm sorry. Do I know you ?
Store security. Please open your jacket.
I'm a cop.
And I'm flattered you go against
your oath as a peace officer.
However,taking an 8-pack of Gillette Daisy
razors is not a good way to meet someone.
Now hand over the loot,lady.
You're not store security.
No
But if I was, you'd have
a real problem right now.
You look familiar. eHave
I ever arrested you ?
Dance class.
Ah,yes.That's right. Dance class.
Just started. I,uh,I'm Mickey.
Amy.
So,uh,Amy the cop.
Why take the razors ?
Ever tried waxing?
Once.
Never again.
So,which is more fun?
The cops ? Or the robbers ?
I don't know yet.
Hey,Janey. How'd it go?
Sorry I didn't make it. I
really wanted to be here.
Didn't go so well,huh?
It's not that.
She thought she saw her father tonight.
Mickey ?
He's been dead seven years.
I know.
Let's just give her a little space.
Throw me the keys!
Sorry,Mick.
This is Detective
Sykes, Robbery Homicide.
I have seven reports from the
Cal Financial bank robbery.
The manifest report said there
were eight units on scene.
Can you find that missing report ?
Excuse me,Detective?
Thanks.
Um,I'm going to have to call you back.
Evans, O'Brian.
Another pizza delivery guy was
reported missing about two hours ago
That's what's taking so long.
Delivery was to a motel room.
The room was cleared out by the
time a black and white got there.
These guys are going again.
What do we got on the first bank?
Well,the bank received a large delivery
of money that Thursday night before closing
So I figured--
-We figure.
They hit it early Friday before the factory
workers had a chance to cash their payroll checks
It's close to freeway exits,
and it also gave them a location
where they got maximum
police on-scene time
It's eight and a half minutes.
Okay,I want you to find me
every bank that fits that profile
Work your sources. Somebody's going to
keep trying until they get this right.
What makes you so sure ?
They didn't get the money !
I have a feeling we won't
have to rob a bank after all
All the news reports said witnesses saw
him get out of the cab and into the bank.
The cab pulls away just before
the first cop car gets there.
Why ?
How would he know the cops are coming, and
why would he care? He's just waiting on a fare.
Unless that cab was
my man's getaway car.
Bingo.
Okay,
But what if the cab was stolen?
Already checked. Wasn't.
So if the cab is in on it, all we
have to do is get an address on him
and stake him.
Ricky and Lola are already on it.
So, why you tellin' me all this now?
'Cause you weren't here earlier.
I got a phone.
I mean,come on,Mick.I'm your partner,
I shouldn't be the last one to know.
You're right.
And I'm sorry,James.
Okay
Now I feel better.
We're not gonna hug.
Aw,hell no !!
So, do you ride horses ?
I hate horses.
Not talking about poneys.
Talking about full-growns.
Full-growns ?
What the hell is a full-grown ?
We are two blocks
from my ex-girlfriend.
Teresa. She broke my heart.
Hey,do you know what's
got a lot of protein ?
Walnuts. Do you like walnuts ?
Can you shut up ?
I'm just trying to get
to know you, that's all.
Wanna know about me?
I don't like people who talk too much.
Oh,me neither.
What else ?
I like craps, not blackjack.
White frosting, not chocolate.
Dogs,not cats. Length,not girth.
I like men, not boys.
Clapton,not Page.
Clapton,not Page ??
You out of your mind?
Did you even listen to my mix?
I like football, not
baseball. Tequila,not vodka and
And I always thought it'd
be cool to be an astronaut
Are you satisfied ? Now shut up.
Transmitting now.
Got it
You were right--
delivery guy,explosives.
Okay,let's go.
Come on, let's go
Check
Good,keep it coming,straight.
That's it, old man.
Keep it coming,grandpa.
Five feet... STOP !!!!
Nice, did you steal this?
No,I won it in Bingo.
Just get to work, stupid.
I got it, I got it.
I don't got it, I don't got it
This ain't gonna work,
it needs to be quick.
I got an idea.
How that's gonna help?
Titanium. Stronger than
steel, light as a feather.
You just bought this.
These are the two banks
that fit our profile.
I want extra units in both areas. And I
want SWAT no more than five minutes out.
Even if we do find the right bank,
how do we make sure that our
pizza guy-- Keeps his toppings?
We contain and follow.
Evans,I want you to be liaison
between the divisions on this.
You got it.
Come on, big boy.
Hey. Hey! Everybody,
this is a robbery.
Do what I say, or everybody dies.
Yeah, no, we're on it.
Detective. A guy wrapped in explosives
just walked into Bank National downtown.
All units,robbery in progress.
Bank National.Bomb squad dispatched.
Yeah
It's going down.
Time to grab some cash.
Ricky,we're moving.
Umf--so,am
I.
Where have you been ?
You got a walkie ? Thanks.
What did you do ?
Look what you've done.
Cedars-Sinai Hospital. Hurry
please,my father's sick.
Off duty, get out.
It's my heart.
Get out !!
He's on his last leg,
move ! Get out,now.
Get out.. -Get to the back of
the cab. All the way to the back.
Open it.
Now get in there. -Ooy.
Lola is so hot.
Good to go.
Hi-yun-ken.
Flag your cab,Mickey.
Keep banging, and I'm
going to set you on fire.
Drive around the block again.
Oh,God. Get out of the way!
Get out of the way !!!
Subject exiting opening one.
Sharpshooters,hold your fire.
Please don't shoot.
I'm supposed to be in a cab.
Do not approach,do not shoot.
Go,Pops,go.
Here comes our boy.
Don't
shoot--
I'm supposed to get in a cab,
please. Let that cab
in. Let the taxi through.
Air support,keep a visual on the
yellow taxicab in front of the bank.
Roger that.
let's roll.
Hi,I'm Ricky-- I
mean,Eduardo. How are you ?
Oh,I'm going to have that
bomb off you in no time,okay ?
Pops,uh,I mean, Ricardo ?
I don't--I don't know if it's the red or the
blue. It's the blue, it's always the blue.
Well,last time it was
the red. Blue damn it,blue
I'm going red.
I said blue, damn it,blue
!! You want to kill the kid ?
Ooh! The kid lost his load.
I'm sorry,man, I always
wanted to do that.
You must be real excited to be riding in
the front of the squad car for a change,huh?
You know,just-- just keep it-- You know
I can actually hear you getting fatter.
Suspect is stopped.
Everyone stay behind.
All right, here we go.
10,000 for you,old man.
Now,give me your driver's license.
Come on,come on. It's
a terrible picture.
Now,I saved your life, so keep your mouth shut.
And,uh,we know where you live. Okay? Buh-bye.
Don't worry,kid. This'll be over soon.
Clear. Okay,here we go.
All cars stay in close behind us.
Do not give them a reason to detonate.
Get back behind, back behind !!
They won't blow up the money.
But they'd have to be able to see.
I have seven reports from the
Cal Financial Bank robbery.
Seven reports, eight units. Can
you find that missing report ?
They're in one of our cars.
22-5 on 3,
22-5 on 3 !
Why's she want us to switch
to secure channel three ?
I don't know, power trip ?
18 Denny 1 on 3.
We have suspects in one of our units.
Repeat,we have suspects in one of our units.
Air patrol,keep a visual on the cab.
Everybody else,on my
count, slam on your brakes.
Ready ?...3,2,1, now !!
Taxi turning,proceeding
southwest on Olympic.
Let's go, get 'em up!
You, you, follow the cab. Yes,ma'am.
Get out of the car, show
your hands,nice and easy.
Get 'em up, get 'em
up. O'Brien,over here.
Get out, get out of the car.
Where's the detonator ?
The detonator,find the
detonator. -Here it is.
Got it. Secure.
Pull over in front of the big rig.
keep the change.
Detonator has been found,stop taxi
and apprehend suspects immediately
Driver,stop the engine and
step out of the vehicle.
Get those hands on top of your head.
Step back, step back. On your knees.
Clear. Check the trunk.
Clear.
Detective Sykes, it's not the right
cab. I repeat,it's not the right cab.
What do you mean it's
not the right cab ?
There's no money, no kid,no bomb.
Big Up To The Bloc Team
Next Episode on Wednesday March 29
2006 nammed "Sex, Lies, and Vinny Momo"