At the beginning of the 21st century,
the Umbrella Corporation...
had become the largest commercial
entity in the United States.
Nine out of every ten homes
contain its products.
Its political and financial
influence is felt everywhere.
In public, it is the world's
leading supplier...
of computer technology,
medical products and health care.
Unknown even to its own employees...
its massive profits are generated
by military technology...
genetic experimentation
and viral weaponry.
All Umbrella staff must wear
their identity tags at all times.
All radiation badges will be collected
at 5:00 p.m. this afternoon.
Thank you! God!
Some people.
Yeah.
- Don't show this to me.
- Why not?
Because I'm busy.
It's nothing. Fire drill.
- What is that?
- Fire drill.
- Shit!
- Hey, what the hell is going on?
- Get the computers covered! Move it!
- Damn it, I'm trying!
The experiments! Move them!
Shouldn't the doors
open or something?
It's supposed to take us
to the nearest floor.
What's happening?
Line's dead.
- What's the problem?
- The doors won't open.
- What about the ones at the back?
- Locked as well.
There's no fire here!
No fire!
- The code doesn't work!
- No fire!
- "What's wrong with you?"
- "The door won't open!"
And this water
isn't going anywhere.
- What?
- It's a sealed room.
- Help me with the door!
- Oh, fuck the doors!
We have to get out of here.
What's going on?
Has this happened before?
We have to get out of here.
- We have to get out of here!
- Take it easy.
- You take it easy!
- Quiet!
What is that?
Oh, my God.
Halo!
Stop it!
Stop it! Stop!
Help!
Let me see.
We're going to have to get out of here.
We have to get out of this building!
Here, give me a hand.
That's as far as they'll go.
They're caught on something.
That's wide enough.
I can squeeze through. I'll get help.
I'm stuck.
You're gonna have to push.
That's it.
A bit more.
What was that?
Oh, Christ!
It's the brakes! Get out!
- I can't move!
- We have to get out of here!
Push her out of the way!
Pull me back inside!
Hello?
- Who are you?
- Move!
Don't touch me! Stop!
- Get away from me!
- Down!
What are you doing?
I'm a cop!
I told you, I'm a cop!
You're breaking my arm!
Report.
Report now.
What?
I want your report, soldier.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Sir, the house's primary
defenses have been activated.
She's probably still suffering
the side effects.
What are you doing with us?
What about the cop?
Matthew Addison.
I'm not getting a match.
Who are you?
I just transferred. They probably
don't even have me on file yet.
The locals are inefficient.
It's possible.
Should I secure him here?
No. We take him with us.
You can't do this!
Blow me.
Prep for entry to the Hive.
Power's down.
- So fix it.
- I'm on it.
Are you done yet?
Jumpy.
Stand clear!
- You got a problem?
- How's that door?
- It's sealed shut.
- Let me.
Jumpy?
Lie still. Lie still!
Watch this light.
Follow it.
- Now, how many fingers am I holding up?
- Three.
Good.
Now tell me your name.
I don't know.
He's fine. Memory loss,
just like the other one.
Let's open that door.
Listen to me. I want to know
who you people are...
and I want to know
what's going on here.
Now!
You and I have the same employer.
We all work
for the Umbrella Corporation.
The mansion above us
is an emergency entrance to the Hive.
You are security operatives
placed there to protect that entrance.
What about this?
Your marriage is a fake.
Just part of your cover
to protect the secrecy of the Hive.
And what is the Hive?
Show them.
Accessing schematic of the Hive.
Raccoon City, nearest urban center.
The mansion where we found you...
and through which we gained
access to the train...
which, in turn,
brought us to the Hive.
The Hive itself
is located underground...
deep beneath the streets
of Raccoon City.
A top-secret research facility...
owned and operated
by the Umbrella Corporation...
the Hive houses over 500 technicians,
scientists and support staff.
They live and work underground.
Their research
is of the highest importance.
Its nature is classified.
Our position on the map
is indicated by heat signature.
Why can't I remember anything?
The Hive has its own
defense mechanisms...
all computer-controlled.
A nerve gas was released
into the house.
"Primary effect of the gas"--
complete unconsciousness
lasting anything up to four hours.
Secondary effects are varied,
but can include acute memory loss.
- For how long?
- Subjective.
An hour, day, week.
So you're saying
this place was attacked?
I'm afraid things are
a little more complicated than that.
Sir! We've breached the Hive.
J.D.
Got it.
Halon content has dissipated.
Makes it easier to work underground,
thinking there's a view.
Looks like we're taking the stairs.
- Status.
- Red Queen is locked onto us.
She knows that we're here.
Who's the Red Queen?
State-of-the-art
artificial intelligence.
She is the computer
that controls the Hive.
This is gonna slow us down.
Our route to the Queen
takes us straight through these labs.
Rain, J.D., see how bad
the flooding is.
Kaplan, find us
an alternate route.
What happened here?
Five hours ago,
Red Queen went homicidal.
Sealed the Hive
and killed everyone down here.
-Jesus.
- When we realized what was happening...
my team was dispatched
to shut her down.
Why did she do it?
That we don't know.
But outside interference
is a possibility.
Jesus!
Hey. You okay?
- Here.
- No.
- I'm fine.
- Please, come on.
It's cold in here.
Are you--
Do you remember anything
from before this?
No. Nothing before the train.
And you?
No. Nothing.
I found an alternate route,
but it's gonna cost us time.
We double back,
cut through Dining Hall B...
then we're right on track.
Sir, no go.
The whole level's flooded.
All right,
we're behind schedule.
So let's move it.
Come on.
Poor bastards.
Dining Hall B.
That's what it says on the map.
Maybe you're reading it wrong.
Maybe the corporation's
keeping a few secrets down here.
Something you're
not supposed to see.
J.D., you and Rain keep the prisoner
here and secure the exit.
Sir, halon levels
are nonexistent in this room.
I think the system malfunctioned.
All right.
There may be survivors.
Give me a search line,
but keep it tight.
Move it.
- I said keep it tight.
- Sorry.
I'm not sure I want to remember
what went on down here.
I don't blame you.
What do they keep in these things?
How do I know?
What's taking so long?
Red Queen's defenses are in place.
She's making it difficult.
Let's pack it up.
You stay here.
The lights are automated.
Nothing to worry about.
- Transmitter in position.
- "Roger."
Running the bypass.
Checkmate.
Move up.
- What is that?
- That's what will shut the Queen down.
Delivers a massive
electrical charge.
Scrambles the mainframe
and forces it to reboot.
Some kind of dormant
defense mechanism.
- Opening the door tripped it.
- "Put it back to sleep."
Working on it.
- Would you open that door now, please?
- I'm trying.
Hold your positions.
Everyone stay calm.
What's that?
- Kaplan, quick!
- We gotta get them out of there!
- Kaplan, you've gotta hurry!
- Come on!
Down! Get down!
- Look out! Something's killing them!
-Jesus! Come on, man.
Don't do this to me!
Medic! Medic!
- Open the door!
- Open this door!
- I am trying.
- Stay conscious.
You're going into shock.
Stay awake!
- I am almost there.
- Sir! It's coming back!
- Open the door!
- I'm trying!
Well, try harder!
It's coming back!
Oh, God!
-Just do it!
- I'm almost there.
Come on!
- Shit!
- Got it.
All right.
Let's do it.
Do what?
We have to complete the mission.
There is no way
I'm going down there.
Her defenses are down.
Dj vu, anyone?
Keep going.
Give me a hand.
Get out! Get out!
You can't be in here.
Don't listen
to anything she says.
She's a holographic
representation of the Red Queen.
You have to get out!
Modeled after
the head programmer's daughter.
She'll try to deceive us,
confuse us.
I wouldn't advise this. Disabling me
will result in loss of primary power.
She'll say anything to stop us
from shutting her down.
I implore you.
- Implore away.
- "Please?"
Please?
You're all going to die down here.
That pulse forces the circuit breaker to
shut down her mainframe for 30 seconds.
After that, if I don't have
her board, she can reboot.
They're late.
I'm on it.
J.D., we got a survivor!
It's okay.
We're here to help.
You seem to be in some serious--
Get off of me!
J.D., get her off of me
before I stab her ass!
Are you okay?
She bit me, man.
She took a chunk clean right out of me.
Stay down.
I'm warning you, stay down!
She's crazy.
Come any closer, and I'll fire.
I mean it!
Damn you.
I shot her five times.
How was she still standing?
Bitch isn't standing now.
- What was all the shooting?
- We found a survivor.
- And you shot him?
- She was crazed. She bit me.
She's gone. She's gone!
That's bullshit!
She fell right here,
but she's gone!
Look, look at this.
There's blood,
but it's not much.
Looks like it's coagulated.
- Yeah.
- It's not possible.
Why not?
Because blood doesn't do that
till after you're dead.
Can we go now?
We're not going anywhere
till the rest of the team get here.
- There's no one else coming.
- What the fuck are you talking about?
Wait.
Quiet.
Fuck!
Don't come any closer!
They're behind us.
Jesus!
They're everywhere.
They're all around us.
I said stay back!
Why aren't they dying?
Watch the tank! The tank!
- Let's go!
- Hurry up!
- Wait!
- Come on, let's go!
- Move!
- Keep moving! Come on!
Move!
I can help you get the virus.
I have access to security codes,
surveillance plans, the works.
Shit!
- We lost the others!
- Keep moving!
- You waited?
- Didn't know the code.
Come on, come on.
- Shit!
- Come on.
- Hurry up.
- Come on, man.
- Shit!
- What's taking so long?
- I'm trying!
Come on.
- Move! What's the code?
- Hurry up!
I'm running out of ammo!
Zero, four, three, two--
No, five!
- What?
- Zero, four, three--
- What is the code?
- Zero, four...
zero, three, one...
nine, six, five.
- Got it?
- See how easy that was?
- Shit!
-J.D., no!
Grab my hand, man!
Come on!
Don't let go!
-J.D.!
- Rain!
Where are the bodies?
Where did they go?
Fuck!
Whatever they are,
there's too many of them out there.
Whatever they are?
It's pretty obvious what they are.
Lab coats, badges.
Those people used to work here!
All the people working here
are dead.
Well, that isn't stopping them
from walking around.
Well, where did they come from?
Why didn't we see them on the way in?
When you cut the power,
you unlocked the doors.
You let them out.
We're never gonna make it
to the surface.
You are security operatives.
Security operatives placed there
to protect that entrance.
I've got one in the breech
and an extra mag.
Lisa?
I can help you get the virus.
I have access to security codes,
surveillance plans, the works.
But?
- "But there's gonna be a price."
- "Name it."
- Who was she?
- My sister.
Corporations like Umbrella
think they're above the law.
But they're not.
There are hundreds of thousands
of us who think the same...
all over the world.
Some of us provide information...
others give their support.
Some take more direct action.
Like you.
If your friends had been
a little more thorough...
they would've seen
right through my false I D.
Then all the red flags
would've gone off--
Quantico, NSA, ViCAP,
all the rest.
There's no way
I could've infiltrated the Hive.
So you sent your sister.
We needed something concrete.
Anything to expose Umbrella
to the press.
Proof of the research
that was going on down here.
What kind of research?
The illegal kind.
Genetic.
Viral.
My sister was going to smuggle out...
a sample of the virus
they were developing.
So how was she
going to make it out of here?
She had a contact within the Hive,
someone I never met.
They had access to security codes,
surveillance, everything she needed.
So why didn't she make it?
Maybe she trusted
the wrong person.
Maybe they set her up.
Kept the virus for themselves.
Do you know how much the T-virus
would be worth on the open market?
- What, worth all this?
- Yeah.
To someone.
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
- Close that door!
- They're right behind us!
Get off!. Get off!.
Stop it!
Son of a bitch!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Right behind us.
What about this door?
- They're waiting out there too.
- And that way?
It's a dead end. There's no way
out of the Queen's chamber.
So we wait.
If someone doesn't hear from you,
they'll send backup or something.
Right?
What? What's wrong?
We don't have much time.
You know those blast doors
we passed...
on the way in from the mansion?
They seal shut
in just under an hour.
If we're not out of here by then,
we're not getting out.
What are you talking about?
They can't just bury us alive down here.
Containing the incident
is the only fail-safe plan they had...
against possible contamination.
And you're only telling us this now,
when we're trapped...
half a mile underground?
We have to find a way
out of this room.
What are you doing?
- Where are you taking those?
- I'm turning her back on.
- That is not a good idea.
- She'll know a way out of here.
That homicidal bitch
killed my team.
may be our only way out of here.
Considering the way she's being treated,
I'm sure she'll be happy to help us out.
That circuit breaker
you were talking about.
- Can you bypass it?
- Yeah.
So do it.
All right,
circuit breaker is disabled.
This time if I hit the switch,
she won't be able to shut down.
She's gonna fry.
Kaplan?
The initial charge
must have damaged her boards.
Ah, there you are.
Things, I gather,
have gone out of control.
Give me that fucking switch right now.
I'm gonna fry your ass.
I did warn you, didn't I?
Tell us what's going on down here.
Research and development.
What about the T-virus?
"The T"-"virus was"
a major medical breakthrough...
although it clearly also possessed
highly profitable military applications.
How does it explain
those things out there?
Even in death, the human body
still remains active.
Hair and fingernails
continue to grow.
New cells are produced...
and the brain itself
holds a small electrical charge...
that takes months to dissipate.
"The T"-"virus"
provides a massive jolt...
both to cellular growth...
and to those trace
electrical impulses.
Put quite simply...
it reanimates the body.
It brings the dead back to life?
Not fully.
The subjects have
the simplest of motor functions.
Perhaps a little memory.
Virtually no intelligence.
They are driven by
the basest of impulses...
the most basic of needs.
Which is?
The need to feed.
How do you kill them?
Severing the top of the spinal column
or massive trauma to the brain...
are the most effective methods.
You mean shoot them in the head.
Why did you kill
everybody down here?
"The T"-"virus escaped"
into the air conditioning system...
and an uncontrolled
pattern of infection began.
The virus is protean...
changing from liquid to airborne
to blood transmission...
depending on its environment.
It's almost impossible to kill.
I couldn't allow it
to escape from the Hive...
so I took steps.
- Steps.
- "You must understand."
Those who become infected,
I can't allow you to leave.
Whoa. We're not infected.
Just one bite, one scratch
from these creatures is sufficient...
and then you become one of them.
A check of my systems indicates
my main drive circuit breaker...
has been disabled.
May I ask why?
Insurance.
We need a way out of here.
If you refuse to help at any time,
we flip the switch.
Understand?
After you.
What the hell is this place?
The utility tunnels.
They run underneath the Hive
for water, gas and power lines.
- It's been in here before.
- Keep moving.
-We're going around in circles.
-This is the route the computer gave us.
- Why are you listening to her?
- Enough already!
We have no choice but to keep moving
'cause those things are right behind us.
That mesh isn't gonna hold.
Keep moving.
Jesus Christ! Hold it!
There's too many of them!
-Jesus!
- Fuck!
Up on the pipes.
Up on the pipes!
Quickly, everyone!
- Let's go!
- Come on! There's a way up!
Watch out! Keep 'em back!
Go on up! Move it!
Shit. Okay.
Get over here! There's too many of them!
Come on! Go, go, go!
Go on!
Go! Go! I can manage!
Gotcha!
Rain?
Rain.
What?
We have to do something
about your wounds.
I'm fine.
I said I'm fine.
You like that, don't you?
Huh?
You like the way it tastes,
don't you?
Like the taste of that?
She was right.
We're all gonna die down here.
No. We're getting out.
All of us.
Kaplan, are you okay?
Oh, God!
Hold on!
- Help him.
- I can't.
- What are you waiting for?
- I can't focus!
I can't see!
- Kaplan, go up!
- Get up there!
You almost got it.
Keep going!
- Come on! Come on!
- You can do it!
You got it!
- Okay, Kaplan.
-Just stay there!
Hold on.
We're gonna come get you.
Cut this wire and throw it to him.
Then we can go get him.
Hold on!
That's lucky.
I want you to go.
- We're not leaving you, Kaplan.
- Yes, you are.
You can't kill all of them.
And I'm not going anywhere.
I want you to go. Now!
Please.
Just do it.
Just do it now!
Please.
Go!
You're gonna have to work
for your meal!
Come on.
Give me your arm.
Up over my shoulder.
Ready? There we go.
When I get out of here...
I think I'm gonna get laid.
Yeah. You might want to
clean up a little bit first.
Hey, wait.
Are you okay?
Blue for the virus.
Green for the antivirus.
- There's a cure.
- What are you talking about?
There's a cure.
The process can be reversed.
There's a cure!
You're gonna be okay!
I was beginning to worry.
This is where
they kept the T-virus.
How do you know all this?
Because I was gonna steal it.
I was your sister's contact.
- You betrayed her.
- I don't know.
- You caused all of this.
- I can't remember.
The truth.
I don't remember the truth.
I don't understand!
It's gone.
It's not there.
I can't.
I just can't.
It's over.
I can help you get the virus.
I have access to security codes,
surveillance plans, the works.
But there's gonna be a price.
Name it.
You have to guarantee me that
you will bring this corporation down.
Spence?
Thank you.
We can still make it out of here.
Come with me.
We can have everything
we've ever wanted.
Money's out there waiting.
You wouldn't believe how much.
Is that how you thought
all my dreams were gonna come true?
Please.
I wouldn't want to shoot you.
Might need the bullets.
Back off.
I won't take any part in this.
Okay, but you can't just...
wash your hands of this.
We work for the same company.
You knew what they did.
I was trying to stop them.
You really believe that...
people like him...
will ever change anything?
Nothing...
ever changes.
Where is...
the antivirus?
It's on the train...
where you found me.
Couldn't have been standing
more than three feet from it.
I so nearly made it out.
Didn't realize that bitch of a computer
had defense systems outside the Hive.
In or out?
In...
or out?
I don't know what we had...
but it's over.
Back...
the fuck off.
I'm missing you already.
Your boyfriend's a real asshole.
He shot the locking mechanism out.
I can't believe that son of a bitch
is gonna get away with this.
I don't think so.
I've been a bad, bad girl.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck is that?
One of the Hive's
early experiments...
"produced by injecting the T"-"virus"
directly into living tissue.
The results were unstable.
Now that it has fed on fresh DNA,
it will mutate...
becoming a stronger,
faster hunter.
Great.
If you knew it was loose,
why didn't you warn us?
'Cause she was saving it for us.
Isn't that right?
I didn't think any of you
would make it this far.
Not without infection.
Why didn't you tell us
about the antivirus?
This long after infection...
there's no guarantee
it would work.
But there's a chance, right?
I don't deal in chance.
Fuck it.
No pressure, guys.
You require
"the four"-"digit access code."
I can give you the code,
but first you must do something for me.
- What do you want?
- "One of your group is infected."
I require her life
for the code.
The antivirus
is right there on the platform.
- It's right there!
- "I'm sorry."
It's a risk I cannot take.
She's right.
It's the only way.
You're gonna have to kill me.
Otherwise we all die down here.
The glass is reinforced...
but it won't hold forever.
- Do it.
- No.
- Get up.
-Just do it.
- Rain, please get up.
- Do it!
- "You don't have long to decide."
- Get up, please.
- You have no choice.
- "Kill her."
Kill her now.
You don't have any choice.
-Just do it now!
- I can't!
- Please.
- "Do it."
- "Kill her."
-Just do it.
Kill her now!
Kill her!
The bitch wouldn't open the door,
so I had to fry her.
Move.
What the fuck was that?
It's a long story.
Start it up.
I'll get the virus.
I'm missing you already.
Okay, we're in business.
Full power.
We're leaving!
I don't want to be
one of those things...
walking around
without a soul.
You won't.
When the time comes...
you'll take care of it.
No one else is gonna die.
Okay?
Here.
I'm not dead yet.
I think I'll have that back.
I could kiss you, you bitch.
What's going on back there?
- Get us the fuck out of here!
- Any faster, we'll come off the rails!
Open the doors!
Now!
I failed all of them.
I failed.
Listen to me.
There is nothing else
you could've done.
The corporation's guilty here,
not you.
And we finally have the proof.
That way Umbrella can't get--
get away with this.
What is it?
You're infected,
but you're gonna be okay.
I'm not losing you.
Help!
Help him.
What are you doing?
Matt!
He's mutating.
I want him in the Nemesis Program.
Get off!.
What's happening?
Matt!
I want her quarantined.
Close observation
and a full series of blood tests.
Let's see if she's infected.
Take her to
the Raccoon City facility.
Then assemble the team.
We're reopening the Hive.
I want to know
what went on down there.
Just do it.
Who's in there?
Let me out!