I heard you interfering little bastards
rummage around my yard.
I'll thank you for keeping
the owls off of my cats.
You sleep OK?
Sorta.
I, uh...
(man) God, Jean,
I don't know what happened.
It's like a red mist or...
Something comes over me and I...
But I feel like you backed me up
in a corner and I...
You do that, and uh...
I hate it when I'm like that.
I'm sorry.
Can you forgive me?
What?!
Fuck!
(girl) You promised...
if it happened again...
You promised.
(woman) OK, this is last week
and up to yesterday.
- All right?
- OK.
- I stuck an extra 50 bucks in there.
- Kitty, I can't...
- You can. Listen...
- Here, just take it.
I don't wanna see you coming around here
anymore looking like this.
You take care.
Take care of that girl. Get going. OK.
(woman) We have a reciprocity
agreement with Kansas.
If you can stay in this shelter for a week.
- I could find you a place in Wichita.
- No.
Every man in town who beats a woman
knows where this shelter is.
Do you have someone you can stay with?
(man) I don't think you really understand
just how worried I am.
I don't know.
Maybe they went shopping.
I wish someone in this goddamn place
would just...
would just give me the truth.
Then we could find Jean
pretty damn quick.
(girl) Tribune, Kansas.
Do you wanna go there?
(Jean) Sure. Maybe. I mean,
we can go anywhere we want.
How about Loving, New Mexico?
- I like that.
- Me too.
Topeka.
Santa Cruz.
Oh, my gosh.
There's a Butt, Montana.
- It's pronounced "Bute."
- (car engine rattles)
- Mom?
- Oh, no. No!
(motorcycle approaches)
Hey!
She's not going anywhere.
There's a rod sticking through the block.
I'm heading to Sioux Falls.
Yeah.
Just take what you need.
So one inch is 83 miles.
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Aloha, Oregon.
It's only ten inches away.
So that's 830 miles
and we've already gone 300 miles...
We're going to Wyoming.
(girl) What's in Wyoming?
It's where your grandfather lives.
I have a grandfather?
Not much of one.
When were you going to tell me?
Oh, I'm fine.
Smells like rain.
It's not gonna rain today.
You haven't been right
about the weather since 1972.
I know what rain looks like.
You got something
on your mind this morning?
The goddamn bear's back.
Well, what do you think
you're gonna do about it?
What I should have done a year ago.
(growls)
Did anyone notice if he had cubs?
Did you see cubs with him?
(siren)
OK.
- It's under control, Einar.
- You get out of the way and it will be.
Come on, let's let
the Fish and Game take care of this.
This isn't some pet dog they're after.
I think they can tell
the difference, all right?
That says what
a college education gets you.
(man) Here we go.
(dart gun fired. Bear growls)
(car horn)
Mom.
Welcome to Wyoming.
Mom, this is us.
So is my grandpa nice?
Why didn't you tell me about him?
(Jean) Einar!
I don't want you here.
At least we agree on something.
I don't wanna be here either.
We need a place to stay
for about a month or so.
Looks like you need every part
of your head examined.
Is this yours?
She's yours too.
You telling me I have a grandchild
I don't know about?
I'm telling you
I was pregnant at Griffin's funeral.
Where you been till now?
We've been on the road for two days.
We lived in lowa.
Now this suddenly seems like home?
What's her name?
My name's Griff.
Griff Gilkyson.
That's an unusual name for a girl.
Einar, please.
Just till I can earn enough
to get us out of here.
There's a room in the basement.
I'm sorry.
Hey. I'm gonna go into town
and look for a job.
You think you'll be all right here?
All right, well, just... be good.
Love you.
(toilet flushes)
I used the bathroom.
I heard you.
- Are you hungry?
- Not yet.
Is there a McDonald's in town?
- You got five dollars?
- No, I don't.
Well, then I don't think going into town
for a meal would be a very good idea.
How was your night?
All right, I guess.
Left or right?
Let's do the right.
Left could use a rest.
(winces)
Pain bad all the time now?
Gets my full attention.
Yep.
What happened with my bear?
It's his own damn bear.
You telling me he's still alive?
He's fine.
He's in that zoo Angie built.
Dreaming about the sea last night.
- Did you get wet?
- (laughs)
I walked right in.
Felt like falling in love.
Smelled like a woman.
Tasted like one too.
Your memory's not that good.
Hey.
Down there.
See Jean kept her looks.
Said she brought her daughter with her.
She says it's Griffin's.
Granddaughter.
That's a nice thing for a man to have.
I might go into town for breakfast.
All right.
Taking the girl with you?
Anything else you need?
Yeah, look in on the bear.
- What?
- Check on the bear.
Check on the?
Why the hell would I do that?
'Cause I asked you to.
(door opens)
Are those my dad's things?
Yeah, they are.
Where does he live now?
He's dead.
Didn't your mother tell you that?
Yeah. But she said you were dead too.
Are you confused about why they call
a room with a table in it a dining room?
No, sir.
Since it looks like you didn't have
any trouble making that sandwich,
I'd like you to make another one at 11:30.
Will you do that?
- Yes, sir.
- And take it to that man in the little house.
And a glass of milk.
Yes, sir.
Bear? Goddamnit. (mumbles)
"Go check on the bear."
(engine fails to start)
(ignition fails again)
Goddamnit.
Nice wheels, Einar!
Where did you get the rig?
Nancy Sidwell had this shipped up from
that retirement village where Ernie died.
Maybe it was the bike killed Ernie.
What killed Ernie was
a lifetime of Nancy's cooking.
- Your pickup broke down again?
- Oh, hell, no. Pickup's fine.
I'm just out here training
for a goddamn marathon.
I like the flag. Without an orange flag
like that, you might look ridiculous.
- Hello, Ken, Catherine.
- Einar.
What have I got? Bills.
- Morning, Einar.
- Morning yourself, Nina.
Do you believe they're still
sending junk mail to my boy?
Well, maybe the dead are flattered
to get a letter. Ever think about that?
I'll let you know when I'm gone.
Maybe I'll send you a postcard
from the other side.
Hey, how's Mitch doing?
Mitch - he's dreaming about the sea.
Oh, yeah?
I used to live by the ocean.
Up in Oregon for about a year.
Yeah, too much rain if you ask me.
But I sure like the sound it makes.
- Grandma.
- What's up?
If you get depressed, pull up a chair
to your kitchen sink and turn on the tap.
If I ever get depressed,
remind me not to come to you for advice.
(laughter) Hey!
I wonder if it's hard being that drunk
this early in the morning.
Oh, it's easy if you
don't stop drinking all night.
- You'd know. How do you want your eggs?
- Scrambled.
Hey, there, boys.
What can I get you this morning?
Get down on this table and I can see if
I can stay on you till the buzzer sounds.
Agh! I hope you're
having a lot of fun, Chris,
'cause soon as I get one arm free,
I'm gonna kick your sorry ass.
Oh, now look
what you went and did!
Good morning, fellas.
I'm gonna be your new waiter.
Want some coffee?
- Why don't you screw off, you old bastard?
- What?
Son, now I don't wanna
work myself short of breath.
You wanna continue this?
It can be over all at once.
Because that's how goddamn fast
your life can change.
You believe me?
Sorry for the mess.
- Hi.
My name's Griff.
My name is Mitch.
That for me?
Thank you.
Yeah, I know.
I almost threw up
first time I looked at it.
You feeling a little queasy?
I'm fine.
OK.
I got queasy first time
I saw a man eat a snail.
- You ever eat a snail?
- No.
Me neither.
This looks good.
- What happened to you?
- I was mauled by a bear.
I saw a bear in a cage yesterday.
Yeah. That was my bear.
About a year ago, he was eating
one of your grandfather's calves
and... well, we sort of
interrupted his dinner, you know.
He thought we were
gonna take it away from him.
You know bears -
they don't like to share.
Did the bear bite Einar?
No, I was closer.
- I didn't know anyone ate snails.
- Oh, yeah, sure.
In those fancy restaurants
up in Cheyenne,
they eat 'em all the time
like there's nothing to it.
Once I saw this kid eat a moth.
- You could hear the crunch.
- Oh, no, no!
(growling)
(child) Oh, my gosh! Look at that!
(woman) Einar.
Hey, Angie.
I didn't expect to see you in this crowd.
I guess at my age it's good
to be seen just about anywhere.
Well, Fish and Game
said he'd settle down in a few days.
Of course, they also said
he'd eat anything, which he doesn't.
I don't get it. Nobody would pay five dollars
for the mountain lion I used to keep in here.
How's Mitch?
He's dreaming about the sea.
I always wanted a boat.
My dad used to take us out.
It was so great.
What happened to the lion?
He died.
Lucky lion.
(growling)
Hello, Griffin.
Well, it says here you might have
already won $15 million.
Probably ought to
send it in for you, though.
Probably the same damn odds
as losing a kid early.
You got that done.
You should know
your wife came back.
You could have steered her
someplace else.
Just 'cause you're dead
doesn't mean you can't be useful.
See you tomorrow, boy.
Kid sure looks a whole lot
like you, though.
Top to bottom.
(Griff) Mom!
- Hey!
- I missed you.
- Guess what. I got a job.
- Really?
I start tomorrow.
So how was your day?
Not so great, huh?
(hammering)
Man, I'm tired.
I think half the people we served
this morning came in just to look at you.
(Nina) Here you go.
- What's this?
- Your half of the tips.
I thought you said
you were used to being on your feet.
I'm not used to telling everyone I meet
where I've been the last ten years.
Well...
Tell 'em you went crazy.
Tell 'em you've been locked up.
That's what I've been telling 'em.
(Nina) Looks like we did real good today.
Guess I got you to thank for that.
Maybe I'll have some music
on Saturday night.
Of course, then again,
you'd have to dance with Billy and Wayne.
Oh, that'd be a sight.
Can I help you?
I'm Einar Gilkyson's daughter-in-law.
Yes, I know.
Did you want to come in?
Thank you.
- Any calls?
- Nothing.
Homemade lunch, you know.
You got something there
you want me to see?
It's a police report.
But I didn't press charges.
A shelter worker in lowa thought I ought to
check in with authorities when I got settled.
He was my boyfriend.
But, um...
The report's not for this time.
It was for another time.
I'll make a copy.
That's it.
What are their names?
- Who?
- Your cats.
They don't have any names.
How do you tell 'em apart?
I don't tell 'em apart.
Goddamn cheap-ass, Mickey Mouse,
foreign goddamn part...
Oscar and Charlie.
Hi, Charlie.
Is that there a water-pump belt?
Why don't you use the one
out on the tractor?
Why don't I use the one
Hey, are you mumbling
over there or something?
The tractor belt's twice this size.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Oh.
Don't we have some
spare belts in the barn?
I got a great idea.
Why don't you go back in the house?
Well, uh, damn. I was...
just trying to be helpful.
If you don't want my help,
I'll just sit over here and shut up.
Pulling that out, it don't look like
you know what you're doing.
Just shut up! OK?
Shut up. You don't know what I'm doing.
- You don't know about the truck.
- Who you talking to?
- Stop being a philosopher...
- Doggone second-generation immigrant,
I bet I come over there
and hang my bad foot in your ass.
(car horn)
- Thanks.
- Anytime.
- See you tomorrow?
- Yep. See ya.
- Hey, kiddo.
- Hey.
- How was it?
- All right.
- (Nina) See ya, Einar.
- Got some groceries for dinner.
OK.
- Do you wanna take these inside, sweetie?
- Sure.
- Got it?
- Yep.
- Hey, Mitch.
- Hey, there.
What happened here?
Why did you stop running cows?
When Griffin died, I ran out of help.
Then I got older, Mitch got mauled,
and I sold the stock to stay on the place.
Dinner will be ready in an hour.
Come here, Sarah.
Nope, stay here.
- You finished?
- Yeah.
Tell your kid to come down
out of that tree.
(Griff) Come on, Charlie.
Come on.
Don't be a fraidy-cat.
(plate smashes)
Oh, Jesus.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry, huh?
Well, that's just fine, then.
- I'll buy you a new one.
- Oh. Just that easy?
Maybe I liked that plate. In fact, maybe
that was my favorite goddamn plate!
- It's just a plate.
- That's it, huh?
Did it ever occur to you
that not everything can be replaced?
Come down out of that tree!
- You want this on the table?
- No, over here. Thank you.
I'm so glad you're back, Jean.
What happened to Nellie?
Nellie left.
About a year after we buried Griffin.
Einar just never got a handle on it.
And then, when he hardly
even noticed Nellie anymore, why...
She found another man.
Who wouldn't?
Think they live in Colorado.
Do you think he blames me
for losing his wife too?
I imagine he does.
I don't want to stay here.
What's wrong with him?
Well, it's not you.
He just never got over it.
He really loved your dad.
You should know that.
- Did you?
- Of course.
You do have a plan, though, right?
I mean, we don't have to stay here forever?
Sure, I do.
Soon as I earn enough money,
I'm gonna get us right out of here.
You know what?
What do you think about...
Butt, Montana?
Come on, let's play.
You don't know how to read anymore?
Where'd the bottle come from?
The granary.
It's been there for a while.
Sometimes I just like to look at it.
15, two.
You gonna open it?
I'm not sure yet. 25.
31 for two. Go.
- Did you check on the bear?
- Eight.
Yeah, you asked me to, didn't you?
Here's a pair for two.
I want you to feed him.
- What?
- I want you to feed the bear.
I don't trust Angie to feed
anything much past herself.
"Feed the bear." "Please feed the bear."
"Bear, do you like bear shoes?"
"What kind of food do you like, Bear?
Steak, chicken?"
- Einar.
- What?
Is her being here gonna ruin you?
- The woman killed my son.
- Oh, come on.
It was a car accident. They call them
accidents because it's nobody's fault.
No, they call them accidents
to make the guilty feel better.
- Is that so?
- I don't give a damn what they call them.
My son's dead.
Your granddaughter's not.
And neither were you.
Have you thought about
how she's gonna remember you?
You know, come to think of it,
I don't feel like playing cards tonight.
Put that bottle someplace
where I don't have to look at it.
You know anything about pickup trucks?
Aw, shit.
Hand me that half-inch
socket wrench, would you?
No, no, no.
Shiny one on the top.
Yep.
Do you wanna see what I'm doing?
That's it.
- OK, see these screws here?
- Mm-hm.
This one I'm tightening, this holds
this thing up which holds the pan up.
If this thing comes loose when you're
driving, you'll be sitting on the road.
And that's not what you want to be doing...
How come you and Einar don't get along?
You're practically his daughter.
What I am is his dead son's wife.
He's always been really good to me.
He's the first friend I met here.
I am not in the mood for their crap.
I'll take 'em.
- The special today is the enchilada plate.
- Thank you.
They're good enchiladas.
Served by good people.
I'm a good person.
I'm also a woman who's taken more
than her fair share of shit off men.
Don't push me.
I mean, I couldn't even take a pinch of crap
from two little cheesedicks like you.
- (Einar) OK, crank it.
- (engine fails to start)
Again.
(engine starts)
(engine revs)
Take your foot off the gas.
Take your foot off the gas!
Is that for lunch?
It's for a bear.
Who the hell knows
what a bear eats anyway?
Did I ask you to do that?
Don't bears like honey?
Winnie the Pooh does.
- Oh, hey.
- Thought you were sick.
Haven't seen you for a few days.
It's only a two-restaurant town, so I try
to spread the county's money around.
Meatloaf. Can I have onion rings
instead of mashed potatoes?
Onion... Sure, I'll ask.
Could you give me a ride home after work?
Sure.
(growls)
(Griff) He looks like he's dancing.
Well, maybe just happy to see
a girl with a sack of meat.
I'll give you some here.
Why don't you toss this in?
- He likes the honey.
- I think he does.
Is that really the bear
that hurt Mr. Bradley?
He's the one.
(Jean) I don't wanna go right home.
- Not just yet.
- You don't?
Can't we just drive a little?
Here's the thing.
I'm gonna be here about three more weeks.
I'm afraid I'm not gonna get through it.
Three weeks, huh?
I don't wanna be in love, Crane.
(moaning)
Don't start without me.
- (Einar) What's that?
- A flower.
That's not a flower - it's a weed.
It's pretty, though.
- Don't you think it's pretty?
- Yeah, I think it's lovely.
You want to wait a little longer
for your mother?
- Just a little bit.
- OK.
I had a music teacher
who was a lesbian.
You guys are gay, right?
(coughs)
I'd think after 40 years of working together,
one of us would notice, don't you?
Well, Einar, I always thought
you had really lovely hands.
- You did? You never told me that.
- (Mitch laughs)
I mean, it's cool.
Everybody needs love.
You got that part right, little girl.
(Einar) Jeez, what's next?
Hey!
- Hey, yourself. How you doing?
- Good. How are you?
Good. There's somebody
I want you to meet.
Griff, this is Sheriff Curtis.
Nice to meet you, Griff.
- Are you hungry?
- There isn't enough.
I gotta swing back
through town anyway. So I'll see ya.
- Thanks for the ride home.
- Take care of yourself, Crane.
- I don't like him.
- I don't remember asking.
I don't remember you ever asking me.
Hey, I don't need your permission.
You confused about how
to treat a guest in my house?
It's just some guy my mom brought home.
I expect you to be pleasant
to whoever comes to my door.
Yes, sir.
Unless it's some guy
looking to sell his angle on God.
There's no excuse for that bullshit.
Well, all right, then. Let's give a try
at these good-looking sandwiches.
There you go.
Hold it right about here.
OK.
- His foot's not gonna go anywhere.
- Oh, yes, it is. Look at that calf run.
He's off and gone.
(Einar) Oops. That's a little bit low.
- Yeah!
- I got it!
- (Griff) Look at that!
- Oh, yeah.
Go on, try it again.
There you go.
You got any more improvements
you wanna make around here?
I thought I'd
straighten some of this mess.
Thought Mitch might
want to work on something.
- Did you ask him about it?
- (Mitch) Well, of course she did.
Now that we've got interesting
company around here, I...
I feel inspired.
Excuse me.
I gotta go to work.
You wanna know
what I dreamed last night?
What?
I dreamed you weren't
such a miserable son of a bitch.
That's not dreaming.
That's wishful thinking.
Did you hear anything
unusual last night?
Yeah. Somebody poking around
down by the river.
I found some footprints.
This.
I sure do miss smoking.
So do I.
Hey.
Hey! What are you doing here?
- We're going to Angie's zoo.
- Really?
What kind of pies you got today, Nina?
Hey! I got three kinds of berry
and chocolate pecan.
Guaranteed to make your teeth ache.
Chocolate pecan, please.
With ice cream.
Two chocolate pecan, one with ice cream.
Kid's got young teeth.
Coming right up.
Be right back.
Crane.
Einar.
She capture your interest?
Have you thought about the girl?
They're a set.
Can I get you anything else, Crane?
No. Just the check.
OK.
How does the law stand on shooting
somebody on your property?
Well, if you didn't want to go to prison,
they'd have to be in your house.
- That's what I thought.
- You think you got a problem?
I'll let you know.
Hey.
You wanna hand me that rasp?
No, those are pliers.
The rasp, next to...
- This?
- That's it. Yep.
Are there really cowgirls?
Haven't you ever ridden a horse before?
No. There weren't any horses
around Gary's apartment.
He was my mom's boyfriend.
We lived with him for two years.
My mom had another boyfriend
before Gary.
His name was Hank.
He didn't have any horses either.
Hank didn't hit my mom like Gary did.
He was just mean with his words.
Like you.
I can see where not learning to ride a horse
would be a disadvantage for a cowgirl.
- You wanna try?
- Yeah.
Here, grab that blanket.
(Griff) What's that?
Wanna have a look?
Good afternoon, boy.
Your father was sure first-rate.
I miss him.
I wish I missed him.