When I was a little girl.
My family and I used to travel a lot.
Well. My parents did. Anyway.
I would only really travel
as far as Montana - the Big Sky Country.
Home of Evel Knievel.
Custer's Last Stand. And Aunt Edna.
Every summer my parents would
pack me up and take me to her house.
while they would go off
on one of their grand adventures.
It's not that I didn't like Aunt Edna.
It's just that all we ever did was make jam.
And then. when we were done...
we would make more jam.
It was during those long summer days
that I learned to love art.
I'd sit on the porch with my crayons
and create a new world.
One that helped me deal
with my isolation and loneliness.
When I was coloring. I was free.
Free to be anywhere I wanted.
Free from jam.
I drew the things around me
and saw the world with new eyes.
But I really longed
for someone to play with. To talk to.
I needed a friend.
And then one day it happened.
That was the day...
I met Sy.
( "Ready to Rain" by Leslie Mills)
I'm so good at flying away
Maybe I'm lucky
Playing my cards at 21
Breaking my heart
Oh well. I fell. what do you know?
Covered in laughter
Touch me again. And then again
Only for a while
Till you get so high
and you've had enough
And you make me swear
I won't give up
Sunshine's ready to rain
Like an ocean view when it isn't fair
Like a Super 8 out of nowhere
Sunshine's ready to rain
Oh man. what then?
Where do you go
When you stop wanting
Everything to fit perfectly
Just as you planned?
Stand back. Feel that bump in the road
Were you expecting
Time to remember you're asleep?
Only for a while
Till you get so high
and you've had enough
And you make me swear
I won't give up
Sunshine's ready to rain
Hey!
You can't move.
Sy!
- I can't resist any longer.
- What are you up to?
I've been working on my own art piece.
Ahh!
Hey, hey! You can't touch it.
This is a work of art, OK?
- This is your nose, your beautiful eyes...
- (door opens)
(both) Jess is home.
Abby?
Abby, are you here?
I need your help.
- This is ridiculous.
- I know, but she can't see you in here.
(groans)
- OK, just be quiet.
- Sorry. What about under the table?
Have you seen my nametag?
- Ryan told me I can't come back till I find it.
- You've lost it again?
I don't know what I ever saw
in that sniveling, slimy, no-good weasel.
- I believe it was his eyes.
- Hey, what are you working on?
- Nothing.
- Oh, yeah, right, like I believe that.
- Jessica.
- Come on, Abby, let me see it.
OK.
Oh.
- Sy?
- Mm-hm.
He's hot.
No wonder I never get to meet him.
OK, that's enough.
I'm telling you, it is time
you start showing your work in galleries.
- I don't know. I'm just not ready yet.
- Sometimes you just gotta take a chance.
You know what? Sounds like a great idea,
but I am late for school. Bye.
- What about my nametag?
- Use mine.
I tried that last week.
( "Satisfied" by Bus Stop)
Oh, yeah!
Few more days,
this baby's gonna be ready to roll.
- Congratulations, Cal. That's quite a feat.
- Thank you.
Now, how do you plan
on getting it out of here?
Through the door?
Good luck with that.
Oh, yeah, that's not gonna fit.
(man) Surrealism
can be expressed as a depiction
of the irrational state
of our subconscious.
What did Neiman say on page 52
of your reading about surrealists?
Come on. Anybody?
Please tell me
somebody read the assignment.
Miss Morrison?
Well, he said that surrealists
believe the dream state...
It could be just as relevant
as our waking lives.
Mm.
Yes.
They also construe that the universe
is only as real as it seems,
and sometimes things that feel
the most real are the least substantive.
Like these papers?
No, Mr. Andrews,
you weren't dreaming.
That is a real D.
(bell)
Please, please, do your reading.
Professor,
I think you made a mistake on my paper.
No, Mr. Andrews,
the mistake was when you took this class
thinking you had an easy Humanity credit.
I understand, but I really need this credit.
You should've thought about that
six weeks ago.
The D stands.
Well, not your finest hour.
I just don't get
this stupid pseudosurrealist crap.
It's not crap.
- What'd you say?
- I said it's not crap.
And how do you know?
Oh, A-plus.
Sorry.
I didn't know I was speaking to an expert.
Well, now you know.
You really need to work
on your people skills.
Ow.
This is the third time today, man.
Nick?
Do you understand
the meaning of "level"?
No, that's OK.
Why don't you come down and follow me?
I've got a job less complicated for you.
You have a wedgie, by the way.
I hate that guy.
- Here you go. Have a nice day.
- See you later.
Jessica's late again.
You told her not to come back
without her nametag.
- I did. Four hours ago.
- She's probably still looking for it, Ryan.
I like you, Abby. I do.
That's why I'm telling you this. I know
you depend on Jessica for part of the rent.
What are you saying? You're not gonna
fire her because she lost her nametag?
Look, nametags are company policy.
Besides, a patron is 76% more likely to talk
to someone with a nametag than without.
Look, you wanna save her job.
I understand that. Stay till she gets here.
- Why?
- We're short.
- Ryan, there's no one in the store.
- That's beside the point.
No. She works books. I mean, I work
coffee. It doesn't even make any sense.
- Are you arguing with me?
- No, I'm not. I'm just...
Ryan, look, tonight's my anniversary, and
I'm making dinner for my boyfriend, so...
I want you to go home.
I do.
But if your friend thinks she can come in
when she wants, someone has to cover...
- Are we clear?
- As mud.
Good.
I think all these should be straight. OK.
Excuse me.
Welcome to Borders... Oh.
You don't happen to carry
The Idiot's Guide to Art Appreciation?
I was told it has lots of pictures.
- It's in the juvenile section.
- That's good. It's even sort of funny.
So, do you wanna order
or did you just come here to annoy me?
Wow. OK. Uh...
Let me get...
the chocolate cheesecake.
OK.
Would you like a coffee with that?
To be perfectly honest,
I feel like you might spit in it.
- That's clever.
- You don't like me much, do you?
Hm.
It's funny, I thought you were slow.
"Abigail."
That's a weird name.
It's Abby.
So, have a nice day.
- Cheesecake?
- Yeah, right.
(whispers) Where have you been?
Your glasses.
OK, here you go.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Oh! Look, um...
One of these. These will work for you.
They're on the house.
No, it's... it's all on me.
Oh, gosh.
( "On a Day Like Today"
by Stephanie Pearson)
What is this I feel?
What used to be a dream
is now becoming real
Only yesterday it had no appeal
But I guess things change
Suddenly
The sky's a bluer blue
And full of possibilities
Suddenly
It's looking like it's gonna be OK
On a day like today
I could take a chance on someone new
I could fall in love with you
On a day
On a day like today
(phone rings)
Oh, no! OK.
Coming.
- Hello?
- I've got a crisis.
I don't like it
when you start off like that.
You know my cousin,
the one who just transferred here?
- Well, I don't "know him" know him.
- You're going to. He's coming tonight.
What? No, Jess, uh-uh...
Hey, I was wondering
where I could find a book on embroidery?
- Shh!
- What? Don't you work here?
Do I look like I work here?
He's not that bad, I promise.
It's just I wasn't expecting to see him
and I really didn't know what to say.
He mentioned
that we should get together,
and I sort of said, "Sure," you know,
because that's what you say,
and he's, like, "OK. Dinner tonight?"
And I'm, like...
You know how I am with the "no" word.
No! Jessica, no! It's my anniversary.
I'm making dinner for Sy. I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't have his new number.
Well, maybe I could, like,
walk around campus until I find him.
No. You know what?
It's fine, actually. Don't worry about it.
- He can come over?
- Yeah. He can come over.
- Bye. Thanks. Abby.
- OK. Bye.
Hi, Ryan.
Happy anniversary.
They're beautiful.
Oh.
- They're for you.
- Oh!
Thanks.
- They smell so good. Thank you.
- You haven't made dinner for me?
You know, you didn't need to do that.
Yeah. Um...
I didn't. I was going to,
but Jess called and said that she's gonna
bring her cousin over for dinner.
What, here?
- On our anniversary?
- Mm-hm.
I know. I'm sorry.
Well, I mean... No, no, that's fine.
I mean, no, actually, it's good.
It's... You don't mind?
Come on.
How could I be mad with you?
I can't. We'II... You know what?
We'll go and do something fun afterwards.
Yeah.
Yeah, we could go see a movie.
We'll see one of those romantic movies.
- You like gushy movies.
- I love it.
I know you do. Thank you.
Oh, it's somewhere.
Abby?
Jess? Jess, it's open.
I need... your...
help!
You know the only difference
between Ryan and the Pope?
The Pope only expects you
to kiss his ring.
OK, tell me what happened.
- I got fired.
- No, you didn't!
No! No.
He said that if I stayed he wouldn't fire you.
I don't know why you dated him
in the first place.
You know,
sometimes I wish I had a boyfriend like Sy.
Yeah.
He would never fire you.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I really needed that job.
Why don't you just get another one?
It's easier said than done.
Here.
You need them more than I do.
Oh.
Where did they come from?
- From Sy.
- Sy. Oh.
No, it's not like that. He's just not very good
at color selection, so I help him out a bit.
I don't think any guy I've dated
has ever given me flowers.
Ever.
Well, except Ryan the Superslut when
he cheated on me with that lunch lady.
Hey, didn't Ryan the Narcissist
send you flowers once?
Yeah. Only so he could hear himself
compliment himself for a week.
Besides, that's when I was still dating "I'm
still in the closet" Ryan, so it doesn't count.
I just don't understand. There are so many
guys. Why only date guys named Ryan?
It's my curse.
(rock music blaring)
Abby, could you get that?
I'm coming.
Turn it down.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
Come on in. I'm Abby.
Nice to meet you.
- She's just running a few minutes late.
- Oh, OK.
- Hi.
- Who's this?
- This isn't your cousin.
- He's not my cousin.
- (knock)
Excuse me.
Hey. I...
Megan doesn't live here, does she?
Next door.
Apartment 14.
- Right.
- Nice to meet you.
You too.
- Hey, brother.
- All yours.
- Hey, Jess.
- Hey, coz.
- Abigail, right?
- Abby.
- You know each other?
- We've met before.
- Really? When?
- We're in the same art depreciation class.
- And at the bookstore...
- Don't go there.
Go where?
Am I missing something?
- No.
- Yes.
- (Abby) Kill me now.
- Well, come in.
Have a seat.
- So, what's with the pajamas?
- Bad day.
OK, pajamas it is.
- I got fired.
- You what?
This egomaniac I work for
has had it out for me since I dumped him.
Let me take a guess. Uh...
- Ryan?
- You know him?
Let's just call it a hunch.
(music on car radio)
Gobble. Gobble. Gobble. Gobble
It's the turkey for "excuse me"
(squeaks)
Oh, shoot.
- She's not gonna want to come, George.
- Well, it's worth asking.
Honey, why don't you bring something with
you, like... why don't you bring that turkey?
You're right. Who could resist this turkey?
Gobble, gobble, gobble.
Yoo-hoo! Abigail!
- Hey, Mrs. Morrison.
- Oh, hi, Jessica.
Mom, Dad, I wasn't expecting you.
Did you want something?
Well, we're just fine.
Aren't we, George?
Oh.
Who's this nice young man?
- My cousin, Quinn.
- Nice to meet you.
- How do you do, Quentin?
- Mom, I asked you what you wanted.
- We're going to the cemetery.
- Gonna decorate for Thanksgiving.
You decorate a relative's grave
for the holidays?
- No, we decorate our own graves.
- Mom!
You see, George bought our plots
as a 20th anniversary present,
and I thought
the poor things looked empty.
So for our 25th,
Mary Louise bought a headstone.
It's got Morrison in big letters, George
on one side, Mary Louise on the other.
- So we'll always be together.
- Oh, sweetie.
- So, please, come with us this time.
- No.
Yes. Please. You never come.
Mom, I don't wanna go decorate
my parents' graves with my parents.
- It's a cemetery. Don't people complain?
- Honey, they can't. They're dead.
Oh, show her the turkey.
We got a little turkey.
- Turkey, turkey. Turkey, turkey.
- Oh, gobble, gobble.
Maybe Quentin and Jessica
could come along.
Thank you,
but I'm not much of a decorator.
Oh, Abigail says that,
and she's quite the artist.
Mom, nobody's interested. You'll just
have to go be morbid by yourself. Sorry.
You'll just have to miss
a good time, then.
In that case, you must come along
with Abigail and Jessica to Thanksgiving.
- I'm not gonna take no for an answer.
- She won't.
- If it's no trouble.
- I wouldn't ask if it were.
Mother, can I speak to you for a second?
Look, I'm sure he's already got plans.
He wouldn't say yes
if he already had plans.
Do you?
- There. That's settled.
- I don't want him to come.
- (whispers) I don't want him to come.
- If I could interject?
- Oh, what nice manners.
- Maybe it's best if I pass on the invitation.
Well, she didn't invite you, dear.
I did.
We're off.
We'll see you all for Thanksgiving.
- Bye-bye.
- Dad, help me. Please, Dad. Dad! Dad!
Nice meeting you.
(crashing from kitchen)
- (Jess) Oh! Five-second rule.
- (more crashing)
OK, uh, got everything.
I'm almost ready.
What are you making?
Mac and cheese?
Are you kidding?
Boil, drain, add milk and butter, then stir?
- Nice catch.
- Thanks.
That's, like, five steps.
I made ramen. That's only three.
Tear it open, dump it in, throw it away.
- So, how are your classes?
- They're all right.
If I don't pass art, I can pretty much
say goodbye to law school.
Abby could teach you.
She's a great teacher.
- No, she's not.
- But you wanna be.
And what better way to get experience?
He is not teachable.
- I'm a great student.
- That's doubtful.
Look, I'll make you a deal.
Help me pass art class,
and I won't ruin your Thanksgiving.
Yeah, no. You see, spending four hours
with you and my parents
is much easier than spending
an entire semester tutoring you.
OK.
What if I get Jess her job back,
and... I don't come
to your Thanksgiving dinner?
- We do need the rent money.
- Final offer.
No!
And that is my final answer.
OK. You know what? You're right. You
have bailed me out one too many times.
Thank you.
So I'll just go upstairs and pack. Don't
worry, I'll be out of your hair by morning.
Jess.
It's fine. I've always wanted to know
what it'd be like to live in a box.
OK, OK.
Jess, it's fine, I got it.
OK, listen.
You get Jess her job back
and you don't come with me
for Thanksgiving and... you've got a deal.
(Abby) Who in the world has parents
that decorate their own grave?
I mean, I must've been adopted.
Oh, gosh!
Oh, and I got conned into
helping this boy out with his homework.
- He's a decent chap, isn't he?
- I don't know.
- Do you like him?
- If you like a migraine.
Come on. If he needs help,
maybe you should just give him a hand.
No. I think he's obnoxious.
Don't you think as a teacher
you'll deal with obnoxious students?
No, I don't think as a teacher
I'll deal with obnoxious students!
No!
Come here!
I'm gonna show you who's obnoxious!
- (Quinn) How long do we look at this?
- Huh?
Well, you seem to know
the routine around here.
What's the standard time of staring
without looking pretentious?
Yeah, well,
it's not about a set period of time.
You just have to appreciate
what the artist is trying to say.
- It looks like spaghetti.
- OK, well, to you it might.
You know,
I happen to see something else.
Fettuccine.
Do you dismiss everything
you don't understand?
I haven't dismissed you yet, have I?
Look, all I'm saying is my sister could paint
something more realistic, and she's ten.
- It's not realism, it's how it makes you feel.
- And it makes me feel hungry.
OK, well, if you want a good grade,
you're gonna look past the spaghetti.
Oh, wow.
- Did you feel that?
- Huh?
We just had our first moment.
- You're an idiot.
- But you felt... Nothing, huh? A little bit?
So your parents are cool.
- To you, maybe.
- What does that mean?
- It means you didn't grow up with them.
- So what's the deal?
I don't know you well enough
to tell you my life history.
Come on.
They weren't around a lot.
End of story.
- Do you wanna hear my life story?
- Hm. I don't, actually.
Come on.
It involves fire, juggling and a midget.
So, you up for something to eat?
I think I'll pass, but thank you.
What?
Do you have a better offer?
Maybe.
(chuckles)
What?
I was thinking,
with your quirky personality,
you must not go out too often.
I get plenty of dates. In fact, that's where
I'm headed as soon as I finish helping you.
- Really?
- Yeah. Don't act so shocked.
What's his name?
His name is...
It's none of your business.
- That's what I thought.
- His name is Sy, which is short for Simon.
Are you always this annoying?
I like to call it being honest.
Well, Mr. Andrews, there is such a thing
as being a bit too honest.
(beep)
Hey. Quinn. It's Nicki. I thought we could
study together for law tonight. And then...
Hey. It's Cal. You know. If you press
this button you could leave a memo.
Check one. Mic check.
Sibilance. Sibilance.
Hey. Quinn. It's Lisa.
I thought we could go dancing.
- (Nicki) Are you calling Quinn?
- (Lisa) Excuse me!
- (Nicki) Ow. My hair!
- (Lisa) I got nothin' for you. Girl!
Hey, buddy.
How's it goin'?
Aaaargh!
Oh! Hey-hey, man! What's goin' on?
When did you get back?
- Just now.
- How was your day?
It was good. I met a girl.
Oh. Be careful, bro.
That's a four-letter word.
No, she's... she's different.
Actually, I think
the proper term today is "challenged."
No, Cal. She's...
I don't know... Better.
- Better? Better than the cheerleader?
- Yeah. Too bubbly.
- What about the librarian?
- Boring.
- That cute little red-headed chick?
- No eyebrows.
Yeah, well, they're all different, man.
That's why they just call 'em women.
Quick question.
When are you gonna get a new game?
They make new games?
Language section.
Financial book you have in your hand.
- Financial section's over there.
- (Quinn) Look what they did. See this?
They're working on the 19 and one quarter.
I haven't seen anything like this since '84.
Eastern and ski resorts on the same shelf.
You be good. OK.
They obviously didn't get the memo.
Can I help you guys?
- Get us the manager, son.
- I'm the manager.
You're Mr...
Sounders?
- I'm Mr. Sanders.
- That's what I said.
- And you are?
- Schlosky.
Jack Schlosky.
Director of Corporate Infrastructure.
- You didn't get the L10 memo, did you?
- L10?
- There goes the Q4 profits.
- Q4 profits?
Who said anything
about the Q4 profits?
- He...
- We just drove in from Corporate.
- Oh, from Michigan?
- Yes, from Michigan. 18-hour drive.
- Without a bathroom stop.
That illustrates
the seriousness of the situation.
Do we have a problem?
Problem is,
your store's in the old format.
- This is last year's format here, son.
- I... I didn't know we had a format.
Consumers have an easier time
locating books
if you move everything from there to there,
and there to there.
- It's all in this packet.
- You can't be serious.
Oh, we can.
We've been serious, we're serious now.
Bottom line is, if you don't move these
sections, we move you. Get the point, eh?
- Are you sure you're from Corporate?
- He transferred from the Canadian offices.
Yeah. They're just like
the American offices, just with... hockey.
The whole store?
Do you wanna lose franchising rights?
'Cause I have the power to shut this place.
- He does. He's got the power.
- I do. The power.
- What power?
- Of Grayskull.
Hey, it's just I'm short-staffed now.
- Why is that?
- I had to let somebody go.
- Who?
- Jessica Lindstrom.
- Why?
- She had less-than-desirable work habits.
- Lindstrom, Jessica. Look that up.
- Lindstrom. L-y...
- L-i...
- N... There's...
- Then it's D, right? D...
- Arghh! Too many letters. No! Sh, sh, sh!
- You guys dated.
- How did you know that?
- It's in your personal records.
- We know ev-ery-thing.
- Everything?
- Ev-ery-thing.
- Everything.
- You fired someone you dated?
You crazy, man? You wanna open yourself
up to a multi-million-dollar lawsuit?
- No. Jeez, no.
- Then I suggest you hire her back.
- Immediately! Without question!
- With a raise! No questioning!
- Now get your store in order.
- I will, I will.
You know what? You got one week. One
week, then we come back with auditors.
- The auditors are coming?
- Prime directive from Corporate, C3... PO.
Can I get your business card?
- Um...
- Uh...
Why? So you can call me, looking for
answers to questions you should know?
- I don't think so, son.
- I understand, I understand.
- Go.
- OK.
- I told you we needed business cards.
- I know.
( "In Your Arms" by Amelia's Dream)
Hey. Baby
Where are you?
I'm running to love you all over
Closer
Kiss me
(Abby) If Monet is regarded
as the Impressionist par excellence,
one must admit
that both Degas and Renoir are also...
If you don't pay attention,
it's not gonna work.
I just don't get it.
It's so boring.
I need a break.
Where's your bathroom?
It's down the hallway.
(Quinn) These are really good.
- This isn't the bathroom.
- What's this?
It's not done.
I know a place you could show these.
I bet you could make money.
You know what?
It's really not about money for me, so...
- Then why do it?
- If I have to tell you, it's not worth it. Go!
There are always two people in art -
the observer and the observed.
Remember, art is subjective.
Each person gains new insights as they
allow themselves to be immersed in art.
Let's turn to last week's assignment. What
new insights did you gain from the exhibit?
- Mr. Andrews?
- Well, uh...
Well, there's this one artist
named, uh, Dylan Thompson,
who said surrealism has less to do
with what is random and senseless
and more to do with accepting that
our lives don't always have to make sense.
Go on.
Well,
I remember looking at one of his paintings,
and for someone willing to take the time,
they could really find something deeper
to connect with.
- (teacher) That's valid.
- Kind of like those who judge people
before they get to know
what's really inside.
Good observation.
Now, let's turn to page, um... 621.
- You see what you've created?
- Oh, I didn't do anything.
You taught, I learned.
So, Sy's cool
with this whole tutoring thing, right?
Yeah, yeah.
He's pretty understanding.
Great. I'll see you later.
OK.
- Hey, Abby.
- Yeah?
- Thanks for your help.
- You're welcome.
- (Abby) I love that movie!
- Me too. And we've only seen it 30 times.
- 32.
- Who's counting?
What guy
would ever indulge me like this?
That is just what I was thinking.
(both) Weird.
- (Abby) It was Goethe.
- Right. I think it was Goethe
who said that people rarely love others
for who they really are,
but rather
what they imagine them to be.
- (Abby) Right.
- So, go on, prepare for takeoff.
- (Abby) OK. One, two, three...
- Ready? One, two, three...
So, Sy, what do you imagine me to be?
- (Sy) An angel.
- Oh, really?
(Sy) But obviously I know
you're really a flesh-eating demon.
I sure am.
That's cold.
I have snow everywhere.
Anyway,
returning to the subject of imagination,
I believe it was Shakespeare who said,
"So full of shapes is fancy
that it alone is high fantastical."
(door opens)
- (Abby) Hey, Jess.
- Hey.
Wow.
You look like death warmed over.
Quinn's plan to help helped too much.
Ryan's killing us
trying to get the books reorganized.
Oh, by the way, Quinn called for you.
Really?
- You like him.
- No.
Well, I think he likes you.
You never know, he may ask you out.
- No, he won't.
- Why?
Because...
he thinks I have a boyfriend.
- You didn't tell him about Sy, did you?
- Sorta.
Well, which part of "sorta?"
Like Sy's sorta not real?
Like he's imaginary?
Sorta.
OK, Abby, what's up with Sy?
You know,
he's just there for me all the time.
That's great when you were five,
but what about now?
Quinn's real, and he likes you.
- He's gonna think I'm crazy.
- I didn't think you were when you told me.
We were five.
We didn't know any better.
Just tell him, OK?
Abby.
(Abby) I'll tell him.
OK. OK, this can work.
This has gotta work.
(Jess) Hold everything!
Oh, no! Oh!
I found these from the World History
section. Someone had them in Gardening.
No, no.
God, this is impossible.
I'm gonna kill Quinn.
- What?
- Nothing.
We should be halfway done by now. We're
not even through the youth section yet.
We'll be fine.
It's starting to pick up.
No, it isn't.
If we don't get this turned around,
Corporate's gonna have my job.
How's it feel?
I need you to work Thanksgiving.
- I can't.
- I'll pay you double.
Triple.
( "Let It Go" by Bus Stop)
(grunts)
- Cal, what are you doing?
- I'm fixing your car.
But my car's not broken.
Oh.
You know what?
You should just go to Abby's.
- Am I supposed to walk?
- Well, I mean, obviously your car's broken.
- Bro, it was working before...
- Shh, kitten.
Why don't you just walk away? It'll be done
by the time you get back. All righty. Great.
Oh, yeah!
Time travel is possible!
Here. Try some of my favorite.
- What is it?
- Won flung food.
Won flung nothing.
- I thought it was funny.
- It was... cute.
Oh, good.
Chinese.
I am starving.
Ohh! That smells so good.
- Ryan has me working Thanksgiving.
- What? No! Jessica, you promised.
I'm sorry.
He's paying me triple.
- What? Was that stupid?
- It's not stupid, just greedy.
I'm gonna take mine to go.
Don't study too hard.
- Did Jess just steal half our dinner?
- Yeah, pretty much.
Here. Take your fortune
before she comes back and steals that.
I love these.
And Confucius says...
"It is important to look out
for that which you cannot see."
Huh.
- What the hell does that mean?
- I have no idea.
Sy? What are you doing?
- I know when I'm not wanted.
- Is this about last night?
- I just hope you're happy with him.
- With Quinn?
Of course with Quinn.
If he breaks your heart, I swear...
What are you gonna do?
Stab him with some imaginary sword?
- Careful.
- Sorry.
That man is a player.
He's a wolf in sheep's clothing.
Wait a second.
Hey, that's mine.
We bought this together.
You can have the telly.
All right, stop.
Enough. Sit down.
Now, listen to me.
I am not gonna leave you for him, OK?
- You promise?
- Mm-hm.
- Then prove it to me.
- Fine. Anything.
Well, do you have to spend so much time
spoon-feeding that baboon?
I mean, couldn't you just lend him one
of your art books? He can read, can't he?
( "Over It" by Halo Friendlies)
I know what you're thinkin'
I know where you're goin'
And I know what you're doin' now
(beep)
(Cal) Hello? Hello?
- Hello?
- That's what I said. Hello?
Hello?
Somebody say something.
Hello, I'm looking for Quinn Andrews.
Hello?
I'm looking for a Quinn Andrews.
Quinn...
- Yo.
- Hi.
Hey. Good.
Thought I had the wrong door.
Wait, then maybe I have the wrong door.
Why does this keep happening to me?
- Is Quinn here?
- Yes. Yes.
Yes. OK.
We're both in the right place, then.
Good. Well, I've actually seen you before.
At the bookstore.
- What bookstore?
- Borders, on Fifth.
- What did I look like?
- You looked like you.
- Oh, except you were wearing pants.
- Oh.
Pants.
Yeah, all right.
That sounds like that coulda been me.
Yeah, all right, come on in.
You're the artist person
helping Quinn with his homework.
- Yeah.
- Dating that guy with the weird name.
- Sy. Right.
- That's not that weird.
Do you think you could just
give this to Quinn for me, please?
You know what? No. No.
It's really not a good idea.
I tend to lose things,
and then Quinn gets mad,
and when he gets mad he yells,
and I fear the yelling.
So maybe you should just
give it to him yourself. OK?
OK.
Your face is good.
You want some chicken salad?
I made it with ham.
- It... I...
- Hey.
- I didn't expect to see you here.
- Oh, yeah. Calvin let me in.
Great. You want something to eat or drink?
I think Cal made chicken... something.
- No. Actually, I came by to give you this.
- Oh, great, then we can study here.
Yeah, I was just kinda thinking
you could study by yourself.
Whoa, whoa.
Are you trying to bail on our deal?
No.
Good.
There we go.
Um, you know what? I think I'm just
gonna... go missing for a little while here.
- I hope you're not leaving because of me.
- It's totally 'cause of you. This is just weird.
- Oh, this awkwardness...
- Well, it was nice meeting you.
- Nice meeting you too, uh...
- Abby.
- That coulda been it.
- He's a little...
Different.
I believe the proper term used today
is "challenged."
Oh.
OK, so 202, 203... Yeah, up to 205.
And the top of 207
and I think you should be good.
All right.
Hey, uh... You hungry?
Uh, no. I'm fine.
- You're not hungry at all?
- Uh-uh. No, I'm good. Thank you, though.
Look me in the eye
and tell me you're not hungry.
You're almost there.
"Quinn, I'm a little..."
- I'm a little hungry.
- Great. Let's get something to eat.
You want me to believe
that Johann Vermeer traced his art?
He used a camera.
Vermeer is a 17th-century artist.
There weren't any cameras back then.
He used a camera obscura,
which was a primitive camera.
Basically, it would project
the image onto the canvas.
You'd be surprised how many
17th-century artists experimented with it.
Just think about it. You get hired
to paint a grand duke or a bishop.
You cannot take any risks.
OK...
Look at the lighting. The perspective.
Most of the models are left-handed.
- So what?
- Most people are right-handed.
The projections
would have mirrored the image.
What happened to the guy
that knew nothing about art?
It was a lot easier to hate him.
Minor in history.
There you go.
- Oh, let me...
- Please. My treat.
Thank you.
I wanna show you something.
- You wanna show me something?
- It's a surprise.
Uh...
Yeah, no thank you.
I'm not good at surprises.
We're gonna change that.
I want you to consider this
a new experience. OK?
Come on.
What do I know about the surreal?
Do I know what it's like to feel?
What's in my heart
but not what's in my mind
A bunch of local artists
have an exhibit here about once a month.
Thought you might wanna check it out.
- How'd you find out about this place?
- Oh, I come for the music.
All kinds of bands come here.
Next week Braid's performing.
Really? I like them.
That's cool.
Why don't you check out the artwork
and I'll grab us some drinks.
OK.
Oh, excuse me.
I used to have this phobia of clowns.
Never did figure out the origin.
Stephen King's It
didn't really help my condition either.
- Well, I think they're beautiful.
- Thanks.
You're an artist?
I'm an art student.
Don't worry. It took me a while
to admit I was an artist, too.
(woman) Hey, Verna,
come here for a second.
Hey.
There you go.
Is everything OK?
I think I should go.
- Yeah, OK. Sure.
- OK.
Quinn.
- Thanks again. I'll pay you back, I promise.
- I know you will.
You guys have a good time.
And you have a terrific boyfriend.
- No, he's not...
- You have a terrific boyfriend.
This must be so exciting for you.
That girl was kinda cute.
Is someone jealous?
No.
She's, uh... she's someone I've known
for a real long time.
Her mom got sick,
so I lent her money to fly home.
That's it.
- You gotta go home soon, huh?
- Mm-hm.
In a little bit.
Good. You up for another surprise?
- It's so pretty.
- Yeah.
Hey, isn't that Calvin?
Out of the way!
You on the skates, out of the way!
That's the Zamboni King.
- I'm Canadian, I can't drive!
- Do you like to skate?
I'm actually pretty good at it.
Great. Then you can teach me.
You brought me here
and you don't know how to skate?
You really can't skate, can you?
I wouldn't lie to you.
Um...
There's something
that I need to tell you about Sy.
What's that?
Oh, gosh!
You OK?
- What would Sy think?
- Well, he...
- There is something I want to tell you.
- Watch out!
(Cal grunts a tune)
(strains)
(knock at door)
Hey, dude, is that you?
Who else would it be, Cal?
That's a fair point, I guess.
I'll be out in a minute.
I'm just taking a dump.
Ever wonder why they say "taking
a dump," not "leaving a dump"?
'Cause once it passes the rim,
I'm not reaching in there for anything.
You spend too much time alone, my friend.
- It gives me time to think.
- Depends on your definition of thinking.
Oh, yeah.
Cal, the light.
Quinn, the pants.
- What are you talking about?
- I thought we're playing word association.
- No. Just shut off the light.
- No, I'm too tired.
- You just walked past it.
- That should show you how tired I am.
(sighs)
You know, when I was in the bathroom
I was thinking.
- Aren't you glad we're not women?
- What?
Don't get me wrong -
having the boobs would be cool.
But girls have to find a place to go to
the bathroom. Guys, the world is our urinal.
Wow, Cal, that's...
that's really profound.
- Who said that, Nietzsche?
- Nie... No, dude, I just did.
Just shut off the light.
So, how's Tabby?
- It's Abby.
- That's what I said. Tabby.
- She's great.
- Cool.
So, what happens next?
I don't know. I like her,
but she's got this boyfriend.
Oh, yeah. She told me about that guy.
He sounds really cool.
Oh, yeah, no, you don't stand a chance.
Oh, great.
- She went out with you though, didn't she?
- Yeah.
Well, then maybe
she'll settle for somebody like you.
- Even if he is the hottest guy on the planet.
- She said that?
Oh, yeah. She went off...
Actually, you know what? That might've
been on TV. I don't remember.
Perfect.
(bulb shatters)
- Cal, the glass!
- Only hurts if you step on it, my friend.
- (crunch)
- Ow!
Good morning, darling one.
Good morning.
- You got home late last night.
- Hm.
Thought you were helping him
with his homework.
It was homework.
Oh, really? At the skating rink?
- That's a date.
- It wasn't a date.
Look, this is very hard for me, all right?
I've never had to deal
with a real man in your life before.
- I don't wanna talk about this right now.
- Fine.
Well, next time you need me,
I might just be otherwise engaged.
(angry squeal)
- Hey.
- Oh, hey. How are you?
- Got us tickets to see Braid tonight.
- Oh, you did? Oh...
- It's on the house.
- Hm... Thanks.
I can't go.
Really? I thought we agreed
on studying tonight.
Yeah, I know we did. I just, you know...
I kinda promised Sy we'd do something.
All right. Cool.
Then, uh... I'll just see you in class.
OK.
(knocking)
It's open.
Wow. You look like crap.
Well, thanks.
I was working all night sorting books.
- Hey, is Abby home?
- Uh-uh.
Let me ask you something.
- Tell me about Sy.
- What?
You know, what's he like,
what does he look like?
Oh, uh...
Well, Sy is...
Well, he's kinda hard to describe.
- Well, he's here all the time, isn't he?
- Well, he works a lot.
Really? What does he do?
He's, uh...
Well, he...
Come on, it can't be that hard.
- Well, it's just that I...
- Yeah?
I don't want
to make you feel bad or anything.
Why would his work make me feel bad?
Well, because...
Because...
he's a lawyer.
Wow.
That's impressive.
What kind of lawyer is he?
Uh...
A good one.
You know the drill.
Books off the desks, no talking.
This is where I find out who simply
needs help and who is simply helpless.
- Hey.
- Oh, hi.
- How'd you do on your test?
- I think I did OK.
That's good.
How come you didn't tell me
Sy was a lawyer?
Oh, um...
- I didn't?
- Yeah, Jess told me.
She did? That's... Well, there you go.
I was thinking maybe I could call him,
ask advice about internships, stuff like that.
- Yeah, that would be great.
- Great. What's his number?
You know, he's working
on a big case right now.
Really? What kind of case?
He works for the government,
so it's sorta shhh.
Oh, I understand.
Well, maybe he could call me.
Yeah, I will. I'll have him call you.
It's a good idea.
Abby? Where are you going?
Yeah, I have another class, it's that way.
You know what I think?
I think you need a break.
- I don't think so.
- I think you do, and I think you deserve it.
- Is it OK to leave our stuff here?
- Yeah. Just put it here.
Give me your hand.
- Why do you need the flashlight?
- Because it's gonna get dark.
- It is?
- Yeah.
Hey, what is this place?
Oh, it's...
Stupid... flashlight.
The flashlight's not working.
- Oh, my God!
- (screams)
(Quinn laughs)
- Don't leave me in the dark.
- You're a bad monkey.
It's the new dinosaur museum
the university's opening next month.
- Are we supposed to be in here?
- It's no big deal.
I don't think this is such a good idea.
My man Big Al is a security guy here.
He says as long as
we don't touch anything, we're cool.
Trust me.
Wow. This place is just... so amazing.
I told you.
- Pretty cool, huh?
- Yeah, it's... great.
- (thud)
- Shh.
- What?
- Oh, it's Big Al. Hang on.
Oh, OK.
(footsteps)
- That's not Big Al. That's not Big Al!
- What?
Run!
(whistles a tune)
- (Quinn stifles giggles)
- Shh...
Please, please...
OK, I think he's gone.
- Come on, let's go this way.
- OK.
( "Make Me Wanna Fall" by Amy Collier)
Don't you know I've lost control
And that's OK with me
You must think you're something special
But that's OK with me
Don't think that I can stop it
When I'm with you
You knocked me off of my feet.
You got me spinning around
Turned my whole world upside down
This thing drives me crazy
Don't you make me wanna fall
Think that love has taken hold now
That's OK with me
You knocked me off of my feet.
You got me spinning around
Turned my whole world upside down
This thing drives me crazy
Don't you make me wanna fall
- Do you have something I could drink?
- Yeah. There's soda in the cooler.
Thanks.
Agh!
- Are you OK?
- Hello, darling one.
Yeah... Um... It...
Do you know how much I love this soda?
Look at him. I wonder how many
naive young women he's lured up here.
Under the pretext
of helping him with his homework.
- No soda?
- Um... Yeah, no.
No soda. Actually, I would never
like to have soda ever again.
OK.
So...
Sorry this place is such a wreck.
I wasn't expecting company.
And I think the last girl we had here...
was Cal's mom.
- Likely story.
- Really?
Don't you just love the way the surrealists
make our wildest imaginings come to life?
Neanderthal man, your thoughts?
Yeah.
Fascinating insight.
It's like a foreign language
we can understand,
but you just don't know how.
- Where the hell did that come from?
- That is beautiful.
- Thanks for walking me home.
- (Sy) It's nothing.
(Quinn) It's my pleasure.
You know, anytime Sy's out of town and
you need a walker-homer, I'm your guy.
- I'm not out of town. I'm very much in town.
- I'll let you know.
I was wondering... I'm sure you've already
got plans about Thanksgiving...
Actually, it's beer
and bacon sandwiches with Cal.
Abby, do not invite him to Thanksgiving.
Would you like to come to Thanksgiving
with me at my parents' house?
- You sure you want me to come?
- Yeah, I'm really sure.
- What about Sy?
- Yeah, what about me?
You know, he's English.
They don't really do Thanksgiving.
- So you invited him to your parents'?
- Yeah. I don't know what got into me.
Whatever it is, I think it's good.
Jess, I need you.
Can't you see I'm having my coffee break?
Yeah. It's just Thanksgiving's tomorrow
and we're only halfway through, so...
Are you harassing me
because of our prior relationship?
No, no. But...
- Do we need to call Corporate?
- No, no, no. No, that's fine.
No, you go ahead and just let me know
when you're... back, then.
That's fun.
So how are things going
between you and Quinn?
They're going fine, thanks.
Well, that's decisively indecisive.
He's kinda cute.
You haven't told him about Sy, have you?
Uh-uh. I was going to, but I...
Maybe it's time you let Sy go.
No. It's not really that easy.
- Well, sure it is.
- No, it's not.
Jess, look at you.
No offense, but every relationship
you get into seems to be dysfunctional.
Abby, having an imaginary boyfriend
is textbook dysfunctionality.
OK.
It's like those paintings you do of him -
they're perfect,
but you need to paint somebody that's real.
Somebody that moves
and, you know, breathes.
Hey! That's my face you're ripping up.
No, it's hopeless.
My work, it's dead, it's lifeless.
It is not. You can't listen to that bookstore
clerk. What did I tell you about real people?
What if she's right
about painting real people?
You mean like Quinn?
Because I'm so boring and lifeless
and he's so full of manly vigor?
- I didn't say that.
- Look, let me tell you something.
I am pretty bored of this soppy, sweet,
sexually nonthreatening persona
you've given me.
"Oh, my darling,
nothing is too good for you."
I do pretty well
with the material you've given me.
Yes - that's exactly the problem.
I give you everything.
- Maybe I need somebody who...
- Say no more. It's fine.
I'll just go and see my other friends
who don't think I'm lifeless and boring.
What other friends? You're imaginary.
Do you really think
you're the only one who dreams me up?
There are thousands of Ionely women
like you, and some men, who dream of me.
Yeah. They lavish their affections on me.
Granted, they may not be as attractive,
but Millie from Minnesota is quite charming
if you can get past her accent.
- Millie? From Minnesota?
- Yeah.
So, I hope you have a spectacular painting
session with your Neanderthal boyfriend.
Thank you.
Oh, and by the way...
I hate romantic comedies.
Great!
All right, pretty boy.
Come on, fire one in here.
Oops. My bad.
Let's go, chief. See if you can
get past the mighty Canadian!
(groans)
You OK?
Mm-hm.
Ohh...
I'm good, baby.
Give me another one. Come on!
But I hit you in the k-nuts.
You only caught the right one.
I'm invincible. Slap it in!
(groans)
O Canada
My home and native land
Come on!
- I'm going to Abby's for Thanksgiving.
- Should be fun. You, her and the lawyer.
- He's not going.
- Oh.
That's great. You can make your move.
You know I'm not that guy.
Besides, we're just friends.
Everything starts as "just friends,"
but the next thing you know...
Oh, my God!
I'm OK.
This happens all the time, man.
- Need help?
- Stuck in the net... I'm good.
All right. I'm gonna get going.
What? Hey, what about our feast?
- Bacon and beer?
- It's Thanksgiving.
- I think I'll take Abby.
- Over bacon?
I like her more than swine, Cal.
- It's love, man.
- Later, bro.
Hey...
You know, if you leave me
I'll just kinda look silly.
All right. OK.
- Here we go.
- Oh... Thanks.
These are for you.
I mean, if that's OK.
Yeah, it's great. Thanks. I've never
been given flowers before. Thank you.
Really?
Well, you know, from anyone besides Sy.
Yeah. Of course Sy. I mean...
Those are more like
"Hey, happy Thanksgiving" flowers.
Idiot!
On a day like today
I could take a chance
on someone new...
(Abby) I want you to think of this
as a new experience. OK?
- Which house is yours?
- Trust me, you'll know.
- Your parents really get into this, huh?
- Yeah.
- You shoulda seen it for the garlic festival.
- The what?
I'll tell you later.
- You ring your own doorbell?
- Yeah. It's safer.
Happy Turkey Day!
Come in, come in.
Your father will be out in a moment.
Very nice to see you again, Quentin.
Look who's here! Good.
Mary Louise, where's my turkey head?
In the attic, next to your Frankenstein suit.
The attic? Great!
Well, come on.
I have some Pilgrim Punch for you.
- OK.
- I make a mean gobbler cobbler.
Look out, turkey coming through.
Watch my tail.
- I'll just take some of this.
- George!
You do that again, I am gonna have
Quentin tie you to the table and baste you!
Besides, I think a turkey eating turkey
is cannibalistic.
Man, you guys have been everywhere.
Yeah, we used to travel all over the place.
- There's no pictures of Abby.
- Well, she was usually taking the pictures.
That's when we went to the Grand Canyon.
Abby, when were we
at the Grand Canyon?
I've never been to the Grand Canyon.
Oh, yeah.
We usually left her with her Aunt Edna.
- Hey, that reminds me of a joke.
- Quinn, come on.
- Why did the police arrest the turkey?
- We'll be back.
Where are you going?
We're eating in an hour.
He was suspected of fowl play.
- Oh, Father.
- That's a funny joke, sweetie.
Sorry about rushing you out of there.
You know, dad jokes are not really funny.
So anyways, this is the place I went to
when, you know, parents were... parents.
I hear you. My dad's a shrink.
- Really?
- Yeah. Psychoanalyzes everyone.
Cal hasn't been to the house
in some time.
- That makes sense.
- Yeah, obvious reasons.
- Do you swing?
- I swing, yes.
Oh!
I remember them being so much larger.
- It's kinda scary growing up, isn't it?
- Yeah, it is.
So, is this where
you and Mr. Wonderful hang out?
Jealous?
No, I'm not jealous.
Someone's jealous!
I love these things!
I hate them. They make me nauseous.
- Are you kidding me?
- They're the worst. They're awful.
- Come on. Real quick, for me.
- No.
30 seconds. What's the worst
that can happen in 30 seconds?
- I don't want to.
- 30 seconds and you're free.
- OK?
- OK. But go slow.
- Slow!
- I haven't even started yet.
- You're going too fast.
- Now I'm gonna start.
I'm getting dizzy. I'm gonna throw up.
No, please...
It's not that bad.
It's OK, you're safe with me.
Just hold on.
Oh...
Agh!
Well, I've just about
got the bleeding stopped.
- This is really embarrassing.
- I'm sorry.
I was a field medic in 'Nam -
I've seen worse than this.
Dad, it's OK. I don't think
he's gonna need your services.
When I was a kid on the playground,
never a scratch. Now look at me.
Abby used to come home every other day
with a bump or a bruise.
- She always blamed it on Sy.
- Mom. You don't have to talk about that.
What about Sy? He ever get hurt?
Mom, there's those buns. Right?
You don't want them to burn, do you?
- Sy never got hurt.
- Yeah... (sniffs) I smell something.
They're on fire! Oh, my gosh!
There's something...
It's burning in the kitchen.
Oh, there's nothing burning.
You're imagining things.
- No, Mom, I'm not imagining...
- Agh! Agh!
You imagine things all the time.
Well, what about Sy?
Her perfect imaginary friend.
At what age did you finally give him up?
Honey, look, the meat.
The meat is frozen to his head now.
Ooh! Yipeys!
- Careful.
- It's OK.
Don't let the dog out.
- I have been trying to tell you.
- Really?
- Will you please just let me?
- Explain? Explain that you lied to me?
That you blew me off
for somebody who doesn't even exist?
Abby, I felt guilty having feelings for you.
And it's all because
you made me believe you had a boyfriend.
I didn't make him up because of you.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
Please, tell me.
I didn't have parents that understood
that raising me was a job.
I just kind of felt like this accessory.
I don't know if you've ever
really felt Ioneliness before,
but I have.
You know, the Sy
that you keep hearing about is...
is just the place that I went to
that made it easier.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry.
That I...
Sorry.
I'm gonna go.
Yeah... I think you should.
Abby...
Take this.
( "Wound Up In You" by Ted Bruner)
Somehow I got myself
Wound up in you...
(grunts)
Quinn!
Quinn? Quinn.
Hey-hey-hey, buddy.
Little help, baby.
Come on, man. The blood's rushing
to my head. I'm starting to feel woozy.
Oh, yeah... Hey, a dime.
(Sy) You're gonna get over him,
and I'm gonna be here to help you.
You've just never fallen
for a real guy before.
You've never felt real pain.
But I'm not sure I've felt real love either.
I was much better off
Before
I got wound up
In you
- Did you find everything OK?
- Yeah. I love the new setup.
- Oh, wonderful. Happy holidays.
- Thank you.
(gasps)
There are two people from Corporate here
and they're looking for me.
Do they look mad?
Ryan, I think you should know something.
What?
Excuse me, Miss?
Well, those two guys from Corporate...
They weren't from Corporate.
They weren't?
- It was my cousin and his roommate.
- Your cousin works for Corporate?
Hello?
No. My cousin did it to get my job back.
(bell rings)
Look, this register's...
It's for you.
Are you Ryan Sanders?
Yeah, I'm Ryan Sanders.
We've been getting some calls on some
changes you've been making in your store.
- I can explain.
- Very impressive.
Most of this is her fault...
- You like it?
- Yes.
- You really like it?
- Like it? We love it!
Love it.
Well, we...
Ryan and I came up with it together.
Then you both should be commended.
Our company needs more self-motivated
employees like the two of you.
We'll be keeping our eyes on you -
since we'll be needing
a new regional manager before too long.
Of course, that's if your lovely assistant
is willing to become manager here.
You know, you could've
taken all the credit for yourself.
- Why didn't you?
- Because we did it, Ryan. As a team.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess we did, huh?
You know, there's a nice way
to handle the books, and that wasn't it.
You're funny.
You're a funny girl, really.
(tutor) I have mixed emotions
with your results.
Some of you, I was pleasantly surprised.
Others, disappointed.
But most of you performed
exactly as I'd expected.
Oh. Hey, Quinn.
Quinn, what did you get on the test?
Wow, a B. That's great.
We've both kept our part of the deal.
Yeah. So when do you wanna start
studying for the final?
I think I'll be better on my own.
What are you doing?
Changing.
To what?
I don't know yet.
This is looking a little tired, too.
And it's got dirt on it.
I sure wish Abby'd come with us sometime.
She could bring that friend of hers, Quinn.
Oh, wouldn't that be fun?
I sure do like him.
- He seems like a nice fellow.
- Tall, too.
I guess this means
things can get back to normal.
Our relationship isn't normal, Sy.
You can't hold me, or kiss me, or...
The thing is...
The thing is that...
The thing is
that it's time for me to say goodbye.
I know.
I can't imagine my life without you.
That's what happens.
Girls grow up and then they leave
their imaginary boyfriends.
I'm sorry that I clung on so hard.
I just couldn't bear to see you suffer.
I'm gonna miss you.
I'm gonna miss you too.
Good luck with, uh... with Quinn.
- He's gonna come back to you.
- I don't know.
Just don't be too hard on him if he doesn't
want to go to lots of romantic movies.
Most guys, they don't like that stuff.
Sy.
Thank you.
Sweetie, I'm so glad you came.
- Hi.
- It's so much better with you here.
Well, it's time to try something new.
- Hey, is everybody ready?
- Yeah.
All righty.
Ha-ha!
Oh.
- Honey, it's not too impressive.
- Oh, it's terrific.
Just wait till tonight.
It's gonna look wonderful.
- You sure I'm not adopted?
- Oh, I love you too, dear.
- Should we tell her about her headstone?
- Let's save that for Christmas Day.
You'll never feel like this again
So remember
The look on my face forever...
It could be fun.
Thanks, but... I don't think so, Sarah.
Hey, call me if you change your mind.
Bye.
(acoustic guitar)
Cookin'
Bacon
I love bacon!
(dramatic vocalization)
- There you go. There it is.
- Cal, what are you doing?
Hey. What's goin' on?
That's my cousin Jasper,
and this is my stepmother's
half-brother's son Darwin.
Yeah, you got it.
What's up? How's it goin'?
We're just getting our music down,
because we're gonna record an album.
Wha wha wha wha wha whaaaaaaa
Ladies and gentlemen, The Crazy Pucks.
- We're awesome.
- Fitting.
- Dude, it's below freezing out here.
- I think the cold helps our musical ability.
So, how's the old dating game going?
Man, it's like a bad reality show.
That good, huh?
No, Cal, that's bad.
Oh.
Is there ever a time when eight of the ten
voices in your head agree on one thing?
I don't know. I've never asked them.
But I know that they wanna know
why you walked away from Abby.
- Why you walked away from Abby!
-  Why did you walk away from Abby?
- Make it Ab-by.
-  Ab-byyy
-  Now he's walking away from us
-  Both of us
-  I better go, he's fragile
-  Now you're walking away from me
I gotta go. He's fragile and like a girl...
Work with that.
Please don't take my sandwich,
'cause that's what I like to eat
That was rude.
We had issues.
You're the one
who's got issues with commitment.
Take it from somebody who's been
committed, let love take care of itself.
That makes about as much sense
as a kamikaze pilot wearing a helmet.
Hey, just because
somebody's a practicing kamikaze
does not mean they shouldn't be safe.
Kamikaze pilots committed suicide, Cal.
Yeah. They understood commitment.
You don't understand.
Her boyfriend, she made him up.
He doesn't exist. He's imaginary.
So? When I was growing up,
I was the kid next door's imaginary friend.
- Not funny.
- Yeah. It wasn't for me either.
Thinking 'cause I'm imaginary I didn't need
the bathroom. Worst month of my life.
Cal, please, just two seconds, man.
There's no such thing
as the perfect woman, bro.
She just doesn't exist.
The only thing I know
is that since you met her
you're the happiest I've ever seen you.
I'm not happy right now.
Well, maybe that's because you're sitting
here talking to the wrong person.
Jess.
- Know where I could find Abby?
- She's not here.
- Do you know where she is?
- No.
And I don't think she's up to seeing you.
- Because of Sy?
- Because of you.
Me?
You are the first real guy she's ever loved,
and at the first sign of trouble,
what did you do?
Jess, please, I just wanna find her.
Excuse me, I was wondering if you could
help me find a book on the mating rituals...
of the African dung beetle.
I know exactly where that book is.
OK, well... I'm gonna get going.
Just let me know if you see her.
Thank you...
Abdul.
No, actually it's Jess.
That's pretty too.
- And your name?
- David.
David.
I like that name.
I saw her face in the clouds
Before the rain
It felt good to see you again
Then it all washed away
I can't explain
How I miss you
If I'd only known
How much this would hurt
How I would be craving
to be in your world
Now I know
I should've never let you go
Abby?
- I saw your painting.
- I wanted to paint something real.
Who are those for?
They're for you.
That is, if...
Sy doesn't have a problem with it.
He's gone.
You know I'm not perfect.
I'm not looking for perfect anymore.
( "This Could Be Everything"
by Paul Umbach)
This could be everything
Everything that we want
I feel my heart begin to race
Every time I see your face
You're everything
That I wish I'd ever known
It's the meaning of why I am here
Turn to me. Don't disappear
I want you to be right here with me
This could be
The feeling that our love's forsaken
But don't be afraid of
Never learning how to fall in love
And maybe
We will be
As one
This could be everything
Everything that we want
It's a world that I begin to see
Every time you're next to me
You're everything
I need you in my heart
It's the meaning of why I am here
So turn to me. My love
This could be everything
Everything that we want
Hold me here beside you now
I need to feel your touch somehow
You'll never ever find a love like mine
No. No
( "In My Arms")
Hey. Baby. where are you?
I'm wanting to love you all over
Come closer
Kiss me
I know you've got to miss me
Well. It would be so damn fine
In your arms
I wish that this could last forever
I can feel your toes
They're snuggled up to mine
I wish you'd just wake up
And hold me through the night
Well. It would be so divine
In your arms
I wish that this could last forever
You're touching
My hair
I'm getting tingles I swear
You move
Close to me
And I am set...
Free
In your arms
I wish that this could last forever