PIXAR
ONE MAN BAND
executive producers
JOHN LASSETER $ BRAD BIRD
PIXAR
celebrating
20 YEARS
Okay, here we go.
Focus.
Speed. I am speed.
One winner.
Fourty-two losers.
I eat losers for breakfast.
Breakfast. Maybe I should have breakfast.
Brakie could be good for me.
No, no. Stay focused.
Speed.
I'm faster than fast,
quicker than quick.
I am Lightning!
Hey Lightning, you're ready?
LIGHTNING McQUEEN
Oh yeah, Lightning is ready!
PISTON CUP
CARS
Got gas, come on here!
Not bad run, sweetie!
Welcome back to the Dinoco 400.
I'm Bob Cutlass. Here with
my good friend Darrell Cartrip.
We're midway through what may turn
out to be a historic day of a racing.
I'm all fresh with student Ruth right now.
If this gets any more exciting, they're
gonna have to toll me out of the booth!
Right you are, Darrell.
Three cars are tied for
the season's point sleeve.
Heading into the final race of the season.
And the winner of this race,
Darrell will win the season's title.
And the Piston Cup.
Of the cage Strip Weathers have
one more victory before retiring.
He's been down to coast
golden boy for years!
Can he win the one last Piston Cup?
And there's always
for the second place.
Bob, we're buying Chick Hicks.
He's been shaking that tail
then his entire career.
Chick tough this was his year, Bob.
He's chance to finally emerge
to the Kind Shadow.
But the last thing he expected was...
Lightning McQueen!
You know, I don't think
anybody expected this.
Rookie sensation came in
at the season unknown.
But everyone knows him now.
Will he be the first rookie to win Piston Cup?
And land Dinoco?
The legend, the runner up and the rookie!
Three cars, one champion!
Go get him!
Dinoco is all mine.
Get through that, McQueen!
Huge crash! Unbelievable!
Wait a second Darrell,
McQueen is in the rackage.
There's no way that rookie
can make it through!
Not one piece that is.
Lightning!
Look at him!
McQueen made it through!
Man, a spectacular move
by Lightning McQueen!
Yeah! Good jump!
McQueen! McQueen!
Yeah McQueen! Gotchaaa!
Everyone else heads for the
pimps but McQueen stays out.
To take it for lead!
Don't pick me out,
I can still race!
Ha, what do you think, boys?
What a beauty.
- McQueen made it through!
- What?
He's got pidding!
Go! Get me out of here, let's go!
Get me back up there, come on!
McQueen not going into the pits.
You know the rookie
just fired his crutie.
That's the third one this season.
Well, he says he likes
working alone, Darrell.
It looks like Shet got
caught up in the pits.
Yeah, after a start like that he's
got a lot of ground to make up!
Get ready boys, we're
coming into the restart.
Come on, come on, come on!
We need tires down!
Come on, let's go!
No, no, no!
No tires! Just gas!
You need tires, you idiot!
Looks like it's all gas and
goes for McQueen today.
That's right, no tires again.
Normally I'd say after a short
term game long term walk.
But it sure is working for him.
Hey, maybe he knows
something we don't know.
This is it Darrell. One lap to go and
Lightning McQueen has a huge lead.
Ah, he's gotten into the bay,
calling it nose, put down a fire.
We knew it grab us a new chase.
Checker flag, here I come!
Oh no! McQueen has blown the tire!
In beholding one time to go,
can he make it?
You fool!
McQueen blew a tire,
McQueen blew a tire!
He's lost another tire!
- McQueen checkers coming up fast.
- They are in term three.
Come on!
I don't believe what I'm watching, Bob!
Lightning McQueen is a hundred
feet from his Piston Cup!
The King and Chick rounding turn four.
The Piston Cup and it's.. And it's...
- It's too close to call!
- I don't believe it!
The most spectacular, amazing,
unbelievable in the history of a world!
And we don't even know who won!
Hey no cameras!
Get out of here!
We're here in Victory Lane
awaiting the race results.
McQueen, that was quite a
risky move not taking the tires.
Tell me about it.
Are you sorry you don't
have a crutchie out there?
Kori, there's a lot more
to racing than just winning.
I mean taking a race by a full lap,
where's the entertainment then?
No, no, I want to give
the falks a little sizzle.
Sizzle?
Am I sorry I don't have a crutchie?
No, I'm not. Cause I'm a one man show.
What? Yeah right.
That was a very confident
Lightning McQueen.
Coming to you live from Victory Lane.
Hey, get out of the shot!
Yo, Chuck! Chuck what are you doing,
you're blocking the camera!
Everyone wants to see the bulb.
- What?
- Now back away.
That's it! Come on, guys!
- Wow! Jee! Where are you going?
- We quit, Mr. One Man Show!
Okay, leave. Fine.
How will I ever find anyone else
who knows how to fill me up with gas?
Adios, Chuck.
- And my name is not Chuck!
- Oh, whatever.
Hey Lightning!
Yo, McQueen!
Seriously, that was some pretty
darn nice racing out there.
By me!
Welcome to the Chicker, baby.
Piston Cup, it's mine, dude.
Hey fellows, how do you think
I'd look in Dinoco blue?
Dinoco blue!
- In your dreams, Thunder.
- Yeah, right!
Dundru, why's he talking about thunder?
You know, cause thunder
always comes after Lightning!
- Who here knew about the thunder?
- I didn't.
Show us some boo!
Ladies, that was one close finish.
You sure made Dinoco proud.
Thank you Kenny. Reflection.
You've been good to me all these years.
There's a late stock in this.
Whatever happened, you're a winner
to me, you old getty rabbit.
Thanks dear.
We'll mean that in that tune.
- I'm Mia!
- I'm Tia!
We're like your biggest fans!
I love being me.
We love you Lightning!
Hey buddy, you're a one
good some gracious.
Hey Mr. Lukane.
You got more talent in one lugn, that
a lot of corners has got in whole body.
- Really? Oh, that's...
- That's you're stupid.
Excuse me?
This ain't a one man deal, kid.
You ain't a wize up.
You get yourself a good
crutchie on a good thing.
You ain't gonna win unless
you got good falks behind you.
And you let them very
top like a computer...
Crutchie, yeah.
THE NEW FACE OF DINOCO
THE KING
LIGHTNING McQUEEN
You figure that out,
you're just going to be okay.
Oh, that is spectacular advice.
Thank you Mr. The King.
Ladies and gentlemen, for the
first time in Piston Cup history...
And rookie got won the Piston Cup.
Yes!
We have a three way cars!
Hey McQueen, that must be really embarracing,
but I wouldn't worry about it.
Because I didn't do it!
It's the turn out high wagger race
between the three leaders will be
held in California in one week.
Well thank you, thanks
all of you there. Thanks you.
Hey, rook. First one to California
gets Dinoco autum sulk.
Ah! No, not me! No, you rock!
And you know that!
Oh yeah! Wow!
First one to California
gets Dinoco all-do-himself.
We'll see who gets there first, Chick.
- Hey kid, congrats on a time!
- I don't wanna talk about it.
Come on, let's go Mack. Settle up.
What did you do with my trailer?
- I parked it over here his boss's tit.
- What?
- You gotta make your first of appearance.
- No. No. No, no, no, no!
Yes, yes, yes!
Lightning McQueen here.
And I use a Rust-eze, medicated bumper
ointment, new rear in formula.
Nothing sues a Rusty bumper like Rust-eze!
Actual results may take up to 36 weeks.
Wow! Look at that shine!
Use Rust-eze, and you
too can look like me!
I covered the scot for scotskin.
He was so Rust-eze
he didn't cash a check!
You can see his dirty undercarriage.
I hate rusty cars.
This is not good for my image.
They did gave you a big break.
Besides, it's in your contract.
Will you stop please!
Just go get hottop.
- Winter is a grand old time.
- Of this there are no 'ifs' or 'buts'.
- But remember, all that soltan grind.
- Can rust your bolts and freeze your...
Hey look, there he is!
Our almost there!
Get you rearranded here kid.
- Lucky McQueen, you are wicked ass!
- Yeah you are funky, McQueen!
- Give me a little room, guys.
- You're my hero, Mr. McQueen!
- Yes, I know. Frank, thank you.
- He knows my name! He knows my name!
Look at that, body!
Lightning, we had a better year.
I mean we may even clear it up
to buy you some headlights.
- Are you saying he doesn't have headlights?
- That's what I'm telling you! It's just stickers!
Well you know, race cars don't need headlights,
because the track is always lit.
So is my brother but he still needs headlights!
Ladies and gentlemen, Lightning McQueen!
You know the Rust-eze medicated bumper
ointment team ran a great race today.
And remember, with a little
Rust-eze and cinema lock
you too can look like me.
We love it. And we're looking towards
to another great year, just like this year.
Not on your life.
- Don't drive like my brother!
California, here we come!
Dinoco, here we come!
Ooh, I need this. Hello?
Is this Lightning McQueen the
world's fastest racing machine?
- Is this Harv, the world's greatest agent?
- And it is such an honour to be your agent.
That almost hurts me to
take 10 percent of your winning.
And merchandising and right and property.
Anyway, what a race! Ha, champ?
I didn't see it but I heard you were great.
- Thanks Harv.
- Listen, they're giving you 20 tickets
for the tie breaker in Cally.
I'll pass them on to your friends.
You shoot me the names.
You let hard rocking for you, all right baby?
Right, friends! Yes, there's...
Okay, I get it Mr. Popular so many friends
you can't even near right that.
Hey, when you get to town, you better
make time for your best friend.
- You gotta break brake with Spooky here.
- Yeah, that would be great! We should totally...
Okay, I gotta jump kid, let me
know how it goes. I'm out.
What? A minivan?
Come on, Mack. He's gonna slow me,
Lightning McQueen you're holding here!
Yes, stop it all brick brick kid.
Poor Mack needs a rest.
Absolutely not. We're driving
straight through all night.
Then we get to California.
We can win through it!
All night! Why don't you
spend a real deal, estate.
Come on Mack, I need to get there
before Chick and hand with Dinoco.
All those sleeping trucks.
Hey kid, I don't know if I can make it.
Oh sure you can, Mack.
Look, it'll be easy.
- I'll stay up with you.
- All night?
All night long.
- Hey yo, DJ!
- What up?
We got ourselves a nodder.
Pretty music!
Yo we go! Lane's changed, Mack!
Right by get ya!
- Oops! I missed!
- You go on vacation?
- Oh no, it's Snotrod.
- He's gonna blow!
Once a mere drive went lousy.
Mack!
Mack! Hey Mack!
Mack wait for me!
Mack!
Mack! Mack!
Mack! Mack, wait up!
Mack, Mack!
- You're not Mack!
- Mack?
I ain't no Mack,
I'm a Peterbuilt Red Sack!
Turn on your lights, you moron!
Mack... The innerstate!
ROUTE 66
Not in my town, you dumb.
Oh, no! Oh, maybe he can help me!
Why is he shooting at me?
Why is he shooting at me!
I haven't gone this fast in years.
I'm gonna boo a gasket or something.
What the ballo blazers
crazy hotrunner!
I'm telling you man,
every third blink is slower.
The 60s weren't good to you, were they?
What? That's not the interstate!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm not the only one seeing this, right?
Fly away Stanley! Be free!
Boy, you're in a heap of trouble.
We're live at the Los Angeles
International Speedway
as the first competitor, winky
McQueen is arriving at the track!
- Is it true he's gonna pumch ricardo?
- What's your strategy?
Come on, do not forget
to wipe my munklabs.
LIGHTNING McQUEEN MISSING
McQueen's driver ride in California,
but McQueen was missing.
Race car, Lightning McQueen
was appointed missing.
MISSING
Scheduled race in
an unprecedent...
Spots have stated.
They have no idea where he is.
I just hope Lightning is okay. I sure would hate
to see anything bad happens to him.
I don't know what target to fun, Lightning McQueen
or cruchie who worked with him!
Lightning McQueen must be found at all costs.
They are all asking the same
question, where is McQueen?
Where am I?
Morning, slave admittee!
More Hollywooding
when you're away kid!
Take whatever you want,
just don't hurt me!
Parking? Why do I have a parking midle?
What's going on here please!
You're funny, I like you already.
My name's Mater.
Mater?
Yeah, like domater but without a 'DO'!
- What's your name?
- You don't know my name?
No, I'm not. Is your name Mater too?
What? Look, I need to get
to California as fast as possible.
- Where am I?
- Where are you?
You're in Radiator Springs, the cuttest
little town in Carburetor county.
Oh, great. Just great!
Well, if you think that's great,
you should see the rest of the town.
You know, I'd love to
see the rest of the town!
So if you could just open
the gate, take this boot off.
You and me we go cruise and
check out the local scene, you know.
- Yeah! Good!
- How's that for you, Mater?
Mater! What did I tell you
about talking to the accused?
To not to.
What creet you're yapping totally is doing
what road has it dedtraffic course.
We'll talk later, mater.
Later mater, that's funny!
The Radiator Springs Traffic Court,
come to order!
Hey you sqashed my tire,
I'll blow torch to you!
You brought the road!
I know that about the cars!
Officer, talk to me babe,
how log is this gonna take?
- I gotta get to California pronto.
- Where's your lawyer?
I don't know. Tahiti maybe.
He's gotta timeshare there.
When a defendant has no lawyer,
the court will assign one to him.
Hey! Anyone wanna be his lawyer?
- Hold on, Sheriff!
- All rise.
The honourable Doc Hudson reside of.
Chill off.
May Doc have mercy on your soul.
All right, I wanna know who's responsible
for reckoning my town, Sheriff.
I want this hoot on a platter.
I'm gonna put him in jail till he rots.
Check that, I'm gonna put him
in jail till the jail rots,
on top of the Mandella while
we move him to a new jail,
and when that jail rot,
I'm gonna...
Throw him out of here Sheriff.
I want him out of my courtroom,
I want him out of my town!
- Case dismissed.
- Yes!
You're pretty good with
this lawyer and stuff.
- Sorry I'm late your honour.
- Holy Porshe!
She's gotta be from my attourney's office.
Hey, thanks for coming but we're all set.
He's letting me go.
- He's letting you go?
- Yeah, your job's pretty easy today.
All you have to do now is stand
there and let me look at you.
Listen, I'm gonna cut to
the chase. Me, you, dinner.
What a... Please!
I know, I get that reaction a lot.
I create feelings in anothers that
they themselves don't understand.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I scare you?
Well a little bit,
but I'll be all right.
- Okay... I'm gonna go talk to the judge.
- Do what you're gonna do baby.
Oh but listen be careful,
falks around here
are not firing on all cilinders
if you know what I mean.
I'll keep that in mind.
- Hey there Mater.
- Howdy Howdy.
Hi falks.
- You know her?
- She's a town attourney.
- And my fiancee.
- What?
I'm just kidding. She just
likes me for my body.
Doc, you look great this morning.
Did you do something different
with your side view mirrors?
What do you want, Sally?
Come on, make this guy fix the road.
The town needs this.
No, I know his type. Race car.
The last thing this town needs.
Okay, I didn't wanna to do this Doc,
but you leave me no choice.
Fellow citizens, you're all aware
of our town's proud history.
Here she goes again...
Radiator Springs, the glorious jewel
strung on the necklace of root 66.
The mother road.
It is our job and our pleasure to take care of
the travellers on our strench of that road.
- Travellers! What travellers!
- Ignore him.
But how I ask you are we
to care for those travellers,
if there is no road for them to drive on?
Luigi, what do you have in your store?
Tires.
- And if no one can get to you?
- I won't sell any... tires.
I will lose everything!
- Flo, what do you have in your store?
- I have gas. Lots of gas.
Okay boys, stay with me.
And Flo, what will happen if no one
can come to your station to buy gas?
I'll go out of business and...
will have to leave town.
And what's gonna happen to all of us
if Flo leaves town and closes her station?
So don't you think that car
responsible should fix our road?
The only guy strong enough
to fix that road is Big Al!
- Lizzie, Big Al lived like 15 years ago.
- Then why don't you bring him up here?
Oh he can do it,
he's got the horse power.
So what do you want him to do?
- Fix the road!
Because we are a town worth fixing!
- Yeah!
Quiet in the court!
Seems like my mind
has been changed for me.
- No!
- Nice ruling!
Oh, I am so not taking you to dinner!
That's okay, stickers.
You can take Bessie.
Oh man, you get to work with Bessie!
I give him a little too loading off.
So if I can.
Bessie? Who's Bessie?
This here is Bessie. Finest road
paving machine ever built.
I'm here by sentencing you
to community service.
You're gonna fix the road
under my supervision.
What? This place is crazy!
Hey, I notice that may be
a bad time right now, but...
You owe me a 32 thousand
dollars in legal faith.
What?
So we're gonna hit you up to sweet Bessie
and you're gonna pull her nice.
You gotta be kidding me!
You start there where the road begins.
You finish down there
where the road ends.
Holy shoot!
Wow, wow, wow,
how long is this gonna take?
Well, solid has it right, it should
take him about five days.
Five days? But I should be in California
shmoozing Dinoco right now!
And if I were you, I'd quit
yapping and started working!
- Hook him out, Mater.
- Okey dokey.
Freedom!
Maybe I should have
hook him up to Bessie.
And then... enter to boot off.
RADIATOR SPRINGS
LEAVING SO SOON?
Good-bye, Radiator Springs!
And good-bye, Bessie!
California, here I come! Yeah!
I feel the wind! Yes!
No. No, no, no.
Not a gas!
How could I be out of gas!
Boy, we ain't as dumb
as you think we are.
But how did you?
We safered your gas
while you're past out.
- Gentlemen.
- Sheriff.
Hey Sheriff.
- Why are the tires so here?
- So the simplest queen.
They were better what they were before.
Guido!
Give me more! I wanna get
look at that sexy Hotrod!
Kiddo, how do you pretty good with!
I can't do now of course sometimes
I'll be that fluid built up my engine blocking.
Top shed don't flew
till he fixed my engine.
That's why we made him do this.
Boy you should have
heard me boom om my.
Hotrod would have drive.
Be funky photos see me get all mama.
- Ah man, that's just great!
- Hey what's wrong?
- My lucky stickers are all dirty.
- Nah, it ain't so, I'll clean it for you.
No, no, no, no!
That won't be necessary.
Hey! Hey big fellow!
Yeah, you in the red!
I could use a little host down,
help me wash this all.
- Where's he going?
- Oh, he's just a little bit shy.
- He hates you for killing his flowers.
- I shouldn't have to put up with this!
I'm a precision instrument
of speeding airodynamics.
- You what?
- I'm a very famous race car!
You are a famous race car?
A real race car?
Yes I'm a real race car,
what do you think, look at me!
I'm heard of racing my
entire life for my whole life!
Then you know who I am!
I'm Lightning McQueen.
- Lightning McQueen!
- Yes, yes!
I must excremetaly well, my exciment is
on the top of some place very high!
Do you know many Ferraris?
No, no, no. They race on Europian circuit.
I'm in a Piston Cup!
What?
Luigi, follow the Ferraris.
Is that what I think it is?
Customers.
Customers!
Customers, everyone!
Customers?
Okay, I want everybody
calm down for a long time!
Just remember what we rehearsed!
Make sure you're open this.
Come in signs and out.
And you all know what to do.
All right, nobody panicks, here we go!
Man, I just don't see
any honour anywhere.
- Minny, I know exactly where we are.
- Yeah? We're in the middle of nowhere!
Honey, please!
Hello.
Welcome to Radiator Springs
gateway ornament valley,
legendary for its quality
service and friendly hospitality.
How can we help you?
We don't need anything,
thank you very much.
Honey, ask her directions,
did the interstate.
There's no need to
ask for directions, Minny.
- I know exactly where we're going.
- I did the same thing on Orchard the Shakapi.
You know we were handed
over there for the crazy days.
Okay, okay, really.
We're just pity.
What you really need is this sweet
taste of my hollay organic fuel.
- Doesn't agree with my tank.
- We're just trying to find the interstate.
Good to see you, soldier.
Come on in my serfless after all
your government surfplace needs.
Honey, surplass.
- I think we have too much surpless.
- I do have a map over the Cosy Comer hotel.
And if you do stay we'll offer a
free Lincoln continental breakfast.
- Honey, she's got a map.
- I don't need a map, I have a GPS.
Never need a map again, thank you.
How about something to drink?
Spop it, Flows, BA Capey.
- Finest fuel on the route 66.
- No, we just stopped off.
And if you need tires you stop
by Luigi's Casa Della tires.
- Bon of the leaning tower of tires.
- We're just trying to find the interstate.
But you do need a paint man.
Ramone will paint you up right.
Hey, anything you want.
You know like the flame job.
- Uh, thanks, but...
- Cool flames.
You like all scoop like this?
Bondage tail.
- Honey, look. Londad.
- Okay now.
We're gonna be going now, okay?
A little something to remember us by!
Come back soon, okay?
I mean you know where we are.
Tell your friends.
NICE BUTTE
RADIATOR SPRINGS
- Okay, yes, you bet.
- Thanks again falks. Bye-bye now.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
I know how to get to the interstate!
- Oh, do you?
- Minny, no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, not really.
But listen, I'm Lightning McQueen,
the famous race car.
I'm being held here against my will.
I need you to call my team
so they can come rescue me.
And get me to California to win
the Piston Cup. Do you understand?
No, no, no!
No, no, this is true!
I'm telling you!
You gotta help me!
Don't leave me here!
I'm in Hill Billy hell!
My IQ stopping by the second!
I'm becoming one of them!
Okay, don't worry.
They know where we are now.
They're gonna tell their friends.
You'll see. It's good.
Still no sign of Lightning McQueen.
Meanwhile Chick Hicks
arrived in California.
And today he became the first car
to practice time on the track.
Yeah well, it's just nice to get out here
before the other competitors.
You know we're gonna hand
to harp fish. Kiss me an A.
THE NEW FACE OF DINOCO
THE KING
CHICK
CHICK LIKES DINOCO
CHICK THUNDER HICKS
CHICK MAGNET
Hey McQueen, beat you art out.
Mater, let me get this straight.
I can go when this road is done,
that's the deal, right?
- That's what they done deed saying.
- Okay, out of my way. I gotta road to finish.
- He's done!
- Done?
It's only been an hour.
I'm done. Look, I'm finished.
Just say thank you
and I'll be on my way.
That's all you gotta say.
I'm the first one on the new road!
It might work move!
It looks awful!
Now it matches the rest of the town.
Who do you think you are?
Look, Doc said when
I'm finished, I could go.
- That was a deal.
- A deal was you fix the road.
Not make it worse.
Now scraple on.
Start over again.
Okay look grandpa, I'm not a bulldozer.
I'm a race car.
Ho, is that right? Then why
don't we just have a little race?
- Me and you.
- What?
- Me and you? Is that a joke?
- If you win you go and I fix the road.
- If I win, you do the road my way.
- Doc, what are you doing?
I don't mean to be rude here, Doc.
But your pride goes 0 to 60
in like what, 3.5 years?
Then I reckon you ain't
got nothing to worry about.
You wanna old timer?
That's a wonderful idea.
Let's race!
Gentlemen, this would be a one lap race.
You will drive to Willie's bute or
around Willie's bute and come back.
There will be no bumping, no cheeting,
no spitting, no biting.
No road raging, no mayman,
no oil sucking, no pushing.
No shouting, no backstabbing,
no road hogging and no lover gagging.
Speed, I'm speed.
Block paddle cadillac,
steam like a beemer.
Let's many we don't here
to get a real race car.
- That can't stop.
- Be stop.
The race is only one lap, guys.
Uno lappo! Don't need any help.
- I work solomio.
- Fine, have it your way.
- No pit stoppo. Comprendo?
- Okay!
Gentlemen, start your engines!
Great idea, Doc. Now the
road will never get done.
- Luigi.
- On your mark.
Get set. Uno parlemarli.
Duo for the show.
Three to get ready.
And quatro to...
Go!
Ha?
Doc, the flag means go.
Remember the flag?
Even go. Go.
Doc? What are you doing man?
Oh dear, would see
my off to a poor start.
Well, better late than never.
- Come on Mater, I might need a little help.
- Ooh, okay.
- You got your chow cable?
- I always got my toe cable. Why?
Just in case.
Oh, man!
Hey! Was that flopping like a cadillac?
Or was that stinging like a beemer?
I'm confused.
You drive like you fix roads. Lousy.
Have fun fishing Mater.
I was starting to think
he knew he was gonna cry!
Thank you, Mater. Thank you.
I can make a little turn on dirt.
You think?
No, and now I'm a Damie High.
I'm never gonna get out of here!
- You're needing a paint job man?
- No, thank you!
- How about some organic fuel?
- Freak juice?
Watching him work is making me thirsty.
Anybody wants to have a drink?
No mate, I'm on one of my flavour special diets.
I'm a pries A dramatic
this feed and airomaniac.
You race like you fix roads.
I'll show him.
I will show him!
DOCTOR HUDSON
DR. OF INTERNAL COMBUSTION
Oh, brake!
I hate it!
- Hate! Hate! Hate!
- Music. Sweet music.
- Maybe this wasn't such a good idea.
- Radiator Springs! I'd rather be eaten!
Okay Bessie, you think that's funny?
Great! I'm talking to Bessie now!
I'm talking to Bessie!
Wow!
Morning, Sally!
Hey look at this, fancy new road that
Lightning McQueen done this night!
Amazing!
Ramone, mama ain't seen you
that low in years.
- I haven't seen a road like this in years.
- Well then let's cruise baby!
No, ain't slow.
Bellissimo, oh so beautiful!
Guido look, it's like
it was built by angels.
I'll tell you what, I bet even
the road on the moon like this smooth.
Doc, look at this.
Should toast him
into a cac lot suiter.
Well he ain't finished yet.
Still got a long way to go.
Dunito, rucca Luigi!
This is fantastico!
That looks like fun.
Mater I got paves, next turn!
Hey Luigi, this new road make
your place look like a dump!
Oh! That crazy old devil woman!
She's right! Guido!
That punk actually did a good job.
Well now, where the hack is he?
Sheriff? Is he making another run for it?
No, no. He ran out an assfull
in the middle of the night.
Asked me if he can get down here.
All he's trying to do
is make that carve turn.
No, no, no!
Ah, great! I've turned on every
track on every race track.
Sheriff, why don't you go get
yourself a quarter of oil that flows.
- I'll keep an eye on him.
- Well thanks, Doc!
I've been feeling about a quart of load.
- This ain't ass fold son, this is dirt.
- Oh great, what do you want?
You're here to globe?
You don't have three wheel brakes,
so you gotta pitch it hard.
Brake it loose and just
drive it with a throttle.
Give it too much and you'll be
out of the dirt within the tulip.
So you're judge, the doctor
and the racing expert.
I'll put it simple, if you're going hard enough left,
you'll find yourself turning right.
Oh, right. That makes perfect sense.
Turn right to go left! Yes! Thank you!
Or should I say:
No, thank you!
Because in opposite world maybe
that really means thank you!
Crazy grandpa car.
What an idiot!
Turn right to go left.
Turn right to go left!
Guess what? I tried it!
And you know what?
This crazy thing happened!
I went right!
You keep talking to yourself,
people will think you're crazy.
- Thanks for the tip!
- What?
I wasn't talking to you!
Oh Guido, bellissimo!
It looks great!
This is great!
Uh, Lord.
Mater, I need you to watch
the prisoner tonight.
It'll be done! Wait a minute,
what if he tries to run again?
Just let him run out of
gas and tour him back.
- But keep an eye on him.
- Yes sir!
I'm stuck here paving
the stinking road!
Chick's in California shmoozing Dinoco.
My Dinoco!
Wow, who's touching me!
You have a slow leak.
Guido, he'll fix.
You're making such a nice road.
You come to my shop and Luigi
take a good care of you.
Even though you're not a Ferrari.
You buy four tires, I give you and
full sizes there episodal liquid.
Look, I get all my tires for free.
Look at his style!
He's driving a hard bargain.
Luigi make you anovile, you
buy one tire, I give you three.
Would you look at that!
Ramone, Ramone.
This is it, my last orc. You buy one tire,
I give you seven tires for free!
Done. If you're interested,
you go to my place.
Oh Red, you missed the spot.
Right there. In the hood.
Help! Please!
Stop!
Thanks Red.
- What was that for?
- Do you wanna stay at the Cosy Cone or what?
If you do, you gotta be clean, cause even
here in Hillbilly Hall we have standards.
- I don't get it.
- Nothing.
I just thought I'd say thank you
for doing a great job.
That's what I thought,
I'd like you to stay with me.
Or not with me! But there.
Not with me there, but there
in your own Cozy Cone.
And I'll be in my Cone, and...
Wait, you're being nice to me.
I mean if you wanna stay at
the beauty impale, that's fine.
- You know I understand your criminal types.
- No, no, it's okay. The Cozy Cone.
It's newly referbished.
Yeah, it's like a clever little twist
on motels made out of cation,
which of course cars
usually try to avoid,
but now we're gonna
stay in them. That's fun.
Take all that on your own, did you?
Cone number one if you want.
Hey, do I spot little pin
stripe tattoo back there?
That's just...
Ah, you saw that?
Just gonna be going... Yeah.
You know whose girl is doloraine?
Good looking girl.
Just like a Jaguar.
Only she was a truck.
You know, I used to cry hand to her,
just so I could speak to it.
- What are you talking about?
- I don't know.
Hey, I know something we can do tonight,
cause I'm in charge of watching you.
No Mater, I gotta finish this road
and I have to get out of here.
Well that's all right,
Mr. I-Can't-Turn-On-Dirt.
- You probably couldn't handle it anyway.
- Wow, easy now Mater.
You know who you're talking to,
this is Lightning McQueen.
I can handle anything.
- Mater, I'm not doing this!
- Oh come on, you'll love it!
- Tractor tip is fun!
- This is ridiculous.
All right, listen.
When I say go, we go.
But don't let Frank catch you. Go!
Who's Frank?
Wait, Mater!
This is what you do,
you just sneak up in front of him.
And then hunk, they'll do
the rest. Watch this.
I just wanted,
turtle is so doomed.
Okay, you are back, you don't
get much better than this.
Yep, you're living in a dream, Mater boy.
I don't care who you are,
that's funny!
- Your turn, bud.
- Mater, I can't.
I don't even got a horn.
- Baby.
- I'm not a baby.
Stop, stop, okay?
I'll do something.
That's Frank.
Hey, look out!
He's gonna get you!
Oh, customers!
Ah, no, no, no.
Tomorrow night we can
go look for the ghost line.
- I can't wait, Mater.
- Oh, yeah!
Oh boy, you gotta admit,
that was fu-un!
Oh yeah, yeah.
Well, we better get you
back to the impound law.
You know I actually Sally's
gonna let me stay at the motel.
- Getting cosy at the cone, is we?
- No, come on, are you kidding?
Besides she can't stand me.
I don't like her, to be honest.
Yeah, you're probably right.
- Hey look, there's Sally!
- Where, where?
You're in love with miss Sally.
- No, I'm not.
- Yes, you do, do.
- No way.
- Way.
- You're in love with miss Sally!
- That's a real mature, real grown-up.
You love her, you love her,
you love her, you love her.
Mater, enough.
Will you stop that?
- What?
- That driving backwards stuff.
It's creeping me out.
You're gonna rack or something.
Rack? Shoot.
I'm the world best backwards driver.
Is what he's right here, lover boy.
What are you doing?
Watch out!
Mater? Mater?
Hey, take it easy, Mater!
He's nuts!
Ain't no need to watch where I'm going!
- Just need to know where I've been.
- That was incredible! How did you do that?
Rear view mirrors. We'll get you
something in Al Deit if you want.
Yeah, maybe I'll use
them in my big race.
What's so important about
this race of yours anyway?
It's not just a race. We're talking
about the Piston Cup.
I've been dreaming
about it my whole life!
I'll be the first rookie
in history ever to win it.
And when I do, we're talking big news
sponsor with private helicopters.
No more medicated bumper ointment,
no more rusty old cars.
What's wrong with rusty old cars?
I don't mean you, Mater.
I mean other old cars.
- You know not like you, I like you.
- It's okay body.
Are you doing maybe one day I can get
a ride in one of them helicopters?
I mean I've always wanted to ride
in one of them fancy helicopters.
- Yeah, yeah, sure, sure.
- You mean it?
- Oh yeah, anything you say.
- I knew it.
- I know I made a good choice!
- In what?
My best friend.
See you tomorrow body!
Queen aunt Sally,
parking made a treat!
Number one, number one.
Ah, number one!
- This is nice!
- Hey stickers.
- I'm sorry.
- You scared me!
You gotta be careful.
- I scared myself scaring you scaring me.
- I mean that wasn't like scare scares.
- No, of course not.
- There was more...
- Just I overheard you talking to Mater.
- When? Just now? What did you hear?
Oh, just something
about a helicopter ride.
Oh yeah, he got a kick out
of that, didn't he?
- Did you mean it?
- What?
- That you'll get him a ride?
- Oh, who knows?
I mean first thing's first, I gotta get out
of here and make the race.
- You know, Mater trusts you.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Did you mean that?
- What?
Was it just a 'Yeah, okay' or
'Yeah, okay' or 'Yeah, okay'?
Look, I'm exhausted,
it's kinda been a long day.
Yeah, okay.
Good night.
Hey, thank you.
- What did you just say?
- Thanks for letting me stay here.
It's nice to be out of the impound,
and this is, it's great.
- Newly furbished, right?
- Yeah.
- Good night.
Where you town this
disrespectful joke off!
Respect the classics, man.
It's Hendrix!
No!
I gotta get out of here!
Hey, have you seen the Sheriff?
- Hey, what are you doing?
- You need a good pit, city boy?
I just need my daily gas
rush from the Sheriff.
Wait forward flows,
now get out of here!
I've been trying to get out
of here for three days!
I hope you enjoy the show!
Ho, Doc. Time to clean out
the garage, body.
HUDSON HORNET
CHAMPION 1951
What?
He has a Piston Cup?
Oh my Gosh!
Three Piston Cups?
HUDSON HORNET
CHAMPION 1952
CHAMPION 1953
HUDSON HORNET
CHAMPION FOR ALL TIME
Science has stayed out.
You have three Piston Cups,
how could you...
I knew you couldn't drive,
I didn't know you couldn't read.
You're the Hudson Hornet!
Wait over at flows, like I told you!
Of course, I can't believe
I didn't see you before!
You're the fabulous Hudson Hornet!
You still hold the records
for most wins in a single season.
Ah, we gotta talk. You gotta
show me your tricks, please!
I already tried that!
You won the championship three times!
Look at those tropheys!
You look! All I see is
a bunch of empty cups.
You know, sumota motor yogurts
can really lower your heart peedun.
Oh, take your carwash, hippy.
Hey! Look at my husband yo!
There's your come.
- You know baby.
- You're smoking hot!
There he is.
Did you know Doc was
a famous race car?
- Doc? Our Doc?
- No, no, no, it's true!
He's a real racing legend!
He's a fabulous Hudson Hornet!
Fabulous? I never seen Doc drive
more than 20 miles per hour!
- I mean have you ever seen him race?
- No, but I wish I could have.
They say he was amazing!
He won three Piston Cups!
He did what in his cup?
I think he'd started
to get to the boy!
I'll say, look how red he is!
I think he needs a
little cortle parley man!
- Are you sick mate?
- You're all looking a little picket.
He ain't needs no
quarter parley for sure!
Hey, what are you doing?
It's okay Sheriff, you can trust me, right?
I trust you all right,
it's him I'm worried about.
I trust him.
Come on, let's take a drive.
- A drive?
- Yeah, a drive.
Aren't you big city race cars
ever just take a drive?
No, we don't.
Hey Stickers!
You're coming or what?
- And you thought he was gonna run.
- Can you believe it man?
He actually thought Doc
was a famous race car!
Smoke too much.
Okay you got me out here,
where we're going?
I don't know.
Oh, yes.
Wow! What is this place?
Well well, used to be the most
popular stop on the mother road.
This place?
Yeah, imagine.
I imagine what it must
have been like to stay here.
You know I don't get you. How does
a Porshe wind up in a place like this?
Well, it's really pretty simple,
I was an attourney in LA.
- Living life in a fast lane.
- Oh you were, weren't you?
- Were you rich?
- What?
- Just clues to the puzzle.
- Yeah, okay.
Well, that was my life
and you know what?
It never felt... happy.
- Yeah... I mean really?
- Yeah, so I left California.
Just drove and drove and
finally broke down right here.
Doc picks me up,
Flo took me in.
They all did. I never left.
No, I understand you
mean a little R&R.
Recharge your old batteries, but after
a while why didn't you go back?
I fell in love.
- Oh.
- Yep.
- Corvette?
- No.
I fell in love with this.
Look at that!
Look at them driving right by, they don't
even know what they're missing!
Well it didn't used to be that way.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
Fourty years ago that interstate
down there didn't exist.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Back then cars came across
the country a whole different way.
How do you mean?
Well the road didn't cut through
the land like that interstate.
It moved with the land and now
it rolls that fellow occurred.
- Good morning.
- Nice day, ha?
Cars didn't drive on it to make great time.
They drove on it to have a great time.
Long ago, but not so very long ago.
The world was different, oh yes it was.
You settle down in your
built town and made it there.
And you watched the grow,
it was your town.
What happened?
The town got by-passed just to save
ten minutes of driving.
Time goes by and time brings changes.
You changed too.
Nothing cause that you
can't handle so on you go.
You never see it coming, when
the world cames in on you.
On your town nothing you can't do.
Main street isn't main street anymore.
No one seems in needers
like they did before.
It's hard to find a reason left to stay.
But it's our town.
You love it anyway.
Come what may, it's our town.
How great would it be to
see this place in its hayday.
Can't tell you how many times
I have dreamed of that.
That one of these days we'll find
a way to get it back on the map.
Yeah... Hey listen,
thanks for the drive.
I had a great time. It's kinda nice
to slow down every once in a while.
You're welcome.
Hey listen, listen if anybody asks you,
we was out some ice mail boxes, okay?
What?
Oh man, the paint's still wet!
No, no, no, get out of a store.
Hey! Don't be deradium!
Here, take this snow tires.
Then where did all these call
dirts transports come from?
Hey, hey guys.
There's one going this way.
I got it.
Come here, little tractor.
Come here.
Yeah, it's a good tractor.
No, no, come here.
What are you doing? You're not supposed
to go wondering all for... alone.
What are you doing with
all those racing tires?
Come on, Doc. Drive!
Wow! You're amazing!
What are you doing?
Doc! Wait!
Come on, tractor!
Doc, hold it seriously!
Your driving's incredible!
- Wonderful. But go away.
- But I mean you still got it!
- I'm asking you to leave!
- Come on, I'm a race car, you're...
a much older race car but under
the hood you and I are the same!
We are not the same!
Understand, now get out!
How could a car like you quit
at the top of your game?
You think I quit?
CRASH!
HUDSON HORNET
OUT FOR SEASON
Right... You're big reckon 54.
They quit on me.
When I finally got put together,
I went back expecting a big welcome.
You know what they said?
You're history. Move right on to
the next rookie standing in line.
That was a lot left in me.
I never got a chance to show them.
I keep that to remind me
never to go back.
I just never expected that
that world would... find me here.
Hey look Doc, I'm not them!
- Oh yeah?
- No, I'm not!
When was the last time you cared about
something except for yourself, hotrod?
You name me one time
and I will take it all back.
I didn't think so.
These are good falk around here.
Who care about one another.
I don't want them depending
on someone they can't count on.
Oh like you? You've been here how long and
your friends don't even know who you are.
- Who's caring about only himself?
- Just finish that road and get out of here!
- Will you turn that disrespectful took off!
- Respect the classics man!
He's done. He must have finished it
while we was all sleeping.
Good riddens.
He's gone?
Well, we wouldn't want him
to miss that race of his.
- Oh dude, are you crying?
- No, I'm happy!
I don't have to watch him
every second of the day anymore!
I'm glad he's gone!
- What's wrong with Red?
- Oh, he's just sad cause you left to town
and went to your big race
to win the Piston Cup
that you've always dreamed
about your whole life
and get that big old sponsor and that
fancy helicopter you was talking about.
Wait a minute!
I know you wouldn't leave
without saying you left!
What are you doing here son,
you're gonna miss your race!
Don't worry, I'll give you the police
escort and we'll make out on time.
Thank you Sheriff.
But you know I can't go just yet.
Why not?
I'm not sure these tires can
get me all the way to California.
Pit stop?
Yeah, does anybody might
know what time Luigi's opens?
I can't believe it!
Four new tires!
- Gracia, Mr. Lightning, gracia!
- Would you look at that!
Out first real customer in years!
I am filled with tears of extasy!
For this is the most
glorious day of my life!
All right, Luigi. Give me the best
set of black holes you've got.
No, no, no, you don't
know what you want.
Luigi know what you want.
Black wool tires.
They blend into the beam.
But these, white wool tires basic:
Look at me! Here I am!
Love me.
All right, you're the expert!
- Oh, and don't forget the spare.
- Perfecto. Guido!
Pit stop!
- What did Luigi tell you?
- You were right!
- Better than a Ferrarri, ha?
- Ah, no.
Wow, this organic fuel is great!
- Why haven't I heard it about before?
- It's a conspiracy man!
They all companies got
a grip on a gun man!
- They feed us a bunch of lives, man.
- Okay, I'll take a case.
Here she come!
Okay, places everybody!
All right! Act natural!
- Hello Sally!
All right, what's going on?
Ladies and gentlecars!
Please welcome the
new Lightning McQueen!
Well, what do you think? Radiator
Springs looks pretty good on me.
I'll say aghrr...
You're gonna fit right in in California.
Oh my goodness, it looks like
you've helped everybody in town!
Everybody except one.
- Hey, is it getting dark out?
- What? What did he say?
Let me say that again.
Is it getting dark out!
Now what does this
much to do after that?
They fixed the neon.
- Low and slow?
- Oh yeah, baby!
Just like in its hayday, right?
It's even better than I pictured it.
Thank you.
- Shall we cruise?
- Absolutely, I'd love to!
Wessie!
I remember when Stanley first
asked me to take a drive with him...
Hey miss Sally.
May I have this cruise?
Of course Mater.
And then I said - No!
And he asked me again and I said - No!
Well, he was a persistent
little bugger for a two cilinder.
- Hey!
- Thanks, Mater.
Good evening you two.
Oh, Stanley.
I wish you could see this.
Is that what I think it is?
I don't know Flo, I hadn't
had a chance to find out.
But I am going to find out hello.
- Not that. That!
- Customers?
Customers everybody!
And a lot of them!
You know what to do?
Just let them a huss!
It's the ghost ride!
We have found McQueen!
Oh wait, excuse me.
- Is that true you've been at rehab?
- Did you have a nervous breakdown, McQueen?
I'm sorry what?
Stickers! McQueen!
- Who's got McQueen prisoner?
- Shoot no, we're best buds!
I'm riding that, but I can beat
him down you see try to it sky.
Sally! Sally!
McQueen, are you still
getting for the Piston cup?
- Stickers!
- Sally!
You're here!
Thanks to manufacturer,
are you all right?
- Mack?
- You're here!
I can't beleve it.
You are a second Stringling light!
I'm so sorry I was covunce.
I'll make it up to you!
Mack, I can't believe you're here!
- Is that the world's fastest racer machine?
- Is that Harv?
Get back you oil thirsty parasytes!
Excellent, this is my good siridea.
Harv! Harv!
- Harv?
- I'm over here.
How you're doing body?
My star client has appeared
on the 'Face Of The Earth'!
- How do you think I'm doing?
- Harv, I can explain.
I'm doing great!
You're everywhere baby!
Radio, TV, the papers. You can't
buy this kind of publicity.
What do you need me for?
That's just the bigger speech,
by the way you signed the contract.
Where are you?
I can't even find you on my GPS!
I'm in this little town
called Radiator Springs.
- You know Route 66, it's still here!
- Yeah, that's great kid.
Play time is over pal.
While the world's been trying to find you,
Dinoco has has no one to wuw.
- Who are they gonna wuw?
- Chick.
Bingo! In fact check out
what's on the plazma right now.
- Show us the Thunder!
- You want Thunder?
You want Thunder!
Hey, that's my bid!
You gotta get to Cally pronto.
Just get out of Radiation Stinks now,
or Dinoco is history, you hear me?
Just give me a second here, Harv.
No, no, where are you going?
Get in the trailer baby!
You want a bigger trailer?
Sally, I want you to...
Look I wish...
Thank you.
Thanks for everything.
- That was just the road.
- No, it was much more than that.
Hey kid, we gotta go.
Harv's going crazy!
He's gonna have me fired if I don't
get you in the truck right now!
- Mack, just hold it.
- You should go.
- I know but...
- Good luck in California.
I hope you'll find what you're looking for.
Sally... Sally...
Come on kid, get in the trailer.
That's right. Go!
You're big shot, you're a superstar.
You don't belong there anyway.
Hey guys, McQueen's leaving in the truck!
Hey, are you Doc Hudson?
- Yeah.
- Thanks for the call.
- You called them?
- It's best for everyone, Sally.
Best for everyone?
Or best for you?
I didn't get to say good-bye to him.
Hello race fans and
welcome to what has become
quite simply the biggest event
in the history of racing.
A three-way battle
for the Piston Cup.
Bob, there's a crowd of
a nearly 200 thousand cars
here at the Los Angeles
International Speedway.
Tickets to this race are hotter than
a blood better seat on a hot summer day.
The King, Chick Hicks and
Lightning McQueen in a 200 lap.
Winner takes all, tie break a race.
Come on, he knew I got
a lot of mouse on way,
but let me tell you something body,
I've never thought I'd see anything like this!
Man, this is exciting!
In fact the country is
almost shut down to watch
what many experts are calling
the race of the century.
Hey King, good luck in your last race.
You're sure been in this race good to you.
Thanks junior, I appreciate it.
- Hey, be careful out there okay?
- Yeah, ma'am.
Oh yeah, you wanna the forecast?
I'll do you the forecast.
A hundred percent chance of Thunder!
Say with me!
Hey you! No quittens
without a garage pass.
Oh, it's okay.
Lightning McQueen knows me!
Hey Marco, it's a beautiful
day for a race, isn't it?
- Absolutely Mr. Andretti.
- And good morning to you, Fred.
Mario Andretti knows my name!
- They gotta let me in now!
- Sorry pal...
Okay, here we go.
Focus. Speed.
I am speed.
Victory. One winner.
Two losers.
Speed! Speed.
Speed. Speed...
Yeah, yeah, I'm ready.
Mack, thanks for being
my pit crew today.
Don't worry about it kid.
It's the least I could do.
After all gas can
is my middle name.
- It is?
- Yeah, not really.
PISTON CUP
Nausing, zoom in 20-16, 10-16.
And there he is, Lightning McQueen
missing all week
and then he turns up
in the middle of nowhere!
In a little town called Radiator Springs
where in quite law tiles of all things.
Hey where you've been McQueen?
I've been kinda lonely.
Nobody to hang out with.
I mean except the Dinoco falks.
Oh, and the twins of course.
You know the twins used to be your fans,
but now they're my fans.
Anyway, listen to what the twins say...
Let's go race it!
- Come on, you can do it!
- Come on King, we're just proud boy!
Fifty laps down and The King
is still holding a slim lead.
And McQueen's gotta run on him!
He's looking to the inside!
Oh, he slammed the door on him!
Chicks not making an
easy autumn today.
Man, he go so much formittable,
now he's gonna chasing back down.
Oh, McQueen spins out on the in-field.
Ha-ha! Just me and
the old man, fellows.
McQueen just settled
the weather today.
- Hey kid, are you all right?
- I don't know Mack.
I don't think I...
I didn't come all this
way to see you quit.
Doc?
Guys, you're here!
I can't believe this!
I knew you needed a crew, chief.
But I didn't know it was this bad.
I thought you said
you'd never come back.
Well, I really didn't have a choice.
Mater didn't get to say good-bye.
Good-bye!
Okay, I'm good.
RADIATOR SPRINGS
RACING TEAM
All right, you can ride as
good as you can fix the road,
then you can win this race
with your eyes shut.
Now get back out there!
Hot snock, we are back in business.
Guido, Luigi, you're going up against
professional pick cruise boys.
You're gonna have to be fast.
They will not know what bit them!
Kid, you can beat these guys.
Fine the groove that works
for you and get that lap back.
- Is it?
- That's him!
Is that...
That's the Hudson Hornet!
Bob, Darrell,
the Hudson Hornet is back!
Darrell, it appears McQueen
has got himself a pit crew.
And look who he has for a crew chief.
Wow, look man, this is a Hudson Hornet!
- Big man, call me slick!
- He surely is!
Wow, this is history in the making.
Nobody has seen the racing
legend in over 50 years!
Hey Doc! Come look at this
from the home avenue.
He looks just like you!
- McQueen has his the lonely inside!
- But he's still nearly a lap failed!
And he catches up to them
with only 60 laps to go!
You're going great kid,
just keep your head up.
- All right! Right! Right!
- Hey trippy, where did McQueen find you?
Those round things are called tires.
And they go under the car!
No, you will have your chance,
we know you will have your chance.
Kid's just trying to be a hero, ha?
What do you think of this?
Yeah, that's it, kid!
What?
Wow! Get him at!
I taught him that.
What a move by McQueen,
he's caught up to the leaders.
Oh yeah, this is what it's all about!
Three way barrel for
the lead with ten to go!
Look at that boy go right there!
Yeah, well you're dumped.
- Doc I'm flat, I'm flat!
- Can you get back to the pits?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Hey, got a yellow, bring it in.
Don't tear yourself up, kid.
We gotta get him back there fast!
Or we're gonna be a lot down
movement ever to win this race!
Guido, it's time.
Hey tiny, you're gonna
clean his windshield?
I don't believe it!
That was the fastest
pit stop I've ever seen!
He was in brace stop but he's still
gotta be careful at brace car out.
It's gonna be close!
Yeah, back in the race!
Pit stop.
Guido!
This is it, we're having another final lap
and McQueen is right behind the leaders.
What a combat!
199 laps and baby it
all comes down to this!
This is it kiddo, you got
four turns left one at the time.
Drive in deep and hope it sticks. Go!
McQueen is going inside.
- Chick and The King are loose.
- I think McQueen is out of the race!
- McQueen saves!
- He's back on the track!
- Hope like a Cadillacs?
- Steam like a Beemer!
Lightning McQueen is
gonna win the Piston Cup!
Come on! You've got it,
you've got it, Stickers!
I'm not coming in again
behind you, old man.
Oh, no!
Yeah! Woo-hoo!
I won baby! Yeah!
What's he up to Doc?
What are you doing, kid?
I think The King should
finish his last race.
You just gave up a Piston Cup,
you know that?
Ah, it's curn field race car and
no one's told me something.
It's just an empty cup.
Darrell, is pushing
on the last cup legal?
Hey man, he's not really pushing him,
he's just giving him a little pump rap.
Hey! What?
What's going on?
That's a lot of racing out there.
- We're all mo and the mio mit.
- Way to go, body!
There's a lot of love out there,
you know man?
Don't embarass me Filmore.
That's my Hotrod.
Come on baby, bring it out!
Bring out the Piston Cup!
Yeah, now that's
what I'm talking about!
Hey! How come the only
one's celebrating is me?
Where are the girls?
Bring on the confetti!
Easy with the confetti,
what's going on?
Come on snap some pictures,
I gotta go sign my deal with Dinoco!
Say with me!
What's wrong with everybody?
This is now Chick era!
- Thanks, Lightning.
- You're welcome.
Way to go King!
You made us proud, kid.
Congrats on a loss, bucko.
- You got a lot of stuff, kid.
- Thanks, Doc.
Hey Lightning, how about coming over
to me and talking for a minute?
Son, now that was some
real racing out there.
How'd you like to become
the new face of Dinoco?
But I didn't win.
Lightning, there's a whole lot more
to racing, than just winning.
Thank you Mr. Tex, but these Rust-eze
guys over there gave me my big break.
- I wanna stand with them.
- Well, I sure can respect that.
Still you know if there's
ever anything I can do for you,
just let me know.
I sure appreciate that.
Thank you.
Actually, there is one thing.
Hey look at me!
I'm flying!
I'm happy in the tornado
in the traid parlots!
Do you think it's about
the time we redecorate?
Hi, Lightning Mcqueen told me this was
the best place in the world to get tires.
How about setting me and my friends up
with three full sets each?
It's a real Michael Shumacher Ferrari!
A real Ferrari!
Punch me Guido.
Punch me in the face.
This is the most glorious day of my life.
Just passing through?
Actually I thought stuff and stay a while.
I hear this place is back on the map.
It is?
Yeah, there's some rumor floating around
that some hot shot Piston Cup race car's
setting up his big racing headquarters here.
Really? Oh, well there goes the town.
I really missed you Sally.
Well I create feelings in others
don't understand and
blah, blah, blah, blah.
McQueen and Sally,
hard to make on three!
Hey ya ask is I in teen!
Pretty timing Mater!
It's my best friend,
what you're gonna do.
So Stickers, last one
that flows buys?
I don't know, why don't
we just take a drive?
Hm.. Nah.
directed by
JOHN LASSETER