"...thirst is more powerful
than the fear of poison..."
Beyond Desire
Come  in.Come  in.
What do you need?
Rogelio. I'm Elvira Fuentes.
Don't you remember me?
- Oh my, so much time has gone by.
- Yeah.
How are you?
- Well, well.
- What do you need?
Lola left me a message,
something about a job.
- Lola?
- Yes.
Lola. Lola.
What?
- Elvira.
- Hello.
Elvira, you're so beautiful.
You were just a kid
the last time I saw you.
At your poor dad's birthday party.
Before the war.
You remember?
She looks like him, right?
Tell me. How is your mother?
And your sister, and Julio?
Well. Julio is still in Carabanchel,
but he'll get out soon.
My mom is still the same.
We're doing okay.
And your son?
In Mexico, since the war ended.
He's lucky he found a good job.
- But he's far away.
- Not that far.
We're getting old and
we're so alone.
Stop that. Elvira is here
for another reason.
It's a good job, I think.
Right, Rogelio?
Of course it is.
It pays 50 pesetas per week.
The time is 9 to 12.
The man lives alone, an Argentine.
He's a business man
and he's single.
He travels a lot,
business related, you know.
You'll do the usual:
cleaning, ironing, cooking.
It's a good job.
Can you start tomorrow?
Yes, of course.
- Good morning, Pedro.
- Good morning, miss.
Hello.
I already took the coal
to your mother's.
Thank you so much.
So?
It's settled. I have a job.
I'm so happy, Elvira.
Be happier,
it pays 50 pesetas per week, mornings only.
You're so lucky.
- How are they? How is Lola?
- Same as usual. The same.
She sends you a lot of kisses.
This way, please.
Thank God. I finally made it.
The claustrophobia nearly drove me insane.
You shouldn't complain so much,
Herr von Bibrach.
These are rough times for everyone.
You're right, Frau Henkel.
Please, forgiver me.
These are the names,
the most important ones.
I'm sorry, but we have to
get back to Madrid tonight.
We should take a look
at these documents immediately.
A good meal is waiting for us at home.
And a hot bath if you like.
They seem all right.
Rogelio has gained some weight.
He's as bitter as ever.
But I found them very well.
It's so great, Mother.
I start tomorrow.
This is the kitchen.
What do you think?
Beautiful.
Let me show you the rest of the house.
This is the dining room.
That way.
A lot of money, a lot of luck.
Be careful not to break anything,
we'd get in trouble.
Don't worry, it won't happen.
Okay, I'll leave you alone.
You enter the library that way.
It's big, but don't worry.
Lola will help you.
Thank you.
- See you later, Elvira.
- See you later.
"How can I tell my soul not to touch yours"
"How I lift it over..."
- Good morning.
- Elvira?
- Yes.
I'm Pablo Balther. Nice to meet you.
- Rogelio told me you'd be here.
- Nice to meet you.
Hello.
- Do you like Rilke?
- Yes.
I do too.
Do you need me to explain
anything else about the house?
No, if you'd excuse me.
Yes, of course.
Rilke?
You think it's normal a maid
likes to read Rilke?
Pardon me.
I've finished.
Your lunch is ready.
If you don't need anything else...
No, nothing else.
Excuse me.
You can take it if you'd like.
Return it later.
Thank you very much.
- I'll bring it back tomorrow.
- Whenever you want.
- Thank you.
- See you tomorrow.
He's handsome.
Very polite.
Well dressed.
But that's easy being rich, right?
The library is the best, Mother.
It's beautiful.
Ours was bigger.
And it had more books,
I'm sure of it.
Do you remember how Father
would make us take care of it?
Hopefully, this will end soon so
we may have a decent home.
I'll go get more water.
- Hello, Rogelio, good afternoon.
- Good afternoon, sir.
- Rogelio.
- Yes, sir.
What are Elvira's references?
The new maid.
My wife took care of it.
Is anything the matter?
No, no, but tell Lola
I want to see her.
She's buying groceries.
Tell her to see me
when she returns.
Sir, there's nothing to worry about.
We've known Elvira since
she was little.
She comes from a good family.
Her father was an extraordinary man,
a doctor.
The world's kindest man.
But he died and...
... the family lost everything.
Things happen.
But they're good people.
Very good. Thank you, Rogelio.
Sir, do you still want to see Lola?
No, it won't be necessary, thank you.
- Good afternoon.
Good morning.
Great, it had been a while since
someone cleaned the library.
[ Skipped item nr. 136 ]