Americans are asking
Why do they hate us.
They hate what they see
right here in this chamber.
A democratically elected government.
Their leaders are self-appointed.
They hate our freedoms.
Our freedom of religion.
Our freedom of speech.
Our freedom to vote in assemble
and disagree with each other.
They went over though existing governments
in many Muslim countries
such as Egypt, Saudi Arabia and Jordan.
FATWA
NOUN: a ruling on a point of islamic law
given by a recognized authority
They want to drive Israel
out of the middle east.
They want to drive Christians and Jews
out of vast regions of Asia and Africa.
These terrorists kill not merely to end lives.
But to disrupt and
end a way of life.
With every atrocity they hope
that America grows fearful.
Retreating from the world
and forsaking our friends.
They stand against us because
we stand in their way.
We're not received by
their pretenses to piety.
We have seen their kind before.
They're the heirs of all the murderer's
ideologies of the 20th century.
By sacrificing human life
to serve their heretical visions.
By abandoning every value
except the will to power.
They follow in the path of fascism,
Nazism and totalitarianism.
And they will follow their path
all the way to where it ends.
In history's unmarked grave of discarded lives.
Americans are asking:
How do we fight to win this war?
No, leave it on, leave it on!
What was that miss Goldman?
Oh, you wanna be a volunteer.
All right, would you put down the
cigarette for just a moment. Thank you.
The Arabian peninsula has never sensed...
The Arabian peninsula has never sensed it.
Ring in by deserts and
encircled with seas.
Been surrounded by any forces like the
crusade armies spreading in like locust
eating its riches and
wiping out its plantations.
All this is happening at a
time in which nations
are attacking Muslims like people
fighting over a plate of food.
In light of the graved situation
and lack of support
we and here should
discuss current events
and we should all agree
on unsettled matter.
First, for over seven years
the United States
has been occupying lands of
Islam and the holiest of places.
The Arabian Peninsula plundering
its riches, dictating to its rulers,
simulating against people
terrorising its neighbours
and turning its spaces in
the peninsula into a spearhead
through which to fight the
neighbouring Muslim people.
If some people having a pass are
eager of the fact of the occupation
all the people in the peninsula
have now acknowledged it.
The best proof...
Put the fucking headphones off!
The best proof of this is the Americans are
continuing agression against the Iraqi people.
Using a peninsula as a stating
post even though all of its rulers
are against their territories being
used to that, but they are helpless.
All these crimes and sins
committed by the Americans
are a clear declaration of war on Allah,
its messenger and Muslims.
On that basis and in
compliance with Allah's order
we issue to following fatwa...
- Fatwa.
Fatwa. We issue to following
fatwa to utmost person.
The ruling to kill the Americans and
their allies and civilians and military
is an individual duty for every Muslim
who can do it in any country
in which it is possible to do it.
Osama Bin Laden, 1998.
Well, that's some tough shit.
Thank you.
A world divided.
Therefore the question becomes:
Is it possible to love an enemy who hates you?
Or should that enemy be destroyed
before it destroys you?
Need I remind you that our
sovereign shores were corrupted
by an evil that knows no boundaries.
We cannot stand idly by affording our
enemies an opportunity to strike again.
Taking the offensive is not our choice.
It is our solemn duty.
Our ethical promise to our children
and to the future of the free world.
Thank you.
- Senator!
Thank you, Senator.
Senator Maggie Davidson.
Thank you.
Twenty-three please.
What's up?
- Sorry for the inconvenience.
- Apology accepted.
Excuse me.
Have a nice evening.
Do I know you?
Aren't you that woman
that was in the elevator?
Is that all I am to you?
Two weeks max.
It's only 14 days.
Such a soft...
- 344 Alexander.
- No.
Out of service.
What the hell do you
have the light on for?
Very sorry friend, out of service.
Grab my throat!
Grab my throat.
Put your hands on my throat.
Grab my fucking...
Today in New York Senator Maggie Davidson,
a member of the Armed Services Committee came in
with her thoughts on
the latest terrorist threat.
I am simply following the will of the people.
In this new world civil liberties are challenged,
not by the bureaucrats in Washington.
But by the men hiding in caves.
And for democrats to
use these events to gain
traction against me in
this election is without moral.
It is simply awful.
- Thank you Senator.
- Senator Maggie Davidson!
Men hiding in cave.
I was in cave.
Cave men in White House.
Cave men in Senate,
cave men in Congress.
Nice shirt by the way.
Clearly none of this leaves this room.
Clearly.
We got a report today from the FBI field office
in New York about Muhammad Fatah.
An Al Caeda operative who's
been living here since 1998.
He was picked up
last week driving his cab
with close to a thousand
smoke detectors in the trunk.
Fire conscious terrorist.
He could have carried less
about the smoke detectors
what he was after was the Cobalt 47.
- A new club on 47th street.
- This is why we don't talk.
First it's not even funny,
let alone clever.
- Maggie.
- Oh, Vince.
- We both know I'm situationally funny.
- Whatever. Shall I continue?
Oh, please.
Continue, Giggles.
Apparently he was trying to extract the
Cobalt 47 from the smoke detectors
in order to build some sort
of radioactive weapon.
- Like nuke?
- Not exactly.
But a weapon of mass destruction.
- Shall I finish?
- Please continue. Go ahead.
He was going to construct
the bomb in a trunk of his cab
and then let it loose
in the financial district.
- Killing thousands?
- No.
Just the ones in closest
proximity to the blast.
See the blast would trigger
a radiological event.
Meaning the toxic particles would
be released into the atmosphere
and depending on the weather conditions they
could be carried up to one mile in radius.
Making the financial district
completely wasted.
A moment of massive disruption.
Hey, what's up man?
Ready for a close-up?
Three, corner pocket.
Where's mom?
Hi dad, good to see you.
Oh good, that's great.
- What can I do for you, sweetheart?
- I'm going to Noa's.
Call.
Fuck it!
Slow down, it's not a race.
- Yours or mine?
- Your.
- Hello.
- It's me, you got any money?
A little.
It's awkward.
John, we're not gonna do this again, are we?
Do what?
I mean Jesus Christ, I'm in the middle
of the toughest campaign of my life.
The world is in perpetual crisis,
I just don't need that shit right now!
- They want me?
- Yeah, you got it!
- All we have is a photo, you set it yourself!
- Go get fucked.
Yeah, that's what I'm trying to do right now!
- Fuck you Maggie!
- Oh shit.
If I can get my phone to work
I'm gonna call you from the train, okay?
Shit!
Look, we just wanna to have
a chit-chat with your husband.
He's not my husband for your information.
He's my lover now.
Go away!
You listen to me.
We're still gonna have to come in to
the house and have a chat with Darrel.
Go away!
I gotta take this.
- You won't work?
- Try to pacify her.
Fuck you! Go!
This will go a thousand times smoother
if you just put that blade down.
I'ma put this blade down
cracking your ass nigger!
Go with him.
- Hello.
- Hello man.
- What's up buttercup?
- If this is a bad time I can call you back later.
No, it's never a bad time, I'm just
wrapping up something at the office.
I'll tell you one more time,
put the blade down.
Put the weapon away and
let me talk to Darrel.
Not in this lifetime, you bitch.
I need you and Grady to come by
on your way home tonight later.
- Sounds like official business.
- Something like that.
Now go!
No!
- No, you didn't!
- Yes, I did!
Give me an hour, okay?
I hope that was important!
- Where did she go?
- In a castle to retrieve the prince.
- So who was on the phone?
- I'll tell you in the car.
Fuck you! Get out!
That motherfucker is your problem now!
Thank you ma'am.
You know what the worst part is?
I just know without the shadow of a duck this
poor son of a bitch doesn't even have the money.
Really?
If you don't wanna do it,
I'll do it this time.
No, it's not that.
Hey Darrel.
Darrel, look here man.
We work for Mr. Sikle.
We're gonna need to collect
all that loan he gave you.
Now where can we go get that money?
- So what is it?
- What?
- What is it?
- You know...
Why can't everybody just
be happy in this world.
Look, I'll ask you one more time.
Do you have the 15 grand?
What's the matter with this guy?
Okay man, grab his arm.
We're gonna take a little something, okay?
Just to let Al know that
you're good for him.
You know I guess it is easier
being a victim.
Gives you real rationalizing
everything in your life.
Sir, this will be a show
of good faith for Al.
You did the right thing.
Yeah, I'd like to report
a domestic disturbance.
I think it got really ugly
next door with my neighbours.
I think the guy needs
an ambulance right away.
8714 Intech road. Hurry please.
Some sitting on my hood again!
First trust into Allah and peace be
onto our prophet Muhammad.
Who said: I have been sent to this world between my
hands to ensure that no one but Allah is worshipped.
Allah, who put my livelihood under my spear
and who inflicts humiliation and scone
on those who disobey my words.
This is another treat.
This is a treat.
This is not a trade.
This is I...
I'll blow up National tomorrow.
- So we're going for a ride?
- I don't know.
Would you cut the bullshit?
Something must be totally fucked up.
- I mean why else would we be here?
- Why does something have to be fucked up?
Because we're in the fucked up business.
- What?
- You know what I mean.
No, I don't.
I don't know. You fancy yourself smart
enough to have that cut both ways.
- Man, this shit must never get old.
- Being rich. He wouldn't fucking know.
What kind of vague shit is that?
You know the cliche:
"Rich in a wallet, poor in the spirit".
- Yeah, I'd take that life.
- Oh yeah?
- The more you have the more you have to protect.
- That's true.
Yet somehow I doubt that we're about
to be engaged in the protection business.
Well there are more of than
two ways to skin a cat.
AMMONIUM NITRATE
I'm so fucked up.
- What is it you think?
- I don't care a thing.
How much?
Maybe a line, I don't know.
See if anything fell in the cab.
Call him.
- What terrorist?
- Yeah, terrorist.
I have to go get my phone.
- Hello.
- Hey, it's me.
Always my girl.
- No.
- You are.
- How long do you want to go?
- A couple of them.
I'll call you back.
He'll call back.
What's that?
I think it's my sister's military ID.
- She's a hotty.
- She was.
Tell me you have good news.
- Tomorrow we're having it.
- Thank you Osama!
Good night my son.
Hey little brother.
What's the matter moonlight
is hurting your eyes?
- Sorry I called you so late.
- I know you're not.
- It's been too long.
- Yeah.
I thought maybe we take a little ride.
- I thought that was our lines.
- Funny! That was funny!
How fucking high are you?
- I miss her sometimes.
- What was that?
Nothing, nothing.
- What was she like?
- She was a lot like you actually.
Moral conviction and civil duty.
Fuck her.
You know what, fuck her!
She never really believed.
No one ever really does, they...
They just fight because
their parents fought.
We're forced to hate one another.
We're not taught to love.
Whatever the fuck with it.
A world without God
is a world devoid of war.
Do you think you really could have done that?
What?
Far from God.
You didn't even think he existed.
Maybe if I did in two weeks
I'll start sleeping with Jesus.
Why, could you?
- Why do you think I'm here?
- You're really draft toucher.
Put it there!
- Man, this must never get old.
- What's that?
All this, I mean knowing that all this is yours.
You got rocks in your house man.
All my rocks are outside.
- It is great.
- Yeah, it's home.
Home sweet home.
Home on the range.
I'm not totally sure how this works
but I think I have a job for you.
What kind of job is that?
I need somebody...
I'm not exactly sure how to say this.
- Removed?
- Something like that.
Have you ever engaged anybody
in something like this before?
No.
Pretty straightforward.
You just give us who, when, how.
We give you a price.
The moment you paid
it's a done deal.
Who and when I can give you.
Fuck.
- What is this fucking joke?
- You're the funny one, tell me.
You're the funny one. You tell me.
You look at me.
- I can't live like this anymore.
- I can't do this.
- I have no place else to go Bobby.
- Try a fucking marriage counsellor!
Do you know where that bitch is right now?
Do you know what she's done to me? Do you?
Look at it! Fucking look at it!
I am done.
This is the only way.
Look I haven't had a chance to
council with my business partner.
Cut the fucking bullshit!
How in the hell are we supposed
to pull off something like this anyway?
Doesn't she have some
kind of a security?
Sometimes she goes
on these trips by herself.
Hypothetically speaking,
how?
Doesn't really matter.
There's a fly. Timeframe.
Let me guess. You need
this done say, tomorrow?
Not bad.
Let me get this straight.
You want us to put a hit on my sister-in-law,
a US Senator in 24 hours.
Yeah, that's right.
Everything you need is in there.
- I can't do it.
- I was afraid of that.
Come on.
This is fucking bullshit.
Let's play the fucking pool game.
Just take it easy.
Watch this baby.
- I love you, little man.
- I love you too man.
Fucking stupid!
It's so fucking stupid.
It's so fucking stupid!
He was my god, man.
She gets back tomorrow early evening.
She always travels back alone
same pattern every time.
She gets in the cab lines,
she grabs a cab.
She's on that way.
- What a fuck are you talking about.
- Nothing. All right? Nothing! Either way.
I'm just saying that if we took the job,
it wouldn't be that complicated.
Oh yeah, not that complicated.
Do I need to remind you that
she is a United States Senator?
- And she killed him.
- No.
He killed himself.
He killed himself with my fucking gun
in his own fucking house!
With what? Like million fucking dollars
in cash he got from fuck knows where!
- What's so damn funny?
- I don't know, it's so funny.
Don't I look cute today, honey?
Do I have a choice?
Do you have a choice?
I am struggling to find another option.
- Then fucking walk out of here!
- I don't want to walk!
I can walk no problem.
I'm done. I'm gone.
But you.
- How hard can it be, right?
- Simple on pape.
Sits gets in a cab, usually
makes a couple of stops.
Before ending up down here.
So in a quiet moment
we do a hit and disappear.
- Is this my phone?
- As far as I know.
Can't make that mistake again.
Max.
- Don't.
- What?
It's not you.
- You know what, I'll leave first.
- No, it's okay.
I wanna make a stop
before I get to the train.
- Are you still on the four o'clock?
- Yeah, why are you so concerned what train I'm on?
Just wanna make sure you're safe, that's all.
Well I'm gonna check this stuff
downstairs if that's okay with you.
I loved you.
No, you didn't.
She's out.
May I check these with you for a while?
Thank you.
I'm so sorry,
I didn't see you.
- I didn't see you either.
- Are you all right?
Yes I'll be fine, thank you.
You have the money?
Why do you pay me
to have sex with her?
When really all you want is to fuck me?
You're tired, aren't you?
Lie back.
So what is it you say
about your grandfather?
You know my granddad
worked at the train station.
- Like you.
- We're keeping in the family.
Following the footsteps.
- So what?
- He worked there like 34 years.
- His name was Hermann.
- Hermann.
They called him George.
Morning George.
- Those are my bags, George.
- Why George? Not Hermann?
They didn't respect the dude enough
to call him by his first name.
But why George?
I don't know why George but
it just wasn't Hermann, that's the deal.
Because why?
You ain't been here long enough,
that's the way it works sometimes.
His name was Hermann,
but they called him George.
You're totally fucking cute man!
That's how it works.
- Okay, thanks George.
- Shit!
Hold on, vibrate.
Hold on.
There she goes!
Aren't you...
Senator Maggie Davidson,
great to meet you.
It looks great.
It's not for me,
it's for my daughter.
Excuse me.
Hey. I was just going to call you,
I'm looking at a dress for you.
- Great. Where's dad?
- Did you try at the office?
- Yes they said he took a day off.
- Maybe he's playing golf, I don't know.
- Is something wrong?
- I just need some cash.
- For what?
- Crack.
Seriously.
Seriously I'm trying to buy tickets for a show
from Noa's brother and it takes some cash.
If you can't find your dad's
why don't you just go over to the house
and take whatever you
need from my stash?
- I love you mom.
- I love you too.
Oh, and we're starting family
dinners again tomorrow night.
So keep your schedule clear.
Done.
Put that thing back in your pants.
- What are you doing here?
- I live here, what are you doing here?
They asked me to keep an eye
on the place for a couple of days.
You remember Noa?
- Hi.
Sorry.
You're so disgusting.
You look really tired.
That's because I was dreaming about you.
That's exhausting.
Tell him to close his eyes.
I don't trust him.
Just close your eyes, okay?
- He didn't do it, did he?
- No.
- So how long you're staying?
- Just another half an hour.
- You can't stay for a dip?
- A dip in what?
All right, you close the
door after you, okay?
- I'll see you.
- Bye.
- Look at you.
- No, look at you.
Cassie old grown-up.
B wake up. We got ten minutes.
Let's roll, come on get up.
Coffee. Coffee man, come on.
Hey, check out the safe.
- What's the combo?
- 57191.
We're gonna need all we can get.
Call your boy. Tell him to visit my house.
Yeah.
- Hey. We're still on for tonight?
- I'll be there around nine.
- I'll call first.
- Okay, grab a pen.
87 Wiskonsin north-west.
Don't be frightened by
all the white people.
Wanna grab a bite?
Hello boys, are we smoking today?
- I don't think so.
- Right this way.
- No smoking.
- I ain't smoking.
My name is Sandy.
I'll be moonlighting as your waitress.
- Can I get you boys a shake?
- Vanilla for me, chocolate for my friend.
Cause it to black thing baby.
You see this guy at the counter?
Which one?
Which one of these things
is not like the others?
Okay what about him?
You think he wants what we want?
- What do we want?
- I think he got here all alone.
This guy he don't wanna be a freak.
He don't?
See, we brought up in this
country to live for ourselves.
But they live for God.
You know it's duty versus free will and shit.
When did you learn how to read?
Okay cutie pies, you're
ready or you need a few?
- I don't know, we'll take it later.
- All right, I'll be back in a flash.
- Here's a fresh one.
- Thanks.
I was thinking that maybe I would
like a big slice of apple pie.
- With the scoop?
- Scoop, yeah.
- What's the occasion?
- Big day.
Good for you.
Big day for me.
- What's the story morning glory?
- You again.
Sandy, give me your story.
The whole novel.
Well, you know the deal.
Working my way through Georgetown law,
do double shifts and all that.
That's great, just what the world
needs now, another fucking lawyer.
With relative moral conviction.
Thank you.
Are you guys gonna order or what?
Yeah, bring us two biggers
burgers you can master. Huge.
- You're sure you're gonna handle it?
- Bring it on.
Why don't you be nice to this girl man?
What's you thinking about?
She's the fucking lawyer.
We're fucking criminals.
She ain't does shit.
Leave her a nice tip.
Groovy.
You boys need anything else?
Give me a shout.
Are you kidding me?
Let's see you exercise
your free will with that.
Only in America.
- You're sure you can do this?
- What? Eat the burger?
- Come on man stop playing.
- There is no choice.
I gotta ask.
Good.
You know, there is much
I missed in this life.
But I won't miss this.
- Guy's just trying to make a little.
- Trying to appear to.
- You always see the glass is half empty.
- Rarely why you can see the glass.
You boys behave.
You do right by the world.
John it's me. I'm back in town.
Cassie was looking for you they
said you were at the office today.
John, I don't wanna fight anymore.
I know you think we can't
get back to that place, but...
Call me when you get this, okay?
Man, that feeling good.
There's only one cop
work in the line.
Pretty fucking amazing.
No, man!
Thanks, George.
- So where to this evening?
- I have to make two stops if that's okay.
You're the boss.
Just head towards north-west.
When we get closer I'll tell you where
to turn so we can go up to Connecticut.
Samir, is that how you
pronounce your name?
Samir.
Could you turn this off please?
- Did it rain here yesterday?
- No, did it rain in New York?
No.
How did you know I was
coming from New York?
Shoes. Only in New York where
the people wear those shoes.
That pretentious, ha?
When you do what I do as long as I do, you can
always tell when the Washingtonians come back.
- Where are you from?
- Libia.
- When did you come over?
- Ten years ago.
- By yourself?
- Something like that.
- No family?
- They didn't make it.
I'm sorry.
Yes, they were supposed to drive me
when I became... how do you say
...established.
My name is Maggie by the way,
I didn't mean to offend you in any way.
No, you have not offended me, Maggie.
So when is he coming?
I don't know.
I guess at 9 o'clock.
Your mom is so fucking hot.
How devastating she'd be
if she found out what we're doing?
She'd only care if the press found out.
Senator's daughter caught doing Bin Laden.
- It's kind of fucked up.
- What?
- Nothing.
You don't think it really
comes from Bin Laden?
You're such an idiot, no!
Now can you just call
your boyfriend please?
I am ready to get high!
- Where the fuck are you?
- Around.
Then hurry up.
Or no soup for you.
I know, I am sorry.
I forgot, I forgot.
I'm sorry. Yes, honey.
I love you. I'll try.
I'll try, I'm working.
Everything all right?
Maggie could we make a quick stop?
My girlfriend is sick and...
I have a medicine.
I'll give you a free ride.
- I guess that would be all right.
- It's very nice of you. You understand.
Hey, this is beautiful building, this one.
US Capitol.
- Five minutes, thumbs.
- Take your time.
I've got inride entertainment.
Let me see what we got here.
No.
It's our special delivery.
I brought it.
- It's good?
- It's bad.
- This.
- Yeah.
No!
Cassie!
- What are you doing?
- Something's wrong.
- What a fuck are you talking about?
- She was kicking at the window.
- So you think she knew...
- No! He won't let you to open her fucking door.
Get out.
What are you talking about?
You stay with the cab,
follow the fucking cab.
I'm gonna check this shit out.
I'll call you.
Why! Tell me why!
You live by your soul.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I had a child.
I don't know what you're talking about!
Do not dare.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for whatever it is you think
I've done to you! I'm so sorry!
Do you not know that when
your foster hand of the world
against innocent that
there will be no retribution.
You are not justified!
Stop it!
Don't do that again!
Shoes! You have shoes!
The rest of the world is barefoot!
You are just like those criminals
that blew the plane in these towers!
You're just like the criminals in towers.
No. No.
I am a mother who watched
her daughter murdered.
I am a father who wants justice.
Justice because you killed my child.
Where are we going?
You will see free light.
No! No!
- I can get you anything you want.
- You Americans.
- Anything.
- You can't play God.
Give him life!
A sweet boy!
You take his life!
I take your life!
This sweet boy!
Don't do that again!
The lipstick.
Fuck you!
I have a bomb in a cab.
And unless you want your President
to die I suggest that you get your lipstick.
Get your lipstick!
Bomb!
And if you would be so kind miss Davidson.
Thank you.
Another way that you
love your enemy is this:
When the opportuny presents itself
for you to defeat your enemy.
That is a time which
you must not do it.
There will come a time and many instances,
when the person who hates you most,
the person who has misused you most,
the person who has gossipped about you most.
There will come a time when you will have
an opportunity to defeat that person.
There is a reccommendation.
You might be in terms of helping that
person to make some move in life.
That's the time you must do it.
That is the meaning of love.
Love is creative, understanding.
Good will for all men.
It is a refusal to defeat individual.
When you rise to the level of love
in which great beauty and power
you seek only to defeat evil systems.
Individuals who haven't been caught up
in that system you love,
but you seek to defeat the system.
I have a dream
MARTIN LUTHER KING