Sharon!
She's not here.
Oh, God.
Christopher, can you see anything?
Sharon!
- Sharon!
- She's there.
Sharon!
Honey!
Wait for Mommy!
Sharon!
Wait.
Sharon! Honey!
Oh, my God. Sharon!
Home.
No!
- Home! Home!
- We're going home.
Silent Hill!
- Silent Hill!
- Rose!
- Wake up.
- Hey.
- It's okay, sweetie. We're here now.
- It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
It's okay, baby.
We're going right home.
- What are we gonna do?
- We'll get there.
We'll find a way through this.
We'll find a way.
No.
- She said it again.
- I know.
- Come on, baby. It's okay.
- Calm down, baby. It's okay.
- It's okay, baby.
- We're right here.
It's okay.
It's okay, baby.
- Wanna see?
- Sure.
What are you doing there, pumpkin?
This is an amazing lion.
Did you do that all by yourself?
I'm so impressed with you, honey.
Hey, you know we're going
on a special trip, don't you?
Do you know where we're going?
No?
Honey, sometimes when you go
to sleep, you go on a little walk.
And sometimes
you talk about a place...
...called Silent Hill.
I don't remember.
Oh, that's okay, sweetie.
That's why we're gonna go there,
so you can remember.
Daddy's not coming?
No, sweetie.
It's gonna be just you and me.
Hey.
Break's over, sweetie.
You awake?
You wanna go?
Damn it, Rose. What's going on?
Hi, this is Rose Da Silva.
Please leave a message,
and I*ll call you back.
Oh, no, Rose.
No.
Honey, you're awake?
Long drive.
Can I ask you something, sweetie?
Why did you change your pictures?
I didn't.
- Mommy?
- You can't remember?
No. I don't like that, Mommy.
- Baby, you can't remember doing this?
- Who did that?
- Hey, hey, baby, it's okay.
- Mommy, who did that?
It's okay, honey. Mommy's here.
Can you wait in the car for me?
Can I sit in front?
- Of course you can sit in the front.
- Okay.
Jimmy, we need
a ham and cheese on white.
Hi.
I just wanna pay for the gas.
And can you tell me the best way
to get to Silent Hill?
I can't seem to find it on the map.
- Why do you wanna go there?
- I- I read about it.
Road don't go through no more.
Your card was declined.
Hey there.
- Is everything all right?
- Don't talk to strangers.
Good girl.
All right. Well, thanks for your help.
Why did you cut off the cards?
That*s not gonna stop me
from taking her there.
Listen, honey,
we gotta put Sharon in a hospital.
She needs constant care,
and she needs medication.
The medication doesn't work.
She's getting worse every day.
Honey, the adoption people said
Sharon came from West Virginia...
...and Silent Hill is in West Virginia.
I*m not giving up on her, Chris.
I*m not.
Have you actually read
the websites, Rose?
Yes, Chris, I read them.
Just trust me on this, please?
Just trust me on this.
Listen, honey...
- I love Sharon every bit as much as I-
- Chris, I gotta go.
- I love you.
- Need any help, ma'am?
- No, we're- We're fine, thanks.
We're fine.
Are we there?
Not yet, honey.
Keep your seatbelt fastened.
Hey!
Mommy!
It's okay. It's just the radio.
- I'm turning it off.
- Mommy!
Sharon?
Sharon!
Somebody! Help!
Please!
We've had an accident!
Anybody!
Sharon. Honey.
Ashes.
Sharon!
Wait!
Sharon?
Honey?
What's happening?
Mommy.
Sharon.
Sharon?
Hello?
Hey!
Wait!
Sharon.
No!
Help me!
Help.
Help me. Help.
Someone! Shit!
Get off me! Get off!
Get off! Get off!
Get off me!
No! Get off me!
No! Get off me! Get off me!
Get off-!
Only the dark one opens
and closes the door to Silent Hill.
Please.
I don't know what's happening.
Do you know what's going on here?
My daughter.
I'm looking for my daughter.
I'm afraid that she's been hurt.
We've all lost our children.
Our light.
They deceived me.
Their evil.
Their hate.
They hurt my child.
They did terrible things to her.
Alessa.
This is my daughter, Sharon.
She sleepwalks,
so you have to be careful...
...but if you see her,
please, tell her to wait for me.
Yes, she's mine.
- It was mine.
- It's mine.
- It's mine!
- Get off me!
Into the fire
she swallowed their hate.
- Hi there.
- Yeah.
Listen, my wife,
she came through here last night.
- Maybe you saw her?
- Daughter worked night shift.
Actually, she was heading
for this place, Silent Hill.
- How do I get there?
- You don't.
Town's closed down
because of the coal fire...
...still burning underground,
you know?
Breathe enough of them fumes,
oh, bound to kill you.
Okay...
...where's the turnoff?
Sharon?
Come on.
Hi, this is Chris.
Please leave a message.
Christopher, it's me.
I'm in Silent Hill.
I'm sorry, I made a mistake.
Sharon's lost,
but I think I know where she is...
...so I'm going to the school
to look for her.
I'm not okay, all right?
I need your help.
Please, please, hurry.
Fuck. Come on!
Ma'am, I want you to put
both hands on the wheel.
Put both hands on the wheel.
Where's the little girl, ma'am?
Please, my daughter, she's gone.
I need your help.
- Get out of the car.
- What?
Move it.
Jesus, what are you doing?
- You're under arrest.
- What?
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
I don't think you understand.
There's something weird going on.
My daughter, she's in danger.
If you really cared,
you wouldn't have sped off.
Listen to me, she's ill.
She sleepwalks.
Just calm right down.
I'm gonna find the little girl.
Officer Bennett to base, over.
Base, do you copy, over?
- Shit.
- You're bleeding.
Cracked my head on the road
pretty good...
...when my bike went down.
I must have been out for a while.
- You all right to walk?
- Sure.
Then it looks like we'll be
hiking back to Brahams.
What?
You're going back to the station.
- Are you kidding?
- Nope.
Have you heard
a single word I've said?
- Yeah, I hear you.
- Have you heard...
...a single word I've said?
I'm sure she's at the school,
we just need to turn around...
- Silent Hill-
- sorry-
- Sharon-
- lost-
- think I know where-
- going to the school to look for her-
I*m not okay-
I need your- Your help.
Please, hurry!
Sorry, sir, this road is closed.
You'll have to turn around.
I'm looking for my wife.
She may have come through here.
She drives a Jeep Liberty.
Silver, Ohio plates.
Sir, this man's wife
was driving the Jeep.
Bring him down.
- Come on.
- You've seen her?
Where is she?
Inspector Thomas Gucci.
Enjoying the weather, are you?
For God's sake,
I'm trying to find my wife.
I know. Hang on a second.
Now, that vehicle you were
talking about, we found it.
It's at the end of the bridge here,
but it's empty.
We've got no indication
anyone's come under any harm.
- Good Christ.
- Now, you mind telling me...
...what your wife's doing
up here, Mr...?
- Da Silva, Chris Da Silva.
- My pleasure, Chris-
The faster we start looking,
the faster we're gonna find her.
All right, hold your horses,
hold your horses, Chris.
I've also got a missing deputy.
And knowing Officer Cybil Bennett
the way I do...
...she's probably out there looking
for your wife and daughter.
Bobby, make sure no one
comes through that barricade.
We're gonna get our asses up
to Silent Hill.
- Let's take a look around.
- Yes, sir.
While Chris here tells me
what's going on.
She disappeared yesterday.
I spoke to her...
...when she stopped for gas
in Brahams.
Why were you coming up here
in the middle of the night?
- I thought it would help her.
- You people. You get off the highway...
...from whatever big city, bringing
all your sick problems with you.
Why aren't you listening to me?
We had a guy come up here
two years ago...
...snatched a little boy from a rest stop,
dropped him into a mine vent.
I never wanna see
anything like that again.
Look, I don't know what
you're thinking, but you're not helping.
There is no way I would ever
harm my own daughter.
How do I even know
she is your daughter?
Come on.
What the hell?
Okay.
Now do you see
what I'm talking about?
Will you take these handcuffs
off me?
No. Get walking.
There's a fire-lookout tower
on the far side of Toluca Lake.
- It should have a radio.
- Fuck you, you stupid cop.
This place is completely cut off.
- You have no idea what's going on.
- Hey!
Hey, you up there!
I'm a police officer!
What's going on?
What is that?
Stand back.
Jesus Christ, shoot it.
Stay where you are!
Stop!
Sharon!
Rose.
Mrs. Da Silva,
I am an officer of the law...
...and I will take you to safety.
Mrs. Da Silva,
I am an officer of the law...
...and I will take you to safety.
- Why don't you let me do that?
- Ninety percent of the time...
...when a wife takes a run...
...she takes the daughter
to a place like this...
...I'd say she's damn mad
at her husband.
You like hauling skeletons
out of your family closet?
No, not all the time, but we're
driving on top of them right now.
Coal fire's still burning
underneath.
You see the barbershop over there?
- Used to be my father's.
- Your father?
He's dead.
November '74,
when the fire caught.
They tried to evacuate this place
as quick as they could...
...but it was hellish, people were
dying and disappearing.
Hell, they couldn't even find
half the bodies.
That was the end of Silent Hill.
These were good people,
most of them.
Some, you might say deserved it.
A little bit.
Sharon!
Sharon.
Where are you hiding?
Burn the witch! Burn the witch!
Burn the witch!
Alessa Gillespie.
Hey!
Wait!
It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
I promise I'm gonna help you.
Come on.
Oh, God.
Help me. Oh, God.
Please, please, help me. Help-
Help me. Please, help me.
Help me. Help me, please.
It's happening again.
Help me! Please! Please!
Come on! Come on!
Rose!
Sharon!
Rose.
- Rose!
- Put your mask on.
Rose, where are you?
- I felt her.
- You what?
Her perfume.
- She was here.
- Who was?
- My wife.
- She wasn't here. Put this mask on.
- Perfume.
- Breathe. Through that mask.
Come on, let's go.
We're gonna go this way.
Chris, come on.
- She was here.
- No, no, she wasn't here.
I know it.
Come on.
Come on. Let's keep looking.
Get off! Get off! Get off!
Get me that pipe.
Rose, the pipe!
Okay. Okay.
- I got it. I got it.
- Quick, come on!
Can we get out of here?
We're trapped.
Last mag.
- That's all the bullets you got?
- Yeah.
Thanks.
You hear that?
That's him.
Stay down! Stay down!
Jesus Christ.
Get down!
Shit!
What?
What the fuck?
You saw that, right?
That was real?
What the fuck is going on?
All right, I know this is crazy. I know.
We gotta calm right down,
because my kid is not here...
...and I've gotta find her
before this happens again.
I don't even know where to start.
I found this.
It's from a hotel.
I don't know where it is,
but she is in this hotel.
Hotel?
Hey.
It's gonna be okay.
We're gonna be okay.
Now, don't be trying
anything, all right?
We got men up here
all night long.
We're gonna find your wife,
we're gonna find your daughter.
Can't have civilians
wandering around on their own.
You're not telling me everything.
What really happened up here?
Just let it rest in peace.
- Directory assistance.
- Toluca County Archives, please.
One moment.
- Archives?
- Yeah, listen.
Do you have the records there
from Silent Hill?
- Which records, sir?
- The police records.
Sorry, sir,
those records are confidential.
No, no, I can't-
No, listen, I-
Sorry, sir,
I can*t access that information.
- Listen, goddamn it.
- Sir.
- This is an emergency.
- I can*t-
I can*t help you.
They used to say
this place was haunted.
I think they were right.
Help! No!
- Stay away.
- Come on.
Stay away, sinner.
Get back!
Hey.
It's here.
Faith is our destroyer.
Faith has brought us doom.
- Get back!
- Hey, hey!
- Hey, stop.
Think you of thee
who cast the first stone.
Lambs without a shepherd,
shepherd without a flock.
It's your sins which hold you here.
- Stop your lies!
- Calm down.
Calm down, it's okay.
- We're not gonna hurt you.
- She's gone.
What's your name?
Anna. My name is Anna.
What's going on here, Anna?
Who was that?
- I've seen her before.
- Dahlia was cast out.
Not even the darkness wants her.
- She's lost her daughter too.
- What?
- Sinners deserve to lose their spawn.
- What are you doing here, Anna?
Mother needs more food.
You mean there are
other people here?
Christabella keeps us safe.
- Anna.
- We take refuge in the church.
Anna, listen to me.
I've lost my daughter.
She's all alone.
Can you imagine how frightened
she must feel?
Tell me, have you seen her?
Do you know where she is?
If she has faith, she might survive.
If not...
I'm taking this.
Have you seen this?
I've seen it at the school.
It's on all the buildings
the elders of my elders built.
It's a symbol of our unity,
a symbol of our faith.
Rose, look at this.
- What is it?
- Just like yours.
- Where did you find it?
- They're all over the floor.
Rose.
Check this out.
- What number did you take this from?
-111.
We gotta go to room 111.
Gucci.
- Directory assistance.
- Yeah.
Toluca County Orphanage, please.
One moment, please.
- Yes, I have that information for you.
- Yeah.
Can you give me that address?
We are wandering far
from refuge here.
Let's keep her with us.
She's all we got.
There's no room 111.
The first burning.
- What is it, Anna?
- The first burning.
Before the town had a name.
The elders of my elders
kept us pure.
The founders of this town
were witch-hunters.
Burning the witch
held back the darkness.
It stopped the apocalypse.
It's here.
There's a room in here.
Look at this.
Here.
Damn.
What is this place?
I don't know.
We're in the next building.
Some factory, maybe?
Looks like there was a fire.
Hey.