Oh, God!
What?
Didn't you see that?
There was a dead cat...
hanging from that sign
we just passed.
Really? Cool.
Don't you even think
about going back there.
What color was it?
Tiger-striped.
What difference
does it make?
Well, I thought it might
be black, you know?
Satanists out in the desert.
Marielle said the Nevada desert
was full of oddballs.
I just don't know who could kill
a living creature like that.
You're traveling through
another dimension...
A dimension not only
of sight and sound, but of mind.
Very funny.
I can't wait to get back
to Salt Lake City, at least.
Too much nature out here.
I'm starting to miss civilization.
What? What is it?
A car. Really movin', too.
Get over.
Give him the road.
It's a cop.
Why is he going so fast
with his flashers off?
Who's he gonna
run them for out here?
Well, there's us.
What's he doing?
I don't know.
Hi.
What does he want?
Well, I guess he wants
to get back behind us again.
Well, why didn't
he just pull over...
and let us pass then,
if that's what he wants?
I don't know.
Why is he stopping us,
Peter? Why?
These asses have
a quota to make.
They keep the posted limit at 55
so they can make it.
Don't pull over.
I don't have a choice, Mary.
Great.
Holy God, it's Sasquatch!
Guess I was going
a little fast, officer.
Had the hammer
down a little, huh?
Can I see your registration
please, sir?
No problem.
But the car's not mine.
It's my sister's.
We're driving it back
for her to New York.
She's... she goes
to school in Oregon.
Rand College.
Have you ever heard of it?
Mar, could you get
the registration?
I think it's in
the glove compartment.
I don't believe this...
I can't find my license.
Sorry, officer, I...
Oh, wait a minute, here it is.
OK, and, um, here's
the registration.
Oh, good.
I see you're
an organ donor.
Think that's wise?
Well...
Is there a problem, officer?
Your name is Jackson?
The one on the pink slip
says Deirdre Finney.
That your sister?
Right.
She's been divorced
for about a year...
but she kept
her husband's last name.
Deirdre's a bit of a flake.
Bit of a flake, huh?
Tak.
Can I ask you to step
out of the car, Mr. Jackson?
What for?
Of course.
Come around back, Mr. Jackson.
Hell!
Peter, what is it?
Our...
our damn license plate fell off!
I doubt it.
Did you stop in Fallon?
Yeah, we got gas
at the Conoco there.
Why?
They got some
light-fingered kids hang out there.
I reckon your license plate
is hangin' in their clubhouse right now.
You know this and
it still goes on?
Oh, Fallon is not my place.
Those are not my ways.
Gosh, no.
What should
we do about that, officer?
Well, you just take
the plate off the front...
and put it in the back.
That's should get you
across the country.
You got a tool kit?
These are yours.
Thanks.
I think I saw a tool kit
in the trunk.
Yeah, OK.
There, behind
my make-up case.
Hey.
What is this?
Damned sister!
Officer, I know what
this looks like.
But we checked her stuff...
But we're not
customs officers!
That... that is not our dope!
No.
Let me have your keys.
Get in the car.
But...
Are you deaf?
Get in the car!
OK, we'll get this
taken care of.
In Desperation.
Get in the car, folks.
Tak.
Slow down,
you'll flip us!
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
Officer, you saw
our registration.
You know that isn't our car,
and it's not our dope either!
Do you think
we'd be so stupid...
Shut up, you
New York deviant.
Wh... wh... what
did you call me?
I'm arresting you
for possession of marijuana...
with intent to sell.
You can't be serious!
You have the right
to remain silent.
If you choose
to not be silent...
everything you say
can be held against you...
In a court of law.
You have the right
to an attorney.
I am going to kill you.
If you cannot
afford an attorney...
One will be
provided for you.
Do you understand
your rights...
as I have explained them
to you?
Do you understand
your rights?
Just... Act normally.
I don't think he understands
what he just said.
Do you understand your rights?!
Do you or not?
Answer me...
you smart-aleck blue state
unisex swingles!
Do you or not?
Yes! Yes,
we understand.
Please, just watch the road.
Don't worry about me.
I got eyes in the back
of my head.
You'd do well
to remember that.
Up there on the horizon's
the china pit.
Gotta go
all the way to Peru
to find a bigger one.
Yeah, we just started
working her again.
They got some kind
of technology...
that makes even
the tailings valuable.
Science, huh?
Gosh.
Yeah, I think we're gonna
be a boom town again...
just like in the old days.
Officer, please don't kill us.
We'll do whatever you say.
Just don't kill us!
Shut your quackin'
yuppie pothead mouth!
We're not potheads.
You look like potheads to me.
Yuppies killed
Princess Di, you know.
Wasn't she beautiful?
Officer...
Shut up and walk.
Where is everybody?
Disneyland.
Come on, walk,
hay foot, straw foot.
You're Peter.
You're Mary.
So where's Paul?
I mean, how can you sing
Puff the Magic Dragon
without Paul?
Wait a minute.
Peter Jackson.
I love Lord of the Rings!
You are useless.
You at least look healthy.
Get in there, girlfriend.
Forgot all about her.
You can never remember
everything, now can you?
I don't care if you're
a Jew, a Hindu, or Mr. Magoo.
In Desperation...
We don't care about
those things much.
Peter!
Peter! Let me go!
Shotgun, get the shotgun!
Shoot him, shoot him!
Get it!
Get it, woman!
Pick it up,
for God sakes!
Don't do that.
Drop it, Mary.
Put it down, Mary.
Put it down.
Drop it.
Now, if you don't
want to see your liver...
come squirting
out of your nose...
I'd put it down, Mary.
Kill me if you're going to.
Now, why would
I want to kill you...
when things are
just starting to get interesting?
He killed my husband!
He killed our little girl.
Three billion red Chinese
don't give a damn.
How they hangin', old timer?
Don't you hurt him!
I'm warning you.
Who are you, boy?
I'm David Carver.
I live at 248 Poplar Street
in Wentworth, Ohio.
Yeah, but...
who made thee?
Canst thou say
who made thee? Tak!
I guess my folks did.
And God.
There's no god
out here, little Dave.
Leave him alone!
Haven't you done
enough to our family?
Even bald-headed
hoppin'- Satan...
don't step his split-foot
much west of Tonopah.
This is Desperation.
Only thing out here
is can tah and can tak.
And don't you forget it!
You're mine.
David, what's wrong?
What's... what's
wrong with him?
There's nothing
wrong with him.
What do you mean?
Are you blind?
I think your son
is praying.
Well. Hey there.
Are you a nice person?
Well, I like to think so...
but, then again,
if I was Ted Bundy...
do you think I'd tell you?
I'd know.
I got a psychic streak.
Up yours!
That's pleasant.
So what's your name,
young lady?
Cynthia Smith.
Smith? Oh. Smith.
That's a likely story.
No, really, it is.
Sure.
Honest!
OK.
Who are you?
Me? Steve Ames.
A noble moniker.
So, haul your psychic
streak on up here...
Cynthia Smith...
And let's make
some miles, OK?
Yeah, I guess you'll do.
Oh. Well, thank you
very much, cookie.
Don't call me cookie,
and I won't call you cake.
Oh, my.
You gonna smoke that
or gum it to death?
Yeah, I quit.
Never hurts to keep
in practice, though.
What you lookin' at, huh?
Your T-shirt.
Yeah, right!
I'm lookin' at your t-shirt!
Come on, that's OK!
We're all animals, right?
Oh, come on, now!
Give me a break.
I worked with Dylan back in '95
when, uh, he did Unplugged.
No way!
Yeah, yeah way. Yeah.
I was doin' amps
and guitar tech...
back in those days.
Are you a roadie?
Well, this truck looks too small
to carry a band's gear.
No, I'm workin'
for this writer...
And he's, uh, he's driving
cross country...
doing little speaking things,
you know?
And he does one
every couple of days or so...
and when he gets back
to the west coast...
he's gonna write a book about it.
Is he famous?
Have you ever heard of
John Edward Marinville?
No.
Well, he's famous
amongst book people, I guess.
Yeah, I pretty much
stick with Dean Koontz.
Is he cool?
Is he cool? Yeah...
you know, once you
get past the ego...
which is like,
the size of Tibet.
Yeah, I mean, he gets cranky
every so often, but I like him...
you know.
People drive across
country everyday.
Why is he writing
a book about it?
Ah, well, it's like he's got
this midlife crisis thing...
You know, the guy's 60 years old.
He's been everywhere,
he's done everyone, you know.
The guy rides a big
Harley soft tail.
Hey, hey! Is his bike
red and cream?
Yeah, red and cream.
I think I saw him
this morning!
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
you probably did.
Lookin' all handsome
on his bike.
Handsome man, yeah!
Yeah, and he knows
it, too, believe me.
Well, he's got
to be what...
like, 50, 70 miles ahead of you.
Yeah, about that.
You know, I catch up to him
when he has a gig...
And I set up the sound systems
for him...
And I, you know...
Make sure he's got
the names straight, stuff like that.
And I'll have dinner with him
if he wants somebody to talk to.
Not with, to.
But the guy's having the time
of his life.
Yeah, he likes to play
the lone wolf, huh?
Yeah. That's...
that's the boss.
Lone Wolf McQuade.
A film before your time.
Come on, come on. Go.
Water in the desert.
Thank you, Lord.
You want to
come up here, sir?
I think we need
to have a talk.
Afternoon, officer.
A wise man once told me...
no matter how much
you squirm and dance...
last two drops end up
in your pants.
Sir. Are you aware
that parking your vehicle
on a state road
is against the law?
And that relieving
yourself in public...
is also against the law?
Well, I didn't see any crowd
gathering to watch me, so...
Sir.
Yeah. Well,
listen, you can...
write me up
if you have to...
and I will take it with a smile
and apologize...
if that will
improve your day.
I'm not gonna
write you up, sir.
Just a warning
will do this time, but...
What?
Something wrong?
Holy God.
Holy God!
You're John Edward Marinville,
aren't you?
- Oh, I...
- Damn!
I'm busted.
You got me again.
Damn!
Glad to meet you.
I am shaking hands
With the guy who wrote Delight!
Yeah.
With the guy who wrote
Song of the Hammer!
- Yeah.
- This is...
Wow!
What are you
doing out here?
And on such an unsafe
mode of transportation?
I mean, they don't
call them murder-cycles for nothin'...
and I'm a wolf.
Are you workin'
on anything new, sir?
Yeah, a book of essays.
I thought I'd cycle
across America...
and get in touch
with the common folk.
You know,
get back to my roots.
That's amazing.
Sir, can I
can I have your autograph?
I mean, that'd... that'd...
that'd make my whole day.
Hell, that'd make
my whole year.
Yeah, that'd be fine.
Right here and?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- All right.
Could you just make it out
to Collie Entragian...
your number one fan.
Thank you.
I heard you saw some
pretty hairy stuff in the 'Nam.
I was just
a correspondent, officer.
Just one more
ink-stained wretch.
But, I must say...
that the Vietnam experience
defined me.
Nobody wrote about
'Nam like you.
I heard you saved some soldiers...
when some suicide gook
blew up a restaurant.
Well, it was gut check time
for a lot of us.
We did what we could.
Yeah, well, some people
don't do anything.
Some made the bread
of forgetfulness...
and drank the wine
of cowardice. Tak.
Hey, you don't want to ride around
like that, Mr. Marinville.
That thing gets caught
up in your back wheel...
you're toast.
How'd that get like that?
It can't be.
I always check these buckles
before I get on the cycle.
It's the last thing I do.
Well, they say the memory's
the first thing to go.
What's that
supposed to mean?
What the hell is that?
That's a wolf!
Shoot it!
Ah, that's just a wild dog.
They're not dangerous.
Ordinarily.
Tak!
Tak ah lah!
Tak ah wah!
What the hell
did you say to it?
Is that some kind
of Indian dialect?
Well, it's a lot
older than that.
Now, since you can't
take care of yourself...
You big baby...
Hey.
Gosh.
Houston, we have a problem.
That's not mine.
You put that in there
when I was off doing my business.
Yeah.
Blame the cop, just like in
your letty New York stories.
Tak.
Why do you keep
saying that?
saying "tak"?
I didn't say tak.
You said tak.
You say tomato,
I say tomat-oh.
You say potato,
I say potat-ah.
What the hell's
the matter with you?
Tomato...
Tomat-oh.
Potato.
Potat-oh.
## Let's call
the whole thing off ##
My nose!
That's not all I'll break.
My children of the desert.
Can toi.
What music they make.
Get up!
On your feet, Lord Jim.
Upsa-daisy, you
worthless piece of crap.
You've been redefined.
Watch what you're
doing to me.
Shut up!
You're in my house now!
You're in the house
of the wolf and the scorpion...
and don't you forget it!
You really did wet
your pants this time.
You're a sorry excuse
for a writer...
and you're a sorry
excuse for a man.
Your whole life is a lie...
and I could just kill
you right here.
Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
No. No. No. No.
It's still showing.
I can still see it.
Cover it up more!
More, please.
Yes.
Thank you for using Sky.
Your call is now
being routed.
Have a great day.
Oh, damn it.
I was in a literary commune
in Chicago.
Yeah, that's
a new one on me.
Well, when you have
a bunch of people...
sitting around
in a roach motel...
smoking crystal meth,
they're addicts.
- Nice.
- But!
If they've been to college,
they're a literary commune.
For a while, though,
it wasn't bad...
But then I realized
I was getting old before my time.
So, I split.
OK, all right...
Do me a favor.
Just don't say anything, OK?
He's... he'll
be cool about it.
But his agent
made a huge stink...
about picking up,
wayward hitchhikers.
Hey, boss, that you?
Steve...
Steve, I'm...
Johnny?
Boss, is that...
Trouble...
I hear you, boss.
What's wrong?
Boss?
About a mile and...
about a mile and a half...
Boss?
Boss? Boss!
Steve...
Boss? Boss?!
Steve, can you...
can you hear me? S...
S...
Shoot.
Lost him.
Miss me?
Where you taking me?
The old calabozo,
my friend...
Where anything you bray
will be abused against you...
in the court of caw.
Well, aren't you going
to at least say gesundheit?
He's in trouble isn't he?
Said something
about the cops.
Oh, God.
Bad.
Not good.
Big ego. Big temper.
Just hope he hasn't
killed anybody.
All right,
brace yourself, Cynthia.
There might be blood.
Yeah, I will.
I'm a woman.
I can deal with blood.
Look, John.
What in the name of God
is going on?
What's up
with the praying, David?
I've been doing it since
Bryan's accident.
Everyone thought he'd die.
Your sister died.
I'd say that's
a pretty lousy bargain.
Honey, leave him alone...
I want to know about this!
He's praying.
That's all.
He's not hurting
anybody.
Praying is great.
Without it, the crusades would've
never gotten off the ground.
Do you do this
all the time, son?
Or is it special?
I ask for help in the morning
and give thanks at night.
In the middle I just
take a few minutes...
and try to...
get open.
Sort of like a football
receiver or something.
It's hard to explain.
Bryan got you going on this?
Bryan's accident.
You remember
the doctor saying...
how his recovery was
almost miraculous?
I saw him, Mom.
It wasn't "almost. "
Bryan, look out!
Bryan!
Bryan, are you OK?
Bryan, are you...
Help me! Somebody help me!
I think he's dying!
Come on, please.
God, please don't
let him die.
If you save him,
I'll do something for you.
Anything you want,
I promise.
Only don't let him die.
Please don't let him die.
God could work a miracle
on your friend...
but not on your baby sister?
He couldn't save her
from that cop?
What kind of a god is that?
I don't know what kind
of god he is.
Look, leave him alone.
I want to know how you
can get on your knees...
and pray to a god
who killed your sister!
Lady, he's your son...
and I don't mean
to interfere.
But why don't you take
it easy on the boy?
I know you lost
your little girl.
I lost my husband.
It's been a tough day
on everyone.
Tough day.
Listen.
Maybe it's help.
No. It's Collie.
I recognize the engine.
His name is
Collie Entragian.
He's been on the force
here for...
about 12 years.
I'm... I'm the vet
in these parts...
and I took care of
Collie's dogs.
He was a nice fellow.
Yeah, a real sweetheart.
Till this, I mean.
I'll tell you
something, though.
He's bigger.
What do you mean,
"he's bigger"?
Bigger.
Taller.
A few inches at least.
That's impossible.
I know.
Look at us, would you.
Just one big happy family.
Tak.
I don't even know
what I'm looking for.
His bike...
Skid marks, or just anything
out of the ordinary.
- Wait, wait... what is that?
- What?
He said something about an R.V.
Hey!
What? What is it?
Just a reflection,
I guess. Go slow.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Look.
This is some little
girl's favorite.
See how the dress
is patched?
So why was it left
in the sand?
Yeah. And why...
Why are all the tires flat, you know?
Like, not just one or two
of them, but all of them.
Eeny, meeny, miney, mo.
Catch a tourist by the toe.
Don't you scream.
Don't you shout.
Time has come
to take you... out.
Leave them alone!
Haven't you done
enough to us?
In a word...
No.
Come on out, hon.
Or this no chin,
pencil neck, paper pusher...
gets it right
between the eyes.
Ellie, no.
And the boy goes next.
No!
I'll be all right.
OK.
That's right, hon.
Fine as fiddlesticks.
If you want that...
take me where my son
won't have to see.
Oh, don't worry, hon.
I don't want "that. "
Especially not from "you. "
Mom, no!
Leave her alone,
you bastard!
Leave my mother alone.
Don't worry, honey.
I'll be back. OK?
Make him stop.
Dad, make him stop.
Oh, God.
I'm warning you.
If you hurt her, you'll be sorry.
Maybe.
But I doubt it.
You're just a little
prayboy, aren't you?
Yes, yes, you are.
You just little prayboy
in a baseball shirt.
Well, go ahead and pray.
See what good it does.
But God ain't here
any more than he was...
when Jesus was dying
on the cross with flies in his eyes.
Tak!
Tak! Ah lah!
Him en tow!
If you set a hand
or a foot outside your cell...
he'll have it off before you
even know it was gone.
Leave her alone.
Son!
I will put a stick through
your mother and spin her...
until she catches fire
if I so desire.
And you'll not stop me.
And I'll come back for you.
Collie!
Don't hurt her!
Carver. Carver.
Well, there was boy here
as well as a girl.
David Carver. Carver.
What do you got?
Jewelry.
Earrings and rings.
You know, not Tiffany,
but not cheap either.
Not the kind of stuff
you'd leave behind...
unless you were in a hurry.
Time for the cops, isn't it?
Well, I'm pretty sure
the boss said something...
about being like
a mile from the R.V.
So...
Before we start
yelling for the cops...
You're crazy.
Cynthia!
Why are you
taking me here?!
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Oh, God.
Please, don't kill me.
Just...
Now what?
Well, there's a town
not too far far east of here...
Desperation.
They got some cute names
out here, don't they?
Yeah, I don't
care about the name.
I just care about if they have
at least one working phone...
and maybe
one working cop.
Yeah.
Wouldn't that be nice.
## Mother Mary ##
## What's the story ##
## Save my soul
from Purgatory ##
Pie.
Murder God.
That's what it really says.
Pie, I'm sorry
he killed you.
Never mind.
I have something for you.
Tak ah lah!
Tak!
Look, David.
David, are you OK?
Could you
please turn around?
This is a little
embarrassing.
David, whatever
you have in mind...
It can't be a good idea.
It's the only idea.
Who says so, son?
My sister...
God.
Are you going to stop this...
before you son does
something he regrets?
David, you don't
have to do this.
The cop's bleeding out.
He can't last much longer.
It won't take him long...
to kill my mom
if decides to.
David, I don't know
what you're planning...
But I forbid it.
Sorry, Dad.
What's he doing?
David! David,
you don't have to do this.
You'll get stuck.
Even if you do get out,
That thing'll eat you
from the feet up.
Lord, close its mouth
like you did with the lions...
When Daniel was cast
into their den.
Amen.
Stop it!
Get away from him
you ugly bastard.
Here, here. Here! Here!
Hey! Hey, come on!
Get over here,
you mutt.
Come to me!
Come on,
take another bite!
Come this way!
Come to me!
David, there's no time!
Come on, move!
Get out of there, David!
David, pull it!
Get out of there!
Come on, come on!
David, push!
Get out!
Call the police!
Run, run, David!
Please help me
take care of my mom...
and do what
I'm supposed to do.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Tasteful.
Operators are standing by.
Hello?! Anybody there?
It's dead!
It's got to be the...
Hey, wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait.
There are some garbage cans
lined up against the wall.
The wind just knocked
one down. That's all.
I don't care.
I want to get out of here.
This place is empty,
and it gives me the creeps.
There's trucks out there.
Where is everybody?
I don't know.
But I just think...
we ought to just keep...
I know, just tell me...
we're going to be
laughing at each other...
and feeling stupid
in a few seconds. OK?
OK. A few seconds.
Good enough.
Let's see what we see.
Do you hear that?
Sounds like a kid blowing
bubbles through a straw.
Do not worry, Little Nell,
for I shall save you.
Dork.
Yeah.
It's just an aquarium.
No, look.
Look.
What?
Behind the boat.