Gone In Sixty Seconds
English subtites
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Old Miss Lucy's
dead and gone
Left me here
to weep and moan
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Old Miss Lucy's
dead and gone
Left me here
to weep and moan
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Bring Sally up
and bring Sally down
Let's done start
Gotta 'till the ground
Old Miss Lucy's
dead and gone
Left me here
to weep and moan
Corner of Wiltern and Wetherly.
Tumbler messed up.
He said the Porsche would be
at the corner of Wiltern and Wetherly.
- It's right there.
- You're bullshittin' me, right?
- 9024 Wiltern?
- What?
- That?
- I gotta get my tool.
- Kip!
- He ain't bullshittin'.
Kip! Man, that's not a tool.
That's a damn brick.
Kip, man, we gonna use a brick, man,
we might as well call prison
and make reservations.
Aw, come on.
- Oh--
- Get the number.
42850.
Hurry up, man.
Man, let's go!
Let's get the hell outta here.
Okay, Billy Bad-ass,
you got us in here.
Now tell me
how the hell we gonna get out.
Oh, no, I know you ain't gonna do
what I think you're gonna do.
- Oh, man!
- Come on!
- This ain't The Dukes ofHazzard!
Yo, so check out my new move.
I call it the stranger.
What I do is, I sit on my hand...
for, like, 1 5, 20 minutes,
until it goes numb.
No feeling at all.
- And then I rub one out.
- The stranger, huh?
It's like a little boy's nursery school
I've come upon here.
Where are they?
- Yeah.
- You want to? All right.
- Hey!
- Man, leave those people alone, man.
- Oh, my God, sweetie,
you're so talented.
- What-- Hey. Hey.
- What did he say?
- No. Stop. No! No!
- Stolen car. Stolen car.
Hey, I-- I love you.
Man, we going tojail, man!
Come on!
Put your hands behind your back.
You have the right to remain silent.
Hey, watch it!
We have a silver Porsche,
estimated speed 80 miles per hour...
heading west on Wilshire Boulevard.
Yeah.
This is Air One.
We have a visual of the suspect.
Southbound on Vincent Thomas Bridge.
- Something wrong, Tumbler?
- Yeah. I'm missing Jerry Springer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
That's right, that's right,
that's right.
- What's up, old man?
- She'll go zero to 60 in 5.2. seconds.
Believe me, I can vouch for that.
Ground units, be advised, suspects last
seen entering south side of warehouse.
Thirteen down,
thirty-seven to go.
- What the hell is that?
- What is that, man?
- Now you've gone and done it, Raines.
- What is that?
- Tumbler!
- What's going on?
- Get the board and get the lights!
- All right, I got it, I got it!
- This is bullshit!
- It's not comin' off!
- Keys! Get the keys!
- I got 'em, I got 'em!
- Come on, everybody, let's go!
Hurry up!
- I got it!
- Let's go!
Toby, get it!
Let's go, boys!
Come on, come on, come on!
I got the light! I got the light!
Go, go, go! Let's go!
- Get busy, get busy, get busy
- Shit!
- l guess l didn't know
l guess l didn't know
Get busy time
l guess l didn't
l guess l didn't know
We got tape
all over the other side.
- Get the VIN number on that?
- Got it.
- We've got some more lamp shades
by the truck.
- Let's get those tools dusted.
What do we got?
All gone.
We didn't get a single one of them.
And we are talkin' about professionals.
No visible damage to locking mechanisms,
steering columns or ignitions...
and, as you can see,
these are not Honda Civics.
This is one ofthree
brand new Mercedes...
a car they say is unstealable.
Yeah, unless you get the laser-cut
transponder key...
sent directly to the U.S. dealer
from Hamburg.
They got somebody
working on the inside.
Let's find out which dealership
sold 'em, who serviced 'em,
et cetera, et cetera.
Yeah, I'll get on it.
- Mr Drycoff?
- Yeah?
Let's impound these cars
for one month.
I don't give a damn
ifthey belong to Tom Cruise.
Control, vision, determination.
These are the three
fundamental components...
of the new generation race car driver.
Speed is a byproduct.
Going fa st.
But remember:
The car is you, you are the car.
Okay? Let's ride!
Billy, you just shaved one second
off your lap time!
Tommy, I don't know what that was,
but it wasn't driving.
Go get 'em.
Well, well, well.
What do you pay your pit crews with,
Oreos and Gummi Bears?
I folded, Atley. You know that.
What are you doing here?
- Is there some place we can talk?
- About what?
About your brother
and the deep shit he's in.
Frank. Would you watch the kids
for a minute?
- Tell me about Kip.
- He took a job and he fumbled it.
Now he's jammed up.
He's jammed up bad.
- What kind ofjob?
- A boost. A big boost.
A boost.
What's Kip doin' on a boost?
Oh, you're shittin' me, man.
Kip's become quite the little
crew runner since you left.
- You don't talk to your ma?
- She neglected to mention it.
Listen, I need somethin'.
I-I need somethin' cold to drink.
I thought we were goin'
someplace to talk.
- Who was the job for?
- A new guy named Raymond Calitri.
They call him ''The Carpenter.''
He's runnin'
all the dark ponies down there now.
It's a full-on
''Devil Came Down to Long Beach'' trip.
He's bad. He's real bad.
And this Calitri
is the one who's after my brother?
Like stains on a mattress.
And you should know,
I work for him.
There weren't a lot ofopportunities
for retired car thieves on the gimp.
He put me to work.
But I gotta tell you, Memphis, this guy,
he scares the shit out of even me.
What are you doing, man?
Stop! Stop!
AtleyJackson.
Right. They have Kip.
Take me there.
Raymond Calitri, Memphis Raines.
I try to learn your ways,
understand your obsessions.
But this baseball,
it's so bleeding boring. Isn't it?
Where's my brother?
Memphis Raines.
Your legend proceeds you.
Atley tells me you're the best.
Afteryou left, auto theft in
the South Bay area went down 47 percent.
Where's my brother?
I'm proud of these. Straddle chair
from the Arts and Crafts period.
Mahogany table with cloud-lift pattern.
Black walnut wine table.
Metal's cold, ugly.
Wood's warm, clean.
Provided by nature.
To see a piece of furniture take shape,
it's like watching a child grow.
I asked you a question.
They threw us out England, threw us
out of France, but here we are.
Flourishing, really, except for
the minor inconvenience of despising
everything about your country.
On this list you'll find 50 cars--
five, zero.
I need all 50 delivered
to Long Beach Harbor, pier 1 4,
by 8:00 a.m. four days from now.
I'm paying $200,000.
I'm not interested.
I'm just here for my brother.
Your Kip came to me.
He had street cred.
The brother
of the notorious Memphis Raines.
So two weeks ago I hired him
and advanced him $1 0,000.
Atley told me. If it's about the
advance, I can understand your anger.
A debt has to be settled.
Ten grand, from me to you.
- I wish it was that easy.
- I don't see the complication.
I have four days to deliver 50 cars,
and I have no cars.
- Well, that's another problem.
- It is another problem, isn't it?
It's about me delivering 50 top-end cars
because I said I would...
because if I don't my South American
friend goes somewhere else from now on.
And that's not good.
It's a humiliation.
Because I'm the asshole
who said I could deliver.
Am I an asshole?
Do I look like an asshole?
Yeah.
- I need that paper satisfied.
- I'm retired.
Now, where the hell is my brother?
I made this as well.
My first one.
It takes 80,000 pounds of pressure
to crush a car.
Kip?
- Who's that?
- Memphis.
- Oh, shit.
- You okay?
- Shut it off!
- Turn it off!
- You've got 30 seconds
to consideryour options.
- Shut it off!
One: You kill me, they kill you,
your brother dies anyway.
Two: You lie, you accept the job,
you take your brother, you run.
I hunt you down, I kill you,
I kill your brother...
and I kill your mother
for the aggravation you've caused me.
Three: You accept the deal, you steal
some cars, you make some money...
and you be a big brother.
- Memphis!
- 8:00 a.m. Friday morning.
The cars are on the boat,
or your brother's in the coffi n.
Get me out of here!
Somebody get me out of here!
Listen, you don't really
have to make me anything.
Oh, hey, you come down here, you
save my ass, it's the least I can do.
Hey, I heard you were pumpin' gas
someplace up north or somethin', right?
- Yeah, I'm workin' with kids.
- Oh, really?
First place.
I remember this.
Oh, yeah, that was a--
that was a long time ago.
Yeah.
- What'd you put in it?
- I don't know.
It's good.
Ow. Ow.
Oh, God.
- Does Mom know about any of this?
- No, no, no, she doesn't.
And, uh, I don't think she should.
You know, she-- she works really hard,
and this, this-- she doesn't need
to know about any of this stuff.
Look, you know,
I got everything under control.
The kitchen's on fi re.
Uh, man.
Hey, Memphis.
It's good to see you.
Yeah, haul the cartons over there!
- Hey, Fuzzy.
- Aw, shit. What are you doing here?
- I told you I don't know anything.
- Yeah, but you're a liar.
- You're gonna get me fired, man.
- Fired? That's not good.
You're on parole, right?
Fuzzy. Hey.
Nobody wants to get you fired.
Wejust need this information
is all.
Two weeks ago a call came in
for a lot oftop-end cars.
- And who made that call?
- I don't have a clue.
- Okay, we'll just go talk to your boss.
- Shh!
The delivery date.
I know the delivery date.
- And when is that?
- Thursday, Friday, end of the week.
Well, you get me a name within 48 hours,
or we'll be back.
- Good to see you, buddy.
- Thankyou.
- I'm looking for Helen Raines.
- Helen.
- Some guy is here foryou.
- What guy? What's he look like?
Like a fi recracker. Like your son.
- You look so good.
- Thankyou, Mom.
Okay, Spring, uh-- Spring Bouquet.
-What are you doing here?
-Well, uh, AtleyJackson came to see me.
He told me something about Kip.
Can I help you with one of these?
Okay. That's yours.
Tell Castlebeck he's not gonna believe
who just walked into the Quality Cafe.
I can't say I'm surprised.
All his life he looked up to you,
tried to be you.
I guess now he is.
So why is this happening?
I send you guys money.
He-- He met some people,
and he changed.
He lost that-- that s-sweetness.
You know?
Okay, tell me.
- How deep in is he?
- Deep.
Can you get him out?
It means doing things.
Things I told you
I'd never do again.
Do what it takes, Randall.
- When did you get into town, Raines?
- Last night.
- Last night? What for?
- I thought I'd catch a Lakers game.
Heard we got Shaquille.
Guys wanna go?
- Guess not.
- Randall, Randall, Randall. Come here.
I get this call from this uniform,
you know.
Axton. Very nice man.
Remembers everything.
This man calls me up, says,
''Guess who's back in town?''
I say, ''Who?''
He says, ''Randall Raines.''
I say, ''Randall Raines, the car thief? ''
He says, ''Yeah.''
I say, ''Impossible.''
He says, ''No, he's back.''
I say, ''No, he's not.''
He says, ''Yes, I will bet you $200
I just saw Randall Raines.''
- You guys said a lot. Look, Detective--
- No, w-w-whoa, whoa.
What's really,
really ironic about this--
Two nights ago we snare these 1 3
fresh stolens waiting for export, right?
And at the time I'm thinking,
''This feels like Randall Raines.''
Now, it didn't have your panache,
your, uh, flash...
but it just fe lt like Randall Raines.
And now here you are.
Look, I don't know what you boys are
looking for, but I just got back. Okay?
It was a family emergency.
Now, that's the truth.
''Family emergency.'' Yeah, I got
a family emergency too, Randall.
I gotta go tell my woman
that I just lost $200 on a stupid deal.
- Mmm, she's mean.
- What?
She can be mean to m--
It's not so--
Come here. Come here, Randall.
Take those glasses off, man, please.
Do me a favour.
Six years ago you make
a real smart move, you know.
You retire from a life
that's gonna get you busted or killed,
or maybe even both.
And I'm thinkin' that not putting you
away when I had a chance...
is like this big bug up the ass of this
real impressive career that I've had.
Oh, yeah, well, without disappointment,
you can't appreciate victory.
- Eleanor tell you that?
- Well, now, that's hittin'
below the belt.
Yeah, all right, let me tell you
about ''below the belt,'' Randall.
I tell you what-- From here on out,
ifyou walk across the street
outside of a cross walk...
ifyou roll through a stop sign,
ifyou use an aerosol can in a manner
other than directed--
I mean, I don't care. You make one slip,
and I will put you away for good.
- Okay.
- By the time you get out, asshole,
there won't even be cars.
We'll all be cruisin' around
in, you know, little spaceships.
That's gonna suck.
- Who's Eleanor?
- It's a damn car.
And don't you ever talk about my wife.
Excuse me.
Do you know where Otto is?
He's in the back in the paint shop.
Is that you?
It's about time you came to see me.
- H-Hey!
- I missed you.
- It's good to see you!
- You look great.
- It's good to see you.
- You too.
- Ah. You remember myJunie?
- Hey,Junie. How are you?
- We're doing good, thankyou.
- Good. Good.
- You look happy.
- Well, I am happy. I really am.
- So what happened here?
- What do you mean?
Well, it's nice. But the chop shop,
the stripped cars, my education--
What happened? Hey.
Old age happened, that's what happened.
Got tired of killin' 'em.
You know, I woke up
one morning and thought...
''I'm no longer a destroyer.
I am a means of resurrection.''
Now we restore, we revive.
- Come here.
Remember when we used to do this?
- What?
You know. Come here. Okay.
The Ferrari 365 GDB4, Daytona.
Le Mans, 1 971 .
- Five cam--
- No, that's a V-1 2.
V-1 2! Right, right, right, right!
Here it peaks at 5,500 r.p.m.!
-What do you know about Raymond Calitri?
-Who?
Raymond Calitri.
Uh, excuse us, sweetness.
I'll be right back.
- Listen, we can talk right here.
- Okay? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's all right.
Raymond Calitri.
He's a jackal tearing at the soft belly
ofour-- of our fair town.
And he's an asshole to boot,
so be careful.
I heard about Kip.
- Are you considering a comeback tour?
- Do you think it can be done?
Don't do this to me, okay?
Pl-- Please.
Please. Not now.
Oh, man.
- How many cars?
- Fifty.
- How many days?
- Three.
- How many in your crew?
- One, but I came here hoping
to negotiate for a second.
No way. It can't be done.
I mean, you need time to prep,
time to shop. You know that.
It has to be.
They're gonna kill him.
Oh, man.
It was a mistake to come here.
You have a great life now.
I don't want to upset that.
Uh, uh, wait a minute.
Whoa. Hold on.
Look around you.
These days
I'm all about second chances.
So, uh, let's make a few phone calls
and we'll go from there, okay?
Okay.
Don't look at me!
Look at the people next to you!
Next to you! Turn the wheel!
Pull over!
Pull it the hell over!
Asshole!
Learn how to drive!
Don't touch nothin'.Just--
No!
You can't negotiate turns,
you can't signal properly...
you can't maintain speed,
you can't parallel park.
Hell, you can't drive, honey.
Shit, I can't swim. I know I can't.
So you know what I do?
I stay my black ass out the pool!
All right, now, just--
Can you-- Oh! Hello.
Memphis! Hey, how are you?
Sure, sure. When? Okay.
- 323-969-81 1 .
- All right, man. Thanks a lot.
Donny.
Just take it around the block
a couple of times. Okay? All right.
- l've seen betterdays
- Hello. I'm calling for Frankie Fish.
Frank's dead, man.
Yeah, h-he got scragged.
- I'm sorry.
- Uh, yeah, I'm looking
for Henry Santoro.
- He went down to Florida with that
asshole Frankie Fish. You see him,
you tell him I want my money.
- I didn't mess with your money.
- Yes, ma'am.
I'm looking for Dan and Mikey.
Both of'em up to Chino.
Doin' a nickel apiece.
Now I'm not so sure I want
to tell you who this is.
- Yeah, try it, asshole.
- You sound, uh, very busy right now.
You sound very, very busy.
- There's only two names left.
- Yeah? Let's see which ones you got.
Sphinx-- Those two? No way.
- There's no one else.
- Are you sure?
- ..going in there.
- You tell him.
- Listen, why should I--
- Come on!
- You were the one
who answered the phone, right?
Fine. But how's a guy who can't speak
gonna take a phone call?
You've got a call!
Sphinx, is thatyou?
Press a button if it's you.
Sway, you set up this brakejob?
Yeah. He warped all four rotors.
He must've been riding those brakes
like an old lady.
- That's nice.
- Sounds like the left bank's
running lean.
The service department's over there.
- Can I talk to you?
- Talk to me? Yeah, sure, talk.
- Well, thing of it is,
I came back because--
- Do you know what time it is?
It's 5:30.
I came back because--
- I gotta go. I'm late for work.
- Here, let me--
- You're at work.
- I got twojobs.
I have discovered that you have to work
twice as hard when it's honest.
- Hey, Sway, can I get another shot?
- Yeah.
You're still looking amazing.
While you look like a bible salesman.
You're healed.
- Can we improvise a little bit?
- Sure. What do you have in mind?
Do you wanna get a little crazy?
There's a Cutlass 442 in the back.
We can strip down and shine the hood.
What do you say?
Uh, that's not what I had in mind.
No?
It's about my brother.
- Kip's in trouble.
- In trouble?
- He took a boost, and he blew it.
- Shit.
- And you got some Italians?
- Five or six.
- Right.
- It's 50 ladies in 24 hours, $200,000.
Well, I've cleaned up.
I understand. I hate to
even come here and askyou--
-Sway, can I get that drink now, please?
-Yes.
And I had to ask a few of the others
too, and I feel bad about it, but--
- But you had no choice.
You had to come here. Yeah.
- Pretty much.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
I'd love to help Kip,
but I-I'm not into the life any more.
- Well, that's a good thing.
- Yeah.
- I'm glad to see you're doing well.
- Sorry I can't help you.
- I'd like to pay for your drink.
- That's fi ne.
How about that drink?
Yeah, how about that drink?
- Raines. Memphis Raines, huh?
- Do I know you?
Well, you should know me, considering
all the business you done screwed up
for me in the past, baby.
-Johnny B.
- That's me.
- What can I do foryou?
- Well, I'm gonna tell you
what you can do for me, baby.
Get out of Long Beach tonight.
I'll be gone in three days.
I'm just here on some family business.
Word on the street says Raymond Calitri
hired you and your brother
for a top order...
a order shoulda went to me.
That's not the way it went down,Johnny.
Hey! Get away from my car, asshole!
You got somethin' to say
before I kill you, fool?
Sphinx.
Otto send you?
l'm gonna call the doctor
l'm gonnaget better
- l'm gonna run for the priest
- Oh, Dad.
We'd probably both be working
at the dealership if he hadn't died...
just like normal people.
Shit.
- What's the matter with you?
- Man, six years does a lot of
different things to people.
You know, I-- I don't know where you
went, but, you know, you're in there,
you're talkin' about bein' normal.
I mean, y-you were always the one who
was goin' after the easy money. Shit.
I didn't do it for the money.
I did it for the cars.
Gleaming in marina blue...
sun fire yellow...
Marlboro red...
begging to be plucked.
And I'd do it.
I'd boost her...
and just blast to Palm Springs...
instantly feeling better about being me.
And then, the next day, it seems like,
I'm getting shot at...
my friends are dying,
people are going tojail.
I didn't like what I'd become.
Yeah, and then you left...
and then I didn't have
a brother any more.
And now you wanna give me advice...
and I don't even know you.
And, you know, I got my own family now.
I got my own friends.
And, you know, you can say what you want
about them, but they're loyal.
Well, when you hit the wall,
the same thing is gonna happen.
You and your family...
are either gonna get shot...
or get a five-yearjolt at Corcoran.
Those Mercedes we impounded,
need those newfa ngled laser-cut keys?
Each one's from Dressner Foreign Motors,
downtown Newport...
where all the employees are clean
except for him.
James Lakewood. Served a nickel
at Folsom for auto insurance fraud.
Well, gosh, I bet hejust neglected
to mention that to the people
at Dressner Foreign Motors, huh?
It gets better. YoungJames there
places orders for lost keys
to the Mercedes home offi ce in Germany.
- The list.
- Ah, the list.
Well, I guess we gotta start
beatin' the bushes and try to
find out where they l-- Whoa.
- 1 967 Shelby GT 500.
- I know. I know.
- You got Eleanor here?
Otto, there's somebody here to see you.
Oh! The puppy's a big dog now.
- How you doin'?
- Hey there, Kipper. What is this up--
What's that up under there?
Hey. Hey, Otto. How you doin'?
It's a long time. Good to see you.
- Uh, what are you doin' here, Kip?
- Well, actually, we-- We actually
came to talk about some things.
- About what?
- Well, you know.
It seems like you guys need
a little help, and we thought
that we should participate.
But I just promised Mom
I was getting you out of this.
Listen-- Loo-- No, we're talking
about a lot of money here.
- A-And ifyou guys think you're
gonna be gettin' into our Kool-Aid...
- Money?
- you gotta be out of your minds.
- Is that why you think I'm doing this?
- You inconsiderate little punk!
- Can you explain to me how think three
washed-up car thieves...
- well, then you call Mom
and you explain to her...
- and an old man...
- how you wanna--
- are gonna steal 50 cars in two days?
Hey. Hey. Hey.
This is why I do not do business
with family.
I thinkyou should consider this.
Oh, come on, Otto, please. No, his
criminal career has come to an end.
Well, his life will come to an end
unless we pull this off.
And how can we do it without him?
It can't be done, and you know it.
- You guys have any skills at all?
- Please.
Yeah, we have skills. We, um-- Mirror
Man here, he's an electronics expert.
You know, h-he's got some gadgets
that-- that you old fa rts
probably never heard of.
You know, uh, Tumbler over here,
he can pretty much drive
anything with wheels...
and, you know,
some things without wheels.
And, uh, and Toby,
he's a computer genius.
He's-- He's-- He does
fa scinating things with computers.
Wh-What exactly can you do
with a computer, Toby?
I can hack into the DMV mainframe,
I can change VIN numbers...
I can change addresses, registrations.
I can do a lot
of really tricky stuff, okay?
All right, all right,
we do this, we do it my way.
I run the show.
You take your orders from me.
- Ifyou have any problems with that,
you can leave now.
- N-No, that's fi ne.
- Yeah, well, w-who is--
- That's fi ne.
- Who is Gilligan here,
Uh, Gilligan is actually Freb. Freb
can order pizzas like nobody's business.
- What?
- It's true.
Hey, people gotta eat right?
This is outrageous.
I want my lawyer.
I'm not saying a word
till I get a lawyer.
- All right,James, that's an option.
- And, frankly, a reasonable one.
So you call your lawyer,James.
You tell him you've been arrested
on suspicion of grand theft auto.
- We indict you.
- He'll bail you out.
- And we move on to trial.
- Okay, okay.
Kid came to me,
said he'd pay $500 a key.
So I put the order forms through, and
he picked 'em up a couple days later.
- What's the kid's name?
- We kept it anonymous.
He was a well-built kid.
Uh, uh, looks like a boxer.
- What do you want me to do?
- When he comes back, you call us.
- What says he comes back?
- A hunch.
To make the Friday 8:00 a.m. deadline
you're gonna have to go old school.
A one-night boost.
Put all your nuts in one basket. Okay?
- ''One night''?
- Yes.
- What, are you crazy? ''One night.''
- What, do you have, like,
a better plan or something?
- Yeah. You spread it out.
- You play shadow games and shit.
- We're on a truncated timetable.
- Otto, I'm sorry. C-Can you just listen
to me for one second? All right?
- We've heard you, Kip. Shadow games.
But what you have to understand is
that ifyou play shadow games...
by the second night
the heat is onto you.
With a one-night boost, by the time the
first car is reported stolen, your ship
sets sail; it's a surprise attack.
This is a complicated list, fe llas.
It really is. Okay?
There are 25 that aren't a problem,
but these exotics are tough to find.
And the new Mercedes,
they require laser-cut keys. Okay?
- Uh, yeah, I got that covered.
- You have that covered?
- What'd I just say?
Yeah, I got it covered.
- Yeah. Yeah.
All right, all right.
Well, then, let's get to work.
Toby, hack into the insurance database
and find as many cars as you can.
Yes! I got addresses
on Hillary, Natalie and Tracy.
Donny, check the DMV
for the remaining cars on the list.
I'm sorry, miss, but you've missed
five questions. That's failing.
- Oh, no!
- Next.
No! Why?
- You're supposed to go fa ster
when somebody tailgates you!
- Ah. Hello again.
Mm-hmm. Here's your list
of the 20 car owners' names
and addresses that you requested.
- Thankyou.
- That's $1 00, please.
- A hundred dollars?
- Five dollars a car, 20 cars.
- Would you like a calculator?
- It used to be two dollars a car.
Thanks a lot.
- That's all redesigned, right?
- My name is Roger, sir.
May I be of some help?
That's funny. My name's Roger.
Two Rogers don't make a right.
- Roger, I have a problem.
- Yes?
I've been in L.A. three months now.
I have money, I have taste.
But I'm not on anybody's ''A'' list,
and Saturday night is the loneliest
night of the week for me.
Well, a Ferrari
would certainly change that.
Perhaps, mmm. But you know,
this is the one. Yes, yes, yes.
I saw three of these parked outside
the local Starbucks this morning,
which tells me only one thing--
there's too many self- indulgent wieners
in this city with too much bloody money!
Now, if I was driving
a 1 967 275 GTB fo ur-cam--
You would not be
a self- indulgent wiener, sir.
- You would be a connoisseur.
- Precisely.
Champagne would fa ll from the heavens.
Doors would open.
Velvet ropes would part.
I don't have one here.
However, I do have one in the warehouse.
Superb.
What else do you have in the warehouse?
Mm-hmm. All right. Uh-huh.
That was Mr Lakewood
from the dealership.
He says that boxer-lookin' punk
is gonna pick up the keys
to three new Mercedes today.
Same make and model as the ones
we already got impounded.
Now we talkin'.
The El Spirito de Graciela
sails Friday...
8:00 a.m. sharp.
We'll target all the cars
within 45 minutes of here.
By the time their alarm
tracking systems are activated...
the cars will already be
in these containers.
Fellas, this is Sway.
No questions. I'm here for Kip.
- All right.
- lt 's me. He's-- He's here.
- ln the redChevy Nova ?
- Uh, that's affirmative, sir.
- Pull over.
All right, as soon as he leaves,
you call me with the owners' addresses.
-All right?
- I'll get those forms right over, sir.
Damn boss.
Always on my case.
- I got three here?
- Mm-hmm.
- Thankyou.
Huh.
Randall Raines,
Donny Astricky, Otto Halliwell.
- Should I set up some tails?
- Uh-uh.
They're too smart for that.
They'll just dump the cars.
No, we'll get them
with the Mercedes.
Let's set up, uh, three surveillance
teams at those addresses.
Now, you go ahead
and you make your move, man...
and I will be waiting foryou.
- Why do you call 'em girls' names?
- That's a good question.
- It's a code.
You say Jane, you say Shirley,
Lucy, Edna...
and nobody listening on the waves
is the wiser.
Got 'em.
All right, we've got the addresses
on all 50 ladies. Let's scout 'em.
- There she is.
- Nice.
Damn, it's cold up here.
They keep these Ferraris refrigerated?
And you know black people
don't like cold weather.
We're a tropical people, man.
When this is over, I'm gonna
smoke a joint, watch two hours of Roots,
and I'm gonna kick your ass.
Hello, and welcome to TVCar Trivia.
First question:
Who was the driver of a '73 Firebird?
- Uh, Otto.
- Uh,Jim Rockford, Rockford Files.
Give me Columbo.
- A Peugeot convertible.
- What colour?
- Grey.
- How you know that?
'Cause llo ve thatshow.
Well, I got three words for all y'all:
get a life.
Oh, this is some kiddie shit, Sphinx.
What's on Magnum P.I.'s licence plate?
- Robin 1.
- Wait, wasn 't Robin that faggoty guy
who hung with him ?
No, that was Higgins.
That was Higgins.
Hey, ten points
for our fearless leader.
Sway, how about giving us the honour
of the Bill Bixby trifecta?
He dro ve a Corvette in The Magician,
a Ford pickup truck
in The Incredible Hulk...
and in The Courtship of Eddie 's Father
he walked.
- Bingo.
- My man.
We get tired of lookin '
at each other
Al, tell me somethin '.
Nothin' doin' here, sir.
Nobody's showing.
Copy.
A minivan approaching.
It seems a little late
for soccer practise.
Heads up. I think we got
some activity right here.
Oh, that is--
Looks like it's Kip Raines.
And we got a Randall Raines.
Ifthey take this,
we will take them down.
He's pulling something out
of his pocket. You see that?
It's a camera. Looks like
he'sjust doing some homework.
All right, let's leave him be. I don't
wanna burn this. They will be back.
Huh.
You know what? Let's go over
to Otto's in the morning.
Kick over some rocks
and see what's underneath there.
We saved the best for last:
the '67 Shelby Mustang GT-500.
- The GT-500?
- Yeah, yeah.
There she is.
Yep. There's Eleanor.
Eleanor is Memphis' unicorn.
- What's a unicorn?
- A fa bled creature?
You know, the horse with the horn?
Impossible to capture?
It's the one car that, no matter
how many times you try to boost...
something always happens.
We're gonna get through this this time,
right? It's gonna be smooth.
- What's he doing?
- It's gonna be easy.
He's talking to her, man,
trying to get reacquainted.
You know, they had a rough history. She
almost got him killed a couple of times.
- I don't want any talking back.
- He flipped one on the Harbor Freeway.
He went off the Long Beach Pier once.
A smooth, easy ride.
We'rejust gonna glide.
Big night tomorrow, guys.
Let's go home.
- Did you-- Did you get the picture?
- Yeah.
See you tomorrow night, Eleanor,
with your fi ne ass.
Man, we're almost home.
You wanna get something to eat?
I'd like to get a chocolate malt.
- Hey! Hey!
- Get out of the car!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
- Why are people shooting at us?
- 'Cause I blew up their car.
Over here!
''Beast.''
Okay, okay.
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
Hey!
Oh, you-- y-you think it's a game?
Johnny B.
The cops, man.
I ain't got nothin' but time, baby.
Oh, man,
we're gonna be here all night, man.
Look! Cop car! Uh-huh!
Long as I'm in here, you'rejust gonna
sit out there. Aren't ya? All right?
Hey, listen, this is the plan.
This is what we're gonna do.
There's a big rig over there--
Uh, mister, is that your truck
out there, the Big Rig Wrecker?
- The Big Rig Wrecker's mine, but--
- That's cool.
What do I gotta do? How do I learn?
What do I do? Where do I go?
- Well, you gotta go
to truck driving school.
- Truck dri-- I know, man, I know.
But I mean, like, um--
You boys ready to play
a little Pin the Tail on the Donkey?
- Can I get you
a jelly doughnut or something, man?
- No, I'm just gonna go ahead and go.
- 'Cause I'm gonna have the waffl e and--
- I'm gonna-- Maybe next time, though.
I'm gonna smoke you!
- Hey! Damn!
- What the hell's going on?
- Want some of this?
- Yeah.
-You guys got permits for these weapons?
-Oh, man.
So you think I can
only get pizzas, huh?
- Boosted it myself.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. How'd you get it?
- Actually, the keys were in it.
- Oh, yeah, well, that kind of
defies the point then, don't it?
You stole a car that wasn't on the list.
You stole a car that wasn't on the list!
Why didn't you just go to the police
station in-- in a red clown suit...
and let everybody know
what we're doin' here?
- What have we got?
- I don't know.
- Shit! Fellas.
- What?
- Give me that.
- Check this out.
- Let me see that.
- What?
- Look.
- This looks like heroin.
- Yeah.
- What?
- Exactly.
- Where did you get this car?
- In front of some poker parlour
in Chinatown.
You ever consider why a car
in a neighbourhood like that
would have its keys left in it?
- No.
- Maybe because nobody in that
neighbourhood would be stupid enough
- All right.
Get this shit out of here. Take it back.
- No, no, no, we can't take it back.
- Get it out of here!
- Will everybody relax for a second?
- Shut up.
- No, no, no! Take it back!
- Take it back!
- I want that shit.
Give me that. Give me that.
- Now! Out!
- Look what you--
- Man, I will knock the shit out ofyou.
- Shut up.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Who is it?
- Detective Castlebeck.
Oh. Christ.
Goddamn it.
- Hey, hello, Otto.
- Detective. Good to see ya.
- Long time.
- Yeah. You're looking good.
Thankyou.
So, Randall, what do we got here?
We got a multigenerational
gathering of players?
- Is that what we got here?
- Yeah, right.
Here's Donny. How you been, D?
- I'm just happy to see you, brother.
- Yeah.
I got to tell you, Randall,
seeing you here, Otto, Donny...
makes me feel almost nostalgic.
Kind of like a big reunion.
You should stick around,
'cause a little later we're gonna...
make s'mores and sing ''Kumbayah.''
- Yeah. What is this?
- What's it--
- This.
They call this a Cadillac. Yeah.
- What's wrong with it, Otto?
- Needs restoration.
- What?
- Brightening.
- Otto. You got a '39 Ford right there.
- Well, that's a pretty car, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Isn't that a nice car?
- And right here you got
Now, these are beautiful cars, Otto.
And here we got a '83 Cadillac Eldorado?
- Yeah.
- I mean, who the hell pays...
to brighten up a Cadillac Eldorado?
I-I think it holds a certain,
uh, sentimental value, you know?
N-Nothing more.
Run me down a tag.
C licence 3-2-9-H-R-O.
That is, uh, Harold, Randall, Otto,
burgundy Cadillac.
No fa ith in our newfo und
goodness, Detective, huh?
Task force runs on statistics
and numbers, Otto. You know that.
- Randall, this Kip?
- That's my brother. He's all grown up.
One-Baker-eleven, Pacific Division,
three-two-niner, Harold, Randall, Otto.
No wants, no warrants at this time.
DMVnot on file.
- Copy that. Thankyou.
- See, I know what you're doin'.
I know. You--
You're thinking there's no want...
but that, uh, I stripped its guts
and crated her up, right?
- Is that what you did, Randall?
- No, I didn't do it.
You know, forget it.
You're trying to hurt my feelings? Fine!
You know what? Go ahead.
Do it. Let her rip.
- Go ahead. Rev it up.
- All right, goddamn it. I will.
Sell it to you cheap.
Yeah, '83, first year they put
the auto-ride control on these boys.
Oh, I don't know. You probably know more
about cars at this point than I do.
- What? You slippin' on me, Randall?
- No, it'sjust your knowledge
overwhelms me.
- It's got a real nice-sounding engine,
right, Otto?
- 4.1 litre.
- Digital fuel injection?
- You got it.
- All right. Let's see what she got.
- You the man.
Give it some more. Give it some more.
- Yeah, that's it!
- Go! Go!
- Let's go!
- Come on.
Baby, don't be so mean!
- Yeah, that's it!
- Hey, hey.
- Oh, yeah, that was good.
Yeah, you break it,
you buy it, my friend.
Yeah, she got some power goin' on.
All right.
I'll catch you later then.
- It's on for tonight.
- How do you know?
They got the call signs
on all the units working tonight.
What-- What were you
gonna do with this?
- I was gonna bonk him.
- What? Bonk?
For the next 24 hours,
all your decision-making privileges
have been removed!
- You got it?
- Got it.
- Yeah, that's cool, man.
Obviously they're onto us.
He's sniffi n' real close.
If anything tonight appears
out of place, I want you to cut bait,
get out of there and walk away.
And get rid of this goddam car!
- What's up, Kip?
- Toby, what are you doin'?
You think you're comin' with us,
but you're not.
- What are you talkin' about, man?
I'm part of the team. I get to go.
- No.
No, no, wake up. You're gonna end up
in jail or in the morgue or some shit.
Don't be stupid.
What am I supposed to do?
Did you see a box
of rubber gloves here, man?
Gloves? Man, you don't need gloves.
This is the new age. Check this out.
- What is this?
- Let mejust see that big claw
you call a hand.
That's not doughnut jelly,
so don't eat it.
Your new fingerprints.
Elvis is back.
- Boy got skills, right?
- Yeah, you do.
Look like a little ghetto Smurf.
I am a bad man.
Thanks. Thanks for doin' this.
Keep it real. Think slow.
We should get through it just fi ne.
''Low Rider,'' Donny.
Donny? ''Low Rider.''
All my friends know the lo wrider
Yeah, the lo wrider
is a little higher
Yeah
Okay, let's ride.
Oh! Shit.
Give me the damn torch.
What? I tell you, I'm the man.
Now, where does this go?
Find a way to get in here. Get this--
I tell you, I'm running this shit!
You do that again, I will kick--
Cool, man. You don't have
to take it so damn personal.
Ah! Everything is perfect.
Hello, ladies.
Always was a sucker for a redhead.
Let's go. Come on.
Move. Move. Go, go!
Workyour magic, baby. I know you know
Ferraris. Work your magic.
Girl got skills.
You all right?
- You think we're gonna make it?
- I don't know. It's too early to tell.
Diana, Tricia, Nadine and Rose
are on their way.
Good goin', guys.
- Al, tell me something.
- Unit Two. Sorry, sir, nothin' yet.
Son of a bitch. I know you're not
parking right in front of me.
Oh, no, I can't see a damn thing.
All right, we gotta move.