-Your shoulder flaring?
-No.
-You winced.
-I didn't wince.
You grimaced.
My shoulder doesn't hurt, Gus.
How long has it been hurting?
Perry wants me to start tomorrow.
You got to be kidding.
You're not doing it. No way.
It's the end of a shitty season.
-I'm gonna talk to Perry.
-Sit down.
Relax.
It's a throwaway, Billy. It means nothing.
Not to the Red Sox.
If I see you wince even one time....
Oh, God.
I've got the ugliest wife in the league.
That hurts. It hurt my feeling.
Buckle your seat belt.
Are we expecting Ms. Aubrey this evening?
We are.
-What name am I registered under?
-Mike Nelson.
-The Sea Hunt fellow, you know.
-All right.
Tell the desk that I don't want to talk
to anybody except her, all right?
Fitch, tonight...
...everything has to be perfect.
Have I ever let you down, Mr. Chapel?
This is Mr. Chapel.
Have there been any messages?
No?
Thanks.
This is Jane. Leave a message
and I'll get back to you. Thanks. 'Bye.
Jane, it's Billy. I'm worried now, so...
...please call.
Are you there?
Jesus. I've been banging out here forever.
What the hell happened to you?
You weren't at the gym.
-Is Jane here?
-No.
Jesus.
Chap, a lot of little bottles
makes a big bottle.
That could be her.
-You got to throw today.
-Gus, do me a favor.
Get the door.
Throw some water on your hair.
It might look like you took a shower.
No, not at all.
He's in the bathroom back there.
-Mr. Wheeler.
-Good morning, Billy. Got a minute?
Yeah, sure.
Not easy to get up here.
-They treat me right.
-They didn't have you on the register.
I can't remember all your names.
Price of fame, huh?
-Can I get you something?
-No.
Let's just sit.
It's been a rough season.
-Always next year.
-Not for me.
It's one of those secrets everybody knows.
What you don't know is it's official.
Billy, I sold the Tigers.
Well, that's great.
Is it?
You've been the heart and soul
of this team.
Like family.
All the negotiations,
the bastards never said a word.
Said what?
They want to trade you to the Giants.
-Is that why you're here?
-No.
I don't know how to say this.
You know, I've been watching you
for 18 years.
Nothing...
...nothing has given me more pleasure.
You're like the old boys.
They were golden.
They had that special pride.
When they were done, they were done.
Nobody had to show them the door.
-Are you saying I should retire?
-Why not?
It wouldn't hurt the negotiations,
and it'd serve those sons of bitches right.
I don't know what to say.
You can't tell me
you haven't thought about it.
And you've been smart with money, right?
Right?
I've always been a Tiger.
I know, son.
That's why this is killing me.
You know, my dad bought this team
when I was seven.
I grew up watching the Tigers.
I was gonna leave the team to my kids,
but they don't even like baseball.
Everything's changed, Billy.
The players, the fans,
TV rights and arbitrations.
It isn't the same. The game stinks, and l...
...l can't be a part of it anymore.
Billy, you want me to....
Hello? Jane.
Where are you?
You're downstairs?
Just stay where you're at.
I'm on my way down.
What do you want me to tell them?
I need more time.
The game doesn't stink, Mr. Wheeler.
It's a great game.
Billy, what's up?
I tried to get her in a cab, Mr. Chapel,
but she said she wanted to...
...just go and walk in Central Park.
Go easy on our boys today, Billy.
Jane, why didn't you wait?
Are you crying?
What's the matter?
They didn't have any Kleenex
in the hotel bathroom.
What's going on, Jane?
I've been sitting in the lobby
for the last two hours.
Doing what?
I'm sorry I didn't call last night.
I could tell that you were worried--
If something's wrong, just say it, Jane.
I mean, we don't....
We never had to fake it.
I'm leaving.
I'm going to London.
London?
There's a job. A good job.
An editor's position.
I've been trying to figure out a way
to tell you but everything sounds so....
What can I say?
Tell me what to say.
I can't tell you, Billy.
It's all right.
I knew it...
...the day I met you five years ago.
-You knew what?
-You don't need me.
You and the ball and the diamond,
you're perfect. A perfectly beautiful thing.
You can win or lose the game
all by yourself.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Have dinner tonight with me
after the game.
-We'll go to Mario's.
-I have a 6:00 plane.
They wanted me there a week ago
when you called, and I wanted to see you.
I wanted to say good-bye.
Good-bye, Billy.
Welcome to New York
and to Yankee Stadium...
...on a crisp and glorious fall afternoon...
...where the Yankees try to win
the divisional title against the Tigers.
Hi, everybody. I'm Vin Scully,
along with Steve Lyons...
...and welcome to our final telecast
of the regular season.
You can smell the fall.
The World Series isjust around the corner.
Mr. Chapel?
Ken Strout. I was your batboy
a long time ago.
My dad was a Tiger.
Joe Strout.
I remember.
How's he doing?
Good. He and Ma are living in Florida.
He doesn't move around too easy, though.
He's got bad knees.
You know, a little arthritis.
-You playing today?
-Don't think so. They just called me up.
Good. Well, good luck to you.
Give your dad my best.
He was a great player.
Thanks. I'll tell him.
Live from Yankee Stadium in New York,
it's New York Yankees baseball.
Today, on the next to last day of the year...
...the Yankees have a chance
to clinch the pennant.
To do it they'll have to beat
Billy Chapel and the--
-Excuse me.
-Good afternoon, everyone.
Excuse me.
Could you turn that off, please?
-The Yankees are set to clinch it.
-No.
But standing in their way is the great
veteran right-hander of the Tigers....
...Billy Chapel.
Does anybody else know?
Nobody knows nothing. Not even Perry.
If they knew,
that's all they'd be talking about.
What does Jane say?
Jane's moving to London.
Moving to London? What the....
-How are you gonna manage that?
-We're not.
This ain't your day.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
That's Wheeler's nephew.
He sent him down to get your answer.
Guess he's gonna sit
through the whole game if he has to.
Poor kid.
He doesn't even know
what he's doing here.
Throw the ball to the glove, son.
Just play catch.
Since you're throwing bullets,
I won't mention you were an hour late...
...and I've been trying to figure out who
my pitcher would be if you didn't show up.
Have I ever not showed?
I mean, in 19 years,
have I ever not showed?
That's true of everyone
till the first time they don't show.
Billy, I had an idea.
I've pretty much made up my mind,
but I wanted to run it by you first.
I want Jimmy to catch today.
I know how you feel about Gus but...
...he ain't hitting.
He ain't hit for a while now.
I haven't said anything
but we need the left-handed bat.
I want Gus.
I know. And I'd love to take
one of these goddamn games.
We're not laying down. We're not gonna
be a red carpet to the Series for them.
Gus catches or I don't pitch.
Me and Gus.
Nobody else.
I hope you hear me.
Are you telling me how to run this team?
No. But today...
...it's me and Gus.
I've never asked you any other time, okay?
Good.
Glad you agree. Can't argue about this
right now. Got to warm up.
I'm sorry. We have a bit of a delay.
We're correcting a bit
of a maintenance problem.
So we don't have a bit of a crash?
Is there someplace I can stay?
The Premier Lounge is down there
on your right.
Thanks.
As the sun goes down,
it'll be an easier time to hit for both teams.
And now talking about shadows
and sunlight...
...that might very well sum up Billy Chapel.
Long has he stood
in the brilliant sunshine...
...in his great 19-year career...
...but now, battling back
from an 8 and 11 record this year...
...trying to find his way out
of the shadows, back into the sunlight.
He'll be facing Mike Robinson,
followed by Jonathan Warble...
...and then Sam Tuttle.
Bottom of the first inning,
no score, and the Yankees coming up.
What's he looking at?
He's looking...
...at the clouds.
You okay, Chap?
You okay?
Catching, Number 27...
...Gus Sinski. Number 27.
At shortstop, Number 7....
-Trying to take my hand off?
-Sorry.
Just let me set for that juice.
Warn me or something.
I'm gonna throw a little harder
than usual today.
There's your warning.
Chap, don't throw it away too early.
Today I'm throwing hard.
You and me? One more time?
Why not?
We got you, Chapel! You're done!
We're gonna stick a fork in you!
You're finished!
The Tigers are done! You're done!
Get out of town!
I can always tell when I'm in New York.
You suck!
You stink on ice!
You couldn't pitch a tent!
Clear the mechanism.
Hello, Mike.
Strike one!
Chapel working on Robinson.
Bottom of the first inning, no score.
And there's a little looper to José Garcia.
One away.
This is my lucky day. How are you?
Fine. What'll you have?
The Bud on tap is good.
This is a beautiful day
for the big ballpark in the Bronx.
Two solid years,
and now a third with the Yankees.
Pretty good breaking ball.
A lot of guys would be upset
about missing their flight...
...delay this and that
but this works out beautiful for me.
Chapel trying to derail the Yankees...
...and the Yankees trying to end a season...
...that has long been finished by Detroit.
They pushed this guy up
to pitch this game...
...so basically we clinch today
and I get to see it. Beautiful.
-What can I get for you?
-Chivas and water.
Here we go.
Everything is.... Look at that. It's early.
You got nuts, chips?
-Got those pretzels.
-I can make do.
Thank you.
Good fastball with some movement on it.
-Down goes Warble.
-He swung at that? He's got nothing now.
If I was Boston, I'd be worried
that they were throwing the game.
This guy used to be a monster.
When he first came up, unhittable.
Now he's a junker.
...three years in a row.
In baseball circles we all know...
...there's no love lost between these two.
They don't like each other too much.
At third base, Number 13, Sam Tuttle.
Sam Tuttle.
I can't think of a better reason
not to be a Yankee.
Sam Tuttle hit .625.
He went 5 for 8 against Chapel this year.
-That would make me not like a guy.
-I would think so.
Fastball on the inside corner. Strike one.
Wasn't that inside?
Never do swing at the first pitch,
do you, Sam?
No. We're off the page now, Gus.
This is between me and Ugly.
Straight heat.
Thatta boy.
-Strike two!
-That shit's outside.
No wonder nobody likes you.
Everything's a goddamn debate.
Fastball, and it runs right on
that outside corner.
So 0 and 2 the count to Sam Tuttle.
I saw that shitty little Hollywood movie
you did.
-Ball!
-Sinski wanted that one.
So did Chap.
You see the reaction on his face.
That's a good pitch on the outside corner.
Tuttle didn't like the first two calls,
and now he gets a break on that one.
That's not the kind ofpitch that Chapel's
gonna like being called a ball all day long.
Don't crowd me, Sam.
I hate being crowded.
One and two the count, and Tuttle
has really moved up on the plate.
He's all over the plate now.
Now you got the idea.
Down goes Tuttle.
What a knockdown pitch that was.
There's a message being delivered.
Yankee Stadium is like a schoolyard...
...and Bill Murdie looks like a teacher
who sees trouble.
They say in every great athlete there's
a mean streak and Chapel's no different....
Bill Murdie goes from umpire to referee.
When I played against this guy,
if he had good stuff he'd flip you like this.
He'd throw a ball right over your head...
...just to let you know,
"I can throw the ball anywhere I want. "
You know,
I've been a Yankee fan since 1958.
I can name a Yankee for every number.
Oh, God. Please don't.
Number One: Billy Martin,
Bobby Richardson.
Two: Frank "The Crow" Crosetti
and Bobby Murcer.
Three: The Babe. Four: Gehrig.
-Five: DiMaggio. Six--
-Excuse me.
-Steve Boyer, Roy White.
-Would you mind?
You can't smoke in a bar.
What, now you can't talk in a bar?
This ain't church, lady.
-Tuttle back up to the plate.
-Two and two!
Same shit, different day?
I'd throw it at you again,
but I'm afraid Murdie'd run me.
-Strike three!
-Good breaking ball.
-Got him looking.
-Greatjob setting up the hitter.
Tuttle looks like a deer
caught in the headlights.
Chapeljelly-legged him.
So at the end of one,
Tigers nothing, Yankees nothing.
Here we go now. Four, five, six.
Let's get something started.
José, atta-baby. It's all about positioning.
You got to wait on this guy.
-Mike, can I have some water?
-Sure thing, Billy.
You all right?
You got it going good out there.
Make sure you save something.
Birch wants to play golf tomorrow.
You know, I played golf with Birch
the day I met Jane.
You doing all right?
I'm not hearing them at all out there.
Yeah, that'll fix it.
I don't need any help.
I can see that. I can see you got your car
kicked completely into submission.
I mean it. Just go away.
I can always tell when I'm in New York.
Do you really know anything about cars?
-Want me to have a look at it?
-Okay.
It's not mine. It's just a trashy rental.
Yeah. Mine, too.
Try the key, see if we can't get it started.
I should've paid attention in auto shop.
-What did you do?
-Well, I was....
I have no idea. I don't....
I don't know anything about cars.
I was just trying to be manly.
That was great, thank you.
You saved my day.
'Course I did.
I said I would.
Where you headed?
I'm not sure.
Bear Mountain, maybe.
I just threw my stuff in the car
and took off. Had to get out of the city.
-How come?
-'Cause summer's over and I missed it.
I work all the time. It makes me feel old.
I don't know.
Thanks again.
-What's the problem?
-My problem seems to be solved.
Oh, no.
Wait a sec. The car's fine.
Listen, honey. I gave up on four calls
hauling my ass out to you.
That's $100 to me,
so if nothing's wrong with this car now...
...there will be when I bring it down
to the city.
-Everything all right?
-Everything's peaches, mac.
You're Billy Chapel.
I can't believe it.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I can't believe this.
I'm sorry.
You're the greatest freaking ballplayer
out there.
I'm sorry. But you really are.
I'm gonna go get that.
You stay right here, okay?
Billy Chapel.
Nice to meet you. Jane Aubrey.
You know, I got this problem.
I'd like to keep talking with you
but I got to...
...go to work.
Just a sec.
I'll get there when I get there.
-Can you do me a favor?
-Anything.
We got a bum deal on this rental here,
so if you could...
...if you could haul this back to town for us,
I'd really appreciate it.
I can't take that.
Wait a second. What are you doing?
-You like baseball?
-What?
-Baseball.
-No, not really.
-You ever been?
-No.
Would you like to go?
Would you like to go
to a baseball game with me?
If she don't want to go, I'll go.
Don't let that happen.
Lady, you can't just stand
in the middle like that.
-Sorry.
-Let me see your ticket.
You're with the players' wives. Follow me.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
-Who are you here with, honey?
-Billy Chapel.
How nice.
This week's blonde.
No, stay. You're cool.
Trust me. I've been there.
-I'm Kisha Birch.
-Hi.
-Jane Aubrey. Nice to meet you.
-Strike three!
-You got a ball?
-Yeah.
You don't lose much, do you?
I lose. I've lost.
About 134 times.
That's over 15 years, okay?
You count them?
We count everything in baseball.
I mean, God, that's all we do.
All right, quit stalling.
What?
You haven't told me anything about you.
Nothing.
I figured if I kept my mouth shut
I could pass for elegant and mysterious.
You're forgetting I saw you
on the highway...
...kicking the hell out of your car.
-Where are you from?
-Oh, God.
Three questions.
Syracuse, New York. That's one.
What are the pads for?
This one is my article on lip gloss
for Elle magazine...
...this one is on skin peels,
and my grocery list.
Last question.
How do you like to be kissed?
You know, I've always thought...
...that men and women
should just carry around signs.
If you're poor and you can't afford it
you would make yours out of...
...cardboard and string. And if you're rich,
you could have it lettered in gold leaf...
...pounded out of tin by Mexican craftsmen,
it doesn't matter...
...but you wear them around your neck.
And they say things
like "shallow" or "horny."
It just would be a hell of a lot easier.
What would yours say?
-Isn't this your floor?
-I think so.
We've been here twice before.
Good morning.
Got to go.
Sleep as long as you want.
You can take a shower, anything you want.
Nobody'll bother you
till you take the sign off the door.
Okay. Thanks.
What's this? A souvenir?
It's my number.
You don't have to give me this.
I know I don't have to do this, but...
...l wanted to.
-When will you be back?
-I already checked.
Four weeks from Thursday
I'll be back in New York, so...
...that Thursday night...
...meet me in the bar downstairs
at 10:00, okay?
I'll be there waiting for you.
If you don't show up, if you leave me
standing in that bar, it'll ruin this.
Well, then I guess I'll just have to show up.
I'm serious.
I'll be there, Jane, okay?
Okay, Billy Chapel.
Birch, baby! Kiss that bitch good-bye!
Take it over!
Clear the mechanism.
You look old, Davis.
Are we that old?
And the fastball sinks at the knees,
and the count 0 and 1.
Don't smile at me, Davis. I hate that.
It was a sad day in Detroit
when Gary Wheeler...
...the owner of the Tigers
and a somewhat beleaguered franchise...
...was forced to trade Davis Birch,
who was a free agent.
Detroit could not come up
with his monetary demands.
The Yankees were waiting
with open arms and an open wallet.
It was your team, too.
How much money we got to make?
You want to see my team?
-That's my team over there.
-You got it. I'll be out in a second, okay?
Billy, are you gonna just sit there
and mope or are you gonna help?
I ain't carrying no books.
Where's the pillows?
You're the best, kiddo.
The best around. The worthy opponent.
The 0-1 pitch, and the bottom
just drops out of it. Strike two.
Look at Birch staring out at Chapel saying:
"Where's that curveball coming from?
He never had that before. "
It don't happen that often,
but I got you mixed up, don't l?
You're guessing now, aren't you?
Here's your fastball...
...right down the pipe so you don't leave
thinking I was afraid to give it to you.
Strike!
Fastball runs on the inside corner.
Strike three called.
I could've hit that.
Billy Chapel all business,
taking care of Birch on three pitches.
Kenny Howell will follow.
Ifyou don't show up, ifyou leave me
standing in that bar, it'll ruin this.
Cab, Mr. Chapel?
You leaving?
I was supposed to meet someone,
but they....
I'm sorry. I wasn't gonna come.
I sat in my apartment waiting till the time
when I was not gonna show up here...
...and then I just....
Oh, God.
Billy Chapel.
Why do you always use both my names?
So I know what I'm up against.
I had a great time with you last month.
It's not that. Don't get me wrong.
It's just that....
I don't mean to sound
like anything or anything....
I don't do that.
-I won't say anything about it.
-What?
-I just don't do it, not since college.
-What don't you do?
-I think I should go home.
-Why?
Because I just don't screw like that!
And I hate that word.
-You want the cab, Mr. Chapel?
-Give it to somebody else.
I don't go to hotel rooms
with men I don't know.
-I can't be a groupie.
-You're not a groupie.
You don't look like one or act like one.
I didn't treat you like one.
-Wasn't I a gentleman?
-Yes, I know.
You pull up out of nowhere, start my car
make me laugh and the next thing I know...
...l'm at a baseball game that you win!
I mean, it's so surreal.
Little boys buy cards
with your picture on them.
They buy those for the gum.
-Goddamn it!
-What?
Goddamn what?
I like you.
So what's the problem?
I'm really not at all
the person you think I am.
And I think it would just be more fair
for both of us for me to just leave.
Forget it.
What's the difference? I mean....
Give me the thing.
What's the difference between
the real you and this other you?
The real me is....
The real me is plain, uninteresting...
...and hates sexy underwear
because it's really uncomfortable.
The real you is a bummer.
This can't be what you were looking for
from this evening.
Be totally honest with me.
That day I fixed your car, I got lucky.
Maybe you got lucky, too.
I know we don't know each other so well...
...but that's what I was hoping.
I mean, we don't have to....
We could like....
Like walk, I mean.... We could just walk.
Walk?
I could walk.
We don't have to talk so much either.
Border collie.
My dad loved the blue heelers.
Is he still alive?
No, they're both gone.
Him first, and then her within a year.
He was a good man.
Very tall. Very reserved.
Passionately in love with two things:
My mother and baseball.
Then he was a lucky man.
How do we do this?
How does this work, Billy?
I told you, I have to be here next month
for a couple of days.
-I want to see you.
-Okay.
When you're away...
...l'll live my life and you'll live yours.
And none of this stupid, bullshit,
why-didn't-you-call-me crap.
And what you do when you're not with me
has nothing to do with me, and vice versa.
No questions asked.
No worrying.
No obsessing.
That sounded perfect.
-Good night.
My back keeps breaking out.
Candy says it's gross.
Use the loofah.
The what?
The loofah. It exfoliates.
You're losing it over this girl.
I met this woman in New York.
I'm thinking of asking her down.
-Call her.
-No, it's not....
It's casual.
I've seen her a few times over the winter
in New York when I happened to be there.
Call her.
Hello?
I'm having this problem with my skin peel.
-I was just thinking about you.
-What were you thinking?
I was wondering when you play
your first series against the Yankees.
-Come down here.
-What?
Come spend the weekend.
Meet my friends.
I don't know, Billy.
What do you mean, you don't know?
I've got a ton of work to do,
and I can't afford to be running off--
-So I'll pay.
-No.
It's not that.
We made the rules.
I think we should stick to them.
There's no rules about having fun.
That's bullshit.
Why is it bullshit?
Because if you just want to have fun,
come down here 'cause this is fun.
You know who sat
in the bleachers last Sunday?
Who?
Sandy Koufax.
You are such--
You are like the ultimate guy.
You don't like guys?
I need a regular guy,
not the guy on the Old Spice commercial.
-It was Right Guard.
-What?
It was Right Guard, that commercial.
I was being metaphorical, Billy.
Look, this is crazy.
What am I supposed to do?
I'm supposed to run down there
and meet Sandy Koufax...
...get his autograph
and sleep with Mr. Right Guard?
-What are you so afraid of?
-I'm not afraid.
I can't be a groupie.
That's the second time
you used that word to me...
...and it didn't really
go down that well the first time.
Now you're mad.
No, I'm not mad. I'm just...
-...pissed off.
-That's not fair.
-I'm gonna hang up now.
-Let's start from--
I'll call you another time.
-No. When will you call me?
-When I don't feel like killing you.
I told her.
I haven't seen you around much lately.
I've been working hard.
All work and no play....
All I've got is my toothbrush
and a bathing suit I bought at the airport.
You're not smiling.
You're annoyed. I'm an idiot.
No, I'm an idiot.
Jane, listen to me.
No matter what happens
in the next five minutes...
...l want you to know
that when I opened this door...
...l was so happy to see you
that my heart leapt.
It leapt in my chest.
Billy, can I borrow your...
...blow dryer?
Don't go.
It's not your....
I have terrible timing. I've always had it.
That's why I failed at acting
and skiing and table tennis.
I should have known when the only flight
to Lauderdale was at 6:10 a.m...
...and the only rental car I could get
was this ridiculous Lincoln.
The car is perfect.
It's perfect.
That girl....
Don't explain. I'm not angry or hurt.
We're not anything. You're fine.
-You can do whatever you want.
-I know I can....
-I don't want her.
-Then what is she doing here?
I like her. She's my masseuse.
It's never quite how you play it
in your head.
What about the whole deal thing?
What deal?
You know, you do what you do,
I do what I do.
You believed that? I was lying.
I was trying to be the man.
And I was doing a damn good job of it
until you invited me down here.
You were right.
I was afraid.
I was afraid you were gonna break
my heart into 1,000 pieces.
I'm sorry. Jane.
I've been thinking about you, Jane.
I don't know what I was.... That was a....
All right, tell me what I can say
so you'll believe me.
I believe you.
Then stay.
-Please, Jane. I want you to stay.
-This can only end bloody for me, Billy.
I saved the sign. You know the "yes" sign?
I pinned it on the wall in my locker.
Goddamn it!
It was stupid!
Strike three called.
On the corner.
-Strike!
-Fastball, got him looking.
That's strikeout number five
for Billy Chapel...
...and he is really on a roll now.
Franklin, obviously annoyed
at what he thinks is a bad call...
...is muttering as he goes up
the first base line.
Bill Murdie showing some patience,
but right back at him, ready to bite.
Here's that pitch again. It looked like
it was in the heart of the strike zone.
It's a little surprising
that Franklin was so annoyed.
And it looks like for Bill Murdie,
the pot is about ready to boil over.
A dominant inning for Billy Chapel,
striking out the side.
You're in the zone.
-Number 24.
-Feels good.
Here's Mickey Hart, 0 for 1.
No score, fourth inning.
Jack Spellman doing well.
Has allowed only two hits to the Tigers...
...and meanwhile,
Billy Chapel in perfect control.
Mickey'll be gone next year, too.
Poor guy. Never could get a break.
Where was that catch he missed?
The one that hit him?
They still play that on Diamond Vision
all the time....
"There goes another rubber tree plant."
Fenway.
Everything's all right, man.
Guess that looked pretty funny
out there today?
Probably end up on ESPN or something.
Lot of shit ends up on ESPN
I don't think is very funny, Mick.
Phone call, Mr. Chapel.
There's a bunch of cameras out there,
waiting to make a joke of this.
You can either stop,
give them the sound bite, do the dance...
...or you hold your head up and walk by,
and the next time we're in Boston...
...we'll go out there
and we'll work the wall together.
Don't help them make a joke out of you.
Old school, baby. He's right.
-Chapel.
-It's Jane.
I got your number from the front office.
-I hope that it's okay.
-No, that's all right.
Don't worry about it. What's wrong?
Something's happened.
It's my daughter. She ran away.
-Your daughter?
-I don't have time to tell you now.
But she's there in Boston.
Her father lives there.
-Oh, God. We had a fight and she--
-All right.
Jane, just slow down, all right?
Just slow down.
She climbed down the fire escape
and went to Penn Station...
...got on a train to go to her father,
but he's not there.
What's the address?
-8245 Clackton.
-What's her name?
-Freedom.
-Freedom?
Scared you, didn't l?
Heather. It's Heather.
It's okay.
I'm the guy your mom said
was coming to get you.
Let's get out of here before we get
our asses kicked twice in one night.
You're Heather.
And you're the baseball player.
My mom can do nothing normal.
Shut up.
Do you want something?
I'll have a V-8.
What is it with single men and V-8 Juice?
I mean, my dad's fridge has nothing
but mustard in it...
...but when I come to visit,
it has mustard...
...fish sticks, and this big jug of V-8 Juice.
Like, if he makes me choke down a glass,
he's being healthy and fatherly.
I like V-8. It's...
...nutritious.
Are you my mom's boyfriend?
I'm not sure.
But you've slept with her.
V-8. It's a refreshing blend of eight...
...vegetable juices.
What did you and your mother fight about?
I didn't come home from school
when I was supposed to...
...because I was with Mark Elton and...
...she freaked out because he has
facial hair and his parents are never home.
And I said, "We didn't do anything."
And she said, "You could have."
I said, "Well, I might love him."
And she said,
"You don't know what love is."
And I said,
"I'm gonna do what I want to do."
And she said, "Not in this house."
So I went to my dad's because...
...he doesn't care what I do...
...'cause he's stoned 90 percent of the time.
She doesn't...
...want me to make the same mistakes
that she did.
I mean, she had me when she was 16.
She never had...
...a love story.
And now she doesn't believe in it.
-Honey, I'm so sorry.
-I'm sorry, too.
Thank you.
Come up.
-Don't ever do that again, okay?
-Okay.
We can always work it out, all right?
Just talk to me.