THE SUM OF ALL THE FEARS
In 1973 Egypt and Syria sent to an attack surprise against Israel.
For the day the 2 forces of Israel was.
In the point to defeat.
In the event in which their ground forceses were destroyed…
Israeli A4 jet I seize of the patrols…
with a nuclear pump
29 years later
This safe one that they are the Russians?
One hundred percent Sir
15 Lanzaron mega tons, every 15 minutes
in Rosevelt we have…
missiles, in Russia also but is
no sufficient personnel.
Sir we have another attack,
is time of the center.
Incredible. What have alla '?
S.A.T. and C.B.M. for the night.
- the probable targets are New York,
Washington, here.
so good What is east ceiling?
Any thing, that is not direct.
Sir is confirmed Bird is in the air,
multiple attacks.
- the first impact esteem that will be
in twenty-five minutes.
Comó we know that he is exact?
He is exact.
Sir I recommend that we go to Def com one.
Who is working in the hot line?
Malcon is not so tendre the reports of the reports of Moscu.
the general is the one that is issuing the orders.
What devils are doing?
The imbecil queria to experiment.
Sir to def com is finishing the time to him.
Háganlo.
Sir president is going to take
a minute before the sequence.
of launching processes depués
of which of the order.
before the order is taken a
revision from the identification
My I number is above.
Sir is its wife.
- Thanks.
If
- Another person of the list of.
approved must approve the order Excrement!
serves the advice to
them as the national security.
Is black?
I already go for there.
We can finish this at another moment?
No.
Mira those ventilators if something gets
to happen not I am going to put.
- there, it is a damn tomb there down.
Also tendre that to choose
to somebody to speak with the Germans.
Really? Let us see we have to
27 thousand threats
of nuclear pumps to worry to us.
Is the type that has it
is the one that worries to me.
speaking of Russia I must send
to somebody to investigate there.
- the facilities of nuclear weapons.
Somebody of its personnel must be in the trip.
I ire.
Envia your personnel.
No, I want to go.
In agreement.
does not underestimate to Zuvalcompel
between its economy, the crime, its liver.
- what it is of him.
Adjustment an appointment for the press.
- it is late we know at least
that it is possible to be stopped.
HEADQUARTERS COMPANY LANGLEY, GOES
You see what I see?
the jacket. - If it even has it buttoned.
- above it is being fattened.
I as one feels.
Miren that.
- Perhaps it is not the same jacket.
No.
- She is not definitively the one that use for the hospital.
Is definitively outside diet.
- Also it is outside the wagon.
- they listened to as it said, vasityvuga?
- That must be the reason by which?
?
- Tawinsky stays with him to help it.
Dondé is Tawinsky?
- Behind? as she is called, the girl?
of the hair cafe?
- Elena Rinsko
No, that is not Tawinsky.
takes hold to You is Tawinsky.
- No, your you are thinking about Chapisky.
I am not it.
- it is not Chapisky Either.
I know It, is Tawinsky.
- I know It, créeme.
Mira is stopped next to
Elena Rinsko acosto with her '?
- in Geniva.
- Tawinsky was not in Geniva.
Chapisky was in Geniva.
- What this saying that Tawinsky..
- it was having relations with Elena?
the only thing that I am saying
is that it is not because they must relate it.
- with sex?
- I agree, escribanlo..
- and if Zuvalcampel this raising
of weight that can bring consequences
- in its health ponganlo in the report of afternoon.
Somebody averigue that is lying down with Elena,
this is good.
VIENNA, AUSTRIA
Ellá requests protection is like a beautiful virgin,
escaping stops.
to save to its district.
- Know the old heads?
- a poet escribio about us those of century 21..
- by than 50 years America and Russia imposing more its war.
- before the European Community,
they even treat to us like children.
- every time we lose a little more our ability and to have of.
- to make the decisions, for our future.
- and every day the war this
a little more near that terrible moment.
- in which the wings of the butterfly
untie a hurricane, that nor.
- God podra to stop.
What is?
These blind person?
- It is a pump.
Where is fuss?
This hot one.
Vamos I do not have all the night.
Is a pump that does not explode.
Pongamosla in the truck.
Comó we are going it to sell?
Always is somebody buys it.
I cannot support all these questions about my health.
robust "and" healthful "Voy to be described like".
Is yours or mio?
Is yours, I did not bring mio.
is not of the hospital.
- Very well.
Even these aqui.
- I must be exact in everything.
- in fact you are your who you are even aqui.
is not that me this complaining.
Jack I that this it is not the moment but.
- I have something I must say or I am going to explode,
is single that I do not want.
- that you are scared.
That?
These enamored with my.
Jack I am a doctor I can read sintomas,
definitively these.
- enamored with my.
and that scares to you?
- Nor just a little bit.
Olvidalo.
- It was extinguished.
Not that is but.
At very badly moment.
- Beam which you must do.
Moller, you called to me?
Detente.
- If jack speaks
God mio, in agreement estare there in half an hour.
Tengo to go to me,
I have an emergency in the work.
I must go to me, I feel it.
we had supper tonight?
- If.
That so tomorrow at night?
- Jack I said tonight that if.
.
What class of emergency has a historian?
Murio to 4:22 eight hours and average
later named a new one.
president, everybody wants to know that is.
Who is?
- Alexander Nemorah.
These joking escribi a paper about for a year.
- I claimed that podria to be president.
Nobody leyo.
- They estan It reading now.
Who?
- Howard.
I have been aqui fourteen months not even knows as I am.
Are you Ryan?
- If Sir.
What is a this persecution of paper?
Was in.
Apurese we go late.
Escuchame is going to you to request
analysis and advice, so it is better than.
- you know that these speaking before
saying it, you are not scared of.
- to say that you do not know,
escoje well your words, the words must
- the custom to become in policy, you hear deme his.
- jacket, we go we will return it.
the necktie.
Well.
Is comite of intelligence?
- No.
I have seen these but never I have been.
Never time one of these.
Our more valuable information comes
from a source in its government
- In its Nemorah opinion to not it
must its ascent him to I exercise.
All has opinions, Mr. Cabit.
I respect that, this morning my wife I
rise and she said to me that.
- I was old, bald and ugly.
Is a question?
I said to Him that the appearances are not everything.
- This in agreement Mr. Cabit?
Certainly.
- Now that type Alexander Nemorah
- it is that his name?
In spite of which it says its source
of intelligence Nemorah is.
- intransigente.
- A intransigente? - No.
Is in a moment for making that information.
According to Cnn its Nemorah this.
- making promises reconstruct
- the Russian empire,
that is heard very threatening from where I am
- seated.
- If it were more in worried estaria Chesnia.
Sir if we left quiet Russia it stabilized and.
When pedi its advice I did not mean that
tapeworm that to speak.
If Sir.
- Mr. Cabit.
Mr. Cherman some of the people who we
know the government
- Russian I have not been possible to
report would like to have more time.
- to collect more data for you,
before jeopardizing it.
but I maintain my opinion that
the appearances can be.
- engañadoras.
- This saying that I am mistaken?
Absolutely Mr. Chapman.
I do not believe that he is ugly.
happens to Me of the ray I feel it.
- To the senator it does not like.
- surprises I was saying to them,
but he is better to hope.
I understand It.
- Well.
Law about Nemorah.
To your fiancèe it likes to be aqui?
That?
Cathi Miller, second year in the Memorial hospital.
Welcome to the company.
Its intelligence has failed in is
subject not llamaria it my fiancèe, even.
Like the llamaria exactly?
- Huge, fantastica..
- he is single that gives fear him to commit itself.
scares the commitment.
- a man scares the commitment
- after three days, they alert to means.
. - What does?
Trabajaba in navy before the back is hurt, now?
- he is a historian.
- Delicious.
No, works for a company crossing rio.
Double delicious.
Vamos to see that you must to
say after which knows tonight.
Is pretty, has big toes. - Cathy.
In scale of pretty from the 1 to the 10.
- God mio.
Not it?
?
- Twelve.
Pregunteles where they found this.
In the field.
Was a war back in 1973.
says that it lost its son
Recuerda if there were some derived airplane?
If destroyed an Israel airplane.
is not worth anything.
Digale that him dare four hundred reason
why him passage to its son.
Thanks.
DAMACUS, SYRIA
Encontre which looks for.
- I ask for 50 million dollars.
Of 1973 done in Israel,
type-12 pump fission.
Alo Cathy.
- Hello thank heavens you called I am.
- a little slow, you can come in half an hour.
I cannot arrive, I feel much.
Was a thing of last minute.
What is that noise?
I am calling of an airplane,
this I am myself deals with llamarte al..
- hospital.
- To where you go?
I cannot say that to you.
- You cannot say to me to where you go?
Jack.
Espera a little while.
- Sir.
- to call to cancel.
- You are not estupido dile for where.
you go, in fact dile for that you work,
is going to be made an impression.
In agreement work for the company
and the director me pidio that came
- with him to Russia to inspect of nuclear weapons.
Alo.
- That is so low.
Cathy you the right of perpetual
ownership is truth we must inspect.
Alo!
Thanks, thank you very much.
President Nemorah?
Is a pleasure.
Sir President.
- General Ryan.
Sir president.
- doctor Ryan.
You must be doctor Ryan
who has made investigations.
- interesting about my.
deberia not to be surprised by this.
In fact we know that escribio
in its report that I had many fiancèes.
- in the University.
Conoci to my wife in the third year
and I have not known another woman.
Where recibio honors.
pleases to Me.
In that case I also.
First that everything dejeme to excuse
to me to take part in the inspection.
- but there is a message that desire
that takes to the president.
had called It.
I would like that she listens to it of.
- you have been your friend by many years, who saw.
- expression of my body and my face while I say it.
Comprendo.
Chesnia is an internal subject,
which we make deberia there not matter to them.
Hay some in my country that would
use this subject to work with me.
Hay some in my country that
dirian that its war in Chesnia is.
- exactly its weakness.
Chesnia is a nation of criminals,
every day attack innocents
citizen Russians,
is not of its interest.
the stability is our interest.
La Paz in Chesnia is our interest
and if I can speak frankly its control
on I exercise is.
- our interest also.
So that you they envolucren aqui
is like sleeping with the wife of.
- another man.
and what you are suggesting you are
that after that we live all.
- under the same ceiling.
But what truely it happens
is that the betrayed husband.
- it does not accept it.
That was well.
Who is Danober?
Nobody has had the nutgalls.
of desacer itself of.
They have found the bodies?
No, because probably it buried the same one.
Aqui is the list that is the one
who and as they are its specialties.
Institute of Russian scientific researches and is.
- birthplace of our first atomica pump.
Great scientists has worked aqui
and many even do it.
Tratan as much to enter here.
I envie three people.
All died trying.
What says the t-shirt?
I am a technician in pumps,
if they see me running try to reach to me.
Sigamos.
Sir I feel it is something small
is not nothing, according to this must.
- to have 17 people working today.
Single conte 14.
doctors Milanov,
Oloff and Vasket does not estan here.
Hare the investigations.
- doctor Milanov is ill.
- Oloff this of vacations and Vasket
moan to say to him that it was assassinated
- while it handled, the last week.
We can continue?
Please.
Very impressive nonwise that
had all that information.
Wise that would ask, doctor Ryan.
HAIFA, ISRAEL
Digale that we see ourselves later.
- Sir.
the three scientists,
the specialty of Milanov is the detonators.
the specialty of Vasket is the
cables and Oloff is a mathematician.
- specialized in the geometrica of
high explosives within one.
- pump Fission.
- Exactly the men who.
- they necesitarian to construct a pump.
Rushcoff thinks that.
- Rushcoff is a mentiroso, Milanov
- he is not ill,
Oloff has not taken vacations in years and Vasket..
- that supposedly dies handling its car,
does not handle.
does not have idea of where they are these types.
I die to ask to him.
- As that knows?
a security source, gives to things I
to me I give things, we maintain him
- the channels of atras opened
to try to avoid the disaster.
Speaking of disasters already
I call to its fiancèe?
No, I am thinking as I am going
away to unearth of this.
Escucha llamala and invitala
the supper in the white house the sabado one in.
- the night, is tiquete hotter of the city,
is going to him to enchant.
brilliant Suena.
- As I enter? - Confia in my.
vere in the car.
It was liking the work desktop?
If I am it.
- It must go to Russia.
So that?
- Three nuclear scientists are?
? - lost, I need to know where they are.
Pense that no longer was going to do this.
- I need information this time.
the airplane waits for it,
that it has good trip.
- sabado at night the Hilton hotel
the tickets you would estaran under the name
- of John Lark.
- It has clothes?
If Sir.
My beautiful Julie wife,
is of New Yersey, fifteen votes.
As they know half is Judios,
we took the twenty votes from Florida
- and we divided them in two.
Perhaps after the supper we can, not it?
- to make reservations.
Already I did it.
When I was in the war of Vietnam
in several occasions smokes marijuana
Californian 54 votes.
Approximately to the
zero six hundred Moscu realized
- that the Russians habian sent
missiles against Grosnia..
- the capital of Chesnia.
the projectiles contains
an experimental chemistry, which later.
- of twenty minutes all the men and
children around 12 miles.
- they presented/displayed
sintomas of cerebral paralisis.
God mio.
Whichever deaths?
Creemos that 80%.
What means that Nemorah finishes
mounting the most massive attack.
- in the history of the chemical war
We speak of the answer.
the worse thing than we can do is nothing.
- I agree, if we left it.
- to send chemical arms.
- That it follows? - Biologicas, nuclear.
In agreement, as is the answer
more hard than we can send.
Mandamos to the pacificadores.
- That does not solve anything.
Well, they asked for recognition, so.
- we recognize, nonrecognition diplomaticamente,
recognition.
- provisional,
soon we cause that the Ches request emergency aid to us.
- national and we sent pacificadores.
- As we entered them?
the fastest form would be to send them from Turkey.
On airspace Arminy.
- To the devil with Russia, they no..
- they are going away to complain.
Hagamoslo.
Doctor Ryan who thinks?
Sir president sabiduria
conventional suggests Nemorah
- the Russian traditional paper
is playing, the aggressive ones desafian al..
- world so that it stops them,
but Nemorah is not conventional.
walks like a intransigente,
speaks like intransigente..
If but yet respect not that is one.
Acaba of destriur the capital of a country,
its respect is single yet.
What so if Nemorah did not order the attack?
- that so if he were a general,
or a unit of I exercise frustada by.
- that could not remove the rest
from the rebels outside the city.
Tiene some reason to think that I
do not order it or is guessing?
you do not know it.
I do not believe that it has done it, Sir.
- Apostaria that did not do it.
That its personnel retires please by a minute.
president Alexander Nemorah is going to go to the town.
Disculpe Sir, can raise to him.
Finally each nation has the right of defenderse..
- the terrorism must finish,
the pump of Chesnia was my decision.
Therefore becomes.
general Phildyan Mitkin copied old Communists.
Bastard.
Sueltenlos- - the mataria i myself.
Single desaparecelos.
- It's execution would not be good.
Since our Russian friend
with this has been affected?
I am not affected,
I remain devotee to our small plan.
I am not surprised.
and the American?
- She is a believer, I put to him little.
- more than money in the account.
- So that '?
So that vivira the sufficient
thing not to receive it.
Where is the package?
- envio of Taifo for one week.
says to Me that these things
can kill to me.
I do not believe that this is good,
have changed so many things.
Perhaps the new situation
suggests we use a different approach.
to perhaps try to bring to Russia
a little more to Europe, a little more a..
- our form to think
Already we have discussed that,
and has been rejected.
Perhaps we exceeded, perhaps our plan is.
Is that?
Not perfectly conceived.
These crazy person?
- Around the world, all.
- the nations we are united European,
Russian Nazis, Aryan.
- all working together.
- Is not that a perfect plan?
I respect the decision of my friends
but in these two weeks I have myself.
- returned incomodo, with this plan,
so I must request to them by my exit.
Perhaps we help him to leave.
BALTIMORE, MARYLAND
Tengan taken care of with that thing,
is going to kill somebody.
Hello Mase.
Always I wanted to ask to him where
they did that tattoo to him.
In Navy.
- I was in the Basket, works.
- in the hospital by six years.
Eight months care.
Is or brother, who you pass it or.
hare.
the package has arrived.
the attack in Chesnia..
Our forces estan in way to Chesnia,
to serve like.
- pacificantes for aids to victimas
of this monstrous attack.
I waited for that.
- Really?
What you go to do?
- Nothing.
we will not do anything.
These has four hours
- they have not moved.
So that they have not moved?
- Nemorah is very intelligent stops.
- to move those tanks.
- The speech.
Jack watches, Nemorah has as
19 thousand tanks there is no form of that.
- they can compete with that.
- For that reason one is not going away them to move.
Is like playing the chess,
this moving three pieces, knows.
- that has many more tanks
than we and it knows that.
- the only form that we must to stop
is using it nuclear weapons
and does not want to risk a nuclear war by this.
Creo that is sending us a message.
the nonbombing to Roxny.
Arzamas-16 RUSSIA
Disculpe.
I am looking for Mrs. Spassky.
- At the end of the runner.
I have not seen Sasha from the university.
You were your assistant of education,
that strange not it memory.
I listen that she was in
Arzamas and me pidio that came.
says that it took me to the West.
That requires of much money.
Single because the imbeciles of do not pay to him here,
does not mean that.
- others you would not haran it.
has a secret work.
For the government?
Imbeciles with money.
One idiotes, you do this, you do not do this.
Until dijieron to him that it did not call to its mother.
Pigs.
Could die at any time and I could not call to its mother.
But my Sasham I am called.
- Last night.
Clark I find out number to us N.S.A.
could obtain all the numbers
- of the calls that entered and they tracked it here,
it is a base.
- of I exercise left Sovietico.
What estan making three atomicos
scientists Russian in Ukrana?
Creo that is constructing a pump.
- Nemorah has thousands of pumps.
So that it needs to do privily?
Negamiento
Construye one of which nobody knows
it can take to Chesnia in.
- the suitcase of its car,
would not be form to track it.
Could send it and say that it did not do it.
its respect Sir I do not believe
Yet that that has sense.
If it has sense.
Is single that you do not like the sense that she has.
Ah, the calidez of the disturbed Plutonium.
completely is disturbed,
you at least have the put gloves.
Quieren to smoke an American cigarette?
These crazy person?
Voy to leave.
Tenemos a pump?
If.
If we have it.
This is an examination.
- If.
Contesta.
- these safe?
Alo.
If.
If Sir.
Tengo to outside go by a minute already return.
Already return.
Sir I write reports.
- Law your military registries.
- Jack you can cuidarte.
- If Sir, but I am not.
- trained for that.
- I am not requesting to him that is.
- an operations officer, single my oidos eyes and.
- I cannot go.
That I must do?
Quiero that him of this to Clark,
to see that he can find out, traelo..
- to house
If Sir.
Jack.
Never we had is conversation.
Which conversation?
KREMENCHUNG RESERVOIR, UKRANIA
Well, this has been for three days.
- Sample vehicles here, guards here and here.
the satellite was On guard the twenty-four hours, shows.
- guards here and here.
- I need to make my task.
Hay two more in the point of revision
between two and three in barricks..
- and two with the package,
which we think that they estan here.
is no problem with tranquilizers we will leave in.
- six minutes.
In fact is a problem.
- Which?
This was yesterday, are no guards.
and so that a problem is that?
For two reasons, or we cannot see them
what is bad or worse.
- they were and we arrived late.
Vistete.
That '? - You cannot go dress thus.
No, I am not an analyst,
I I do not go to missions.
Double Relajate 007 is not a
mission is single an investigation.
Well, like is that I call I do not do that,
single I write reports.
In agreement writes a report about it, vistete.
Clark no. - Clark.
No.
told Me that you were in the
supper of the white house.
you passed it well?
Clark, Who '? - No
I am not going to enter.
- I that not quedate here and.
- asegurate of which nobody robs my boat.
Already return.
God mio.
God mio, did not call immigration?
I feel It, English speech?
- I do not speak Ucraniano.
I that this is not seen well but
am myself an American I have my?
- papers here.
In agreement noncoat the papers.
Please single lowers the weapon.
the light?
- They want that it lowers the light?
Either, or, calmense lowers the light.