Pretty windy out.
-That better not be the violent one.
-It's not, Mom.
Dad, look what I can do.
I've been practicing.
-Spectacular, kiddo.
-Cool.
You're inside out.
I knew that.
Doesn't work for you?
I can't believe you taught him that.
I didn't. He did it on his own.
-Charlie, did you brush your teeth?
-Yes.
-Charlie.
-I brushed them.
-Look at this, Con.
-Let's go. I'm serious.
You're driving me bonkers, Mom.
Remember when you said no
to buying Omnidell?
-Remember what the price was?
-One fifty.
Close. Sixty-one.
-I'll do it, Mom.
-No, I'll do it.
You know what it's going for now?
-Say "E. "
-E.
-Guess, Con.
-Edward, I don't know, all right?
-Now rinse.
-Seventy-four.
Really rinse. And pee.
Seventy-four. Should have bought it.
Shit.
-So buy some.
-Too late, Con. Too late.
Lift the seat, honey.
Don't forget to put it down.
When you finish.
-Do you really need all that stuff?
-Mom, no one wears these dorky hats.
-You do and you're not a dork.
-How do I look?
Very handsome.
Love you.
Okay, come on, let's go.
Come on.
You shouldn't go in.
I have stuff to do for the auction.
And there's a birthday soon.
Latrell Sprewell jersey, Mom.
Don't forget.
-He's on the Yankees, right?
-Mom, you're driving me bonkers.
You're driving him bonkers.
Jesus.
Taxi! Shit.
Taxi!
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'll get your things.
Taxi! Taxi!
My books.
-Could you help me get a taxi?
-Okay.
-I'll watch your books.
-Thanks.
-Bad day for taxis.
-It's this horrible wind.
Yeah, you shot down there
like a bullet!
If you flapped your arms,
you'd be home now.
I'll remember that next time.
-That's not good.
-I know.
Listen, that's me up there.
The flowerpot.
I'll get you a Band-Aid, okay?
Hold onto something.
Don't blow away.
Or you can come on up
and clean it off, no?
Come on.
I'm not an ax murderer. I promise.
Shit.
Fucking elevator.
One more.
-Pardon the mess.
-Are you a writer?
I'm a book dealer.
Bathroom's right down there,
on the left.
Go ahead. There's a medicine cabinet.
You can sneak a peek
at my prescriptions.
Hello?
-I made you some tea.
-Thank you.
-Do you box?
-I used to, when I was young.
This is an amazing place.
-Yeah, but it's not mine.
-No?
The owner is a friend, a sculptor.
He's in Paris.
That's cool.
We can stay here, me and my books.
Can I use your phone?
I have to call home.
Sure, there's a phone just behind you.
Thank you.
Gloria? Hi, it's me.
Good, good. How's Charlie?
Hi, honey. How was your day at school?
Yeah? What was the best part?
Guess what? Can you believe it?
Mommy missed her train.
Ice.
About an hour.
You should start your homework.
I promise to tell you all about it
when I see you. I love you. Bye.
That was my son, Charlie.
He's 8. He'll be 9 next week.
I'm Paul Martel. I'll be 28 in July.
I'm Constance.
And I'm late. I have to go.
Before you go, take a book.
No. I couldn't.
Sure you can. A souvenir.
Go down there. You know, like before.
Okay.
Keep going. Stop.
Now right.
No, right.
Okay, now the second shelf
from the top. . .
. . .take the fourth one from the left.
Got it?
-Think so.
-Open to page 23.
Drink wine, this is life eternal
This, all that youth will give to you
It is the season for wine, roses
And drunken friends
Be happy for this moment
This moment is your life
I have to go. Thank you.
-Can you find your way out?
-I hope so.
That's my bedroom.
It was nice meeting you, Constance.
Come back if you need more books
or medical attention.
Hey, Glo.
-That wouldn't be the TV on, would it?
-I was just turning it off.
Sure you were.
-The wind knocked me down.
-Yeah?
You all right? You need anything?
-Gross. Were you in a fight?
-No, just fell over.
-Does it hurt?
-Little bit.
-Cool!
-Where are you going?
-To get the camera!
-Try this.
-Why do you need the camera?
-It's for school. We're doing blood.
Okay, now look like it really hurts.
-Ready?
-Yeah.
This will be great.
The wind blew her down.
She bled and everything.
-Everybody's hats blew off.
-Quite the war photographer. You okay?
Yeah. It took me down
like an old lady.
-It was humiliating.
-Dad, look at the pictures.
At least we got the evidence.
Anyone we can sue?
No. There was this nice guy
who helped me.
It was like this, Dad.
It was a twister.
Dad, look. It was like this.
-Wow.
-It's a tornado.
He lived around there. He got me
some Band-Aids and put me in a taxi.
Was he good-looking?
I feel sick.
-You do your homework?
-I can't. I don't know how to do it.
Come on, I'll help you.
Then you can help me with mine.
Did you get his name, this guy?
We could send him a bottle of wine.
Cheap wine.
Con, stand there a second.
Wait a minute.
Stay there a second.
I'm trying to figure out the. . . .
The thing I can't figure out
is the zoom-thing.
There it is.
Okay, hold on, stay there.
Got the zoomy-thingy zooming.
Stay there. I'm trying to figure
this out. I wanna see if it focuses.
Cool. Very cool.
So beautiful. If you only knew.
Look at you. God, what a beauty.
Something the matter?
Nothing. Nothing at all.
-This is really good.
-No, it isn't. Go away.
I think I'm really zooming.
I found the zoom. Found it.
Dad.
-Shit.
-Mom.
I can't sleep.
I'll be back. I'll be back.
Don't fall asleep.
It works.
Mom, are you nuts?
You forgot my lunch.
I did not. It's by the door.
Come with me.
-What are you chewing?
-Nothing.
Spit that out. What is that?
-That's lovely.
-Mom?
I don't want to be a dumb bunny.
Honey, it's a play. There's lots
of other bunnies. It'll be cool.
-You're bonkers, Mom.
-So you tell me.
-Love you.
-Love you too. What's that?
Thank you.
Bye.
Hi, this is Paul Martel. Leave
a message after the beep. Thanks.
Hello? Hello?
-Hello?
You're there.
This is Connie Sumner,
the one from the windy day.
Oh, that one.
How's the knee? Did you ice it?
Yes, I iced it and I elevated it.
You name it, I did it.
It's much better.
I just wanted to call and thank you.
I wanted your address
because I wanted...
-Where are you?
-What?
I said, where are you?
I'm in Grand Central.
It's really hard to hear you.
-Come and see me.
-What?
Yeah, take a break.
I'll make you some coffee.
Coffee?
-Okay.
See you. Bye.
Fuck.
No permanent damage, I see.
-We take Medicaid, Blue Cross. . . .
-I'm uninsured.
No. I'm afraid we don't
take charity cases.
It was a joke.
Look at this. Jack London.
First edition of White Fang,
in the original dust jacket.
And I got it for a buck fifty.
-What's it worth?
-About 4000 times more.
-Those are in French.
-I took it in school.
Do I want to take off something?
Your coat. Would you like
to take off your coat?
Yes, my coat.
Thank you.
But I can't stay very long.
I have some errands I have to run.
-I'll get the coffee.
-Okay.
-It's in Braille.
-Braille.
No, no, Braille.
He was French.
Close your eyes.
-What?
-Close your eyes.
My mother makes me chicken
Her chicken makes me cough
I wish that when she made it
She took the feathers off
It doesn't say that.
-I had better go.
-Yeah?
I'd better go.
Take care. Don't fall.
-Thanks for the coffee.
-You didn't drink it.
-Lindsay, hi.
-Connie.
-Let me buzz him.
-Thanks.
Hey, what a surprise. Look at you.
-Hi, Bill.
-Hi, Connie.
-Am I interrupting?
-No, I'm leaving.
-I'll get you the budget later.
-All right, thanks.
-Would you like a coffee?
-No, thank you.
That's nice.
I didn't know
you were coming in today.
You're freezing.
What is that?
I was around the corner
and I brought you a present.
Wow. What's the occasion?
Nothing. I don't know.
It's a medium,
but they said it runs large.
-Look at that.
-You don't have to try it on.
I'm the boss.
I can do whatever I want.
What do you think?
Hold on just a second.
Yeah?
Okay, but hold the other calls.
-You're busy. I'll go.
-Sit.
-I'll go.
-No, sit.
Hello, Henry?
So, what is this suspension problem?
No, I never received it.
Well, get it to me.
It's not good enough. I'm sitting here
with 200 trucks I can't use.
Well, set up a meeting.
And I want Frank Birnbaum there.
Because when I tell someone
to do something, I want it done.
I'm sure you will.
So, what else you up to?
-Auction.
-Yeah? Who'd you hit on?
The usual suspects.
Who?
-Bob Gaylord.
-Bob?
Get Bob to pledge and they should
send you to the Middle East.
So tell me.
What?
What do you think?
It's a keeper.
-Hello.
Here I am again. I brought muffins.
-What is this music?
-Do you like it?
Yes.
Do you want to dance?
-Now?
-Yeah.
Okay.
-I have to warn you, I tend to lead.
-Of course. You are American.
-You've done this before.
-What?
How many girlfriends have you had?
Two.
-Really?
-Would I lie to you?
I don't know. Would you?
Your eyes are amazing. You should
never shut them, not even at night.
You should learn to sleep
with your eyes open.
-I'll work on that.
-Will you?
Hang on.
I think this is a mistake.
There are no mistakes. There's what
you do, and what you don't do.
I can't do this.
Forgot my coat.
-I can't.
-What?
What's wrong?
I don't know how to do this.
It's wrong.
-Hit me.
-What?
Hit me.
-Hey, Ed.
-Hey, Bob.
-Haven't seen you in a while.
-No.
-I've been working late this week.
-Really? How's the boy?
-It's his birthday.
-How old?
Nine.
So any major armed robberies?
No. No, not this week.
Speaking of which,
watch out for Connie.
-She'll have you sign over your mortgage.
-What?
-Did she try to hit on you for money?
-No.
I thought she talked to you about
this school auction, or whatever.
Not me.
I've been out of town.
Maybe she talked to Maggie.
Yeah, I guess I got it wrong.
Anyway, we owe you a dinner.
Yeah.
He's out.
Can I get you anything?
No. No, I'm fine, thanks.
-Tough day?
-No, not really.
What about you? How was your day?
It was good.
You know, the usual stuff.
Sure you don't want anything?
No.
-Con?
-Yeah?
Do you love me?
Of course I love you.
What a silly question.
I guess. . .
. . .I'm just feeling silly.
I'll be up in a minute.
Okay.
Oh, sorry.
What are we doing here?
Having lunch.
-I shouldn't be doing this.
-You shouldn't have lunch?
Not with you.
I think we should leave.
Listen.
See those guys over there
paying the check?
-Yes.
-Okay. If the guy on the right pays. . .
. . .we leave right now.
If the guy on the left pays. . .
. . .we stay.
And I kiss you.
No.
Give me that.
I win.
-No.
-C'est la vie.
Don't do it. Don't.
-Room for two?
-Of course.
Nice music. What is it?
It's. . .
. . .African, I think.
I like it.
Here.
Let's go to bed.
-Come on.
-Stay here with me.
-I'm cold.
-Stay.
-Stay here with me.
-I'm cold.
Let's go.
How about lunch today?
You free?
I have all this fundraiser stuff.
Auction things to pick up.
We can do an early one if you want.
How about 1 2:00?
1 2:00?
Yeah.
Will I be hungry at 1 2:00?
We could go in together.
I'll wait for you.
-I won't be ready for another hour.
-That's all right. I'll wait.
-Oh, shit.
-What?
I just remembered. . .
. . .I have a facial at 1 2:30
at Georgianna's today.
Oh, well.
You gotta stay beautiful, right?
Georgianna's, huh?
Waste of money.
Yeah, Manhattan.
A beauty salon called Georgina.
Oh, yeah, right. Yes, Georgianna's.
That's right.
Thank you.
Hello, I'm calling to confirm
an appointment today at 1 2:30.
Sumner. Connie Sumner.
S-U-M-N-E-R.
Could she be down for another time?
No, thank you.
Connie?
It's Connie.
Tracy?
-Hi. I was gonna call you.
-They all say that. . .
. . .when I call about bunny costumes.
You know Sally from Planned Parenthood.
-Hi. It's been a while.
-Too long.
-You look amazing.
-So where you headed?
I was going to look for some
window shades for the kitchen.
We're gonna go and have coffee.
Why don't you join us?
-Oh, I'm gonna be late.
-For window shades?
-Come on.
-Okay.
Hi, how are you?
I'm just gonna make a phone call.
-Sure.
-Let me get that for you.
-She could've used my cell phone.
-Oh, you're right.
Hi, it's me.
You won't believe this.
I'm at that café around the corner.
Why do you introduce me
as Sally from Planned Parenthood?
It makes it sound like
I'm handing out condoms.
I'm stuck here.
Will you wait for me?
Wait for me.
I called Gloria to remind her
to pick up the dry cleaning.
Charlie is so adorable.
Thank you.
I can't eat.
-I'll have a coffee.
-Well, I guess I'll have coffee too.
Excuse me again. Ladies' room.
God, she looks good.
-You think she's had work?
-Why would she? She's still gorgeous.
They do it early now
before it goes to shit.
I have friends out there.
You take me to the best places.
Let me.
-She's not like that. She's really nice.
-Of course she is.
That makes it worse.
She's nice and she's sweet.
And her ass is in exactly
the same place it was in college.
Are you taking tennis?
Oh, I wouldn't call what I do
"taking tennis. "
-There you are. I was starting to worry.
-No, I'm fine.
We thought that heartthrob
abducted you.
What heartthrob?
You didn't see him at the counter?
He was gorgeous.
-I miss everything.
-Your button's undone.
Oh. Thank you.
That's him.
I can see the appeal.
If he looked at me twice,
I'd be on my back.
-You would not.
-I would so. Why not?
A couple of reasons:
Adam and your kids.
You know, Trace,
they wouldn't have to know.
It could be something I did for myself,
to broaden my horizons.
Like taking a pottery class.
-An affair isn't like taking pottery.
-Could be.
It would start out like that.
Then something would happen. . .
. . .someone finds out or someone
falls in love and it ends disastrously.
They always end disastrously.
No.
When?
It was a long time ago.
And it's the one thing in my life
I would undo if I could.
Did you just fuck me
across the street?
I did.
We could end this now
and no one would get hurt.
Yeah. I think if we ended this now,
I'd get hurt.
-So no matter what, someone gets hurt?
-Maybe not.
Maybe we'll get tired of each other.
God, I hope I get tired of you.
You're in my mind.
You're the only thing in my mind
when I wake up every morning.
You're in my brain
before I even open my eyes.
-What do you think of?
-That depends.
If it's a day when I don't know if I'm
gonna get to see you, I'm anxious. . .
. . .thinking of excuses to come to
the city to see you.
And the days you know we'll meet?
On those days. . .
. . .I'm. . .
. . .calm and hating myself.
This is what we have over here.
I'll have it ready for you
this afternoon.
Ed, what's up? Sounded important.
I've heard you're talking with
Dunbar and Brinks and other companies.
Where did you hear that?
Well, look.
I suppose they could be wooing me,
if that's what you mean.
Apparently a lot of people
are wooing you. Or who's wooing who?
What are you talking about?
So I talked to some people.
-So what?
-This is about loyalty, Bill.
I'm letting you go. You'll have
my recommendation if you need it.
I have a family, Ed.
You had a family here.
No, wait a minute.
You're telling me about family?
You don't know the first
goddamn thing about it.
Look at your own fucking family, Ed.
Take a goddamn look at that.
-Ed.
-Frank.
Thanks for coming on such short notice.
This is personal, it's not business.
Think about it.
You might not want to get involved.
But I need someone I can trust.
I want you to follow somebody.
I want you to follow my wife.