Only a white man would make
a fire for everyone to see.
Maybe there's more than one.
There might be three or four.
I know three or four who will not be
making the trip back home.
We have nothing to show
for this trail.
We have no rifles.
White men
are sure to have rifles.
It's hard to say how many
might be down there.
We should forget this
and go home.
Then go.
I would rather die...
than argue about a single line
of smoke in my own country.
He will not quit
until we are all dead.
I do not care for this talk
about a white man.
Whatever he is, he is not Sioux
and that makes him less.
When I hear that more whites
are coming, I want to laugh.
We took a hundred horses
from these people.
There was no honor in it.
They don't ride well.
They don't shoot well.
They're dirty.
Those soldiers could not even
make it through one winter here.
And these people
are said to flourish?
I think they will
all be dead soon.
I think this fool
is probably lost.
Wind In His Hair's words are
strong and I have heard them.
It's true the whites are
a poor race and hard to understand.
But make no mistake.
The whites are coming.
Even our enemies agree on this.
So when I see one man alone
without fear in our country...
I do not think he is lost.
I think he may have medicine.
I see someone who might speak...
for all the white people
who are coming.
I think this is a person with
which treaties might be struck.
Kicking Bird is always
looking ahead and that is good.
But this man cannot cover
our lodges or feed our children.
He is nothing to us.
I will take some men.
We will shoot some arrows
into this white man.
If he truly has medicine,
he will not be hurt.
If he has no medicine,
he will be dead.
No man can tell another
what to do.
But killing a white man
is a delicate matter.
If you kill one,
more are sure to come.
It's easy to become confused
by these questions.
It's hard to know what to do.
We should talk about this
some more.
That is all I have to say.
We'll be heroes.
They'll write songs about us.
What happened?
I don't know.
My arm doesn't work.
You shouldn't have fallen off.
Now we'll get in trouble.
It was your idea.
My idea was only to take
the horse, not fall down.
Otter hurt himself.
What are you looking at?
I'm the one who's hurt.
I will be when my father finds out.
His bow will be across my back.
I am Wind In His Hair.
Do you see
that I am not afraid of you?
Do you see?
You are not welcome here.
Go away from us.
You are not welcome.
Stop.
The soldier did not come
to fight.
He is going away
and we will let him.
I am in agreement
with Kicking Bird.
We will go down and talk
to the white man.
And find out why he is here.
If this council decides to talk
to the white man...
then it will be so.
But in my mind
it's not right...
that a chief as great
as Ten Bears...
goes to ask the business of
a puny, trespassing white man...
who has only a smart horse
and a few white man's clothes.
I will not go.
You will go.
And you will go.
That is all I have to say.
His mind is gone.
Stands With A Fist.
We will talk awhile.
Your wounds are healing well?
Yes, they are.
You are happy here,
with my family?
I am glad to be here.
I am missing my husband.
Perhaps you will marry again
when the time is right?
Perhaps.
We have word from many places
that the whites are coming.
They are coming
into everyone's country.
I think they
will soon be in ours.
This white man who lives
at the old soldier fort...
I have visited him and I believe
his heart is a good one.
I am afraid of the white man
at the fort.
I am afraid he will tell others
that I am here.
I am afraid they will
try to take me away.
I've heard they
take people away.
Every warrior in camp
would fight them if they tried.
I cannot make
the white man language.
He cannot speak Sioux.
It has been a long time
since I made the talk.
I want you to try.
I don't know how.
Yes, you do.
I can't.
I can't. It's dead in me.
I don't ask this for myself.
I ask this for all the people.
He knows things about the whites
which we do not.
Now, you must remember.
I can't.
Will she make the white words?
She won't try.
She is being difficult.
Well, she's the one
who's crying.
Perhaps the difficulty is yours.
We were waiting for you.
Now tell him we are glad
that he is here.
Ask him why he is at
the soldier fort.
He's right.
Introductions should come first.