'Twas a long time ago,
longer now than it seems...
in a place that perhaps
you've seen in your dreams.
For the story that you
are about to be told...
took place
in the holiday worlds of old.
Now, you've probably wondered
where holidays come from.
If you haven't,
I'd say it's time you begun!
Boys and girls
of every age
Wouldn't you like to see
something strange
Come with us
and you will see
This our town
of Halloween
This is Halloween
Pumpkins scream
in the dead of night
This is Halloween
Everybody make a scene
Trick-or-treat till the
neighbor's gonna die of fright
It's our town
Everybody scream
In this town of Halloween
I am the one hiding
under your bed
Teeth ground sharp
and eyes glowing red
I am the one hiding
under your stairs
Fingers like snakes
and spiders in my hair
This is Halloween
Halloween, Halloween
In this town we call home
Everyone hail
to the pumpkin song
In this town
Don't we love it now
Everybody's waiting
for the next surprise
'Round that corner, man
Hiding in the trash can
- Something's waiting now
to pounce and how you'll
- Scream
- This is Halloween
- Red and black
- And slimy green
- Aren't you scared
- Well, that's just fine
Say it once, say it twice
Take a chance and roll the dice
Ride with the moon
in the dead of night
Everybody scream
In our town of Halloween
I am the clown
with a tear-away face
Here in a flash
and gone without a trace
I am the who
when you call who's there
I am the wind blowing
through your hair
I am the shadow
on the moon at night
Filling your dreams
to the brim with fright
This is Halloween
Halloween, Halloween
Tender lumplings everywhere
Life's no fun
without a good scare
- That's our job
- But we're not mean
In our town of Halloween
In this town
Don't we love it now
Everyone's waiting
for the next surprise
Skeleton Jack
might catch you in the back
And scream like a banshee
Make you jump out of your skin
This is Halloween
Everybody scream
Won't you please make way
for a very special guy
Our man Jack is king
of the pumpkin patch
Everyone hail
to the Pumpkin King now
This is Halloween
Halloween, Halloween
In this town we call home
Everyone hail
to the pumpkin song
- La, la, la, la, la, la
- Halloween, Halloween
La, la, la, la, la, la
Whee
- It's over!
- We did it!
- Wasn't it terrifying?
- What a night!
Great Halloween, everybody.
I believe it was our most horrible yet.
Thank you, everyone.
No! Thanks to you, Jack.
Without your
brilliant leadership--
- Not at all, Mayor.
- You're such a scream, Jack.
- You're a witch's fondest dream.
- You made walls fall, Jack.
Walls fall? You made
the very mountains crack, Jack.
- The deadly nightshade
you slipped me wore off, Sally.
- Let go!
- You're not ready
for so much excitement.
- Yes, I am!
- You're coming with me!
- No, I'm not!
Come back here, you foolish--
Oh! Oh! Oh-oh-oh.
Ooh, Jack, you made
wounds ooze and flesh crawl.
Thank you. Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Hold it. We haven't given out
the prizes yet.
Our first award
goes to the vampires...
for most blood drained
in a single evening.
Our second and
honorable mention...
goes to the fabulous
Dark Lagoon leeches.
Nice work, Bone Daddy.
Yeah, I guess so.
Just like last year...
and the year before that,
and the year before that.
There are few who deny
at what I do I am the best
For my talents
are renowned far and wide
When it comes to surprises
in the moonlit night
I excel without ever even trying
With the slightest little effort
Of my ghost-like charms
I have seen grown men
give out a shriek
With a wave of my hand
and a well-placed moan
I have swept the very bravest
off their feet
Yet year after year
It's the same routine
And I grow so weary
of the sound of screams
And l, Jack
the Pumpkin King
Have grown so tired
of the same old thing
Oh, somewhere deep
Inside of these bones
An emptiness
Began to grow
There's something out there
Far from my home
A longing that
I've never known
I'm the master of fright
And a demon of light
And I'll scare you
right out of your pants
To a guy in Kentucky
I'm Mr. Unlucky
And I'm known throughout
England and France
And since I am dead
I can take off my head
To recite Shakespearean quotations
No animal nor man
can scream like I can
With the fury
of my recitations
But who here
Would ever understand
That the Pumpkin King
with the skeleton grin
Would tire of his crown
lf they only understood
He'd give it all up
If he only could
Oh, there's an empty
Place in my bones
That calls out for
Something unknown
The fame and praise
Come year after year
Does nothing for
These empty tears
Jack.
I know how you feel.
Sally!
You've come back.
- I had to.
- For this!
- Yes.
- Shall we, then?
That's twice this month
you've slipped deadly nightshade
into my tea and run off.
- Three times.
- You're mine, you know!
I made you with my own hands.
You can make other creations.
I'm restless. I can't help it.
It's a phase, my dear. It'll pass.
We need to be patient, that's all.
But I don't want to be patient.
No, Zero, not now.
I'm not in the mood.
All right.
Here you go, boy.
Mornin', gents!
Jack, you home?
Jack, I've got the plans
for next Halloween.
I need to go over them with you
so we can get started.
Jack, please! I'm only
an elected official here.
I can't make decisions by myself.
Jack, answer me!
- Huh?
- He's not home.
- Where is he?
- He hasn't been home all night.
Where are we?
It's someplace new!
What is this?
Whoa-oa-oa!
Whoa!
What's this, what's this
There's color everywhere
What's this
There's white things in the air
What's this, I can't believe my eyes
I must be dreaming
Wake up, Jack, this isn't fair
What's this
What's this, what's this
There's something very wrong
What's this, there's people
singing songs, what's this
The streets are lined
with little creatures laughing
Everybody seems so happy
Have I possibly gone daffy
What is this
What's this
There's children throwing snowballs
instead of throwing heads
They're busy building toys
and absolutely no one's dead
There's frost in every window
Oh, I can't believe my eyes
And in my bones
I feel the warmth
That's coming from inside
Oh, look, what's this
They're hanging mistletoe
They kiss, why that looks
so unique, inspired
They're gathering around
to hear a story
Roasting chestnuts on a fire
What's this
What's this in here
They've got a little tree, how queer
And who would ever think
And why
They're covering it
with tiny little things
They've got electric lights on strings
and there's a smile on everyone
So now correct me if I'm wrong
This looks like fun, this looks like fun
Oh, could it be I got my wish
What's this
Oh my, what now
The children are asleep
But look
There's nothing underneath
No ghouls, no witches here
to scream and scare them or ensnare them
Only little cozy things
secure inside their dreamland
What's this
The monsters are all missing
and the nightmares can't be found
And in their place there seems
to be good feeling all around
Instead of screams, I swear
I can hear music in the air
The smell of cakes and pies
are absolutely everywhere
The sights, the sounds
they're everywhere and all around
I've never felt so good before
This empty place
inside of me is filling up
I simply cannot get enough
I want it, oh, I want it
Oh, I want it for my own
I've got to know, I've got to know
what is this place that I have found
What is this
Christmas Town?
Hmm.
Ho-ho-ho-ho!
- This has never happened before.
- It's suspicious.
- It's peculiar.
- It's scary.
Stand aside. Coming through.
We've got to find Jack!
There's only 365 days left
till next Halloween!
Three sixty-four!
Is there anywhere
we've forgotten to check?
I looked in every mausoleum.
We opened the sarcophagi!
I tromped through
the pumpkin patch.
I peeked behind
the cyclops' eye.
I did! But he wasn't there.
It's time to sound the alarms!
Frog's breath
will overpower any odor.
Bitter!
Worm's wart. But where,
where is that worm's wart?
Sally? ls that soup ready yet?
Ah. Coming!
Lunch!
Ah, what's that?
Worm's wart! Mmm!
And frog's breath?
Wh-What's wrong? l-l thought
you liked frog's breath.
Nothing's more suspicious
than frog's breath.
Until you taste it,
I won't swallow a spoonful.
I'm not hungry. Oops.
You want me to starve...
an old man like me,
who hardly has strength as it is.
Me, to whom you owe
your very life.
Oh, don't be silly.
Mmm! See? Scrumptious!
Did anyone think
to dredge the lake?
Oh, this morning.
- Hear that?
- Ah, what?
- Shh.
Zero!
- Jack's back!
- Jack's back! Jack's back!
- Where have you been?
- Call a town meeting and I'll
tell everyone all about it.
- When?
- Immediately!
Town meeting! Town meeting!
Town meeting tonight!
Town meeting!
Listen, everyone!
I want to tell you
about Christmas Town.
There were objects so peculiar
they were not to be believed
All around things
to tantalize my brain
It's a world unlike anything
I've ever seen
And as hard as I tried
I can't seem to describe
Like a most improbable dream
But you must believe
when I tell you this
It's as real as my skull
and it does exist
Here, let me show you.
Ooh!
This is a thing
called a present
The whole thing
starts with a box
- A box
- Is it steel
- Are there locks
- Is it filled with a pox
- A pox, how delightful, a pox
If you please.
Just a box with
bright colored paper
And the whole thing's
topped with a bow
- A bow
- But why
- How ugly
- What's in it, what's in it
That's the point of the thing
Not to know
- It's a bat
- Will it bend
- It's a rat
- Will it break
Perhaps it's the head
that I found in the lake
Listen now
You don't understand
That's not the point
of Christmasland
Now pay attention
We pick up an oversized sock
And hang it like this
on the wall
Oh, yes, does it still
have a foot
- Let me see, let me look
- Is it rotted and covered with gook
Um, let me explain.
There's no foot inside
but there's candy
- Or sometimes it's filled
with small toys
- Small toys
- Do they bite
- Do they snap
- Or explode in the sack
Well, perhaps they just spring
out and scare girls and boys
What a splendid idea
This Christmas sounds fun
I fully endorse it
Let's try it at once
Everyone, please
Now not so fast
There's something here
that you don't quite grasp
I don't know.
Do you get it?
Well, I may as well
give them what they want.
And the best I must confess
I have saved for the last
For the ruler
of this Christmasland
Is a fearsome king
with a deep, mighty voice
Least, that's what
I've come to understand
And I've also heard it told
That he's something to behold
Like a lobster huge and red
When he sets out to slay
with his rain gear on
Carting bulging sacks
with his big great arms
That is so I've heard it said
And on a dark cold night
under full moonlight
He flies into a fog
like a vulture in the sky
And they call him
Sandy Claws
Well, at least they're excited
But they don't understand
That special kind of feeling
in Christmasland
Oh, well.
Hmm.
There's got to be a logical way
to explain this Christmas thing.
You've poisoned me for the
last time, you wretched girl.
Oh, my head!
The door is open!
- Hello!
- Jack Skellington!
- Up here, my boy.
- Doctor, I need to borrow some
equipment.
Is that so? Whatever for?
I'm conducting a series
of experiments.
How perfectly marvelous!
- Curiosity killed the cat, you know.
- I know.
Come on into the lab
and we'll get you all fixed up.
Hmm. Experiments?
Zero, I'm home!
Interesting reaction!
But what does it mean?
You can come out now
if you promise to behave.
Sally?
Oh, gone again!
Hmm.
Oh!
Something's up with Jack
Don't know if we're ever
going to get him back
He's all alone up there
locked away inside
- Never says a word
- Hope he hasn't died
Something's up with Jack
Christmastime
is buzzing in my skull
Will it let me be
I cannot tell
There's so many things
I cannot grasp
When I think I've got it
and then at last
Through my bony fingers
it does slip
Like a snowflake
in a fiery grip
Something here I'm not quite getting
Though I try I keep forgetting
Like a memory
long since past
Here in an instant
Gone in a flash
What does it mean
In these little bric-a-brac
A secret's waiting to be cracked
These dolls and toys confuse me so
Confound it all, I love it though
Simple objects, nothing more
But something's hidden through a door
Though I do not have the key
Something's here I cannot see
What does it mean
Hmm. Hmm.
I've read these Christmas books
so many times
I know the stories
and I know the rhymes
I know the Christmas carols
all by heart
My skull's so full
it's tearing me apart
As often as I've read them
Something's wrong
It's so hard to put
my bony finger on
Or perhaps it's really not as deep
as I've been led to think
Am I trying much too hard
Of course
I've been too close to see
The answer's right in front of me
Right in front of me
It's simple really, very clear
Like music drifting in the air
Invisible but everywhere
Just because I cannot see it
Doesn't mean I can't believe it
You know I think this Christmas thing
is not as tricky as it seems
And why should they have all the fun
It should belong to anyone
Not anyone in fact, but me
Why I can make a Christmas tree
And there's no reason I can find
I couldn't handle Christmastime
I bet I could improve it too
And that's exactly what I'll do
Eureka!
This year,
Christmas will be ours!
Patience, everyone. Jack has
a special job for each of you.
Dr. Beetlestein.
Your Christmas assignment
is ready.
Dr. Beetlestein,
to the front of the line.
What kind of noise is that
for a baby to make?
- Perhaps it can be improved?
- No problem!
I knew it!
Doctor, thank you for coming.
We need some of these.
Hmm.
Their construction should be
exceedingly simple, I think.
How horrible
our Christmas will be.
No! How jolly!
Oh. How jolly
our Christmas will be.
- What are you doing here?
- Jack sent for us.
- Specifically.
- By name.
- Lock.
- Shock.
- Barrel.
Jack, Jack,
it's Boogie's boys.
Ah, Halloween's finest
trick or treaters.
The job I have for you
is top secret.
It requires craft,
cunning, mischief.
And we thought
you didn't like us, Jack.
Absolutely no one
is to know about it. Not a soul!
Now.
Tree.
Christmas Town.
Ow! Hmm.
And one more thing.
Leave that no-account
Oogie Boogie out of this!
Whatever you say, Jack.
- Of course, Jack.
- Wouldn't dream of it, Jack.
Kidnap Mr. Sandy Claws
- I wanna do it
- Let's draw straws
- Jack said we should work together
- Three of a kind
- Birds of a feather
- Now and forever
La, la, la, la, la, la
La, la, la, la, la
Kidnap the Sandy Claws
Lock him up real tight
Throw away the key
and then turn off all the lights
First we're going to set some bait
inside a nasty trap and wait
When he comes a-sniffing
We will snap the trap and close the gate
Wait, I've got a better plan
to catch this big red lobster man
Let's pop him in a boiling pot
And when he's done we'll butter him up
Kidnap the Sandy Claws
Throw him in a box
Bury him for 90 years
Then see if he talks
And Mr. Oogie Boogie man
Can take the whole thing
over then
He'll be so pleased I do declare
That he will cook him rare
Whee
I say that we take a cannon
Aim it at his door and then
Knock three times and when he answers
Sandy Claws will be no more
You're so stupid
Think now if we blow him up
to smithereens
We may lose some pieces and then
Jack will beat us black and green
Kidnap the Sandy Claws
Tie him in a bag
Throw him in the ocean
Then see if he is sad
Because Mr. Oogie Boogie
is the meanest guy around
- If I were on his boogie list
- I'd get out of town
He'll be so pleased
by our success
That he'll reward us too
I'll bet
Perhaps he'll make
his special brew
Of snake and spider stew
We're his little henchmen
and we take our job with pride
We do our best to please him
and stay on his good side
- I wish my cohorts weren't so dumb
- I'm not the dumb one
- You're no fun
- Shut up
- Make me
I've got something, listen now
This one is real good you'll see
We'll send a present to his door
Upon there'll be a note to read
Now in the box we'll wait
and hide until his curiosity
Entices him to look inside and then
we'll have him one, two, three
Kidnap the Sandy Claws
Beat him with a stick
Lock him up for 90 years
See what makes him tick
Kidnap the Sandy Claws
Chop him into bits
Mr. Oogie Boogie
is sure to get his kicks
Kidnap the Sandy Claws
See what we will see
Lock him in a cage
and then throw away the key
Sandy Claws, huh?
It goes something like this.
How about it?
Think you can manage?
A-one, and a-two,
and a-three, and a--
- Next!
- Fantastic!
Now, why don't you all practice on that,
and we'll be in great shape.
Sally, I need your help
more than anyone's.
You certainly do, Jack.
I had the most terrible vision.
- That's splendid!
- No! It was about your Christmas.
- There was smoke and fire.
- That's not my Christmas.
My Christmas is filled
with laughter and joy.
And this: my Sandy Claws outfit.
I want you to make it.
Jack, please listen to me.
It's going to be a disaster.
How could it be?
Just follow the pattern.
This part's red.
The trim is white.
- It's a mistake, Jack.
- Now, don't be modest.
Who else is clever enough
to make my Sandy Claws outfit?
- Next!
- I have...
- Oh.
- every confidence in you.
But it seems wrong to me.
Very wrong.
This device
is called a nutcracker.
Jack! Jack! We caught 'im!
We got 'im!
Perfect! Open it up. Quickly!
That's not Sandy Claws!
- It isn't?
- Who is it?