Under Siege 1992, 25 fps
Pearl Harbor outer marker,
30 minutes.
Hey, Case!
What's happening?
Where's your whites?
The Prez is coming.
He won't miss me.
What's this? You're in the Navy,
you've got to look good.
-Cue Ball!
-Ryback, where's your whites?
-Poor boy doesn't have a dress uniform.
-I've got the dress, I forgot the pumps.
Tell him not to worry.
Everything here is handled.
Oh, my God.
No, no, that's okay.
We'll take care of it.
Well, it's going to be a zoo.
Chief Ryback.
Send him in.
Get in your dress uniform.
You know how I feel about ceremonies.
I thought this time--
If I had your ribbons,
I'd wear them to bed.
Yes, sir.
Get in your whites.
I'll introduce you to the President.
-I appreciate that, but--
-That's not a good idea.
For once, Commander Krill and I
are in total agreement.
I have 50 gallons of bouillabaisse
I need to prepare...
...by tomorrow.
My birthday?
I could do the cheeseburger routine.
It's not for me, it's the crew.
They really love that stuff.
Just don't show your face
till after the ceremony.
You're a sorry-looking sailor.
That I am. Thank you, sir.
Sir...
...why do you tolerate that clown?
I know he's a good cook--
He's more than a good cook. You have
no idea. Now let him be, XO.
Yes, sir.
Fifty years ago today...
...the infamous Japanese attack
destroyed the Pacific fleet...
...here in Pearl Harbor.
Today, in honor of those who died,
the USS Missouri returns.
Built to avenge Pearl Harbor,
she did.
Days after we dropped the bomb
on Hiroshima...
...Japan surrendered
on the Missouri's deck...
...ending World War ll.
The ship fired
the first shots of the Gulf War.
Her powerful 16-inch guns
destroyed lraqi bunkers.
Her Tomahawk missiles rocketed deep
into the heart of Baghdad.
The fastest and most powerful
dreadnought ever to sail the seas....
Where's your tattoo?
Where I got it, you don't want to see.
Now the ship will be decommissioned.
President Bush is paying final tribute
to the ship...
...and her great history.
Did you hear the joke about Andre
and Beaudreau hunting on the bayou?
"Where're the guns, Druillet?"
That's about right.
In the end...
...this unity of purpose....
These ceremonies not only remember war,
they celebrate peace.
The President ordered the removal
of all Tomahawk cruise missiles...
...from U. S. surface ships.
Tomorrow the ship embarks for
San Francisco for her final voyage.
Her weaponry will be removed,
dismantled and never fired again.
The vessel will then
take her place in naval history.
We will gain the inevitable triumph,
so help us God.
Look at the money spent
on this photo opportunity.
Ready to go, sir.
Very well, let's single up.
Aye, sir.
Single up all lines.
Captain, you have clear water to port.
Very well.
Krill ain't running this ship.
The old man has to okay
all helicopter landings.
How's the captain going to authorize
a surprise party for himself?
We already stowed all the gear.
What's on this helicopter?
This little sweetheart.
-She's in the--
-Yeah, she's in the cake.
That is Miss July '89. Jordan Tate.
We'll be ready for her.
Good. Go ahead and keep that.
Lieutenant, we don't have time
to talk about this now.
No time for the security
of nuclear weapons?
Maybe I'm not being clear.
Any watches not crucial shall be
secured during the party...
...including the Marine roving patrol.
We're operating
on a skeleton crew.
This is an order.
The log will show I consider this
unsafe, and obeyed under protest.
Fine.
Hey, Cue Ball.
Cue Ball in the house.
Show me a move!
Turn up the tunes! Turn up the tunes!
Come on, show me some moves.
Come on!
Go, Cue Ball!
Go, Cue Ball, go! Go, Cue Ball, go!
That was cute.
Petty Officer Ryback?
Ensign Taylor.
Sir.
You don't have to "sir" me.
We're casual in the galley.
I'd watch it.
We still have a week together.
So I won't get to see you
go through puberty.
What is it?
I have orders from the XO
on the captain's birthday.
We're having dinner flown in
from Hawaii.
This galley will be cleared by 17:00.
You are to report to the mess deck
prior to the helo's arrival.
Negative.
Excuse me?
Only I cook for the captain.
You don't like that, talk to him.
I don't believe you get it.
See, this is a surprise party.
No one is going to talk
to the captain about this.
You know something?
He don't like surprises.
Neither do l.
Then I guess we'll just see
what we'll see. Won't we?
"l guess we'll just see
what we'll see. Won't we?"
Krill's going to skin you alive.
Why is it that I'm
starting to shake so bad...
...and there's this deep fear in me...
...thinking about Mr. Krill and
the horrible things he'll do to me?
Commander Krill.
Send him in.
You wanted to see me, Captain?
Commander Krill...
...how'd you expect to land
a helicopter without my authorization?
-It was a mistake to think--
-It was a mistake to try.
Your actions are
grossly insubordinate.
I want an explanation. Now.
Admiral Bates wants to thank you
for how smoothly things went.
He has a surprise for your birthday.
He's flying in from Hawaii.
I see. If the admiral wants
a party, I guess we'll have one.
Let's keep it simple.
Off-duty personnel can attend...
...but watches remain.
Yes, sir.
Captain...
...since he wants this to be
a surprise...
...if you could stay here
till we come for you...
I'll be engrossed in a novel.
Very good, sir.
How's that bouillabaisse?
Heads up!
If I'm not mistaken...
...every one of you has orders
to report to the mess deck...
...for the party.
Stand fast.
Everyone else go! Now.
See you at the party.
You know...
...this does look delicious.
It smells like a lard omelet.
I put up with your shit...
...because the captain likes
your cooking.
But this time he won't be here
to save you.
Really?
Little flavor.
You like that?
That's striking an officer!
It is not!
-Okay! All right!
-Cuff him and throw him in the brig!
In the brig!
You need the old man's signature.
Good point.
Secure him in the meat locker.
Now!
Right now!
Let's go.
Now I know why you're a cook.
You hit like a faggot.
Steel.
Private Nash...
-...you came on board in Hawaii?
-Yes, sir.
Then you don't know about Ryback?
He is an extreme psychopath.
He hates officers.
He hates America.
This is the captain's birthday.
I don't want him ruining it.
No one speaks to him
or lets him out.
If he tries to escape,
shoot him right here.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Another cold day in hell.
It speaks well for the Navy
that we can entertain a crew at sea.
It's so human.
And I love that. Don't you?
I just hope I don't throw up.
You'll be fine.
I love it. I love it!
Welcome to the USS Missouri.
Fantastic!
We're looking forward
to a great time.
I love this business!
My future wife.
She's landed.
The Bunny's landed. See you.
Private!
Doesn't it seem strange
that Krill put me in here?
I ain't listening to you.
Welcome aboard.
Guys, make a hole.
Don't let them bother you.
They've been at sea too long. You okay?
I still feel really queasy.
We'll go to the wardroom,
where you can change.
Let the lady through!
Be careful with the cake.
Make sure the wires are covered.
That's the way it goes.
-Are you lost?
-No, no. Where do you want us?
-Is the band ready?
-Ready.
You're over here.
Starboard side, right now.
You'll knock the captain
off his feet. You're beautiful.
For motion sickness. Take two.
Thanks.
What happened to your face?
Cut myself shaving.
The cake's almost ready.
We have a room for you to change.
You'll be safe from my men.
I'm going to go put on
my party dress.
Don't worry. You can play
this with your eyes shut.
Private!
Let me out!
You follow Krill's orders, you'll
go to the brig! Use your head!
Go get my pies out of the oven!
I must be nuts.
Very sick.
We want to give you
a great big welcome...
...to the big,
beautiful Missouri lounge...
...out here in the middle
of the big, beautiful Pacific Ocean.
I'm Bad Billy.
And these are
the fabulous Bail Jumpers!
I have orders not to talk to you.
Understand? Orders.
You could be held accountable...
...keeping me in here like this.
You have to think about that.
Private?
He didn't say
you can't talk to the captain.
Go ask him if he wants me in here.
You little E-1 prick.
Lieutenant,
this is absolutely beautiful.
Old man says keep her level.
How about an hors d'oeuvre?
What have we here?
All right. There's the Twinkies.
Where's Miss July?
And there she is.
Miss July, 1989.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
That's not Miss July.
My God, look at him.
Commander Krill.
Welcome to the revolution.
This party'll make history.
No wonder he wanted everyone here.
Maybe Krill isn't
such an asshole after all.
That's great. Go get the old man.
He's been waiting on you now.
All right.
Miss July!
We're going to surprise the captain now.
-Have a good party!
-Come on, dear.
Where's the chief?
In the meat locker
until after the party.
It's only like 40 degrees in there.
He'll be fine. He's got a guard.
Krill's a maniac.
Tell the captain...
...he spit in my soup.
You got a fire in here.
Get my pies out of the oven!
These pantyhose feel good!
It's okay. I'm here
to escort the captain to the party.
Aye, Commander.
Commander Krill.
Send him in.
I'm your date tonight, Captain.
Wait.
Wait a minute!
Who is the highest-
ranking officer here?
Who is the highest-ranking officer
in this room?
Stand up.
Stand up and be recognized.
Part the waves there.
Get out of the man's way.
Put a light on the man.
Now you, sir, are the highest-ranking
officer in this room?
Yes. Operations Officer.
Third in command.
It's a pleasure to meet you,
Commander Green.
Get down!
What's going on?
The party's just beginning.
Captain!
Good shot.
Lay down! Hands up!
Heads down!
What are you looking at?
On the floor!
Put your head down.
You want to be good now?
What is this, a joke?
No joke!
I hear gunfire. What's going on?
It's done.
Four minutes ahead of schedule.
Mother Goose,
the quails are in the nest.
It's just the music.
You got shit for brains.
That's gunfire. Call the bridge.
I don't know who you're talking to.
No one's listening.
I ain't asking you to listen to me.
Call the captain. Listen to him.
Seal it!
Eyes on the man in front of you!
Goddamn it,
that's the last time I'll tell you!
Let this be a learning experience.
If you resist, we will
kill you and the man next to you.
Now move out of here
in an orderly fashion.
Now!
Turn around. Hands on your head.
Where is it?
Here it is.
Listen to the shit
I've had to put up with.
"Commander Krill has become
increasingly hostile to the crew...
...possibly due to anger over
reviews of his performance.
I recommend psychological
evaluation before his next assignment."
Do I look like I need
a psychological evaluation?
Not at all.
I got to change.
Behind your head.
Up against the wall.
XO on the bridge.
Listen up.
Hands on your head and move
to the counter, right now.
Your destination is the fo'c's'le.
Cooperate and you won't be harmed.
Change of watch.
You've done a good job,
but you're relieved of duty.
Get your hand off that console.
You're a cheeky bastard. Move out!
My God!
Bunch of wussies.
The disk, Mr. Pitt.
Guard it with your life.
Of course.
Bring up the layout, if you will.
-We've overridden their systems.
-We control crypto, CIC...
...engine rooms, boiler rooms,
bridge and all open decks.
We've welded shut the hatches.
A few loose sailors may be berthing...
...or they're caught in nonessential
areas and can go nowhere.
The rest are in the fo'c's'le.
Excellent.
Reactivate the weapons systems,
Mr. Pitt.
Mr. Daumer...
...you may deploy the welding crews
and chop up broadway.
Commander Krill,
you're hereby promoted to captain.
Congratulations. The ship is yours.
The ship is mine.
Thank you, Billy.
All right!
Can we get something to eat in here?
Get some food!
Krill warned me you were tricky.
I'm not tricky, I'm just freezing.
Something's going on here.
Call the bridge.
No one'll yell at you.
It's just your job.
Check right away.
All right.
All right, I'll check.
That's all.
Do that. And be careful.
'Tis a rare thing.
This is good. It'll work.
Got a call from Private Nash
on guard duty in the kitchen.
Pitt, pull it up.
That's an unsecured area.
They can access the whole ship.
Ryback. A cook.
A pain-in-the-ass cook.
Give me that.
Private Nash.
I'm glad you checked in.
I've been with the captain.
Keep Ryback under control,
and don't open the door.
Tell him you're sending relief.
Tell him you are sending
somebody to relieve him.
Stand your station fast.
I'm sending someone to relieve you.
Is everything okay?
We heard what sounded like gunshots.
Gunshots? Oh, that.
Those are party poppers. Firecrackers.
Part of the party.
Stand firm until you're relieved.
-Yes, sir.
-Over and out.
Anything else you didn't tell us?
Any further memory lapses
or oversights, perhaps?
No other memory lapses
or oversights, perhaps.
There's two men. One's locked up.
I'll take care of it.
We'll handle it. Secure the galley.
Send Cates and Ziggs.
This Marine's armed.
We need more. I'll go.
Don't worry. They're professionals.
They can handle 20 Marines...
...and 100 cooks.
You're wrong, Ryback. You're wrong.
-They were party poppers.
-You got shit for brains.
I know they brainwashed you,
but you have to question authority.
Trust me, boy.
That's gunfire.
Free me and I'll take care of it.
I'll be relieved in a few minutes,
so just shut up and sit tight.
Something's going on.
Use your head this time.
Do what you got to do. Let me out.
Or when I'm out,
I'll shoot you myself.
Commander Krill?
Is that you?
Get your hands on your head.
Turn around.
Get down on your knees.
Cross your ankles.
Where's the cook?
In the reefer.
Which one?
Son of a bitch!
We've got an F-18.
They sent an F-18
to look for the chopper.
Heading 315 miles, speed 430,
approximately 8000.
207, 61 miles now.
430. 5000 now, into descent.
We're going down now.
Looks like one helo on deck.
Going in for a closer look.
31 to Missouri, over.
Goodbye!
Are you tracking me?
Negative.
He's locked me up! Mayday.
Welcome to the revolution.
Better call the office.
You're in deep kimchi, buddy.
Better have it all
in one sock for this one.
Claims he was a company man
who worked for you.
What's his name?
William Strannix.
Jesus Christ!
Not good.
Mr. Breaker...
...you better be candid
with us here tonight.
We need answers,
and we need them now.
Gentlemen, if any ships or aircraft
approach within 100 miles...
...we will kill the crew and
retaliate using the ship's arsenal.
Bill, this is Tom. What's going on?
I have 32 Tomahawks under my thumb...
...and all you can do
is alert the media.
You don't have the launch codes.
Let me guess.
5-6-6-0-4-9-9-7-8-0?
This is insane.
Be careful with that word, Tom.
This is Admiral Bates speaking.
Tell us why you're doing this.
Hi, Admiral!
Six months ago, Tom Breaker
canceled Operation Cleopatra.
Shortly thereafter, two young men
from Langley tried to cancel me.
Didn't you receive
each man's forefinger in the mail?
Yes.
Did you expect us
to wait for you to try again?
I know things are a little...
-...chaotic for you right now.
-Chaotic!
Wake up!
You and I know that chaos and
bedlam are consuming the entire world.
UV rays are only the beginning.
We have an inch of topsoil left.
Topsoil?
Sexually transmitted diseases,
depletion of the gene pool.
It adds up to oblivion.
Governments will fall.
Anarchies will reign.
It's a brave new world.
What are you planning to do?
Do you realize that whatever I do
is inevitable? Can we agree on that?
Not necessarily.
There you go.
You can't argue with me
or negotiate or attempt a ploy.
You have to reconsider your philosophy.
All right, I'm sorry.
Whatever you decide to do is inevitable.
Look at my life.
The life you tried to take.
There was Annapolis, Vietnam, so on.
I missed the 60s,
and I believe if I had been there...
...to contribute,
everything would've been fine.
Bill, if this is about
reliving the 60s, you can forget it.
The movement is dead.
Hence the name.
It moves a certain distance,
then it stops.
Revolution gets its name by always
coming back around in your face.
You tried to kill me,
you son of a bitch.
So welcome to the revolution.
There's more to follow.
I'll stay in touch.
He's flipped.
He's completely flipped.
I want a list of everything
on that ship.
General, here's what we know.
The threat is verifiable. It is real.
I repeat, it is real.
Shit! You son of a bitch.
Think they believe you?
They believe I'm crazy, paranoid
or something.
I have a harpoon locked on.
Fire when ready.
Pipe down, men!
Pipe down.
Missile away.
Oh, boy.
Oh, boy, oh, boy.
Bang! You're dead.
-He's taken out satellite relay.
-What doesn't he want us to see?
He wants to blind us.
It's illogical. We can
follow his movement from Pearl.
You can vector an AWACS.
Or send E-2C from Nimitz.
Do it.
Wake up the President.
Bring it in.
Keep it coming in.
Cut it fast.
Time is money on this deal.
They better be competent.
Get your ass up there!
Watch your heads.
Glad I sent you the blueprints.
I have 4 sections this way,
7 sections this way.
I'll have it cut and up
within the hour.
Time is money, on this job!
Time is money.
This will cut them to the bone.
Right to the bone.
What's that noise?
That's my beloved crew.
Keep trying. Keep pounding.
Someone will hear us.
Shut the music off.
What the hell's going on?
What happened to them?
Who are you and why are you here?
My name is Jordan Tate.
I'm Miss July '89.
I was hired to jump
out of the cake...
...but I got airsick
on the way here, and so...
...this guy gave me these pills.
-I guess I fell asleep.
-What kind of bullshit is this?!
I am an actress, okay?
I did a Hunter episode
and a Wet'n Wild video.
My agent said I was
going to jump out of the cake.
How many on the chopper?
I don't know.
It was full.
There was a band and caterers.
Where's the crew?
I don't know. I didn't see anything.
You didn't see or hear anything
and don't remember anything?
I've done stupid things in my life...
...but believe me,
I don't know anything.
All right, I believe you.
So who are you? Are you
a special forces guy or something?
I'm just a cook.
A cook?
Just a lowly, lowly cook.
My God, we're going to die.
The ship contains 40,000 rounds
of 20mm CWIZ.
Over 1000 16-inch projectiles.
We believe there's 15 harpoon
cruise missiles still aboard...
...and 32 Tomahawks.
What kind of Tomahawks?
It's all right. It's okay.
Eight of them are specials.
Nuclear-tipped. 220 kilotons each.
Mr. Breaker, would you explain how
this nut could hold a top position...
...in an intelligence agency?
Would you answer that?
High-level covert operatives
like Strannix are under great stress.
They're creative thinkers
who, by their very nature--
Tom trains everyone
in the CIA who's crazy.
All we want to know...
...is how he got our battleship.
That's his specialty.
North Korea was refitting a sub
to fire antiship missiles...
...so we sent Strannix in.
You've been financing
this maniac's private army?
You didn't think
it might be a problem?
Once we realized
we'd lost positive control...
...we tried to neutralize him.
We missed.
Excuse me.
This North Korean sub...
How do you know he sunk it?
Oh, we're positive he sunk it.
Positive.
Roadrunner to Tweety Bird.
Do you read me? Come in.
Tweety Bird to Roadrunner.
We're nearby.
-How's it going?
-Sub's up.
-It's all rock and roll to me.
-Any sign of Wile E. Coyote?
No. Meet at the birdcage.
Roadrunner out.
You're the Roadrunner?
Never been caught.
Problem. Cates and Ziggs are missing.
I radioed them repeatedly.
No response.
-The last location?
-The galley.
I told you to send more men.
I told you.
Please don't leave me here alone.
Believe me, this is the
safest place you can be. Understand?
Let me out of here!
Let me out!
Do you understand what'll happen
if anybody hears you?
They'll try to kill us.
Now be quiet.
I hate being alone.
Do you hate being dead?
Clear!
Put those on.
You're coming with me,
you got to be invisible.
If you're by a hatch and
see the enemy, you become the hatch.
I'm giving you this rifle
with a selector switch on it.
One is fully automatic,
one is semiautomatic.
The definition of semiautomatic is,
when you depress the trigger...
...one round will go off.
That's what I want to give you.
Spend one round at a time.
Turn on the lights.
Check the breaker box.
It's happened before.
Man who did this is a professional.
-Who is he and why is he on my ship?
-Your ship?
You wouldn't be on this battleship
if not for me.
He's a cook, plain and simple.
A cook didn't do this.
He came with the captain.
I know his routine front and back.
He's good with cooking knives.
Cooking knives!
He got lucky.
In my professional opinion,
he is a military reject...
...in command of a galley.
Get down!
-What was that?
-A bomb, jackass.
He used the microwave as a detonator.
Secure everything
between here and the CIC.
You see anything, radio at once
for backup. Understand?
Put these fires out!
I'd like to see the personnel file
on this "simple cook."
Put out these goddamn fires!
SEAL Team 5 will launch from Nimitz
aboard a CH-53 Echo...
...with an Apache gunship in support.
At the objective area, the Apache
will take out the ship's radar...
...and her electronic warfare systems.
Then SEAL Team 5 will board
and retake the ship.
And the odds of success?
If it's a lunatic who only
partly controls the ship...
...the odds are good.
But if he's ready for us...
...if he's prepared to repel boarders...
...the odds are not good.
Bear in mind, the operators
from SEAL Team 5 are the best there are.
This is our only hope of saving
the crew and retaking the ship.
Let me make one thing
absolutely clear:
If the SEAL team fails...
...we will have no alternative
but to launch an air strike...
...and destroy the Missouri.
You know what that means.
We'll get her back for you.
Make it happen. Make it happen.
22... 12... perfect.
It's 44 feet from the weather deck
to the missile canisters.
It'll take a half-hour to assemble
that section of the crane.
Ryback's file was in the captain's
private cabinet.
Ryback is an ex-SEAL.
The goddamn cook's a SEAL?
Shut up and listen.
"Expert in martial arts...
...explosives, weapons, tactics.
Silver Star. Navy Cross.
Purple Heart with cluster.
Security revoked after Panama."
So he could only rate as a yeoman...
...or a cook. How little did I know.
We lost two more men in the engine room.
You were told to review
every crew member's file.
I know, but I didn't have access
to the captain's files!