Dark Water
And tomorrow we can practice
singing, ok?
-Yeah! -OK, see you tomorrow!
-Bye! -See ya!
See ya!
B'bye.
Yoshimi... no one's come for you?
Yoshimi Matsubara
Well, your husband has no objections
on the division of property.
So it's...
our daughter?
Yes.
He's absolutely insistent
on being the legal guardian.
Why is he saying this now?
He has completely neglected her
from the beginning.
Perhaps it's just that
you've never noticed. He may...
No, that's not it at all.
He forgets her birthday every year.
Where are you living?
Presently I'm looking for a place
for my daughter and me.
But I'll be deciding this week.
-Just a small question.
-Sure.
Is it true you had once received
psychiatric treatment?
Did he tell you that?
Yes.
That was before we were married.
Over 10 years ago now.
I was working proofreading novels
at the time, and...
You mean correcting spelling mistakes,
that sort of thing?
Right.
And some of the novels
I was working on then...
were extremely graphic and sadistic.
So it was a distraction to your work?
No you see, the content was
just so horrible...
and I had to read them
over and over again.
So that's when
you started going for treatment?
Yes.
I see.
Is that going to... ?
No, that shouldn't present a problem.
You know I...
haven't been at all since then.
Don't worry about it.
And unless something major occurs,
the mother usually has the advantage
when the child is under seven.
Right.
My being seen before...
that doesn't matter anymore.
Hey, a fact is a fact.
What's wrong with speaking the truth?
I don't think
it will get you very far now.
Go straight along the river.
Right here? Thank you very much.
Tired?
This will be the last one, ok?
Alright, I'm going on ahead...
Ikuko
What do you think this room's for?
That's where you eat.
How about this one?
Where you sleep?
How about this little room here?
That's my room!
Ok, I'm off to see Ikuko's room! Bye!
Hey!
How many floors?
Gee, I don't know...
Can you count them?
One, two, three, four, five...
So what do you think?
A real bargain, I'd say.
We'll think about it.
Thank you.
Ms. Matsubara? -Yes.
Come right in.
Please, come in.
The apartment manager lives here too.
So you can feel safe
coming home at night.
Disappointed?
It is a little old.
But it's built solid, you know.
Please.
Mr. Kamiya,
I told you to wipe this up.
Sorry,
a bucket of water spilled earlier.
After you.
Which way?
Here we are.
Go right in.
How old are you, Ikuko?
Tell him how old you are.
Almost six.
Oh, you're in kindergarten.
Yup!
Where's my room?
How about this one here?
Yay!
The kindergarten is really close.
And next week
we're having the wallpaper replaced.
Then it will look as good as new.
The humidity in here is unreal.
Well, with all the rain we've had...
Most people use this room as a bedroom.
Oh, right...
I haven't shown you the kitchen.
Please.
We're having the kitchen done over too.
You'll find it very easy to use.
You know the other family
also liked the room.
''The early bird catches the worm.''
I see.
It's just the two of you, right?
Yes.
Oh, then there's plenty of room!
A real steal.
Ikuko?
Maybe she went outside?
I'm going to go check.
Ikuko?
Excuse me,
has my little girl been here?
We haven't seen her.
Really...
Baron, have you seen her?
He says he hasn't either.
Ikuko!
That's...
my daughter!
What floor was that?
Can't tell. They all look the same.
Ikuko?
Ikuko!
Mommy!
What were you doing?
I was looking all over for you.
Where did you get this?
It was lying on the ground.
Where?
Over there.
There aren't any kids living here now.
Well maybe some kids came over to play.
Your lucky day.
No.
She can't have these.
We don't know who they belong to.
Careful now, honey.
No problem!
''Lost and Found''
Mine!
Hey!
Come back here!
You silly!
The sound really carries, huh.
Yeah, it really carries.
Gotta be careful, huh.
Yeah, careful!
Count each tooth 10 times now.
Yup, I am!
Chee-ze! Chee-ze!
Everyone, I'd like to introduce...
our new friend, Ikuko Matsubara.
Hi, I'm Ikuko Matsubara.
I think we can do better than that!
Alright! Pleased to meet you!
Nice job!
What floor, ma'am?
First floor, please.
Certainly.
What's...
Hello?
Excuse me.
There's water leaking from our ceiling.
I'm Yoshimi Matsubara,
just moved into Rm. 305.
There's a wet spot on my ceiling,
and water dripping down from it.
Well the building is very old, you see.
So it gets a little rickety.
Ok, and so...?
I'll make a note of it in the log.
Ok, everyone!
Quiet and listen up now.
I want to introduce our newest friend
on her first day!
Can you tell us your name?
Hi, I'm Ikuko Matsubara!
Now let's all be good friends
with Ikuko, ok?
Ok!
Please. -Thank you.
We believe in giving children
the freedom to do what they desire.
This is our basic
educational philosophy.
All our kids are really outgoing.
Ikuko will make friends in no time.
Thank you.
Not at all.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you. -Please.
Sir, Kobayashi's here.
I hear you called
Ms. Tsushima ''stupid''?
Come on, you're almost in
first grade now.
You said it to Kusano and Uesugi,
right?
That Ms. Tsushima was stupid.
Why is she ''stupid''?
What was it you said...
''Ms. Tsushima's stupid
because she's fat.''
Right?
What's that all about?
Everyone overweight is ''stupid''?
Well?
What are you crying for?!
Kobayashi!
Yes, why?
You think it's our fault?
Well, it's nobody's but your own!
Hello?
The place may be old,
but I really doubt that's the cause.
I think it's a plumbing leak
from somewhere above us.
Maybe the room right above you...
That's what I thought,
so I went up and checked.
But no one answered...
All done.
Ok, I'll tell the apartment manager
myself tomorrow.
No, you see...
he won't lift a finger,
that's why I called you.
But I'm not involved with management,
you see.
But water is...
dripping down from my ceiling.
Ok, see you tomorrow!
Sorry to keep you waiting,
I was a little tied up.
Where were we...
Oh yes, Yoshimi Matsubara.
You have previous experience, correct?
I worked up until six years ago.
Right, right...
At Sanyu Publishing...
quite a large company.
As you can tell, we're quite small.
Why did you leave Sanyu?
I got married and then had a child.
Oh-right, right.
Are you sure you'd be happy here?
The pay wouldn't be as high, you know.
Well, I'm in a situation right now
where...
I really want to start working soon.
Of course,
I don't mean taking a job
just anywhere...
That's alright. I understand.
Mr. Kono!
Coming!
Excuse me again.
Sorry about this.
What is it?
Bye, now. Thank you.
There's mommy.
Hello?
Who's picking up Yoshimi?
She's been waiting all alone for...
What? You can't just...!
So who's coming to pick her up today?
I see.
Yoshimi
Today, daddy's coming to get you.
So just a little bit longer, ok?
What about mommy?
Mommy? Well, she...
Sir, what can I say?
Tomorrow is just too early for us to...
Ms. Matsubara?
Oh yes, I worked at...
Sanyu until I had my daughter
six years ago.
My job was proofreading,
and I look forward...
to working with you.
Right...
Hey, wait a second...
Ms. Matsubara!
Ikuko
Ikuko...
Have you seen this child?
Mitsuko Kawai (5), born 11/3/93,
4'5'', 45lbs., long black hair.
Last seen 7/14/99,
wearing a hooded yellow raincoat.
Ikuko!
Mommy!
What are you doing?!
I had no choice!
You didn't pick her up!
Stay out of this.
Waiting there all alone...
Do you know how that feels?!
Come on.
Let's go.
-It's so pretty. -It is, isn't it!
Want to try?
Let's get some on the way home.
Where should we do them?
We'd get in trouble
on the balcony, huh.
Mommy?
I don't need anyone but you.
Did daddy say something to you?
I'm sorry.
You know what?
I can handle anything,
just as long as you're with me.
You have one new message.
This is Mr. Kono
from Mitsuba Publishing.
I'm really sorry for all the commotion
today at your interview.
Anyway I was thinking, if you'd like,
we could have you start
proofreading tomorrow.
No!
What?
I just got a job!
Really? Alright!
You did it!
Top floor, ma'am?
Please!
Fourth floor - toys.
Going up!
Ok!
Come on!
No!
Ikuko, don't
Ow! That hurts!
There! I win!
But that's not yours, Mitsuko.
No fair.
What?
I like this one, so I'll give you
this one here.
You like it?
Ikuko, turn off the water
and come on out.
But she loves the bath...
We've been in here so long.
Come on now, time to come out.
Ok, let's play hide and seek!
Yay!
Once, twice, three...
Rock, paper, scissors!
Ok, Mao's ''it''!
One...two...three...
four...
Hey, can I...
This is our spot. Hide over there.
I'm ready!
What happened?
Well...
She ''threw up and collapsed''?
That's never happened before.
You probably forced her
to do something.
Not at all...
You two...
Just what have you done to my child!
We haven't done anything.
But...
Try and calm down.
Come on, let's talk.
It seems that lately,
Ikuko has been behaving oddly.
Apparently she talks to herself a lot.
I also hear you're divorced.
That must be affecting her.
We see this a lot
with children of divorced parents.
''Come home soon, Mitsuko''
As a matter of fact,
she used to behave oddly too.
However in Mitsuko's case,
her mother had abandoned her.
Just got up and left one day.
You never heard of her?
The girl who disappeared two years ago.
Mitsuko Kawai.
She was one of our kids here.
Is she...
still missing?
Yes.
I think she was kidnapped
by some perverted individual.
Excuse me?
Apparently you're late picking up Ikuko
almost every day.
''Almost every day''?
That's an exaggeration...
Oh?
Well, sometimes...
I get there late because of work,
but really...
''Every day'' ...who told you that?
And is it true you yanked her arm
and dislocated her shoulder?
Dislocated it?
Why no... of course not!
And how about wandering around
aimlessly at night?
Do you deny this?
I was a child then.
My parents had divorced.
Apparently I did such things
without realizing it.
But it was only for a short period.
And I can assure you
that would never happen now.
If the mother can't show
she can raise the child...
Stop exaggerating everything!
What are you talking about?!
Don't deny it!
-Please, let's remain calm.
-Who is he!
I'm Mr. Hamada's private lawyer
Masato Nishioka...
Using a guy like this...
as your personal spy!
Hey, I'm just worried about Ikuko.
Since when?
I don't care how you rationalize it...
stop playing dirty!!
Please, both of you.
We need to set the next date.
Right. Sorry.
So it was you...
And the bag... you put it there.
What?
The red bag, on the roof!
-Why did you do that?!
-What are you talking about!
-Why?! -Ms. Matsubara!
Take it easy!
Let's go inside, Mr. Hamada.
Are you alright?
I take it... you're still
in the middle of mediations.
If you let them see you like this,
they'll think you're unstable,
which can only hurt you.
My secretary's off today,
so this may be a little strong.
Woops! Forgot the cream and sugar.
If they take her away from me...
I...
Your husband seems pretty serious.
He could move against you anywhere,
anytime.
They say with children under seven,
the mother has the advantage.
But if you continue along this path,
growing weaker by the day,
it will be nearly impossible for you
to gain custody.
In any case,
now is the most critical time.
If you want to continue
living with your daughter,
the first thing you need to do
is pull yourself together.
Right...
Come on, we can't get very far
like that now.
It'll be alright.
Let's fight this together.
Thank you.
Did she eat her lunch?
Sure did.
Girls are just the cutest things.
Auntie, leaving already?
Yup, have to stop off at the store.
You know how he leaves it all to me.
Sorry, I know it's far...
You're the only one I can ask.
That's ok.
You've done well with Ikuko.
A far cry from the mother you had.
She just couldn't think of anyone
but herself...
Ok, see ya.
Thanks.
Bye.
Ikuko...
Ikuko
Ikuko!
Ikuko...
Mommy!
Ikuko
Ikuko?
Are you there?
It's me... Is Ikuko with you?
No.
Don't lie.
I wouldn't lie about that!
Why, what happened?
Yoshimi! What's going on?!
Ikuko!
Iku... Ikuko!
Hello! Open up!
Hello!
Ikuko, are you in there?
Ikuko?
Ikuko...
Are you here?
Ikuko?
Ikuko!
Shoji and Mitsuko Kawai
Mitsuko Kawai...
May I come in?
Sure.
What are you doing?
We're moving out.
So Ikuko will...
have to change kindergarten again?
That's right.
Why not wait a while?
I can't.
Ms. Matsubara,
... you know we're at a disadvantage
as it stands.
If you move again now, think of how
the committee will view this.
I don't want to hear that now!
Mitsuko has returned
to the apartment upstairs,
and she's trying to take Ikuko away!
So the room upstairs was open...
I realize you're busy,
...but I'd like you to see this.
What the... ?
Mr. Kamiya!
But I locked it...
Wow, you were right...
What in the name of...
The family of that girl
who disappeared...
when did they move out?
Well, let's see...
the end of last year, wasn't it?
The father lived here
for a while by himself.
Said his little girl would have
no place to come home to.
Which means,
the water in here may have been running
for the past six months.
Mr. Kamiya
Ms. Matsubara complained to you
about this, didn't she?
Did you look into it?
Mr. Kamiya
There are a lot of people
in line for your job.
A lot of people to replace you.
Mr. Ohta
I believe she also called you.
We'll... I'm uh...
Well...
what about the footsteps I heard?
Well, we know Ikuko was in here.
So someone else
could have gotten in too.
The bag was lying right here.
Did you throw it away again?
Well, I threw it away once.
But that's all I know.
So it's disappeared...
Maybe part of some superstition.
Either way, it must be the local kids.
Look how dirty this thing is...
Do you have it cleaned?
That's the cleaning company's job.
I can go now, right?
Woops...
Think he's upset?
And then right over there,
I saw someone.
Did you get a clear look?
It was just for an instant,
but I saw something.
But I'll bet no one was there
when you checked.
Well, yes...
See the highway over there?
And the neon sign on that building.
This water tank is exposed to light
from all around.
So if something passed
in front of the light,
it would cast a shadow on the tank.
Then it would be natural for your eyes
to play tricks on you.
Although,
coming up here all alone at night
and seeing what you saw...
that would scare anyone.
Your husband's lawyer
has also looked this over,
and has agreed to the terms.
I don't think this will
compromise your position at all.
Thank you.
Just remember,
this is simply a set of legal points
worked out by lawyers.
So just continue with your daily
routine, and try to remain focused.
I will.
Hey, you're just about there.
Ikuko.
Ready to go back to school?
Sure!
Well, you sure seem better!
I would...
really like to thank you
for all you've done.
By myself, I was so confused...
Not at all.
I can see Ikuko needs you.
And that you need her. That's all.
I can see now
that I need to be stronger.
But it's not over yet.
The final decision will probably
be made at the next session.
In any case,
even if something happens before then,
don't act alone.
Contact me immediately.
I will.
One, two, three!
All auntie makes is okayu rice.
Hey come on, you were sick.
It's good though, isn't it?
I like this better.
She brought her own water
to make dinner.
She did?
Yeah, she said
the water here is no good.
Yeah...
the water here is
definitely not the cleanest.
Are you sure about school tomorrow?
I'm sure!
Alright! Let's get your things ready.
Ok, I'll go look for your bag.
Ikuko... how did this get in here?
I don't know.
Did you go back to the roof?
I swear, I don't know.
I won't be mad,
so just tell me the truth.
Did you go up there?
No!
Ok.
I'm sorry.
Connecting to personal voicemail...
Hello, this is Kishida...
Hello, Kishida Law Offices.
Hi, my name is Yoshimi Matsubara.
Is Mr. Kishida there?
He's out at the moment, and
we don't expect him back today.
Is that so?
Well, thank you very much.
No!
Ikuko, stay right here.
Mommy
Stay here!
Water tank cleaning log
7/14/99
Last seen 7/14/99
Ikuko...
Ikuko!
What happened?
What the...
There we are.
I'll never leave you alone again.
I'm always going to be with you.
It's going to be ok.
Ikuko?
Mommy...
Mommy?
Mommy!
No!
Stay there!
Please... Stop...
I'm not your mother!
Mommy!
No, Ikuko!
Stop!
Ikuko!
I'm...
your mother.
Mommy!
10 years later
-Let's give her a call. -Ok.
Hello? We're here.
Ok, we'll be waiting here... bye.
Is she coming?
Yeah, said she'd be right down.
-Let's get some ice cream.
-Alright!
Come on.
Ikuko, what about you?
What?... No, I'm all set.
I don't remember much from
when I was in kindergarten.
Just that for a very brief period...
I was living together with my mother.
-Mommy! -I'm sorry, honey.
See? There she is!
-I'm so sorry. -Not at all.
Ok, see you tomorrow.
Bye!
B'bye.
Yoshimi and Ikuko Matsubara
Mom?
Welcome home.
You've gotten so big.
Why... ?
Nobody told me.
Have you been living here
all this time?
My friend's house is right near here.
I'm going over there today.
It's next to my old kindergarten.
The Shimizus, do you know them?
That's my kindergarten, isn't it...
over at the bus stop.
This used to be... my glass.
So you're already in high school...
How time flies!
If only I had known, I would've
come to see you long before this.
That's ok.
You came to see me today.
Mom?
Remember when you said,
that you could handle anything
just as long as I was with you?
Of course.
Do you... still feel that way?
Yes, I do.
Good.
Mom...
Could I live here together with you?
I'll tell dad myself, alright?
I'm sure he'd be ok with it.
He has a new wife now,
and more children.
I...
Ikuko...
I'm sorry, honey...
that we can't be together.
Mom?
Mom!
My mother was here all that time,
...protecting me.
Yoshimi Matsubara  Hitomi Kuroki
Ikuko Matsubara (6 years old)
Rio Kanno
Mitsuko Kawai  Mirei Oguchi
Ikuko Hamada (16 years old)
Asami Mizukawa
Cinematography by Junichiro Hayashi
Lighting Director Meicho Tomiyama
Production Designer Katsumi Nakazawa
Music by Kenji Kawai
Edited by Nobuyuki Takahashi
Production Sound Masayuki Iwakura
Sound Mixer Kiyoshi Kakizawa
Theme song by Shikao Suga
The End