- To a wonderful film. You were great.
- Thank you.
- What a romantic you are.
- To the agency and my little protege.
Bless you.
Thank you, daddy.
Eight years at Berlitz,
that's what you learn?
He learned chin the first month
and then chin-chin.
Am I right?
I can't be clever.
It was really beautiful,
what you guys did.
It was beautiful,
and you guys are great.
I love the food here.
The nicest thing about the film
is that we get to handle guns.
- I had never done that.
- Peter.
- Very rare.
- What?
- How are you?
- Wow. Ben, how are you?
Outstanding, sir.
Excuse me.
Ben Sanderson, Marc Nussbaum.
- Of course.
- How are you?
- Sheila.
- Ladies.
- Hi, Ben.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm a big fan of your writing.
I thought Bay of Pigs was great.
Actually, I didn't write it,
I just got the credit. I was fired.
Didn't I talk to you a couple
of years ago when you both worked...
- at MGM with Laddie?
- That's right, by God.
So are you still at ICM?
- I'm at TriStar.
- You're at TriStar.
- You'll have to say hello to Mike.
- I will.
He's not there anymore,
but I'll hunt him down.
- Can I talk to you, please?
- Sure.
- Please?
- Be right back.
Hold the fort, kiddo.
I have my own office this way.
- What is the matter with him?
- He's sick.
I can't help you anymore.
Do you understand?
This is the last time. I promise.
I just need some cash tonight.
- How are you?
- I lost my credit cards.
The money will be on your desk
first thing in the morning.
How's the new one coming along?
I hear you got Dickie Gere.
- That is great, man.
- I got everybody in the movie.
Look, you're sick.
This is all I have in cash.
Please, don't drink it in here.
- Man.
- That's fine, Peter.
I'll messenger it over to you
in the morning.
I don't want it.
I think it would be the best thing
if you don't contact me again.
- What's your name?
- Terri.
- Terri, I am going to buy you a drink.
- I'm okay. Thanks.
Bud, please. Buy the lady a drink
and another one for you.
I'm Benjamin. Ben.
Benny Goodman, that's me.
I think you're sexy. That's right.
Look at those eyes.
Sexy like a kitty cat.
You turn me on
You're not too tall
You're not too short
You're not too round
You're like a cat
The cat in the hat
Look at those eyes.
Honest to God.
You're luminescent, baby.
What?
- You've been drinking all day.
- Of course.
Speaking of drinks,
here is yours.
- Thanks.
- Down that hatch.
And here is mine.
Cheers. Come on.
There we go.
Let's do it to it.
I just thought
of an amazing concept.
What do you say
we finish these...
and we go back
to my apartment on the beach!
I'll throw a movie in the VCR...
and mix you up
a gooey blender drink.
Sound good? Sound sexy?
Bud, give me another.
I really wish you'd come home with me.
You're so cute.
I'm really good in bed too.
Believe me.
And you smell great...
and you look great
and your hair's great.
Look, I've got to wake up early
in the morning.
I have to go. Thank you.
Maybe you shouldn't drink so much.
Maybe I shouldn't breathe so much.
That's it, pal.
We're closing up now.
I'm gonna finish this.
Hey, Mr. Erection,
you want a date?
The room is 20.
You pay for it.
But only because I think...
that the concept of surrender...
fits with the big picture right now.
Hey, get outta the street!
I don't remember
if I started drinking...
because my wife left me or...
my wife left me
'cause I started drinking.
Fuck it anyway!
Next, please.
One moment, sir.
Sign the back
of the check, please.
- Can't you just cash it as it is?
- Is there a problem?
I'm a little shaky right now.
I had brain surgery.
I'll go get some lunch,
and then I'll come back...
and take care of it then.
Next I'll have a gin and tonic.
Do you know what time it is?
You should be drinking coffee.
You're a young guy.
It's none of my business...
but if you could see
what I see...
you wouldn't be doing this
to yourself.
I understand
what you're saying.
I appreciate your concern.
It's not my intention
to make you uncomfortable.
Please, serve me today,
and I'll never come in here again.
If I do, you can 86 me.
Stop fucking with me!
I can 86 you anytime I want to.
I don't give a fuck what you do.
That one's on the house, son.
Were you in Los Angeles
for the earthquake?
- It was pretty scary.
- Did you have a lot of damage?
- Just a little bit.
- Are you desirable?
Are you irresistible?
Maybe if you drank bourbon with me,
it would help.
If you kissed me, and I could taste
the sting in your mouth, it would help.
If you drank bourbon with me naked...
if you smelled of bourbon
as you fucked me, it would help.
It would increase
my esteem for you...
if you poured bourbon on your naked body
and said to me, "Drink this".
If you spread your legs and you had
bourbon dripping from your breasts...
and your pussy and said,
"Drink here"...
then I could
fall in love with you.
Because then I would have a purpose:
to clean you up.
And that would prove...
that I'm worth something.
I'd lick you clean so that you could
go away and fuck someone else.
Our business is
to make our customers happy.
Next, please.
I am back.
I've got my check,
and, baby, I'm ready to sign.
There.
Steady as a fucking rock.
Excuse my French.
Want to have dinner with me?
But what's the back end like?
By the time we're through
with P and A...
the "above the line"
is gonna take it to about 15.
With something like this,
what would Disney think?
Messages.
What did Diller say?
Listen, I'm very busy.
Just kidding.
Can I call you back on this?
Ciao for now.
Could somebody fix the phones
around here?
- Good morning.
- Mr. Simpson's looking for you.
He wants you to go in
as soon as you get...
- Are you all right?
- Outstanding.
But I have to go
to a very important meeting.
Could make a couple million
for the company.
What?
You should go in there now.
- Hi, Bill.
- Take a seat.
We're gonna let you go.
This is too generous, Bill.
We really liked having you around,
but you know how it is.
I'm sorry.
What are you gonna do now?
I thought...
I thought
I'd move out to Las Vegas.
My name is Yuri Botsov.
Where you from, Yuri?
You sure don't sound like you come
from around these parts.
That is very true.
Very good observation.
I am from Latvia.
Very tough place.
I hear this,
but I am not a tough man.
I am a humble man who is here to learn
from my friends in the New World.
This must be Yuri's friend.
Sera is my gift to you all.
You will find her a very willing girl
for each of you...
just as we arranged.
So, I have business to attend.
Please, enjoy.
Do you wanna watch?
Are you scared?
It's all right.
It's okay.
I bring out the best
in the men who fuck me.
It's not easy,
but I'm very good.
It's amazing. I haven't worked
for a really long time...
and I can just turn on a dime.
I can just become
who they want me to be.
I walk into that room,
I know right away...
this is their fantasy,
and I become it.
I'm that service.
I perform it, and I perform it well.
I'm an equation mostly.
Thirty minutes of my body
costs $300.
That's just to get into the room.
It's about $500 after that.
We negotiate.
But it's a performance.
It's definitely a performance.
I am very pleased with how
you've moved up in the world.
It is, after all,
a glamorous world I showed you.
Why did you leave me
in Los Angeles?
Because you are sly.
You knew there was more money
here in Las Vegas.
You don't need to fear me, Sera...
because we belong together.
Don't we?
- Are you lonely?
- I am lonely, Yuri.
So am l.
Janek, we called you last night!
There was no one home.
We're 30 miles
outside of Las Vegas.
Someone saw him there yesterday.
No, this is the end of it!
Yuri knew what he was doing.
That was a red light.
I walk, you stop.
Are you sorry?
Good.
Three towels in each room
and a complimentary bar of soap.
If you run out of soap,
you can buy an extra bar.
Feel free to use our pool,
but use it at your own risk.
- There are three towels in your room.
- Do you have vacancies?
We do.
I'll be with you in a minute.
Linens are provided for you.
Rooms are $29 a night.
You pay at the beginning of each week.
Maid service is optional.
It costs $3.50 a day.
Feel free to use the pool,
but use it at your own risk.
We don't have a lifeguard.
No kids, no pets and no guests
after 11:00 at night.
You've been provided
with three towels.
We expect when you check out
there will still be three towels.
There's a complimentary
bar of soap.
I walked into the room,
and he was lying on the bed.
He had his arms
behind his head...
and there was
just hair everywhere.
He was really, really fat.
He had a large erection.
I remember he was so proud
of his large erection.
I asked him where my money was,
and he pointed to the dresser.
And then I asked him
what he wanted...
and he said,
"Lie down, I'm on top".
He started pounding me
really hard.
I had to bite my tongue
to keep from crying.
He did that for awhile,
and then I started to get up.
He pushed me back down,
and he held my hair.
He was pulling it,
and he stuck his penis in my mouth.
I tried to get up again,
and he said...
"Stay there, baby,
I'm gonna come on your face".
So he did.
Then he rubbed his semen
all over my face and in my hair.
Then he kicked me off the bed
and told me to leave.
- Are you working?
- What do you mean? I'm walking.
Just wait one second.
Great ass!
- Want some?
- Isn't it illegal to drink and drive?
That's pretty funny.
I wonder if you'll take $250
to fuck me?
That is, if you'll come
to my room for one hour...
I will give you $500.
- You're pretty drunk.
- Not really.
My room's not far.
It's The Whole Year lnn.
You could drive with me if you want
or we could walk.
Or I could give you cab fare.
- In the car.
- Whatever you want.
Why don't you give me the money
in the car?
I'm Ben.
I'm Sera.
Sarah with an "H"?
With an "E". S-e-r-a.
You wanna start the engine?
What this room needs
is more booze.
- Can I use the bathroom?
- Of course.
Want a drink?
I'm having one.
Sure. I'll have a shot of tequila,
if you can spare it.
Your drink's here.
For 500 bucks, you can do
pretty much whatever you want.
- You can fuck my ass.
- Oh, my God.
You can come on my face.
Whatever you want to do.
Just keep it out of my hair.
I just washed it.
Just because my feet
were too big in the morning
Just because I can't remember
your mother's name
Just because I put the octopus
in the bed
Just because, because
because, because Bill Cosby
You wanna fuck now?
Maybe something to drink first.
More tequila?
Whatever.
What's the story?
Are you too drunk to come?
I don't care about any of that.
There's time left.
You can have more money.
You can drink all you want.
Just stay.
That's what I want.
I want you to talk or listen.
Just stay.
So, Ben with an "N"...
what brings you to Las Vegas?
Business convention?
I came here
to drink myself to death.
Cashed in all my money...
paid my American Express card...
gonna sell the car tomorrow.
How long is it gonna take
for you to...
drink yourself to death?
I think about four weeks.
I don't know for sure,
but I think.
I got enough
for about 250, $300 a day.
That should do it.
What am l? A luxury?
You're a luxury,
and your meter just ran out.
That's a nice watch.
You do like it?
You can talk
a little bit more.
I don't have to be anywhere.
Talk.
In Los Angeles...
I kept running out of booze
and the store would be closed...
because I forget
to look at my watch.
I used to live in Los Angeles.
But I don't anymore.
I think the tough times
are finally behind me.
There'll always
be bad things, but...
my life is good.
It is as I want it to be.
It's good.
It's good being here with you.
Shit.
Hey, Bill.
How are you?
Is this a full night's work?
I'm really sorry.
It was such a slow night,
and I couldn't score.
What do you think?
You're just a 16-year-old girl
on Hollywood Boulevard?
Is that what you think?
ls that what you play?
Here.
Go ahead.
I could kill you, Sera.
You work tonight,
and you bring me the money.
It doesn't matter how late.
I will.
He cut me a couple of times.
He'd always say,
"Never on the face".
So, he cut me right here.
He cried...
and I felt sorry for him.
In his mind,
I'd done something bad...
but in my mind
I hadn't done anything bad.
He's kind of paranoid.
This ring is a ruby.
It's my lucky ring.
This watch is real gold.
It's not plated.
It's the real thing.
Feel how heavy it is.
- These rings, $3,000.
- One thousand.
One thousand?
Look what you're getting.
It's a ruby. It's my lucky ring.
It's a beautiful thing.
I can put that in.
Two thousand dollars.
- I can't give you more than a thousand.
- But I just added the ring.
- Synthetic ruby.
- Look...
What can I do for you?
Five hundred.
Five hundred dollars
for a 1993 Rolex Daytona watch.
I'll do it.
- How are you doin'?
- I'm doing fine, thank you.
Are you here for the convention?
I didn't think I was that obvious.
- It was just a wild guess.
- My name's Paul, honey.
- Vodka Seven.
- And for the lady?
- Are you ready for another one?
- Sure.
- I'll have a margarita.
- Good choice.
Are you alone?
Or are you using me
to make someone jealous?
Alone. I'm here alone.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Where are you staying?
Right here at the hotel.
Why?
I thought
you might be looking for a date.
"A date"?
What are you, a hooker?
What exactly do you mean
by a date?
I got a wife waiting
for me at home.
- I just came over to talk.
- I'm sorry. I guess I misunderstood.
- I guess you did.
- Just keep your voice down.
I won't bother you again.
Here, have another one on me.
Christ.
Maybe you should give it a miss
for tonight.
I don't know, it's just...
I really like this guy.
I've never felt anything...
for anyone I've ever been with,
as a trick.
It's weird.
I feel kind of confused about it.
We were with each other
only one night...
but I felt like
the relationship...
I felt like there was
a relationship being formed.
I was kind of scared.
I don't think
I should see him again.
But I look for him.
I went out last night.
I was looking for him.
Where's your car?
I sold it this morning.
I'm gonna take cabs from now on.
What's it tonight?
Another 500 to watch you sleep?
- What's up?
- I was looking for you tonight.
I don't know
if you have a boyfriend...
or a girlfriend...
but, if you have
some free time...
I thought maybe
we could get some dinner.
Are you serious?
I think you know I'm serious.
I'll pay you if you like,
but I just want to see you.
I can't have dinner with you.
We could get prime rib.
They've got it on sale for $2.99.
I love that dress.
I had a really good night.
I think things
are finally picking up.
We made so much money.
Look.
Come here.
Now listen.
Do you hear?
They're talking about me.
Are you all right?
Get out.
Do not come back here.
I'll not see you again.
Do you still wanna have dinner?
I think I put too much salt on it.
- It's not good.
- It's good.
- Why are you a drunk?
- Why am I a drunk?
Is that really
what you want to ask me?
Then this is our first date
or our last.
Until now,
I wasn't sure it was either.
First.
It's our first.
I just wanna know.
Why are you killing yourself?
Interesting choice of words.
I don't remember.
I just know that I want to.
Is your drinking a way
to kill yourself?
- Or killing myself is a way to drink.
- Very clever.
Shoot.
Can I have another one?
What are you thinking?
Are you angry?
Good night.
- I had the most wonderful...
- Why don't you stay at my place tonight?
Look, you're pretty drunk.
- I like you. I trust you.
- Wow. That's astonishing, Sera.
I hate to think of you
in that cheesy motel.
I'll move to a real smart hotel tomorrow
if it makes you feel better.
Let's talk about tomorrow.
Do you want to do something?
We'll talk about it tonight
at my place.
I'm not much good in the sack.
It's not about sex.
I'll make you up a bed
on the sofa.
We'll talk till late.
We'll sleep till late.
As you know,
I am my own boss.
Do it, Ben.
I'll do it.
This is the home of an angel.
- Are you okay?
- Of course.
You look extremely beautiful.
I do?
It's really weird because...
you know...
it's just like
this thing's happening...
really quickly.
I just don't know
what's going on.
Just the second I met him,
and the way I said my name.
I just said, "Hi, my name's Sera,"
and that's not what I do.
And it's just...
It's all happening really quickly.
I just felt like
we've been together for a long time.
It just felt so easy...
and I felt like...
I felt like I was me.
I didn't feel like I was...
trying to be somebody else.
When is your rent coming up
at the motel?
What do you mean?
I think you should go
and bring all your stuff over here.
- Sera, you are crazy.
- So?
Don't you think you'll get
a little bored living with a drunk?
- That's what I want.
- You haven't seen the worst of it.
These last few days,
I've been very controlled.
I knock things over
and throw up all the time.
Right now I feel really good.
You're like an antidote that mixes
with the liquor and keeps me in balance.
But that won't last forever.
All right,
you go back to your motel.
I'll go back to my glamorous life
of being alone.
The only thing I have to come home to
is a bottle of mouthwash...
to take the taste
of come out of my mouth.
I'm tired of being alone.
That's what I'm tired of.
Don't you like me, Ben?
What you don't understand is...
No. See? No.
What?
You can never, never...
ask me to stop drinking.
Do you understand?
I do.
I really do.
I'm nuts about you.