For some, time passes slowly.
An hour can seem an eternity.
For others,
there's never enough.
For the Tucks, it didn't exist.
Time is like a wheel...
turning and turning,
never stopping
and the woods are the center,
the hub of the wheel.
It began the first week
of summer
a strange and breathless time,
when accident, or fate
bring lives together
when people are led
to do things
they've never done before.
On this summer's day,
not so very long ago
the wheel set lives in motion
in mysterious ways.
It set Mae Tuck out
in her wagon
for the village of Treegap
to meet her two sons as she did
once every ten years.
Ma!
Miles!
Jesse!
Oh...!
Oh, I missed you.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I couldn't wait to see you.
I missed you, Jesse.
Oh, wait,
I got something for you.
Oh, look at you.
I got something.
Here, look.
The Eiffel Tower.
Would you look at that.
Got it in Paris, France.
Oh, Mom,
you've never seen anything
- So tall in your life.
- Hello...
Oh, I got something else.
I got something else.
How are you, old friend?
Your favorite... chocolates.
Oh, I've died
and gone to Heaven.
Oh, Jesse.
Miles...
Miles.
Give your mother a hug.
Ten years.
You're as cozy as barbed wire.
I have you back.
Winifred!
Yes, Mother?
I need a new name.
One that's not all worn out
from being called so much.
Come inside this instant.
You're getting filthy!
Ow! I can scarcely breathe.
"You must suffer
to be beautiful."
So say the French.
The French are crazy.
For Winnie Foster
one thing was true:
the heat of summer was not
nearly as stifling
as the formality of her life.
With every passing day
the feeling grew stronger.
She was coming closer
to the end of something
and moving towards
the beginning of something new.
Change was in the air.
It was only a question of when.
Wait for me in the car.
I won't be a minute.
In the car, Mrs. Foster.
Throw it home! Throw it home!
Come on, throw it home!
- Go!
- Run to me!
Yay!
No, no, no, no, no.
Too large for tea cakes.
None of these will do.
I prefer petit fours.
What kind of a funny hat
is that?
Well, look'ee here.
If it's not Miss Moneybags
in her fancy car.
What's the matter?
Don't want
to get your feet dirty?
Well, I'm sorry, Mrs. Foster.
Not much call
for such treats out here.
Well, I could just make them up
for you, special.
Winnie Foster?
You've got to be kidding!
Wow!
Winnie, run!
Run, Winnie, run!
Throw it! Throw it!
Throw it home! Come on!
Slide, Winnie, slide!
Winifred!
Oh, and they had
their arms crossed
and you see, the lines
were perfectly square.
Come here, come here.
I want to teach you. Come on.
Oh, all the way from France.
How about that?
Oh, look. Look-Look at this one.
I want to see, Pop. Let me see.
Look it.
Oh! Aah, he shot me!
Oh, I'm dead!
Oh, oh, my!
- Oh, my!
Oh, you'll have to see this one.
Miles, look at this!
Oh... let's see.
Okay, come here,
I want to show you.
All right.
Good to have you home, son.
I'm glad to see you.
And the family together.
But don't get used to it.
War's coming, I hear.
I'm joining up.
I'm going to fight the Huns.
Get as far away
from this place as I can.
Oh, you think
that'll solve things, do you?
You haven't had enough killing
for two lifetimes?
Somebody's on to us.
I know it.
There's a man who's been
following us
and we've lost him
several times, but...
he keeps coming back.
I think he knows something.
This man...
Jesse...
- Whoo!
We're being tracked.
Oh, Miles, we lost him.
Don't go spoiling everything.
Yeah, we lost him, Jess...
but he keeps coming back.
It was only a matter of time
before someone found us.
The world is closing in.
Entire forest is almost gone.
All except this little wood.
I saw tire marks down
on the lower wash...
a few weeks ago.
There'll be more.
I don't want anyone going
to town.
Not for anything,
and that's that.
Tuck.
You see any strangers
in the woods getting too close
you know what to do.
No exceptions.
Our time here is almost done.
I can feel it.
You'll never catch one that way.
Do you know
about catching fireflies?
Afraid not, never tried.
I prefer... bigger game.
Though I suspect the strategy
is much the same.
Strategy?
One must never announce
one's presence to the prey.
One must become part
of the scenery...
invisible...
almost disappear.
And be patient
until the exact, right moment
arrives...
Take a prisoner.
For you?
No, thank you.
You're quite right.
A girl of your age
should find...
trapping suitors
more interesting
than trapping insects, anyway.
Far easier, I might add.
Have you lived here long?
Forever. Why?
I'm... looking
for some old friends
who live hereabouts.
Thought you might
help me find them.
My father
practically built Treegap.
He knows everyone.
Perhaps he can help you.
Perhaps.
I quite like talking to you.
Winifred?
Winifred, who are you talking to
out there?
I don't know.
He hasn't told me his name.
Good evening, madam.
Please forgive my intrusion.
This young lady tells me
you've lived here forever.
I thought you might know
of a certain family
goes by the name of...
I hardly know everyone,
nor do I want to.
And I don't stand outside
discussing such a thing
with... strangers.
Then I beg your pardon.
Good evening, young lady.
Madam.
This is why I worry
about you, Winifred.
You don't have the sense
not to talk to a man like that.
A proper education gains one
entré into society.
Your mother and I have given
this a great deal of thought.
Middlehouse Academy for Girls
in Pensford,
has an excellent reputation.
Middlehouse?
But that's a terrible place,
everyone says so.
It's like a jail.
Nonsense.
Girls emerge from there
as refined young ladies
well-versed in etiquette
and manners,
both of which
you are sorely lacking.
But I don't want to be
one of those girls.
Which is precisely why
you must go.
I cannot let
your unbridled nature
ruin your chances
for a respectable future.
Winifred... I'm sorry...
but we have to do
what's best for you.
I won't do it.
I'm not like those girls.
I won't go!
Winifred!
Winnie Foster was to be sent
500 miles away to be educated.
But what her parents didn't
understand
was she only wanted to step
just outside her fence...
so she did.
What in these quiet woods
should be so forbidden?
Winnie had always sensed
a mystery
waiting for her there.
It was a place so entirely
different from what she knew
so far away from her tight,
pruned world.
Ah!
Ah...
How long have you been
standing there?
Not long at all.
I was only walking past,
and I...
Well, you shouldn't...
be in these parts of the woods.
It's best you turn around
and go home.
Well, go on, now, get!
Excuse me,
but I own these woods, and...
I'll go on and get
when I want to.
You own these woods?
Yes, I do.
What's your name?
Winifred.
Winnie... Foster.
A Foster?
Well, I'll be.
Is that a fact?
Well... Winnie Foster,
like I was saying
you need to turn around
and go home.
It just so happens
that I was on my way home
before you made
your rude suggestion
and I would be happy
to continue on my way
if I only knew which way to go.
In other words, you're lost?
I'll point you home.
I'd be much obliged.
But I want a drink first.
Wait... no!
No!
What?
You don't want that water.
Uh, it's poisoned.
I saw you drink some.
Well, now I'm feeling sick.
You don't look ill.
I'm dry as dust.
I said, leave it alone!
Let go of me! My father
will have you arrested!
You're not going to go
and tell him, now, are you?
Hey! Come back!
Don't run away!
Come back!
Where you going so fast, Miss?
Miles, wait!
- No! No!
- You know what Tuck said, Jesse.
- No exceptions.
- Help!
You can't do this.
Stop! Let go!
We can't.
Miles!
Miss Foster!
Where are you?!
Ho.
We're stopping here.
- Not a word out of you, hear me?
Miles!
- What are you doing?
- No!
Let the poor girl go.
There's no reason
to be frightened, young lady.
I caught her at the spring
with Jesse.
She's a Foster.
Oh, Lord.
It's finally happened.
I want to go home, please.
I want to go home.
There, there, child.
Please don't cry.
We're not bad people.
We'll take you home
just as soon as we can.
I promise.
Miles, go find your father.
He's across the lake.
He'll know what to do with her.
Tell Jesse I'm going to fix
that mouth of his.
I've heard that.
Have you?
It's, it's my little music box.
I found it
in the forest one day.
Just waiting for me, I expect.
I've had it a long, long time.
Oh!
I put my baby boys
to bed with it every night.
Gave 'em such sweet dreams.
I'm sure my boys
didn't mean you any harm.
Then why did they bring me here
this way?
Why am I here?
You have every right
to be upset.
And I know your family
must be...
worried sick about you.
Where's the child?
She's no child... Angus.
Does she know?
Why do you think
I brought her...?
Yeah, but now she knows
about us, thanks to you.
Shh! Shh!
She's a Foster,
she only knows...
Know what?
Miss Foster,
this is my husband, Angus Tuck.
Angus, meet Miss Foster.
Hello, Miss Foster.
She's the most important event
that's taken place in this house
in 80 years.
You hungry?
Oh, well, let's, let's all eat.
Yeah.
Jesse, pass your mother
a plate, please?
Mmm, where's the fish?
Oh, they weren't biting
for some reason.
'Cause Pa can't fish?
Don't matter. There's plenty.
I catch fish.
If there's no fish,
there's no fish
if you keep scaring
the fish away.
Mmm, this looks good.
Oh! Isn't this nice?
Everybody sitting down together
and having Miss Foster here.
It's just like having a party.
My father will come looking
for me.
Your father... will cut down
the entire forest
the way things are changing
around here.
Make himself a very rich man.
Oh, now, let's not ruin
a perfectly good meal
with a lot of talk.
My father has plenty of money.
He'll pay.
Anything you want.
We don't want your father's
money, Miss Foster.
Then let me go home.
We will.
We'll let you go home...
just like I promised.
Directly.
We'll need to be able
to trust her first
before we're sending her
back to her folks.
Trust her? We can't trust her.
Or any normal people.
She'll turn on us in a second.
No, she won't.
You're a fool.
You don't even realize
what you've done here.
Him.
It's him.
Robert!
I expect you to find her, Henry.
That's your job.
I've already wired her
description down the main line.
They'll keep a lookout
and we'll get up a search party
come morning.
My wife is certain that this man
wearing a yellow suit
has something to do
with Winifred's disappearance.
And Miss Foster says so
based on...?
Her instincts.
Hmm.
Well, maybe you better step
in here, Mr. Foster.
Am I whom you're looking for?
I do believe I fit
the description.
My wife said she saw you
talking to my daughter.
Yes, I did.
She's a charming girl,
full of fire.
Perhaps too much.
She's gone, is she?
Looks like she... ran away.
Did she now?
Somehow I'm not surprised.
My daughter did not... run away.
And I'm not interested
in what surprises you, sir.
I want to know
if you know anything
of her whereabouts.
No, Mr. Foster.
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but I do not.
I am quite coincidentally here
in search of someone myself.
I'm seeking a family
that used to live
in these environs.
I thought the constable could
help me locate them,
but ironically, Mr. Foster
your daughter thought
you could help.
Name of Tuck.
Long lost relatives.
l-I can't help you.
Nor I you.
At least not now.
However, I'd be happy
to search your woods
for you, Mr. Foster.
I'm rather talented
at finding people.
I just might meet with success.
Good evening, Constable.
Find out what happened
to her, Henry.
Please.
She's our only child.
Angus made that cradle.
Brought it all the way
from Scotland.
Oh, it's rocked a few Tucks.
There you go.
The breeze off the lake
will keep you cool all night.
The boys sleep up in the loft
when they're home
so you'll have your privacy.
Oh, that corset looks painful.
May I help you off with it?
Oh, honestly, I can't understand
why women torture themselves
this way.
It's no way to live.
Do you have a daughter?
A granddaughter.
And a grandson.
Anna and Beau.
Oh, Miles loved them so.
What happened?
They died.
Their mother, too.
I'm afraid the good parts
of Miles died along with them.
You'll have to forgive
what's left of him.
I'm sorry.
Well, it's... it's the way
things are, Miss Foster.
Can I call you Winnie?
Do you have brothers
and sisters?
No, it's only me.
My mother...
There.
So where do they go?
Oh, they go different places,
do different things.
Miles can do carpentry
and he's good with his hands.
Jesse, now, he seems
to have settled himself.
Of course, then, he's...
he's young yet.
Well...
I hope you will be
comfortable here.
It's a good feeling
having another woman here.
Try and get some sleep now.
Hello?
Have you lost your way, friend?
Not hardly, Reverend.
I'm looking
for a family name... Tuck.
Are you familiar with it?
Tuck. Tuck?
I'm afraid I can't help you.
There are no Tucks
in this cemetery that I know of.
No, I wouldn't think so.
Ha!
Or in any other.
Tell me, Reverend
you who have attended
so many deathbeds...
what is it people most desire
as they face the end
of their lives?
More time?
Well, I suppose.
Exactly.
They'd give almost anything,
I imagine, for one more year.
Imagine what they'd give
for all eternity.
Sir, I don't quite understand
what...
You will.
Reverend, are you prepared
to die right now, this instant?
If it's God's will.
What if it is my will?
What if you could be eternal?
Right now, this instant?
Without having to face
the uncertainty of death?
Hmm?
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
No muss, no fuss.
Invincible to disease.
Never having to suffer
the stench and rot of old age.
Forever young.
You speak blasphemy, sir.
Fluently.
Good night, Reverend.
Hey, Winnie Foster, you asleep?
Not anymore.
Good.
Hey.
Listen.
How would you like
to see the Eiffel Tower?
What?
Someday.
No, now.
While the day is still ours.
Get those dogs over there.
Yes, sir.
Come on, boys, let's go.
Henry, this is
Winifred's nightgown.
Give it to the dog handlers.
Start in the north end.
Let's split up
when we get to the lake.
We'll find her.
I know we will.
Winifred!
Miss Foster!
Winnie!
Winifred Foster!
Miss Foster!
Winifred!
Over here!
I found something!
There it is.
This is the Eiffel Tower?
The one in Paris,
it's pretty tall.
Mine's two feet higher.
Here.
Come on.
Have you really seen
the real one in Paris?
Yes, I have.
And climbed 1,652 stairs
to the top.
Much easier than this.
Yes.
You doing all right?
I think so.
You're doing great.
Here.
If I went to the Eiffel Tower
I would take
one of those elevators.
Not with me.
You'd take off your shoes
and walk up
every single solitary step.
How old are you?
Do you really want to know?
Yes.
104.
I'm serious.
So am I.
Let's just call it 17.
There's my Paris.
The view from the Eiffel Tower
can't be better than this.
I've seen a lot of views,
and this is one of the best.
Come on.
Winnie Foster was beginning
to lose track of time.
Had she been there a day,
a week, a month?
It seemed to Winnie
that the Tucks lived in a way
the rest of the world
had forgotten.
They were never in a hurry
and did things the slow way.
For the first time
Winnie felt free to explore,
to ask questions, to play.
Me?
I'm going to see the world.
Every speck of it.
Heck, I may even find some
new continents or something.
I mean, I've been
to a lot of places
but the world is huge!
Jesse Tuck,
what-what are you doing?
What does it look like?
Woo-hoo!
Woo! Ah, whoo.
Come on!
I can't!
Why?
You're not afraid of a little
cold water, are you?
No.
Are you afraid of me?
Well, what then?
I can't swim.
You're joshing me.
I wish I were.
So, you're afraid you'll drown,
right?
Swallow too much water,
sink to the bottom and die.
Thank you for putting it
so vividly.
And, yes,
considering I'd sink like a rock
drowning is a fair concern.
Well, I guess I'm just going
to have to enjoy this
all by myself.
Hmm...
Hmm!
Ah, Jesse!
Hey, hey, it's okay.
Come here, come here, come here.
I've got you, I've got you.
I've got you, relax.
Relax against me.
You all right?
I think so.
Whoo!
You did it!
I did it!
Ah, it feels wonderful.
I'm weightless.
That's 'cause we're
carrying you, see?
The water and me.
We're both carrying you.
You like the feeling?
I love it.
Jesse, don't let go!
It's okay, it's okay.
There's no chance of that,
Winnie Foster.
I'm never going to let you go.
You know, I don't like
being laughed at by a cheat.
Now "cheat" is a nasty word,
sir.
I much prefer "card sharp."
You are looking for trouble,
aren't you, mister?
Yes, sir, I sure am.
Going outside!
Come on!
Perhaps next time...
He can't hurt me!
Whoo!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me, citizen.
You hear that?
Tuck says
it's the most melancholy sound
in all of nature.
Listen.
Just listen.
They're playing for you.
Whoo! Yeah!
I wish this moment
could last forever.
Forever?
You want to spend forever
with me, Winnie?
I do.
You know, we could see
the world together.
We could do
everything together.
Have a million moments
like this one that...
never, never stop.
There's a part about us
you don't know...
the part I've sworn
not to tell you.
The secret?
The reason you don't want anyone
to find out about you?
I knew it.
You're... you're bank robbers
or grifters.
You are the first human
I've ever met
I wanted to know the truth.
Jesse Tuck, you're the first
human I've ever met
that I've ever wanted to...
to...
...to do that.
Winnie, listen.
Remember the giant oak tree
at the center of the wood
where we met?
The little spring bubbling up
you saw me drink from?
You remember when I told you
I was 104 years old?
Well...
it's the honest truth.
I'm going to live forever.
I'm never going to change.
The same with Miles
and Tuck and Mae.
Something happened to us.
As far as I know, I'm...
I'm going to be 17
until the end of the world.
It's the spring, Winnie.
The water,
something's wrong with it.
It stops you
right where you are.
If you had a drink of it today,
you'd stay just like you are.
Don't you wish he'd told you...
before you kissed him?
Did he tell you
immortality isn't all the
preachers crack it up to be?
Hey, leave her alone, Miles.
Oh, now... you want her
to hear it, Jesse boy.
She's the first person
you want to tell the truth to.
You just don't want me
to have what you lost.
Stop this...
...both of you
and tell me the truth.
I want to know.
We all had a drink...
...except for the cat...
that's important.
The water tasted like...
Heaven.
Floated over your tongue
like a cloud.
Tuck carved a "T" in the trunk,
to mark where we'd been.
We moved on west, looking
for a place to settle down.
Put up a house for Mae and Tuck
and a little shed
for Jesse and me.
That was the first time we
figured there was something...
peculiar.
Jesse fell 30 feet,
landed right on his neck.
He was up on his feet again
before Mae could work up
a good cry.
Didn't hurt him a bit.
No broken bones... nothing.
That's not all.
Not by a long shot.
Things began to happen.
Some brushpoppers mistook
Mae's horse for a deer.
Thing is,
the bullets didn't kill him.
Barely even left a mark.
Then Tuck got bitten
by a rattlesnake,
and you know what?
He didn't die...
...but the cat did
of old age.
And Miles got married.
Daddy!
Beau.
Little Anna.
Tuck figured it early on.
It's the spring.
We all drank from it,
even the horse.
Had to be... the source
of our changelessness.
I begged her to come back...
for me
and find the spring
and drink from it.
The children, too.
It was our only hope
to be together.
She made up her mind
I'd sold my soul
to the Devil...
... and she left me.
She took my babies with her.
Everyone...
pulled away after that.
There was talk of witchcraft...
black magic.
I went looking for wars
to fight...
and I saw brave men die
at Vera Cruz...
and then Gettysburg...
thousands,
in the blink of an eye...
...but not me.
I couldn't die...
...like little Anna.
The influenza took her
before she's 15.
And Beau.
He'd be almost 80 now
if he were still alive.
And my sweet...
...my sweet young bride.
She died in an insane asylum...
...old and alone.
But I'm still here.
I'm still here.
Winnie Foster, you're the only
other person in the world
who knows about us.
We'll have to have a talk.
Pa.
Come on.
Look around you.
It's teeming life.
It's flowers and trees
and frogs.
It's... it's all part
of the wheel.
It's always changing;
it's always growing
like you, Winnie.
Your life is never the same.
You were once a child.
Now, you are
about to become a woman.
One day, you'll grow up
and you'll do
something important.
You'll have children,
maybe, and then one day
you'll go out...
just like the flame of a candle.
You'll make way for new life.
That's a certainty.
That's the natural way
of things.
And then, there's us.
What we Tucks have,
you can't call it living.
We just... are.
We're like rocks,
stuck at the side of a stream.
Listen to me.
Winnie, you know
a dangerous secret.
If people find out
about the spring
they'll trample
all over each other
to get to that water.
There's one thing I've learned
about people.
Many will do anything,
anything not to die
and they'll do anything
to keep from living their life.
Do you want
to stay stuck as you are
right now, forever?
I've just got
to make you understand.
I don't want to die.
Is that wrong?
No.
No human does...
but i-it's part of the wheel...
the same as being born.
You can't have living
without dying.
Don't be afraid of death,
Winnie.
Be afraid of the unlived life.
Your tea, sir.
She's with them now.
I came directly here,
knowing how tormented
you must be.
We-we just want her back safely.
Course you do.
Dreadful business, kidnapping.
Fortunate I was witness.
I'm perhaps the only person...
who knows where to find her.
Just what is your game, sir?
What is my game?
You detect in me a playful mood?
"Playful" is not
the word I had in mind.
What I have in mind
is a simple, clear-cut trade.
You see,
I very much like your woods
not for their timber, mind you
but for their natural assets.
Wh-What is it you want?
You want your daughter.
I want your woods.
You're involved in this,
aren't you?
If you have touched
my daughter...!
I have my faults, Mr. Foster.
Kidnapping is not amongst them.
These are rough people,
the ones who took her.
No telling what they might do.
Unless we do what you say.
Give the man whatever he wants.
Done and done.
Nice to have things legal
and tidy, don't you agree?
You're an intelligent,
reasonable man, Mr. Foster.
I'm seldom wrong
as a judge of character.
Have your friendly constable
on hand
to make
the appropriate arrests.
Your terrible ordeal is
as good as over.
I'll get there before you.
We have to move quickly.
They were packing to leave.
What kind of horrible people
must these kidnappers be?
HENRY:
There is evil in the world,
Mr. Foster.
There aren't fences high enough
to keep it out.
Bring your men
directly to my house.
I'm going with you.
It isn't fair, Tuck.
No, it isn't...
but when has life
ever been fair?
How am I going to take you home
when I can't make my feet move
from this spot?
If I could die tomorrow,
I'd do it...
just to spend one more night
with you.
Forgive me for interrupting
such a tender moment.
Hello, Winifred.
Everyone's been so worried
about you.
I'm relieved
to find you so well.
You know this man?
I met him once.
Hello, Mr. Tuck.
You have no idea what a pleasure
it is to meet you.
You're the man
who's been following my boys.
Been expecting you.
Yes, and here I am.
Tell me, is it a relief...
to finally be discovered?
Over a century of hiding out
must have taken its toll on you.
Who are you?
And how do you know so much
about us?
I first heard about your family
from my grandmother.
She knew a woman
in a mental facility
who used to...
rant and ramble about a family
who never grew old
and never died.
This woman,
she used to call out a name.
What was it, now?
Anna.
Crazy old woman.
Kept on talking
about a music box.
It seems the melody had a
calming effect on her children.
I'm sure you know it, Mrs. Tuck?
You have no right...
to come to our home...
and bring us such pain.
There, good mother.
I mean no harm.
Tell us, sir.
What is it you want?
Well, you see, the Fosters
have given me these woods
in exchange
for bringing young Winifred
back home to them.
I have the papers,
all signed and legal.
Gives me the rights
to the forest
and everything in it.
Don't be alarmed.
I'll let you stay here...
on my land
if you prove cooperative.
Cooperative?
I want you to take me
to the spring.
I don't know what you mean.
Don't insult me, Mr. Tuck.
It's immediately clear to me
that the water's powers
have been wasted on...
unimaginative people like you.
I intend to make
this fountain of youth,
as the simpletons would call it
available to those
who deserve it...
for a price, of course.
You'll die of old age
before I'll take you.
Is that so?
Then, perhaps Winifred will!
No!
Jesse!
Yes!
Bravo!
Come now, Winifred.
I'm feeling thirsty.
Show me where the spring is.
Perhaps I'll let you have
a drink.
After all...
...then we can spend...
eternity together.
Winnie, Winnie, come here.
It's okay. It's okay, I gotcha.
Pa.
There they are!
Winnie Foster!
I see her!
I got her!
Circle around to the right!
Watch the water!
Go!
Don't let anyone get away!
Jesse, come on.
Winnie!
Block that trail!
It's my father.
Keep them alive!
Be careful of the girl!
Winnie!
Let's go!
Wait...
Get on.
Behind the house, men!
He's setting the house on fire!
Winnie!
You're all right.
We found you. You're safe.
You're safe now.
Everything's all right.
Winnie.
Hyah!
The hall clock chimed the hour.
Outside, the wind was still.
Everything, it seemed,
was waiting.
We just want to understand
what happened.
Winnie... try, please.
They didn't kidnap me.
I was with them
because I wanted to be.
- She doesn't know
what she's saying.
The Tucks were kind to me.
They're my friends.
If they didn't kidnap you,
why on earth
did that woman club that man
over the head with a shotgun?
Because Mae Tuck
was protecting me.
Doesn't matter anyway.
That fella died.
It's a murder charge now.
I didn't much like the man
but that won't stop
that poor woman from hanging.
Miss is an eyewitness.
She'll have to testify.
Oh, my God.
I figured you might want this.
Doesn't exist,
far as I'm concerned.
I sure am sorry about all this.
Good day.
Thank you, Henry.
Winnie.
Jesse!
Oh, it's you.
I was afraid
I would never see you again.
I need you to help me.
I need you to help us.
Mae can't go to the gallows.
She won't die.
She can't die.
They're going to find out
our secret.
We have to get them out.
Help me!
Please, help me!
Somebody, help me!
Please, someone help!
Please! Help!
All right.
Help me, please!
All right!
Help!
PI... Please!
Help me! You have to stop them!
They're after me!
Miss F... Miss Fo...
Who's after you?
The people who kidnapped me!
They're going
to take me away again!
My parents couldn't stop them!
They're right outside!
You have to stop them, please!
Help!
They'll kill me if they find me!
Please, they're going
to kill me, please!
Stay right there!
I'll handle this.
Hurry!
Help!
Come out and meet your doom!
Hell is upon you!
Stop right there!
You're under arrest!
Come on, we have to hurry.
The boys are outside.
Stay back, now!
I'll shoot!
My dear, sweet Winnie.
What I wouldn't do to keep you.
I wish you were ours...
for Jesse.
For all of us.
You have to hurry
and get away from here.
Winnie...
Winnie, come with me.
There's nothing for you here.
We can be together forever.
If she comes with us,
they'll hunt us down.
They'll never stop looking.
Tuck is right.
If I go with you
it'll be too dangerous
for all of you.
I can't go without you.
You have to.
Go back to the spring.
Drink from it.
When it's safe...
I'll come back for you.
Will you?
I have to show you
the Eiffel Tower, don't I?
1,652 steps to the top.
Winnie...
until we're together again...
wake up with the dawn.
I will.
We got to go...
before it's too late.
Winnie Foster...
I will love you
till the day I die!
She's going fast
but you can have a couple
of minutes with her.
How are you?
"...and to Almighty God
"we commend the soul
of our sister
"and we commit her body
to the ground.
Earth to earth, ashes to ashes,
dust to dust..."
"...Resurrection
into eternal life
"through our Lord Jesus Christ;
"at whose coming in glorious
Majesty to judge the World
"the Earth and the Sea
shall give up their Dead;
"and the corruptible bodies
of those who sleep in him
"shall be changed, and made like
unto his own glorious Body;
"according to the mighty working
whereby he is able
to subdue
all things unto himself."
Mother?
I was just wondering
what it is about these woods
you love so much.
Mother, are you all right?
I'm going to miss her, too.
Oh...
Every time I look at you,
you're different.
I'm losing you, too.
I'm right here.
Forgive me, Winnie.
I just wanted to keep you
my little girl forever.
Go back to the spring.
When it's safe,
I'll come back for you.
ANGUS:
What we Tucks have,
you can't call it living.
We just... are.
We're like rocks stuck
at the side of a stream.
The first weeks of summer
were long over.
There was a feeling
that the wheel
was turning again...
... slowly now,
but soon to go faster.
Winnie and her family
left Treegap to see the world.
She wasn't certain
what herjourney might bring
but this much she knew...
it would be something
of her own choosing.
For some, time passes slowly.
An hour can seem an eternity.
For others,
there's never enough.
For Jesse Tuck,
it didn't exist.
Tuck said it to Winnie
the summer she turned 15:
Do not fear death,
but rather the unlived life.
You don't have to live forever.
You just have to live.
And she did.