SMOKEY : I know
you don't smoke weed.
I know this,
but I'm gonna get you high today
'cause it's Friday,
you ain't got no job,
and you ain't got shit to do.
SONG: # Yeah
# Ooh
# Tryin' to see
another day
# Well
# Tryin' to find
a better way
# Got my mind
# On my money
# And my money
# On my mind
# Ain't got time
# To be lonely
# 'Cause my woman
takes all of my time
# And I know
# You can't wait
until tomorrow
# I wanna see
what tomorrow brings
# Whoo
# Tryin' to see
another day
# Well
# Tryin' to find
a better way
# Tryin' to see
another day... #
(Snoring)
# Tryin' to find
a better way
# Ain't got time
for my homie
# He's somewhere high... #
Mmm...hrrm...
Give me
the 2-piece special,
lots of hot sauce,
and all the fries
you can give me.
(Snoring)
Thank you. Thank you.
# Until tomorrow
# I wanna see
what tomorrow brings
# Whoo
# See a better day
# Tryin' to find,
find a better way
# I know
# Tryin' to see
another day
# Tryin' to find
a better way... #
CRAlG: For most people,
Friday is just the day
before the weekend.
But after this Friday,
the neighbourhood
will never be the same.
(Bangs on door)
(Hits toe)
Oh, shit.
What's up?
Good morning.
Are you prepared
for Jehovah's return?
Because if you're not,
I have a pamphlet here that--
Well, fuck you.
Half-dead motherfucker.
Come on, sister.
Yeah.
(Chuckles)
Uh-oh.
I gotcha.
Gotcha baby.
That's right.
(LOUD ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
Stop!
Hey! Wait!
lce-cream!
Oh, shit.
Wait!
lce-cream!
What you gonna do?
Hi.
Hey, hey, hey, hey hey, hey!
(Kids stop shouting)
Damn.
What you want?
What you got?
Boy, what the fuck you want?
Gimme some chili fritos.
Come here.
Come here!
Step aside.
What's up, Big Perm?
I mean Big Worm.
You sell that bud?
I sold some.
Give me the rest.
Somebody want a couple
20s around Compton.
Man, I was just bullshittin' ya.
You know I sold that shit.
Then count out my money.
Hurry up!
Don't you see we havin'
grown folks business?
Damn.
Now shut the hell up.
20...
40, 60, 80...
100...
120, 140...
Hey, man, that's $ 100.
Stop playin' with me, Smokey.
You know what happened?
You gonna laugh your ass off.
You know Craig?
Craig got fired yesterday.
What the fuck
that gotta do with me?
Let me explain.
We was talkin' over
all our problems, right?
And you know how WE do it.
We started getting high.
Nigger, we got fucked up!
Look, nigger, I'm gonna
be here 10:00 on the dot.
Not 10:03. Not 10:36.
If you ain't got my money
or my bud,
I'm killin' you AND him.
You gonna kill me?
Get the fuck
out of my face, man.
Baby!
Can I have my chili fritos?
You can't have shit.
I'm closed, fat boy.
Then give me my money back.
My money.
Mama!
Man, I hate him.
What'd he say?
Huh?
Oh, he just said for us
to pay him at 10:00.
What you mean "us"?
Man, that fool
ain't gonna do nothin'.
Man, I know you didn't tell...
Worm!
What you doin'?
Craig.
Worm!
Damn.
What's up?
What'd you tell him?
I just told him
we were smokin', man,
and that we were just chillin'.
Man, you were smokin'!
I smoked half a little
piece a joint with you.
Man, that fool
ain't gonna do nothin'.
What'd he say?
He said if we don't
pay him by 10:00,
he gonna bust a cap
in both our asses.
We need to pay him. He crazy!
Let's stick together.
I can't believe you got me
in the mix with this fool!
Aw, man, I didn't make
you smoke that joint.
Might as well.
"Come on, Craig, man.
"Stimulate your mind, man.
"It's Friday.
I'm gonna get you high."
Why you bringin' up old shit?
I could knock...
Hey, Craig,
I left my purse
in your house.
Can I go get it?
Yeah. Come on.
(RAP MUSIC
PLAYS IN BACKGROUND)
# Big booty hos
# Hump with it
# Hoochie mamas
# Hump with it... #
Fool...
Where Craig at?
Fool?
Oh, he in the house.
(DOOR OPENS)
Ahem.
Uh-uh.
Hell, no.
Psssh.
Yeah.
Uh-uh.
Who is that, bitch?
Yeah, who was that bitch?
CRAlG: Who you talkin' to?
Nigger, I'm talkin' to you!
Now, who is she?
That's just Debbie
from down the street.
So? What the hell's
she doin' in there?
She was just...
just go in the house!
What you lookin' at?
Get yo' ass in the house!
Hurry up!
I'm going in to straighten
this girl out.
I'll be right back.
Alright, man.
I'm gonna go to my crib,
man. My stomach hurt.
Ey.
Come back!
Alright.
Mama!
Shit.
(Grunts)
What the hell you want,
boy? Damn!
Mr Jones, can I use
your bathroom, please?
What you gonna do,
number 1 or number 2?
Number 2.
Shit.
You ain't gonna drop
no stinkin' loads here.
If anybody drops
a stinkin' load,
it's gonna be me.
Mr...Mr Jones!
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Man!
Fuck.
Mama!
Shit.
# La la la la la la
# La la la la... #
Smokey!
Smokey.
Smokey, what the hell
you doing back here?
Hey, nothin', man.
Hey, I'm fixing something.
Just stay over there.
I thought you wanted me
to wash the car.
Hey, man, wash it later.
Stay over there!
I ain't the smartest man
in the world,
but from here it looks
like you takin' a shit.
Ezel, get the hell off
my back lawn!
Ugh! It look like
you been eatin' corn?
Fool, get the hell
out of my back...
Get on, man!
Alright, but between
me and you, man,
when you're done,
I'll clean all that shit
up for you for $2.00.
Hey, Ezel!
What?
You better not tell nobody, man!
I'm not, man.
Keep it on the down low.
All right. I'm not like that.
We'll keep it down, bro.
Ey! Smokey back here
takin' a shit!
Ezel!
Well, I ain't gonna
tell nobody else.
# La la la la
# La la la la la... #
See, you need to control
that little funky ass temper.
I know. I be forgettin', baby.
You got to be reminding me.
I'm sorry.
My mama know
that's you calling
and hanging up.
What?
That ain't me calling
and hanging up, baby.
You know I love your mama.
Hey, you got some money?
What? Some, huh?
Nigger, how much you need?
About $200.
Well, I guess so.
What are you gonna to give me?
WOMAN: Craig!
Craig!
Craig! Craig!
Can I talk to you
for a minute?
JOl: What?
What?
Could I use y'all's
VCR right quick?
I want to dub a tape.
Hell, no!
It's the Mack!
Uh-uh, wait a minute!
Who the fuck is that bitch?
Fuck you, motherfucker!
You think you're slick,
asking me for money!
Well, ask that bitch
for some money!
Damn.
What's wrong with your ho?
Damn!
We had the money right there
in my motherfucking...
We ain't have shit.
So what we gonna do?
Man, that fool's
just playing, man.
I ain't sweatin' it.
That's your problem.
Ain't nobody playin' but you.
You walk up and down
the street all day playing.
He ain't playin'!
You think he playin'
about his money?
You done dragged me into this.
He know where my mama stay.
he know where your mama stay.
You say he had a gun
when you seen him, right?
Yeah.
Well, name one person
in the hood
that play like that?
I know, huh?
Look, man...
I'm sorry I got you
in this shit.
I'm going to tell him
you ain't had nothin'
to do with it.
I smoked up his weed.
I'm gonna face
the consequences.
If I get dealt with,
I get dealt with.
Craig, have you seen my sh...
What's that for?
Protection.
Protection?
Protection from who?
Me and Smokey.
I got to walk Smokey
down to his house.
Aw, man. your mother and l
never would have moved
into this neighborhood
if we had known
you'd need a gun
to walk down the damn street.
You know how it is around here.
Oh, no, son, that's
not the way it is.
Kids today are nothing
but punks, sissified,
so quick to pick up a gun.
You scared to take
an ass whippin'.
This is what makes you a man.
When I was growing up,
this was all the
protection we needed.
You win some, you lose some.
But you live...
You live to fight another day.
You think you're a man
with that gun in your hand,
don't you?
I'm a man without it.
Put the gun down.
(Puts gun down)
Put up your dukes.
Now you're a man.
Your uncle picked up a gun too.
He had to find out
the hard way.
22 years old.
You got a choice.
These are all you need.
Alright?
What's up, man?
What's up, Red?
Ah ah ah! Get your ass up.
They was clownin'
you at work today.
I saw the tape.
We kept rewinding it.
It looked like your head,
but you can't tell from the
back.
How your eye?
Oh, it's cool.
Damn! Damn!
Put your glasses back on.
What's up, Craig?
What's up, Red?
Hey, Smokey, sell me a dub!
Ain't selling you nada.
Come on, homes.
Let's let bygones be bygones.
Raise the fuck up before
Craig's father come out here.
You need to go and do that.
Hell, I ain't selling him shit.
You better get your ass
off your shoulders.
You ain't going
to get me shot up.
You better make that money.
Hurry up.
Hey, Eze.
(Mocks Spanish)
Man, this nigger
got us in some shit.
You know that shit
was fucked up, man.
It's alright.
You have nice legs, man.
Shit, here come Deebo!
Who?
Dee-bo!
I'm going to tuck mine in.
(BIKE FALLS OVER)
What's up, y'all?
What's up, Red?
Thanks for the bike.
What you got on my 40, homie?
I thought you had $200.
I do, but I want to
spend Red's money.
I'm broke.
Give it up, Red.
Come on, Deebo, stall him out.
What you got on my 40, homie?
I don't have nothin'.
Yeah, you got something.
Why you trippin', Deebo?
Shut up, or I knock
your ass out.
Why don't you give him
back his chain?
What chain?
Yeah, what chain?
Man, why y'all didn't help me?
Man, I'm high.
That's fucked up.
I would have helped y'all.
What about the time
he tried to choke me
in smoke's backyard?
Oh, that was different.
Man, let's jump him.
Sit your ass down.
Man, I got mind control
over Deebo.
He be, like, "shut the fuck up,"
I be quiet.
But when he leaves,
I be talkin' again.
Man, my grandmama
gave me that chain.
Man, he trippin' hard.
SMOKEY :
Only on people he know.
He don't be pullin'
that shit
on them fools
around the corner.
RED: Man, fuck that!
Aw.
(Turns alarm off)
He going to cry in the car.
(RAP MUSIC PLAYS)
Here come Dana
and her punk ass boyfriend.
What you doin' with
that on your head?
Don't even ask.
Alright,
don't get homeboy fucked up.
Debbie came by here
looking for you.
What did she say?
She just said
to tell you she came by.
Alright.
Hey, Dana, when
we going to hook up?
Boy, please.
Alvita, Alvita!
That's ok! She'll be back.
Another Quaalude,
she'll love me
in the morning.
Ain't that right, Frank?
Get off me.
Aah! He's crazy! He's crazy!
Oh, shit.
Ah, he's going off.
Goddamn preacher!
Craig!
Craig, Daddy wants you.
Look.
What Daddy want?
I don't know. Go see.
Tell me if anything happens.
Go see.
Hey, what's up with me and you?
I was in there
on the phone with Debbie.
What's up with Rita?
Rita who?
Rita that's going
to be here at 7:30.
Girl, that's my friend.
Uh-huh.
Dana! Dana!
Anything else happen?
No.
Look at Ezel.
Scandalous.
Damn! Damn!
ls Dana in there?
Yeah. Just go on and knock.
What's your name?
Shana. Excuse me.
Stop!
Don't come over here
with that attitude, girl.
What's up, girl?
Nothing. Did you remember
to pick up the hair?
Yeah. Daddy wants you again.
Damn!
What he want?
Go see.
Outrun the dog.
Run. Go for the tree,
Mr Postman.
Go!
Huh?
Get me a glass of water.
It's your ass, Mr Postman.
I look like the Kunta Kinte
around this mother...
Go, go, go, go, go!
Took long enough.
I know.
Alright, man.
I'm going to run over
and get you the gun, right?
Then I'm going home to chill.
You wait for them niggers.
Later on, call me
and let me know what happened.
You're making me nervous, ok?
I'm trippin' out,
scared as shit.
Aah!
Stop!
Alright. Damn!
# Little child, running wild
# Watch awhile
# You'll see
he never smiles... #
What car is that?
I don't know.
I don't know who car that is.
Hey, what time is it?
7:45.
Oh, nigger,that's Janet Jackson.
Who?
Janet Jackson -
the girl Debbie
hooked me up with.
Hey, hold up.
I'll be right back.
Smoke, hey,
see if she got a friend.
Alright.
Ooh, what's up?
Not a damn thing.
(Farts)
So we going
to kick it, or what?
We can kick it,
but I forgot I had to go
pick up my mom from work,
and you know how that is.
I'll take you to get her.
She don't like a lot of people
with me when I go get her.
Who's that girl
Smokey's talking to?
Some girl he hooked up with.
She's a big one.
Humongous.
Why don't you go get
something to eat?
Lord, let me go inside
and see what's going on
with this crazy man.
I'm right behind you.
Uh-uh, 'cause, see,
I ate twice before I came.
God damn!
Craig, where the iron?
Right there.
Hey, Dana.
What?
Loan me $200.
Me and Smokey got into it
with Big Worm today.
We owe him $200.
He said if we don't pay him,
he going to kill us.
So you going to loan me
the money or not?
Not.
You going to call me?
I'm going to call you.
But if you come by,
I won't call you. OK?
Don't ever, ever, ever, ever,
ever, ever, ever come by here.
OK?
OK.
Alright.
'Bye, Smokey.
(PHONE RINGS)
Ew...
Damn it!
Craig, telephone.
Who is it?
That girl.
Tell her I'll call her back.
OK.
Hey, Mama.
What?
Loan me $200.
Craig, I wouldn't
feel comfortable
lending you $200
without a job.
If I was working,
I wouldn't need $200.
Exactly.
Y'all ain't never got no money!
I hate to live with
a bunch of broke-ass people.
Shit!
Come here!
What?
Why you hook me up with that
fat-ass baldhead girl?
Who? Rita?
Yeah.
Rita is not fat.
She's just big boned.
Shit! That girl wider
than all outside.
Talkin' about she looked
like Janet Jackson.
Oh, no, she didn't go there.
Bitch got out of the car
looking more like
Freddie Jackson.
Don't laugh. it ain't funny.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm not trying to laugh.
I just thought that
you two would like each other.
You knew she was baldheaded.
You knew she had no damn hair.
(Laughs)
Don't laugh. It ain't funny.
Ooh, I'm sorry.
What Deebo doing over here?
He's in there
asleep with Felisha.
Felisha fucking Deebo too?
Could you mind
your own business?
Where your mama at?
My mama is in Vegas
with her boyfriend.
So y'all just parlaying up
in here, huh?
Oh, shit. Party over here.
Uh-uh, uh-uh.
What? What?
Bye-bye.
You trippin'.
I'm out of here anyway.
Peace out.
Ohh!
Nasty motherfucker.
(Snorts)
(ITEM BREAKS)
Ezel?
Smokey!
What you doing in here?
When YOU doin' in here?
Shh!
I seen the window open,
so I said fuck it.
Man, get the hell
out of here.
All right, man.
Look here, loan me $2.00.
(Knocks on door)
(Laughs)
I'm clowning.
Janet Jackson ass
get just a little fat.
Man, forget that.
I almost had the money.
What?
You remember that money we stole
from Stanley house?
Yeah.
Deebo was over Felisha
and Debbie house asleep.
I snuck through
the back window
to get the money
out of his pants,
and little Ezel come
through the window
and woke him up.
I tried to beat
his ass, but he ran.
You ain't catching
no crack head.
Forget that, man.
Let's just go over.
He's probably still asleep.
you breaking in, though.
You going to be with me?
I got you man.
(CREAKING)
Damn.
Oh, well. Forget that plan.
What time is it?
8:50.
I'm just going
to go in the house
and chill, man.
Oh. Now you're getting scared.
You want to go
in the house and lay down?
Hell, no,
nobody run me in my house,
like no little bitch.
This my hood. Fuck Worm.
Boo!
Punk!
Y'all busters can't catch me.
(SHOUTING)
Papa!
Do you know what we just did?
We finally got
that little motherfucker.
Calm down.
What?
Who car is that
coming up creeping?
Drive-by! drive-by!
Get off my ass!
Man, let's go in the house.
Slippin'.
Wish you weren't slippin' today.
(BEEPING)
Shit!
Who was that?
Big Worm.
(PHONE RINGS)
Hey, um, somebody,
uh, page Smokey?
Don't play dumb, nigger.
You know who this is.
You got my money?
Man, you don't have
to holler, man.
I ain't got it yet,
but I'm going to get it...
(DIAL TONE)
What happened?
Man, he just hung up.
I think we better stay
in the house.
Damn!
See anything?
Man, I can't see shit.
Too damn many trees
all in the way.
I'm going to try again.
Hey, hey, hey!
Dana told me about
that big snake situation.
Big Worm.
Big Worm, Big Hole -
I don't give a damn.
Get your ass on
out of this house!
You always got some shit goin'.
You, you keep your ass here.
Big Snake, Big Worm...
What kind of a name is that?
I bet y'all drinking that wine
and smoking them tweeds,
wearing them clothes
all half-off your ass.
What the hell's going on today?
Weeds.
Your punk ass dad.
He always talking shit.
Just wait. Well, hold up.
Tell him to comb
his goddamn hair.
Like spiders is having
a meeting on his head.
I'm about sick of you.
I'm sick of you.
Now I'll walk
you home, punk ass.
You see him?
There ain't nobody
even out here.
I don't even know
why I'm trippin'.
Nobody want to mess
with the smoke dog.
(Barks)
Man, who's that?
# It ain't the niggers
that act hard... #
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
Quick!
You don't know
who you're messing with!
Aah!
Damn!
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hey, hey, hey.
Look and see if they're coming.
Hell, no. You look.
We both look on the count of 3.
1, 2, 3!
Craig, thought you said on 3.
You ain't bullshittin' me?
1, 2, 3!
Craig, what the fuck you...
You see them?
Yeah, they coming, man.
I ain't never going
to smoke weed again.
Craig, I love you, man.
Shut up. Let me go!
(Whimpers)
Shut up, man.
I shot one of them.
I know I shot one of them.
Hey, hey, look again.
Fuck you.
Stanley! Stanley!
What's going on?
I don't know. It sounded
like machine guns.
Oh, Lord.
Mama, where Craig at?
I don't know.
There's Joann. Go ask
her if she's seen them.
Sounded like a bomb.
Joann, you seen Craig
and Smokey in there?
I thought they were over there.
Deebo, you seen Craig
and Smokey around here?
Earlier.
Damn.
What she say?
She ain't seen him, and Deebo
ain't seen him.
MRS JONES: See why you have
to tell us before you leave?
Look at your face!
It'll be OK.
No, look at your face.
Who do you think you are?
What are you talking about?
You know what
I'm talking about, punk.
You hit my sister like
she was a fucking man.
She had no business
going through my pants.
My sister don't need
to steal nothing
from your broke ass.
Take your ass home.
I'm not scared of you.
All these niggers around here
might be scared of you,
but I'm not.
You take your ass home.
No, fuck you.
You're lucky I'm not a man.
Otherwise l'd kick
your ass myself.
Shut up!
Deebo, man, you trippin'.
What you say, little nigger?
Man, that's a female.
Shut your little
punk ass up, nigger,
before I drop you
like I did this bitch.
Man, I ain't trying
to fight you, Deebo.
Ezel.
You want to fight me
'cause you ain't nothin'
but a bitch too.
What are you going
to do with that...
..besides make me mad?
Put the gun down, son.
DEEBO: Huh?
Yeah. Put that gun down, son,
and get knocked down
like your father used to.
(GUNSHOT)
This was all the protection
we needed.
You win some, you lose some.
But you live...
You live to fight another day.
You think you're a man
with that gun
in your hand, don't you?
I'm a man without it.
(ECHOING)
Yeah.
Put that gun down, son.
And get knocked down
like your father used to.
Give me the gun, son.
Craig.
Give me...give me the gun.
Give me the gun, son.
(Laughs)
That's all you got?
Drop him, Craig! Craig! Craig!
Craig! Aw, shit!
Get up, Craig! Get up, Craig!
Oh, shit! God!
God damn.
Uh-uh!
No, no, no, come on,
baby! Let him be a man.
Go to sleep! Go to sleep! Yeah!
Shoot him.
See, he's not fighting fair!
Uh-uh!
I been down before.
I taught him better than this.
Come on, Craig!
Told y'all! Y'all want some?
Beat him down! Beat you down!
Who else want some?
Who else want some of Deebo?
DANA: Craig, get up!
MR JONES: Get up, Craig!
Come on, Craig!
Stand up, Craig! Stand up!
There you go!
Hey, punk!
Yes, Mr Big Shot.
Fucking... Yeah, crawl, punk!
Crawl, bitch!
Whoop him, Craig! Whoop his ass!
Ooh, that's what
I'm talking about!
That's my dog!
Take that.
Ain't that right, Ma?
That's my dog! Mr Parker!
That's my dog!
Cutie pie.
If anybody got to say anything,
you let me know.
That's my dog.
You OK?
Yeah.
Craig.
No, no, cupcake.
Leave him alone.
Let him be a man.
I taught him good, didn't I?
Now who's the punk?
He think he a mack.
Macaroni.
You got knocked
the fuck out, man.
Give me my goddamn money.
The payback's
a motherfucker, ain't it?
Pow, pow, pow.
Shana, come on.
Come on, Mama.
My grandmama gave me this chain.
Deebo! Deebo!
Man, you should have been
bobbing and weaving.
Look at you. Get up!
Since you ain't,
I'll take these shoes.
Big foot motherfucker,
you can have your knife.
'Cause I steal, I don't kill.
How's your back feeling?
It'll be cool.
Bleeding and shit.
What time you waking up
in the morning?
8:30. Why?
I was just wondering
if maybe you were
feeling better,
then, um, you could come over.
I'm feeling better already.
I'm going to call you tomorrow.
Alright.
8:30, right?
Yes.
Hey...7:30.
(Laughs)
That's right.
(PHONE RINGS)
CRAIG: Hello?
JOI: Why you can't
call nobody back?
Which one of your hos
has somebody
shooting at you?
I don't know why
I waste my time
on your old
stupid ass anyway.
I don't know either.
It's over. Bitch!
(DIAL TONE)
Yeah, I got your money,
and I don't appreciate
you sending your punk ass,buster
ass, jheri curl ass friends
to shoot at me and my homie.
They liked to got dealt with.
Don't be calling here like you
some straight up "g",
'cause I'll cut your balls off
and hand them to you, partner.
I had to warn you too many times
about my money, Smokey.
It's the principle
of the whole thing.
There's principalities
in this.
Well, yeah. I got
your money anyway,
and you sell that shit
yourself next time
'cause I'm going to rehab.
I'm through with this shit.
I was just bullshittin',
and you know this, man.
RAP SONG:
# You know it ain't no stopping
# All the dogs I'm dropping
# It's Friday night,
so everything is popping
# I got spin
that's been on the head
# So let the games begin
# Yakety yak, don't talk back,
go to a song
# Calling up earl
on the car phone
# Mac 10
just got out of court
# Roaming through the hood
in a super sport
# Bumper too short
# 18's got the rear view
mirror's vibrating
# And deep dish dating
# You know how we do it,
ain't nothing to it
# But the floss of the crowd,
Harris & Ross
# 'Cause if you fuck with ours,
we leave scars
# On a "g" right course,
living like stars
# Might hit the highway
on the Vegas run
# Fool, 'cause it's Friday
# Oh, yeah, throw
your neighbourhood in the air
# If you don't care
# Oh, yeah, throw
your neighbourhood in the air
# If you don't care
# Standing outside
on the Friday
# Living on the edge
# 'Cause we all
got them hard heads
# It seems like we all away
# For the drive-by,
playing tag with Satan
# But we chillin',
yeah, we ready and willin'
# You hear about
the latest west side killing?
# But we slippin', say trippin'
# For dipping, pistol gripping,
never slipping
# Big g's
trying to hang out
# But old "g" said, take
your little ass in the house
# My big homie just got out
# Used to be damned,
now we just crack dead
# He's about
as hard as Darth Vader
# In his sweatshirt,
khakis, and chuck taylors
# Just seen them
in the driveway
# Getting beat like a smoker,
fool, 'cause it's Friday
# Oh, yeah, throw
your neighbourhood in the air
# If you don't care
# Oh, yeah, throw
your neighbourhood in the air
# If you don't care, fool
# Why must I be like that
and chase the cat?
# Or settle for a hood rack?
# Do be brave
# No dreadlocks flying
in and out of town
# With half a chicken
and a cock
# And I love her
# 'Cause she dared
to fuck around
# With the underground
# Pussy hound, and her ass
is big, round, and wide
# Jacked up,
making niggers down the rye
# Smoking in dope,
playing that super Nintendo
# Hear a rat-a-tat
on my window
# There goes that
pelvic thrust
# Don't trust a rubber,
'cause it's bound to bust
# In the oven, in the nappy
# I had on 2, so I was happy
# 'Cause that HIV will
make your dick hang sideways
# And that ain't cool, fool,
'cause it's Friday
# Throw your neighbourhood
in the air, if you don't care
# Oh, yeah, throw
your neighbourhood in the air
# If you don't care. #