There's an oJd saying:
"Why buy the cow
when you can get the miJk for free?"
It's a fascinating phiJosophicaJ query,
marriage versus sex.
And if you're considering the former...
...odds are you'JJ hear the saying
from a friend...
...who cJaims to be getting
an abundant amount of the Jatter.
And incidentaJJy, it's buJJshit.
Bullshit. You think this is bullshit.
- Yeah.
- Well, it isn't.
After five years, I think
I have the right to broach the subject.
So you broach and we talk.
You don't have to go
and give me an ultimatum.
Don't use that word. I hate that word.
I'm not too fond of it either,
but what else would you call this?
A deadline.
So I'm a little indecisive.
That doesn't mean you have to hold
a gun to my head.
- Sorry.
- Don't be so melodramatic.
That's why I'm taking this transfer.
I'll be 3,000 miles away.
I can't hold a gun to your head.
- Stop saying that!
- Shit.
Admit it. You're using this transfer thing
as an ultim... Deadline.
Okay. So I wouldn't have signed up for it
if you hadn't freaked on Tyler's news.
Hello.
David! What's up, what's up?
Tyler, you are wasted. Sarah.
Damn. How'd you know, my brother?
- The faux urban street slang.
- Nigger, please!
- What time is it back there, like 2:00?
- You know this city never sJeeps.
Y'all be counting on your sheep.
Listen, man,
I met the most amazing woman.
- She is...
- Fly?
Better than fly. She's super fly.
What did I tell you about drinking and
dating? Go to bed and sleep her off.
We're getting married!
What?
You got to meet her, you and Sarah.
She's Jike...
- Super fly?
- Better than super fJy, man.
She's the one.
You know how they say
that you can just teJJ? David?
You still there, bitch?
- Yeah, I'm here. I'm just...
- This is it, man. It just hit me.
It was like a blinding realisation.
Like pure truth.
Anyway, you and Sarah got to meet her.
You're gonna Jove her. Her name's JuJie.
She's sweet, she's beautiful...
...she's "chocolicious"...
Tyler? Hello! Tyler, you okay?
Sounds like true love.
So you are leaving me alone
to deal with this for two months.
You need to be alone to deal with this.
Which is why I strongly advise you
against consulting with Mike.
BeJJissimo. Magnifico.
You are so hot!
You beast.
Is that Ricky Martin over there?
God, no. It's Mike Hanson.
You're beautiful. Modesty, now. Modesty.
I love you. No words.
No, I'm not. Yes, I am.
Don't do it. I'm doing it.
Don't do it.
I did it.
I'd do me.
- Oh, man! The "testy" tuck again?
- Do you like what you see?
- No?
- Would you put on some clothes?
We only got two hours
of "Happy Hour" left.
Let me just get my towel, okay?
Got it. There we go.
You got issues, I mean, real issues.
He may be your friend,
but he's no Deepak Chopra.
He is also not running off to New York.
CUse this time to make an informed
decision or none of this'll mean anything.
I can't let this not mean anything.
So you love her, right?
- Of course I love her.
- There you go.
Let's not get carried away here, guys.
No one's doubting your love for each other.
A blind man could smell your love.
- But this is a major...
- Huge.
No, colossal, thing you're considering here.
As your friend,
it's my duty to ask the tough questions.
- What?
- Sex.
- Sex is still good?
- The sex is awesome.
I've got no complaints
about what we have.
It would be a lot easier if I did.
It's got to be something.
You waited five years.
- So what is it?
- It's nothing. Let's drop it.
We're your friends. We want to help you.
But we can't do it unless you let us in!
It's no one thing!
There's a lot of factors
in these kind of situations.
- So what is it? Give us one.
- Other women, all right?
You've had other women? How many?
I'm not quite sure that I've had enough.
- That's ridiculous. How many is enough?
- Twice your age.
It's not about quantity, it's about quality.
What's wrong with going
for both quality and quantity?
Being the best he can be,
that's the American way.
Foul.
- Foul?
- It's foul.
- What foul?
- Humping before the shot.
- I was humping you?
- Prison-style.
Whatever. If I was humping you,
you'd know it.
- Would I?
- Yeah, you'd know it.
You'd feel it. I wasn't humping you.
- Deep, right?
- Yep.
A little help?
The thing is,
I never expected to feel empowered.
For better, for worse,
something is set into motion...
...and I set it off.
Am I a manipulative bitch or what?
Welcome to my world.
You should feel empowered.
It wasn't easy, but it had to be done.
What was the alternative, to keep waiting?
It's not like the sex gets better
with every passing year. Am I right?
I'm sorry that was so quick.
I'm kind of beat.
That's okay.
Orgasms are overrated anyway.
Hey, South Park is on.
You had the courage
to look him in the eye and say:
"Buddy boy,
it's time to shit or get off the pot."
And marrying me would be the "shit" part
of that colourful analogy?
Thanks.
I'm sorry, I don't get it. Sarah is hot.
Behind every good-Iooking chick is a guy
who's tired of nailing her.
- Am I right, Davey?
- No, you're wrong, asshole.
So who's missing from your repertoire:
cowgirls, wilder chicks, the Amish, what?
It's not like that.
Let's just drop it, all right?
- Do you guys believe in "the one"?
- As in one soul mate?
The perfect match that completes us,
makes us whole?
- Exactly.
- Hell, no.
I don't know. But if there's such a thing
and Sarah's it...
...then that means it's inevitable.
It's a lock, right? It's like destiny.
I guess so.
Okay. So, if it's inevitable,
why rush into it?
- You're still not telling us everything.
- Of course, I'm not. You're my friends.
- It's stupid, it's stupid.
- Come on, help us help you.
Please, man.
Okay. I'm going to tell you guys
a little story.
I have never told anyone this before. Ever.
When I was 18 years old...
...my family and I were flying home...
...from a vacation we took
in the Caribbean. It was a fun time.
Very nice beaches. CJub Med.
We were in Jine to get on board...
...when I happened to gJance over
to the gate across from us...
...and that's when I saw her.
She gJowed.
It was Jike a Jight aJJ around her.
It was bJinding.
I swear I have never felt anything
that powerful before or since.
Something about her sucked me
away from the plane...
...and drew me right back to her.
There she was.
With strength I wish I still possessed...
...I floated towards her.
I introduced myself and told her how I felt.
I gave her my address...
...and told her if she felt it too,
she should write.
Young blood had him some balls.
I had no choice.
I was being driven by a higher power.
Call it "the lightning bolt,"
call it a connection, destiny, whatever.
- So did she write you?
- Not at first.
Every day I'd check that maiJbox.
I checked aJJ that summer, and nothing.
Then one day, it came.
It was more than I couJd've hoped for.
She professed her Jove to me.
She said that she, too,
got a joJt down her spine...
...that gJorious day we first met.
It was more beautifuJ and poetic
than she was...
...which I didn't think was possibJe
at the time.
I immediateJy wrote her back.
I toJd her that I wanted us
to run away together...
...make Jove under the stars. Make babies.
It was clear to both of us.
We belonged together.
No fear, no doubt.
- Perfect.
- Young love.
Too young. As it turned out.
ApparentJy she was an amazingJy...
...hyper-developed 11-year-old girl.
- What?
- Eleven?
Her parents found my letters and...
...quite understandably freaked out.
They contacted our JocaJ authorities...
...who swiftJy moved in to stop
the town's budding paedophiJe.
They made my father promise that
his sicko son...
...wouJd cease contact
with any more JittJe girJs.
They Jeft him to scream at me
for over an hour about...
...how I could flush any chances
of a political career down the toilet.
- That's a fucked up story, man.
- You're the only people I've ever told.
Can you keep it that way?
It makes you seem kind of creepy.
David Collins Graphics.
- Hey.
- Sarah, hey, how are you?
I just thought I'd caJJ
and see how you were.
I'm fine. How are you? How's New York?
Busy. But the city is so incredible.
I wish you were here with me. Oops, shit.
"Oops, shit," what? Why "Oops, shit"?
I made a Jist of aJJ the things
I wasn't going to...
...say to you like, "I miss you.
I wish you were here."
So how are you?
Miss you. Wish you were here, all that.
I talked to Tyler.
He and I are going to try
to get together for dinner.
So maybe I'll get to meet the fiancée.
Great. Be sure and thank them
for ruining my life.
Listen, I just wanted to let you know
that I made it here okay.
Oh. Is that it?
WeJJ, I got to get back to work.
So I shouJd go.
Yeah, me, too.
Okay. 'Bye, David.
I'm just saying,
it's been a week and a half now...
...and all you've done is sit around
the apartment. It's no good.
She wants me to give the situation
serious thought...
...that's exactly what I'm trying to do.
Finish it, Tiny!
And how's that working out so far?
Been doing a lot of thinking?
No! You are useless!
- What was that? He can't do that.
- Actually, I think he can.
She wants me to make
an informed decision...
...and I'm gonna respect that.
No, what she wants is for you
to wallow around your apartment...
...like some socially-retarded hermit.
Ante up. Who do you like?
- Give me $5 on Super Thong.
- I'm gonna take the one with the nice rack.
She is banking on your misery, bro,
hoping you'll sit around bumming out.
That's got to hurt.
And that, my friend,
is how you make an uninformed decision.
You want to make
a truly informed decision?
Get off your ass and
go see what it's like out there.
Get in the game.
The game? I.e. Hitting
the meat market clubs with you.
No. Hitting them with me and Jonesy.
There are some major fundamentaJ
probJems I have with...
..."Why buy the cow when you can get
the miJk for free?" conundrum.
For one thing, women are not cows.
And by that I mean, not so generic.
I think most reasonabJe peopJe
wouJd agree...
...that a cow is a cow is a cow.
This is not true of women.
Things might be simpJer if it were.
- Yo, Mike!
- Excuse me.
Scotch.
- It's packed.
- Yeah, busy.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
You might have offered to help me.
If you please? A beer for my friend?
Thank you.
I'm sorry to do this to you, but I got to go.
- Hey, asshole, what is your problem?
- You shouldn't drink anymore.
- Why shouldn't I? I just got here.
- Because you're driving me home.
- Oh, God.
- Hey.
- Buy you a drink?
- Actually, I'm think I'm gonna leave.
- You aren't married, are you?
- Not yet. You better hurry, though.
- Another round.
- Did Mikey show?
- Yes.
Cute. How'd he play?
Actually, I think he used the
"You're less than nothing to me" strategy.
It never fails, man.
- You miss her, huh?
- Are you kidding?
Surrounded by all these available women?
More than ever.
I know the feeling, only worse.
Imagine feeling like that in this place
without having anybody to miss.
How you doing?
You ready to go?
Okay, so you had a close encounter
with something.
You saw the light in the airport.
And 10 years later,
it's still messing with your head.
It was important.
It set the bar for me on some level.
Is that so bad?
It's bad if it keeps you from hooking up
with a woman...
...who's attractive, smart,
and of legal, consenting age.
What if she's still out there?
Don't I owe it to myself...
...to try and find her?
You're hunting Sasquatch.
- See. There she is.
- The shadow lady?
She's a Sasquatch?
She's a myth. The perfect woman.
A figment of our dumb-ass
male imagination.
Slap a face on the shadow bitch,
and she ceases to be perfect...
...because she becomes real.
- So what exactly is all this crap?
- It's market research.
Insurance for the creatives who came up
with this shitty campaign.
If I can coerce a focus group...
...to say that a picture of
an anorexic model...
...bottle-feeding two large men
in diapers...
...makes them want to buy a pair of jeans,
then I've done my job.
That is a twisted way to make a living.
I know.
But at least it's the fashion biz, right?
So why don't you just move here?
- I don't know. Maybe I will.
- Who is that?
- It's Mr. Hahn. My boss.
- And you get paid?
Look at it mathematically.
If just one person hooks up with somebody
who isn't their soul mate...
...you got a chain reaction that
screws it up for everybody on the planet.
Your soul mate ends up with someone
else's who settles for someone else's...
Which makes it all the more important
to find the right person.
It's a glass-half-empty,
glass-half-full scenario.
If you ask me, the glass is half full of crap.
You sure you don't want any
late night eats?
No. I'm out of here. Take care, man.
- You got a problem?
- How's the chili?
I'd give my right arm for a bowl.
I'll hand that... I'll have that.
Oh, my God. My God, that was the glow.
That was the feeling you got in the airport.
It's happening again.
I'm gonna do this. Can you do this?
You've done it before,
you can do it again. Go!
I'm gonna do this. I'm gonna do this.
Can you? Can you?
Don't let her get away.
- Where did she go? Where did that girl go?
- What's your problem?
She left, crap sack.
Creep.
Wait up! Stop! Stop!
Stop! Wait up! Don't go! Don't!
Quick Match Personals. May I heJp you?
I'd like to place a personal ad.
I'm sorry, can you pJease speak up?
A personal ad.
I want to place a personal...
Hello. Is anyone there?
HeJJo?
I'm sorry. I dropped the phone. I'm here.
This is my first time.
Okay. Here goes.
Wanted...
...soul mate.
Potential soul mate looking
for his soul mate.
You, souJ-mate materiaJ.
Me, open, inteJJigent, and...
Soul-matey?
Yes.
Who's dead? Somebody better be dead.
Hey, Tyler, it's Mikey. Did I wake you?
What time is it?
It's 1:00 in the morning, 4:00 to you.
Sorry, man.
What's wrong? What happened?
- Nothing. I just wanted to talk.
- At 4:00 in the morning?
It's cheaper.
Listen, Ty, how'd you do it?
- How'd I do what?
- How did you, you know...
How did you find somebody
who made the cut?
I don't know. It was just this
feeJing that hit me.
Like a blinding realisation, like pure truth.
- Mikey, what is this all about?
- Nothing.
Nothing. Forget it. Congratulations.
- Mike?
- Yeah?
Pull this shit again,
you don't get to be my best man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Always a best man, never a man.
Oh, my God, this is so exciting.
I think I just met
Naomi Campbell's hair person.
So, anything I should be doing?
This is the glamorous world
of Market Research.
We just sit around
untiJ somebody wonders.
Why are those men wearing diapers?
I guess I can answer
that question for you, sir.
- You can answer that?
- Yes.
We did research in the Midwest
which indicated...
...that our target market was
getting younger and younger...
...as you can see.
Our focus groups taught us that
it'd be wise to do a preemptive strike...
...and showcase young imagery
in our new campaigns.
I see and this explains
why I'm spending $2 million...
...putting grown men in Huggies.
You realise if I did this in my basement...
...and post them on the internet,
I'd be arrested.
Also save a lot of money.
What are you doing for lunch?
I'm sorry Julie couldn't make it tonight.
She really does want to meet you.
- Me, too.
- Yeah.
But at least now you can tell me
how all of this happened.
- You used to refer to marriage as...
- I know, cruel and unusual punishment.
- It's her. She just hit me like a truck.
- But you were ready for it, right?
- You were wandering around in traffic?
- Yeah, I guess it was in traffic.
I mean, if it can happen to me,
it can happen to anybody. Right?
Anybody who isn't Mike, of course.
I actually got a strange call
from Mike the other day.
I think he seemed genuinely concerned
not to have somebody in his life.
Mike, in a relationship?
Isn't that one of the signs
of the Apocalypse?
Nostradamus actually predicted it.
He said, in the latter part
of the twentieth century...
..."the Ione cock would crow no more."
That's scary.
Why do you think David's so reluctant
to take the next step with me?
Oh, David.
I was playing the field,
and I got burned out on it.
David hasn't exactly been out
playing the field.
- He's been playing house with me.
- A fun game.
So Jet me get this straight.
By working in a reJationship
with this guy for the past five years...
...I have actuaJJy undermined
any possibiJity of a future with him?
Yeah. Maybe. I don't know.
David's a reaJJy sharp guy...
...and I think he'JJ probabJy come
to his senses.
- I mean, you're all he wants.
- I'm all he knows.
That can work.
David, it's me.
It's Jate and you're not home.
That's good. I hope you're out having fun.
I know this sounds weird...
...but if you need to see other women
to figure this out...
...I can handJe it.
Maybe it's being here on my own
or from asking you for a decision.
I've gained a new perspective on things.
I think it's important for us to expJore
whatever options we need to.
So, if that's part of it for you
just know that I understand.
I know what you mean.
She second-guessed our move.
She's even more cunning than I thought.
She's good.
You're lucky I'm on board.
It's not like her. Why would she say it's
okay to go out with other women?
Why indeed?
Shouldn't you be out there
playing wingman for Jonesy?
Oh, please.
I never realised you were so picky.
You think I'm one of these
assy scam hounds?
I have very particular tastes.
A strict list of qualities
I look for in a woman.
I'm not just fucking around out here.
What?
Seriously, all this play I get?
I'm not wasting my time. It's practice.
- It's practice for the big game.
- Maybe it's not a game.
You've been off the circuit too long.
Of course, it's a game.
It's better than a game, it's a sport.
It's better than a sport, even.
It's sport fishing.
Case in point.
Look at him.
See those chicks he's wasting it on.
Hi, ladies! Those are bass.
And we all go bass fishing
from time to time.
Hell, you can get really good at it
with practice.
But while he's spending all his time
hooking up with bottom feeders...
...the crucial skills he'll need
to hook his wife are atrophying.
You see, scamming is like fishing.
If your dream girl were a fish,
what would she be?
- I don't know, a tuna?
- Yeah! No.
A marlin.
A big trophy fish.
To catch a marlin,
you must use entirely different skills.
You don't go out marlin fishing with
a sorry-ass fold-out pole, six-pound test.
That'll do for bass.
But it sure as shit
isn't gonna land a marlin.
You have to up your game.
Know where the elusive beauties lie.
You gotta know where to fish.
They're rare, brother. They're rare.
Most days you don't catch shit.
But when you do...
Wham!
The two of you are back
at the dock taking pictures.
Okay, another huge fJaw I have...
...with "Why buy the cow when you can
get the miJk for free?"...
...is simpJy this. MiJk is not free.
The point is,
if you're hankering for some miJk...
...one way or another,
you're gonna have to pay for it!
You digging this, Davey?
I told you I'd make it up to you.
Please point out which
of these lovely young ladies is a marlin.
We're done fishing for the day.
We're at the aquarium now,
checking out the exotic fishies.
Look, Davey. They even got
one of those petting tanks.
Oh, my God.
I have aJready toJd him aJJ about you,
and his friend is totaJJy hot.
Sarah, come on.
You have got to get my back.
I have been after this guy
for almost a week.
They're gonna be here in an hour.
So, come on, just get my back.
I have to go. I'll do what I can. 'Bye.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Have you given any thought
to our conversation the other day?
It's all I've been thinking about.
But the problem is,
I'm involved with someone back in LA.
But I'm not sure what's happening with us.
I just need a little more time
to figure it out. Is that okay?
Of course. Just don't take too long.
Gosh, a dollar.
Now I can quit stripping,
go back to vet school...
...and save my sick pony.
Thanks, Mike. You're a prince.
- Amy!
- David, you know her!
Holy shit! It is Amy.
Give me a sec.
I have to make one last go-around.
You guys know her?
From school.
I can't believe this is happening.
- I can't believe this is happening.
- She looks great.
- She definitely lost that "Freshman 15."
- She looks hot. Damn!
Hey, you guys. How are you two?
- You work here? This is awesome.
- No, Mike, I'm just hanging.
- This is such a surprise.
- Yeah. You look good, David.
Amy, this is Jonesy. Jonesy, this is Amy.
- How you doing?
- Pleasure to meet you.
The pleasure is all mine.
Why don't you turn it down a notch?
You're channelling Barry White again.
Was she this hot when you two
were dating?
- He went out with a stripper?
- Yeah.
Actually, no.
I was just a freshman back then...
...studying to be a stripper.
David helped me bone up
on my pole-dancing exam.
Can I buy you a drink for old times' sake?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
They're going to do it.
I often wonder how long we would've
lasted if I hadn't broken up with you.
Two and a half days. I was gonna
dump you right after my last final.
I didn't have the time to get into
a big emotional thing with you.
- I had to study.
- What a relief.
This whole time,
I thought I broke your heart.
Give me a break. We weren't in love
or anything. We were just having fun.
- There were no expectations back then.
- Give me a hand with this.
I mean, when did that change?
It didn't. You did.
It only seems different now
because you outgrew it.
- I don't know.
- I do.
Look at your dick-with-ears friend there.
Do you think that Amy chick
would take the bid?
- I thought that was Dave's old flame.
- Key word: "was."
Damn it! I bet I could have had her.
When she was going out
with your best friend.
Yeah, that would have been real cool.
You bet.
Although, I'm sure she wasn't as hot then.
- You look unbelievable.
- Thanks.
When did it get so difficult
to figure out what I want?
If you're like most people, darlin'...
...right around the time you found
something worth wanting.
Hand me that dildo, will you?
She circled my ad.
She circled my ad!
Quick Match maiJbox number 247.
You have 32 messages.
To pJay unheard messages, press three.
To deJete messages, press two.
Hola, souJ mate.
I have searched for you for a Jong time.
I think we shouJd get together.
I have dark hair,
dark eyes and a nippJe key ring.
I'm a maid, so I have Jots of keys.
Your ad intrigued me, souJ mate.
A JittJe about myseJf:
I Jove dressing up and getting down.
I'm a waJking contradiction...
...open-minded, yet Jactose intoJerant.
And I yearn for someone
who enjoys big surprises.
CaJJ me.
If you'd Jike to make a caJJ,
pJease hang up and try again.
HeJJo, David.
I've been waiting for your caJJ...
...ever since I saw you
in that Mexican restaurant.
I've fantasised about us.
- Our bodies entwined and covered in saJsa.
- Salsa!
We're destined to be together, David.
- It's just like...
- Chips and salsa.
That's right.
And now... That's my other line. Hold on.
- HeJJo.
- David, it's Mike. You there? Pick up.
Come on, pick up, David.
This is important.
- Mike.
- David, it's happened to me.
Congratulations.
Look, I'm really not feeling very...
No! Listen, David.
I'm lying naked, in a strange bed...
...staring at the most beautiful woman...
...I have ever seen in my entire life.
Tell her I said, "Hi."
I've really got to go now.
She's not here.
I'm looking at her picture, okay?
Damn marlin jumped right into my boat,
caught me unawares.
What are you talking about?
That whole after-hours rave?
Complete blank.
The last solid memory I have
was drinking some green, glowy shit...
...from a test tube
and dancing like a bastard.
- But, David...
- What?
Something magicaJ happened
in this room Jast night.
Something...
...bigger than sex.
- Although sex was definitely a factor.
- But you don't remember.
No. Last night's a totaJ bJur.
But Jisten to me.
I woke up this morning and I've got...
...the feeling.
- Is it a burning sensation?
No, David. The feeling...
...when you just know the pure,
blinding truth stuff.
I've met her, David.
For the first time in my life,
I think I'm in love. Me.
Shit. Here she comes.
Moment of truth. 'Bye.
Good morning, sunshine!
Is that for me?
Whoops. You've been, deflowered.
I can't believe you're even up
after that performance last night.
In my book,
you deserve to sleep for a week.
Hungover and clumsy.
I'll take care of that.
You just save your strength.
- The bathroom?
- What?
- The bathroom. I don't feel too well.
- It's right around the corner, lover.
You pretty boys are all the same.
Strong stamina and weak stomachs.
It's right there.
You okay in there?
This isn't happening.
- Michael?
- Just a sec!
Laura was pretty impressed
with you last night...
...even before you two started
waking the neighbourhood.
I'm into chicks. I love chicks.
Breasts, legs, long hair.
And breasts.
I've never seen her
make breakfast for herself.
And we've been roommates
for three years.
Laura ran to the store
to get you some B12...
...and she should be back soon.
Dad. Sit down.
I'm gay.
No! Or I was fucked up or experimenting.
You know, like Mom's college years.
Oh, God, it is genetic.
Michael, I'll be out on the deck, okay?
When you're done, let's talk.
After what happened last night...
...it would mean a lot to me
if we got to know each other better.
Yeah! You bet! I'll be right out!
Jumpy little breeder.
Shit!
Stop it! You're scalding me!
Wow! That was just like Spiderman!
Actually, kid, I am Spiderman...
...and I lost my costume. I need your shirt.
Sure, Spidey.
- This is so cool.
- Yeah.
I'll give you a little hand here.
Billy! Get away from that man!
No, no, no. Sir, I can explain.
No, it's not this.
Sir!
Sick son of a...
No, no.
Daddy, no. Don't shoot Spidey.
He's my special friend.
Billy! Stop, drop and roll!
Don't do it!
Run, Spidey, run!
Okay, dog, it's Snausage time.
This country has just gone to shit.
Damn. Look at that little sodomite go.
Nice work, Laura. Another asshole.
Hello, is Susan there?
Hi, Susan. My name is David.
You answered my personal ad a couple...
Yeah, that's the one. That's me.
Hi, how are you?
Nice to talk to you. Listen...
...I think we should probably
get together sometime soon.
Hi, Cynthia. How are you? David.
That's right. Soul mate guy.
What do you say,
Papa Shan, 5:00, Tuesday?
All right. We'll see you then.
Going to hell.
Hi, Kathleen. I got it. Tuesday, Papa Shan.
Tuesday, Papa Shan, 5:00?
I don't know. Papa Shan, 5:00, Tuesday?
Hi. Excuse me.
You aren't David by any chance, are you?
No. No. Sorry.
I'm going straight to hell for this.
- David?
- It's Ralph.
Close enough.
Sorry, I'm meeting someone.
I have to get out of here.
- Hi, David.
- Nicole, what are you doing in LA?
I'm in town for my cousin's bar mitzvah.
What are you doing?
I'm leaving.
This place is such a meat market.
It's a total singles scene.
- Did you just call him David?
- Yeah. That is his name.
It's my nickname.
My close friends call me that.
- David, what are you talking about?
- Who the hell has David for a nickname?
I do. It's short for Davidian.
Branch Davidian.
- Are you here to meet a David, too?
- Yeah. Who are you?
Did you answer an ad in
Quick Match PersonaJs?
- David, do you know these women?
- You son of a...
Soul mate, my ass!
Stop it, please!
Excuse me, I'm supposed to meet
someone here named...
Some shit monkey invited four women
from the same dating service!
Why? Why?
Look, just get down here, all right?
And send ambulances, lots of them.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I've been a bad boy! I'm sorry!
How does it look? Is it bad?
No. You're good.
So, we're about the same age.
Tell me, how does one develop
such intense hatred for women...
...in a short amount of time?
Publicly humiliating four women
you've never met before?
I thought maybe I had met
one of them before.
I was wrong.
Go ahead, call Sarah.
Rat my miserable ass out.
Forget it.
I'd lash out at an entire gender too
if I had your problems.
It must be tough.
You're the last person I would have
expected sympathy from on all this.
It can't be easy. Especially now.
What do you mean, now?
Maybe you'd better call her.
Sarah, pick up the damn...
- HeJJo.
- Hello, Sarah?
This is Amber. I work with Sarah.
Can I take a message?
I need to know where she is.
She Jeft a JittJe earJy today.
Had a dinner engagement.
An appointment.
- With who?
- Who is this?
This is her boyfriend, David.
I didn't know she had a boyfriend.
She does.
Listen, I'm sorry.
I really don't know who you are...
...but I'd appreciate it
if you told me who she was...
She's out with Andrew. Mr. Hahn.
- Mr. Hung?
- Yeah, the big guy.
Are you sure you're her boyfriend?
I mean, she knows that you're
her boyfriend and everything right?
So how long have you been married?
- Seven years.
- Must be nice to have that kind of security.
I'm the poster boy for happily married.
But security,
that's a rare thing these days...
...especially in marriage.
That's a sombre outlook for
the happily-married, poster boy.
Fifty percent divorce rate in the CUS.
The only security you have
in this world is yourself.
The point I'm making, Sarah,
is your talent is yours alone.
And you do have talent, Sarah.
Your designs are amazing.
Only you can decide what you want to do
with that talent.
- I just wish it were simpler.
- Simpler?
I'm offering you a job in New York
doing what you love doing.
I know. And it's a dream come true.
Dreams don't come true very often.
Maybe it's not supposed to be simple.
Bellissimo. Magnifico.
Mike, it's me. Where you been, man?
I haven't heard from you since
you met your true Jove.
I've reaJJy got to taJk to you.
So why don't you just pick up the phone
and give me a caJJ between orgasms, okay?
From the makers of the hit videos,
Are You Gay? ...
...and So You Think You're Gay...
...United HomosexuaJ Headquarters
presents...
...Just How Gay Are You?
HeJJo. I'm Tim Chadway...
...President of United HomosexuaJ
Headquarters.
My buddies caJJ me Timbo.
You know, Jike miJJions of Americans...
...you're probabJy wondering just
how gay are you?
That's an important question.
But, come on,
the answer is pretty obvious, isn't it?
Face it, chief.
If you're watching me now,
you are pretty damn gay.
But that's okay.
Because, you see,
here at the Headquarters...
...we speciaJise in making your
journey out of the cJoset...
...as smooth as possibJe.
From our handy Gay Pride Starter Kit...
...to those convenient,
"I'm here, I'm queer...
"...stop by sometime for a beer"
change-of-sexuaJ-orientation post cards...
...you'JJ be out and about in no time.
Your famiJy and friends wiJJ admire you...
...for your abiJity to make that transition
with styJe and fJair.
- I still can't believe it.
- Why don't you just call her?
You don't even know for sure
what's going on.
If she wants to talk, she can give me a call.
I'm done sitting around like a sucker.
- You got to stop being hard on yourself.
- Mike was right.
If I'm gonna make an informed decision,
it's time I started getting busy.
Wait a minute. What's this bar
that Mike wants us to meet him at?
"The Cock Pit."
You might want to wait till tomorrow night
to start getting busy.
Why is that?
Because tonight,
we're drinking in Boys' Town.
A lot of guys claim they
practically knew it in the womb.
Like something was wrong...
...they felt different than all
the other fetuses.
How did you figure it out?
After a string of girlfriends...
...a couple ex-wives,
and a Great Dane or two...
...I started thinking, "Hey, maybe it's me."
- Was that difficult for you?
- Sure.
Most terrifying thing that you can do
is look inside yourself carefully, honestly.
But you have to do it, Michael.
And when I did,
it was a feeling that just hit me.
A blinding realisation like pure truth.
- Mike, what's up?
- Guys, hey! Sit down.
- Are you aware that this is a...
- A gay bar?
It's okay to say it. And yes, I know.
But I like it, I think.
I'm trying to, anyway.
Stanley! A beer for my friends, please.
- I get it. I get it.
- You do?
He's trying to go the distance
with that chick he met at After Hours.
Right. Avoiding places that
tempt you to stray...
...off the gilded path of monogamy.
I can't wait to meet this girl.
She must really be something.
She didn't...
...turn out to be the person
I thought she was.
- Sorry, man.
- I'm sorry. She sounded different.
Let's just drop it, okay?
So what's up with this bar?
This isn't really our kind of place.
What do you mean?
It's got beer. It's got bar stools.
- What more do you need, Jonesy?
- How about women?
I'm shocked.
I never would have pegged you two
as homophobes.
What the hell do you guys have
against gay people, anyway?
We've got nothing against gays.
Some of my best friends' friends are gay.
That's right.
- Holy shit.
- What's that?
The Mikey Chronicles, man.
The Sacred Scam Scrolls.
This is the black book?
I want you to have it, David.
I don't need it anymore.
Look at all these numbers.
What are these little black diamonds?
Stick to the blue squares.
I'd hate to see you get hurt.
This is bigger than I thought.
That chick must have really snuck up
from behind and nailed you.
David?
You must be Nikki.
I hope I'm not too early.
- So you're a friend of Mike's?
- Yeah.
David, Mike owes me $200.
Is cash okay?
Hi.
Come on in.
David. What are you doing here?
If you're this upset, then why has
it taken you two weeks to call me back?
I've been busy.
Never mind that. Who's this guy?
He's my boss. And all he did was
offer me a new position.
What's the matter, our old positions
aren't good enough for you anymore?
As a designer.
He wants an answer,
but I told him I had to talk to you first.
This is about more than a job offer.
You tell me to explore,
to meet other women.
That's got nothing to do with this.
I can't make a decision until I know
all the variables...
...one of which is still in your hands.
Great. So now I'm just a variable.
This has just gotten more complicated.
Why don't you just admit it?
You love it there.
You don't want to say no to this offer
and I'm not going to be a reason you do.
Look, if you already have made up
your mind, then say so.
But don't try to hide behind
some noble gesture...
...of not holding me back.
Why don't we be fair here?
Things have changed, Sarah.
This is no longer just my decision.
You're right, it isn't.
And that's why I'm coming home early.
What?
They're paying for me
to come home and taJk to you.
They reaJJy want me, David.
Possibly more than you do.
Oh, shit.
Dave!
What's up, man?
De-bachelorising for the little lady.
She gets back today. What's up?
You didn't get me a coffee?
I didn't know how you took it.
But here, I grabbed your mail
on the way in.
So what's the verdict?
I get to comb the thrift stores
for a new, used suit or what?
Not yet. I'm just as confused as ever.
Are you all right?
- Just lock up when you leave.
- What?
I wasn't sure if you'd be here.
I'm here. Where else would I be?
- What's this?
- I'm going to New York.
What?
- What?
- There's somebody I got to see.
- What are you talking about?
- Options, remember? Just in case.
You're out of options!
This means staying here or going back.
These are your options.
- Sarah.
- No, listen.
Listen to me carefully.
I flew back here for one reason...
...and that was to give you a chance
to talk me out of taking this job.
I can't do that until I do this.
I won't be here when you get back.
I swear to God, I won't.
This is it, David.
I know.
There are times in Jife when you have
to make extremeJy difficuJt choices.
And there are times when it seems Jike
you don't have a choice at aJJ.
Like those rare moments...
...when your onJy option practicaJJy
shows up in your maiJbox.
- David!
- Tyler.
I'm psyched you're here.
- You look great.
- It really means a lot to me.
- So what the hell are you doing here?
- I know it's sudden.
I just wanted to see you.
Things are gonna start getting crazy
for you and Julie.
And I wanted to see you. Both of you.
I talked to Sarah, you know.
She said that you guys met up
when she was in town.
No. I talked to her about three hours ago.
She called,
while you were in the air, from LA.
- She's freaking out.
- Everything's fine.
I know what you're going through.
It's a scary leap.
The trick is you have to let go
of your fears...
...and just kind of go for it.
Believe me, the worst thing you can do
is lose the right girl...
...because of a fear of commitment.
The worst thing you can do
is marry the wrong girl...
...because of a fear of Ioneliness.
I can't wait for you to meet her.
I've told her all about you.
You have?
Yeah. I told her about all you guys.
I had to warn her.
Even my name?
You didn't mention my name.
No, of course not your name.
We refer to you all by your general nature,
like the Indians.
Mike is "Fucks Whatever Moves."
You're
"Dances Around Major Life Decisions."
What'd she say,
when you mentioned my name?
- What is wrong with you?
- I'm sorry.
What would she possibly say about...
Oh, there she is.
This is David. David, this is Julie.
So nice to finally meet you.
I feel like I already know you.
- I feel the same way.
- Isn't she beautiful?
You look like I did first time
I laid eyes on her.
I just knew right away.
It hit me like a blinding realisation, like...
Pure truth.
Was he always this sappy?
- Since I met you, baby.
- Will you order me a drink?
I'm going to go to the ladies' room.
Excuse me.
Now you know, buddy.
Now you understand.
That's it. This guy Jeff works
at Tyler's firm...
...knew my roommate,
and they hooked us up.
End of story.
That's... Wow, what a story.
The important thing is
that you ended up together?
Yeah.
I mean, think of all the people
you've met in your lives.
All the paths taken, not taken.
You can probably trace back to
your very first romantic memory.
- Lf you tried.
- Oh, yeah. Fifth grade drama class.
Miss Liska had us lie on the ground
and pretend we were driftwood.
And then as she walked
around the "beach"...
...she would step over us...
- We get it.
That's nice, sweetie.
What about you, Julie?
Oh, no. The airport guy?
The airport guy?
What about the airport guy?
- Tell me about this airport guy.
- It's okay, honey.
He's a friend.
Okay.
I was travelling with my family once.
We were in an airport...
...and this guy came up to me
from out of nowhere.
And he started,
saying aJJ these strange things to me...
...about how he feJt something
when he saw me...
...and he wondered if I feJt it, too.
I didn't know what to say,
so I just kind of smiJed at him.
He gave me his address...
...and asked, if I feJt the same
I shouJd write him.
And as he waJked away,
I had this frozen grin on my face.
I didn't want to agitate him or anything.
I was terrified
that he was going to hurt me.
Can you believe that?
How old were you, honey?
- Eleven.
- Eleven years old.
If that son of a bitch
were here right now...
But you wrote him!
I mean, did you ever write him?
No. Of course not.
Honey, do you want me to finish the story
for you?
- There's more?
- Yeah.
No, it's okay. I can do this.
So as soon as the guy was gone
I threw the address away.
But what I didn't know at the
time was that my JittJe sister Katie...
...who was two years younger than me...
...saw everything.
She wanted to be Jike me.
She worshipped me
and she started writing this creep, as me.
She even sent him my picture.
Then, of course, when he wrote back...
...weird stuff about how
he wanted to run away with her...
...and make babies.
Can you imagine that? Make babies?
And this is before the Internet.
What a sicko.
- I'm sorry, honey. Are you all right?
- But...
...did you ever find out who this guy was?
My parents did.
Sort of.
They overheard Katie
bragging to me about her boyfriend.
She had mentioned it before...
...so we just assumed it was
this imaginary pJay friend or something.
But when she started teJJing me about how
he'd promised to run away with her...
...and make Jove to her...
- CUnder the stars.
...they stepped in.
She was only nine.
So my dad called the authorities...
...gave them the guy's address...
...and, as was his style,
told us to forget the whole thing!
It wasn't until years later...
...that I realized the guy
thought he was writing me.
And then I pieced it together,
and I remembered the airport incident.
But I never told anyone.
I have to go.
- Are you all right?
- Where are you going?
I have to... Thank you for the...
Congratulations with... Good-bye.
I'd seen the Jight.
It was this gJaringJy-obvious,
bJind reaJisation...
...Jike pure truth.
And it was not about anyone in particuJar,
but about peopJe in generaJ.
I reaJised at that moment
there is no such thing as "the one."
It's more of a mind-boggJing,
whoJe heJJ of a Jot of potentiaJ ones.
And whiJe that shouJd be comforting,
it was actuaJJy pretty terrifying.
We'd aJJ Jike to kick back
and wait for some magicaJ force...
...to show us who we shouJd spend
the rest of our Jives with.
But the truth is...
...there isn't a Jightning boJt
to sJap you on the ass...
...and teJJ you to pick
this person over aJJ others.
If anything, it's Jike the rain.
Rain faJJs aJJ the time.
Sometimes you're prepared for it,
sometimes you're not.
Depending where you are when it hits
you either get caught or you don't.
In fact, most of us usuaJJy try Jike heJJ
to avoid it.
You might miss the bus.
You might catch the bus.
Maybe you remembered your umbreJJa,
maybe you didn't.
No big signs.
Just random,
torrentiaJ bursts of opportunity.
And that's the most fate can do.
The rest is up to us.
And now, by the power vested in me...
...I now pronounce you husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
So the eternal bachelor
was the first one to go.
I don't think I'll ever understand men.
- You look amazing.
- Thanks.
I'm very happy for you. I mean it.
Thanks.
I had a tough time for those
first few months.
It was really hard.
But then I had to take Nicole
to the emergency room...
...to get her stomach pumped again
and there he was.
Our eyes just met...
...and it was like
this indescribable feeling like...
I get it. Not that happy yet.
It's terrific you found someone
who deserves you.
But I'd be lying
if I said I didn't miss our friendship.
Okay. I think it's time
to stir things up on the dance floor.
Join me?
I think I'll pass.
I didn't bring any singles with me.
Joke.
Please remember there are
impressionable children out there.
- Let's keep it PG-13.
- No problem.
Hand me that dildo, will you?
- Amy.
- Yeah.
- Haven't seen her since college.
- She's great.
- You two...
- No. We're just friends.
I saw that goofy-Iooking bastard
that Sarah's with.
That guy, he's like missing
a chromosome or something.
- What a freak.
- We both know he's an attractive guy.
But, thank you for trying.
I bet he's no brain surgeon.
Shit. Really?
There you are.
Baby, you remember David.
You met him at the restaurant
a couple months ago.
Glad you didn't have to rush out
early today.
It was a beautiful ceremony.
Thank you. I'm just glad
my little sister got to catch the end.
Katie showed up? Honey, that's great.
I didn't think she would make it.
What happened?
- Your sister is here?
- Yeah.
But she doesn't like weddings.
She never got over that airport guy.
- The paedophile, the sicko.
- Asshole.
Honey, settle down.
You know I should really
introduce you two.
- You would totally hit it off.
- What a great idea.
- Why don't you go get her?
- No, no. That's not necessary.
- Virgin. Hot.
- I think I see her. Stay here.
I'll be right back.
What's the matter? You look like you did
the night at the restaurant when you...
I have to go.
...bolted.
- Lightning Taxi.
- Hi. I need a cab. Fast.
Ladies and gentJemen at this time,
Mike Hanson, the best man...
...wouJd Jike to make a toast
to JuJie and TyJer.
AJJ right, thank you.
Thank you.
Many of you don't know me...
...but I had the pJeasure of being...
...TyJer's roommate
in our fraternity house at schooJ.
Yeah, you were! Phi Lamb!
Who's my boy, Mikey? You're my boy!
And today I have the priviJege...
...of being the best man in his wedding.
Suffice it to say, I was shocked
to hear that he was getting married.
But over time as I taJked to him
on the phone...
...I began to understand.
We used to do everything together.
We were joined at the hip.
It struck me that
what these two peopJe were doing...
...was giving themseJves in to...
...a bJinding reaJisation.
Pure truth.
They stood before everyone they knew
and confessed their new found seJves.
I don't know,
but witnessing such strength...
...and courage in my friends...
...inspires me in a way
which I can bareJy put into words.
You see, whiJe many of you
don't know me...
...the rest of you onJy think you do.
The truth is you're about to meet
Mike Hanson for the first time.
My name is Mike Hanson...
...and I'm a raging homosexuaJ.
Thank you.
I didn't really know him that well.
And Jet's give it up to the newJyweds.
Congrats, guys.
Hit it.
Why does everybody keep trying
to set me up?
They're never him.
Katie, please come out and meet him.
You look amazing.
All right, let's go meet this guy.
Ladies! There you are!
- Katie, I'm so glad that you could make it.
- Thank you.
- We have to go. The limo is here.
- Wait. Have you seen David?
No. I think he left with Mike and Amy
because I haven't seen them, either.
But you know what?
We should forget about them.
I'm gonna meet you up front.
We really have to go.
- It's okay. You just go.
- No. You're coming with us.
No. It's your day. Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
- Are you sure?
- Positive. Just go, all right?
- Love you.
- Love you, too.
So, I don't mean to belittle
your big announcement...
...but come on, Mike,
you never even worked retail.
It makes sense.
All my life I've treated women like dirt,
never letting them get too close...
...just using and cruising.
That doesn't make you a homosexual.
It makes you an asshole.
- Excuse me, are you waiting for someone?
- No, I'm not waiting, I'm not waiting.
Wait a minute, that's my cab! That's my...
These insolent swine!
They call you and they tell you
to come right away. Big hurry!
And you come, they're not there.
And I feel like...
How do you say, "assholes"?
Yeah, I know the feeling.
You know the feeling?
Do you know the feeling?
So it was nice wedding, yes?
No, not again!
My God!
No, no. Please get up.
Are you all right?
It's you.
I have been looking everywhere for you.
What took you so long?
I feel all tingly inside.
I know. So do I.
No, in a scary way.
Right. We should get you to a hospital.
What are you doing?
You said you were gay.
Yeah, and your point is?