Male reporter: The U.S.
military presence abroad
was rocked today
when a bomb exploded--
Female reporter:
In the army barracks
in Dhahran, Saudi Arabia.
Second male reporter:
A multinational force--
Third male reporter:
Ripped the front
offthe 8-story
military dorm,
exposingjust how vulnerable
U.S. troops are here.
And marines on duty seem,
for the most part,
numbed by the horror
ofthe morning bombing.
Female reporter:
Early indications suggest this
to be the work
ofSheikAhmed Bin Talal,
a radical fundamentalist cleric
known to have issued--
The explosion appears
to be the work ofterrorists.
And ifthat is the case,
like all Americans,
I am outraged by it.
[Woman Singing In Arabic]
The cowards who committed
this murderous act
must not go unpunished.
Eagle Eye: Sand Leader,
this is Eagle Eye.
We have a fix on the package.
It is in a Mercedes sedan
traveling south--
Woman on radio:
Com-sat 1 ,
your coordinates
are as follows.
1 -8-0-5-0.
Package is approaching
target area.
Estimated time ofcontact
is approximately 1 -4 seconds.
[Speaking Arabic]
[Honking]
Yallah! Yallah!
[Speaking Arabic]
[Machine Gun Fire]
President Clinton:
Let me say again.
America takes care
ofour own.
Those who did it
must not go unpunished.
Sand Leader: Eagle Eye,
this is Sand Leader.
The sheik is in our custody.
Sand Leader:
He is alive and well,
and will be delivered intact
by 0800 tomorrow.
[Chanting In Arabic]
[Telephones Ringing]
Woman:
FBI. Good morning.
Man: FBI. Yes.
Good morning, sir.
Woman: FBI.
Counter-terrorism task force.
That was NYPD.
Brooklyn South
issued a code blue
less than 2 minutes ago,
and they think
hostages are involved.
Business or residence?
A bus.
Wejust got word
there's some kind
ofbomb on the bus.
Haveyou set up
a perimeter?
Working on it.
Okay. What about negotiators?
We got our people on the way?
Got it.
And what about
the bomb squad?
They're going in now.
[Police Radios Crackling]
[Sirens]
How soon
can we get there?
This time ofday?
Maybe tomorrow.
[Beeping]
[Siren]
[High-pitched Beep]
[People Screaming]
[Explosion]
Oh, fuck.
Man: Open the door!
What?
And nobody's hurt?
Electronically altered voice:
This is our first
and last warning.
We expect our demands to be met.
There will be no negotiation.
No more communication
ofany kind.
That is all.
Demand forwhat?
You hear any demand?
Maybe it's a prank.
Some sense ofhumor.
Here's what I know.
B.P., as in blue paint.
Voice-altering technology.
What doyou think?
Available from the
SharperImage catalog.
Last I looked, they didn't have
an exploding paint bomb.
Still, the rhetoric
sounds political.
You think it's militia?
- No, not their style.
- Frank?
IslamicJihad aren't known
for their sense ofhumor,
and Hamas is raising
so much money here.
Why queer their deal?
Isn't green the color
ofIslam, not blue?
Another good point. Tina,
rub these good points together.
Come up with a composite
ofthe suspects
by the end ofbusiness
today. Anita!
Anita: Yeah?
Run that against the mainframe
for me, okay?
Mike, lab analysis
on the paint.
Report's not in yet,
but we're checking
to see ifany blue paint
was sold in quantity.
Good. Danny, how are
the interviews going
with the victims?
Not great.
Check the bus stops.
Maybe somebody
saw him get on.
Hub, I thinkwe're all eager
to give up ourweekends on this.
Itjust occurs to me--
Has anyone
committed a crime here?
I mean assault
with a deadly color?
Here's what I don't like.
They know explosives.
That's not such a big deal.
Everybody on the internet
knows explosives,
but they know
our response time.
They put in a call,
and then theywalk.
I don't like that.
Excuse me, sir.
I thinkyou should see this.
Itjust came in
on the fax.
'' Release him.''
Release who?
Who do we got?
Bill Clinton?
He didn't do it.
Charlie Manson?
Danny: Hamas guy
was let go in April.
Frank: Under protest.
Yeah, but why be
so coy about it?
You think
it's a phony?
Tina: It's Floyd Rose.
Somebody's flashing
a government badge
at the warehouse where
they're working on the bus.
Our tech guys want to know
ifwe're cooperating
with any other agencies.
She's looking for the wiring
signatures for the device
and asking for copies
ofany fingerprints
we've managed to lift.
She CIA?
Smells like it.
Turns out she's also
been talking
to some
ofthe passengers.
Which one is she?
That's her over there
by the table.
Howyou doing?
Hi, there.
I'm Anthony Hubbard.
I'm the assistant
special agent in charge.
Oh, shit.
I've been trying to
liaise with you all day.
I'm Elise Kraft,
National
Security Council.
Pleasure. You've been trying
to liaise with me all day?
Haveyou checked
the phone book?
We got 1 4 lines, not including
the unlisted ones.
Hi. I'm Elise Kraft.
National
Security Council.
Howyou doing?
I'm Colin Powell.
What doyou people want
with my bus?
Hey. We're on the same team
here, Agent Hubbard.
Who, exactly, is ''we''
on this particular team?
It's never the question
that's indiscreet.
It's only the answer.
Tell you what, Elise.
You send me an official
interagency request
for cooperation, then
I'll giveyou copies
ofeverything we come
up with. How's that?
Other than that,
I gotta askyou to leave
beforeyou contaminate
my crime scene
any more
than you already have.
CIA has no charter
to operate domestically,
which puts you in violation
offederal law.
Hey, there's no reason
to be nasty.
You think
I'm being nasty?
Ifyou got something you
want to share with me,
being that we're
teammates?
Well, unfortunately, notyet,
but as soon as I do--
You'll let me know?
I'll tell you
what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna ask
some ofmy teammates
to escortyou
out ofhere.
Is that all right
with you?
Swell.
Peachy.
Elise.
Thankyou.
Is that Elise
with an ''A'' or an '' E''?
Nice meeting you, too,
Assistant Special Agent
in Charge Hubbard.
Anthony.
Pin a tail on her.
I'm on it.
You sleep here?
Immigration called.
Underneath the false bottom,
we found this.
All in small bills,
so we figured smurf, right?
And considering yesterday's
terrorist alert,
and where he's been recently,
we'd better call Frank.
Who's trying to score points
with his boss big-time.
Has he broken
any laws?
No, sir. He is $20 under
the $1 0,000 limit.
Not anymore.
So, Khalil,
you're saying this
is an inheritance?
Somebody died, and you're
bringing them the money.
No, no. Doory.
He means dowry.
Check out his neck.
1 0,000 for a wedding?
Frank: The tobacc--
[Puffs]
[Hisses]
Territories.
Put him in play.
Hub: He's heading north
onto Bell Parkway.
Back home
the security services
would be up this guy's ass
with a poker.
What do we do?
We let him go.
Stay back
a little bit, Frank.
It's not
my first date, Hub.
He's taking the BQE.
Looks like it's Brooklyn.
Probably Brooklyn.
He's all yours, Ray.
Ray, go a little softer
on him, okay?
Pass him offto Patsy.
Patsy, watch out
for reflections.
Hub: Okay, you got him.
Ah, here.
Got thejudge.
Morning,judge.
How areyou?
Yeah. How are things
down at Second Circuit?
Yeah, right.
I know whatyou mean.
Listen,
we got a situation here.
Who's he talking to?
Hold on one second,Judge.
Who is he talking to?
We getting film on this?
Who's he talking to?
Don't know him.
Ifwe were allowed
to get sound
on them, we'd know.
Hub: Yeah, yeah,Judge.
No, sir.
No, sir, notyet.
No, notyet, sir, but--
We got reason to--
Damn it, Mike.
Mike, back off.
Frank: Oh, shit.
He's making him.
Shit! Fuck!
Hub: All units go!
Look, I got to get
back toyou,Judge.
Shit!
[Horn Honks]
Hub: Go around.
Go around, Frank.
I got him, I got him.
Frank: There he is.
We got him.
Stiverson and Throop.
Cut him off!.
There he is.
Hey, come back, Khalil!
Khalil!
All units, we got a red van
going east on Stiverson
offofVernon. Red van.
Did you get plates
on that, Frank?
Plates? No.
Butyou got to love
that move.
No plates.
Theyjust found the van.
Doesn't look like
they'll find any prints.
Hub: Vehicle I.D.?
Reported stolen
plates are bogus, too.
What about hair, fiber?
Already on its way
to the lab.
Hub, we're checking
this guy out
in the red book
right now.
Goodjob, Mike.
It's Floyd Rose.
Go, Floyd.
Floyd: You're not
gonna believe this.
Guess who
just showed up.
How's she living, Floyd?
She's got 2 in a Plymouth,
at least 3 inside,
and see that guy
walking his dog?
He did his business
about an hour ago,
and they're still walking.
I had a dog
like that once.
It's not his dog, wet wick.
They're spies.
The dog works
for the CIA?
Hub over radio:
All units report.
This is unit one.
We're good to go.
Man on radio:
Unit 2, we're ready.
All right, let's roll.
Federal agents!
Against the fence!
[Dog Barking]
Man: FBI!
Putyour hands
behind your head.
Hi, guys.
I expectyou know the drill.
Man: Hold it right there.
Hello.
Elise.
I never touched him.
Really?
Well, we're gonna
have to take him
into custody anyway.
Mike, Frank.
What areyou gonna charge
him with,jaywalking?
I don't suppose I could have a
little chat with him here first?
I don't think so, Elise.
Not in this lifetime.
You know, Hub--
May I call you Hub?
Yes, you may.
Ifyou guys hadn't blown
the surveillance,
we'd have been able
to follow the money.
What doyou say, Khalil?
You would have led us right
toyour friends, wouldn'tyou?
What friends?
Take him out.
What friends, Elise?
What haveyou got
for me, huh?
Come on. Share something
with me, Elise.
Enlighten me.
You can tell me now,
oryou can tell me downtown.
You know, one phone call,
and he's mine.
You know the number.
I have about, uh--
You have the right
to remain silent.
to an attorney.
That's whatyou also have.
Oh, come on.
Hey, doyou have
any idea
whatyou're
starting here?
What kind ofshit storm
this could turn into?
Kidnapping,
obstruction ofjustice,
assault.
Get her out ofhere.
I love whatyou've done
with the place.
Frank: So, Elise,
you okay back there?
you don't get carsick
or anything?
those handcuffs
too tight?
Shuf Mountains, Right?
Shiite or Sunni?
Wow.
You're really good.
She's really good.
So what's going on
here, Elise?
Paint bomb,
was that a warning?
American University
of Beirut.
I was there
from '79 to '82.
No shit.
Yeah. My father taught
economics. Henry Kraft.
Is there a terrorist cell
operating in the city
that we're unaware of?
It's such a tragedy.
Growing up there
was like paradise.
Like an exotic Paris.
Right, Frank?
Yeah, it's real exotic
on Rikers Island, too.
You know what they do
to women in there?
Mmm, yum.
Okay.
[Telephone Rings]
Frank here.
Go.
3 men, definitely armed,
and this time
they're still on the bus.
So no communication
ofany kind?
No, no, it's weird.
They'rejust in there.
Just in there. Okay.
See ifyou can get the frequency
ofthe bus driver's radio.
We'll try and get him
on the phone.
Frank.
Yeah.
Get a couple
ofdat phones, okay?
Make sure they're
secure portables.
Perfect.
The negotiator's on his way.
A couple oftechies,
too, Frank.
We want sound.
Sir.
There's children
on that bus.
We counted about 6.
That gives us something
to workwith, then, doesn't it?
Elise: What's happening
out there?
Take her outside
the perimeter, will you?
They've taken another bus,
haven't they?
Hey, talk to me.
You want to talk now.
You want me to beyour
friend now. Is that it?
Listen. These guys
are the real deal.
Are they?
How doyou know?
Is there a terrorist cell
operating in Brooklyn?
Yes.
The blue bus,
was that a warning?
Yes, and I'm afraid
they're gonna blow this one.
How doyou know they're
gonna blow the bus
ifthey haven't
blown it already?
- I don't know.
- You don't know.
They haven't asked
for anything, have they?
Frank: The driver's name
is Larry Kaiser.
He says they've got
explosives
strapped
to their chests,
they've got
automatic weapons,
and he thinks they're
speaking Arabic.
Where the hell
is the negotiator?
The tunnels
got 20-minute delays.
They're working
on both bridges.
Okay, did he say anything else
about the device?
Did he describe it an anyway?
Did he talk about cords
or buttons or anything?
No. He didn't say.
Oh.
Oh, God.
They're not here
to negotiate.
Meaning?
Theywere waiting
for the cameras.
Theywant everybody
watching.
You've got
the shooters in place?
Yeah. So?
Use them.
Kill them now.
Look, it's lose-lose
anywayyou play it.
You want to lose
little or lose big?
I got the marksmen
on the com.
They're waiting
for a clean shot.
Let me have the phone.
Hello, Larry.
This is Agent Hubbard,
FBI.
I'm gonna be negotiating
ourway out ofthis.
Hub: Yes, we got somebody
here who can translate,
butyou gotta remain calm.
All right.
Put them on the phone.
Hello, sir.
My name is Anthony.
I wantyou to know right from
the start I'm not the boss.
[Speaking Arabic]
I don't have the authority
to negotiate any deals
or to respond to any demands.
[Speaking Arabic]
You need anything in there?
Any medical supplies?
Anybody need any help?
[Speaking Arabic]
I don't even know
ifthey understand.
Look, I knowyou may not
want to talk to me,
but areyou willing
to listen to me?
[Speaking Arabic]
Whatever grievances you have,
whatever quarrels,
surely it doesn't involve
these children.
[Speaking Arabic]
I'm asking you, please,
would you please
let the children go?
[Frank Speaking Arabic]
Please.
[Speaking Arabic]
Thankyou.
Thankyou very much.
I appreciateyour gesture.
The best way
to get whatyou want
in this situation is to show
yourselfto be reasonable,
which you have done.
I appreciate that.
I really do.
This way, kids.
Come on.
Keep going.
Now we got some more
to talk about.
As you can see,
I'm unarmed.
I have no weapons.
And what I propose...
is thatyou let
these people go...
and I'll take their place.
This wayyou don't have to worry
about pizza deliveries
or people running back
and forth to the bathroom
or anything like that.
[Speaking Arabic]
And I guaranteeyou
that the police department,
FBI, everybody,
they'll disappear.
You look out
yourwindow now,
you'll see the helicopters
are already moving out.
I'm gonna takeyour silence
to mean thatyou're
considering my offer.
I'll tell you what.
Why don'tyoujust let
the elderly people go?
[Speaking Arabic]
You know these old people.
They've been standing
up there for a long time.
Why notjust let them go?
[Speaking Arabic]
Thankyou very much.
Now wejust--
[Sirens]
[Inaudible]
Female reporter:
The worst terrorist bombing
in the United States
in the past 5 years
took place on this site
earlier today.
Male reporter: Beirut came
to Brooklyn today
when the worst terrorist
bombing in the United States
since Oklahoma City
took the lives
ofmore than 25 people--
Second female reporter:
Authorities are withholding
the names ofthose
who died--
Second male reporter:
No group has yet stepped forward
to take responsibility
for the blast.
Authorities are refusing
to comment
other than to say
that the investigation
is alreadywell underway.
All right,
everybody take a seat.
ASAICs, supervisors.
Just got offthe phone
with leaders
ofthe Arab community.
We have their complete
support and cooperation.
they love this country
as much as we do.
Theywant these criminals
brought tojustice
as badly as we do.
Having said that,
let me say this.
I want to rumble
every trap, hole, market,
community center,
every student organization
that has ever said a bad word
about this country,
I want to know about 'em.
I wantyou to turn the heat up
under every one
ofyour resources. Every one.
Every snitch,
twist him inside out.
Every source,
turn him upside down.
See what falls
out ofhis pocket.
Shake the trees,
throw some money at 'em.
Whatever it takes.
I want results.
Call your families,
find a sleeping bag,
Because nobody
is going home
until we find a strand
to pull on.
I don't want to see
anybodywalking!
You better be running!
What?
- Now, mike.
- Yeah.
Haveyou got
positive I.D.?
We don't have a positive I.D.
on anybody.
All right.
Oklahoma City.
The first 24 hours
are the only 24 hours.
Do whatyou do best.
[Whispering]
Tell me about the money.
[Speaking Arabic]
He says he loves America.
He onlywanted to get away
from the security services.
Sure, sure. Tell me
about the money.
[Speaking Arabic]
He'sjust sorry.
He didn't know he was
doing anything bad.
Tell me about the money!
[Speaking Arabic]
His cousin
introduced him to a man
who promised him $200
for his dowry
ifhe took the suitcase
to an address in Brooklyn.
He's a mule.
[Door Opens
And Closes]
I want to run down
every rental agreement
from every landlord
in Brooklyn.
Hotels, motels, flophouses.
It's cash.
They're the only ones
in America using cash.
We got a positive I.D.
on 5 ofthe victims so far.
I need a 6-man team.
I have put a lot
ofmoney in thisjoker.
It's about time
he started earning it.
I don't care about
any convention.
I want to see all
security cam videos
from every nearbyATM,
convenience store, bank...
What's the time difference
between here and Amman?
Uh, 7 hours.
This is a plasmagram
ofthe symtex used in bus 87.
As you can see,
the signature's identical
to that used
in the army barracks.
Frank: What kind ofidents
do we have so far?
We're still checking all
the latents on the computer.
Man: I'm looking
for real-time video.
I need faces,
not voices.
Ifit's
international,
we're talking
a $2 million reward.
Yeah, I want a list
ofthe next 1 0 targets.
Frank:
Checkwith Interpol.
Any foreign matter?
We got some shrapnel.
We got to run it
through the lab,
see ifit matches
the metal on the bus.
Does the lab stay open
till we find out what
we're dealing with orwhat?
24 hours. You busy?
What a fuckin' mess.
Excuse me, sir.
Got a hit.
I found him.
This is the list
ofthe probables.
And that's the hit.
Ali Waziri.
Ladies and gentlemen...
[Clears Throat]
meet the late, uh,
Ali Waziri,
one ofthe bombers
ofbus 87.
We were able to trace
this sucker
to a, uh...
group in Ramallah.
That's West Bank,
not west side,
for all you peoplejust
joining us from Nebraska.
Tina.
We pulled his landing card
and his I-94,
so now we know he came in
3 days ago out of Frankfurt.
What we need now is to fill in
the time between his arrival
and the time
ofthe incident.
We need
all known associations,
and most ofall,
we need an address.
Here's the kicker, guys--
Ali Waziri was on
the terrorist watch list.
How'd he
get into the country?
Here it is.
Student visa.J-one.
Now, where's
the original?
Probably in his passport.
Where's
the passport?
It's in a million pieces.
Where's the copy?
Point ofissuance.
Could be American consulate
in Tel Aviv, Amman, Cairo...
every legal attache
that we have
in every consulate
in every city that Frank
just mentioned,
get them on the phone.
I want the visa. Yes?
Sir, they need you
in the lab.
I want the visa,
Danny.
It's cotton.
Pure unadulterated
egyptian cotton.
Soyou're saying
they're Egyptian.
No. What i'm saying is
this isjust--
What they use
in funerals.
Guywas wearing
a shroud.
The real deal?
That's right.
I'm gonna go have
a little chat
with our new friend.
I thought one phone call
and you were out ofhere.
Yeah, well,
I didn't make the call.
Why not?
Areyou all right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. A little tinnitus
in the ear.
I need to know
what I don't know.
Yeah, life's too short.
Areyou hungry?
Are we ordering in?
The funeral shroud
is the final step
in the ritual of
self-purification.
First, a fast, then--
the washing ofthe body,
then the shroud, right.
I saw it
on 60 Minutes.
Tell me something
I don't know.
In March,
we identified the man
we believed responsible
for bombing
the army barracks lastyear.
In August, he went to Lebanon
where he was extracted.
Extracted?
Extracted bywhom?
I see.
His name's
SheikAhmed Bin Talal.
He's Iraqi.
He's something
ofa religious leader.
With something of
a devoted following?
Hmm.
Okay, I can understand.
Whywe wouldn't want
to advertise the fact
that, uh, our government's
in the kidnapping business,
but why not let us know?
Well, he's still
being debriefed.
They don't want to go public
with the charges.
What about
his followers?
Well, clearly
they're committed.
Meaning?
In this game,
the most committed wins.
Hub. Excuse me.
We made the guy
in the picture.
Frank: My people.
The last of
the unambivalent smokers.
His name is
Samir Nazhde.
He teaches Arab Studies
at Brooklyn College.
He's the one who sponsored
Ali Waziri's student visa.
And dig this--
His brother blew up
a movie theater in Tel Aviv.
You might consider
leaving him alone.
Whywould we
consider that?
Well, you can play him
like a cop
and haul him in now
and getyour arrest,
oryou can tag him,
let him lead you
to the really big fish.
[Speaking Arabic]
You're fishing, and he's
getting visas for bombers.
You ever heard of
catch-and-release?
Mm-hmm. And he's on
the first plane to Tunis.
[Sighs]
Hub.
Hub, now's the time.
Take him down.
Go.
FBI.
FBI. Freeze!
Hey, hey, hey! Ow!
Uhh!
Samir Nazdhe,
my name is Frank Haddad.
I'm a federal agent.
We have reason to believe
thatyou're an accessory
in the bombing ofbus 87.
Areyou crazy?
You were an associate
ofAli Waziri.
Sir, I know nobody
ofthat name.
You sponsored
his student visa.
I sign these applications
as a matter ofcourse.
Hundred ofthem.
You know how it is.
Everybodywants
to come to America--
You spent 2 years in Israeli
jails during the Intifada.
Well, yeah, I did,
but the only ones who didn't
were women, likeyou.
Ay!
[Both Speaking Arabic]
Frank.
I'm sorry.
Family matter.
You're going downtown,
my friend.
You cannot harm me.
I know my rights.
Defrauding the I.N.S.
is a federal offense.
Reservation for one,
please.
We need a search warrant
on Samir.
Samir.
Frank, let me talk
toyou for a second.
You ever hit
a prisoner again,
I'm gonna have
your badge.
Someday I'll tell you
what his people
did to myvillage in '75.
All right, all right.
Your preaching's required.
Just don't do it again.
All right?
Now act like I'm capable
ofsaying something funny.
Some people are watching.
Hey, Danny,
find me ajudge
who'll play ball
with me this time
and set up a polygraph
for Samir.
You know, I still
don't understand
whywe're tipping
our hand with him.
What's there
to tip?
Yeah,
what's there to tip?
Protecting your asset,
aren'tyou? Aren'tyou?
He's your asset,
he's yourjoe,
he's working foryou,
you're his case officer, right?
Uh, sometimes, in addition
to being a nationality,
being a Palestinian
is a profession,
a very lucrative one.
Meaning he's yourjoe,
right?
Mine, yours,
the Israelis,
the Saudis.
One time or another,
everybody
in the Middle East
is sleeping
with everybody else.
Soyou're saying
you sleep around.
Only professionally.
So we share.
- No.
- No?
Call I.N.S.,
check Samir's status,
start deportation
procedures.
I can't letyou do that.
Oh, you can't
let me do that.
What precisely
is your involvement
with these people, Elise?
Samir has been
a very important project
ofmine for some time.
I'm the only one
he'll deal with.
He's verywell-connected
and extremely high-strung.
Call I.N.S., Frank.
How easy is it
to get inside, Frank?
How good areyour sources
in the community?
How many people
you got in Hamas? Huh?
No surveillance. I've
seen your deft touch.
Daily reports,
we tap his phone.
I see the transcripts.
No problem.
- And I run him.
- We share him.
No. He can't know
we're talking.
I won't tell him.
- And no poly?
- Never.
Done.
All right,
let him fly, Frank,
but I want to see
some food on my plate,
you understand me?
Any more surprises
for me, Elise?
Not tonight.
I'm gonna get some sleep.
You let him hit me!
How can you
let them hit me?
Well, next time,
don't be such a smart-ass.
Hey, don't tell me
what I have to do.
Do we really have to have
this conversation again?
Do we?
[Speaking Arabic]
I need you to help me.
I need you
to be strong,
likeyou've always
been strong,
for both ofus.
Samir, look at me.
Look at me.
[Telephone Rings]
[Ring]
[Beep]
Go.
Yeah, Frank?
You know, some peoplejust
cannot live in the camps.
For my brother,
it was already like dying.
The only thing
he lives for is movies.
And then some sheik came
and tell him that...
to die forAllah
is beautiful.
And ifhe does this thing,
our parents
will be taken care of,
and he will live on
in paradise with 70 virgins.
I mean...
[Chuckles, Sniffles]
70.
And my brother,
he need to believe it
very much.
So he straps 1 0 sticks
ofdynamite to his chest.
And he went to the movie.
And then I become a V.I.P.
It's very confusing.
So who areyou
afraid ofbetraying?
We know these people.
They bomb, they maim.
They represent the Palestine
you want to build?
They're using you.
You are using me, too.
Everybody uses
the Palestinians.
Hey. You make reports
about our little talks?
And what about fucking me?
I had to get special
permission for that.
Beats the shit
out ofcable.
He asked to wait inside.
Good morning.
Bill Devereaux.
I know whoyou are.
I was with the 82nd--
Airborne.
Yeah, I know.
I was in the 1 73rd
at the time.
God, duty,
honor, country--
- Remember?
- Mm-hmm.
Where on Capitol Hill
orWall Street or Hollywood
haveyou heard anyone utter
one ofthose phrases
in the last 1 0 years?
What brings you
to New York, General?
The president's concerned.
He's worried that--
Haveyou met the president?
Uh, no, I haven't.
I read the newspapers,
though.
I know he's concerned
about terrorism.
Well, with all due
affection for the man,
the president
doesn't know fuck-all
about the Mideast
or terrorism
that I don't write
on his cue cards.
He is an expert
in covering his own ass,
ifyou catch my meaning.
Yes, I do.
So I guess you didn't
come up here
just for a cup
ofcoffee, huh?
With all due respect,
I thinkwe're on
the right track.
That's exactly
what I told the president.
The army's not some big
green police machine.
Stickwith the men
on the ground
is what I advised
the president.
Well, I appreciate
your support.
As long as you're sureyou're
not chasing your tail here.
So what can you
tell me
about the Sheik
Ahmed Bin Talal?
Just that he's old news.
But we received
2 communications
from the bombers
to release him.
We can't release him.
I know our stated policy
is to never negotiate--
We can't release him
because we don't have him.
We never did.
Our latest intel
says that he's dead.
The agency
doesn't think so.
The CIA didn't know
the Berlin Wall was coming down
until bricks started
hitting them in the head.
Who's your source?
Elise Kraft.
A woman will never
understand the Middle East.
Just between you and me,
Elise Kraft wouldn't know
a sheik from a prophylactic
by the same name.
Well, I, uh, appreciate
the heads up.
Hub, we followed up
that tip on--
Why, Elise,
what a nice surprise.
How areyou?
Hello, General.
How nice
to seeyou again.
Please,
don't let me interrupt.
Uh, sorry. The tip on
the landlord--it looks solid.
Sounds like I should
get out ofyourway
and letyou
get back to work.
Agent Hubbard. Pleasure.
Ifyou need anything,
you know where we are.
Thankyou.
Making new friends?
Not 2 judges from now,
not 2 hours from now,
not 2 minutes from now.
These guys are gonna
split any second.
Frank's working on
anotherwarrant.
You don't understand.
These guys are pros.
From the age of 1 2,
they've been dodging
people likeyou,
people better than you.
Yeah, well,
even people likeyou.
Hub, this isn't about
your sparkling record, okay?
Okay. It's
against the law, Elise.
Yeah,just because
you went to night school
or filled out the back
ofa matchbook,
whateveryou did
to get a law degree,
doesn't makeyou
SirThomas More.
Andjust because
you checked my files...
You're gonna lose them!
doesn't makeyou
an expert on me.
You think
I want to lose them?
You think I'm in
the losing people business, huh?
IfI don't
take them down properly,
they hit the streets
in 2 hours.
I don't care ifI find symtex,
plutonium, dynamite,
self-lighting
charcoal briquettes--
without the right warrant,
theywalk, you understand?
They've also
got a warrant, okay?
A warrant from God.
They're ready to die.
Your quaint laws,
they don't mean shit
to these people.
Last I checked,
you're an American citizen.
You know,
I sawyour file, too.
And I'm sorry
that the Cold War is over
and all you little masters-
of-the-universe CIA types
got no work over in
Afghanistan or Russia
or Iran orwhatever
the hell it is,
but this ain't
the Middle East.
Oh, really?
We're in.
[Men Speaking Arabic
Over Headphones]
Frank: It's the same guys
as the bus. I know it.
What are they saying?
They're discussing
how difficult it is
to find a decent
cup ofcoffee over here.
I make out 3 voices.
What haveyou got?
It seems like 3.
Ifwe had microwave,
we'd know for sure.
The CIA's got microwave.
How come we don't
have microwave?
There are 3 ofthem.
All day long,
theywatch TV.
And eat pizza.
Nothing but pizza.
Pizza, pizza, pizza.
Pizza.
You want change
orwhat?
No. Put it on floor.
Haven'tyou heard? Crime
is down 7% in this city.
[Speaking Arabic]
[Clapping]
Hooray for pizza!
[Conversing In Arabic]
FBI! Hands in the air!
Putyour gun down!
FBI! Freeze!
Aah!
Abort!
- 2 up!
- 3 up!
We're clear!
Hubbard: Everybody okay?
We're good.
Good, good.
You all right?
Yeah.
How we doing
over here? Fred?
He's terminal.
Mike?
He's dead.
Elise?
Gone.
Hub.
Take a look.
It's all here,
every component.
Det cords, symtex.
Just like the bus.
We got 'em.
Female reporter: 3 men
were reported killed today
after a shootout
with the FBI
in a quiet neighborhood
in Brooklyn.
Male reporter: Already there are
unconfirmed reports ofa link
between the victims, who are
reported to be Arab-speaking,
and the bombers ofbus 87.
FBI spokesman,
Anthony Hubbard.
Uh, we are presently
following up on as many leads,
and, uh, we're confident
that we're on the right track.
I thinkwe're all happy
that these criminals
are offthe streets,
and we can all get on
with our lives.
Dad!
Yeah!
[Chanting In Arabic]
I think the FBI
deserves special recognition
for the speed
with which they handled
this current crisis.
I'd especially like
to single out
Special Agent Tony Hubbard
and the men and women
ofthe NYPD, FBI...
Here we are.
Drink up, everyone.
My first boyfriend
was Palestinian.
You know, my father
used to say
they seduceyou
with their suffering.
Haveyou ever
been over there?
Haveyou seen the camps?
No. No, never been.
Oh, there's these incredibly
warm, hospitable people,
living in
this horrible place.
Butyetyou work
against them.
Only the crazy.
I tend to be suspicious
ofall true believers,
present company
included.
Areyou saying
I'm a fanatic?
Why areyou a fed?
You read my file.
You tell me.
Okay. All right,
I'll tell you.
Catholic school...
St. Raymond's
in the Bronx.
President ofthis,
captain ofthat,
hard work,
make a difference,
fair play,
change the system
from within.
Rah-rah-rah.
What?
What aboutyou?
What doyou believe?
Like what?
Like right and wrong.
It's easy
to tell the difference
between right and wrong.
Is it?
yes. what's hard is
choosing the wrong
that's more right.
I just...
Okay.
[Laughing]
No, I just want
to make things
a little better, okay?
Ignore me.
I'm shitfaced.
Elise. Elise.
- Frank.
- Ahh.
Hi.
Tell us all about
being a spook.
Come on.
It's the Bay of Pigs.
You're there on the beach
with all the Girl Scouts.
I love the wayyou guys
predicted the fall of
the Soviet Union. Genius.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, right.
AndJ. Edgar Hoover
wore a dress, right?
Mmm. I love Lebanese men.
Come on, let's dance.
Come on, Hub.
Dance with me.
Sure.
It's yourwife.
[Laughing]
[Slow Song Playing]
Oh.
Oh,jeez.
This feels
like high school.
Yeah.
Except my prom date
didn't wear a gun.
So what's the latest
on Samir?
I want a list ofevery
visa he sponsored.
I'm not sure
he'll do it.
No?
You know, I once knew
this undercover guy
who cared so much
for his source...
He's a source,
period.
You ever consider
the fact
that he might be in bed
with the other side?
Samir in bed with them?
That would be too much
to wish for.
You're so confident.
Only in bed.
[Glass Shattering]
[Rumbling]
[Horns Honking]
[Siren]
Frank:
It's a Broadway theater.
It went offjust as people were
getting up for intermission.
There are bodies everywhere.
[Horns Honking]
[Screaming]
Sir, help 'em!
They're trapped inside!
Male reporter: No group
has taken responsibility
for the bombing yet
so far as we know.
Female reporter: Scores of
the wealthiest and brightest
of New York society
were killed last night
when a bomb ripped
through a crowded theater.
The list ofvictims
is a veritable who's who
ofthe city's
cultural leaders.
You can be sure that all of
our considerable resources
are being brought to bear
on the situation.
Male reporter: New York City
has been brought to its knees
by the events
ofthe past week.
Retail sales are down 72%.
Hate crimes
have skyrocketed.
And the FBI seems,
at least for the moment,
incapable ofstopping
the terror.
Once busy streets
are eerily silent
as many have fled.
Man: Ira, why do they let
those people in the country?
They know
who those people are.
Woman: Ifyou think i'm
gonna let my kids out there
with all this stuffgoing on,
you have got to be crazy.
Female reporter: The Senate
Intelligence Committee
today authorized
a special panel
to investigate the current
situation in New York City.
Announcer: Tonight at 1 0:00--
terrorism in the United States.
Man:
The worst kind ofreaction
is a reaction
that's based on fear.
Frank:
He says ifyou're
on the State Department
terrorist watch list,
you cannot get
into the country.
So I sayAli Waziri
was on the watch list,
and he got in.
What did
the State Department say?
They told me
to call I.N.S.
What did I.N.S. say?
They told me
to call State.
[Loud Bang]
Oh, God!
The purpose ofthis meeting--
is to keep
our city safe,
and your department's
responsibility--
My department what,
asshole?
is to keep us safe.
[Arguing]
[Feedback]
Look, I'm very sorry, but we're
gonna have to raise our hands
before we ask a question, okay?
Yes, sir?
Howard Kaplan, I.N.S.
Howyou doing,
Howard?
Good, thanks.
So, we pulled every
ethnic visa in the city
and traced them
to the source.
Danny?
Bring 'em in,
and we talk to 'em.
What about translators?
Woman: How many people
we talking about here?
1 ,600, maybe more.
- 1 ,600?
- That's right.
Where are we gonna
put 1 ,600 people?
Danny, slow down, okay?
Yes, sir?
What about
a military presence
atJ FK and La Guardia?
I don't thinkwe're thereyet,
and I don't think it's gonna
stop these criminals. Sir?
What about protecting
the Arab population?
There's a lot
ofanger out there.
I represent the Arab
Antidefamation League.
Whatever injustices
my people may be suffering
at this very difficult
moment, we will continue
to show our commitment
to this country.
I appreciate that.
thankyou, sir.
And I want to thank everybody
for their patience today.
This has been
an extremely difficult--
[Beeping]
time.
London, Paris,
Athens, Rome,
Belfast, Beirut--
We're not the first city
to have to deal with terrorism.
In Tel Aviv--
[Beeping]
In Tel Aviv, the day after they
bombed the market in Tel Aviv,
the market was open,
and it was full.
[Beeping]
This is New York City...
[Ring]
[Beeping]
We can take it.
[Pagers Beeping,
Cell Phones Ringing]
Oh, my God.
It's the Buckley School.
Not kids.
One ofthe moms
was carrying a gun,
wounds the guy as he's
planting the device.
He kills her, then he
locks them all on the roof.
Any kids get hurt?
I don't know.
It's over there
on the table.
I don't know ifit's
a radio or a timer orwhat.
Whoa, hold right there.
See ifyou can move in
a little closer on the device.
Right there. Focus that.
Radio device.
He's got a radio control.
Frank: What the fuck's
the news media doing here?
They must have been
monitoring our frequency.
Danny, your boys were
supposed to call the F.A.A.
to clear the airspace!
I'm on it, I'm on it.
Do it now.
This is NYPD...
Get those fuckin' birds
out ofhere!
[Girl Crying]
Hub.
[Screaming]
Everybody out.
Takeyour time.
Frank:
Need some help here.
All right, come on.
Eitherwe answer this threat
quickly and convincingly,
or next week, there
will be a hundred more
all over the world.
Sounds great, General.
Why can't we find out
who's behind it?
It seems to me,
gentlemen,
that conventional
law enforcement
just isn't
up to the task.
How about who's behind
who's behind this?
Either Libya, Iran, Iraq,
possibly Syria.
Ask a question,
get an atlas.
All I know is
that we must respond.
That's an excellent
idea, Senator.
How do we do that?
Find out who they are
and bomb the shit out ofthem.
And ifwe
can't find out?
I hate to be the voice ofdoom,
but it keeps escalating.
First a bus, then a theater.
What's next?
How about sending in
the National Guard?
The National Guard is
for riot control, Senator,
not for counterterrorism.
The army then. I've read
the contingency plans.
It's established
legal doctrine--
posse comitatus.
the army can't be turned
against our own people.
Even ifthat's what are own
people are asking for, 3 to 1 ?
Ifthe president's willing
to declare a state of--
President Lincoln declared
martial law in 1 862.
he suspended habeas corpus.
Which
the Supreme Court
later found
unconstitutional.
Ex parte millegan.
And I've got an election
in November--
Ex-United States
Congressman.
Let's save the quips for
the Sunday morning talk shows.
The president's plane
lands in 2 hours,
and we owe it to him
to have a consensus.
You don't fight ajunkyard dog
with A.S.P.C.A. rules.
Whatyou do is
you take the leash
offyour own
bigger, meaner dog.
General.
The army's a broadsword,
not a scalpel.
Trust me, Senator,
you do not want the army
in an American city.
But hypothetically,
how long would it
takeyou to deploy?
You know we can't go in
until the president invokes
the War Powers Act.
I understand that,
General.
Let's assume
for a moment
that the order
has been given.
1 2 hours after the president
gives the order,
we can be on the ground.
One light infantry division
of 1 0,700 men.
Elements ofthe rapid
deployment force,
special forces, delta,
A.P.C.S, helicopters,
tanks,
and, ofcourse, the ubiquitous
M-1 6 A-1 assault rifle.
A humble enough weapon until
you see it in the hands ofa man
outsideyour local
bowling alley or 7-1 1 .
It will be noisy,
it will be scary,
and it will not be mistaken
for a VFW parade.
I remind you,
General Devereaux
does not speak for
official army policy.
A police function
has become accepted
as our role in Haiti
and Somalia.
Make no mistake.
We will hunt down
the enemy,
we will find the enemy,
and we will
kill the enemy.
And no card-carrying member
ofthe ACLU
is more dead set against it
than I am,
which is why I urgeyou...
I imploreyou...
do not consider this
as an option.
I knowjust what
the president's going to say.
That's exactlywhyyou're
the only man for thejob.
I'd like to introduce
Anthony Hubbard.
He's myASAIC on the ground
up in Brooklyn.
His team was able to take out
the first cell within 36 hours
ofthe attack on the 87 bus.
He's also the man
who took out the terrorist
in that schoolhouse.
Hub.
Thejob ofthe FBI is to...
to respond.
Thejob ofthe army--
to defend.
With the presence
ofthe army,
our ability to investigate
will be seriously inhibited.
It will push these criminals
further underground.
Most importantly,
you can't fight a war
against an enemy
you can't see.
I think ifwe exercise
patience, restraint,
allow our men and women
up in New York
to do theirjob...
I thinkwe'll be effective.
Thankyou,
Agent Hubbard.
I, too, think that we should
proceed with caution.
Some ofyou may not know
Sharon Bridger.
Sharon was posted
in Iraq
as part of
our covert operations
during the GulfWar.
Sharon.
Sir, ifI may.
Thankyou.
I'm sure everyone here
knows the traditional model
ofthe terrorist network.
One cell controls
all others.
Cut offthe head,
the bodywill wither.
Unfortunately, the old wisdom
no longer applies.
The new paradigm
is each cell
operates independent
ofthe other.
Cut offone head,
another rises up in its place.
Bus 87 was the work
ofthe first cell
whose remaining elements,
we believe,
the FBI took down.
This then activated
the work ofcell 2.
The theater gala.
At the most,
we believe, there are 3,
possibly 4 cells.
Well, then how much longer
before we can take out
the last cell?
We don't know.
Male reporter: This is a tragedy
ofstaggering proportion.
One Federal Plaza
was the headquarters
ofthe FBI counterterrorism
task force,
as well as many other
federal agents...
Female reporter:
Authorities are withholding
the names ofthose who died.
Male reporter: The worst
in New York City's history.
The most devastating...
Second newsman:
Letters ofcondolence
have been received from
leaders around the world.
Boris Yeltsin forwarded
a message...
Body count's
a little over 200 so far.
What about our people?
Mike, Tina.
Theywere all
in there working.
Hub.
This is Colonel Hardwick,
army intelligence.
Colonel.
I'm here as an advisor only.
I intend to keep
a low profile.
Appreciateyour concern.
I don't mean
to be insensitive,
but, uh,just what exactly are
your capabilities at this point?
Your infrastructure?
You're standing on
our infrastructure.
Excuse me.
Hey, Hub,
they managed to get
a partial VI N number
offthe van.
DMV says it was reported
stolen the day before...
in Brooklyn?
You got it.
Hub, the final body count
just came in.
600 dead.
[Doorbell Buzzes]
I'm very sorry
aboutyour friends.
Frank, it's, uh...
Sharon.
I didn't catch
your last name, Sharon.
Bridger.
Howyou doing, Frank?
Been better.
[Sighs]
Well...
the agency came up with
another list ofprobables.
I thinkwe should
circulate them.
Hey...
this stuffmight be good.
Whywas there
no warning from Samir?
Because he didn't
know anything.
Says Samir.
Says me.
Maybe I'll ask him.
Yeah, over my dead body.
Over 600 dead bodies.
Look, he's one
ofthe good guys, okay?
How can you be so sure?
Because he was part
ofthe operation
to destabilize
Saddam Hussein with me, okay?
Samir is a go-between.
He risked his life
for us over there.
Go-between who, Sharon?
Look, come on,
I need names, okay?
I need--I need photographs
or something, okay?
I don't need
a history lesson.
I can't giveyou pictures
because I don't know
what they look like.
We did everything
at arm's length.
Soyou got nothing?
I've got Samir.
Well, does Samir have
any contact with them?
Minimal.
So how does he do it?
He can't.
They initiate.
And otherwise?
He's waiting.
He's--He's waiting?
What the hell
is he waiting for?
More bodies?
More buildings?
We got a lot ofbuildings
out there.
Maybe he's waiting to blow up
a few more ofthem.
Hey, look, I know
howyou must feel.
Hey, look, you don't
know how I feel.
I lost friends
ofmine tonight.
You don't know how I feel!
They'll make
contact soon.
When? That's what I want
to know--when?
Why soon?
Why not now?
What is the trade craft?
What are the visuals?
What are
the iron sights?
You know, all that
CIA spy shit.
All right, I'll tell you
what I'm going to do.
I'm going to take
your boy Samir downtown,
I'm going to strap his ass
to a polygraph machine,
and I'm going to ask him
questions aboutyou.
Then I'm going to take
those transcripts--
I'm going to take them
to a friend ofmine
at the New York Times
whojust loves
to write stories
about the link between the CIA
and political horror shows.
Ifyou burn him, you'll lose
any chanceyou've got.
So what?
It's lose-lose,
isn't that whatyou said?
I'm not fucking with you.
How could you possibly
rememberwhoyou're fucking?
- 24 hours.
- Forwhat?
24 hours
forwhat, Sharon?
Elise.
Have anything for me?
Man:
Nothing new.
Man: Now, we've got
3 bombings in New York City.
We've got 600 people dead.
The NYPD, the FBI,
they don't seem up to it.
Do we need to bring the army
into this, Arianna?
Absolutely. How many
people have to die
before we do
bring the army...
U.S. government troops
are not trained
to police
their own population.
That's why
we have an FBI.
That's whywe have
a police force.
No. You see--
We don't want
an occupying army
in Brooklyn.
I would imagine
you would have to speak
to the army
to verify those rumors.
Arianna: And here
we have the FBI
having failed
to do theirjob,
having failed...
Devereaux:
This is an attack.
This is a time ofwar.
The fact that
it's inside our borders
only means that
it's a new kind ofwar.
Man: This is
the kind ofshit
these towel heads
do in their own country,
and now they're
bringing it here.
Man: People must understand
that the word ''Arab''
is not synonymous with
the word ''terrorist.''
Islam
is a religion ofpeace.
These people defile the Holy
Koran when they use...
Man: You know there's a lot
ofpent-up frustration...
Reporter: A merchant,
Abdul Hassam,
was beaten today and
his store vandalized.
Reporter: The president
released a statement today--
''One of
our greatest freedoms
is the freedom from fear,''
and he pledged to protect
that freedom
with all the resources...
The FBI has
received another fax.
Ahmed Bin Talal.
Apparently, they're still
under the impression
that we have him.
Do we...
have him?
Let me giveyou
a little advice, Steve.
Do not come between me
and the president.
I am speaking
for the president.
As far as the president
is concerned,
no, we do not have him.
General, did you know that
afteryesterday's attack
halfthe parents
in this country
kept their kids
out ofschool?
They're attacking
ourway oflife.
It ends now.
Areyou saying
the president is prepared
to take the necessary steps?
I am saying
the president
is prepared to be
presidential.
[Telephone Rings]
[Ring]
Hello.
Sharon: It's me.
Turn on the TV.
Hang on.
Female reporter: The senate
remained in emergency session
late into the night
debating the president's
call for martial law.
We have,
in this country,
a tradition ofinvoking
martial law...
Yeah, I got it.
onlywhen the most dire
ofcircumstances
require it,
but at what cost?
All eyes now turn
to New York City
to see ifmartial law will
bring the terror to an end.
Man: Move it!
[Whistle Blows]
Good morning.
Today, with the invocation
ofthe War Powers Act
by the president,
I am declaring
a state ofmartial law
in this city.
To the best
ofour knowledge,
we are opposed by no more
than 20 ofthe enemy.
He is hiding
among a population
ofroughly 2 million.
Intelligence tells us
that he is most likely
Arab-speaking,
between the age
of 1 4 and 30--
narrowing the target
to 1 5,000 suspects.
We can further
reduce that number
down to those that have
been in this country
less than 6 months.
Nowyou have 20
hiding among 2,000.
Ifyou are one ofthese
20 young men,
you can hide
among a population
ofsimilar
ethnic background.
Unfortunately foryou,
you can only hide there,
and that population,
in the classic
immigration pattern,
is concentrated
right here in brooklyn.
We intend to seal off
this borough,
then we intend
to squeeze it.
This is the land
ofopportunity, gentlemen--
the opportunity
to turn yourselves in.
After sundown tonight,
anyyoung man fitting
the profile I described
who is not cooperating
will be arrested
and detained.
There is historically
nothing more corrosive
to the morale
ofa population
than policing
its own citizens,
but the enemywould be
sadly mistaken
iftheywere to doubt
our resolve.
They are now
face-to-face
with the most fearsome
military machine
in the history ofman,
and I intend to use it
and be back on base
in time for the playoffs.
Thankyou foryour time.
[Man Shouting]
Good to seeyou
again, Hub.
Can't say the same thing
aboutyou, General--
not like this,
not in that uniform.
I thought
you were against this.
I am against this.
This was not my call.
Soyou'rejust
following orders, huh?
The president madeyou put
tanks on the Brooklyn Bridge?
Areyou questioning
my patriotism?
I'm questioning
yourjudgment.
Man on radio:
Negative, command.
I'm here serving
my president
and quite possibly
not in the best interest
ofour nation.
My profession
does not allow me
to make that kind
ofdistinction.
I won't question
your patriotism,
but don'tyou ever again
question my command.
Doyou understand me?
I'm not underyour command.
You really
believe that, hub?
Take a look around
and tell me that's true.
[Helicopter]
Arrogant prick.
You ever met anybody
so in love
with the sound
ofhis own voice?
We're putting Samir
into play.
Now? With all this
going on? He'll freak.
Yeah, He'll freak.
I'm already freaked.
The whole damn city's
freaked.
Oh, fuck it--One more lamb
to the slaughter.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's fine.
He's cool.
What's he fucking
doing here?
Hey, doyou know what's
happened outside?
They're killing Arabs
out there.
You can put
a stop to it, Samir.
What areyou talking
about? The army's here.
They're setting up
interrogation centers
right now.
They're torturing people
in cellars.
Calm down, all right?
I got to get
out ofhere,
and you have
to help me.
We'll helpyou.
I--I just need
more money.
Okay.
You got a student visa
forAli Wasir.
I told you. I know
nobody ofthat name.
Liar!
Uhh!
Tell him what he wants
to know! He knows!
She's fucking crazy!
You don't know
who they really are!
Shut up!
Stop simpering.
Look, I've got a picture
ofthe two ofus, Samir.
You remember
that picture?
Well, I'm going
to post it
in every shop
in Brooklyn,
and then I'm going
to send copies
to some friends ofmine
in the West Bank.
Your mother's
still there, isn't she?
All right, all right!
Fucking let go ofme!
All right,
get out ofhere.
Get out!
I'm sorry.
Hey, nobody's going
to burn you, okay, Samir?
nobody's going
to call anybody.
- Who asked you to get the visa?
- Oh, come on.
Hey, hey, Samir,
just calm down, okay?
I'm telling you, there's
nothing to be afraid of.
I'm afraid
ofgoing to hell.
Me, too.
[Sniffles]
His name is
Tariq Husseini.
He runs an auto shop
on Commerce Street
in Redhook.
Commerce Street.
Redhook.
Hubbard: Ifanybody
bothers you--
anybody--
you call me.
Man over P.A.: This is
foryour own security.
Do not be alarmed.
Got it.
You're good.
Yeah, you're not so bad
yourself.
Hey, Floyd. Yeah. Hub.
Listen, we got to put
something together
in a hurry, all right?
Yeah.
Where's frank?
All right, well,
give him a 91 1 , okay?
And get a beat-up
car for him.
[Man Talking Over P.A.]
Yeah, well, beat it up
yourselfifyou have to.
896 Commerce Street--
It's a garage in Redhook.
Man over P.A.:
Do not be alarmed.
[Crowd Yelling]
Sharon: Oh, shit,
they're going
house-to-house.
You know, Tariq
will go underground.
We're going to hit him
in less than an hour.
Well, hit him hard.
[Yelling]
Where areyou going?
I'm going to go stash Samir
someplace safe.
All right,
I make out 3 inside.
The 2 guys by
the trash barrel are ours,
and they're going to wait
until we're set.
Then they're going
to come in after us.
Okay.
All right, let's roll.
Yo.
Hey, guy.
Yo, I'm looking forTariq.
Anybody know Tariq?
He's supposed to be
fixing my shit here.
Huh?
I got that card here
somewhere.
He gave me
this paper--
Tariq Hossidy or
something like that?
Yeah, yeah.
He's back there.
- Back there?
- Yeah.
All right, man.
Thanks.
[Knocks]
Hey, Tariq!
Areyou
Tariq Husseini?
- He's not here.
- He's not here?
[Speaking Arabic]
Can I leave
a message for him?
Ofcourse.
Tell him the FBI
is after him.
Ha! You'rejoking.
I'm notjoking.
Put the phone down.
Putyour hands up.
Freeze! Hands in the air!
Okay.
Interlock them
behind your head.
[Speaking Arabic]
Yeah, right.
Same toyou, too.
Everything's going
to be all right.
[Helicopter]
Man over P.A.:
Tariq Husseini,
this is
the United States Army.
you are surrounded.
You have 30 seconds
to throw out anyweapons
and vacate the premises
with your hands
on top ofyour head.
I repeat--
Freeze!
Freeze,
god damn it!
God damn it.
Code red. Code red.
Pilot: Leader,
we are locked on target.
Request permission
to fire.
Yes! Now!
Man: Freeze!
- Drop it!
- Hold it.
I'm FBI.
Put the gun down,
motherfucker!
Hubbard: All right,
all right. I'm FBI.
I'm FBI.
Just relax. I'm FBI.
Get down on your knees,
would you, man?
I'm FBI!
[Yelling]
Ladies and gentlemen,
there'll be a--
Who was that?
Ladies and gentlemen...
there will be
a full briefing
for all journalists.
[People Yelling]
[Helicopter]
Man over P.A.:
Do not be alarmed.
[Chattering]
Frank: Frankie!
Frankie Haddad!
Frank Haddad!
- Frank!
- Hub. Hub.
- They got frankie.
- What?
My kid's in here.
My kid's in here someplace.
He's only 1 3.
All right, we'll get him
out. We'll find him.
Frank,
we'll get him out.
Frank Haddad!
- We'll get him out.
- Out?
They came into my house!
Mywife told them
who I was!
How many times did I
put it on the line, Hub?
How many times?
20 years, we're
American citizens,
1 0 years in the bureau!
They knocked her down.
They took him
out ofmy house!
Frank Haddad!
Listen to me!
Frank!
It--
It's wrong.
We'll find him.
All right?
All right.
Come on.
No. No!
I'll find him.
Besides...
This is where I belong.
Here.
Tell them I'm not
their sand nigger anymore.
[Mispronounces] You say
his name is Haddad?
No. His name is Haddad,
Frank Haddad.
H-A-D-D-A-D.Junior.
His father's a Shiite.
We're checking him out.
His father
is a federal agent.
His father happens
to be my partner.
Don't get in my face,
Hubbard.
I just might decide
you're an Ethiopian.
You know, you are
stupid enough
to think that
that's an insult.
Ifa mistake's
been made, we'll fix it.
What doyou mean,
ifa mistake's been made?
There's no mistake.
I'm vouching for the kid.
I want him out.
Why don'tyou getyour
priorities straight?
I said we'll
look into it.
Yeah, you'll
look into it--
just likeyou've been
looking into me, right?
Surveilling me?
You think I'm stupid?
You think I don't know
what's going on?
I'm doing
yourjob foryou,
and I damn near get my head
blown off for it.
Now I want FrankJr. out,
and I want to see
my prisonerTariq Husseini.
Let's go see
your prisoner.
[Speaking Arabic]
Tariq.
Tariq...
[Speaking Arabic]
[Spits]
How long
haveyou been at him?
Not long enough,
apparently.
How much longer,
doyou think,
before he gives up
the other cells?
He can't give up
the other cells
ifhe doesn't know
where they are.
He knows.
No, he doesn't.
You said ityourself,
Sharon, didn'tyou?
In the strategy meeting,
the briefing--
The one cell
doesn't know
where the other one is,
right?
How long before
he breaks, Sharon?
Well, at this rate,
too long.
The theaterwas hit
9 hours afterwe took
down the first cell.
So...
what other models
do we have?
Shake him?
- What about it, Sharon?
- Won't work.
It works
for the Israelis.
Only in conjunction
with sleep deprivation.
It takes at least
36 hours.
We don't have 36 hours.
Electric shock?
The neurotransmitters
just shut down.
- Water?
- Palestinian authorities...
producing good intel
with water.
Ofcourse,
there's cutting.
[Praying In Arabic]
It's extremely messy.
Areyou people insane?
What areyou
talking about?
The time has come
for one man to suffer
in order to save
hundreds oflives.
One man?
What about 2, huh?
What about 6?
How about
public executions, huh?
You're free to leave
wheneveryou like.
Come on, General,
you lost men, I've lost men,
butyou--you can't do this.
What ifwhat
they reallywant--
What ifthey don't even
want the sheik?
Haveyou considered that?
Huh?
What if
what they reallywant
is for us to herd children
into stadiums
like we're doing?
And put soldiers
on the street
and--and have Americans
looking over their shoulders?
Bend the law,
shred the constitution
just a little bit?
Because ifwe
torture him, General...
we do that,
and everything
that we have bled
and fought and died for
is over,
and they've won.
They've alreadywon.
Escort him out.
Tariq: Aah!
He knew nothing.
Aah!
[Gunshot]
[Man Singing In Arabic]
Hubbard: You got
to call offthe dogs.
Steve: We can't
call offthe army
until the threat is gone.
The army is the threat.
They're the ones
out ofcontrol.
Devereaux's killing
innocent people.
You guys took the leash
offofhim.
Just put it back on him.
Areyou wearing a wire?
Areyou?
It was devereaux
who took the sheik
in the first place.
Devereaux?
So we do have him?
What doyou think, Hub?
Our government operates
as one coherent entity?
Everybody, you and me,
we all wanted that
sheik's head on a plate.
Devereaux didn't start
this agenda
about hunting down
terrorists.
He'sjust kind of
pushed it a little bit.
[Man Speaking
In Arabic Over P.A.]
Hang on a sec.
So, now what do we do?
There is this growing feeling
in certain circles
that we ought tojust
let the sheik go--
set him free.
I mean, after all,
we kidnapped him.
We kept him in isolation.
Ajudge might let him walk.
You don't let
a murderer go free--
any murderer.
Any murderer!
Sharon thinks we can
get to the last cell
ifthey believe we're going
to release the sheik.
Why should they
trust her?
I mean, why should I
Ask her.
I ran the network
in Iraq for 2 years.
Samir recruited them
from among the sheik's
followers,
and I trained them
in the north.
The sheikwas going
to help us overthrow Saddam.
I mean,
he was our ally.
We were financing him.
And then...
then there was
a policy shift.
It's not like we
sold them out exactly.
Wejust stopped
helping them.
Theywere slaughtered.
So I quit the operation.
I took another assignment.
Butyou helped them
first.
What doyou mean?
You said theywere
being slaughtered.
They needed to get out.
Theywere on the terrorist
watch list,
soyou got them visas,
you and Samir.
I promised them we would
take care ofthem.
Theywere working for us.
Doing what exactly?
I told you.
No, you didn't.
You told me
thatyou trained them--
trade craft, subversion.
That's whatyou said,
wasn't it?
You're leaving something
out, aren'tyou, Sharon?
You taught them...
how to make bombs.
That's whyyou were
looking
for the wiring signatures
on that blue bus.
And now they're here...
doing whatyou
taught them how to do.
Right?
You've got to let me
make this right.
Please?
Man: The president
is in close conference
with the mayor
of New York,
the governor of New York,
and the attorney general
of New York,
and I can assureyou...
Man: ...putting them
in a stadium
as we did
with theJapanese.
Man: This is the time
for all ofus to proclaim
our brotherhood
with these people.
TheJewish community
opposes the military
to take back in a peaceful
fashion our democracy
from the people...
Woman:
The people of Brooklyn
will not be
held hostage!
Join community
and religious leaders
in a march to protest...
Man: Well, what ifit was
black people, huh?
What ifit was
Italians?
Puerto Ricans?
Female reporter: American Arabs
are a vulnerable,
visible population,
and they have no power.
Critics say this is
a racist decision,
and the government
would not dare do this
to any other--
[Turns OffTV]
Samir's made contact,
Frank.
It's the last cell.
He set up a meeting,
but we got to get the army
offour tail.
I need your help,
Frank.
Frank, it's still
ourwatch.
I don't want to see
another dead body,
and I knowyou don't.
And when this is over,
I promiseyou--
we'll getyour boy back.
[Crowd Shouting]
Woman: March on
city hall today!
No fear!
What timeyou got,
Frank?
Just 1 0:1 5.
How's he doing?
You shouldjust tell me
the message,
and I will pass it on.
I need to deliver it
myself.
Believe me,
they're gonna want to
hearwhat I have to say.
Woman: No fear!
Let's show them
we're not afraid!
Sure he's gonna
go through with this?
Well, ifhe doesn't,
he knows I'll give him
to Devereaux.
So...
You know,
this is the end game,
you understand?
Ifthis goes wrong...
Nothing's
gonna go wrong.
We're the CIA.
Something
always goes wrong.
Well...
Ifthings get hairy,
uh...
just remember,
the most committed wins.
Let's go.
The 3 ofyou really do
make a lovely couple.
Sharon, I beg you,
do not
make me do this.
Ifthey even...
Ifthey even dream
we've been followed,
theywill kill us.
South on
Cadman Plaza.
Sharon:
Relax, all right?
Col. Hardwick:
General Devereaux,
it appears the feds are
in motion. Doyou copy?
Right.
Just staywith Hubbard.
The man is definitely
not on our team.
Col. Hardwick: Roger that.
Airborne, he's all yours.
Helicopter pilot:
This is airborne.
We got him.
Soundgarden's ready.
Hey, wait a minute.
This is not the way
to the bathhouse.
You said to get a key
from my uncle.
Stop whining.
You'll cue the surveillance.
Hey...
I have a bad feeling here.
Just relax.
Keepyour head down.
[Helicopter]
We ready?
All set.
We got to hurry, Sharon.
We can't be late.
Here we go.
Pilot:
All units, all units.
Subject is on foot.
Pilot: All units, he is running
to First and Pearl.
Man on P.A.: This is U.S. Army.
Halt!
Freeze!
We're all clear.
All right, let's do it.
Why are we stopping,
Sharon? We've got to go.
Just calm down.
Everything's gonna be fine.
[Turns On TV]
Look, wejust have to
sit tight for 3 minutes.
Can youjust do
that much for me?
I don't believe it.
Look at this.
[People Shouting On TV]
Arab andJew,
side by side.
Black and white.
Christian
and Muslim.
what?
It's so tragic.
What? What's tragic?
What doyou mean?
Are they gonna hit the march?
Can you imagine
a better target?
Because our government
has no right...
[Crowd Cheering]
to declare martial law.
[Cheering]
No fear!
We've got to hurry,
Sharon.
Put this on.
Oh, shoot.
It's 1 1 :00.
We gotta get out ofhere.
They're getting
ready to move.
Units 1 and 2
on my signal.
Units 3 and 4,
stand by.
Units 5 and 6...
FBI!
Ohh.
Microwave.
This is an unlawful
disturbance!
You must disperse!
I repeat!
These soldiers carry
live ammunition!
This is
your final warning!
I repeat!
These soldiers carry
live ammunition!
[Keystrokes]
[Computer beeping]
Hub...
we missed them.
The bathhouse.
So what's
going on?
Why aren't they
here?
They'll be here.
Don't worry.
[Whispering In Arabic]
What areyou doing?
What message
doyou have for them?
There's no one else coming,
is there?
[Chuckles]
So...
what message doyou have
for me, Sharon?
You're the last cell.
There will never be
a last cell!
It'sjust the beginning.
[Crowd Chanting '' No Fear!'']
Frank:
Move out ofthe way!
Move over! Move over!
How could I have
missed the play?
It's because ofthe money.
You believe money is power.
Beliefis power.
Just don't tell me
we financed your operation.
[Chuckles]
The world is a wheel,
Sharon.
Samir...
the Koran preaches...
Do not speak to me
ofthe Koran, woman!
Firstyou left me there
in Iraq
like a piece ofshit!
And then you take
our leader, a holy man--
you put him in prison
for preaching
the word ofGod!
So nowyou have to learn
the consequences
oftrying to tell to
the world how to live.
It's over.
Your point's been made.
Why shed more blood?
[Crowd Chanting Outside]
Those poor people
out there.
They're fucking marching
foryour cause.
Yeah...
and they, too, will
become its martyrs.
Hubbard: Samir.
Let her go, Samir.
Move away
from the door.
Don't!
He's got a bomb!
Get up. Get up!
Get up!
No!
Samir, let her go,
and you'll live.
I said move away
from this fucking door!
Don't!
Samir...
Hub, I'm here.
No shots, Frank.
No shots.
Samir...
Doyou
want to die?
Doyou?
Look, I'll blow it!
Then we all die.
Nobody's leaving here.
Move away from
this fucking door!
- Shoot!
- Shut up!
- Shoot me!
Shoot!
Kill him! Shoot!
I'm coming!
Shoot!
[Opens
Radio Channel]
One ofours down.
Stomach wound.
Get here now.
Here.
Is he dead?
Hub?
I'm right here.
[Groans]
I'm right here. Shh.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
[Groans]
You're okay.
I'm cold.
Okay.
[Groans]
[Crying]
Shh, shh.
You're okay.
Ohh...
Just relax.
'' Forgive us our trespasses,
as we forgive...''
''Those who trespassed
against us.''
''And lead us...''
'' Lead us not
into temptation,
but deliver us...
from evil...''
[Crying]
'' For thine
is the kingdom...''
[Speaking Arabic]
No fear!
Agent Hubbard,
would you mind
explaining to me
whyyou detained
Colonel Hardwick
and 6 of
my C.I.D. staff?
The last cell
was taken down.
It was Samir.
We took him out.
How can you be sure it's
the last ofthe cells?
- Sharon.
- Sharon's been compromised.
Sharon is dead.
She gave her life.
Sorry.
It's all overwith,
General.
What's all overwith?
The sheik.
Is that so?
Clearviolation
ofinternational law.
Hmm?
Congressional
oversights,
couple ofstatutes,
treaties.
Kidnapping, perjury,
Logan Act.
Conducting your own
personal foreign policy.
I know the whole story.
You don't know shit.
Poor suffering Sharon
and her poor
suffering people.
I did what
was necessary,
and I won't apologize
for it.
Go fuckyourself,
bureau.
I serve my country.
Why don'tyou try
serving yours?
You have anything else,
Agent Hubbard?
Yeah.
One more thing.
This is a writ from
the U.S. District Court
ordering the release
ofall persons being held
in this stadium.
My authority overrules
the courts.
Your authority ends now,
General.
William Devereaux,
you are under arrest...
for the torture and murder
ofTariq Husseini...
an American citizen.
FBI, freeze!
Freeze! Nobody move!
Hold it!
Don't move!
Putyour guns down!
Is this some kind
ofajoke?
Doyou see me laughing,
General?
Captain.
Don't!
Orderyour men to lower
theirweapons, Hubbard.
Can't do that, General.
Do it now.
The law states--
I am the law!
Right here, right now!
You have the right
to remain silent.
Order them to lower
theirweapons!
You have the right
to a fair trial.
not to be tortured,
not to be murdered,
rights thatyou took away
from Tariq Husseini!
You have those rights
because ofthe men
that came beforeyou
who wore that uniform.
Because of
the men and women
that are here waiting
for the order to fire.
Give them the order,
General.
Doyou think that I would
hesitate to kill you
or every other federal agent
in this room
ifit was in the best
interests ofmy country?
No, no, no.
You wouldn't hesitate.
I know that.
But they might.
Give the order.
Make murderers
out oftheseyoung kids.
Give the order.
Give them the order,
General!
Stand down, Sergeant.
Woman:
General Devereaux,
would you care to
comment on the charges?
[Reporters Shouting Questions]
[Cheering]
[Women Ululating]