You're late!
Can't get her to go to college with
you, but you have to pack her shit.
That’s just pathetic.
He's a big dinosaur now, mom.
Pathetic is that you're not even
going out with her anymore...
and you still have to
pack her shit.
You'll always have a room here.
- Bye, honey.
- Bye!
Don't get too busy to
give us a call once in a while.
Bye!
That’s why you're not
dating her anymore.
I forgot something.
- Bye.
- Love you.
Shut up!
- Hello? Where do I sit?
- Right here, babe.
- So where's the party tonight?
- Genius!
- I'm the one going to Harvard.
- So did the Unabomber.
Oh, my God!
We should at least try
to meet people.
Why?
Good question.
She thinks she's hot.
She's not so hot.
She really isn't.
Thanks.
This is our last night together. Do
you think we can do something else?
- I could probably think of something.
- Yeah?
I am definitely not cut out
for the Greek life.
You'll be all right.
You'll join the swim team,
you'll meet people.
Plus you've got Annie, your
best friend, right here with you.
My best friend will be 2 thousand
miles away, in California.
What are you thinking?
I'm picking it up.
Wait! I got it. You're thinking...
I'm thinking... I'm thinking...
I'm thinking
my ass is getting wet!
I knew it was something
about your ass.
I'm going to miss you.
I love being with you.
I miss you already.
Close your eyes.
If you ever want me...
just come to this spot...
and I'll be here.
One last kiss before
they say good-bye.
- I think I'll puke.
- After that, can we go somewhere?
- I want to have some real fun!
- I'm ready for that.
- Let’s go to the club I heard about.
- What club?
I don't know. It’s out of town.
It’s kind of a moving party.
But I can't move.
Try not to act like a college boy
because they're not allowed.
Come on, you guys,
let’s do this thing. Come on!
Isn't this great?
I just can't control her anymore.
Look out!
Come on, let’s dance!
I want that blonde tonight.
Look at those ravers.
Come on, let’s go!
Come on, it’s time.
We're doing it!
Get off!
Annie, come on!
There is no light
- This is a church.
- One more minute...
All of a sudden, I feel that we are
making a mistake saying good-bye.
Cassie, you know how I feel.
I don't care how young we are.
You're the one I want
to be with, that’s it.
I feel that way too.
So we're lucky.
Most people never find that.
We have our whole lives
ahead of us.
Right?
I can wait.
I know what I want.
I love you, Cass.
You've never said that
to me before.
No one's ever said that
That makes two of us.
How do you feel?
You know.
Is there some reason
you can't say it?
Like what?
Like maybe you're still
thinking about Matt?
No.
No, it’s just...
I don't want to say it and then...
have you leave me tomorrow.
- Okay.
- But I feel it.
Maybe tonight you should
tell me how you feel.
I...
- What are you doing out here, man?
- Drinking.
I was going to go get Annabel,
but now I think I'm going to...
Right.
All right. I'll get her.
It’s freezing out here.
Can you unlock it?
Here. Warm it up.
You're driving.
The darkness is here!
Harvard laid our serious financial aid
for the brain cells you're trashing.
They're still my brain cells.
They don't know me yet.
Besides, I lied.
I'm not really drunk.
I'll miss you.
Sorry.
It’s not very fair, is it?
You know, Matt...
...I care for you, but then...
- Please.
Not the "I care for you,
but..." speech.
I got that last summer, remember?
Yeah.
- I guess I'm just a bad loser.
- It’s not a competition.
Right.
Well, I'll settle for nothing less
than friends for life.
- Deal.
- And one last kiss.
I'm sorry. I won't end the most
meaningful relationship of my life...
with a lousy handshake.
I'm not a business man.
All right, forget it.
I'm sorry I asked.
You know, sometimes
you can be a real shit.
2O years from now,
when you and Sean are married...
and you're a mom with your rug rat
children in your suburban home...
do you think it will really matter
whether we shook hands or kissed...
the night we said good-bye?
One last good-bye forever,
my former love.
A kiss.
And it 's in the past...
What a cold rain!
Sean!
- Where did you guys go?
- Nowhere.
- Sean, it 's not what you're thinking.
- Really? What am I thinking?
Matt just...
We were just talking, and he...
- Did you have fun?
- Oh, yeah. You?
Sean, don't walk away
from me, please!
Sean?
Look, it was nothing!
I'm sorry!
If it was nothing,
why are you sorry?
Sean, please, talk to me.
Hello? What 's the drama?
Yeah, Cass, tell Annabel
what the drama is.
Come on, it 's freezing back here.
Come on.
Let’s go! It 's freezing!
I know what it looked like, but
believe me, it 's not what you think!
Cassie, watch the road.
Will you talk to me?
Oh, my God! Cassie!
Cassie, break!
Can you hear me? Hello?
Anybody in there,
can you hear me?
How much did you
have to drink tonight?
Watch it now.
The loss of a young life
is a most terrible thing.
...our beloved Sean will...
...for we have loved...
Matt 's taking me back to school.
Why don't you come with us?
I'm not sure I'm going back.
All right, class, remember.
This coming midterm, we'll...
Are you still
thinking about Matt?
Maybe tonight you should
tell me how you feel.
Cassandra?
This test is critical.
Hey, excuse me.
I wasn't here last week.
Do you have a study guide?
Sorry.
How much did you
have to drink tonight?
If you ever want me,
just come right here to this spot...
Just come to this spot,
and I'll be here.
Hello.
Maybe tonight you should
tell me how you feel.
I love you, Cassie.
Cassie!
I've been out there pounding!
It took me 5 minutes to try the door.
Hello?
You look like shit.
- What have they got you on?
- It 's for headaches.
Zombie food!
Lovely, lovely.
You're not going like that, are you?
Going where?
To the club! Don't you remember?
God, Cass! We've got
to get you ready, girl!
I have to study.
I have a midterm.
Everybody has a midterm.
Cass...
You remember when my mom died?
And went into, like...
this black hole and...
If it wasn't for you...
You've got to
get out of here, girl!
Join the living!
This is my friend, Raven.
Hello.
- Hi.
- I've got to pee.
Who's this?
He was my boyfriend.
He died three weeks ago.
He's here now... Sean.
Inside you and Matt...
in the car that night...
He's afraid.
You're in trouble!
So, are you coming?
- No.
- Cass?
- Just go, okay?
- You wanted to meet people!
I'll call you later.
Don't run, baby!
You're mine, baby!
Cassie!
Hold on, Cassie!
Hey.
Welcome back to the world.
What happened?
You fainted.
Some priest brought you here.
He was walking around outside
like somebody died. Scared me.
I'm supposed to keep
an eye on you. It sucks, but...
somebody's got to do it.
Not me.
What about Harvard?
It will be there when I get back.
The doctor said you can go...
but they want you
to come back to do some tests...
to make sure it has nothing to do
with your injury from the accident.
- Is there something wrong?
- They're just covering their asses.
You know doctors.
They love tests.
Well, I hate tests.
I borrowed your keys
and I did a little shopping.
That 's incredible!
You're so sweet.
- And there.
- Thank you so much.
I talked to Annie.
She said you're not doing so well.
- Do you want to talk about it?
- He shouldn't have died that night.
It 's not your fault.
Yeah... I think that
it was our fault.
Because if it wasn't for us then
Sean and I wouldn't have fought...
and I wouldn't have
lost control of the car!
Those guys we hit were trashed.
They did a18O right in front of us.
There's no way you could've stopped.
There's no way
anyone could've stopped.
Matt, it 's not that I miss him.
I saw him!
You saw him?
- Tell me exactly what happened.
- I was running...
and someone put their hand
on my shoulder...
and they turned me around,
they said my name...
- It was him.
- Why were you running?
Do you remember that guy
from the club that night?
The one that grabbed me
when me and Annie were dancing?
- Yeah, you shoved him.
- He's here, he's on campus!
No, he's not, Cassie.
Sean isn't either.
You know that, don't you?
You could've died that night too!
- But I didn't, did I?
- No, and you feel guilty about that.
- What about school?
- I'm not going anywhere.
But Harvard is, like,
your life, you know...
that 's all that matters to you,
it always has been.
You're all that matters now.
Shit!
Hello? What's the drama?
Cassie, watch the road.
- It's included.
- What's the cranial pulse?
Well, Cassandra...
the tests indicate
you have a hemorrhage.
We're going to relieve the pressure
on the right part of your brain.
I want you to breathe normally...
and count back from 1OO.
Feeling better?
You're the one that saved me.
You're the priest?
I try not to wear my collar
when I'm around here.
I do volunteer counseling
once a week.
My name is Jude.
- Cassie.
- Hi.
I've got a minute before my next
appointment. You want to sit down?
Sure.
So...
Do I call you "father"?
I'm sort of a lapsed Catholic.
I think all Catholics lapse
once in a while.
Probably especially
during midterms.
Yeah...
I've sort of been having
a rough time, actually.
I lost my boyfriend recently.
Can I ask what happened?
Car accident.
I was driving.
It was really sudden, and there was
something that I wanted to tell him.
But I never got the chance.
It 's...
difficult to be a survivor.
But you've got to remember...
that it 's up to God
who lives and who dies.
I know it sounds crazy, but...
sometimes I feel like
he's still here with me.
I mean, really here.
Like he's not gone yet.
Maybe he is still with you.
Oh, that 's my friend.
I've got to go.
Well, feel free to come by anytime.
You're going to be okay.
- All right.
- Bye!
Hey!
- Didn't mean to interrupt confession.
- You didn't.
Come here,
I want to show you something.
Come on, come on.
Alright. You can kick
all their asses at the free style.
Matt...
I just want to see you
in a bathing suit again.
Come on, I've got another idea.
It was about time!
We saved you a roller.
I'm a brush chick.
Here.
There's more paint on my shirt
than you have on your walls!
Here.
Oh, my gosh.
- So how's Raven?
- Interesting.
- Talks about you a lot.
- He does?
Raven thinks you're not
really here with us.
He says you're still
kind of with Sean.
Maybe I am a little.
Do you feel that way too?
You know how I feel
more than anything?
That I'm finally free. We're on
our own for the first time, Cass.
We can do anything,
no boundaries.
Don't you feel that way?
I wish I did.
Don't worry.
We'll get you there, Cass.
Cassie?
Cassie, what is it?
Cassie, it 's okay!
What happened?
It 's okay!
It 's nothing, sweetie.
Hey.
- What are you doing?
- We're going out, right?
Because I feel like dancing.
- We said we'd stay in tonight.
- Yeah, well, now...
I want to go out.
Fine. I'll see you guys later.
Matt, let her go.
I want to sleep.
Why are you doing this?
Is everything okay?
Hey, there.
I miss you. I'm sorry.
- It 's okay. Just hang in there.
- I want you.
Make love to me!
Matt?
Hey.
What 's wrong? You don't look so
good. I'm going to get your pills.
- We didn't... Tell me we didn't...
- What?
Tell me we didn't sleep
together last night.
You don't remember?
No.
- What happened?
- You said you missed me, that you...
What?
Annie?
Hi.
- Okay, I get it.
- No, Annie, it 's not what you think!
Stop it, Cass!
I'm quicker than that.
Not as quick as you, though.
- Annie, let me just...
- Let me talk to her.
Sudden, don't you think?
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- It 's not what you think...
I can't even believe you.
Get away from me.
Hi.
Cassie?
Listen to me. I can't talk to you
if you're afraid.
If you want me to leave you alone,
I will. I'm not going to haunt you.
This can't be happening!
You came here...
because I said
that I would be here.
So here I am.
It 's okay.
It 's really you.
I miss you.
It 's okay.
Come on.
I must really be crazy.
You're not crazy.
I'm here.
Don't let go, don't let go.
Come with me.
Where?
Away from here.
The guys are going to
keep tracing you.
Cassie?
I want you with me!
Do you love me?
I don't want to die!
If you stay here,
you're going to die.
Cassie.
Cassie!
I've been looking all over for you.
Cassie, let me explain.
Look, you called out,
you said you missed me...
and that you wanted me to be there.
You said, "Make love to me".
I thought you had
feelings for me again.
I'm so sorry, Cassie.
I was wrong.
Tell me how I can make it up
for you. I'll do anything.
I just need to be alone
for a while.
Cassie?
I just need some time.
Annie!
- What 's wrong?
- This guy was...
This guy was chasing me.
He was trying to...
- Who was chasing you?
- I don't know.
I think it was one of those
weird guys from the club.
He had a scar on his face,
and he had long hair...
- Oh, God, I was so scared.
- All right, you're in a safe place.
You don't believe me!
I'm worried about you, Cassie.
I think you should talk to someone.
You think I'm crazy?
I am not crazy! Everyone else is!
Nobody is chasing you, Cass.
I saw what I saw.
Why don't you believe me?
I believe you believe it.
But I also think you haven't
accepted what 's happened yet.
So it 's like it 's still happening
to you in your head.
I want to help.
I love you.
- Matt, I don't...
- No, it 's okay.
You don't have to love me back.
Just let me take care of you.
I'm going to go get your medicine.
Hi, mom, it 's me. Can you call me
as soon as you can? I need to talk.
How did you get in here?
I copied your key while
you were in the hospital. Here.
You need to get some rest.
There were two girls in the locker
room. They didn't see anybody.
Do you always get here
before everyone else?
No, I'm trying to get my time down.
I have first meets Thursday.
You had a pretty serious head injury
in that car accident, didn't you?
Dr. Haverston?
Excuse me.
Hi. Why wasn't my grade
posted with the others?
There is no grade
for this kind of test.
- Wait!
- Cassie.
Cassie?
Come in, come in.
Sit down.
Let 's see now...
What 's wrong?
Everything.
Everything's wrong.
I don't know
what 's happening to me.
You feel alone in a world
that you don't understand.
You don't know who to trust.
But you're trying
very hard, I know that.
How do you know?
Because you're not
the first person to be here.
And I promise you, that whatever
happens, you'll find your way.
You just have to be strong.
I don't want to be strong.
I'm so tired.
Lie back, Cassie.
Try and rest.
I want you to have something.
This is Saint Jude...
one of those guys that they made
you learn about in Sunday school.
He looked after people
that were lost...
and that 's who
my father named me after.
I'm so tired.
Rest.
Thank you.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah, I'm looking for Jude.
- Who?
- A priest.
I don't know his full name. Jude?
- Father Jude?
- Yeah, do you know where he is?
Sit down.
- I really can't stay.
- Are you a member of the church?
No, I met Jude when
I started school this fall.
Is there something wrong?
I can't stay.
I really need to find him.
- What 's your name?
- Cassie.
Well, Cassie, perhaps there's
been some confusion, but...
Father Jude was head of the church
here until he passed away in 1981.
I don't understand.
Well, I don't either.
It must be a different priest.
I need to find him. I'm in trouble.
Maybe there's something I can
help you with, Cassie. But first...
I really need to know
if you're a member.
What the hell are you doing?
Go, Cassie! Let 's do it!
Hang in there, Cass!
You're going to make it!
All right, Cassie!
Incredible!
You looked like you were in trouble,
but you pulled it on. Nicely done.
Yeah! What got into you?
I saw Sean.
And that guy with the mask
from the club.
- What guy?
- And the one with a scarred face.
I saw you talking with him.
He went back there.
What do you guys do there?
- What 's going on?
- Nothing's going on. Take it easy.
I did go back. I went back to tell
those guys to leave you alone.
Yeah, but I saw him
at school with you.
You're paranoid.
You're hallucinating.
And I saw you with Raven
that day at school and...
That 's it, okay?
We've got to get you out of here.
We'll hop in the car, drive you to
your folks. We'll drive all night.
No.
Come on! We'll make a little
road trip out of it. It will be fun.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
This whole thing with Sean is
screwed up. You're screwed up.
Let us help you, Cass.
Just come with us.
No.
Sean's not coming back! You want to
be with us or with him somewhere?
- Take it easy.
- I'm sick of waiting for you to decide.
You're with us or you're not!
- What is that supposed to mean?
- It doesn't mean anything.
You want to stay here, don't you?
That way you get it all, I mean...
you get Sean, Matt and you get
everything, and we don't get shit!
That 's enough!
- Raven was so right about you.
- Stop it!
Look, I know you're angry at me
about Matt and about Sean...
- Please...
- People from the club are dangerous.
- Those people?
- One of them tried to kill me!
Isn't that ironic?
What?
You're the murderer.
Cassie!
- Annie! Oh, God, I'm so sorry!
- You're going to die.
Annabel! Let 's go!
Trick or treat!
Let 's go.
I need to go back and get my stuff,
and then I'm going home.
Okay, I'll drive you
to your parents.
- I'll be right out.
- I won't let anybody in.
Matt?
Hello?
Got you!
Wait. Come back!
Cassie, are you okay?
Wait, it 's me. It 's me.
It 's okay!
He tried to kill me.
He's back there and he's dead.
- What is it?
- I killed him. He's in the water.
What are you talking about?
I was just up there.
There's nobody up there.
I promise.
I promise,
there's nobody up there.
Come on.
There's nobody up there.
Come on!
There's no one out here.
He was here.
He was right there!
Take me home.
Take me home to my mom.
Come on. Come on.
What are we doing here?
You said you'd take me home!
I am, take it easy. I'm just going to
go get Annabel. Then we can go.
I'm not leaving her here.
- I'm not going in there.
- Fine. Stay in the car.
Wait!
Matt!
Welcome to the party, Cass.
We're getting out of here!
I'm not going anywhere.
I like it here.
- Annie?
- Let her go.
- She belongs here now.
- Go back to the Addams family!
Your friends are not
your friends anymore, Cass.
You belong to Sean.
Go now, while there's still time.
- Jeez! What are you doing?
- When you kissed me that night...
it wasn't just good-bye.
You liked it.
What are you talking about?
Let 's get out of here!
How do you think I feel when
I gave up my first semester...
to take care of you, and you
haven't even said thank you?
What? Let 's just get out...
- How did you hurt your hand?
- How do you think I feel...
when I'm here for you, and
you're still hung up on a dead guy?
Let me go!
You kill me, Cassie.
One last good-bye
forever kiss is all I want.
Get off me now!
When are you going to wake up?
Why do you think Annabel hates you?
Sean is the only one who didn't
betray you, and you killed him!
Sorry...
God.
Annabel?
It 's her.
Miss?
I... I killed them.
I killed them.
Cassie, hold on.
Hold on.
I killed them.
No, you didn't.
- Don't leave me.
- I won't leave your side.
Stay with me, Cass.
I'm here. I'm right here.
Stay with me.
Look at me.
Look at me. I'm right here.
Stay with me, Cass, stay with me!
Your tests indicate
you have a hemorrhage...
as a result of your accident.
Why wasn't my grade
posted with the others?
There is no grade
for this kind of test.
Mom!
Miss?
Try to take it easy!
Don't be afraid.
You have to fight.
Eternal father, I offer you
the precious blood...
of your divine son, Jesus.
Eternal rest grant onto them.
And let perpetual life
wash over them.
May they rest in peace.
I'm dying.
Fighting!
You're very strong, Cassie.
But all this time...
It 's been another kind of time.
It 's like a dream that
your mind is creating...
to keep you from waking up to
what you're not ready to accept.
- You're fighting.
- They said that you were dead.
I fought my own fight years ago.
And I know that even a dream
of life is better than facing death.
But what about Annabel,
and Matt, and the others?
They're lost.
- Sean?
- He survived.
I loved him very much.
- I don't want to die.
- Lf you were to die...
so that he'd live,
would you feel absolved?
I would.
I would die for him.
Do you love him enough
to live for him?
I don't want to die!
Sean...
Sean!
Sean?
Sean, I'm sorry.
It 's okay, it 's not your fault.
I never told you.
- What? Tell me now.
- I...
Love...
I love you.
I love you too, baby.
You made it, honey.
You made it!
We told you to hang on,
and you did!
We told you not to leave us!
How long have I been here?
It 's been two days.
Sean kept talking to you
all the time saying...
"Don't give up.
Keep fighting."
I know. I heard him.
I heard all of you.