In my planet,
the women are barren.
I traveled secretly...
across the depths of space,
assuming human form...
so I'd may came to know
earthly women...
and repopulate
my desolated planet.
I wish for you to know
my true name. Xunobulax.
Xunobulax?
Our race makes love just once.
We put all our cosmic energy
into that one explosive... act...
and then,
like your terrestrial mayfly...
we die of a sweet
early content.
I want to make love to you
in the manner of my people.
I want it to be my last act.
Keep that up and it will be
your last act.
- I have to accomplish my mission.
- I said stop.
- I want my first time to be with you.
- And so do I.
Cool, I understand.
Please, Stacy.
What the fuck is this?
Hold on.
Ben!
Get your ass over here!
Mark, is that you in there?
This isn't funny!
What the hell...
Rod!
Stacy.
Stacy!
No! Rod!
Oh, my God!
I was supposed to be home
15 minutes ago.
Sixth graders can stay out
later than you can.
Stop!
Doesn't it ever bother you
you could die a virgin?
It 's right up there
with global warming.
- We should see other people.
- What?
We've been dating for about a year,
and I don't think it 's working out.
All right?
- Hi, Mrs. Marken.
- You two having fun?
Hi, mom.
Kenny, you'd happen
to have a cigarette for me?
Sure.
Mrs. Marken,
smoking is really bad for you.
The industrial strength.
I owe you.
I'll have to smoke this here.
Brent doesn't like me
to smoke in the house.
- It 's my last guilty pleasure.
- Is daddy still up?
- You were out late tonight.
- Kenny was just leaving.
Too bad.
It looks like the coast is clear.
If you want to beat the heat,
you better hurry up.
Mrs. Marken?
- Your headlights are on.
- Very observant.
Thanks.
Good night.
So, is this goodbye
or good night?
Pick one.
- Pick one.
- I think it 's up to you.
Don't... slam the door.
Like a little tiny mouse.
Good night.
- Do you know what time it is?
- Don't scare me like that.
You're grounded the next two
Friday nights.
- Most 6th graders stay out later.
- They're not the sheriff's daughter.
Marken.
I'll get down there
as soon as I can.
Daddy.
- You're the only one here?
- First on the scene.
The forensics and Homicide
are on their way.
That 's the victim's car.
It 's covered in blood.
Over here, I found the boy
faced down in the water...
with about a million stab wounds.
And the girl...
nailed to a tree.
A lot of blood pumped out of
her wounds, which means...
Which means all this was done
while she was still alive.
I'm trying to pump out a special
edition of the paper before lunch.
It you tell me all that you know,
I'll be your best friend...
and you can be co-editor of the
paper, what do you think?
Don't be silent like that. Talk to
your daddy and snoop dog for me.
I don't have a clue
what you're talking about.
You haven't heard about
Rod e Stacy?
Are you taking fun notes for
your pathetic gossip column?
- Did they break up?
- Break up? Wake up, they're dead!
They shuffled up the mortal coil,
they went to see their maker.
How can you be so
critically uninformed?
Look, the whole school is
buzzing with that music.
Look! Maybe there's something for
my pathetic gossip column after all.
Like I'm not paying attention.
Mr. Sisler, sheriff Marken is here.
Shall I bring him in?
Thank you, Diana.
- It 's been a while, Brent.
- Tom!
I don't need to tell you what
an uproar the school is in.
I canceled all the
regular classes...
and asked the teachers to
counsel and console the kids.
I know there are professionals
for this sort of situation...
...but I thought it 'd be best...
- I'll have to stop by some classes.
Ask a few questions.
I would like to start with the ones
those two kids attended.
Naturally, you're
all horrified...
by the sudden senseless loss
of your classmates.
Perhaps some of you feel guilty
that you weren't nicer to them...
or maybe you're...
haunted by something unpleasant
you might have said to one of them.
Once, in the 8th grade,
I had a fight with Rod...
I told him to fuck off and die!
Come on, guys.
It 's alright, Heather.
Maybe we'll all feel better if we
talk about them and how we feel.
Mark, you were friends with Rod.
Do you want to say something?
Oh, man...
I don't know, I'm just...
Thank you.
How about you, Sandy?
I guess at times like this...
...I just hope there is a heaven.
- Lame.
Cindy, come on!
It 's important in times like this
we offer each other some support.
I'd like to offer the killer some
support in the electric chair.
It 's alright, but the means of
execution is by lethal injection.
Ben, I know you have a different
point of view regarding the tragedy.
Go head.
I'd like to know whether
this killer...
removed any body parts, or sexually
defiled any orifice of the victims.
You're sick.
I wanna know, because if he didn't,
I think he deserves thumbs down.
- How can you be so insensitive?
- And you are Mother Teresa?
- You told him to drop dead.
- You're fooling yourself with this.
Jackass, you're not playing
Death quake, this is the real world.
Fuck you.
It 's Ben's pathetic concept of cool,
just to pretend he's not afraid.
Hello Cindy Freud.
What 's your concept of cool?
Bang the entire senior class
starting with "A"?
If I'm what you just said, why do
you try to hook me up nonstop?
- I find the experience attractive.
- Shut up now, would you please?
Everyone!
What 's wrong with you people?
Jody...
certainly I can count on you to say
something singularly constructive.
Dad?
Please, excuse the intrusion,
Mr. Marliston...
but sheriff Marken would like
to address the class.
- It 's a pleasure to meet you, sir.
- Likewise.
Class, please give your attention
to sheriff Marken.
Two of your fellow students,
Rod Harper and Stacy Twelfmann...
were murdered
last night at the falls...
by a person or persons unknown,
in a cold-blooded fashion.
The reason I came here was to ask
you, as friends and good citizens...
to come forward to me
or my staff...
with any information you might have
concerning this terrible crime.
- Is there a suspect yet?
- No.
- Is there any other information?
- I can't discuss the case.
Plato says, policy can only remain
healthy if truth is available to all.
Plato can give all details he wants
when he's the sheriff of this town.
He's doing it deliberately.
Of course he is.
All the more reason why
you should ignore it.
Do you think she goes
all the way?
I doubt it.
Who'd want to fuck her?
Look.
Shit.
Stop throwing shit!
I'm done with relationships...
but I see a hope for you.
Come on.
- No, Jody.
- Come on.
You watch him eat every single day
and you never talk to him.
My parents have been married for
25 years and they do the same.
You're going to go.
You don't want to make a scene!
How are you doing?
- It 's a pretty freaky day today.
- I guess so.
Shit sucking liar!
I'm gonna kill you!
Better than a cock-sucking liar!
I'll kill you.
What 's going on here?
It 's a compliment when a guy
says you can suck good dick.
You got something
on your mouth there.
- He's lying to everyone about me.
- Tell me about it in the office.
Leave your phone number.
It wasn't me.
- What 's up with that?
- He's saying she gave him a hammer.
- Did she?
- Are you kidding?
She thinks fellatio is Shakespeare's
character. She never saw a dick.
That 's funny.
What do you think, Mark?
I think these ribs rule.
Come on, honey, we're late.
Hi, handsome.
Here we go.
It 's good to see you!
Who is it?
Annette?
- It 's Loralee Sherman.
- Excuse me?
Loralee Sherman.
Is your mom home?
She didn't tell you
I was coming by?
I must have just missed her.
Can I leave a note?
Just one second.
Could you slip it through
the door, please?
I think I'm ready for the run.
What 's the hurry for?
Slow down.
- Who left the door open?
- I don't know.
Annette?
Grab there, grab underneath.
Get a good grip.
Step through, let their weight and
their momentum take them over.
The most important thing
is this grip. Like a pitbull.
Is there any way you could give me
a ray gun, stun gun, anything?
It 's against the law.
Here I come.
Take 5, champ.
Marken.
Looks like we have
an encore performer.
Agent Bronhill, this is
special agent Majestik.
- Who was first on the scene?
- My deputy.
I responded to the father's call
11:OO pm, then I called the sheriff.
I'll get this.
We're in the big league now.
As you can see on the inside left thigh
there's a one inch deep carving...
of the word "virgin".
Also found in all 3 victims.
Like Stacy Twelfmann...
Annette was in fact a virgin
at the time of death.
The hymen was intact. We found no
evidence of semen on the clothes...
skin, hair, mouth, or the anus.
No abrasions or contusions
in the pubic region.
In fact no evidence of
sexual penetration of any kind.
Neither was the boy we found in the
first killings sexually assaulted.
Of course I can't tell you if
he died a virgin...
but I can tell you that he had no
sex at the time of the killings.
It would appear...
that your killer has been accurate
in the application of his signature.
Come in.
Hi, honey.
Hi, daddy.
Listen...
I need to ask you
a personal question.
- About what?
- About you and Kenny.
- What is it?
- How far you've gone?
Gone?
Gone, you know...
base wise.
Are you two kissing?
Of course.
I'm not a child anymore, dad.
That 's normal.
- I'm not criticizing.
- I know.
Have you gone further than that?
I wouldn't ask you this unless
it was absolutely necessary.
Can you go further...
than you have?
Yes.
But you don't have
to worry about it.
We just broke up the other day.
Are you disappointed, dad?
Are you disappointed
that I'm still a virgin?
Not at all.
I'm very, very proud of you.
You're still my little girl.
Good night.
I love you.
Parents in our town need to know
what 's going on here.
Does that mean revealing
the signature?
I suppose it does.
Textbooks say don't.
It leaves us no conclusive way
to verify the killer's confession.
- It could inspire copycat crimes.
- This is different.
This isn't a signature.
It 's a message.
Message?
Set up an emergency town meeting.
Tonight at 6:OO pm.
I want every parent of every
teenager in town there. Do it.
We don't have a venue
big enough for that.
We'll use the gym
at the high school.
No kids.
Not yet.
There you are, Mr. Marliston.
I finished my T. S. Elliot paper.
Great.
- I really love his work.
- Good.
"Less our dried voices
When we whisper together
Are quite and meaningless
As wind and dry grass
Or rats feeding of broken glass
In our dry cellar"
Do you think that that 's how it is
between people, Mr. Marliston?
Everything dry...
and meaningless
and hopelessly empty?
I heard that you broke up
with Kenny.
What does that have to do with it?
I'm very over him.
Do you think that any serious
thought that I have...
is solely attributed to my one
misspent year with Kenny?
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm very embarrassed
that I just yelled at you.
I'm really sorry,
it 's none of my business.
What 's wrong?
It 's weird. I just saw
someone standing there.
Come out!
- Anything?
- No.
I guess we've spooked each
other pretty good, didn't we?
Come on, I have to go to this
meeting your father organized.
Are you gonna be alright?
Mr. Marliston?
Can we talk again sometime?
- Of course, Jody.
- I mean just the us.
Sure.
Go home, Jody.
Run!
You cannot tell these parents
somebody is murdering virgins.
Maybe Annette would be
alive today...
if I had revealed details
about the first two killings.
Get a hold of yourself.
You've got responsibility.
Get your hands of me.
Don't talk to me about it! We know
what it means to walk away from it.
If word got back to these kids
that somebody is...
murdering virgins, we are
gonna have a goddamn...
...fuck festival on our hands.
- It 's better than dead teenagers.
- What are you doing here?
- I am getting the scoop.
- Then, get it.
I want to thank you very much
for coming out this evening.
As I'm sure you all know...
in the last two days
we've lost 3 of our children.
We've know established the
common link between those killings.
What is it?
All 3 victims attended
our public high school...
and all 3 victims,
to the best of our knowledge...
appeared to be... virgins.
Holly hymens, Batman!
They're killing virgins!
- You mean it 's more than coincidence?
- Are you close to an arrest?
- What are we going to tell our kids?
- To go out and get laid to be safe?
- I'm not saying that.
- I can't lock my daughter home.
- I wouldn't worry about it, Victor.
- What are you saying about her?
Sit down, I was joking.
It 's a hell of a time to be joking
about a thing like this!
Back off!
This is totally excellent. They've
turned into a bunch of wild animals!
Get out of the way.
- Battery! Can I use your phone?
- You never turn it back.
Please, remember why
we came here.
Just give this to me.
Elway? Stop the presses,
I've got a story for you.
Virgin killer terrorizes...
You're breaking up.
No, not virgin killer...
I have to get our of here.
I'm asking you
for the last time.
Alright, that 's enough!
Oh, daddy!
Timmy?
I need my cell phone back.
Shit!
Timmy, come on!
This isn't funny anymore.
I'll be your best friend.
Your very, very, very best friend.
Is that for me?
Virgin.
She was after me.
She killed Timmy! She's in there.
- Take her. Stay back!
- Dad, be careful.
Maybe the nose was just
a little bit smaller.
And there was a gray
streak right there.
Like that.
That 's her.
That 's at least what I saw of her.
Can you make her, sheriff?
Listen to me! Listen to me!
- Listen to me!
- Give me the bell.
You stupid FBI sons of bitches,
why don't you come here and get me?
- You did good, baby.
- Listen to me, I killed those kids.
I've got to make
a couple of calls.
Your mother will be here in
a couple of minutes. You'll be fine.
- I killed those kids.
- Watch your language.
You're a bunch of sons of bitches!
That 's what you are.
And you know what? I loved
to kill them. They were evil.
I loved to kill them. Do you know
what I did before I killed them?
I kissed them.
Like this!
Rolly is my name!
Don't you hurt me!
I know my rights.
Brent.
Great meeting last night.
Very comforting to parents.
Listen, are you alone?
Good, because I have something
to show you. I'm faxing to you now.
Are you looking at it?
Tell me that's not her.
- Who?
- Loralee Sherman. Isn't it her?
Brent, you are cracking up.
Years ago, I tried to contact her.
I traced here to West Virginia.
About two hours from here.
This time I'm going out there.
Nobody has seen or heard of her
for over 25 years.
Why the hell would she
be showing up now...
as some sort of
a psycho killer?
Put the phone down,
I'll call you back.
- What are you doing?
- What is wrong?
Were you listening to me?
What did you hear?
I didn't hear anything. I just
picked up the phone to call mom.
I couldn't figure out how
to get a line out, that 's all.
Sorry, honey.
This case, I guess...
it 's really getting to me.
Sorry, baby, it 's not your fault.
It 's not your fault.
Hi, sheriff Marken.
Hello, Sandy.
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Everybody's been asking about you.
Sheriff! Rolly, prisoner wants
to make a full confession.
I hope it 's faster than
last week's confession.
- You're not gonna believe this.
- What?
Hurricane hormone has hit
the whole entire school.
Word got out that your attacker
has this thing for virgins.
Everyone's decided to leave the
endangered species list. Have sex.
- You make it sound like a flu shot.
- We're talking hymen holocaust here.
But they couldn't print the location,
so I'm gonna give you the 411.
- Where is it?
- The old Donkey Hill hunting lodge.
That disgusting place?
That place is such a shithole.
All we need is floor space.
Didn't you want your first time to be
something beautiful and romantic?
You have to go!
Everybody is gonna be there.
Mark is going, of course.
And Kenny.
And you cannot leave saving his life
up to that slut Sharon.
Cindy is holding her pre-game talk
at the bleacher's at lunch. All girls.
How is my baby?
How is your leg?
Sandy, good to see you.
I'm so happy you're here.
Honey, are you finished yet?
Are you ready to come home?
- I was gonna go to school with Sandy.
- I don't think that 's a very good idea.
Why don't you go home
with your mother?
I'd really like to be
with my friends right now.
She will be safe with us.
It 's okay.
I'll keep an eye on her.
Come on!
It 's nice to see you, Jody.
Are you alright?
How did you make it?
I almost lost you.
I couldn't go on living if I had.
- Really?
- Of course.
How about, what 's her face?
Jody, I love you.
But I still have female friends.
- But?
- But...
Let 's not fight. Come with me
to this party tonight.
I promised my dad I'd be home after
school and stay there. I promised.
Look, if you don't want
to go with me...
just say so.
Don't use your dad as an excuse.
I'm not.
Who is that?
- It 's my bodyguard.
- Bodyguard?
I told my dad I'd be home at 3.
But will you come with me? Come
with me later and we'll go together.
I'll think about it.
Girls have to do everything.
Boys are totally clueless when
it comes to sex.
It starts with them trying to unhook
our bras and it never changes.
Wait until they try to put
their dicks in you.
- Do they need help with that?
- Always.
What about birth control?
Girls, there's no time
for the pill...
and certainly no chance
for withdraw...
so, I recommend condoms.
What about clitoral
or vaginal orgasm?
Unless we're talking about
masturbation, forget it.
Aren't you being just
a little hard on the boys?
Dennis asked me today
if chicks had 2 holes or 3.
- I did not!
- How could you not know that?
I forgot I was hanging
with the experts clan.
I get it that the four kids
are dead, but...
I'm sorry, this is
still a pretty choice.
No shit!
Next thing we have to do,
is find a psycho...
who is after chicks
who don't give head.
Then I won't have to worry
about one hole.
This is Stan Michaels, coming to
you live from G. W. High School...
the epicenter of what can only
be described as...
the senseless slaughter of innocence
here in Cherry Falls, Virginia.
In the last 3 days, four teenagers
have been killed, and one attacked.
Certain local officials believe
the killer, still at large...
may be targeting teenage
high school virgins.
And now the students here on campus
have organized a sex party...
to actually eliminate themselves
as possible targets.
Attention, this is your
principal speaking.
It has come to my notice
that certain individuals...
have taken it upon themselves
to organize a wild party tonight.
I want you to know...
that any G.W. student
attending this gap...
will be disadvantaged by every
penalty it 's in my power to impose.
Local school officials don't know
how to handle the situation.
We'll get comments now
from the students...
Virgin High!
Drop your pants to fuck, or die!
Hi, mom.
How's my brave little baby?
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Don't worry, deputy Mina was
watching me like a hawk all day.
Must've been a very
interesting day at school.
Definitely, it wasn't
your typical Thursday.
I smell fresh cookies here.
These are a little bit burned, but
I've got another batch coming out.
Don't eat this.
Spit it out.
Then let me get you some water
to wash it down.
Mom? Do you know anything about
a woman named Loralee Sherman?
No, why?
I overheard daddy talking to
Mr. Sisler and they mentioned her.
I have no idea who
you're talking about.
Mr. Sisler said that she had
disappeared 25 years ago.
Wouldn't a story like that
make small town news?
I've never heard of her,
and I have lived here all my life...
except those two years
at Berkeley.
I think you should go lie down,
take a little rest. You look pale.
- I'll call you for dinner.
- I'm wasted.
Okay, sweetheart?
I'm going to West Virginia.
West Virginia?
We need you here.
There's something
I've got to do there.
Okay, I'll hold down the fort.
But we are getting some calls
from some irate parents.
What do you want us to do
about this sex party?
Sex party?
Do you know where it is?
I'll find out.
Treat it like any other party.
If there's trouble, move in.
Otherwise, lay off.
I could be gone a while.
- Mom!
- What are you doing here? Go home!
Mom, tell me about
Loralee Sherman. Tell me!
Tell me!
When I was in high school...
there was a girl named
Loralee Sherman...
that claimed she was raped by...
4 drunken seniors.
And?
Nobody was ever
formally charged. Nobody.
Nobody was ever charged.
Was there any evidence?
Did she identify them?
And why weren't they charged?
Because they were from good
families, stars of the football team.
And she was just this Loner
that nobody cared for.
She just thought she was
smarter than everybody.
Nothing would have
ever come from it.
I don't know if it would have
held up in court.
Not then, and I don't think
they would now.
So, you all just let it go?
She left town...
and nobody ever
saw her again.
That was 27 years ago.
Who are the men that raped her?
Well, two of the guys left town
about the year after that.
And that was good, because we
were all able to move forward after.
Who else?
- Tommy Sisler.
- The principle.
You said that there were
four men.
Who is the fourth?
Mom?
Who is the fourth, mom?
Mom!
Your father.
Honey, he didn't participate. He was
sick, he was falling down drunk.
But he went to the police, and
he told them what happened?
Honey, those were his good friends.
He couldn't do that.
And besides,
what would he tell police?
That a drunken girl had sex
with three drunken boys?
You said it was rape.
441O-5 to 45.
45.
What's twenty?
I'm heading back now.
Did you find what
you were looking for?
- Sir?
- I don't know.
I've got a message for you to meet
up with Tom Sisler at the school.
Did he say why?
Something to do with a Loralee
Sherman. I spoke to his secretary.
Sir, are you there?
Roger that.
I'll check it out.
I really need to see you.
You're early.
My parents are total frauds.
- Disgusting.
- Of course they are.
They're your parents.
My dad is into hookers.
I think my mom probably
was a hooker.
I can't believe I let them influence
every decision I've ever made.
You lose your
spiritual virginity...
when you realize
that your parents...
are even bigger hypocrites
than your friends are.
Bite it.
Harder.
Harder!
Let 's do it now.
You've been pressuring me
for a whole year to sleep with you.
Let 's just do it.
You're only doing it because
you're pissed with your parents.
What 's wrong, Kenny?
Can't you decide?
It doesn't have to be
this complicated, baby.
Don't you like my body?
I love your...
I love your body, baby.
I just want you to be with me
because you want to be with me.
That 's all.
Spare me the violins.
Where are you going?
I changed my mind about tonight.
I don't need some
stupid kids sex party.
You have a better company
in mind?
- Frankly, yes.
- Like Mr. Marliston, maybe?
Where did that come from?
I've seen you
hanging out with him.
You probably have. So, I should start
looking for you around every corner...
eaves-dropping, snooping,
sneaking about.
Kenny, I had no idea
that your poor mind...
was so diseased.
If you go now,
I don't want to see you again.
It 's over!
You take the north side, you take
the rear. Beau, you get the south.
- I'll watch the front.
- Do you want to go in with me?
- Be undercover for half an hour.
- Get moving!
Sharon, you look voluptuous.
What is that smell?
It 's just a little cologne.
I wouldn't go near any candles
if I were you.
It might spontaneously combust.
What 's that smell?
Nothing.
I like it.
You like to dance?
Have you ever
played Death quake?
Okay, but you have
to wear a rubber.
- And I want your CDs.
- Not my imports.
I want everything. Domestic,
imports, bootlegs, works.
Okay, you can have my CDs.
- And your snowboard.
- Not my snowboard.
Alright, the board too.
You know, that 's an awful lot
for 1O minutes of sex.
Don't flatter yourself, you'll be
lucky to last 1O seconds.
You just hope when I erupt
you don't end up in the ceiling.
You don't have to be nervous.
You are the one who is shaking.
You okay?
What 's wrong?
I can't face this is
happening again!
Twice today I stopped a girl from
putting her hands in my pants.
Is there something you want to
tell me? I don't mind a challenge.
Right. Neither do I.
Thank you, Sharon.
You could've given it a shot.
I always knew he was
a butt pirate.
- You wanna get with a real man?
- No. Do you?
- You scared me.
- Sorry.
- How are you?
- Good, and you?
What have you got in this trunk?
Just some old memorabilia.
Do you want a hand?
I could use a hand with this.
Are you sure? It 's going all the way
into my basement.
This way.
You're just about the only person
that I trust these days.
Me? What about your dad? I know
how close you are with your father.
I found out some pretty terrible
things about my father recently.
Like what?
That he's a liar, a fraud...
a criminal?
What 's in the trunk?
Your dad.
Maybe mine.
Daddy!
Brent, tell us about what
happened 27 years ago...
when you were very drunk.
Tom Sisler is in the story, and so
is a woman named Loralee Sherman.
There are people
who can help you.
Don't hurt her.
Please.
I'm not gonna hurt her.
You are, with the truth.
I'll get you started.
I remember the story like this.
It was a dark and scary night...
kind of like tonight.
My mother already told me
the story. You can't hurt me...
Shut up!
I'll kill you
if you don't shut up.
Alright.
I'll tell you.
There were four of us.
We were drunk.
About ready to graduate
from high school.
We were going to a party to
celebrate the end of our senior year.
Then, we saw a car broke down
on the side of the road.
It was Loralee.
We all knew her from school.
She was a weird kid.
Kind of pretty in a way, I guess.
I was in really bad shape.
Tom told her to get into his car...
but she wouldn't do it.
So, they started teasing her.
Laughing at her.
And then she got mad.
She called Tom a homo...
and she just took off.
They took off right after her.
That's when things got crazy.
They poured booze
down her throat.
I guess what happened...
You know what happened.
I don't remember,
so, keep going.
First Tom,
then Harry...
then Jim.
Then, they came looking for me...
and they grabbed me...
and threw me on top of her.
But I knew what I was doing.
God help me, I knew what
I was doing!
God, daddy, no!
Happy graduation.
I knew.
Did you know that
she was in love with you?
Love letters, poems,
songs...
All things she wrote
before you raped her.
That 's why she came over to the car.
Because she saw your face.
She never had the nerve to approach
the big star quarterback Brent.
You never knew that
she loved you, did you, Brent?
How could you?
She never had the nerve to approach
you before you raped her.
And after you raped her,
there was no one to tell.
Except me.
Over and over again.
It 's difficult to look like the one
person your mother loves...
and hates the most.
We have the same
color of eyes...
dad.
It 's a stinking hypocritical world,
isn't it, Brent?
Where rapists become
the pillars of the community.
And the stinking
hypocritical people in it...
wouldn't even miss their own
worthless lives very much.
So...
what better to deprive them of
the only innocence they have left.
Their precious...
virginal children.
Please!
Don't hurt her.
Does that hurt?
Help!
Shut up!
Goddamn that bell!
I'm coming!
Hi, Kenny. What are you
doing here at midnight?
Mister Marliston...
Something wrong with your mouth?
What do you want?
- Where is Jody?
- How should I know?
- Her bike is parked by your stairs.
- No, it 's not.
Why are you looking at me
like that, Kenny?
- Why are you wearing lipstick?
- Because it makes me pretty.
Jody!
You hurt my daughter.
I'm gonna kill you!
Get out of here!
Go!
Come on!
The music!
To the lounge, come on!
- Hold! Stop right there!
- Mr. Marliston just killed my daddy.
He killed all those kids.
He tried to kill us!
- Who is that with you?
- Kenny Ascott. And it 's all true.
White Knight to Black Queen,
do you copy?
Black Queen
to White Knight, over.
Brent is dead.
Marliston is the killer.
- Do you copy, over?
- You better come now.
This is my post,
I can't just split.
Shit!
Goddamn it!
Nobody is here.
- Help!
- Run!
It 's Mr. Marliston!
He is the killer!
Class dismissed.
Run, Jody!
Come on!
Jody!
Stay there.
Kenny!
- Mark, don't!
- Man, get back here.
Mister Marliston.
So you have absolutely no idea why
your father was in West Virginia?
And you can think of no reason why
Marliston committed these murders?
And after all this, you can't think
of nothing else to tell me?
I think you've asked my daughter
enough questions.
Thank you for now, ladies.
You've been very cooperative.
Let 's go