**[Radio: Loud Rock
"I'm Gonna Be A Wheel Someday"]
*Hey, hey *
*I'm gonna be a wheel someday
I'm gonna be somebody *
*I'm gonna be a real gone cat
Then I won't want you *
*Everything gonna go my way
And I won't need nobody *
*I'm gonna be a real gone cat
Then I won't want you *
* You can cry-y-y *
* You're gonna cry
hy-hy-hy *
[Sabrina's Voice]
I know what you're thinking.
Beautiful car.
Beautiful girl.
Pride of her mother's eye,
right?
Hmm... wrong.
*I'm gonna be a real gone cat
Then I won't want you *
**
[Dog Barking]
[Woman]
Come along, baby.
Come, Fi-Fi.
Come to mommy, dear.
Come on, baby.
Ahh.
**[Car Radio]
Come on. Fi-Fi!
Here, baby.
Oh! Ah.
Fi-Fi!
My mother says that everyone has a
certain measure of good and bad in them,
but that I have too much of one
and not enough of the other.
*I'm gonna be a wheel one day
I'm gonna be somebody *
Oh! Fi-Fi, come!
Hurry!
*I'm gonna be a real gone cat
Then I won't want you *
No, no, no, no, no!
[Screams]
[Sabrina's Voice]
My mother doesn't know me at all.
Oh, nasty ol' car.
* You'll be wonderin' why I don't look
at you when I go rollin'by **
**[Piano]
**
[Sabrina]
"Teach the young, and set them free. "
[Chuckles]
They haven't met me.
[Car Horn Honking]
[Man]
Look at the car!
[Horn Honking]
- Hi.
- I'm lost.
- New girl in town, huh?
Yes.
My first day.
- Where're you headed?
- The A.B.P. house.
That's just
right around there.
Great. Thanks.
That's a real nice chassis
you got here.
Well, if you'd like to take it
for a spin one of these days,
just ask for Sabrina.
[Horn Honking]
[Giggling, Cheering]
[Girls Together]
Sabrina, we welcome you.
To Alpha Beta Pi,
forever be true.
Every sister
across the land,
forever united,
hand in hand.
[Cheering]
- Did you just make that up?
- Oh, of course not, dear.
- That's the Alpha Beta Pi cheer.
- Oh. Ha, ha.
I'm Mrs. Billings,
your housemother.
- Nice to meet you. Sisterhood forever!
- [Girls Cheering]
I'm Rita,
the sorority president,
- and your new roommate.
- Lucky me.
And this is Tina.
I'm her sponsor.
Oh, and the best friend a pledge
has ever had. Welcome to A.B.P.
- Thank you.
- [Rita] And this is Ellie.
She'll be your new
little pledge sister.
Oh, it's so great
to meet you!
Where did you get this incredible car?
I would die to drive a car like this.
Well, how 'bout now?
Would you park it in the back,
little sis?
- Well, let's go inside.
- Oh, thank you.
Oh, I can't believe I'll be rooming
with Julie Masterson's real-life sister.
[Cheering]
[Mrs. Billings]
Your sisterJulia was my favorite.
Finest president
this sorority ever had.
[Sabrina] You know,
I'm nothing like my sister.
You know, I've always suspected
I was adopted.
- Just kidding.
- Oh.
Come on.
I'll show you to our rooms.
Well, this is it.
This is my bed,
and... this is all my stuff.
That's your bed.
And this...
is our closet.
Oh, and the bathroom is
down the hall and to the left.
Down the hall?
Well, you'd think the sorority president
would have her own bathroom.
Yeah. Well, we have to
improvise a little around here.
Um, I made
this shirt myself.
- Do you sew?
- Not if I can help it.
Gosh,
this closet is tiny.
You don't mind if I use
the extra space on your side, do you?
Not at all.
Wow! These are all
French designers.
I love this!
"Coco Channel."
It's pronounced
CoCo Chanel.
And I don't share
my clothes.
I didn't ask you to!
Oh, wait.
It's just that I had a bad experience
with my last roommate and...
I guess I'm a little jumpy.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
[Sabrina]
I know that guy.
Really? That's my boyfriend Mort.
How do you know him?
Well, I met him when I drove on campus.
Isn't he a student here?
Oh, not anymore. He owns
this little joint by the beach.
Well, maybe we should go
for a drink there sometime.
Well, what are you doin' tonight?
There's a frat party at Mort's.
Oh, I'm not very good
at parties.
Shy, I guess.
[Music, Party Chatter]
* Cherry Lips, Cherry Lips
Whisper in my ear *
Whisper loud and clear *
* You drink cherry wine *
*Sweet as the grapes
hangin'on the vine *
[Boy] This is for you.
Will you wear it?
What does that mean?
Means you're my girl.
- Yes.
- **[Continues]
* Yes, just tell me do *
[Music, Chattering Continue]
- Oh, that's such a cute name.
- * Cherry Lips, Cherry Lips *
* Whisper in my ear *
* Cherry Lips, Cherry Lips
Whisper loud and clear *
- All right. Excuse me.
- * You drink cherry wine *
*Sweet as the grape
hangin'on the vine *
Surprise!
- How 'bout that spin?
- [Chuckles]
It doesn't take you long
to make friends, does it?
Well, you can never be
too popular.
- If you like someone, let 'em know.
- Next dance is ladies'choice.
**
So, what do you do around here for fun
when you're not working?
Run around with Rita.
Excuse me.
- Hi.
Mmm, the place looks great.
Thanks. Yeah, I put up
the tiki lights just for the party.
- They look great. Leave 'em up.
- Thank you.
I have some good news
for you.
- What?
- I got into medical school.
- Oh! Congratulations!
- Thank you.
[Rita] That's great.
But what about the bar?
- The bar is just my fall-back plan...
- No.
In case I realize I don't like
the sight of blood.
You're gonna be
a great doctor!
And you are gonna make
a great doctor's wife.
Hey, doll, this oughta
loosen you up, huh?
I don't need
loosening up.
Excuse me. I believe it's ladies'
choice. Do you mind if I cut in?
Some other time.
Right now I'm dancing with my girl.
*Now my heart's
no longer empty *
* Those happy days are here *
[Giggling]
*My face is full of gladness
My eyes get no more tears *
Don't take it personally, Sabrina.
Mort never dances with anyone but Rita.
So, doll, a bunch of us are going
to the lake next weekend. You wanna go?
- Hi, Ellie.
- That sounds great! Let's go, Sabrina.
Ellie, that cake looks delicious.
Would you go and get me a piece?
- Sure! It's got chocolate.
- Mm-hmm.
- [Screams]
- [Laughing]
That is not funny!
Come on, Ellie.
Tina, I love you.
I love you too.
I want you.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Do you have, uh, one of
those things in your pocket?
No.
I didn't plan this.
Bonjour, Mama.
Ah, no, I can't hear you.
- It's a terrible connection.
- Sabrina, I can hear you perfectly.
- How's school?
- It's wonderful here. Thank you, Mama.
- Did you get my letter?
- Oh, yes, yes, I got the check.
- How's Daddy?
- We're all fine. We miss you.
Oh, I miss you too.
- I have to leave with the tour tonight.
- Wait, I can't hear you.
Tomorrow we're going to...
- Wait. That's a better connection.
[Dial Tone Buzzing]
Oh, Mama,
I need your permission.
A few of the frat boys are going
up to the lake and they invited me.
Can I go?
- Thank you. It's so good to be trusted.
- [Dial Tone Buzzing]
- [School Bell Ringing]
- Well, I have to go to class now, Mama.
Yes, send my love to Daddy
and my beloved sisterJulia.
For me too.
Oh, and Mrs. Billings sends her love.
Right. Au revoir.
That is a lovely shade
of lipstick, Mrs. " B."
- Whoo!
- Ya-hoo!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
- Whoo-hoo-hoo!
- Whoo! Yea!
So long, suckers!
- Can't this go any faster?
- I'm tryin'!
- Here, move over, angel. Let me drive.
- Oh, come on.
Let me drive!
Whoo!
There's a good marker.
- First one to pull away buys dinner!
- Yeah!
All right!
Go!
[Shouting, Laughing
In Speedboats]
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Whoo!
[Laughing]
- Watch this.
- Go ahead.
Shit!
- Come on, Sabrina!
- I'm no chicken.
- Hurry up!
- Mommy!
- What are they doin'?
- Mom!
- Damn! Keep goin', keep goin'.
- Sabrina, what're you doin'?
[Laughing]
We won!
Shit!
[Joe] Hoo-hoo. Come on.
Let's go celebrate.
[Sabrina]
Oh, you got it!
I realize that some of you may find
the reading a bit difficult.
Just be glad you're
studying French, not German.
Instead of just masculine and
feminine nouns, there are neuter.
[Mispronouncing French]
Well, vive la difference.
On the last page
of Huis Clos,
who can tell me what Sartre meant
when he said " Hell is other people"?
[Sabrina Laughing]
Mademoiselle Masterson?
What?
Did you read
the assignment?
I hardly need to study
elementary French, Professor Leland.
I've been to Paris many times, and I
speak well enough to get by, thank you.
Mademoiselle Masterson,
please read the first paragraph
on the last page and explain it,
in French, of course.
[Clears Throat]
"Je n'aurais jamais cru.
"Vous vous rappelez:
"Le soufre, le bucher,
le gril.
"Ah! Quelle plaisanterie.
"Pas besoin de gril:
- I'enfer, c'est les Autres. "
- She kisses better than she speaks.
- And, what did Sartre mean?
- If you know what I mean.
Well, you're the teacher.
You tell me.
- I know the answer.
- Mademoiselle Summers.
"L 'enfer,
c'est les Autres, "
which means
" Hell is other people."
I think since Sartre didn't
believe in an afterlife,
he meant we create our own hell with
the people we choose to be friends with.
Magnifique, Rita!
- [School Bell Rings]
- [Clapping]
Bravo.
Sabrina! Sabrina!
I'm sorry if I embarrassed you.
I didn't mean to.
To what? Make me look
like an idiot back there?
Look, I really want us
to be friends.
I've always been an overachiever, and
I don't think before I open my mouth.
I'm really, really sorry.
Okay, Rita. I wouldn't want us
to be rivals.
Anyway, "sisterhood forever."
Remember?
Rita,
there's a letter for you.
[Mrs. Billings]
Rita!
- What's wrong?
- She must not get much mail.
[Crying]
- Bad news?
- Oh.
I just... Letters from my mother
make me very homesick.
Unless there's a check in it, right?
It takes the edge right off.
No, it's... it's not
that kind of letter.
Oh, come on.
It can't be that bad.
It's just I, uh, I don't get to see
my mother very often.
And I miss her
very much.
Well, just go home
and surprise her.
Um, she's not really home
right now. She...
She kinda works at this hospital,
and she's gotta live in there.
Well, then, just go there
and see her.
I can't. She's real busy and it's...
weird to see her there.
Huh. That is weird.
My mom and I
are so close.
- We're more like sisters.
- You're so lucky.
There's so much that I'd like
to share with my mom.
You know, like about school
and boys,
and what I want
for my future.
But it's so hard to write that
in a letter.
I tell my mom everything.
She takes me shopping,
on long, lazy lunches.
It sounds like your mom's
a lot of fun.
Yeah.
You'd love her.
**["Express Yourself
Back Home"]
**
[Giggling, Laughing]
* That train won't stop till
we're rollin'into New Orleans *
*Express yourself back home *
* The trains may come
alone *
Ah, the water's great, girl.
You should really take a swim.
[Wolf Whistle]
* Get your booty on home
to me *
[Wolf Whistle]
* Well, the boss keeps yellin'
Sees the work's not like before *
- Where's Mort?
- Surfing. Why?
Just asking.
Come on, Ellie,
let's go get some more iced tea.
- Yeah, I'll come too.
- I'll have one with lemon.
*Express yourself
back home *
*Before I scream and moan *
* Oh, Mama
I done need to be *
* Get your booty
on home to me *
**
Hey, baby.
[Wolf Whistle]
* Well, the boss keeps yellin'
Sees the work's not like before *
- * Well, the boss keeps yellin'*
- Just put it on the table.
- *Sees the work's not like before **
- You're in my sun.
- Mother!
- [Music Stops]
What a surprise.
I thought
you were in Paris.
Thank you.
- What do I owe this honor? Someone die?
- Not yet.
How was the lake?
Did you catch any trout?
I'm sure I don't know
what you mean.
I spoke with Mrs. Billings last night
when I returned from Paris.
She told me about your
little weekend excursion...
to which I supposedly
gave my permission.
You lied, Sabrina.
I thought we had an agreement.
It was a harmless little
camping trip, Mother.
And hardly worth bothering you about.
I'm sorry, Mother.
I'm ashamed of you.
I won't allow you to humiliate our name
again, and the memory of your sister.
What are you gonna do
about it, Mother? Spank me?
As of today, your allowance
is terminated.
What is the matter
with you, Sabrina?
You behave like a brat. Your grades
are atrocious. You're failing French.
- Why can't you be more...
- LikeJulia?
Sorry, Mother, but God was only able
to make one perfect daughter for you.
Now you'll just have
to suffer with me.
Don't bring God and your sister
into this, my little darling.
If it weren't forJulia's
impeccable reputation,
you never would have gotten into this
school, let alone this sorority.
I'm warning you, Sabrina,
don't blow it.
If you want my respect,
you'll have to earn it.
I'm going now.
And by the way,
don't bother trying to use
your charge accounts.
They've also been frozen.
Good-bye, my darling.
But, Mother.
Mother, I'm trying.
I'm trying as hard as I can.
Try a little harder.
- Out of lemon. I hope you don't mind.
- I'm not thirsty anyway.
Can I borrow one?
- Oh, sure!
- I thought you said I could have one.
- Janet, I put it on your bed.
- Thanks.
Curfew, girls.
[Clock Bonging]
[Mrs. Billings]
Curfew.
[Clock Bonging
Continues]
[Tina] I don't know.
Jimmy, just tell me what to do.
Curfew, girls.
[Knocks On Door]
Good night. Curfew.
Sabrina?
Can you help me? Tina is going to
get in a lot of trouble.
[Tina] It just happened. You don't
have to marry me or anything, Jimmy.
I can go away. I can have the baby
by myself if that's how you want it.
- [Tina] Is that how you want it?
- [Jimmy] I don't know.
I gotta think.
- I'll call you.
- [Motor Revs]
- [Mrs. Billings] Curfew, girls.
- Good night, Mrs. Billings.
Lights out, Sabrina.
Good night, dear.
[Door Opens]
- Uh, Mrs. Billings?
- Yes, dear?
- Can I have a word with you?
- [Mrs. Billings] Certainly.
I was wondering...
if it would be all right if I ran
for sorority president?
Oh, your mother would be
so proud of you!
Yeah, I know, but I don't want to cause
any bad feelings between Rita and I.
She seems like a good sport,
but, well, you know her better than I.
Oh, I think it would be
perfectly fine.
A little competition...
it's good for the race.
Oh, Mrs. Billings, thank you.
I feel much better now.
Well, I better get to bed now,
curfew and all.
Good night, dear.
[Knocking On Door]
Curfew, girls.
- Lights out.
- Good night, Mrs. Billings.
Good night, Ellie.
- Boy, Sabrina really saved your butt.
- Yeah.
What are you gonna do,
Tina?
What do you mean?
I heard you and Jimmy.
I know about the baby.
I don't know, Ellie.
I'm really scared.
I don't think
Jimmy wants to get married.
[Crying]
What am I gonna do?
Don't cry, Tina.
Girls have babies without
getting married... sometimes.
I can't.
My parents
would kill me.
I'll get kicked out
of school.
[Crying]
I think I would rather die.
Well...
there's other ways.
I knew this girl who got
pregnant in high school.
She got it...
taken care of.
Even if I wanted
to do that,
it takes money,
and I don't have any.
What aboutJimmy?
Won't he help?
[Sighs] No.
He's on full scholarship.
He works two jobs
just to buy books.
He doesn't have a cent.
I heard about this place...
- In Mexico.
- Where?
Tijuana.
It's cheaper, and it's not
that far from here.
I'm... dying
to ask you this, Tina.
What?
What was it like?
The first time?
What do you mean?
I only did it once.
Yeah, right.
No, really.
I only did it once.
Where'd you do it?
On the beach.
You're kidding!
- Did it hurt?
- No.
It was great.
But the sand gets...
into everything.
[Giggles]
[Sound Of Ocean Waves
Breaking On Sand]
The happiest times at this sorority
have been since Sabrina arrived.
She is the most supportive and selfless
big sister I could ever have hoped for.
[Door Opens]
Hi. I'm sorry I'm late.
Mort's car broke down.
Okay.
What did I miss?
- Ellie was saying something.
- Oh, good. The floor recognizes Ellie.
I was just saying that...
I thought maybe it would be good...
if maybe, ah, Sabrina
was nominated for president too.
That's so sweet, Ellie.
I had no idea you were going to nominate
me to run against Rita. I'm honored.
I don't think that
that's such a good idea.
I mean, Sabrina
hasn't been here very long.
It doesn't matter how long
somebody's been a sister.
[Girl Mumbles]
That's right, you know.
Is there any other sister that
would like to second this nomination?
I second it.
Sabrina...
would make a great president.
[Tina]
Don't you think?
[Rita]
Fine.
I don't mind the competition.
I accept Sabrina's nomination
for presidency of this sorority.
[Excited Chatting]
Good work.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Sabrina dear, according
to the sorority charter,
you must maintain a " B" average
in all classes in order to be president.
[Mrs. Billings] So you better do
something about those French grades.
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, Prof. Leland, I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm, I'm fine.
A-Are you all right?
Yeah. I think
I just sprained my ankle.
- Oh.
- Oh, ah, yes. Uh, here.
Ow! Oh, I'm
so clumsy sometimes.
No, no, it's, uh,
it's my fault.
I, uh, I never I-look
where I'm going.
Oh, well. Oh!
I think I need to sit down.
Y-Yes. My office is...
is right down here.
- Oh, I'm really terribly sorry.
- [Groaning]
Okay. Ow. Careful.
Oh, I'm sorry.
There.
I'll... go get some ice
from the, uh, teacher's lounge.
Oh, thank you, Prof. Leland.
You're so kind.
Oh, uh, uh,
it's nothing.
Oh, ah...
Here.
Ice.
Shoot!
What,
no French poodle?
[Snickers]
[Door Opens]
Oh, y-you poor thing.
I feel terrible
about this. There.
Oh, that's very...
very good.
- It feels... better?
- Yes.
Professor, I wanted to apologize
for what happened in class.
- Well.
- I guess I was just showing off.
I just wanted the kids
to like me.
And I'm very,
very, very sorry.
- [Crying]
- Oh, no, no, no.
Of course,
of course I understand.
Why, uh,
actually you show...
a good deal of promise,
Sabrina.
I'm sure with a little work,
you'll do magnifique in French.
I love when you speak French.
[Sighs]
Oh, do you really
think so?
Oui, mademoiselle.
Oh!
Oh, Professor,
could you move the ice a bit?
- Yes. Oui.
- Yes.
- Yes, like that. Maybe a little higher.
- Higher.
Yes!
Just a little slower.
- Slower.
- Yes, like that.
Oh, that's very good.
Oh, Professor,
it's very hot.
[Sighs]
- Are you hot, Professor?
- Oh.
[Moans]
Oui.
- Oui.
- Ahh.
Oh!
Oh, Professor!
Yes.
- Sa-Sabrina!
- Yes?
- Ferme la porte.
- Oh, oui.
Professor?
[Snickers]
Well, well, well!
I guess we won't be having
any more problems in French class now.
Will we?
[Snickers]
Au revoir.
Hmm.
[Girls Chatting]
[Chatting Continues]
**["Every Night"]
* Oh, every night
Oh, every night *
Hi, Tina.
- Hi, Rita.
- Hi.
- Hi, Mort.
- Hi. What can I get for ya?
- A beer, please.
- Very good.
- I thought you were studying tonight.
- Oh, I was... but my mother called.
She felt so bad about what happened
at the pool, she wanted to apologize.
She's actually sending me
a check...
to buy a fancy dress
for the mother-daughter tea next week.
Is your mother coming?
You know, Rita, I still
haven't met your mother.
She wouldn't miss the tea,
would she?
- Excuse me.
- [Mort] Rita?
Rita!
- What happened to her?
- She saw a ghost.
[Music, Chatter, Laughter]
What do you want,
Sabrina?
I want you to pull out of
the race for sorority president.
That's ridiculous.
Why would I do that?
Otherwise, everyone
will find out about your mother.
Wh-What about my mother?
I guess she won't be able
to make the tea...
unless they let her out of jail
for a day.
What are you... What
are you talking about?
Oh, please, Rita.
Don't try to deny it.
Your mother is
a convicted felon.
- It wasn't her fault.
- That's not what the jury thought.
Wait till Mort finds out.
Well, no one can blame him
for dumping you.
I mean, your mother
is a jailbird.
A lot of people will feel differently
about you when they find out.
Well?
I will not let you
blackmail me, Sabrina.
- Fine. Mort!
- Wait.
[Sighs]
Okay... I'll do it.
Just give me some time
to back out gracefully.
[Music, Chatter]
Mother?
Hello, Sabrina.
What a surprise!
Skipping classes? James.
Why didn't you call?
Well, I have an announcement,
and I wanted to tell you in person.
Well, hurry up, dear.
I'm running late.
Mother, I'm going to be
sorority president.
Really?
Well, that's very nice.
- Just likeJulia.
- I'm very proud of you.
- And what about your French grades?
- Oh, not a problem.
I've been working on it, and the
professor and I have an understanding.
That is wonderful news.
Where are you going?
I'm meeting your father
at the airport.
An impromptu business trip to London.
Ten days at the Savoy.
It didn't sound too bad.
Oh, look at the time.
But what about
the mother-daughter tea next week?
They'll announce
the sorority president then.
I'm so sorry, Sabrina.
I'm not going to be able to make it.
But I told everybody
you were gonna be there.
Well, I said I was sorry.
I'll make it up to you.
Listen, I'm late, and you know
your father hates to be kept waiting.
Have a safe drive
back to school.
Mother...
**[Soft Rock]
**
Hi, Mort.
- Hi, Sabrina.
- Have you seen Joe?
No.
You're early.
Can I get you something?
Well, I could use a friend.
I don't think you make that
an easy job, do you?
How 'bout a soda?
I think you'll find that if you're
nice to people, they'll be nice back.
Like Rita.
- Yeah, she's an angel.
- [Trey] Hey, Mort!
Five beers.
- Sabrina, you want to join us?
- In a minute.
So where is Rita anyway?
She's gone home
to visit her mother.
Really?
They allow visitors there?
What? What are you
talking about?
- Gosh, I thought everyone knew.
- Knew what?
Rita's mom's in jail.
Murder, I believe.
You're crazy.
Don't say things
like that.
It's true. Rita's mom mowed
a man down with her car.
What's the matter
with you?
Don't you have any feelings,
any loyalty? She's your roommate.
- Yeah, and her mom's a murderer.
- Shut up, Sabrina.
What about you? You almost mowed
a family down on the lake.
They don't give you
ten to fifteen for that.
Yeah. Come on, gang.
There's a nice table outside.
And you wonder why
you don't have any friends.
[Sighs]
Sorry.
[Radio]
*Baby, I miss you *
*I long to kiss you *
- **[Continues]
- Hi.
- [Door Closes]
- Oh, hi.
- How are your folks?
- Fine.
They're fine.
What gives? I thought you
were gonna stay the night?
Yeah, well, I decided
to come home early.
Did something happen
at home, Tina?
I didn't go home.
So, where did you go,
then?
Tijuana.
[Tina Sobbing]
Oh.
- [Sobbing Continues]
- Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Please, sit down.
Oh, Ellie.
- I couldn't go through with it.
- Ooh.
I was fine on the bus
all the way down there.
When I walked
into the clinic...
I was so scared that I just ran
all the way back to the bus station.
Oh, I don't blame you,
Tina.
I wouldn't have had the nerve
to go to Tijuana for,
you know.
[Sobbing]
What am I gonna do?
We'll think
of something.
Maybe... you should ask
Sabrina for some help.
No. I can't tell
anyone else.
Sabrina doesn't know
about the baby, does she?
No.
Of course not.
I wouldn't tell anyone
a thing like that.
You're my best friend.
[Rita] I wanted to tell you about my
mother. I didn't know how you'd react.
- I was too ashamed.
- [Mort] You don't have to be ashamed.
- It doesn't change my feelings for you.
- Sabrina pretends to like me,
and when
I turn my back...
You could have told me. I wouldn't have
cared, and neither would anybody else.
- She's so mean.
- It doesn't matter.
The gang laughed at Sabrina when she
walked in and made her announcement.
- Really?
- Sure!
Oh, I wish I could've
seen her face!
It's, uh...
[Mort] It's kind of warm
tonight, isn't it?
Mmm.
Oh, Rita.
Rita.
[Rita]
Mort, stop.
I mean it, Mort!
Stop.
[Sighs] Rita,
I can't take this anymore.
- I'm sorry. It's just that I'm not...
- I know.
You're not that kind of girl.
I've heard it before.
- I should go inside.
- Fine.
- I'll see you tomorrow?
- Yeah. Good night, Rita.
[Sighs]
[Car Door Closes,
Engine Revs]
[Car Pulls Away]
Is it closing time,
or can a girl still get a beer?
[Clears Throat]
Make it a quick one.
Hmm. It's warm tonight,
isn't it?
- Drink up. It's late.
- Hmm.
We have all the time
in the world, Mort.
What are you up to, Sabrina?
What's going on in that mind of yours?
- Hmm. I like you, Mort.
- **["For Your Love"OnJukebox]
- Do you like me?
- *For your love *
- Why do you do those things to Rita?
- * Oh, I *
- Because of you, Mort.
- * Would do anything *
I want you.
- *I would do anything *
- I guess I get a little jealous.
- I'm flattered.
- *For your love *
Dance with me.
I can't do that,
Sabrina.
- *For your kiss *
- Tell me you're not that kind of boy.
* Oh, I would go
anywhere *
I want you.
- *I would go anywhere *
- All the way.
*For your kiss *
*More foolish *
*I grow *
* With each heartbeat *
*But we all
get foolish *
* That's why I repeat *
*For your love *
* Oh, I would do
anything *
*I would do
[Moaning]
*For your kiss **
Mmm.
- Going somewhere?
- What's it to you?
- Mort and I are going for a bike ride.
- [Laughs]
I doubt that.
He had a pretty late night
last night.
- How would you know?
- I was with him...
till very, very late.
- I don't believe you.
- It's true, Rita.
You know, you don't know
what you're missing.
Mort is
a fabulous lover.
Shut up!
I fucked
his brains out.
- [Car Horn Honks]
- You're a liar.
Why are you so upset?
You know it's true.
Go ask him yourself.
Is it true?
It can't be!
- Rita, what are you talking about?
- Is it true?
Sabrina said that...
Sabrina said that you...
- It isn't true, is it?
- [Sabrina] Is it true, Mort?
Tell her.
Rita, I'm sorry.
- [Crying]
- I hope you can forgive me.
Rita, I'm sorry!
Rita!
[Door Slams Shut]
Well, I...
I guess you're free today.
You wanna do something?
You are the biggest mistake
of my life.
- You'll be sorry, Mort.
- [Car Door Closes, Engine Revs]
[Car Screeches Away]
Real sorry.
I'll kill you, man!
I'll kill you!
Joe, what the hell's goin'on?
What did I do? I didn't do anything!
- You fucked Sabrina, man!
- What?
She said she couldn't even stop you,
man. That's my girl!
C'mon! C'mon!
C'mon!
Agh!
[Coughing]
- Goddamn it! She threw herself at me!
- Liar!
[Coughing]
[Gasping,
Coughing]
[Gasping]
I'm tellin' you,
she's bad news, Joe.
This girl hurts
everything she touches.
No, Mort. She wouldn't lie to me, Mort.
She wouldn't lie to me.
[Gasping]
Joe, I'm sorry.
I did not rape her.
I...
I love Rita.
- I'm sorry.
- [Panting]
Shit!
Hi, Tina.
Hi.
I haven't seen Jimmy
around lately.
What?
What are you
talking about?
Come on, Tina.
I heard you and Jimmy
talking.
But it's okay.
Your secret's safe with me.
Have you told
your parents?
[Crying]
No.
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
I know a doctor.
Oh. I tried
the Mexico thing.
It was a nightmare.
No.
He's a real doctor.
He's a friend of
my parents, but...
Well, he's expensive.
Do you have any money?
No.
I'd lend you money,
Tina, but...
my allowance
was cut off.
Oh, Sabrina,
I'm so scared.
I'll help you.
But you're gonna have to do exactly
what I say. Do you understand?
Yes. Anything.
Just, what should I do?
You say that Mort
is the father of your baby.
Why Mort?
Well, he saved all that money
for medical school.
- But he's not the father.
- Who cares?
[Door Closes]
I gotta go.
Oh, hello, Rita.
Forget something?
I have nothing
to say to you.
Please, Rita.
I did you a favor.
Mort's not the kind of guy
you think he is.
No, he isn't,
thanks to you.
It's not just me.
What about Mort and Tina?
Tina? Ha.
She's his waitress.
And what do you think
those two do after closing time?
Wash glasses?
You are despicable.
Have you no limits?
Wake up, Rita!
Tina's pregnant,
and guess who the father is?
[Siren Wailing
In The Distance]
It would be in the best interest
of the college and the sorority...
if you left school
immediately.
- But it wasn't my fault.
- It doesn't matter.
We simply cannot have
a pregnant girl on campus.
It sets a bad example
for the other students,
and we'll lose donations
from the alumni.
I've spoken with your parents.
They completely agree with me.
You can't imagine
how disappointed they are, Tina.
[Sobbing]
[Sabrina]
Tina, no!
Tina, no, no, no, no!
Don't worry, Tina.
- No, it's not worth it.
- Leave me alone! Leave me alone!
- Tina, stop it! Tina, no! Tina!
- Leave me alone!
- Leave me alone! [Sobbing]
- Tina, no. [Gasping]
No!
Nothing will ever be
the same again.
I can't stay here,
and I can't go home.
Well, we can move to a new town and
start a new life. I could go with you.
[Sobbing] But where are we
gonna get the money?
I told you...
Mort.
[Dog Barking]
[Knock On Door]
- Hi, Tina.
- Hi.
I was expecting you.
Come on in.
- Why don't you come sit over here?
- Okay.
I just... hope
this won't take long.
- I really have to pack.
- No. This won't take long at all.
Do you have the money?
Tina, why are you
doing this to me?
I'm not doing
anything to you.
You're the father
of my baby.
Tina,
I never kissed you.
I never touched you.
I never even thought about it.
I've gotta go.
Just give me the money.
Tina, I trusted you,
and I was your friend.
Now, I'm gonna give you
the money anyway, okay?
All you have to do
is tell me the truth.
Now, that's Jimmy's baby,
right?
Tina, it's okay.
You can tell me.
And you know what?
I'm...
You can just think of this money
as a loan, and just take it.
- It is Jimmy's baby.
- [Sighs]
I was alone.
I was scared.
Sabrina made me blame you.
I'm...
I'm sorry, Mort.
It's okay.
You can go.
It's all right.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Bye.
- Nice job.
- * Ooh, baby, you treat me so good *
* Crazy 'bout your charm *
* You love me
like a good girl should *
*And when I'm in your arms
you make me snap crackle and pop *
- *Snap, crackle and pop *
- Hi.
*Hey honey, Ooh baby
Don't stop *
- *I like the way you hug and squeeze *
- Hi.
*And every kiss is sweet *
*Don't ever leave me
Please, please, please *
*But when I tell you it's me
you make me snap crackle and pop *
*Snap, crackle and pop
Snap, crackle and pop *
- Hey, thanks for voting for me.
- *Hey honey, Ooh baby, don't stop *
**
Rita, I...
need to tell you something.
- What is it, Ellie?
- Uh, mmm...
[Loud Chatting,
Laughing]
I think...
Tina is lying.
I know she is.
It's Jimmy's baby,
not Mort's.
*Snap, crackle and pop *
*Hey honey, Ooh baby
Don't stop *
*I like the way you hug and squeeze
and every kiss is sweet *
*Don't ever leave me
Please, please, please *
*But when I tell you it's me
you make me snap crackle and pop *
*Snap, crackle and pop *
*Hey honey, Ooh baby
Don't stop *
**
- Hi.
- How's the rally goin'?
- Good. Good.
I think everyone's
havin' fun.
*But when I feel your touch
you make me snap crackle and pop *
- We need to talk.
- Yeah, I'm glad you came.
There's something I want
you to hear inside.
*Hey honey, Ooh baby
Don't stop *
* When you press
your lips to mine *
* Chills run up and down
my spine **
[Crying]
[Knock On Door]
Tina, dear,
there's someone out front
to see you.
I don't wanna see anyone.
I don't want any good-byes.
No, no, no.
This is different, dear.
Come on.
Go ahead.
Tina.
You look beautiful.
I've missed you
so much.
You're the one who left
without saying good-bye.
I'm sorry.
I had to get away and think.
I had to be alone.
I've been kicked out
of school.
I know.
Why did you come back,
Jimmy?
I came back
for you, Tina.
What do you mean?
[Sighing]
Tina...
will you marry me?
Oh, what I did to Mort.
It was so horrible.
[Tina On Tape Recorder]
Do you have the money?
[Mort] Tina, why are you
doing this to me?
[Tina] I'm not doing
anything to you.
You're the father
of my baby.
I've gotta go.
Just give me the money.
[Mort On Tape Recorder] Tina,
I trusted you, and I was your friend.
Now, I'm gonna give you
the money anyway, okay?
All you have to do
is tell me the truth.
Now, that's Jimmy's baby,
right?
[Tina On Tape Recorder]
I was scared.
Sabrina made me
blame you.
- It is Jimmy's baby.
- [Tape Recorder Clicks Off]
[Rita] You slept with Sabrina,
though, didn't you?
[Mort] It was a mistake.
It didn't mean anything.
[Door Squeaks]
Ooh!
[Sabrina]
That'll teach you!
- You killed him!
- Stupid bitch! I'll take care of you!
No! No!
Get off me!
[Screaming]
Get off of me!
Get off!
- Oh, Sabrina!
- Oh! Tina! Jimmy!
The bar's on fire. I'm, I'm gonna
go get the fire department.
- Where's Mort?
- I, I don't know! I haven't seen him.
[Tina] Well, his car's
in the parking lot.
[Rita, Muffled Voice]
Help!
- Jimmy, no!
- There's somebody in there!
- I don't hear anything. Don't go in!
- You don't hear that?
- No.
- I gotta go in.
- [Sabrina] Wait, Jimmy! No!
- Jimmy, no!
[Rita]
Help!
- [Yelling]
- What's goin' on?
Is somebody in there?
- [Gasping] Jimmy. Jimmy, no!
- [Jimmy] Mort! Mort!
[Crashing]
- Jimmy!
- No, Tina. Don't go in there!
- No!
- What happened?
- Jimmy's in there. Go get help.
- Rita and Mort.
I saw them go in!
- Sabrina, what happened?
- How should I know?
I saw you follow Rita.
[Jimmy Coughing]
[Rita]
Help!
[Grunting]
- [Explosion]
- [Screaming]
[Man] Get back, Jerry!
Get back! Get back!
Jimmy? Jimmy!
Jimmy!
- Jimmy! No! No!
- Tina!
[Crying]
[No Audible Dialogue]
** [Soundtrack Music Plays
Over Following Scenes]
**
**["I'm Gonna Be
A Wheel Someday"]
**
*I'm gonna be
a wheel someday *
*I'm gonna be somebody *
*I'm gonna be
a real gone cat *
* Then I won't want you *
*And everything's
gonna go my way *
*I won't need nobody *
*I'm gonna be
a real gone cat *
* Then I won't want you *
* Well, you can cry-y-y *
* 'Til you are
high, high, high *
*lf you are wonderin' why I don't look
at you when I go rollin'by *
* Well, I'm gonna be
a wheel someday *
*I'm gonna be somebody *
*I'm gonna be
a real gone cat *
* Then I won't want you *
**
* Well, I'm gonna be
a wheel someday *
*I'm gonna be somebody *
*I'm gonna be
a real gone cat *
* Then I won't want you *
*And everything's
gonna go my way *
*I won't need nobody *
*I'm gonna be
a real gone cat *
* Then I won't want you *
* Well, you can cry-y-y *
* 'Til you are
high, high, high *
*lf you are wonderin' why I don't look
at you when I go rollin'by *
* Well, I'm gonna be
a wheel someday *
*I'm gonna be somebody *
*I'm gonna be
a real gone cat *
* Then I won't want you *
*No, I won't want you *
**
*I'm gonna be a wheel *
* 'Cause I won't be a nobody *
*Everything's gonna go *
*My way *
* Gonna go my way *
*It's gonna go my way *
* You can cry
Cry *
* Cry, cry *
* Oh, me **
**