5 competitors for "Reality Show", being 6 months in one marry. If
somebody to leave, everybody loses.
You he is the perfect competitor?
Click to enter.
Oh. I am Emma...
... and I have 33 years and...
I want to enter in the house.
Oi. I am the Matt.
Oi, my name are Dany.
Charlie, só Charlie.
Rex.
- I would like to be in the show because... - ñ ÿ ¿1 I want to be
famous!
price continue 1 million of dollar,
certain?
- the challenge... - ñ ÿ ¿1 For the experience, I find...
grow as person, that besteira.
- Because you he would have to choose me? - He would have to choose me
because...
I am one cursed popular person.
- Because it would have to choose me... - Because I am a team player.
What I find on the rules...
What, touch to collect to the night?
If house are in the way it
nothing...
... which would be the reason to break
the touch to collect, in any way?
Ficar inside of house, without being
able to sleep during the day go to be a difficult thing.
Good, normally I not taste of rules,
but, you know, these you do not bother me.
I find that I can follow the rules for a
dollar million.
I, only sees. I find that we are being
observed.
Acorde!
Good day.
Are certain that it does not have
interesting things on you.
- Vocês always wastes food. - I feel lack of cool food.
You go to eat this?
Vá in front.
Sabe of that I feel lack?
Of the ocean.
Sinto harmony lack. For the social work
and harmony, if it is attending this...
... I am with homesicknesses.
- I feel lack of the purchases...
Sabe that when we will sairmos, nor we
go in remembering them yesterday.
and then we go to have much money pra to
buy new things.
This there.
Of that it feels Emma lack?
intelligent Colloquies.
What she wants to say, sister?
Sinto lack of my grandfather.
Oh! Vovô!
Already I had my vacations. Badly I can
wait pra to come back.
I never obtain to sleep here right.
worse one of everything is the
animal cursed ones is there.
and howl of coiote?
Are always one cursed coiote.
Odeio this house. Frightful fodidos
idiots.
- he is seeing some thing? - Not, nothing abnormal.
- It is one gracinha. - Then?
Then?
Then I prefer that my close moments are
close moments.
are not a site pornô.
You could make underneath of the cover,
or inside of freezer...
I do not know. He has some thing... It
is so intense the time all.
Oh, yes Are one face that is in the bone
has 6 months almost...
... it with one is cursed accumulated
tesão.
Ok, we go to give one looked at.
Are definitively cold in the house.
Nobody brought the low lantern here pra,
né?
What I make with...
Poor fellows, this deliberately were
jammed, see this.
Everything have that to have an angle
pra you. It cannot only have broken?
Then what we will make?
- I do not know. - We go to make a fire.
But do not have dry wood are there.
Not, but have an excrement mount in the
attic. We could only choose what to use.
To the work, youngsters.
Oh, God. It is with I smell here of
piss.
Parece that the mother and the papa
liked to leave the children in the attic.
Who would make this?
You would have to speak with my adoptive
father.
Always wanted one that spoke.
- Oh, Emma
- Yes Matt?
Emma, Matt, Emma, Matt...
Matt, wait! Matt waits! What? What?
This are mine bunda! I know, Emma, I I
know.
Coopere, Rex.
and do not come with this besteira of
face bonzinho. It does not want to trepar?
do not come with this thing of being
bonzinho.
Oh, Matt, you do not have wood!
Because you do not have... You do not
have wood!
Gosta to speak of small woods?
Pare of speaking on the Emma.
What it is looking for?
Would be the first day of the remaining
portion of its life as a not-smoker.
Not!
Jesus, I never heard as much cursed
animal.
Acha that they have a ribbon there is?
Then, what they find, when we will come
back...
... we go to take all or not?
- We will have that in hiding them. - We will have persecutors.
Sabem which the biggest cause of
persecutors? The esquecimento.
Esquecimento!
the people forgets to close its
curtains.
Its curtains!
Li on this woman, who costumava to walk
inside of its house...
... bare one, of lighted light. Curtains
all opening.
It always forgot to close them because
it gave direct for a forest.
Nobody is, certain there?
But had...
... this persecuting face, only looked at
it to pass every day for the windows.
It started to think that it did not
close because she wanted to be seen...
... that it was inviting it it to enter.
Then it started to imagine everything as
a relationship with it.
Criou a small fancy when it was hanging
its clothes...
... found that a love message, an
offering.
Then, steal its panty, what itensifica
more and plus all its theory of the love.
Finally it force the entrance.
When it finds it, find a stranger.
It finds it stranger because it is
terrified and orders it pra is of the house.
It finds that it only is only if making
of difficult of new. Then it decides to act...
... raping and strangling to hinder it to
cry out.
- Obliged, Matt. -É, debtor.
good thing pra if to feel in this
game.
You already feel yourself thus in this
game, you only look at...
... alô, alô, alô.
In the cameras are a thing, are of my
window are another one.
Vocês do not have that to be worried.
Estatisticamente strange does not go
behind strangers.
Are much more easy to be died for that
you know.
boy, when I was in the school, killed
its parents.
serious Fala. What it happened there?
It used a hammer. It beat in them until
the death.
Jesus!
- That tragedy. - Who age it? You it knew it?
I cannot really remember to me, I
changed myself before this happening.
Which age the name of it?
Excrement!
Are calmed, are alone the wind.
- What it is this? - I do not know.
-Matt? Matt? Oh! Jesus!
-Desculpe.
Dany, have somebody up there. In the
attic.
Are certain?
- I have. - All good.
Vamos there.
are come there from above.
All good.
It only is with fear.
"Crows can bring, the death when they
arrive, entering in its house, flying in its bunda".
Acho that if hurt. It holds.
I caught it. I caught it. He is with a
broken wing.
Age the thing gentile pra if to make.
Vou to take it pra there low.
What devils vocês are making here in
top?
- We had a visitor. - What?
If despaired because he was imprisoned.
Are, I can see. This fodida house.
Ei people, our package.
Good Notice, Dany.
Cigarettes please!
- Bricks. - Bricks.
- and a letter.
- This is not funny. We need suppliments.
we are ferrados.
Are for you.
- Who ordered a letter to you? - What it is, face?
Dany? Ei!
Then, the letter said that daqui the two
days, the o grandfather of it goes to have its funeral.
- Funeral? - Yes.
Then, obviously, it goes to want to go
even so and to break the rules.
we cannot stop it if it will want to go.
Not.
We go to have that to convince it that
its interest is better to be here, certain?
Better interest of it?
We nor know if this letter is real or
not, certain?
Alone mind pie would think this.
Yes and they are pies, want to say, what
it is this? Bricks instead of food?
do not find that this is part of the
game of them?
Jesus Christ!
You could construct a more frightful
house?
is fodendo with people, certain, wants
to say...
... first one, in does not order food to
them. Now this.
do not find that it can be part of the
game? Dany goes to want to leave,
they wants in separating them.
- Ah, we go. - Not, I thought on this. It thinks well on this.
We are to this distance to gain 1
million of dollar. We are to this distance.
They does not want in paying them, does
not want that we arrive there.
Or they wants to apimentar a
little for the viewers.
perhaps Or grandfather of it are
died.
Emma, if the grandfather of it is
deceased, feels very, does not have nothing that can make.
grandfather of it practically
created. You do not have no feeling?
Oh, stop with this excrement. I am here
for the money, ok?
and you also.
Expresse this as it will want,
exposition, censorship, to find itself same...
... I do not know, but the only person
who is not here for the money...
... are probably who need more, but not,
Dany is here for making friends.
Ok, excellent, we go to be friends of
the face. We go to give it some aid.
great period of practical aid.
We cannot hold the face against the
will.
Ok, we go to say it that we do not have
alternatives if it will be itself.
Emma, say it.
You say it.
Vamos Emma, you know that it likes you
more than. But it gentily has asked for.
It would make best.
We would have to leave to go it.
Have more important thing that money.
What, buceta?
Ei, face, go to foder itself! Family
does not mean nothing pra you?
You do not feel lack of that never she
had, face.
sick Puta.
Veja.
What? What devils...
Jesus...
Must have been one of the youngsters
sacaneando.
Not, Charlie...
... I find that she was another person. -
Who?
Sabe to that everything that I counted,
on the child who killed its parents?
name of it were John Riley.
It were not alone a boy of my school. It
liveed in my street.
Costumávamos you play to together to
after the lesson.
One of our favourite games were the game
of the panic...
... pra to see who obtained to scare more
the other.
and started, you know, jumping of high
trees and giving a scare, this type of things.
But then were more serious. John had a
good looking one...
... that it adored. It entered hidden in
the school in its knapsack.
One day, I changed the good looking one
for a brick.
and I played the knapsack of it in the
swimming pool of the school.
It were so scared that it mijou in the
pants.
In the front of everybody.
Disse it who the good looking one was
well.
It only gave that look to me.
Its dark look.
Never turn its coasts. Because one day,
I go to catch you therefore.
Because you if it did not relieve in the
game?
and it continued crying out. Sick its
puta.
First the bricks in the package and now
somebody write this?
This seem so personal, want to say,
because I am only being attacked?
Charlie...
... you do not find that perhaps...
They only finds that we are in this
house has time excessively...
... they is making of everything pra in
them to catch and people to give up...
As they would know everything this?
I do not know.
Research, I find.
Vamos to come back pra bed, ok?
Vamos. It goes to be all good.
Venha, give its hand to me.
Youngsters, package!
Espero that it has food of this time.
Oh, that dôce, champagne. They still in
love them.
-Ótimo. What devils... frightful -É, I find.
What?
I know what these sucking fodidos of
prick...
... I know what this means. Fodam.
Façam its research, ok, I am making
everything pra this being the best thing that happened with me. Fodam!
What?
Certainly they wants in making to give
up them.
Vamos there pra top.
They finds that they can foder now with
me?
father of it, certain?
Veio to verify me here?
are not façade, face, I are not only
imported.
I wanted to import myself, I do not
import myself.
funny one are that they had brought
my proper mechanism.
Are felt.
give that book to Me.
Quer to be worried about somebody, are
worried about the Bundy...
... I do not know if I feel penalty of it
or if I feel fear of it.
Because they had chosen you, Matt.
Which is the skeletons of its closet?
Good, I would have to speak now?
Dar they the ammunition pra to shoot in
me?
This were good. Yes, good.
But can wait that they already know.
Clearly, unless you it does not have
none.
You only are sliced as white bread.
Have somebody are there?
Emma?
You are well?
light of security had finished to
light.
I would swear that he has somebody in
the side of the forest.
Olha, you are only terrified.
Charlie in counted them what it had in
the last night.
Emma, you cannot think that this
everything has to see with...
With what?
Good, you know, when she was a girl...
Acho that this would be ridicule.
I know.
I do not want...
... to think on this.
- What he had?
- What he is this?
- Oh, excrement!
- This is some type of joke?
- You it placed this there?
- It goes to foder itself, Charlie.
Who made this fodida trick!
I did not place there. I did not place.
You heard some thing? It has people
walking in the house?
Everybody if calm. They are calmed,
please, per 2 seconds.
Emma, do not have nobody, ok here?
Youngsters, are the new, certain company
of? They are planning to foder with the game...
... then, please, is calmed.
- They are entering here inside, then?
- the game finished.
- I cannot support this.
- What it is making?
- I go to use the radio pra that they come to
search me.
Not, not! It is. Emma. It listens. Were
I, ok? I was.
Desculpe. It was a dull trick. It
forgives. It forgives.
What it thinks that is making? Which its
problem? Which its problem?
Ei, which its problem! How it makes this
with the people?
Parem with this! It is not functioning.
You are well?
I am here for the money.
Which are its excuse?
What? You do not have proper life? Is
not real sufficiently pra you?
Without family? What it is this?
I have penalty of you. You it said fuck.
I only wanted to say that exactly come
of you this really he was fodido.
Because you he would make this?
I did not place there, ok?
I did not place there, Charlie, I I only
said that I placed pra it not to go even so.
I want the money of the prize, certain,
I I did not go to leave to go it.
Oh, excrement!
Oh, God, do not make this. It does not
make this.
I continue finding that it is the
company, certain?
Are the company.
But as they would place here inside?
I do not know. They control all this
excrement, certain? She is what they make. It is part of the game of
them.
They wants to esquentar the things then
is this that they make.
and still I find, you I know,
perhaps...
... they is putos for not having had no
"action", or something thus.
Good, no union, in any way...
Acha that they are in punishing?
Yes, perhaps.
Or we are in punishing, we
understood?
- God, I wanted to have a cigarette!
- Ei, Charlie, wait one minute.
Charlie, Charlie, wait, wait.
Ok.
Quer a cigarette?
do not say that never I made nothing pra
you.
cigarette mallet, pra you.
Oh, my God.
What devils are this?
Its small bastard!
Charlie, wait.
Charlie, silence the mouth.
- Charlie.
- It goes to foder itself, its imbecile.
Vou expli...
Excellent one...
Because it caught cigarettes? It nor
smokes.
Pra to sacanear with me.
face are a snake. It probably would
change the grandmother for money.
It said that my grandfather is not died.
That this is false, are alone a part of
the game.
Acha that is truth?
Vocês have that to give a little, you
know to me?
You are an egoistic bastard.
Oh, go to foder itself.
Vá to foder itself. You she is so
self-centered, you is so presumptuous.
Quero to say, all this besteira of John
Riley, for the love of God, find that it gives to the minim pra now
you?
Jesus, you must give much value. You
must really give value.
- He stops with this, Rex.
- He goes to foder itself, Matt.
Because it does not go.
Sabe, if I was a psychopath...
... I would not be walking there I am.
I would have my hiding place here,
inside of this house.
Already arrive, Rex.
if are not deceptive, face. It is not
important.
Ei, psychopath!
are not an ackward one fodido, Rex
murderous Psychopath!
Rex.
Between. He is excellent here.
We have food, we have liquor, we have
women.
Pare!
One in particular one you must be
interested. We go!
Without sacanagem, have somebody are
there!
Excrement, we go for here!
Esperem. We go to be together.
Vamos, are close to the door pra to see
if you recognize it.
I do not know. I do not know. I do not
know. -É the John?
- They could open the door?
- I do not know.
- Not! He does not open.
- It is all good, is all good.
- its identity Shows to us.
- What?
Identification. It leaves to see us.
All good, I am Travis Patterson.
Pleasure in knowing them.
Ligue the light. It binds the light.
- Oh, can be counterfeited.
- Oh, we go there...
... seem that I have less than 21 years?
- Which is its sign?
- Cancer, and its?
- I am Twin.
- He saw there plus somebody it are?
Alone river. I swear, I do not have
nothing I am there. Not in these days.
Jesus, these batteries is finishing.
Leave to see me this.
- Some localizer?
-É.
Then you know where we are.
Yes You does not know?
Not.
I do not want to be coarse...
... but obviously vocês one very is
worried com.segurança.
But, who devils is vocês?
You do not recognize people?
- I would have?
- the USA InterNet?
Yes, the time all. I am a programmer.
- and it does not know who we we are?
- it forgives Me, you knows...
... I am tired. It is some type of trick?
We are one part "reality show" of the
InterNet. As a Big Brother.
Veja, have cameras in all the places,
even in the bathroom.
Was 247 people and in they had chosen
them.
Which age the name of the site?
-"Nós we are high".
-"Nós we are high"?
company decided to start to make
propagandas when we arrived here.
Good, had not made a good work because I
never heard on this.
- and I live online.
- Perhaps alive you in the wrong area.
You know, you are InterNet. World-wide
net.
- Well, many sites for there exist.
-É, is, has same...
... then because I would go to want to
attend vocês? What vocês they offer?
- It takes off the clothes.
- One keeps silent, idiot.
- I am the Charlie.
- Ei, Charlie, Travis, are an honor.
You are definitively certain of whom
never she saw me before?
Not, definitively would remember to me.
- Where we are?
- Here.
- Obliged.
- Which the scale of this map?
- In this map, which the scale?
-1 for 50 a thousand.
Putz, we are in the way it nothing.
Are same.
Which the city next?
Will Munich Tid.
- Where it is?
- It is...
... well for here.
Then, where is its esquis?
- In my pickup truck.
- Where it is its pickup truck?
Where I left it, I wait.
- Ei, somebody wants to dance?
- Yes.
You believe this history to be skiing
here alone?
I do not know.
I am being paranóico, but he
seems convenient very.
It was not nor a little constrangido
with the cameras.
Remember as we are quaint when in we
change them?
- Clearly.
- Ei, can pass this?
Espero that the Charlie knows with who
it is if putting.
Emma, you want to dance?
Not, Dany, debtor.
I go pra bed.
You want to dance?
- Idiotic. - Ok.
Quer to go pra there top?
I hate that face.
Abnormal person!
Mr. sire!
I said that I could eat it.
Ei are well clearly pra me.
God, the Charlie are not excellent?
It finds that we are idiotic.
Sabemos pra who you work.
Quero that it says the company that we
go to catch those 1 million of dollar.
I have that to go pra not to delay me.
Between garotão.
garotão already left the house.
Sugar?
Dany!
Vou to say a thing you and I want that
it listens with much attention
I very feel on everything what he
happened with you.
But are not excuse. Pra is not excuse
you to catch my things.
I cannot be friend of whom it makes
this, ok?
I did not catch nothing.
Dany, I found this in its room, ok?
- I did not catch!
- Dany!
Olha, people more do not go to be here
for much time, ok?
Then because we do not try to be
civilized, to be educated and be honest ones with the others, ok?
Matt, youngsters, comes here.
Delivery?
I found close to a tree. It is the
knapsack of the Travis.
Some track?
Not, did not have signals of the Travis.
No mark of footprint.
We have that to use the radio pra to ask
for aid.
- Aid pra who?
- Aid pro Travis.
Youngsters, are not real. It is not
real, is part of the game. They relax, please.
I do not know.
Have blood, it can be hurt.
- It is not hurt, Dany. Real estate
-É pra me, Rex.
are not wounded. If it is wounded, where
is the body?
Querem that people have asked for aid,
youngsters, are this who want, that people have asked for aid.
and if people to ask for, find that some
strap bonitão goes to come here until and giving to the minim pras
rules of the game
nly thing that obtains to think are
in the fodidas rules?
If we will call the straps, us we lose.
Are what they want. It is what they
want.
Oh, Christ, Excellent, Excellent.
Quer to know, if vocês had believed
this, speaks with them.
Fale with them. They go to help,
certain, speak with them.
- Somebody...
- Vocês capsizes what it happened here...
... knows where we are. They order aid.
Oh, yes. Travis, if this is its true
name...
... go to foder itself.
ou do not go to far frighten me pra of
my money. Ok, friend?
does not give it this pleasure,
youngsters, does not make this.
The more in we will worry them more go
to laugh at our face.
- Especially You, Charlie.
- What?
- Especially you.
- It goes to foder itself.
You know that everything to that was
scaffolding, certain?
You know of this. He is therefore that
it caught the target most easy.
uero to say, know that you do not fear
the cameras, certain?
Travis, Travis, Travis, where you are
now, its son of puta?
- Emma!
- Dany.
I did not catch its clothes.
Had been they. They are sacaneando with
people. It is part of the game.
- Dany, please, not... - I made this pra you.
- He catches. - Dany, I cannot catch this.
I made pra you.
Ok.
Charlie.
Of The Dany.
Oh, already I understood. He is its good
looking one.
- good looking Oi of the Emma...
- Not!
Ah, we go gives a time. It spent
hundreds of hours back in low...
... hitting with its negocinho. I want to
say... Emma! Emma!
- Good looking quaint of the Emma! Horrible -É.
Youngsters!
- Dany? Dany?
- Matt, not, not!
It is died. He is died.
- Oh, my God. - I cannot look at.
- All good.
- it is not all good. It is not all good.
do not have nothing well!
- What we go to make?
- We go to wait for the helicopter.
ame finished, certain? We cannot
continue now.
- and on...
- it is not our responsibility...
... are the cursed game of them.
Fizemos all certainty so far,
youngsters...
This are not our guilt. We did not make
nothing of wrong. We did not make nothing wrong here.
we cannot. We cannot leave it there.
We would not have to be passing
therefore.
I cannot believe.
Or we can take it pra it are there.
pra is There!
We not... What we have to lose?
Ok.
Vocês takes it there pra is while
people try to make contact with the radio.
Please.
Parece that is this. Alô? Somebody can
hear me?
Please. Somebody is died. Please, they
help.
- Please, we need aid.
- it does not have nobody there.
I cannot believe.
This have that to be outside of the
plans of them.
Naõ, are not are of the plans of them.
That type of fodido sick person if would
inscribe in this?
One minute. I had one cursed idea.
Sinto very for the things that are
happening with us.
All good.
Venha here.
- Emma, I...
- Youngsters, youngsters.
Youngsters, vocês have that to see
this, ok? Where it is the Charlie?
Charlie!
"Aréa without cameras". "1 person in
the maximum per 15 minutes".
Already had been asked as the company
plans in paying them?
Already had thought as they pay for this
house, food and for the cursed helicopter?
- Propagandas of the site.
- ñ ÿ ¿(Taxes of Registrations.
Certainty, you do not have one, if it
will not have the other, certain?
Quero to say, if nobody to enroll
itself, they will not have money.
and I was thinking, this face, the
Travis...
... it were one cursed programmer of the
InterNet.
It had to pass its cursed life in the
InterNet, then as it never had seen a fodida propaganda?
Have tons of excrement in the InterNet.
Are, certain.
- Therefore it wanted to enter in the InterNet.
- How it entered in
the InterNet?
This localizer have one link with the
satellite that functions.
- Where it learned this?
- Club of the computer.
Estive looking for for the site,
certain? I made a research...
... in all the sites of existing searches
that I could remember and I did not find nothing...
... I want to say, nothing exactly, not
even a propaganda.
- Nothing. Nor one cursed propaganda.
- the InterNet is a great place.
Are a great place, but I want to know
because it is being so difficult to find a site...
... I want to say, if they want that the
people visit the site, because she would be so difficult?
Good, I found, I was difficult pra
devil, but I found.
Are, but it is fodido, wants to say,
does not have a name...
... are one cursed type of site base.
Are a trip of hackers. It is as a code
made for one cursed group of hackers
- What it means a site base?
- a site base is one...
... are as a password, one bagunça
fodida of letters and numbers in time of the real name.
It is fodido!
ejam alone!
- This is our site?
- I do not know.
Quero to say, I do not know. I am trying
to inscribe me, but I am using...
... credit card of the Travis, but do
not have credit for 50 a thousand dollars.
- How it knows that he is 50 a thousand?
- I learned many things in
the Club of the Computer.
I can ask pra that?
Are, but without the 50 a thousand
dollars, we will not arrive at the fodida password of the site.
- I do not understand.
- I also do not understand.
I also do not understand. This place
does not have a fodida propaganda.
It nor has a real address.
Then, I cannot understand. The only
thing that I can imagine is that they do not want to call the
attention.
But because this? E the security,
excrement, the security...
... are insane. Already I passed all the
archives of hacker that I have in this thing...
... and we are speaking of serious
decoders of passwords.
and I continue not obtaining to pass for
the password.
Then which its point of view, Rex?
My point of view...
... my simple point of view are why
devils somebody would pay to as much money pra in seeing them?
I want to know if this fodida thing is
regularized. This excrement is legal?
As a site pornô?
re, as a site pornô, but except for
it, we did not make nothing pra this to seem a fodido site pornô.
Then what it is? What?
I am the only person who thinks for
here?
Quero to say, I am the only person. He
is only clearly pra me?
Nobody heard to speak before of a film
of real murder...
... I want to say, Dany already is
died...
... are alone to join the things. - Not,
Dany if killed!
As we can be certain?
- Jesus!
- Not, Matt, then explains this to me...
... because this seems fodido very pra me
now.
Quero to say, I am missed? This me seems
fodido!
What devils?
What they mean the colors of each one?
- Died or not.
- Oh, my God!
Are one cursed died or not!
That rendered unhappy.
Its poor fellows.
Relax. I go to try to order email for
somebody. We go, its poor fellows. They had cut to me!
- We have that to leave daqui.
- She waits, Rex, she calms myself.
- She calms myself!
- You do not understand, they you are malucos...
- He calms myself, calms myself!
... they had killed Dany and now they
go in killing them!
Relax. This is not a site of murder.
Vamos, thinks about this, wants to say,
who they goes to kill? We four?
Because not to continue saying that this
is one of the games of them?
Are everything what this is. It is only
another game.
Is only fodendo with people.
Vamos. We are very nervous. Tomorrow
people go even so...
Tomorrow? E what we will make this
night?
Olha, vocês does not need to be worried
about this.
Vou to catch the weapon and to be of
morning guard even.
is playing.
Are dark are there. I cannot see
nothing.
alarm of security go to go off will
have somebody are there.
- What it is looking for, Rex?
- I am trying...
... are for here in some place.
- What? - We go, son of puta!
Bingo! The beeper of emergency of the
Travis.
We can prepare it.
Are, but we have that to go pra there it
are to go off it.
I know.
Could go off it of the roof.
Ok. I do not only want to have that to
go there it are alone.
Çíà÷è.. .
I go with you.
Ok.
if do not worry. If it does not worry,
this goes to function...
... this go to function and somebody goes
to see it...
... and somebody go to call the policy.
Who? Some good citizen?
They exists, Emma. We know one.
You would have to be with this. It is
the knife of the Dany.
- Dany, I never gave to a possibility it.
- It did not have a
possibility, Emma...
... they had not wanted that it had a
possibility, ok?
They?
Emma, this are not on its past.
They only wants that you it thinks this.
Then because they had chosen me?
In the first light of the day, people go
even so, together, ok?
and they who if fodam with the money of
them.
perhaps When I to leave daqui I can make
another attempt.
You know, I you were really with hope of
this being a success.
Are in the noble schedule now.
You find?
do not have choice. She is always hourly
nobleman in some place.
Great auditorium.
Sabe to be same you in front to the
cameras?
relaxed Ficar?
After the problem?
Acho that...
... I do not feel myself relaxed very
now.
Venha until here.
Vou to help you to relax.
Oh, yes, I can feel it.
Are as a great knot.
Chegue pra front.
You have everything. Because he decided
to enter in this?
Curiosity.
- To see what it is to feel.
- What, to be isolated?
- the fear. - the fear?
Yes Are gostoso.
I must kill it now?
You want to attend this, right?
Were all good?
Excrement.
Matt?
Youngsters?
"Alô? It lights the light "
"are There. We go."
"In the start I found that everything
went to be equal."
"Type, nothing really happened."
"I wanted that everything I was alone a
nightmare."
"Good, I was missed."
"Oh, not. It not."
"Emma do not have no possibility."
It is here. It came in searching them.
We go to leave daqui, we go.
Vá, go, go.
You saw it?
It caught the Charlie.
Charlie! E the Rex?
- Matt! - we are taking care of of you now.
- What it is making? - we Are two now.
- the door... - We have that to be together.
Emma, we have that to be together.
- it is hearing? It is there is. - What he is...
- John? - Not!
- John, is there is! - Not, Matt, not!
Because you are lighting the light?
Because I want that they see what I go
to make with you.
All that excrement on the John Riley in
its daily one...
You really believe that you she set in
motion psychosis of it?
After all this time, it escape of the
frozen land of wastefulness...
... pra if to only avenge of you.
Rex were certain. It is a great
fodido ego, Emma.
Vá for the bed. It goes for the bed,
Emma.
fodida Piranha!
- it helps Me! Aid! It is there inside!
- He calms myself! What he is
having?
- He goes to have that to calm itself.
- Not!
Quero that if it calms and it is here,
inside of the car.
- I go to take care of of this, not if it worries. - It killed
everybody.
Were you who went off the beeper? It
was? Yes?
- and it has somebody there inside? - Yes.
- and it is armed? - Yes, an axe.
- Ok, I go to verify. - it does not leave me!
calm, young Fique, already I will be in
return, ok?
Car 157 requesting reinforcement.
Have that to leave me to make this. I
was in this house for 6 fodidos months.
What devils forgot to make for last the
6 months?
give the cursed keys to me, Matt.
What you go to make? To direct?
I can make.
... cursed keys!
Hour to celebrate!
- For the company. - Company.
- It finds that they had been satisfied?
- You, probably go to be
promoted.
- He finds exactly? - Yes, they are in the parking.
- Parking? - Who thinks that we are?
Acha that we have an office, business
card or folder?
do not exist "they", Matt. "they" we
are.
I, very rich Travis and some
customers.
Low costs, maximum advantage.
productive Good.
Good, have always much people of low
income ready pra to go pra sepulture.
Always 5 idiots.
Quer to say, 4?
It is durona well.
- It is seeing this, Travis?
- Yes, he is excellent daqui.
It leaves you see me.