Kevin Smith directed and acted
in his New Jersey Chronicles:
Clerks, Mallrats,
Chasing Amy, Dogma...
...and the final chapter,
Jay and Silent Bob Strike Back.
Smith presents his own lens through
which we may view the world.
And although it's not
always rose-colored...
...we learn a new way
to examine spirituality...
...sexuality and human relationships.
Give it up for Kevin Smith!
Are there signs that say "applause"?
'Cause I don't think I've ever
gotten a reaction like that.
Reaction like that makes up for every
chick ever said I had a small dick.
We'll just sit here until you're quiet
and then make up the time afterwards.
Are we starting on this side?
Is that why the camera's in his face?
- First one of the night, dude.
- First question: What's a Nubian?
No, I'm just...
I'm kidding.
I'm sure that's a first.
Not for nothing, but I will
do the fucking jokes here.
Well, there went all my questions.
Actually I got a lot.
But big question right now...
I haven't heard the answer before.
You've probably stated it.
You're Silent Bob in the movies.
You wrote and directed. Why give
yourself the Marcel Marceau part?
I'm sorry. I stopped listening.
Why give myself
the Marcel Marceau part?
I would think it's obvious.
I can't really act.
Which is why I wrote a movie
in which I was the lead.
Because this is America,
damn it, you know.
It happened by accident.
I'd written the role
of Randal to play myself...
...back when I wrote Clerks...
...which is why he has the best jokes.
As we got closer to production...
...I was like, "Who am I kidding?
I can't act. I can't memorize dialogue.
Who can memorize this in particular?"
There's a lot of dirty words in it.
So I gave the part to Jeff Anderson,
a dude I'd went to high school with...
...who'd never shown any interest
in acting and was perfect for it.
And I said, "If this is the only flick
I'm gonna make, I wanna be in it...
...because I want to be able to look back
years from now when I'm still paying...
...$28,000 in credit card debt,
get really drunk with my friends...
...and be like, 'Remember
the worst mistake of my life?
The one I'm still paying for?
Here it is. I'm in it.
Wait, here it comes.
Look at that jackass."'
I at least wanted to be in it.
So I was like, "What's left?"
I said, "Silent Bob." I'd written the
part for a friend, Michael Bellicose...
...and he wound up as the guy who
comes to the counter, and Dante's like:
"My girlfriend sucked 37 dicks."
And he says, "In a row?"
That's the guy.
You guys are easy.
I'm just, like, gonna
read from my scripts.
Then on page 19 in Chasing Amy,
Banky said this.
He was supposed to be Silent Bob.
I'd written it for him.
I thought he'd look good next to Mewes.
Mewes is thin and always moving...
...and Mike's the opposite.
Then I said, "Wait a second.
I'm way bigger than Mike.
I'm way less mobile and way stockier."
I said, "I don't have
to memorize dialogue...
...and I'll look good standing
next to Mewes."
Plus Mewes was not real reliable
when it came to acting.
So I could stand there and pinch him.
If you look at Clerks...
...and the other movies,
we stand closely in Clerks...
...and sometimes
you see me going like:
He's like:
"Snoogins." You know.
Because really, it is kind of like
two steps away from:
So I did it because I wanted to
be in it and not do dialogue...
...having no idea that I'd be
so bereft of original ideas...
...that I'd keep those characters
coming back.
I wrote Jay for Jason Mewes
because I wanted to see him act...
...and I thought he was funny and wanted
to see if others would find him funny.
Then I jumped in, and I said...
..."This is it. It's one time I'll be in
the flick. We may not make another."
Then we kept going, and I kept bringing
back the characters because...
...l'm not very creative and
because Jason Mewes is very funny.
So I kept coming back with him.
You don't want to split them up.
So I just kind of, you know,
stepped into it quite by accident.
Well, thanks. And on behalf
of all big men everywhere...
...doing a good job!
Don't lump me in with you.
I can say I'm fat.
When you say it, it's insulting.
I've been watching his movies for
a long time. I love all of them.
I saw Mallrats first.
I fell in love with him after that.
The first thing I saw was
Mallrats, and it was funny.
I connected to it
for some reason.
I love his dialogues in his movies,
like the random rampage people go on.
Especially in Clerks.
Me and my buddy Jay here have spent
a lot of time mentoring ourselves...
...in the ways of Jay and Silent Bob.
It's... Ever since, you know...
Clerks is really where we started off.
Awesome.
It's a whole new breed and a whole
new era of movie-making...
...that he's brought on and everything
from Jersey has been wonderful.
Kevin, thanks.
It's been a great ride.
Do you think that this guy
looks like you over here?
That guy?
That's Nathan and Gene. I'm in a
sketch-comedy group with them...
...and we also wanted to know
if you wanna hang out after...
...maybe go home and drink some beer.
Got a big house...
Yeah, especially after that. Yeah.
You guys had a little shtick going on.
That was cute. Got right up and went,
"You be Jay, I'll be Silent Bob."
That's tremendous.
Don't ever fucking do that again.
That routine is copyrighted.
Does the cat look like me?
A little bit.
How short's your hair?
Take your hat off.
I would never wear a sweater like that.
I guess it's easy to look like me.
Just pack on, like, 400 pounds,
grow a beard.
But can you do this?
No?
Fuck. Because I was hoping
to go out and get a cigarette.
I figured you could take over
since we look so much alike.
Is that it?
Do you wanna hang out after?
We're gonna be...
...drinking some beer and
smoking some tobacco.
Like, fuck, no. No.
No. After the show,
I go home and go to sleep.
- Why? What?
- We're gonna have fun.
- I can give you our phone number after.
- All right. Stick around.
- Okay. Thanks.
- Wait a second. Why "oh"?
Like, am I supposed to get stoned,
fuck a sheep, something like that?
I wanted to thank you for coming here.
I got fired from my job so I could come.
- Get out of here. What a waste of time.
- I'm dead serious.
Where did you work?
It's a Italian restaurant.
I was busing.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Want me to call your boss?
- Yeah!
- I'll get you the number.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Write it down and bring it up here.
"This is Kevin Smith."
"Who?"
"It's Silent Bob, man."
What's his number?
Come up.
- What's the number?
- Right, the number is 8-1-2...
- That's the area code?
- Yeah.
9-3...
- Ask for...
- Shut up.
- Tara's working...
- Get him on the phone.
And then I'll talk to him. Go.
Like to help when I can.
Amy, hey, this is Matt.
Is Tara or Teresa still there? Okay.
They're about to come on.
- Which one?
- I don't know.
- They'll say.
- What's your name?
Matt. Brown.
- Lf this works, I want 10 percent.
- All right.
Hey, Tara, this is Kevin Smith.
I'm here with... What's his name?
- Matt Brown.
- Matt Brown?
A dude who used to work there
until tonight?
He wanted me
to smooth things over.
He's in a room with about 30...
3200? 3200 people.
Sorry. And he said that he had to...
- Did you quit or get fired?
- A little of both.
He said his job's in jeopardy
because he came...
...and he wanted me to ask
you if you could keep him on.
- No?
- No!
They're turning on you, Tara.
Are you sure? Are you sure?
- Thank you.
- No?
Thanks a lot. Anyway.
I just... I have no juice whatsoever.
We're all proud to have Kevin
here as part of the Clark community.
I ignored my Jewish duty
to be here tonight.
I'm a huge fan of Kevin Smith and his
films and his comic books he's written...
...with Green Arrow and Daredevil.
I read on your website how you
had just finished Jersey Girl...
...and it was, I wanna say, 184 pages...
...and how you were thinking
of doing that with Affleck...
...but he was doing Daredevil
and there was stuff going on...
- There was static.
- There we go.
I was wondering
if you could tell me about it.
- Elaborate?
- Lf you could.
- I think you had all the details.
- Okay.
Back in...
On the Fourth of July I went to...
I was in Los Angeles
working on Jay and Bob...
...and we went to Affleck's house
for Fourth of July.
He's a big fan of Chasing Amy.
Still is, to this day.
He liked playing the Holden part.
He wants me to write
something like that again.
He's like, "Write something like
Chasing Amy again. You've gotta.
Who else could write it?
You've gotta. Fuck! Write it."
And I'm just like, "Motherfucker,
one of us won an Oscar for writing."
I started telling him about
this idea for a movie...
...which would become Jersey Girl.
He's like, "I love it. Write it."
I said, "I will.
When do you wanna do it?"
He said, "April."
I said, "Yeah. April's good."
It was July, and we had a few months.
I'd written 40 pages, and I sent them
to him, and he fell in love with it...
...because I'm like a pusher.
You know, the first taste is free.
And then you have to pay for the rest.
And how he pays is
we make him work very cheap.
He earns $ 15 million a picture...
...but we bring him on and pay him
about $ 15 an hour.
Around the same time...
...there's a dude named Mark Steven
Johnson who's directing Daredevil.
He'd been hanging around while
we were shooting the movie.
He said, "Who could play Daredevil?"
And I said, "Affleck."
'Cause that's my answer for everything.
I think Affleck could play...
I'm a big fan, so I think he can play
anything. If people are like, "Jaws 5?"
I'm like, "Affleck.
Affleck plays the fucking shark."
So I was like, "Affleck."
He said, "You think?"
I said, "He'd be great.
He'd dye his hair red."
Because Matt Murdock,
Daredevil, is a redhead.
I said, "He'd be great, and he's a fan.
He wrote the intro to the
Daredevil paperback I did."
I told Affleck, "There's a dude
checking if you wanna play Daredevil."
He's like, "I love Daredevil. "
I said, "That's what I told him."
He said, "What'd you say?"
I said, "You should play it."
He said, "Why?" I was like,
"I think you should play everything."
"Like, even the shark from Jaws?"
"Yes, the shark from Jaws. "
So they hooked up, and they
kind of dug each other...
...and soon Affleck called me
and was just like...
..."I'm doing it. I'm gonna put on
the red tights and have the horns."
I was like, "It couldn't be any more
embarrassing than Pearl Harbor. "
I said, "When do you start?"
He goes, "April."
I said, "That's when
we're doing Jersey Girl. "
He said, "We can wait on Jersey Girl.
I do Daredevil,
I get paid my big nut...
...and then we go do Jersey Girl,
and you pay me $ 15 an hour."
I said, "I don't know, man, I think
we should do Jersey Girl first."
He's like, "Don't get upset."
I said, "I'm not upset, but fair's fair."
He's like,
"You recommended me."
"I didn't know it would coincide
with Jersey Girl.  Fuck Daredevil. "
Because I'll turncoat real quickly.
At this point, I haven't even written
more than 40 pages...
...but I insist that we go in April,
even though I'm not done.
So two weeks go by, and he calls.
I'd let word leak out through Miramax...
...that we were gonna go in April
with or without Ben.
He calls and is like, "You'll shoot
with somebody else? That's for me."
I said, "But you're gonna put
on the tights, so fuck you."
He said, "How we gonna work this out?"
I said, "I'm going in April, and
if you're there, great.
If not, no hard feelings.
Go do Daredevil.
But I want to do something in April.
I want to do this movie."
He's like, "Jesus Christ.
Look, if you...
If you're saying you want me
to do Jersey Girl in April...
...and you want me to
pass on Daredevil, I will."
I was just like, "Well, if we
move the movie to the summer...
...you have to promise to take far,
far less than you normally take."
And he was just like,
"God. Fine, dude. If that'll do it."
I said, "Excellent.
That means a lot to me."
Then there's a long pause, and he's
putting shit together in his mind...
...and he goes, "You didn't finish
writing the fucking script yet, did you?"
And I said, "Nope, sucker. Goodbye."
I'm excited.
I have a couple of
great questions for him.
I really like Mallrats.
He uses a large vocabulary and
manages to get obscenities in there too.
When we called up the activity board,
we said we'd be shooting at Kent State.
They were like, "Bullshit!
We went through that shit
once before. Never again!"
That's a tough thing. That'll always be
associated with this school.
They'll never live it down.
The shooting.
It's a horrible thing,
but it's kind of like Germany.
Kent State's not like Germany,
but I went to Germany...
...with one of the flicks, and they're
nice people, but when you get there...
...the first thing, you're like,
"Where's the concentration camps?
We want to see the camps where you
slaughtered many people. Where?"
They're like, "They're here,
but we're Germans...
...we make cars and culture, beer.
I'm sure you like beer.
Wouldn't you like to see
any of that?"
We're like,
"Just the concentration camps.
We want to see the biggest colossal
blunder of any culture, anywhere.
Take us." They're like,
"All right, get in the fucking car."
There's always an older person,
like the cab driver.
And you're like, "Were you around?"
The dude's like 26.
And he's like, "No, but my grandparents
were. They were alive."
"Well, did they know? Were they
in trouble? Tell us. What? More!"
The guy's like...
He's heard it a zillion times.
"They teach it in school, and then we go
accuse our grandparents of atrocities."
I think that's what he said.
I can't understand German.
I'm sure he was just like,
"Shut the fuck up, fat American."
That's a tough thing to live down.
One day somebody from Kent State...
...will cure cancer, and it'll be,
"At Kent State we cured cancer."
And they'll be like, "Yeah, but didn't
you have those shootings there?"
I'm hoping for mass carnage
and orgies and chaos.
It'll be weird to hear him talk
for more than two seconds at a time.
He doesn't say much in the movie, but
when he does, everyone turns and looks.
There are questions I wanna ask.
- Gotta love the dialogue in Clerks.
- Mallrats.  Much better.
- How come?
- More lowbrow humor. I love that.
- Third nipple's awesome.
- Dick and fart jokes.
I hope Jay shows up.
They do some crazy stuff.
I was supposed to have
somebody with me today.
However, fucking moron
missed his plane.
But I brought the phone
so we can call him.
Bear with me.
- See you later, man.
- Get off the cell phone!
How much you guys pay for this?
- Hello.
- Hello. Hold on.
I'm in... I'm in fucking Wyoming.
You should see it. It's desolate.
What's up?
I'm driving out here,
there's nobody on the road.
It was like the opening
of Mallrats.  Nobody.
That's why I didn't go.
I'm gonna count to three...
...you say, "Hello, Wyoming."
Ready? One, two, three.
What up, Wyoming?
Don't cheer too loud.
He missed his fucking plane.
Explain to these people why
you're not here. On three.
- Jay, you fucking stoner!
- One, two, three.
I missed the plane, man.
I overslept. I was getting ass.
- You're not supposed...
- You fucking asshole!
Somebody just called you a
fucking asshole. Kick his ass, dude.
You can't miss shit like this, dude.
When they put "Jay and Silent Bob"
on the marquee, you have to show up.
Fuck that.
- We fire people for this kind of thing.
- What are you talking about?
What up? Look at that.
Look at that sign.
We tricked them, dude.
Who called me an asshole?
- Who called me the asshole?
- That dude over there.
What's up, dude? What's up?
So that was our little bit
for the evening.
It was good.
You can see we're such great actors
they gave us our own movie once.
And that'll never happen again.
- My name is Erin Guy.
- Hi.
- Hi, how you doing?
- I'm good.
I'm very well, thank you.
- Two questions.
- Yes.
One, how did you come up with
the characters Jay and Silent Bob?
- Yes.
- And two, are either of you married?
To each other?
Because it feels like it.
How did I come up with Jay and
Silent Bob? It came from Mewes.
Growing up...
Watching Mewes grow up, rather...
All right, chill the fuck out.
Get the microphone, come on down.
You can be on camera, don't sit
pussy back and be like, "Yeah!"
Basically, Jay and Silent Bob
came from knowing Jason Mewes.
When I went off to film school
in Canada, I said:
"I'm gonna come back and
put you in a movie."
He said, "Okay." At that point, he was
straight edge. He wore the black X.
- And he was just like no...
- Bullshit!
Exactly. This:
No booze, no drugs,
no cigarettes, no women.
The women thing confused me.
Straight edge, I understand, is...
...no booze, no drugs, no cigarettes.
But most straight edge people
fucked, except for this guy.
Since he didn't fuck, he was like,
"Well, no, they're no good either."
Because he wasn't getting laid.
But he would talk about pussy
incessantly. All the time.
Like, "I'm gonna get that pussy.
I'm gonna lick it, I'm gonna do this."
You look at him, and you're like, "You
haven't seen pussy since you were born!"
You could tell, because
he talked a good game...
...but as soon as a girl was around,
he'd fucking clam up.
And he'd get on his stone face.
His "I am Mewes," very cool face.
He'd be like,
"I'm gonna lick that pussy."
The girl would be coming over here.
He's like, "I'm gonna lick..."
This used to be... He doesn't do it now.
This used to be his cool face.
With the eyes affixed
to whoever he was studying.
But looking this way
and they were that way.
It was a peripheral thing.
Then the girl would walk past him.
Then the moment she was out
of his peripheral and earshot...
...he'd be like,
"I'm gonna lick that pussy."
So he talked a good game, and then
I left for Vancouver and came back.
I dropped out after four months,
but I was gone for a total of six.
By the time I came back,
he was completely debauched.
Like, you know,
the straight X was long gone.
And the "no women" thing was
also long gone.
If he had a belt that was notched...
...it would be like the fucking
Chewbacca belt around his body.
Because he's like the Wilt Chamberlain
of indie film. He's fucked a lot.
Right?
When I came back,
he was a little different...
...but I wrote Jay based
on who he was when I left...
...who he was when he was younger.
The weird sonic boom with dirt on it.
- Thanks.
- How long have you known each other?
Obviously, a long time,
but I don't follow up.
I'm not like, you know,
a connoisseur, but...
I love your guys'
movies and everything...
But... No... Okay, I'm
digging a hole here, so...
Just deep.
- It's like 13 years.
- Yeah.
You don't have to be a connoisseur
to know that, though.
I met him through my friends
Bryan and Walter at the Rec Center.
I worked with them for a year...
...and then I left. And they told me
these stories about Mewes...
...who everybody kind of knew,
but didn't know.
He was younger than us,
but you saw him in town.
He was the town's kid, the kid of
urban legend or suburban legend.
"There's Mewes. He broke the
fucking window at Katz's."
Or, "Here's the Mewes kid.
I hear he fucked a dog."
- Did you really fuck the dog?
- Only once.
I didn't know him, and Bryan and Walter
would tell me stories about him.
They're like, "He's so funny.
He says these funny things.
He's really fucking weird and funny."
I didn't like that, 'cause I was their new
funny friend, so I was kind of territorial.
We'd go to comic book shows,
and I'd drive to the city...
...because they were too pussy
to drive to the city.
One day Bryan and Walter
showed up with Mewes.
I said, "What's this? What's with
the kid? What, are you babysitting?"
They said, "We're gonna bring him.
He loves comics, take him to the show.
Make fun of the people there. Not us."
I said, "I'm not bringing
a minor across state lines."
The show was in New York.
Bryan was like, "I'll drive."
Mewes is the kind of asshole
that's like, "Shotgun!"
He jumps in the front, and I'm crammed
in the back. What was it, a Firebird?
Yeah.
With my knees
up to my fucking ears...
...and he's in the front:
"Snootch. Snoogins."
And Bryan and Walter are like:
I'm in the back, like,
"He ain't so fucking funny."
Bryan and Walter lost interest in him,
and he started coming over to my place.
He'd knock, and I'd go
out and be like, "What?"
And he'd be like, "You want to do
something today?"
I was like, "No."
I said, "We share friends,
but we're not friends.
We're both friends
with Bryan and Walter.
I know you live around the block,
but we don't hang out."
He's like, "All right, all right.
So, what do you want to do?"
I said, "If you really want to hang out,
come with me to the store...
...Quick Stop, 5:30 Sunday morning.
We'll make papers."
You ever make papers?
The Sunday newspapers
come in, like, five sections.
You have to put them together.
We had five Sunday papers...
...which was a lot.
You have 200 of each, so you're
doing this for hours upon end.
- That job sucks!
- Terrible, isn't it?
- Yes.
- This one's not much better.
I'd asked Bryan and Walter
to go, and they're like, "Fuck you."
"5:30, Sunday morning, it'll be fun."
They were like, "No."
But Mewes, I was like,
"You want to hang out?
Come down to the store.
I'll give you $2.00."
He was like, "All right."
So he'd come down.
We'd stack some of them
on the ice cream case...
...that Dante and Randal sit on in
Clerks when he's doing the salsa shark.
We'd stack them there, and Mewes
would sleep on the freezer case.
Mewes is a horrible fucking sleeper.
When he sleeps, he drools like a child.
Here's this dude sleeping
with his mouth open...
...tons of liquid pouring out
onto the freezer case and freezing.
So he had this icicle thing going on.
Then people would get papers...
...and as the piles got lower
and lower, he'd show up.
So somebody would be like,
"What the fuck!"
We started hanging out that way
and bonded.
The day that I realized he was a
comedic genius without knowing it...
...hopefully he still doesn't know it...
...was the day that Walter and I
were in the Rec Center...
...the kids hadn't come in yet...
...and it's all quiet and the door
fucking gets kicked open.
Mewes marches in like Groucho Marx
and fellates anything somewhat phallic.
So if there's a pool cue,
he's sucking it off.
Grabs the phone,
sucks it off.
Grabs the flag,
takes the eagle off, sucks it off.
Everything, going...
Sucking everything in the room off.
Walter and I are watching
him go, just like:
He never looked at us for approval.
Like, "This is funny.
I'm sucking everything off."
Almost like he didn't know
we were there or didn't care.
Like, he had an agenda. I always
pictured him walking around town going...
..."It's 2:30. I better go to the Rec
and suck everything off."
He does this for 15 minutes,
then reaches...
We had an Asteroids machine,
which, if you remember...
...has a roller ball instead
of a joystick.
And he fucking stops dead.
Because there's no joystick.
And me and Walter are like:
You know, 'cause what's a guy to do?
He ran out of phallic symbols.
And he shrugged, and he went
down on the roller ball.
So I said, "This is a dude
I wanna hang out with forever."
Because A: He's pretty funny.
B: He looks like he sucks a lot of dick.
For them slow nights,
that's a good guy to have around.
It's like, "No chicks.
We saw all the movies.
Wanna suck my dick?"
"All right, moves."
We've been hanging out for 13 years.
- Cool.
- Okay.
- Thanks for coming.
- Thanks for having.
In the comics and the movies,
does Jay's tiny dick...
...and latent homosexuality come
from his escapades at the Rec Center?
Or is there something else
behind that?
- You're writing the shit.
- Yeah.
- What are you writing about?
- So I should answer?
- Answer it, Jay.
- Yeah, why don't you answer.
- What?
- Is any of it true?
Well, are you asking
if I have a small dick?
I don't know about my dick.
I don't know if it's small.
I know it's not big, though.
But...
You got a thousand judges here.
Whip it out.
- I'm not...
- They'll let you know.
I'm not gay, though.
No, I love pussy.
I love pussy. So much.
- Pull his cock out of your mouth, dude.
- Who, him? Me or him?
No, they're talking about me.
No, I like the cock in my mouth.
Why don't you put a cock in
your mouth and shut your face.
You got unleashed for a second.
You're like, "Put a fucking cock
in your mouth and shut your face."
Jay and Silent Bob have great
chemistry, great sexual tension.
How come in the last one they
never got it on? I was disappointed.
How come they didn't just fuck?
- Yeah. The whole movie...
- Wait till DVD. Wait till DVD.
Thank you. On your final project,
Jay and Silent Bob porn, whole movie.
Jay and Silent Bob porn.
There are days when I'm afraid
that that will become true...
...because Mewes isn't the most
discerning actor on the planet.
He was hanging out with
this dude named Johnny Nitro.
Guy makes porn. He was like,
"I went to the set of a porn."
I was like, "What was that like?"
He was like, "It was cool.
They were fucking, and they asked
me if I wanted to get in, so I was..."
I said, "Wait. Wh...? What?"
He was like, "It was a courtroom scene.
They asked if I wanted to sit in the jury."
I said, "You didn't do it, did you?"
And he was like, "N... No."
I was like, "Just as long as it's no."
So periodically I cruise
the porn aisle...
...to make sure Mewes
isn't in any of the movies.
Just for that, you know.
But, no Jay and Bob porn
in the future.
There is a Jay porn that exists without
Silent Bob. But Silent Bob watched it.
- Can I get a copy?
- A copy?
Yeah.
Not tonight. Because I don't
have it on me.
But I'll try to make it
publicly available.
We sell everything else
on that website of ours.
www.viewaskew.com
- You like Jay, do you?
- Yeah.
Is he single? Is he single?
Is he single? Yeah.
Inasmuch as, like,
he's tied to no one person.
- So there's a chance?
- There's always a chance, my friend.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- Hey, Kevin...
- Wait. Wait. Wait.
You saying you're
"into Mewes" into Mewes?
Not yet.
You owe me for
that tremendous setup, sir.
Would you like to hear
about how he almost got married?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
You gotta ask him one day.
It's pretty funny.
Mewes had a girlfriend for a long time.
And one day...
I don't wanna say her name...
...'cause he's no longer with her.
We were going to the mall...
...and he goes, "So I did it last night.
I asked..."
Fuck it, her name's Jamie.
"I asked Jamie to marry me."
And I said, "Really?"
He's like, "I kind of did it all cool too."
He has this fish tank. He's like,
"I got her these expensive fish...
...and then I put the ring in this box
at the bottom of the fish tank...
...you know, bubbles,
a little treasure chest, and it opens...
...and she came in, and I said,
'Look at the fish. '
She saw the ring, and I got down
on one knee and proposed."
I was like, "That is really fucking
cool, man. Like, I'm shocked. You?
That is really sweet.
I wish I'd been there for that.
It would've been nice to be a
fly on the wall for that."
He's like, "Well, I taped it."
I said, "You did?"
He's like, "I set up a tape
recorder in the corner...
...and turned it on when I knew
she was coming.
And then she pulled up and was
talking to my mom for a bit...
...and I was getting pissed...
...and I wasn't gonna propose
to her anymore...
...because she was making me wait."
The exact mind frame you wanna
enter into marriage with.
He's like, "But then she came in, and we
went through it, and it's all on tape."
I said, "I would like to see that.
Give me the tape."
He's like, "I will." And he's like,
"There's another tape too."
I was like,
"What do you do on that one?"
He was like, "We fuck." And I was
like, "Get the fuck out of here!"
He was like, "We were celebrating.
We got engaged.
So I changed the tape,
and we started going at it."
And I said,
"I gotta see that one too!"
He's like, "You wanna see it?"
I was like, "Shit, yes!
Give me the tape."
So he gave me both...
...the engagement tape
and the Jason Mewes fuck tape.
I took them home and threw
the wedding tape aside.
He told me about it, fuck it.
I wanna see this man in action.
I put in the tape. And it's one of the
worst amateur porns you've ever seen.
It's a real one-camera setup.
It's like Clerks.
But even funnier.
Sets up the camera, and the MTV Video
Music Awards plays in the background.
Whole time. Now across from them,
in the frame...
...is a framed poster of the X-Men.
The comic book version.
And in the reflection of the X-Men
is the Video Music Awards.
So the camera the whole time is
auto-focusing between Jay and Jamie...
...and the Video Music Awards.
So, number one, it's the most
irritating porn in the world to watch...
...because you're like:
Number two, he pretty much gets
in there and blocks the whole thing.
You're not seeing anything good.
Just his ass up and down.
And I've seen that a zillion
fucking times.
But the best part about it was
what I told him...
...because he wanted me
to critique it.
I was like, "I'm the last guy
that should be telling you this...
...but you gotta work on
your camera work.
But number two, I gotta talk
to you about your whole finale."
He's like, "What about it?"
I'm like, "Dude, it's weak sauce."
He's like, "What do you mean?"
And I was like, "This is you:"
And he starts fucking cracking up.
When he really starts laughing,
he's like:
His veins pop out.
I'm like, "I'm serious.
You fucking give three thrusts,
one tug, and you walk away.
Try a little tenderness, you know?
A cuddle, something."
I was like, "And it went on forever.
At a certain point, I stopped watching...
...and concentrated on the VMAs
because it was on in the background."
But he promised to work on
his technique.
And I've yet to see the follow-up.
But now that I know
you're available...
That's the one I would like to see.
I've seen him fuck a chick,
and I wasn't impressed.
My name is Abe Mohammedian.
I got a question about you
and Scott Mosier.
What's the history
about your relationship...
...and the dynamic that's followed
through with the five movies?
My history with Mosier...
I went to Vancouver Film School
in British Columbia...
...because it was a quick tech program.
It was eight months.
Nine grand for eight months.
At the end...
...they don't give you a degree, you get
a certificate that says you finished...
...which is about as useful as a degree,
you'll find out.
So I was there for four months and then
dropped out and went back to Jersey.
I went for hands-on technical stuff.
They were like, "It's all practice.
All practical. No theory."
Then we did theory for three months.
I don't need some Canadian dude...
...telling me what Demme was trying
to say with Silence of the Lambs.
So I stuck around for a little bit,
but during that time I met Mosier.
The first day I went to class...
We had one class, 25 people.
And we, you know, went through
every class together.
They bring in a new bunch,
I think, every four months.
Mosier was a guy in a class that
I was like, "Look at this pretty boy."
He had, like, this real 90210 'do,
a Luke Perry thing going on.
He came in in a leather jacket,
like, a motorcycle hood...
...but, like, a good-looking one.
Like, the motorcycle hood
with a heart of gold...
...whose mom died,
and he's just really misunderstood...
...and he'll hook up with Brenda before
the season's out. That was my take.
Mosier said his first take on
me was, "Look at the blowhard asshole."
So we didn't really speak...
...and then we got thrown
together on this project.
Turns out, we had a
similar sense of humor.
We joked about calling our production
company "Post Party At Spago's."
We both got it, and nobody else did. So I
was like, "I wanna hang out with this guy.
He gets the obscure,
bad references."
We started hanging out more and more.
That's where our friendship built.
I was like,
"I'm not gonna stick around.
If I get out
before the four-month mark...
...I get to walk with five grand.
I'm gonna take my five grand
and put it in a movie.
I'm gonna go home
and start writing."
But he wanted to finish the course
because his parents would be proud.
I didn't care about my parents.
They were like,
"Look, we know you're a failure.
If you drop out, it's fine."
So I did.
I said, "I'm gonna go home and write.
You write, and whoever gets done first,
the other will help the other one out.
If you finish your script, I'll help you.
If I finish mine, you help me."
I finished Clerks first,
and he came down.
He got trapped into
the role of de facto producer.
Nobody goes to film school going,
"I wanna produce."
Everyone wants to be a filmmaker.
My job is kind of the dream job.
I get to write, you know, fucking,
"Jay and Silent Bob run into a wall."
Then I hand it to him. He's like,
"All right. It'll cost this much.
We have to hire this many people."
His job is the tough job.
Particularly on Chasing Amy,
his head almost exploded.
We were trying to make
that movie for $250,000.
Initially, we wanted to do it
for $3 million.
We had done Mallrats for $6 million.
First one was $28,000.
Second one, Mallrats, $6 million.
We were like, "We'll go
to a sensible budget, $3 million."
We pitched the movie
to Miramax, gave them the script...
...and they were like, "This is great.
Who do you wanna put in it?"
I was like, "I wrote it for Ben Affleck,
Jason Lee, Joey Lauren Adams."
And the exec was like, "Oh, no.
We have to put celebrities in it.
We were thinking Drew Barrymore,
Jon Stewart, David Schwimmer."
And I was like, "Why?
Where'd you get that grouping from?
Did you just pick those three
off the top of your head?"
They'd had deals with them.
I said,
"I wanna make it with my people."
And the exec said words
I will never forget:
"Kevin, it's not about making
a movie with your friends."
I was like, "Really?"
That's been the whole point
of my career.
So I went to see Harvey Weinstein,
the chairman.
I said, "Look, you guys wanna do
the movie at $3 million with a cast.
I wanna use the people
I wrote it for.
Let us make the movie for $200,000.
We'll bring it back. If you like it, buy it.
If not, we take it someplace else."
We have an overall deal with them.
He said, "200,000?
I'll give you 250."
And I said, "That's really generous.
All right, man, that's cool."
I went home and said,
"Mosier, Harvey gave us the money."
He's like, "Get out!" I was like,
"I asked one amount, he gave me more."
And Mosier was like, "Terrific.
You're really good at this shit.
So, what's the budget?"
And I was like, "$250,000!"
And Mosier was just like:
The brain came out, and he was like,
"$250,000? Are you nuts?
We can't make a movie for that."
I was like,
"We made a movie for $28,000."
He's like, "That's barely a movie.
This movie is more complicated.
How are we gonna do it?"
I was like, "You'll figure it out.
I gotta call Ben and Jason."
He's like, "Good Lord."
So he spent most of Chasing Amy,
like, sleeping in his office...
...trying to figure out
where the money was coming from...
...trying to make everything work
on a shoestring.
Shooting that movie for $250,000
almost killed him. And I never noticed.
My job's kind of always the same
no matter what the budget is.
I write it, and then I rehearse
the actors and hope...
...they give the performance that
I heard in my head when I wrote it...
...if not a better performance.
No matter the budget,
my job doesn't change.
But Mosier's job is
always affected by the budget.
The last one was 20 million bucks.
Jay and Bob Strike Back.
And he was happy as a pig in shit.
I'm like, "There's a problem."
He was like, "That's fine,
throw some money at it."
Problem solved, you know.
But with the other ones, it's like,
"We got a problem."
He's like, "It's not my fault. You asked
for 200 grand, asshole." I'm like, "Oh."
He runs the gamut, depending
on what the budget is.
Dogma was tight. We had $ 10 million.
We should've had more to do it.
Also, we were dealing with crazy
schedules of people coming and going.
They were paid scale, which is, like,
minimum wage of the movie business.
So we had to allow them
to do other things if they wanted.
That became a nightmare for him.
But the last one
he had a great time doing.
He's like, "I love making movies with you,
but I hate the shit I have to go through.
I hate dealing with these people."
And I'm like, "All right, we can
make movies with puppets."
But he's not real...
He's afraid of puppets.
So he's in this weird headspace
where he bought a VW conversion van.
And Mosier... You don't know him
so it's not gonna play as well...
...but Mosier doesn't buy
extravagant things.
He kind of lives
a very monk-like life.
So one day I came to the office, and
I saw this tricked out conversion van.
I was like,
"Whose piece of shit is that?"
He's like, "That's mine."
I was like, "Why'd you get that?"
He's like, "I don't know. $38,000.
I figure instead of walking the earth,
I can drive the earth."
He's like, "Here's the sink
and a stove.
Out back there's a little shower thing.
The top is a pop-out.
I got two beds up here
and beds down here.
Me and Monica could sleep up here.
You and Jen could sleep under us."
I'm like, "I'd be up for that."
So he's in this weird kind of
"I've got a VW van" headspace...
..."and I don't know if I wanna keep
making movies for Miramax."
If that makes any sense.
- Yeah, so...
- We should call him.
- Call Ben!
- You know, Mosier first. Hold on.
Believe me, I'd much rather
call people all night.
Just hold the phone to the mike.
Hey, Monica? Is Scotty there? Okay.
Hey, man, what's up?
I'm at Kent State on stage.
I'm gonna count to three.
I'm gonna put you to the mike.
In 20 seconds, give them a rough
breakdown of your conversion van.
Yeah, like what it's tricked
out with. All right, ready?
I'll hold you to the mike.
Ready? One, two, three.
It's got a fridge, it's got
a two-burner stove, a sink.
It can sleep four.
It's got the pop-up.
Runs off propane so I can run
a thermostat, keep it hot.
Make a little love, you know.
- Anything else?
- Not much more to say than that, man.
Come on, you sold it to me bigtime.
That's about it, man.
What did you pay for it?
- It cost, like, about between 35 and 40.
- You got ripped off.
Look, I've been working
a long time, man.
- All right.
- What color?
What color is it? It's beige?
No, it's white.
That's beautiful, man!
Some guy in the back went,
"That's beautiful, man."
All right, man, that's it.
All right, bye.
Hi, I'm Shawn Johnson.
In your writing...
...do you take any of your own
life experiences and put them in?
Yes, one time me and my friends were
running from this rubber poop monster.
Smart ass.
And then we tried to sneak
into Miramax Studios, you know...
...fell onto the set
of Good Will Hunting II.
No, generally not. Because
real life tends to be very boring.
Which is why the dialogue I write tends
to be the way it is, 'cause people say:
"It sounds like you write down the
conversations of friends. It's natural."
Not at all. The conversations I have with
my friends are probably similar to yours.
Like, "What did you do?"
"Got laid."
"Awesome."
One word. Really monosyllabic,
caveman-type talk.
But I've read somewhere the writer
crafts their ideal world.
In mine, everyone has long conversations
about interesting pop-culture shit.
And everyone talks in monologues.
But generally not.
There are instances of real life.
I did work at Quick Stop and RST.
That's about where it stops.
There were people that would
check the date of the milk...
...but not like the lady in the movie,
who was my mom, incidentally.
People do check the eggs
at the counter. That bugged me.
Check eggs in front of you...
...as if I'm sitting in the back
with a little hammer, like:
Like, "I'll break one,
and they'll never know."
You blow that shit out of proportion.
That makes it interesting.
If I wrote about real life,
Chasing Amy would be about the fact...
...that I couldn't stand that my
girlfriend had gone to Bali and I didn't.
Not a very interesting movie.
So I'm like, "Maybe her boyfriend
suggests they sleep with his best friend."
That's more interesting. Shit like that
doesn't happen to me in real life.
I've never said to Scott Mosier,
"We should fuck my girlfriend."
He's like, "We have budget problems."
"I know, let's fuck my girlfriend."
He's like, "I don't know
if it'll help, but okay."
You tend to exaggerate,
but you start with a kernel of truth.
Like, Chasing Amy...
I was very much like Holden.
I was insecure about girlfriends'
pasts when I wrote that.
And now I'm beyond... I'm 31.
Now I'm insecure about the grave.
I don't care who fucked who.
I just don't wanna die.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, man.
Comedy in general, and especially
your kind of witty satire, often...
I'm sorry.
Often stems from some sort...
I've never heard it described like
that: "Your kind of witty satire."
"Your bullshit." Go ahead.
Comedy seems to me like it stems
from a level of frustration in life.
Is that true for you? Is there
a specific area of your life...
...where you were frustrated
as a child or when you were younger?
You talk about, "This is for the girls
who said my dick was small."
Is there some area of life that
was particularly frustrating...?
Take a fucking guess, dude.
I don't... I think... Here, I can
answer it. I'll put my spin on it.
I think I do what I do
because I grew up fat.
The room came down. Don't get
all serious. It's fucking true.
It's not like a life-threatening
afflic... It is, but it's not.
Because I grew up a heavy kid,
it tended to make me want to be funny.
If you can't get over
with your looks...
You don't know what I mean.
You're a good-looking man.
- That's the first time I've heard that.
- What are you doing after the show?
I'm not just talking about girls.
People hang out
with a certain aesthetic type...
...people that look "normal." When you
don't look "normal," you're castigated.
Kind of like,
"Well, that kid's fat. Yipes!"
If you have something else going for
you, they overlook your physical flaws.
That's my theory, what I've found in life.
So... From you fucking thin people.
It came from there.
My comedy comes from that.
Thank you.
Thanks for bringing up really
painful fucking memories.
I like how the room got. They're like,
"Holy shit! He's about to cry."
Go ahead.
What do your parents feel
about your films?
My parents... My mother,
when she saw Clerks...
...when I sat her down to watch it...
...she turned to me and goes, "You spent
$27,000 on that piece of garbage?"
I was like, "Thanks, Mom.
That's real Carol Brady of you."
Then she grew to like the movies.
She didn't care for Mallrats either...
...but Chasing Amy she really loved
and connected to for some reason.
I know.
I'm watching the movie with her,
and she's laughing at blowjob jokes.
Like, her and my old man are chuckling
at blowjob jokes, and I'm just like:
"Oh, God. She's giving him head."
She cried at the end of the movie.
I was really moved by that.
I was like, "Oh, my God,
you really got into it."
She was like, "I identify with that
movie in ways you'll never understand."
And I was like:
They've caught on. She liked Dogma
because she's a lifelong Catholic...
...and it addressed many
issues that she has as well...
...but would never voice
for fear of going to hell.
Which, she maintains,
is where I'm going.
And Jay and Bob
she thought was really cute.
That's what she says. She's like,
"It was cute. You guys ran around a lot.
Was it tough to run around like that
in that long coat?"
I felt like I was at a fucking college
q and a, the caliber of that question.
That wasn't directed at everybody.