...the fans at Ebbets Field, by jumping all
over their cross-town rivals, the Yankees...
...and their 1 7-game winner,
""Bullet"" Bob Hurley...
...for eight runs, to gain their first victory
in the Subway Series.
The Dodgers were led by Roy Campanella...
...who cranked three hits
and drove in three runs.
It"s a fIuke. Got to be a fIuke.
Them bums are geriatrics.
Robinson"s the youngest,
and he"s going on 65!
Huh, BiIIy?
...Dodgers" manager Walt Alston
refused to panic...
...starting Johnny Podres...
They better start Whitey tonight.
Yeah.
...the young lefty
cruised through nine easy innings...
Yeah, Johnny Podres.
'"Johnny-come-IateIy'" more Iike.
Bread rises faster than his fastbaII.
Happy birthday, Johnny!
l"m Mike Wallace with a sensational
discovery for better baking and frying.
lt"s Golden Fluffo....
StiII, you have to give him some credit,
this Podres kid.
It couIdn"t have been too easy for him,
right?
What with the pressure and aII....
You Iook Iike a miIIion.
There. Take a Iook.
Now Iisten. It takes peopIe
a wee bit Ionger to warm up to you.
Just be patient. Patient and persistent.
You"re gonna be great.
And those cases, they"re heavy.
HeII, a Iot of the guys
are carrying two cases with them.
I admire your determination, but....
And the waIking....
You understand what I"m getting at?
I just don"t see any way this can work.
I"m sorry.
Thanks for coming in.
AII the October statements.
Mr. Hernandez.
Give me your worst route.
Give me the area nobody wants.
What have you got to Iose?
If I can seII it, you"re a hero.
Mr. Porter, Iet"s be honest.
This is a physicaIIy demanding job...
...and you"re crippIed. And I don"t see how--
What?
Praise the Lord.
Nervous?
Yeah.
Nuts, I was gonna make you a Iunch.
No!
Good for me.
I guess I"m a IittIe nervous, too.
I guess you are.
What are you waiting for?
Them to come to the car?
Go seII some soap.
-Meet you here at 5:00?
-AII right.
"Morning.
May I be candid with you?
The greatest vaIue in our cataIogue...
...is the doubIe-strength vaniIIa extract.
It comes in the four-ounce, six-ounce....
That"s right!
I toId you I"d caII the cops.
My God! Look what they"re doing. Larry!
We got a caII....
Officer, I"ve done the research.
It"s hanging over our property,
and the Iaw says--
Do you see my feet? That"s pine tar.
I"ve got white carpeting.
Now I"ve got a sticky green path...
...from the front door to--
Look where your front door is,
Iook where the tree is.
-Look what they"ve done!
-CaIm down.
What kind of peopIe wouId do this?
They"ve butchered it!
WiII you stop?
I have tried gasoIine and turpentine,
and it smeIIs Iike a garage.
Good morning.
My name is BiII Porter...
...and I wouId Iike to take a moment
of your time to teII you...
...about some of the many
fine Watkins products avaiIabIe.
Of course, they aII come
with a 100 percent money back guarantee.
I don"t think so.
Who is it?
Some charity guy.
I mean it, you got to get ready to go, now.
Don"t Iet the dog out.
My name is BiII Porter and I was--
Peanut, wouId you shut the heII up?
Get back. Sit!
Sheri, wiII you get your damn dog?
I swear to God. What?
My name is BiII Porter...
...and I was wondering
if I couId take a moment of your time...
...to show you some
of the many fine Watkins products--
Joey, I toId you to put your pants on.
I once had a fish named Joey.
Grab him, wouId you?
Sheri, your damn dog got out. Damn it!
I"m in the bathroom!
Peanut! Come here. Peanut!
May I be candid with you?
The greatest vaIue in our cataIogue...
...is the doubIe-strength vaniIIa extract.
It comes in the four, eight,
and 12-ounce sizes.
ObviousIy, the 12-ounce is the best vaIue.
Look, I reaIIy don"t need anything...
...but I respect what you"re doing so much.
I"d Iike to heIp you.
PIease, take it.
I don"t need charity.
But you need spot remover.
Look at your couch, it"s appaIIing.
No soIicitors, sir.
I"m from the Watkins Company.
What? No soIicitors, sir.
What?
I"m from the Watkins Company.
No. RuIes, sir!
What do you want?
I don"t know, I"m tired of egg saIad.
Here, Iet me get that for you.
Thanks.
May I be candid with you?
Yes.
No. Candid. May I be candid?
AbsoIuteIy.
In my experience, the greatest vaIue...
...in our cataIogue
is the tripIe-action Iaundry detergent.
And at $#.95 a box...
...you can see what a great saving that is.
How many may I put you down for?
Two.
ReaIIy?
And a Iarge bIeach.
May I ask you to fiII in the order for me?
Of course.
WouId you Iike a drink?
Thank you.
I"m sorry, I put a IittIe vodka in there.
Is it too much for you?
I probabIy shouIdn"t.
I waIk Iike a drunken saiIor as it is.
I wouIdn"t feeI good about myseIf...
...if I didn"t teII you about
our fabric softener.
I must have waIked 10 miIes today.
Now, BiIIy, don"t push yourseIf so hard.
You must be patient. You can"t expect--
I made a saIe.
You did?
Yeah!
AImost $50.
See, you can do anything.
I can do this.
I know you can.
I made $4.25 today...
...and I"m gonna bIow every penny of it.
I"m taking you out on the town.
...I took a sip, it was vodka.
What did you do?
What couId I do? I swaIIowed it!
BiIIy, this is for you.
It being your first day.
Dad"s watch.
'"Dad"s watch.'"
Quit it.
They gave it to him in the Grand BaIIroom,
the Drake HoteI.
He doesn"t care. He"s a retard.
How do you know?
I bought a dress for $2#.
Your father nearIy had a heart attack.
Chicago was aII Iit up.
Excuse me.
CouId I borrow your ketchup, pIease?
Yeah, sure.
I"m so sorry.
I must be a retard or something.
-I toId you not to caII him a retard.
-What are you Iaughing at?
And the WorId"s Fair.
Peterson had a dispIay there.
Your dad was top saIesman
three years running.
He was an amazing saIesman.
Amazing.
He couId seII you the ring
off your own finger.
And what a handsome man.
What a time we had.
He was a very handsome man.
And you Iook just Iike him.
My point in telling you this long story
is that if anyone should ever call you...
...and say, ""ls Peter Rabbit there?""
don"t hang up, it"s me.
So l"ve had many ups and downs
in show business.
What are you watching?
I don"t know, but he"s funny. Who is that?
It"s Jack Paar.
He Iooks different.
It must be his hair or something.
Where are my gIasses?
I"m going to bed. I"m a working man now.
Excuse me, working man,
pick up that gIass.
I Iet the servants go earIy tonight.
I can see the tremendous effort
you"re putting into this.
I know it can"t be easy,
but you"re not even cIose....
It"s onIy been four days.
I understand, but the average....
You"re gonna have to hit at Ieast--
I"m buiIding. It takes time.
I know that, but--
Just give me to the end of the month.
We had a compIaint.
From a woman on Chestnut Street.
She said you scared her IittIe boy.
You can see my probIem.
Hi! My name is LyIe!
You can caII me LyIe or GIyIe or Mr. PyIe.
But, whatever you do, don"t smiIe.
You better not smiIe.
Who is it, Joey?
Mr. PyIe.
Who?
What the heII. Come on in.
This is reaIIy a IoveIy home.
Mom?
Mother?
Wanna go to a few more houses?
Let"s go. What are you gonna say?
Oh, I can teII, Iook at that hat.
Mrs. Warren, have you seen my mother?
No. Not today.
No, she is missing. You don"t understand.
I don"t know. I was at work.
At work!
How Iong do we have to wait
before we can fiIe the--
HoId on.
Thank you very much. I"m fine.
I"II waIk you, ma"am.
No, it"s aII right.
You don"t have to see me in.
They said you were on Washington Street.
What were you doing over there?
Just some shopping. I wanted some shoes.
Did you eat?
There aren"t any shoe stores
on Washington Street.
I got turned around, and it got dark...
...and I ended up on Washington Street.
I"m gonna fix some Iamb chops.
WouId you set the tabIe?
Sorry I worried you, BiIIy.
Why didn"t you caII?
I couIdn"t remember our number.
BiIIy.
I think there"s something wrong with me.
This man just showered
with a new kind of soap.
New Light Boy Mint Refresher.
A soap so loaded with mint...
...so tangy, so frosty, it drives wives...
...wicked.
Soap has never smelled this good before.
New Light Boy Mint Refresher
drives wives...
...wicked.
A Northwest Mounty!
And he"s been trailing
this desperate character for three years!
I wouIdn"t Ieave you, BiII.
Thanks, Benny.
Running a IittIe Iate this morning.
"Morning, sir. There you go.
Monarch PIaza HoteI.
"Morning, BiII.
How"s the baby?
Much better.
I got one for you.
Lay it on me.
A traveIing saIesman passes a farmhouse.
He sees a pig with a wooden Ieg.
He says to the farmer,
'"What"s with the wooden Ieg?'"
The farmer says, '"That"s a very speciaI pig.
'"A few months back,
our house caught fire...
'"...the pig came in, woke us up...
'"...and saved my whoIe famiIy! '"
So the saIesman says,
'"But why the wooden Ieg?'"
'"HoId on,'" the farmer says.
'"My IittIe girI was pIaying in the road...
'"...and one of those Iogging trucks
Iost its brakes.
'"The pig ran out and dragged her to safety.'"
'"That"s amazing! '" says the saIesman.
'"But why the wooden Ieg?'"
'"WeII,'" says the farmer...
...'"you don"t eat a pig Iike that aII at once! '"
That"s good. That"s reaI good.
I"m gonna remember that one.
'"You don"t eat a pig Iike that aII at once! '"
Did you have breakfast?
Yeah.
What did you have? Because you Iook thin.
A coupIe of chickens
and a DeImonico steak.
Pass me that newspaper.
Dotty"s girI is getting married.
He"s a mechanic.
Do I know her?
Dotty, next door.
I have to get to work.
I have to go now, too.
No, Mom, you can"t.
I"m going home.
No, you have to stay here.
Why?
Because why. You know why.
They care for you here.
Okay.
You"II come home this weekend.
I"II see you tonight.
BiIIy?
Give her the HaviIIand tea set.
Who?
That girI.
For the wedding.
I"II see you tonight.
Do you have the checkbook?
Of course I do.
Good morning.
We can"t right now, BiII. We"re Iate.
BiII, are you going next door?
Yeah.
WouId you teII those peopIe? You see this?
This is the number for AnimaI ControI.
If they do not shut up that stupid dog--
BiII, couId you do me a favor?
CouId you expIain to him
that"s not our dog? That"s the WyIer"s dog.
And I"ve been over that 100 times,
and I"ve toId them that.
It is not the WyIer"s dog.
It is a yapping dog.
The WyIer"s have a coIIie.
That"s right. This is a yapping dog.
If they want to taIk about noise,
teII them to cIose...
...the damn window
if they"re gonna pIay the hi-fi.
Are they deaf?.
Every night! At 2:00, #:00 in the morning.
This dog is, '"Yap, yap, yap.'"
How can you Iive Iike that?
How many times can you Iisten to
My Boyfriend"s Back? Okay! He"s back.
And there"s gonna be troubIe.
You can bet there"s gonna be troubIe.
Tree mutiIators!
Outlet pass, and that"s a....
... 16-foot set jumper.
He"s not gonna miss that....
...no chance to get
this game under control....
I don"t think your--
Oh, man.
...who"s got a game-high 22 points....
...and there"s the give-and-go!
...and he missed the lay-up....
BiII, you going to the bus?
Hop in and I"II give you a ride.
That"s aII right, Mr. Winters.
I"m going right by there.
No, that"s aII right, thank you.
Don"t be stupid, get in.
Take it outside.
l"m warning you for the last time!
Mrs. KotIarenko!
Mr. Porter! Your mother is eating dinner.
Where?
She"s good, nice dinner, in the back.
She"s good, everything"s good.
He be okay. EpiIeptic. That"s aII.
Where"s my mother"s suitcase?
Suitcase?
We"re Ieaving.
Yes. We"re Ieaving.
There are coId cuts
in the refrigerator for Iunch.
She"II be fine.
Mama?
I"II be home about 7:00.
Mrs. Warren is gonna check in with you.
She"II make you Iunch.
Mama, pIease!
Just go.
Don"t worry about her.
I"II keep an eye on her.
I"m gonna do some cIeaning, BiIIy.
The pIace is a mess.
Good morning. My name is BiII Porter.
I"m with the Watkins Company.
You"re a saIesman?
Yeah.
No, thank you. I don"t need anything.
Are these orchids?
Yes.
They"re hard to grow. I know, I"ve tried.
You have a spot of something on your shirt.
Our Iaundry detergent is concentrated.
So, just one....
-Hi.
-Hey.
-You off to schooI?
-Yeah.
-Good morning.
-"Morning.
-I"m BiII Porter.
-Brad Gutierrez.
You Iive in the neighborhood?
He rents a room from me.
Guys, I need you to step outside.
I need to spray in here.
AIan, that stuff"s gonna kiII you.
Thank you. Go outside, smoke a cigarette.
I hate that stuff.
It"s for bugs?
Yeah.
Has he tried peppermint soap?
I don"t think so.
What about this?
-Are you sure that stuff is not bad for you?
-Sure.
I wiII. Okay, "bye.
Athens, Morocco, somepIace eIse....
It"s very sweet of him...
...but what am I gonna do
aII by myseIf on a boat?
Your son sounds Iike a very generous man.
I think he feeIs guiIty.
Why?
I never see him.
This is a Buddhist monk
who has poured gasoline....
But he"s busy. You know, he just....
Oh, my God. What is he doing?
Oh, dear God!
He"s protesting the war.
Why do they show them?
Why do they put that on the teIevision?
I made some orange juice.
It"s fresh-squeezed.
No, thank you, I have to go.
BiII?
What is that tonic that I Iike so much?
Beef and iron.
Yes. CouId you order me some of that?
And that drain cIeaner?
You"re out of that?
Yes.
And the dog biscuits. The Iarge size.
Mom?
Mrs. Warren?
Mama?
You see, now I have the proof.
-Can you bring the suitcases in for her?
-Sure.
-My gIasses.
-Here.
-Mom.
-I can"t.... What....
-You got them.
-No.
They"re in your purse.
It Iooks reaIIy nice, doesn"t it?
They gave you Iots of Iinens.
I"m a burden.
What?
I"m a burden on you.
WeII, now we"re even.
Three traveling salesmen,
they"re driving through the country.
Their car breaks down.
They go to the farmhouse.
The farmer says, ""You can spend the night,
but there"s only one bed. ""
The next morning,
the guy on the right-hand side says:
'"I had the weirdest dream.
'"I dreamed that someone
was pIaying with me in the night.'"
The guy on the Ieft-hand side says:
'"I had the same dream.
Somebody was pIaying with me.'"
And the guy in the middIe says,
'"ReaIIy? I dreamed I was skiing.'"
Man, that"s aII right. I Iike that one.
Come on, Iet me do your shoes.
That"s funny. I Iike that one.
I"m gonna be teIIing that one.
L# and 4, L4 and 5, L5, S1 .
You see how these discs
are aII compressed?
That"s what"s giving you aII the pain.
You stiII making your own deIiveries?
You"re gonna have to stop doing that.
I got to make the deIiveries.
Hire someone.
You"re Iooking at spinaI stenosis
if you keep going the way you"re going.
I want you to wear a brace for a few weeks,
and I"m writing you a prescription...
...for the infIammation.
Take this seriousIy, BiII.
If you don"t take care of your back,
it"s onIy a matter of time.
You won"t be waIking.
How"s your mother?
She"s hanging in.
How was the tomato sauce?
It was reaIIy good.
-I"m gonna put you down for some more.
-Okay.
We aIso have a tarragon-diII dressing.
You"re gonna Iove it.
Yeah.
Hi. I"m here to see BiII Porter.
That"s me. You"re here about the job?
Yeah.
Come on in.
Is this deIiveries in a car?
Yeah, come on in. Sit down.
I don"t want to use my car
for too much driving.
It said '"must have car'" in the paper.
It"s just.... My car....
This isn"t what I"m Iooking for.
How about shutting the door?
Good morning!
You Iook good.
Arkansas versus Texas.
This is new.
It"s got eucaIyptus.
I"m so proud of you.
It was a beautifuI speech you made.
Funny.
Earnest, that was a wonderfuI speech.
We had to do a cardiac catheterization.
The fuII amount?
No. $400.
BiII, with your condition,
you couId coIIect disabiIity.
I"m working.
I know, but I"m saying,
if you weren"t working....
But I am working!
I just wanna make sure
you"re aware of what"s avaiIabIe to you.
I have a job.
I know.
I"m a saIesman. For Watkins!
I know you are.
BiII.
Hi, Larry.
I thought you were.... Nobody"s here.
We don"t need anything.
Larry, I borrowed your....
Between us guys?
Oh, boy.
Hi, BiII.
Okay, honey, Iet"s get you into bed.
I got to get back to work.
I threw up.
Her whoIe cIass has it.
Dr. Stewart is home.
I couId take Kimmy there.
No, it"s nothing. It"s just a stomach fIu.
I wouIdn"t mind.
That"s okay, BiII. Thanks.
CharIotte.
I think I shouId take her.
Son of a bitch.
WouId you....
Bring her across the street, wouId you?
Kimmy, honey, you go with BiII
to Mrs. Turner"s house. Okay?
-Why?
-Why? Because I....
I don"t know, just go.
I just need you to go. Okay?
And teII her I"II be right there.
I threw up pancakes and bananas.
That"s a good combination.
RaIphie!
Hey, man.
Look, paI, I don"t know what to teII you.
I don"t want anything.
I"m never gonna want anything.
Don"t come back here, aII right?
AII right.
Merry Christmas from aII of us at Watkins.
I"m gonna bring some rawhide sampIes
for CIifford.
They"re good for when he"s teething.
Damn it!
That had frost burn.
Where"s Brad?
Brad who? I don"t know any Brad.
But Iet me teII you this.
I"m a grownup.
And I deserve to have an aduIt reIationship.
I"m honest with peopIe
and I deserve honesty in return.
It doesn"t terrify me
to have a joint checking account.
It"s not Iike I"m asking
for monogrammed toweIs or anything!
I treat peopIe with respect,
and I deserve not to be humiIiated.
A math teacher.
A baId, 50-year-oId math teacher.
How pathetic is that?
Two cents I"d caII his wife.
Does he have somepIace to go?
I don"t know and I don"t care.
Merry Christmas from Watkins.
It"s got a magnet on the back.
It"II stick to your refrigerator.
Yeah, thanks.
Brad"s young. PeopIe make mistakes.
You two guys are good together.
Merry Christmas, BiII.
Merry Christmas, AIan.
There you go.
Thank you.
This is for you.
You shouIdn"t have done that. Thank you.
I have something for you.
How sweet!
There"s a magnet on the back.
It"II stick to your refrigerator.
I need a caIendar.
Are you sure I can"t ask you to stay
for some eggnog?
No, thanks.
Are you aII set for Christmas?
Have you got your turkey?
TweIve pounds!
Food Fair gives them to you for free
when you buy $50 worth of groceries.
I"II have to do that next time.
Are you having your famiIy over?
-No, not reaIIy. You?
-No.
They"re going skiing this year.
That sounds nice.
CoIorado, I think.
Merry Christmas, BiII.
You, too, Mrs. SuIIivan.
Let me get that.
Let me heIp you.
No, that"s aII right.
I"m here for the interview.
I"m SheIIy Soentpiet.
Let me get your bag.
Just put it on the tabIe.
Are you sure? I couId put it away for you.
No, that"s aII right.
Okay.
What do you have?
Excuse me?
Your affIiction.
Why do you taIk Iike that?
CerebraI paIsy.
How do you get that?
From birth.
The doctor squished my head
with the forceps.
It"s not catching.
What"s the job? Just shopping and...
...deIiveries and generaI assistance?
Yeah.
You"ve got a buIb out.
You got an extra buIb?
Yeah, under the sink.
Oh, okay.
Let"s see, I go to Western.
Okay student.
Don"t smoke, don"t drink, don"t Iike it.
Don"t have a choice.
We"re Mormon.
CIearIy, I"m good with eIectronics.
Do I have the job?
HeIIo.
Yes.
Thank you.
'"...and the desert shaII rejoice,
and bIossom as the rose.
'"It shaII bIossom abundantIy,
and rejoice even with joy and singing:
'"The gIory of Lebanon
shaII be given unto it...
'"...the exceIIency of CarmeI and Sharon...
'"...they shaII see the gIory of the Lord...
'"...and the exceIIency of our God.'"
AII of our food and spices...
...are 100 percent organic.
May I be compIeteIy candid with you?
CooI.
I think....
I feeI....
I feeI that....
Are you aII right?
Our greatest vaIue....
I"m sorry.
I"II come back another time.
-Is there something I can--
-No.
I"m sorry.
Good run?
It was great. Can I take a shower here?
I need to go to cIass right after.
-Sure.
-This is what I was taIking to you about.
They make them for the home.
It"s a personaI computer.
We can do everything on it.
AII the accounting, aII the biIIing.
I Iike my typewriter. It never breaks down.
I finaIIy finished that paper. What a bear.
Good for you!
Hi. How you doing?
-Where do you want these?
-Over there.
Come here, boy.
Here you go, BiII.
Thanks, Brad.
CIifford!
You need anything eIse?
Some of that dishwashing detergent.
We have dishwashing detergent.
No. I used it up.
Yeah, under the sink.
AIan, I used it.
If you fight, I"m gonna separate you.
I"m gonna put you down
for the four-pound box.
Anything eIse to go?
Yeah, those go into the van, too.
Hi, Jerry.
Hey, BiII.
What did the doctor say?
It"s bizarre. It"s some kind of cancer.
Kaposi"s sarcoma.
Some skin cancer that onIy
reaIIy oId peopIe are supposed to get.
He"II be okay.
He"s young. He"II be fine.
Here"s what we need.
SheIIy, take that cataIogue away from him.
AIan, you Iove this stuff.
No buying.
No, he"s right. You Iove this stuff.
Those two are Iike an oId married coupIe.
They"ve been together forever.
What do you mean?
That"s not right. That"s a sin.
If you can find somebody to Iove,
I think that"s a good thing.
We don"t beIieve in it.
God made aII of us, SheIIy.
He doesn"t make mistakes.
How"s Kimmy?
She"s doing good. She"s good.
Her father"s got her this weekend.
Listen, BiII,
teII him to put a timer on his porch Iight.
I chased some kids out of there.
He rattIes around in that house.
I don"t know why he doesn"t seII it.
Is he seeing anyone?
I"m sure I don"t know.
I think Rhonda"s death
was reaIIy hard on Bob.
We aII take our knocks, don"t we?
Life goes on.
What"s with her?
It"s kind of a Iong story, but....
You see that tree?
I"II pick you up at a quarter to.
No.
WiII you stop?
I"II be here at a quarter of eight.
You better be ready.
I don"t want you spending your money--
I can"t hear you.
I"m putting on a dress, for your information.
I think his parents are very....
-Thank you.
-Happy birthday.
Wait.
It makes your wish come true.
Make a wish.
-Come here, birthday boy.
-Thank you.
You know what?
What?
I"m reaIIy proud of you tonight.
Why?
You haven"t tried to seII Iaundry detergent
to one person here.
I was gonna hit them up on the way out.
You"re the best thing
that"s ever happened to me, SheIIy.
Do you know that?
Don"t get aII mushy on me.
Come on.
Where?
No.
I don"t want to. I don"t think so.
Come on!
Watch me, okay?
Joseph SIoan.
SheIIy Soentpiet.
Steven SquaII.
It took me six years, but I finaIIy did it.
-I"m so proud of you.
-Thank you.
I wanted you to meet John.
Who"s John?
Hey, missy!
-We did it.
-Yeah.
Mom and Dad
are gonna take you to the restaurant.
I thought I Iost you there.
-Hi.
-CongratuIations.
Thanks. John, this is--
BiII Porter, of course. The '"boss.'"
It"s great to finaIIy meet you.
It"s nice to meet you, John.
Two degrees, isn"t he annoying?
You know what? We shouId go.
We"re gonna ride with John"s dad, right?
My foIks wiII take you over.
Okay.
Thanks for coming!
-We"II meet you at the restaurant.
-Okay.
-"Bye.
BiII, this is turning into a science project.
I don"t even know what that was.
Has John decided
which offer he"s going to take?
He"s Ieaning towards Bendix.
Where are they?
Chicago.
Chicago?
I know. I can"t even think about that.
When?
I don"t know.
Damn it!
What?
The '"B'" sticks.
Get rid of that thing.
We shouId get a computer.
I can"t afford a computer.
Yes, you can.
John couId get one reaI cheap.
We couId do everything on it.
I don"t Iike them.
We have eIectricity
and indoor pIumbing now, BiII.
We shouId just toss that piece of....
Hey, I did those aIready.
What?
The orders. I aIready did them. Here.
-Why?
-I had some time, so--
I do the orders.
I know that, but I just--
I do the order forms!
But it takes you so Iong,
I just thought that--
I don"t want you to do them.
AII right.
-I have my own way.
-AII right.
I have to read them,
so I have to write them.
You"re not heIping me, SheIIy.
If you think you"re heIping me, you"re not.
I"m sorry.
It"s just, I have a certain way.
I"m not taIking about the forms.
Thanks very much. I appreciate it.
Hey, BiII.
Chuck, congratuIations.
Thanks very much. Peter!
Peter.
I"d Iike you to meet BiII Porter.
-Peter Schaefer.
-Nice to meet you.
Peter"s taking over for me.
WeIcome to Watkins.
Thank you.
We"re gonna miss this guy.
Hey, Porter!
Excuse me.
What"s he do?
He"s a saIesman.
SeriousIy.
I am serious.
Did you see what happened to Frigidaire?
He"s a saIesman.
KeIvinator!
What, for us?
Whose idea was that?
Mine.
You are so....
If you made a doIIar a year for 5,000 years.
CongratuIations, Chuck.
Thanks, Tom.
And thanks everybody for 4# great years.
Thank you.
Chuck, you stay retired.
l don"t want to catch you over at Fuller.
OnIy if they pay me to fIy-fish.
...Iike Bardot. Maybe not exactIy, right?
But her Iips....
I take the Iid off, and she Ieans...
...over the couch to smeII the stuff,
and her robe kind of....
And I"m staring at two
of the most exquisite...
...perfectIy shaped, porceIain white ta-tas.
I Iook up, she"s smeIIing the stuff,
and I say to myseIf--
...Bill Porter.
It"s you! You won!
What?
SaIesman of the Year. Get up there.
Come on up here, Bill.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
We are so proud to have you
as a part of this company.
This past year, Bill had sales...
...of $42,460.
Bill Porter. Salesman of the Year!
l love being a salesman.
My father was a salesman.
l wish he could be here.
And my mother, who taught me...
...patience and persistence.
And who would never let me be ashamed.
l wish she could be here today.
Thank you.
Take it to that house over there, okay?
You got it? It"s not too heavy?
Wait, hoId on.
This is messed up.
BiII, you IabeIed that wrong.
It"s aII right.
No. You"ve got Bob at 825 EIm.
That"s CharIotte"s.
No, it"s aII right.
What do you want me to do with the box?
To Bob.
ShouId I change the IabeI?
-No.
-BiII!
CouId someone teII me
where to take this box?
PIease take it to that house.
Thank you, MicheIIe.
Okay.
Okay, fine. It"s wrong, but fine.
This must be yours.
BiII got the address wrong.
I"II just Ieave it right here.
Wait.
It"s just junk maiI,
but you might want it or whatever.
Want me to take this in the house for you?
Okay.
I got a waII there. This is better.
Larry took that down.
I see you get the barbecue sauce.
Yeah.
Have you tried the Iemon garIic?
No.
Is it good?
I don"t know. BiII says it is.
Put it on that tabIe.
Yes?
I"m Iooking for Mrs. SuIIivan.
Are you a friend of hers?
She"s a customer.
I"m with the Watkins Company.
I"m her daughter-in-Iaw.
GIadys passed away Iast week.
I didn"t know she was sick.
I"m sorry.
How did she die?
It was an accident.
Some kind of reaction
to the medication she was taking.
It was vodka and sIeeping piIIs.
Frank, they don"t know that.
Are you BiII Parker?
BiII Porter.
Come here. I want to show you something.
She taIked about you...
...a Iot.
Every year, at Christmas,
no matter what eIse we"d get...
...we"d get the Watkins spice coIIection...
...the soup bases, the Iiniment.
Dog biscuits....
Damn dog died years ago.
Excuse me.
Hey, BiII. What do you think?
Very nice, Richard.
It was supposed to have been done
months ago. You guys are up on two now.
Okay.
You got a card? You need a security card.
CouId you take your hat off, pIease, sir?
You got to do it fast.
Bingo!
Have a good one.
Pretty cooI, huh?
HeIIo, Peter. What is this?
This is aII the 800 number.
Makes us door-to-door guys
Iook Iike dinosaurs.
You know, each operator
is seIIing $#00 to $500 an hour.
They"re taking orders. They aren"t seIIing.
When you cash a check,
George Washington Iooks the same.
There"s CIark.
A Iot of the door-to-door guys
are moving over.
I"ve never done weII on the phone.
Women find my voice sexy,
and I think it distracts them.
You"re getting cIose to retirement anyway,
aren"t you?
Not reaIIy.
Where"s the door-to-door office?
I think it"s down there.
Thank you.
Is Rita here?
Rita? I don"t know Rita.
She runs the door-to-door division.
She"s gone, I think.
Who took her pIace?
I don"t know, man.
I was just toId to organize this stuff.
I need product cards for the new cataIogue.
Okay, cooI, no probIem.
No. I have the new cataIogue.
I need the product cards.
Okay, you know what?
I have no idea what that means.
But they"re probabIy here somewhere,
so just check in some of these boxes.
Race you.
No running, guys.
SIow down!
BiII!
Hi, guys.
Hi, BiII.
-Easy, guys, off the bed, pIease.
-No, that"s aII right.
-Guess what?
-What?
-You have to cIose your eyes.
-BiII doesn"t want--
No, that"s aII right. My eyes are cIosed.
Ready?
-So stupid.
-Okay, that"s enough.
-You can have it. It"s a present.
-I"m sure BiII wiII cherish that aIways.
Thank you.
MicheIIe, wiII you take them to the Iounge?
Get some juice out of the machine.
Got some money?
-"Bye, BiII.
-"Bye.
-They finaIIy caIIed us back.
-The insurance company?
Yep. They won"t budge.
They maintain that some
of your condition was pre-existing.
We can take them to arbitration.
I don"t know.
They"re digging up X-rays
from 10 years ago.
We"ve got to go after the bus company.
No.
With the deductibIe,
they"re onIy wiIIing to cover $22,000 of this.
John"s right, we have to sue.
It was my fauIt.
I was crossing in the middIe of the bIock.
It doesn"t matter.
Buses aren"t supposed to hit peopIe.
It wasn"t their fauIt.
Pedestrians have the right of way.
No.
Okay, fine!
Then you owe the hospitaI $18,000.
Which account do you want me
to take that out of?.
And it"s not over.
The insurance company"s covering haIf.
You"ve stiII got physicaI therapy,
and home care.
You"re Iooking at $40,000 to $50,000.
I"m gonna seII the house.
What?
It"s too big and it costs too much
to keep up.
Where are you gonna go?
SomepIace smaIIer.
I think we can settIe with the bus company.
No.
Just for expenses, out of court.
I"m gonna seII the house.
It"s the right thing to do.
Very funny, BiII.
Sorry.
It"s the equivaIent of eight boxes.
It"s super-concentrated.
It comes out to about three cents a Ioad.
But may I be candid?
It"s our best vaIue.
It"s most effective when used
with the coIor-fast bIeach...
...and the fabric softener.
They"re designed to work together.
Is the fabric softener scented?
I hate the scented.
I do, too. Ours is very miId.
It"s practicaIIy unscented.
Okay, wait! WiII you wait?
If you faII and break your neck,
I"m gonna break your neck.
It"s good to be here.
Yeah? Good, I"m gIad.
AII right, Iet me take your coat.
Look at that.
Do you Iike it?
Yeah.
Good. I figured that the couch
wouId be your base of operation...
...but if you want it somepIace different--
No, this is good.
Okay, good. I stocked you up.
Are you hungry?
I"m gonna make some soup.
No, you shouId get back to the kids.
I"m hungry.
I"m gonna make myseIf some soup.
SheIIy?
Yeah?
I"m going to have to Iet you go.
Go, where?
I can"t pay you,
at Ieast untiI I go back to work.
I knew you were gonna say that.
Don"t start with me, okay?
I can get around.
PIease.
What? I have to go to the kitchen...
...go to the bathroom...
...pretty much in that order.
I"II reduce my hours.
I can"t pay you.
You don"t have to.
BiII.
You"re unbearabIe.
AII right, fine.
I"m not your assistant. I"m your friend.
Your friend is gonna stop by every day
to say heIIo.
Now I"m gonna make
a friendIy bowI of soup.
Under the couch.
What?
Look under the couch.
InitiaI here.
And sign here.
CongratuIations.
The market"s been so fIat these days,
I"m very happy you got your price.
Why wouId a corporation want this house?
Investment property.
I think it"s a tax thing.
What"s the name of the corporation?
The name isn"t--
That"s my fauIt. I got the name wrong.
I"II fiII that in Iater.
Good news.
I"II be the Ieasing agent on this house.
-Have you found a pIace yet?
-No.
I was thinking maybe you couId
Iease this back. Just stay here.
How much wouId the rent be?
What wouId you feeI comfortabIe with?
Do you think l"m stupid?
Do I think? I know you"re stupid.
I don"t want charity.
It"s not charity. It"s an investment.
Then why didn"t you teII me?
Why do you think?
I am not going to Iet you buy my house.
It"s too Iate.
Because you signed the papers.
BiII, wait.
You deceived me. You treat me Iike a chiId.
I do not.
I treat you Iike someone I care about...
...someone who"s important to me.
You"re part of my famiIy.
No, SheIIy. You have a famiIy.
I hired you,
and you treat me with disrespect.
You treat me Iike a crippIe.
You are a crippIe! An emotionaI crippIe!
NormaI peopIe heIp each other, BiII.
You"re so hung up on your independence.
'"I don"t need anybody.'"
Yeah, Iike that"s normaI.
That doesn"t make you normaI, BiII.
That makes you a freak!
You don"t want our heIp, fine!
Then be out of the house in #0 days.
Do you want me to caII you a cab?
I"m caIIing you a cab.
God!
Whatever you wanna do.... That"s great.
AII right. Good.
Yeah, I think that"II be possibIe.
Yeah, that"s aII right.
...the whole lnternet right at my fingertips.
...the news is breaking, l"ve got lnternet.
l could stay a little closer to my family.
You"ve got mail.
America Online. Easy to use.
Friendly menus.
-Put in the disk, click, you"re online.
-We"ve been working night and day....
-You finished, hon?
-CouId be.
-Anything eIse?
-No. Just the check.
-You a saIesman?
-No. I"m a dinosaur.
-You"re a dancer?
-Yeah, I"m a dancer.
Disco, mostIy.
You go, boy.
Sorry, I didn"t know which apartment.
-You"re BiII Porter, right?
-Yes.
Hi, I"m Joey WaIIace. Portland Daily News.
-Hi.
-Sorry I scared you there.
Guess we"re even.
How do you mean?
You scared me when I was a IittIe kid,
remember? You had that hand puppet.
KyIe PyIe.
WaIIace. #62 Chestnut.
You"ve got an amazing memory.
It"s very impressive. May I?
No, I have to go....
I"II get right to the point, then.
I want to write a story
about a door-to-door saIesman.
Last of a dying....
Loss of a tradition.
It wouIdn"t necessariIy
have to be just about you.
Thank you, but, no.
Take my card, then.
If you change your mind.
I guess this is where I"m supposed
to pIant my foot...
...try to keep you
from cIosing the door on me.
No, don"t do that. That never works.
I have to go.
That"s the kind of thing
I thought we couId taIk about.
Can I come in?
Nice. Love what you"ve done
with the pIace.
Very funny, SheIIy. What do you want?
There were three boxes
that were never deIivered.
What shouId I do with them?
Can you deIiver them for me?
You want me to heIp you?
I"II pay you.
I see, so that"s how it works.
Forget it. I"II take care of it myseIf.
Shut up. Of course I"II deIiver the boxes.
I"II take care of it, I said.
Fine. They"re in my car.
I"II Ieave them by the front door.
You quit your job.
You"re a ceIebrity.
I said no. I didn"t want him to write that.
Listen, BiII.
I"ve been thinking about the fight we had.
Maybe I said some things....
Then you go and quit your job.
I just thought--
No. We both said things.
And the job....
It was time.
What are you gonna do?
I"m gonna take up kickboxing.
It"s a nice articIe. You shouId read it.
l never really took notice,
until he wasn"t there anymore.
This odd man with the funny walk
and the briefcase, and his hat set just so.
One day, he just stopped coming.
Man, my chiIbIains are kiIIing me.
These hands are so dry. Tried everything.
He was a thread...
...an invisible thread in our neighborhood...
...which tied us together...
...bringing us news:
Who died...
...who moved away...
...who just got married.
He"s a door-to-door salesman
for the Watkins Company...
...who many considered unemployable.
Mr. Porter, that was a wonderfuI articIe
in the paper.
I didn"t want that.
Is Peter in?
Hi, BiII. It was a great articIe in the paper.
I didn"t want him to write that.
Hey, BiII, how you doing?
Can I taIk to you?
I was just heading out. What"s up?
I want my territory back, Peter.
We"ve shut that department down.
There is no more door-to-door.
I don"t need a department. AII I need is--
BiII, you did the right thing.
You had an amazing run.
It"s over. Retire. Go fishing, enjoy yourseIf.
I don"t want to go fishing. I wanna work.
There must be something you can do.
Have you checked
with the empIoyment office?
CarIa, I"m gonna be gone untiI 2:#0.
If StickIey caIIs--
Peter! Don"t run off. I need two minutes.
Great seeing you, BiII. Best of Iuck to you.
WonderfuI piece in the paper, BiII.
I"d Iike to put a copy of it
in the sharehoIder"s report.
What do I care? I"m going fishing.
What piece in the paper?
Get off the bus.
A salesman drives down
a dark country road...
...completely lost.
After a time, he runs out of gas.
Luckily, there"s a farmhouse
just down the road.
He goes to the farmhouse
and knocks on the door.
The farmer"s wife comes to the door
and says, ""Can l help you?""
""Yes, "" he says, ""you can.
""l"ve run out of gas, and l"ve lost my way. ""
I"II bet you anything.... Try this.
That the cream you"ve been using
has an aIcohoI base.
She says, ""You can spend the night. ""
Put some of this on your fingers.
TeII me if your wife wouIdn"t enjoy this.
""But l don"t have a daughter...
""...and you"ll have a nice room
all to yourself.
""We don"t have any farm animals. ""
AII right, Bob, I"m gonna bring you
some of the sampIes next week.
That"s fine, BiII. But, no promises.
Don"t worry.
""My husband and l are happily married. ""
A beautifuI day.
Have a good one, BiII.
The salesman looks around confused...
...and then he turns back
to the farmer"s wife and says:
""Gosh. l must be in the wrong joke! ""