Top that off for you, honey?
There you go.
What's in the case?
I'm sorry?
You're always lugging that case
around. I'm curious, what do you sell?
I'm in restaurant supplies.
I'm sorry, I didn't get your name.
You must travel a lot, huh?
Whole country or just hereabouts?
- I don't mean to be rude, but...
- How's your wife feel about it?
- What?
- She must get lonely...
...you gone all the time.
- Look, I...
- Do you get lonely?
You miss fucking her, Harold?
Look, I don't know who you are,
but you can't just sit down...
Did it myself.
Kind of a hobby.
Take a look at these pictures...
...and you tell me if you see
anything you want.
I've got lots more.
Would you like to see them?
Tell me, the jokes about the salesman
and the farmer's daughter, they true?
Here. This one's my favourite!
Really says it all.
Wouldn't you agree?
You are sick.
It's a matter of opinion.
There's a rest stop next off-ramp.
Pull into it.
- I have money, it's not a lot...
- Nobody wants your money.
Just pull in.
Why?
Because I wouldn't wanna do this
at 70 miles an hour.
Could be dangerous.
Agent Mackelway.
Welcome to Albuquerque.
Rick Charleton.
Miss Payton's
the nice girl at the front desk.
She puts together a package
for all the new agents.
Everything you need to know
about the area...
...help with finding apartments
and such.
- This one's yours.
- Okay.
- Gonna get it all set up for you.
- All right.
Not that different from Dallas, is it?
No, sir.
If you need anything, just yell.
Thanks.
I'm Tom, guys.
- Nice to meet you, Tom. Don here.
- Hello.
- I'm Bill.
- Hey, Bill. Tom.
Tom, do you like Frito pies?
I don't know, Bill.
I don't know what they are.
Welcome to the minors.
Here, let me do that.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Don't know how to make coffee.
- That's okay. It takes some experience.
Isn't there a Starbucks around here?
- That's a joke, right?
- Yeah. Yeah, that's a joke.
So you're Mackelway?
Yeah, Agent Mackelway.
Katie Payton.
A fax is coming in for you.
It's the room next door.
- Really? Fax for me?
- Yeah.
Okay. Thank you.
- No problem. Nice meeting you.
- Yep.
Mackelway...
...you gonna stand around all day,
or you wanna do something?
No, sir.
Afternoon, Rick.
Looks like a robbery-homicide.
- Body is back over there.
- You run the plates?
Fellow's name is Harold Speck,
travelling salesman from T or C.
T or C?
Truth or Consequences.
It's a town, slick.
I'll write that down.
Hey!
- What the fuck are you doing?
- What's it look like, bud?
You ever heard of
evidentiary procedure?
Icarus case number 690.
Physicians in charge,
Dr. Galin J. Peterson...
...and Dr. Ferdinand Kovoskis.
Theta-wave entrainment
for RV subject O'Ryan...
...to be used with GPS
for target management.
Session to commence in...
...five, four...
...three, two...
...one.
Target number, write it now.
Focus.
Stay objective.
Smells like clove.
Okay.
Describe. Describe it.
Short, one word.
One word.
Draw the environment.
One target at a time.
Draw the environment now.
Sir.
Sort of a stickler for procedure.
I imagine you would be.
Christ.
See it.
See it, draw it now.
Draw it now.
Shoes are on the wrong feet.
All American Diner,
Gallup, New Mexico.
- Passed that on the way here.
- He had breakfast there this morning.
Startling off the bottom of the inning,
Barry Matthews.
Got on base with a line-drive
single his last at bat.
And he takes the first pitch
high and inside for ball one.
Looked like Leonard was trying
to get the breaking pitch inside...
...but it just didn’t have
any break on it that time.
Agent Mackelway,
we're over here.
I was gonna introduce you two, but I
understand that won't be necessary.
Seems your former office
decided we needed help...
...so they sent us Agent Kulok.
- Hey, Tom.
- Hi, Fran.
I guess we're gonna skip
the tearful reunion.
Have a seat, Tom.
How are things in Dallas?
Wouldn't really know.
I've been chained to a desk.
Okay, what do we know?
Picked up a footprint in the back seat.
A size and a half bigger than Speck's.
Okay.
Wounds on Speck's throat indicate
he was strangled from behind.
I think our guy was waiting
for him in the back seat...
...sprung this on him
once the car was moving.
Lab picked up talcum traces
along the edges...
...consistent with powdered gloves.
So he gets this dropped in his lap...
...it spooks him,
car ends up in the ravine.
That car was pushed
to the state line.
The depth of the tire tracks...
...footprints near the embankment.
That car wasn't going
more than 3 miles an hour...
...and it stopped literally
on the state line.
Guy must have used GPS.
Why would he push it
to the state line?
Same reason he did everything else,
to get the FBI's undivided attention.
There's an association here.
You have a circle...
...and a lidless eye that's always open.
Seeing.
Or making sure that we're seeing.
It's just a feeling.
He was a normal guy.
You know, kind of quiet.
He liked to read fishing magazines,
and he wasn't much of a tipper.
- Is that a lousy thing to say?
- No, it's fine.
Could you tell us
about the other man?
Like I said,
I never really saw him.
Harold came up complaining
about the guy...
...but by the time I turned
around, he was gone.
- Can you desc...?
- Desc-
- Can you describe him, ma'am?
- Oh, sure.
You could tell he wasn't
from around here.
Did you see what he was driving?
You know, now that you mention it...
...there's a Torino out in the parking
lot with a real crappy paint job.
It's been here since last night.
We need a protocol
for interviewing witnesses.
Fine. I'll handle it.
Always in control.
Tell you something, Tom...
...I want my life back,
so I want this over quick.
So, what happened?
Your ring.
It didn't work out...
...just like us.
So why are you here?
You vacationing in Albuquerque?
Oh, Tom, you sure haven't changed
in six whole months.
Keys are in the car.
I don't need a babysitter...
...so let's do it right this time.
Then don't make things so
unnecessarily complicated again.
- Trunk's ajar.
- You listening to me?
You think I wanna be down here?
I'm not interested in hanging out...
...and I'm not your babysitter.
I'm your partner.
I didn't put you here, remember.
And I'm not going through
this again with you.
Holy shit.
A circle with a slash.
- Dispatch.
- I need help down here.
- What's your 20?
- The All American Diner in Gallup.
Hey, Tom, got an iD on our body.
Barney Fulcher, age 50...
...sixth-grade teacher from Colorado.
These plates aren't gonna help.
Forget them. This guy started
in Oklahoma, left these for us.
Mrs. Speck...
...I just heard.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know him well, but I think
Harold was a more complex person...
...than people realize.
He was, wasn't he?
I'm really sorry
for your loss, ma'am.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
So it wasn't Fulcher's car?
Car was registered to
a Daniel Dyson...
...runs a halfway house
In Oklahoma City.
Dyson?
Daniel Dyson?
Hello?
Fucking freak!
What a fucking freak.
Can I help you?
Why didn't you report it as stolen?
The truth is, I always hated that car.
Nobody but Benjamin
could ever make it run right.
Is that his name, Benjamin?
It's hard to say.
That's what he liked to be called.
This bad wiring.
I think we've got an
obsessive-compulsive here.
I'll call Grieves. Get him to work up
a list of behaviourists for us to talk to.
Give me that.
Excuse me.
These came from Benjamin?
He used to spend hours down here.
It was like... Like his office.
What are these?
With those numbers and pictures,
he said he could find anybody.
Benjamin O'Ryan?
Special Agent Benjamin O'Ryan, FBI.
It was his fantasy.
Oh, fuck.
Agent Mackelway, what the fuck
were you thinking?
He's got nine murders in his pocket,
and he's gonna walk.
Hey, Starkey.
What made you think you could
cross the border into Mexico...
...without an extradition order?
I knew he was gonna
disappear into Mexico.
You knew?
Agent Mackelway, you have shamed
and vilified this bureau...
...with your methods.
I have no choice but to recommend
you be suspended...
...for a period of six months...
...during which you'll undergo
a psychological evaluation.
Let the record show that the case
against Agent Fran Kulok is pending.
Turn it off!
I guess you guys are never
unaccounted for, huh?
This guy really likes you.
This is O'Ryan's room.
Tom.
You got it?
Yeah, I got it.
It's Agent Kulok. Can you run this
number and iD the subscriber for me?
- You're breaking up, Fran.
- Hold on. Let me get outside, hold on.
Thank you.
Ever see a 50-foot shark?
I'm sorry?
A 50-foot shark. You ever see one?
No.
Doesn't mean there aren't any.
Excuse me, sir,
did you know him?
The guy with the Torino, O'Ryan,
the guy who lived upstairs?
Why? Is he dead?
- I don't know.
- You said "did."
- Is he dead?
- Oh, no. I'm sorry. I misspoke.
You ever seen this before?
It's a circle with a slash
through it.
It's not a circle.
It's a zero.
And how do you know that?
Did he tell you that?
Why are you whistling?
What does that mean?
Have you seen this, sir?
Circle with a slash through it.
Have you seen that?
A circle with a slash through it?
Circle with a slash through it.
Take a look.
Have you seen a circle
with a slash through it?
Benjamin O'Ryan? Sir?
A circle with a slash through it?
Benjamin O'Ryan.
He was here seven years.
- Tom?
- What?
We got a trace. Faxes and Things,
Sleeper, Missouri. Come on.
Come on.
I'll have a 7 &7 please.
Got some iD?
It's in the car. No one's asked me
for it for a couple of years now.
Nothing personal, honey.
Excuse me...
...you forgot this.
- Oh, I don't have...
Kiss it!
Hey.
Hey, hey!
Fuck you.
You fuck.
Hi.
Turn around.
Turn around!
- Ma'am?
- FBI.
Excuse me.
Do your parents know?
Tom.
You got an iD?
- What?
- Raymond Starkey.
- Starkey did this?
- Tom, Starkey's the guy on the ground.
You son of a bitch...
...why are you baiting me?
You want me
to see what you see.
You want me to see.
I'm trying to see it.
- He opens up an old wound.
- Yeah.
- What does he want?
- I don't know.
Maybe he's got something
against law enforcement...
...like the Zodiac.
"You're welcome, Tom.
You're welcome, Tom."
Not FBI. Tom. He's baiting me.
He wants me.
Why? What does he want?
Okay.
Tom, I want you to take me
through this.
Explain this to me.
Okay. See if this makes sense
to you, okay?
Each of the 45 abduction dates
on these faxes correspond...
...to one of the GPS coordinates
on O'Ryan's map.
- What about the two bodies we iD'd?
- Okay. Well, let's find the faxes.
Here we go.
Male victim.
Last seen, Trenton, New Jersey.
Okay. Found in Dyersville, Iowa.
Okay. Female.
Last seen, Dayton, Ohio.
Found in Brownsville, Texas.
So we have two bodies...
...that were found 1000 miles
from where they were last seen.
What's this?
- That's Tucumcari, New Mexico.
- Why blue?
That's the only city where the date on
the fax and the map didn't correspond.
Date of disappearance: Christmas.
On O'Ryan's map, 8-27.
The only thing we know is there
never was a Benjamin O'Ryan, FBI.
He would have made
a hell of an agent.
Autopsy reports just arrived
for both the new positive iDs.
- Bruises?
- No, they're burn marks.
We've got them here too
on our female from Dayton.
And these marks relate to the marks
found on Fulcher and Speck how?
They don't. There were no burn marks
on Speck, Fulcher or Starkey.
And we have no slash-circles
here on these bodies.
Right.
My office, as soon as someone
finds something useful.
No luck on
the behavioural specialists.
I do have a couple other leads
that I'm following up on.
- I'm hopeful they're gonna pan out.
- Great, thank you.
A professor of criminal biology,
Professor Daitz, just called.
He says he's got time
for you on Saturday.
Thank you, Katie.
I was operating under the assumption
that O'Ryan was somebody's fantasy.
Oh, no, he's real.
He was a student of mine.
That fax you sent me,
this circle with the slash through it?
That's his construct, his theory.
He called it "Suspect Zero."
Suspect Zero?
He posited a theory
that a serial killer...
...could cross the entire country
without ever getting caught.
What makes a killer catchable?
Patterns, repetition of behaviour.
He imagined someone
with no patterns...
...no telltale fetishes, no rituals...
...just a random killing machine
that never leaves a clue.
But a serial killer by definition
is condemned to repetition.
I mean, isn't that
what he's all about?
Well, he is until he isn't.
And this Suspect Zero, is that
something that you believe in, doctor?
It's something O'Ryan believed in.
He swore guys like that existed,
only we couldn't see them...
...because they didn't obey
the usual laws, like cancer doesn't...
...or the HIV virus that
tricks your immune system...
...into thinking it isn't there.
So you're saying a guy
like that could exist?
Do you know the definition
of a black hole?
Not precisely, no.
It's a celestial body
with a gravitational force so strong...
...that nothing escapes it.
Not even light.
Well, then how do you find
something you can't see?
Well, it was there and we found it.
Why do you think O'Ryan is convinced
a person like that is around?
In this time and place.
What about a split personality?
Could you have a stone-cold
killer on one hand...
...and a thoughtful man
with a conscience on the other?
I mean, could O'Ryan...
...possibly be this Suspect Zero?
Yeah.
It's a viable theory.
I mean, the point is, I don't think you're
gonna know until you find O'Ryan.
Point is, I don't think you're
Just a random killing machine
that never leaves a clue.
Yes, Lord. Yes, Lord.
Sing it, Lord.
Everybody inside.
On the double, let's go.
Come on. Keep moving.
Storm's coming.
Get inside!
Come on in, right now! Girls!
Come in, now. It's starting to rain,
and I don't want you out there alone.
Turn around!
- Fran.
- Hi.
- Fran, I need some help.
- You're so wet. Are you okay?
Yeah, Fran, I need
somebody to talk to.
It's driving me crazy.
Listen to me.
There's Speck, a small-town
New Mexico travelling salesman.
Fulcher, a schoolteacher
from Boulder and then Starkey.
I got a lock on him. It's just there's
something missing, and I can't...
It's okay.
Why don't you come in.
No, come out. Get dressed.
We're right on the edge
of this thing, come on.
Come here. Come here.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
You gotta keep calm, okay?
Fran...
I've been having these dreams.
I've been seeing things again...
...and I don't know what they mean.
Come inside, Tom. Come in.
No, I can't.
I almost have it, Fran.
I'm worried about you.
I love you, Fran.
I love you.
Mrs. Speck, did your husband
keep any chemicals?
Did he have any unusual hobbies?
Did he...?
Was he an avid photographer?
- Did he have an interest in sewing?
- No, why?
I'm taking your time. I'm sorry
to ask you these questions.
I'm sorry I don't have more time, Agent
Mackelway, but it's my PTA day.
I'm sorry. I should have called.
I wish I could've helped you.
I'm FBI.
Yeah, I'll bet.
What the hell is that?
We managed to identify the remains
of 10 of the 21 victims found...
...In the attic of Harold A. Speck...
...the travelling salesman
from Truth or Consequences.
They were mostly teenagers.
More than half were runaways.
The revelation that Speck
was a serial killer...
...led us to examine
Barney Fulcher...
...the victim that Agent Kulok and I
found at the All American Diner.
After an extensive search of his home,
we found the remains of nine people...
...mostly boys between
the ages of 9 and 14.
The last victim, Raymond Starkey...
...who vanished after his acquittal
six months ago, we all know about.
For some reason, this man is
Identifying and targeting serial killers.
Not necessarily. We got two
other bodies from Santa Fe...
...so killers aren't his only victims.
We don't know those bodies
had anything to do with O'Ryan.
Stick to what we know.
He's a transient with mental illness.
He also happens to think
he's a former agent of this bureau.
I want this man apprehended now.
Swung on and missed. Strike two.
Here's the wind-up.
Swung on and missed. Strike three.
Even though he hit over .300
his previous three seasons...
...It wasn't until last year that
he made the all-star team.
Sergeant, copy that.
Possible stolen vehicle.
We are checking NCIC
for warrants.
Good afternoon.
Afternoon, officer.
See your driver's license, sir?
Of course.
Is there a problem?
- Can I see your registration, please?
- Sure.
You mind stepping out
of the car, please?
I'm carrying something that could
be construed as a weapon.
I'd like to hand it over so you won't
think I'm trying to conceal anything.
What kind of weapon, sir?
A hunting knife,
right here on my hip.
On my way to the woods.
My gear's in the trunk.
Would you like me to hand it to you?
I don't know what the procedure is.
Take the weapon off your hip, place it
on the ground, kick it towards me.
Happy to.
What exactly were you
planning on hunting?
A 50-foot shark.
- I used to be in law enforcement too.
- Is that right?
FBI. Of course, that was
some years ago now.
Psy ops, strictly classified.
Are you on any type of medication,
or have you been drinking today?
- Sir?
- I'm sorry.
I just found myself wondering
what was inside that truck.
Sir, I'm gonna ask you to hand me
the keys to your vehicle, please.
- Fran?
- Yeah?
O'Ryan was here.
Damn it, O'Ryan was here.
He left that in my jacket.
Don't do this again, Tom. Don't.
Tom, don't do this.
You're gonna help me.
You're gonna help me turn it off.
Nobody told me how to turn it off.
- And you're gonna help me turn it off.
- You're here.
Help me turn it off.
Icarus began as a means
of gathering military intelligence.
But its applications in the world of law
enforcement are proving promising.
The reason you men are sitting here is
because you've all fit into the profile...
...that best suits a remote viewer.
You've been selected
and evaluated...
...based on recurrent symptoms
of elevated dream activity...
...migraine headaches, tinnitus...
...and your psy test results.
Target reference number.
One- seven...
...four-six. Go.
Don't close your eyes.
Don't think.
Focus on the target.
Everyone is gonna wind up
with severe psychological trauma.
You're high
or genius-level intelligence...
...unmarried, with no record
of long or serious relationships.
- The fear.
- And you're all obsessive...
...In nature.
- Describe the person.
Don't stop the pen from moving.
This girl’s afraid.
She's afraid.
Afraid. You're becoming emotionally
entrained with the victim.
Collection process.
It is not meant to be an experience.
You're gonna help me.
You're gonna help me turn it off.
Nobody's told us
how to turn it off...
...and you're gonna help me
turn it off.
Help me turn it off.
You're gonna help me.
Turn it off.
Icarus began as a means of
gathering military intelligence...
...but its applications
In the world of law enforcement...
...are proving promising
In several different areas.
These are areas which you
will be involved in your studies...
...and, as you've been advised, they're
classified top-secret and confidential.
FBI profile 6765031.
Icarus case number 754.
Physicians in charge,
Dr. Galin J. Peterson...
...and Dr. Ferdinand Kovoskis.
Audio enhancer
for remote viewer O'Ryan.
Session to commence in...
...five, four...
...three, two...
...one.
Focus.
Target number, write it now.
One target at a time.
Stay objective.
Do not identify with the victim.
Charlie?
Charlie!
Charlie?!
Charlie!!
Here they are, Mackelway.
Look.
No, I won't tell! No, please!
Shut it off for me!
You got one of those pins in Deming?
O'Ryan was spotted there yesterday.
He took a squad car and a sidearm
off a highway patrolman.
About an hour later a 5-year-old boy
was abducted a mile up the interstate.
We also found the bodies of two
females in a Dumpster off the highway.
Your boy's been busy.
We're establishing a perimeter
around the city.
Was the patrolman hurt?
- What's the difference?
- He wasn't, was he?
He was fine. The girls in
the Dumpster had fatal injuries.
O'Ryan's not the guy.
He's chasing the guy
or that patrolman would be dead.
Can I ship this guy back to Dallas?
O'Ryan was FBI, you ever
heard of a project called Icarus?
- No.
- Have you?
It's agents trained
to see distant locations...
...using only the mind.
They call it remote viewing.
Bureau stole it from the Army.
They use it to track down
serial killers.
What? You don't believe me?
It's bullshit? It's voodoo?
It worked.
They made a science of it.
That's how he drew this.
He'd never been in this house...
...he just saw what was there.
The bureau taught him...
...and he's using it to track
Suspect Zero.
You know what?
I'm extremely tired of that term.
Profile the guy.
He's straight out of Quantico.
He's working like we would.
He's not kidnapping,
he's chasing the guy...
...that's doing the kidnapping.
Look at the map.
Okay.
What you're telling me is all these
abductions are the work of one guy.
Yes.
Mac, do you realize
how insane that is?
Fran, please help me.
He's not listening to me.
Tom, I'm not sure that you're seeing
things very clearly right now.
Tom...
...let's just try something
that actually makes sense.
This guy sends in these faxes.
He picks off three scumbags. Why?
So that we'll think what you're
thinking, that we got a friend.
Somebody who's willing to take out
the trash for us, and it's horseshit.
What if it isn't?
What if there is a Suspect Zero, and
O'Ryan's the one guy who's got a shot?
For fuck's sake, Mackelway. When did
you start buying into this guy?
Well, he's smarter than we are.
Speak for yourself.
I'm going to Deming.
You can take the rest of the day off.
I'll be damned.
- Kulok here.
- Hey.
- Where are you?
- I'm headed towards Tucumcari.
Listen, those marks on the bodies,
could they be freezer burns?
Let me get into this.
Yeah.
There's crystallization because
the blood never clotted. Freezer burn.
He keeps the bodies in a freezer
and buries them 1000 miles apart?
- Hey, Tom, what's going on?
- I got a possible suspect.
That kid's been a brat all morning.
I turned around...
See what you caused?
Are you afraid?
It'd be custom here at this point
to start praying. I see a lot of that.
Haven't heard too many
answers though.
You're alone.
Come on. Are you afraid?
- Where's the boy?
- My, my!
Must be extremely satisfying to hear
yourself say something so heroic.
I'm almost envious.
The boy's in pieces
under the bed.
Now are you afraid?
I know what you're thinking, "Pain
is coming. Will I take it like a man."
Let me put you at ease, you won't.
None of them do. Men, women,
children, they all weep, they all beg.
They pass out, piss themselves,
attempt negotiations.
You wouldn't believe how many men
I've seen where you are.
Grown men with wives
and children at home...
...offering sexual gratification for a
five-minute reprieve. It's pathetic.
Are you afraid?
When they realize there's nothing left
to negotiate, and they're helpless...
Well, the look in their eyes,
the level of surrender...
...it's almost pornographic.
I put that mirror here because
I didn't want you to miss it.
Are you afraid?
- Look in the mirror.
- Are you afraid?
Look in the mirror, O'Ryan.
- Hey, you, fucking Mackelway.
- Look at yourself, look in the mirror.
- Are you afraid, Mackelway?
- Look at yourself.
- Are you afraid?!
- No, I'm not afraid.
Open your eyes!
Open your eyes, goddamn it...
...or I'll cut the fucking lids off!
- Then cut the fucking lids off!
The initiation used to be more civil.
I'm sorry about that.
You're part of it now.
There were five of us, you know.
The most skilled...
...technical remote viewers
on Project Icarus.
You come in in the morning, have a
cup of coffee, talk about the Yankees.
You go to your room
with your pen...
...and your pad of paper,
always alone.
You try and lock in,
you crank out an ideogram.
Son of Sam,
John Wayne Gacy, Ted Bundy.
He might be driving his car,
having a beer, brushing his teeth...
...cutting someone's eyes out.
If you did it right,
you got it all.
The way it sounded,
the way it smelled.
Those people were looking right
up at you, begging you for mercy.
It was like being God.
But, of course, you're not God.
Can't do a thing for them.
They wired us into this current,
the five of us...
...darkness, the pit itself.
We were plugged right into it,
and no one taught us how to turn it off.
We saw things men shouldn't see.
Agony...
...torture...
...evil.
It never shut off.
I checked once
with all the guys that'd...
...been on the project when it
was just used for intel.
You know, finding gun-runners
and drug lords, Soviet missile sites...
...even the iran hostages.
Anyway, I checked with them,
and they're all okay.
But the five of us...
...plugged into the brains and
nervous systems of human beings...
...that's when we lost it.
We're all either dead
or institutionalised.
After a while, those conversations
about the Yankees became impossible.
O'Ryan.
Those faxes...
...the missings...
...how many of them are his?
All of them.
You were the missing piece, Mac.
Now everything is in place.
All you have to do is finish it.
This is Mackelway.
I'm travelling north, approaching
l-54 at Tucumcari, request backup.
I'm pursuing a possible suspect
in a refrigerated truck.
Brake!
Hey, Tom!
- Tom!
- Get the trailer open!
There's a kid in the trailer.
Hey, buddy.
You okay?
I got you, okay?
Okay, come here.
I got you.
- Get an ambulance.
- Yes, ma'am.
I knew I was right about you.
No. No, that wasn't me.
Of course it was you.
Wasn't me. Wasn't the wind.
You beat him to death.
Now all you have to do
is finish it. Finish it!
Understand, none of this
was arbitrary.
We were chosen, you and I.
It's not a bad start, Mac.
You made the world a little safer.
We made justice.
- This wasn't justice.
- Yes, it was!
And so is this.
I'm not going to kill you, O'Ryan.
You already have.
I've seen it a thousand times.
- No, you saw wrong.
- That's impossible!
I saw us here. I saw all of it!
Me baiting you, testing you!
Look at him!
You've arrived!
You're cursed, like me...
...only you keep running from it!
You hear things, you see things...
...that's why you can't sleep.
Why your head always aches.
Get up.
There is no Zero.
You're confused, old man.
Can't you see that?
You think we did something
mythical here today?
You think we put an end to evil?
We killed a deviant, that's all.
There are thousands
of them out there.
O'Ryan, you're a guy with a skill.
You're not God.
You can't see everything.
You don't decide what's justice.
Freeze!
Please, Mac.
I can't sleep anymore.
I keep seeing all those faces.
The ones I couldn't save.
All those missings.
You know, they never blink.
They're all in here.
I want you to shut it off for me.
Please, Mac, I'm so tired.
I just want you to shut it off for me.
Shut it off for me.
I can't.
I'm not you.
Yet.
So tired.
Thank you.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group