I want to tell you about the craziest
white man I ever met.
We go way back, Eddie and me.
Met in the army.
Hadn't heard from him in a while
before l got his postcard.
Never been to visit before.
Postcard says you were
bringing me a surprise.
ls that it?
- Yeah.
- I appreciate it, Eddie.
I really do.
Always loved that bike.
l'm sorry it broke down.
Hey, it's an old Indian,
just like me.
It's not the end of the world.
What are you gonna do, kill yourself?
That's what I'm here for, Johnny.
Postcard didn't say
when you were coming...
so I lit a fire last night.
Smoke told me when you'd be here.
- I've been watching for you.
- You know why I came to see you?
I got a pretty good idea, amigo.
What good did we do?
Nothing!
We used to do it real good, Johnny.
Killing.
The memories--
they haunt me, Johnny.
Haunt me, Johnny!
That's why you got the medal, Eddie.
Hey.
l had this dream about the Devil.
He reserved a whole floor of hell...
just for me.
What do you think about that?
Tell me more about your dream.
Oh, my dream.
l think about it a lot.
Checking out!
Enough.
That's why l'm here, Johnny--
to kill myself.
l need your okay.
l need your okay, man.
You know?
Eddie...
you may not need my okay.
Look at this. Look at this!
He could have killed me.
What the fuck is wrong with this guy?
Hey, you ! Cycle man!
What in the hell
are you shooting at, boy?
- You damn near killed us back there.
- Leave me alone.
- I don't want any trouble.
- What l think you need to do, son...
is apologize to me and my brothers
for almost killing us.
Hey, Johnny!
What do you think?
- Maybe they can do it.
- Who the fuck are you talking to?
My best friend.
l'll tell you what, mister.
Why don't you just give us
this here motorcycle...
and maybe me and my brothers will just
forget about this whole incident.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's a gift for my friend.
Hey.
You really shouldn't be driving
the way you are, mister.
Please. Leave me alone.
And you, get off of my bike.
Whatever you say, chief.
So sorry, man.
Come on !
Get you some!
- You can do it.
- Get up.
Yeah !
Look at that.
I'm fresh out.
Hey, there's a car coming.
Wait. Slow down, Vern.
Wait a minute.
Vern, slow down.
Somebody is in trouble.
Yeah, and it's none
of our business.
Vern, they're gonna kill him.
- lt's just Vern and Dottie.
- They ain't gonna say nothing.
-They better not.
-l don't want trouble with the Hogans...
and if you're smart,
you'Il keep your mouth shut too.
- l'm putting this in the damn truck.
- I'll give you a hand.
- You make sure he's dead first.
- Give me the gun, Petey.
- Petey, give him the gun.
- l can do it, Matt.
You go on.
l can do it, all right?
- All right, Jess. Let him do it.
- Don't miss.
- Come on, hurry up, man.
- What are you waiting for?
- Let's go!
- l'm sorry, mister.
- Damn! l didn't think he had it in him.
- Me neither.
Come on.
Thanks, Buddy.
- Where's Dottie today?
- Late, as usual.
Oh. Well, could you give her
these for me?
- What's that?
- These.
Oh, Buddy, that is so sweet.
- She's really gonna like those.
- Really?
WelI, Rhonda, do you think
Dottie would go out with me?
She likes you, Buddy.
Why don't you ask her?
All right. l will.
l better get my ass in gear...
or they're gonna discontinue the run.
There's one passenger out there,
and it's military. Half price.
Oh, could you teIl her
I'm sorry l missed her?
- Sure wiIl.
- See you, Pop.
It's not my turn.
l paid last time.
What do you say you sit on my lap
and we talk about...
the first thing that pops up?
Let's split this hole.
Keep the change, sweet thing.
Ow! Give me frostbite.
- You're late.
- The shortcut through the dry lake...
we saw this poor boy
getting the mess beat out of him...
- by the Hogans, and I think--
- We saw a flying saucer. Unbelievable!
Please. Please!
Just start fiIling
the ketchup bottles.
And Buddy left these for you, Dottie.
- lsn't he sweet?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
l thought you said
they cancelled his run.
Look what he got me, Vern.
Says here the army may be
conducting maneuvers around here.
Army's not coming, Pop...
and the flyboys have gone too.
Should have sold this place
when l was a kid--
before they put in the interstate.
Here's a fresh cup, Mr. Early.
Oh, thank you, Rhonda.
Thank you.
My Bertie should be here
any time now.
She's been away
finding me a job as a handyman.
She should be here any time.
Any time.
l wish you'd teach me some patience,
Mr. Early.
Oh, Rhonda, patience is always there
waiting for you.
Well, that is good to hear.
You know, Bertie is gone three years
now, and he is stilI waiting.
He's my kind of guy.
Little old for you, isn't he?
- Way to go, Petey, man.
- We didn't think you had it in you.
Two shots in the head.
That's my littIe brother.
- Ain't no big deal.
- l wonder where that son of a bitch...
was from-- what planet.
Petey, what's that thing worth,
that .45?
- Four hundred, maybe more.
- All right. Run that over to Eli's.
Tell Lester if he don't give you
four and a half for it...
l'll shove it up his brother's
tight little ass.
l don't know.
They might enjoy that.
Hey, you guys, hurry it up.
I don't want to be late
and get Ramsey all riled up.
- Come on, Petey. You need the practice.
- Bullshit.
l'm every bit as good
at collecting as you are.
We'll see about that.
Hey, good morning, y'all.
lt's time to pass the plate.
l'm afraid we're a little short
this month.
Oh. Count it. And I'm afraid y'alI are
gonna have a serious problem then.
Yeah, like a goddamn broken arm.
You can't take
the Lord's name in vain, sonny.
Sorry, ma'am.
Look, Mrs. Howard, l don't want Petey
to get any more upset than he is...
and end up breaking both of his arms.
Oh, no.
Not that, Henry.
Well, looky here. lt's a miracle.
HalIelujah!
- You all take it easy now.
- Have a nice day, ma'am.
- Why did you do that?
- Oh, by the way.
Saturday night l got this date
with this cute little sinner.
CouId l get some clean sheets
this time?
- l gotta lie down.
- Lord, Lord, oh, Lord.
That was the reverend's money.
Come on, let's see.
- Pure this time, right?
- Hundred percent.
Good.
Anybody seen my idiot sons?
You know those boys, Gunney.
You just-just can't count on them.
Goddamn it.
l told them to be here.
Goddamn it!
It looks like the plane's on time
for a change.
We're sitting ducks.
Count's good.
- You haven't lost your touch, Chang.
- Thanks.
Be back on Friday for the rest.
We'll be ready.
No sweat.
Good morning, Dad.
Sorry we're late.
Morning, Petey.
Where you two been?
You were supposed to be here
to back me up.
What about you? You're on my payroll,
and you do like you're told.
What the hell is that?
Oh, it's like a '49 lndian, Pa.
l got a good deal on it.
l see that.
Now you show me the pink slip.
Well, like l said,
l got a great deal on it, Gunney. lt--
Damn it! The last thing l need
right now is trouble.
- ls this bike gonna be trouble?
- No, sir.
- You sure?
- Dead sure. Right, Petey?
Right. Absolutely, Dad.
No troubIe at all.
Don't even think about it.
Shit. Fucking dickwads!
Stupid sons of--
Oh, great. Just fucking great.
Do you know how to tell time?
- Yes, sir.
- Then be here on time for once.
We been through this a dozen times,
and you're never fucking here.
Oh, shut up.
You're fading on me.
That's a good boy, Oki.
l could really use your help.
What do you say?
Man, you're a sick mother.
- Hey, what's the stink in here?
- SmelIs like death.
- Check your boots.
- lt ain't me.
- Smells like some damn manure in here.
- Maybe the outhouse fell over.
- Can l get you boys some coffee?
- Who you talking to?
- You, bitch.
- Better red than dead, asshole.
Fuck you! Your boss shorted us
15 gallons of ephedrine.
Why don't you boys
take your differences outside?
Well, you heard our town constable.
You gents best be moving along.
- Shut the fuck up!
- Shut the hell up, ass wipe!
- Get the fuck out of here.
- You want to fucking make me?
- No need to be rude.
- Get the fuck out of my way.
- Oh, shoot me.
- Get out of my way.
Say hey to your wife and my kids
for me.
Fuck you, fucker.
- What'll you have?
- Come on, Rhonda.
You know we like Dottie
to take our order.
Dottie the hottie. You got nice tits--
no offense--
but hers are bigger and firmer.
And people say you're
not sensitive, Jessie.
Sure l am. Especially right around
the tip of my dick.
- Don't talk to Rhonda like that.
- You gonna stop him, Pop?
Hey, sweetheart,
did you maybe see something...
that could have upset you
or something?
No. I'm fine.
Really.
You sure about that?
- l'm fine.
- She won't even look me in the eye.
Johnny.
John--
- Sixtoes.
- Morning.
How'd you find me?
l feel like a football.
I did a lot of stitching
on you, Eddie.
See you still like your tequila.
lf l stay drunk...
l won't kiIl anything.
Except the tequila.
You seem at peace.
l think I am.
Boy, but we had some wild times, huh?
All the broads and the booze.
Cigareets and whiskey
And wild, wild women
They'll drive you crazy
They'll drive you insane
Cigareets and whiskey
And wild, wild women
They'll drive you crazy
They'll drive you insane
Remember?
l remember.
l remember the killing too.
l remember that if it wasn't for you,
l wouldn't be here.
You know, my people say
that if you save a man's life...
your souls are locked together forever.
That's why l came to see you.
l wanted to get your okay...
to take a journey.
Well, l got things l gotta do then.
l have to look at the moon.
Talk to the smoke.
Listen to the wind.
Nothing's easy with an lndian.
They buzz me all the time.
There's an Air Force bombing range
right over those mountains.
Looks like F-15's today.
What are you gonna do
when you catch those three brothers?
- Get your gift back.
- You got me a gift and they took it?
Yeah.
They're gonna kill you.
And if the Hogans don't,
then the Heathens wilI.
Heathens?
They're in the dope business
with the Hogans.
Hey, what do you say we do
a little ''divide and conquer''?
Like we used to in the old days.
They're making life pretty miserable
for the good people around here.
Hear that coyote?
You and him are a lot alike.
Coyote's got courage, wisdom,
a sense of mischief.
And he's got a small dick,
just like you.
- I'm gonna take a piss.
- lt's windy up here.
This ain't windy.
lt's Oki.
He's glad you're feeIing better.
Good morning, Mr. Early.
Ah. Good morning, Rhonda.
What has got you up
at the crack of dawn?
Well, l had a dream last night.
Oh, a dream.
What was it about?
Well, I dreamed that l heard the sound
of the coyote...
and that today was going
to be a glorious day.
- Oh, a glorious day, huh?
- Very glorious.
Well, I would Iike to hear
more about that.
Why don't you come in
and help me make the coffee.
That would be my pIeasure, my dear.
My pleasure.
My lucky hat, Eddie.
Thanks.
Here. You might need this.
I've got a gun...
and I'm going to get it back.
Which way is town?
Take the game trail
down to the road...
then head west.
Highway Patrol comes through
about once a week.
See you around, lndian.
l'm gonna get your gift back, then...
l want your okay
to take a journey.
Yo! When you get to town,
head straight for the diner.
Some of Rhonda's apple pie
will put a smile on your face.
My heavens! What was that?
Nothing to worry about, ma'am.
Just the flyboys showing off.
- You folks just passing through?
- Yeah. We're looking for some UFOs.
We got lost the minute we turned
off the interstate.
- Lost, huh?
- Well, not exactly lost.
Oh, Clarence, you've always been lost.
You got a map to the interstate?
Don't need no map, lvy.
- Well, we're fresh out.
- Choke and die, you old farts!
- What was that?
- Let's go, lvy.
- What'd he say?
- I don't know, lvy.
- Come back and see us, hear?
- Oh, you bet ya.
- I'm gonna head to the Pearly Gates.
- All right. l'll meet you there.
See you in a few.
Check up on that .45.
You two jackasses
ain't sold that gun yet?
Does it look sold to you?
Man, that's pitiful.
Come on, give me the envelope.
l ain't got all fucking day.
You inbreds. You're real good
at running credit card scams...
and ripping off oId folks
looking for space ships.
That's reaI cute, but if my father
has to come down here...
you two lowlifes are gonna pee
your Iittle SWAT team pants.
Isn't that right?
Thought so.
Oh, my God.
Rhonda, you remember
about the time l told you...
when me and Vern saw that guy
getting all beat up by the Hogans?
That's him.
- Dottie, l talk to you for a minute?
- Not--
l thought I told you
to keep your mouth shut.
Keep your mouth shut!
Hey! lf you're looking for UFOs,
take a fucking hike.
That guy on the bike--
who is he?
Hey, scumbag, you want information,
dial 411.
Now get the fuck out.
That .45--
where did you get it?
From your grandma.
Oh, yeah, my grandma.
Yeah, she's-- she's dead.
l've been taking shit all day.
Catch!
- That a gunshot, Pop?
- lt's probably Lester and Leon...
shooting ground squirrels
out in back.
There hasn't been any ground squirrels
around here since l was a baby.
I bet it's him.
Praise the Lord!
Praise His everlasting glory!
Save us, Jesus!
Save us--
Henry, what are you doing out there?
Not five minutes ago l saw a man
in a straw hat go into Eli's Emporium.
Then l just heard a gunshot.
- We'd better call the State Police.
- Why?
lt takes them an hour to get out here
even when they know where they're going.
What if the man in the straw hat
is a robber? A rapist?
What do we do if he comes in here?
We could rent him a room.
- Praise the Lord, praise the Lord
- Rent him a room?
If there's anybody
still alive out there...
l'd sure like you to get me out
of the stink back here.
Well, don't just stand there.
Get me out of here.
They keep the key
over the door jamb.
Well, that's better.
Now, let's get out of the stink.
My whole damn foot's asleep.
Follow me.
Where's the tank?
Bring my goddamn tank.
Well, get it out here.
l ain't gonna live forever.
You do Lester like this?
And Leon too?
You done them both--
both at the same time?
- They left me no choice.
- Well, that sounds like them.
Leon looks kind of peaceful,
don't he?
- Yeah.
- You got a name?
- Eddie Lomax.
- Boys, meet Eddie Lomax.
- Eddie Lomax, meet the boys.
- Hi, boys.
Oh, that feels good.
My name's Eli Hamilton.
About two months ago,
when I took ilI...
Lester and Leon come down here
supposedly to help me run the store.
The bastards.
Run the store, hell!
They took over.
Well, don't just sit there.
Bring me the tank.
They chained me
to that chair back there.
Told everybody l was in the hospital.
No visitors allowed.
They starved me
and then they beat me.
And they was my nephews.
lmagine that!
They hoped l'd die, but I didn't.
And then you come along
and killed them.
l know where they hid their money.
Here.
- You can have it all.
- Don't want your money.
Well, then, take a truck.
Make a run for it.
- No. l've got some unfinished business.
- What business?
- You know the Hogans?
- Oh, you gonna kiIl them too?
My advice is go ahead and kill them.
Yeah. Wipe out the whole
poisonous nest.
- All of them?
- AbsoIutely.
But what about them?
My kin folk?
My mess.
l'll take care of it.
Where you going now?
- Get a bite to eat.
- Straight ahead.
And Rhonda's apple pie is famous
in these here parts.
- Thanks.
- Oh, no. Thank you.
- He's still alive.
- I figured he would be.
Trouble on the hoof,
and it's coming this way.
Shut up, Vern.
So, just passing through?
You're just passing through?
- More or less.
- Sure is hot today.
What'll you have?
l would like a piece
of your famous apple pie.
Famous?
And how would you know?
Eli just told me. And Johnny said
it would put a smile on my face.
Johnny?
- Johnny who?
- Sixtoes.
How do you know Johnny Sixtoes?
We go way back.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Way back.
How about you?
l was ten,
and l got bit by a rattler...
on my ankle-- here.
See?
Johnny saved my life
and we've been friends ever since.
Johnny was right.
About what?
It's a good pie.
Thank you.
You know Lester and Leon?
- Not anymore.
- Oh.
- So, uh, what brings you to town?
- l'm looking for the Hogans.
- You just missed Jessie.
- Dottie!
- You got business with the Hogans?
- They've got something of Johnny's...
- and l'm gonna get it back.
- Yeah, right.
Well, maybe I could help.
Eddie Lomax.
Rhonda Lomax--
Uh, Reynolds.
Rhonda Reynolds.
And my granddad, Billing Reynolds.
Oh. Sorry. Pie.
- Just call me Pop.
- Hi, Pop.
Excuse me. l don't mean to be intrusive,
but l'm curious.
Did my Bertie send you?
Bertie did send you, didn't she?
She said she was going to get me
a good job...
because l'm such a wonderful handyman.
A handyman?
- l can use a handyman.
- Well, then, l'm your handyman.
Yeah.
Oh, no. No.
lt's on the house.
- You're very kind.
- My pleasure.
- Let's go, handyman.
- Right-o.
See? l told you, Rhonda. lt's gonna be
a gIorious day today. Glorious.
HoId on there.
Hold on.
Gotta fix that door.
Hold on there.
My name is Jubal. Jubal Early.
- Hi, Jubal. Good to meet you.
- Thank you. And you are?
- Eddie Lomax.
- Eddie Lomax. l like that.
Nice to meet you, Eddie.
This your first time though here?
- Yes. First time.
- l hope you have a great stay.
HelIo.
What do we have here?
Leon?
And Lester?
Did you kill them?
Not my business, not my business.
As far as l'm concerned,
l won't miss them one iota.
Had a beautiful dog once.
They shot him dead, and never said
one word about it. Not one word.
- Always wanted to do that.
- Oh, you're back Eddie. Good.
Hi, Jubal.
l see you've met Eddie Lomax.
Yes, l have.
So, Eli, how are you?
l've not seen you in quite a spell.
- Quite a spell.
- Yeah, well, l've been tied up.
So, Mr. Lomax, what is the job?
- Lose the bodies.
- Privacy. That's me motto.
No job too big or too small.
l'll tend to it straight away, sir.
Gadzooks!
BIoody well bled all over back here.
He bloody well bled all over.
However, not to worry.
Some Spic and Span,
a little elbow grease...
several yards of Saran Wrap,
and everything will be as good as new.
Good as new.
Well, gents, if you'll excuse me,
l'll go fetch me truck.
I won't be long.
Won't be long.
Why does he always repeat himself?
l don't know.
Those damn hooligans.
Now what are they up to?
- The Heathens?
- Yeah. Mangy pieces of shit.
Hey, I've got something better
than a .45.
Follow me.
Bring my goddamn tank!
l knew you couId do it.
My nephews, them spawns of hell...
they ripped off some of this stuff
from an army depot.
You know how to use them?
Well, l guess you do.
Help yourself.
l just need this for now.
You're very kind.
Thank you.
- l owe you a debt of gratitude.
- My pleasure.
What are you gonna do now?
Take a shower.
Good idea.
Bungalow five.
Made up fresh this morning.
Thank you both.
Young man? Have you been saved?
l'm afraid l'm a bad boy, ma'am.
But it's never too late.
l hope you're right.
Oh, ma'am.
- l Iove your hair.
- Why, thank you.
- Henry, l don't think he's a rapist.
- How would you know?
Night-night, fellas.
Hey, what do you say
we do a little ''divide and conquer''...
like in the old days?
- Good evening, Eddie.
- Evening, Eddie.
Good evening, boys.
You sure smell a lot better.
Thank you, Eli.
Tell me. The Heathens--
where do they hang out?
You got a plan, huh?
Not that you need to tell me what it is.
There's a roadhouse about 15 miIes
down the highway--
the Bomb Bay Cafe.
Run by a talI, dark fella
by the name of Singh.
But fair warning.
lt can get pretty rough in there.
Yeah, it can get very rough
in there, Eddie.
But that doesn't worry you,
does it?
You'lI need some wheels.
Take that Dodge pickup there.
Here. Help yourself.
Thank you.
You know, l bet he gets
Iots of pussy.
Yeah. l bet.
No! No, no, no, no!
No more dancing.
l don't want to dance anymore.
- Get out!
- Where the hell you going?
- l can't dance aIl by myself.
- You promised...
to take us to the bus depot.
- We want to go home!
- One more dance, please?
No more dancing. l want to go home.
l'm not putting--
You'll go when l goddamn tell you to go!
Now you dance!
No more shooting!
Please, l beg you, pIease!
l teIl you what.
The next round is on the house.
- Yeah !
- The next round is in your foot!
Now, dance!
Hey!
Can't we aIl just get along?
- l don't want to get along.
- Ah.
Hey, Jack. Your girls here
seem to have a thing...
for this sissy in his sissy hat.
What are you looking at?
l own your ass.
Hey!
You're a very naughty boy.
You're one smart motherfucker,
ain't you?
- Thank you.
- Make him dead.
Who's next?
Drop your guns.
Please.
Hey, mister,
take us with you.
- Okay. Pick up the guns.
- God! Oh, my God!
You have just dispatched three
of my best customers. l am a ruined man!
Prithee, sir, who is going to pay
for all this damage?
- My new boss.
- And who might that person be?
- The Hogans.
- Son of a bitch.
All of you, inside.
Thank you.
Hey girls, did l look tough enough?
Yeah. Real tough.
You took a big chance for us, mister.
Oh, no. I have my own reasons, and they
have nothing to do with you two.
Put your guns in the back
and jump in.
Maybe he's some kind of gunfighter
or bounty hunter or something, you know?
Whoever he is,
he sure finished off that pig Spider.
l mean, he just kiIled him
Iike a bug.
Yeah, but Eddie's got
those gentle eyes, you know?
Yeah. He sure does.
l wonder if he's circumcised.
Henry?
Henry, you should be in bed.
Marge. Marge.
Good Lord.
I can't help wondering...
about those two poor, innocent girls.
- What's he gonna do to them?
- l don't know, dear.
But l have to go to the store.
We're out of Depends.
And you should be asleep.
Take your pills.
You're right.
You're always right.
Eddie.
lt's Carol, from next door.
What do you want?
I want to thank you.
You're welcome.
No, l really want to thank you.
Hi.
- Hi.
- May l come in?
Sure.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, when the saints
Go marching in
Oh, when the saints go marching in
Oh, Lord, l want
to be in that number
Oh, when the saints
go marching in
- Eddie, it's Rose.
- What do you want?
l just want to say thank you.
I didn't know you were busy.
Hey, you're next.
- Really?
- Praise the Lord.
The door.
He's spreading joy to everyone.
Wait. Eddie, where are you going?
l'm gonna go check on my bike.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Where is he going?
For a bike ride.
Where does he get the energy?
Sweet dreams.
You're up early, Eddie.
- Sorry l woke you.
- Aw, forget it.
At my age
you don't sleep much anyway.
- Do you mind?
- Help yourseIf.
Okay. Oh, listen.
Send Jubal to the Bomb Bay Cafe.
He'll know what to do--
cIean-up job.
And l've got two girls
in my bungalow.
Put them on the bus to Cleveland.
Two girls. Yeah, sure.
l can take care of both of them.
How many of them Heathens
did you get down at the Bomb Bay?
- Just three.
- Not bad. Not bad.
And are you going after the Hogans?
Cowards!
Why the fuck didn't you kill him?
- He was outgunned and outnumbered!
- Fuck you, Ives. You weren't there.
Who the fuck you talking to, fool?
l'll screw this up your ass and splatter
your brains all over the desert.
- Do you understand?
- Back the fuck off.
lf you had any balls,
you'd take him yourself.
You keep talking like that, lrma...
you're gonna look funny
sucking my dick with no teeth.
We've tried to live in peace
with the Hogans.
Ramsey's broken the truce...
by hiring this gunman.
- So let's blow up his lab.
- We ain't gonna blow up his lab...
'cause we're gonna need it,
brothers and sisters.
We're gonna need it...
'cause we're gonna take over
his entire operation.
Everything!
Cut off the head of the snake...
the body dies.
Let's kill Ramsey.
What do you say? Come on!
Hold it!
Ramsey's not even in town.
- How do you know that?
- 'Cause l know my enemies.
First Thursday every month,
the fat pig goes up to Vegas...
with his bastard sons.
He sees his stockbroker...
then over to his hooker
to get his knob waxed.
He usually gets back
between 12:00 and 1:00.
We'll be waiting for him!
Can l ask you a question?
What's the matter now?
You gotta go pee-pee?
No, sir. lt's just that, well--
Spit it out, weenie boy.
l was just wonderin', why are you ridin'
me and Jesse so much and never Petey?
- He rides me plenty.
- He does not.
- Shut up!
- Yeah, alI right.
l love Petey
'cause I loved his mother.
She died giving him birth.
- He's our love chiId.
- Oh, my God.
What about me and Jess?
You two are
the unfortunate results...
of some recreational fucking
back when fucking was fun.
Geez.
Get over it.
We got company.
And they're closing fast.
Heathens.
They got us outgunned!
As soon as we round the bend, jump!
I'm a chemist.
l'm not a doctor.
lt looks like he may have a concussion
and possibly some internal injuries.
- He should be in a hospital.
- Okay, Chang, go back to work.
- He's your son.
- You're goddamn right he is!
- You sure you're okay, boy?
- Yeah, Dad, just a headache.
l'm gonna get some real firepower.
Wait a minute. Daddy! Think about it.
Why would they attack us?
We're in business together.
lt don't make no sense.
A man shoots at me and mine,
l shoot back and ask questions later.
l'm paying 500 bucks a head, and that
weaselly little rat-fuck lves is mine!
- l want you to stay in and rest.
- l'll rest when l'm dead, Daddy.
Hell, they tried to kill me too.
WelI, ain't you a block
off the old chip.
We're going pig hunting tonight.
Sixtoes?
Always forget how easy it is
to sneak up on a white man.
I've been thinking
about your problem.
You been wanting to die
for how Iong now?
A year? You're not dead yet?
lt's easy to come up with 100 reasons
to take the journey...
but you only need one
to go on living.
l don't have one.
WeIl, what about Rhonda?
She's a nice girl.
Ought to marry her,
have some kids.
Hey, there's something
moving down there.
Looks Iike a bunch of white guys
with bushes on their heads.
Old ''divide and conquer'' working, huh?
Should we even the odds?
Bastards!
- Thought we got rid of you!
- Think again!
Answer me one thing!
- How come you tried to kill us tonight?
- Stop firing!
Stop firing!
- Forgot, huh?
- Forgot what?
Your hired gun
wasted three of mine!
At the Bomb Bay!
l don't take that laying down !
- What hired gun?
- Ramsey, you piece of shit.
You know.
Your man with the Colt .45.
Matt, that's the guy
from the dry lake.
lt's gotta be!
- You toId me you killed him.
- l did!
- What the hell is he talking about?
- Stop firing!
The guy with the motorcycle.
Motorcycle?
- lt ain't my fault!
- You told me it would be no trouble!
lt ain't my fault! Petey was supposed
to cap him. He told me he would.
There you go, screwing up again!
- You just keep screwing up!
- Lay off me, man !
- When are you gonna learn, weenie boy?
- Get off me, old man !
l said it wasn't me!
I didn't do it!
- Think you're tough enough?
- Yes, l do!
You killed him.
You killed him, Matt.
You killed him!
You killed him, Peter,
'cause you didn't shoot that guy...
like you said you did!
You lied to me, boy.
And that's why Gunney's dead!
You're one of us!
You're family!
l'm glad l ran away from home
when l was a kid.
You understand?
lt's getting a little too cozy
down there, don't you think?
- You Iike barbecue?
- I love it.
l'm sorry, man!
l told you we didn't hire
no gunman !
Up in the tower!
It's the guy from the Bomb Bay!
l'll get the cable.
Get their attention. Then you beat it.
lt's a good plan,
but one thing's wrong.
There he is!
He's going up the side!
Get him!
Get that bastard!
That ain't him!
Where did you get the hat?
- Do you Iike it?
- You damn smart-ass!
l guess it's my hat now.
You like it? Damn it!
Wait, wait, wait. Maybe it's that
spooky lndian we always heard about.
No, he never was for real.
The guy with the Colt .45, you don't
know nothing about him neither?
- Who is he, Chief?
- Tell me!
- He's a coyote.
- Coyote my ass!
- String him up.
- Somebody get me a rope, huh?
Coyote my ass. Coyote man!
Where you at? You hear me, boy?
Stick around, we'll have
a little fun with your friend here.
A little puppet show!
How many cowboys does it take
to find a stray dog?
Eddie!
Shut up!
He's over there!
This journey ain't over
for you or for her!
Stand him up!
Say sayonara to your lndian friend!
There he is! Get him!
Name your first kid after me!
You rejects can't do nothing right!
Home, sweet home.
Cigareets and whiskey
And wild, wild women
They'll drive you crazy
They'll drive you insane
ls everything alI right, Mr. Early?
No, Rhonda, I'm quite upset.
Oh, well, what's the matter?
l had a dream again last night,
and it was quite troubling.
l heard the howl of the coyote...
but this time there was violence
and blood and death.
But that was just a bad dream.
That's nothing to worry about.
Gather around, now.
We all hanged that lndian!
And l'm offering a $10,000 reward for
anybody that gets me that Eddie Coyote!
Dead or alive.
You understand?
Now, Beserko, you go take--
- l gotta go.
- Good luck, my dear.
Petey, come with me.
We're gonna check out Pearly Gates.
Sixtoes, is he okay?
He's gone.
You gotta listen to me.
They're looking aIl over for you.
You got a $10,000 reward
on your head.
It's okay.
- l'm going back to town.
- l'm gonna go with you.
Forget it.
Johnny was my friend too.
You all hold up.
- Hey, we're closed!
- ReIax, Pop.
Can't you read?
- You're on deck!
- Just shut up!
Shut the hell up!
- l'm not gonna thank you for shit!
- Shut up!
l'm telling you, we are not--
Shut your pie hole!
- l get a share of the reward, right?
- Sure you do.
Just show us where he is.
- Oh, Vern--
- lt's all right, Pop.
He's at the motel.
Right there, the blue one.
Let's go see if he needs
room service.
Let me go!
Leave her alone!
- You can't do that!
- l just did!
Come on !
- You want to dance?
- Yeah!
Your dancing days are over,
old man!
l'm sorry, Pop!
Stick around, Dottie.
You and me got a date.
- Why'd you shoot Pop?
- Put a lid on it!
You want your reward?
Shut the fuck up!
He's in bungalow three. The third one
in the middle. The bIue one.
Remember,
he's a damn cold-blooded killer.
All right?
Joe Bob, head over to Eli's.
Quick, let's get some ammo!
- How's this?
- No, that's a .38.
- There.
- No, that's a .45.
- And this?
- No, that is a suppository!
Get your frickin' hands up
wh-wh-where l can see them!
What the hell was that?
l gotta talk to you.
This is getting way out of control !
Someone could get hurt, even kilIed.
Sounds Iike it should mean
something to me, but it just don't.
That's it! l quit!
Get off me!
l ain't crossin' this line untiI
l get a piece of that ten grand.
Jess, go turn that chicken-ass tenor
into a soprano for me.
- Back off, Petey.
- Jessie, it's me.
We went to high school together.
l signed your yearbook.
- l thought l recognized you.
- Okay, l'm coming.
That wasn't funny!
Good Lord!
Why, you cleaved him open
from collarbone to belly button.
You don't see that every day.
You got back doors
to these shacks?
- No, just windows.
- All right, we'll cover them.
- All right, then.
- Come on. Let's go!
Let's get this coyote man.
Mine eyes have seen the glory
- Patience, Elijah.
- Of the coming of the Lord
Hey, mister!
They got the place surrounded!
Give yourself up!
They're serious about this!
- Get the hell out of there, Vern!
- Come on out!
- Get out of the way, punk!
- They'll kill you if you don't!
My God!
Nobody could live through that,
right? He'd dead.
- That's right. Now, go check it out.
- Yeah, right!
- You go in there and make for sure.
- But he's dead!
- He's dead.
- Get your ass in there.
He's dead!
Stick your head in the door!
Make sure he is!
Go on!
Mister, are you there?
There's nobody in there.
It's empty and it's full of holes.
lrma, go check it out.
Buck, go with her.
We got your back.
lt's a booby trap
that didn't go off.
Circle around, men.
We gotta find him.
We can't let him get away!
Y'aIl see anything?
- No, Matt, nothing.
- Y'all search over here?
What in the hell
are you doing over here, boy?
- Backing you up.
- Backing me up.
Yeah.
You didn't even fire
one damn shot, did you?
Did you?
Man, that's just weak, man.
Real weak.
Shit! Can't even count
on your own blood.
Quit your fussin' over that booby trap.
Let's get out of here!
- I got me a new shotgun.
- No, you didn't. l saw it first.
Buck, lrma,
help us find the coyote!
- lt's caught on something.
- Yeah, your greedy hand.
No, it's not.
I feel something over here.
- You okay?
- EIi was right.
- You get good mileage to a full tank.
- You did a good job.
Go check on Pop, huh?
- Be careful.
- Go get him then, big King Kong!
- Take your ten grand and shove it!
- Petey, you alI right?
- Beserko! Shark!
- Jess, you okay?
No, l'm pissed off!
Now what?
Y'aIl head over to Eli's,
check on Joe Bob.
This is your last chance to be a man.
Are we straight?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
I'm gonna check out
that gas station.
l won't let you down, okay?
l'm gonna kill him!
Come on, you son of a bitch !
All right, Mother Theresa,
where is he?
Repent! Repent, you sinner!
Take him, Lord!
Take him now!
- What's going on?
- The Lord's will.
- Get it off me!
- Again?
You got a coyote, huh?
Right hat.
Wrong guy.
What the hell is this?
You know what the Bible says:
''Live by the sword, die by the sword.''
That's funny.
Where's the dude with the .45?
Don't you joke with me, little chink!
l am not joking with you !
- l'm gonna ask you one more time!
- He ain't gonna know where is.
- Let's go find him, bro.
- You are not my brother!
You are a liar and a coward...
and you do not tell me
what to do!
We would not be in this mess
if you had just shot that guy...
when you had the chance,
you Iittle coward!
Now's your chance.
He's a Iong bugger, this one.
We'll need another one of these.
Get out of here.
You should've killed him...
'cause l'm gonna kiIl him
as soon as l'm done kiIlin' your ass.
Now, drop it. Drop it!
Now, turn around,
nice and slow, like.
What's the matter?
That hurt?
Where are all
your Iittle friends now?
This is what happens
when you mess with my town !
Last chance to see the coyote!
l said get up, boy!
Get up! Get up!
Stand up, little one!
You're pissing me off, you mutt!
Come here, baby.
Say adios, baby.
Checkout time.
Come on. Get up. Need a little hand?
You need a hand?
You've been causing too much hell
around my town!
Stand up!
l don't want to kill you laying down.
Come on !
Teach you a damn lesson.
You gonna pay for what
you done to my family.
Knock it off, old man!
Everybody see this?
ls everybody watching?
lt's a beautiful day to die.
l got the bastard!
You? No!
lt was me.
Army didn't give me a sharpshooter
medal for nothing, you know.
What the hell you talkin' about?
You're all blind!
- l got him!
- l love you.
l love you.
lt has never missed a shot!
Never missed a shot!
I beg your pardon, but my grandfather
was close to Rudyard Kipling...
another excellent marksman.
They were very close, like this.
You didn't even have
a bullet in your gun.
- Oh, prithee, sir. What was in my gun?
- A suppository!
- Cream, no sugar.
- This is a gold mine.
They're gonna start running busses here
every two hours.
I know. It's a Iifesaver for us too.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, ma'am.
I don't want to be forward,
but do you like Samurai movies?
l don't know.
l've never been to one.
Well, they're like Westerns,
only Japanese.
Anyway, there's a special showing
on in Sun City...
one of my favorites,
calIed Yojimbo.
l'd sure love it if you'd
see it with me on Friday night.
Well, that sounds real nice, Buddy.
l could just drive down.
What time should l meet you?
Oh, no, no. l'll come pick you up.
Say around 5:00?
- l'll be ready.
- Great.
My God, that must be Bertie.
- King me, sir, please.
- AIl right.
Very lucky day for you,
Mr. Singh.
And a very lucky day, indeed,
for us all. Very lucky.
Our town is experiencing
a genuine renaissance...
and we owe it all to Eddie.
A hell of an idea of his,
telIing the tabloids...
about all the alien activity
around here.
Whoever knew there were so many
nuts in the world with money.
- That's a good one.
- l made you boys some brownies.
Thank you very much.
- Now, Bertie, you must sit and rest.
- Thank you.
- And Eli, you must stop smoking.
- Why?
Because my Bertie and l
are having a baby.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Congratulations, my friend.
Hey, look who's here!
You see hi m too?
I do now.