One, two, three...
Hold up.
Here's the story about a man
A simple man
A man with a dream
To do the world some good
Here's a story for rich and poor
For young and for old
About a man from the 'hood
Trying to do the world some good
Here's the story about a man
An everyday man
A man with a dream
To be the head of state
Alderman Gilliam's office.
What are you upset about?
It's not a black-owned business?
- But it's a Chinese food restaurant.
- So, what's with the fried rice?
I know it's fried rice, but it's not "fried" rice.
Alderman Gilliam's office.
Kim. How is it going, honey?
- Got tickets to the symphony.
- Really?
- Hold on a second, I got another call.
- You better not put me on hold.
Vote for Gaines and James.
- The Million Babies Mamas March?
- It's a very good cause.
Call Reverend Barton for that one. No...
you can't use food stamps to buy tires.
I'm sorry, Mr. Hawkins.
What can I do for you?
Your girlfriend is on hold.
- Hold on a second.
- How could you put me on hold?
- What was it, Mr. Hawkins?
- The bus.
I read that they're going to shut down
our bus line.
If they do that, I can't get to work!
Unless they give me a job
in that new mall they're building.
Don't worry. I've been talking
to the people downtown...
and I promise you this:
If they shut down this bus line,
I will drive you to work myself.
You got my word.
Alderman Gilliam, quick! Miss Pearl is back!
Okay. I got to go.
Hi, that's me, Mays Gilliam, alderman
of the 9th Ward of Washington, D.C.
Not the part of D.C. you're familiar with.
I work in a neighborhood so bad,
you can get shot while you're getting shot.
Around here when people have a problem,
they don't call the mayor, they call me.
Miss Pearl!
What's going on?
Dionne is in the house. I know she is.
I don't know what she's talking about.
We checked the house, nobody is in there.
Hey, man, Dionne is her cat.
Whatever. Cats got nine lives. She'll be fine.
Can we let one guy go in
and help this lady get her cat?
Can't do it. Once they laid the explosives,
there's nothing I can do.
She just showed up.
You took the lady's house.
Can you at least let her get her cat?
We didn't take it, we gave her $40,000.
What kind of house is she supposed to get
with $40,000? A crack house?
I think she'd be happy to get out
of this rattrap.
Who are you to call this place a rattrap?
This is my neighborhood, where I'm from.
I got my first bike stolen right there.
My daddy got his bike stolen right there.
When I have a son, I hope he's fortunate
enough to get stuck up right there.
- Can't you let somebody go check?
- We already looked.
There's nothing in there. We got work to do.
Leave the people alone, damn it!
- Let's get this thing going.
- Come on.
- Stop being in such a hurry.
- We've been here all morning.
Let the lady go inside.
Come on, baby! Sugar baby.
Could you at least turn it off?
Let the lady get her cat.
Dionne, baby? I got something for you!
Miss Pearl, no!
All right, turn it off.
Wait till this woman gets her cat.
Shit, it's not working!
Turn it off!
She better get out, it's going to blow!
Miss Pearl! Come out!
No, Mays!
You've only got a minute!
- Fix it! Get to work.
- I'm trying.
Get a union man on this.
Get your ass out!
Miss Pearl, we got to get out of here.
They're going to blow this place up.
They wouldn't do that, baby!
They know we're in here.
I love you, I've known you a long time.
You've seen a lot in your life.
You've seen churches burnt to the ground,
dogs sicced on kids...
you've seen Malcolm X and JFK killed.
They shut up Muhammad Ali
and Richard Pryor.
They gave Magic Johnson AIDS,
turned Michael Jackson white.
Do you really think these people
give a damn about you?
We interrupt the Jay-Z song
to bring you this special bulletin.
Presidential candidate Senator Gaines...
and his running mate,
General Olson James...
were both killed when their planes
crashed into each other.
We now return you to the Jay-Z song
already in progress.
What's up?
Trying to be like you, hero!
What's up, man? Saving kittens?
Don't steal my car now.
I don't want that garbage.
What will I do, feed your car to my car?
Let me get ten Nine Lives,
four Lucky Ducks, two Straight Pokers...
three Crabpots and five Powerballs.
Thank you, here you go.
You all need to stop.
Why are all these people clapping?
- You didn't see me on the news?
- No, I didn't.
I got meat!
More beef than East Coast, West Coast rap.
Check it out!
Superman! Saving lives and stuff.
Why don't you cop
one of these pork chops?
Know what you need to do?
You need to leave. I won't tell you again.
Nobody wants your meat.
Who the hell wants to buy stolen meat?
- I'll take a T-bone.
- You like gizzards, too?
Did you hear about that guy
running for President?
Who will replace him?
Maybe they should get Shaq.
Nobody can beat him.
Are you getting gas?
You're holding my line up.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
$10 on three.
You've got a lot of nerve hanging up on me.
Hanging up?
- What's going on?
- I'm leaving you! That's what's going on.
The only reason I accepted this engagement
ring from you in the first place...
is because I thought you had potential!
I thought you wanted more!
Why can't you just play the game?
Wear a suit!
Be a real politician!
What's my clothes have to do with...
Are you seeing somebody else?
I'm seeing everybody else!
I've met mosquitoes
with more force than you.
I'm tired of your little games,
tired of being your little secretary.
Here's the light bill. I didn't pay it.
Here's the cable bill. I didn't pay that, either.
And here's the bill for your car note.
I hope they take it!
Wait a minute, that's my car!
Wait, come back!
I hate that piece of shit!
I'm tired of spending my time
waiting for you to quit acting like a child...
and act like a grown man
for a change, Mays!
I need to get on with my life!
I want a house, I want children!
I want to go on vacation!
You're horrible in bed!
I am tired of being engaged.
I am tired of being...
I wish you would.
For the last time,
I'm not running for President.
I'm not crazy! Gaines was 20 points behind.
It's ten weeks to Election Day.
Damn it!
They should have known better
than to talk on a cell phone in a plane.
- What about Sanderson?
- That's a joke.
Lewis has been Vice-President
for eight years.
He's a war hero and Sharon Stone's cousin.
He can't lose.
- What about Mosley?
- Girls.
- Connelly?
- Boys.
- McMasters?
- Big boys.
So we concede the election to Lewis?
Nobody is talking about conceding,
Debra, but let's get real here.
We'll lose this one.
The thing to do is to set the party up
for the next election.
We need a candidate
that will put on a good show.
This isn't a circus,
it's a presidential election.
You can't just pick some guy...
to run for President.
It's unprecedented,
but if I put in a call to the party chairman...
we find a candidate, he'll back him.
Who will run a race
they know they can't win?
Who says he has to know?
What the...
What now?
No, not my bike!
When I went in there
I wasn't thinking about being a hero.
I was just trying to help Miss Pearl.
Miss Pearl.
I think we found our man.
Look at this! This is great!
This is America, see?
Little guy against the big guy,
corporations against the people.
Young versus old. What's better than this?
Give me a break!
I am going to run an alderman
for President?
He's not an alderman.
He's a hero.
- Who doesn't like a hero?
- Big business loves a hero!
See?
You said we needed somebody
who can help the party.
Now, how in the hell
does this guy help the party?
I'm glad you asked.
The United States is changing.
America is changing.
Inside of 20 years, you know the numbers...
20 percent black,
21 percent Asian, 39 percent Hispanic.
The minorities will be the majority.
The smartest thing we can do...
is be the first party
to nominate a minority for President.
- How about a cripple?
- I don't think so, Charlie.
Now, we'll lose, of course,
but the minorities will be happy.
The minorities will be happy
and they will vote for us in 2008...
because we've shown we support them.
And the white people will vote for us...
- Because our guy isn't black.
- You got my vote!
Geller, see if you can track down
this Mays Gilliam.
Go check our accounts.
Give me one good reason
why I should go along with this.
Don't you get it, Debra?
I intend to run for President in 2008.
Now give me one reason why you shouldn't.
He would take a lot of work.
We can run a background check...
but it's obvious
he's not a party line candidate.
He's just some kid
who thinks he can make a difference.
Don't worry. Go out there,
put the machine behind him.
You get 25 points in the polls,
consider it a win.
Make sure he doesn't embarrass us.
After this is over, we get to work.
When I'm President, I'll take care of you.
Help me. They locked me out of my office.
I know. The mayor is fed up with you.
How many times have I told you?
You got to quit trying to fix shit.
I could've got you into the council
next term. Now you're red-lined.
Shannon is taking over your district.
They need to smooth over the mall
situation, that bus thing is heating up.
- They don't trust you.
- I'm not the one stealing people's houses.
That's what your problem is.
You got to work with us.
That shit you pulled over there
cost the city money.
Makes the mayor look bad.
Now, contrary to popular belief,
politics is no place to express yourself.
You want to get in, you got to fit in.
And look at you.
Grow up, you got to dress better.
Even Puff Daddy wears a suit to court.
I'm sorry, brother, but ain't nothing I can do.
- Nice car.
- Ain't it, though?
Got it for a song at a repo auction.
He feels bad, mighty low
Got nowhere to go
What can you do when you're feeling low
Man, I want to know
He feels bad, mighty low
Got nowhere to go
What can you do when you're feeling low
And your car just got repo'd
Here we are.
Mays Gilliam, Debra Lassiter.
Nice to meet you. Take a seat.
We know what happened today.
We know you lost your job.
How do you know that? It just happened.
We're the government. We know everything.
We'd like you to do something for us.
Sure, I'd love to work
on a presidential campaign.
I'll make phone calls, send out fliers.
Who have you guys chosen
to run against Lewis?
That's exactly what we wanted
to talk to you about.
We'd like you to run for President.
- Of what?
- The United States.
- Of America.
Which America?
North...
America, Mays.
Get out of here!
We're not joking.
We want you to be the nominee
for the office of President...
of the United States of America.
Let me get this straight.
You guys couldn't find anybody else to run?
You couldn't find nobody?
Something is wrong here.
You couldn't find a congressman...
a senator? I'm just an alderman.
Congressmen, senators,
they work with other politicians.
You're an alderman.
You work with the people.
And that's what we want,
a man of the people.
This is a big joke, right?
They've got a hidden camera somewhere.
You all will get a big laugh out of this.
You know what? I don't care.
One of you all will drive me home
because my bike is messed up.
You an American?
- Are you an American?
- Yes.
This isn't just an election. It's a moment.
This is the moment when you have
the opportunity to show boys and girls...
men and women, what America is about.
Look at that.
When I see that, I think of our forefathers
fighting to make this country what it is.
When I see it I think about the guy who has
to scrub Lincoln's balls for minimum wage.
That's why we want you.
You care about the little people.
What will it be?
It gives me great honor...
to accept the party's nomination...
for President...
of the United States of America.
No!
Welcome to your campaign headquarters.
These folks will do everything they can
to help you get elected.
These are your people.
Here. Let's take a look at this.
Mark, is that cued up? Roll it, please.
This is a great spot.
If you love America,
vote Mays Gilliam for President.
But I'm not in it.
You don't even see my face.
It's a template.
We'll get you in there eventually.
There's a couple of people
I want you to meet.
This is your security director, Mr. Earl.
- You'll be in good hands.
- Pleased to meet you, sir.
If you're in trouble, yell "Security!"
and my people will handle the situation.
This is your decoy, Mays Junior.
He enters events before you.
If anything'll happen to you,
it'll happen to him first.
Tupac could have used a guy like you.
This is Nicollette White, she's
your executive director of Internal Liaisons.
Call me Nikki.
It will be a pleasure to serve you.
I'm available to you around the clock,
just let me know.
- What does she do?
- She sleeps with you.
We got tired of getting caught up
in sex scandals...
so we commissioned
our own team of super whores.
You call yourself whores!
Move that fat ass! One, two, three!
- These girls are good.
- Good morning, Mays.
I took the liberty of choosing some options
for this evening's fundraiser.
You don't mind, do you?
I'll wear whatever you need me to wear.
What fundraiser is this?
Your coming out party.
Campaigns cost money.
The people you meet tonight
have plenty of it.
Geller and I will advance the party...
and Mr. Earl will bring you at 8:00 sharp.
Here are your off-the-cuff remarks.
Learn them. See you later.
Remember, sir, just nod and move.
Nod and move.
What do you plan to do about taxes?
Do you plan to support
paternal leave incentives?
Get my demo to somebody. Anybody.
Don't take unscreened packages.
Security reasons.
You have some people to talk to.
Tomorrow, work.
Tonight, smile, shake hands,
and be nice to the wives.
I'll double-check the PA system.
You'll make a brief statement at 11:00.
Let's go.
Hi, how are you doing? All right.
You all right.
- I wish you luck, sir.
- Arigatou.
It's like Timberland,
and I got a bit of Missy moving up there...
but I'm trying to go through
that Neptune feel...
Excuse me, the Teamsters are here.
What are you doing talking to the help?
Gentlemen, Mr. Mays Gilliam.
Guys, I'm all for labor, I'm all for unions.
But you know and I know
that you will endorse Lewis.
It's business.
We'll do what's best for the union.
- Have you decided on a running mate?
- We're thinking about it.
- You should consider Sanders.
- We're considering several options.
Excuse me.
Well, that depends.
What's up with this guy?
Track four. Check out track four.
What do you have there?
We got shrimp puffs and cheese snacks...
- Just some finger foods.
- Thought that was you.
So what's up with the two jobs? Bad credit?
Why do I have to have bad credit?
Can't I be saving up for a car or for school?
Maybe I like to work? Excuse me.
I'm sorry. You know what?
I never got your name.
Hey, Lisa Clark. Mays.
Why you being so rude, Lisa Clark?
I am not being rude, I am working.
We can't mingle with the guests.
Plus, I don't know you.
- You know me.
- No, I don't know you.
But you know me.
You've come to the gas station
a couple of times...
and I see you, but I don't know you.
Let's get to know each other.
- Let's dance.
- I have to work.
I know you're working. I'm working, too.
So let's keep working. Want to dance?
Okay, you'll get me in trouble.
I cannot believe
you got me out here like this.
- Yeah, but you like it, right?
- A little.
I'm feeling it.
Go ahead, girl, work it!
Oh, my God. I'm having too much fun.
I got to get back to work.
No, come on, stay!
Come on!
Come on, brother,
I know you know how to do this dance.
No, sorry, I don't.
I know you know
how to do the Electric Slide.
No, I can't say that I do.
Get your ass in there!
- What the hell is this?
- Where's Mays?
Over there.
- Oh, my God!
- We've got to stop him.
Excuse us, please.
I am getting so hot
I am gonna take my clothes off
- What do you think you're doing?
- Stop it.
I'm just trying to get the party started.
Throw your hands in the air
And wave them like you just don't care
And if I got your vote for President
Let me hear you say, "Oh, yeah"
Shake that ass, Grandma!
Let me see you bounce!
Bounce!
We got a couple of freaks over there.
Let me see you shake!
Crip walk!
The roof is on fire!
No, it's a saying!
It's just a saying. Come back!
You turned the party out.
I have never seen anything like that.
Great party. Too bad about the fire.
- So, where are you off to now?
- I'm not even sure.
We start campaigning tomorrow.
We'll be all over the country.
Need a ride home?
I still have to clean up.
I don't know how long that will take me.
I could wait.
Are you sure?
I could send a car to pick you up.
No, thanks, but I got to go.
It was good seeing you again.
You too, buddy, old pal.
- Can I get a good-night kiss?
- No.
- I'm coming!
- She's coming!
I got to go. Good luck,
and call me if you get a chance.
Didn't you see me talking?
What kind of display was that?
I was getting the party started.
If the party needs to get started,
I'll handle it.
Just do what we say.
I don't think everybody appreciated
what you did in there.
We really had a great time.
It was off the hizzle for shizzle.
- They liked it.
- I don't care what they liked.
Mays, darling!
Darling, are you done yet?
No? If not, it's okay. I can wait.
But if we hurry,
we'll be able to get a table at Jezebel's.
Good evening. We're getting married.
I'm exhausted.
Know what I can't decide?
I can't decide whether we should have
a DJ or a band.
Security!
Thank you for inviting me
to the land of milk and honey.
It's you people, the dairy people...
people that make eggs, milk, cheese...
butter, bacon, that make the country great.
Milk makes the body good,
and you make the country good.
Thank you for inviting me
to Memphis, Tennessee.
It's people like you, the church people...
who are the backbone
and the spirit of this great land of ours.
I love the Lord,
and I love the King, Elvis Presley.
I want to thank you for inviting me
to the Lone Star State.
Home of the cowboys!
How about them Cowboys?
It's people like you, the ranchers...
who are the backbone of this country.
Now, before I go,
I got one more thing to say:
The stars at night are big and bright
Deep in the heart of Texas
It's not bad.
Will I get another speech anytime soon?
What's the matter with this speech?
I should be talking about something
a little more relevant.
Relevant?
People would be cheering
if I read the recipe for corn bread.
It's not working.
I'm only one point up in the polls.
Don't worry about the polls.
They're just a sampling. Polls change.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
We're here to help.
The people really like you.
Cheer up, we'll be in Chicago in a few days.
You got a brother there.
Then the people will find out
what you're all about.
Yeah, but I don't even know
what I'm all about.
In the latest polls, Mays Gilliam is up
just one point, to 10 percent.
Vice President Brian Lewis
still holds a commanding 84 percent.
Six percent are undecided, saying...
they don't know who they're voting for,
they just know it's not Gilliam.
When you get out there, listen to the crowd.
Talk to them, make it look like
you believe in what you're saying.
I know we haven't exactly
always seen eye to eye...
but this is very important.
- I can't stress that enough.
- Alderman Gilliam?
There's a Mitch Gilliam outside.
He says he's your brother.
Send him in.
Tonight, America will get
its first impressions of Mays Gilliam.
You know what they say
about first impressions.
Look at my little brother!
You said you'd call when you got here.
I was trying to call you,
but I've been doing press all day.
My little brother, running for President.
Let me introduce you to Martin Geller,
Debra Lassiter.
What's happening, baby? Thanks for what
you're doing for my brother. Appreciate it.
How about you, thriller? What's going...
Nice to meet you.
What do you do for a living?
I'm a bail bondsman.
I got an office on the Southside.
- Bail bondsman.
- Yes, sir.
How's business?
I tell you how business is.
Business is great.
Thank God for crime.
Could you give us a minute?
Five.
Nice. Real nice.
Look at you, man!
I see you all on the shows, politicking.
You like the way your campaign is going?
Look at this.
Let me ask you something, brother.
When they gonna let you speak?
I've been talking all day.
I was talking to the press.
You been talking, but when they gonna
let you speak your mind?
This ain't you. You gonna say this shit?
This shit is booty.
Say this if you want to, watch that man
come sweep your butt off stage.
Look at this poster: "Mays."
Who are they talking about? Willie?
Let me tell you something.
They're the everyday common folk,
working people. Laborers.
Construction workers, nurses.
Play the game
when you're working for them.
This is your campaign.
You're supposed to be in charge.
It's time.
I got to go.
I love you, man,
and I'm with you no matter what.
- Go get them.
- I'll see you out there.
Speak.
Chicago, please welcome
your next president:
Alderman Mays Gilliam.
What the hell is he doing?
They had a speech written for me...
about what the people need.
But you guys are the people.
You know what you need.
Better schools...
better jobs...
less crime.
How many of you, right now...
work two jobs
just to have enough money to be broke?
That ain't right.
If you work two jobs,
and at the end of the week...
you got just enough money
to get your broke ass home...
let me hear you say, "That ain't right!"
That ain't right!
How many of you have children
that they call stupid?
Don't be ashamed! It ain't your fault.
I asked my niece the other day,
"What's four plus four?" She said, "44."
But that ain't her fault!
That's the school's fault.
If your child's school has old-ass books...
and brand-new metal detectors,
let me hear you say, "That ain't right!"
That ain't right!
It ain't right.
And now we got these corporations
stealing all the money.
They ain't stealing their money,
they stealing our money!
The pension.
You work for 35 years.
You thought you'd leave your kids
a will, now you'll leave them a won't!
You show up to get your pension,
they give you a pen!
A damn pen! What in the hell
am I supposed to do with a pen?
I should stab you in the neck
with this pen, Mr. Pension Taker.
Get your hand out of my pocket!
Taking everybody's pension,
and nobody going to jail.
That's some bullshit. Ain't it?
Meanwhile, we steal a Big Mac with cheese...
next thing you know, we on Death Row!
That ain't right!
How many of you work in a city
you can't afford to live in?
That ain't right!
How many of you work in a mall
you can't afford to shop in?
That ain't right!
How many of you clean up a hotel...
you ain't never gonna be able to stay in?
That ain't right!
We got nurses that work in hospitals
they can't even afford to get sick in.
It ain't right!
It isn't right!
That shit is wrong!
It's dead wrong!
I'm Mays Gilliam...
and I'm running for President
of the United States of America.
No questions. Sorry.
Where's Mitch?
Go to work. Handle your business.
If you need me, call me.
I'll call you.
Are you insane? You can't just go out
in front of 5,000 people and talk!
And you said "shit."
Presidential candidates do not say "shit."
Show me a man that's never said shit,
I'll show you someone full of shit!
Debra, hold on.
What you just did, that was great.
Maybe you're right.
We could tailor the speeches more to you.
My speeches?
Come on, did you hear them?
If this is gonna work, it's got to fit me.
It's got to be my campaign.
This is not your campaign.
You do what I tell you to,
or you'll be back in D.C. on your bicycle.
I'm the one running for President.
If we're gonna run this campaign,
it's got to go my way.
We're gonna do it the way I want it done.
Hold on.
I don't know if that's such a good idea.
If you don't know, you better ask somebody.
After a slow start, Mays Gilliam
has made some dramatic changes...
in his presidential campaign.
Hi. I'm Mays Gilliam,
candidate for President of the United States.
This is my new headquarters.
The individuals you see before you
will help me guide my campaign.
These are my people.
Mays Gilliam is turning the establishment
on its ear...
with his new controversial campaign ads.
If you love America,
vote Mays Gilliam for President.
Paid for by Citizens for Mays Gilliam.
The part of Mays Gilliam's
security director...
will now be played
by Muhammad Muhammad Muhammad.
Childcare is one of the most important
issues facing this country today.
The working mother
has to take her child to a nanny.
The nanny has to take her child
to a babysitter.
The babysitter
has to take her child to daycare.
On the count of three, I want everybody
to take care of their own damn kids!
Whose baby is this? It ain't mine!
Gay people want what every American
wants. A good house, a good job!
I believe in gay rights
because when I see gay people...
all I'm seeing are people,
normal people like every other American.
Thank you for inviting me
to the Player's Ball!
America needs to change its ways.
I promise if I'm your President,
I will take care of everybody:
Big business and small business,
show business and ho business.
Hello, Debra.
Bill?
I am in Detroit at a Player's Ball
with pimps and whores.
Excuse me, hoes!
I can't do this. You got to get me
out of here. I can't control him.
He won't listen to me!
No, Debra.
I need you out there, and this is going great.
This is what we wanted.
I love this guy. "That ain't right."
He really thinks he can make a difference.
Stop worrying. This will work out fine. Bye.
Don't I know you?
No!
He feels good
Things are going his way
He just might be
The President someday
Mays, darling, I've been thinking.
I want a small wedding.
I think I want 150, maybe 200 people.
I've always said
I wanted a wedding in a church...
but lately I've been thinking about
the Botanical Gardens.
We could do it by the tulips.
It'll be beautiful...
Security!
Who the hell is Mays Gilliam?
He's running against you, sir.
What happened to Gaines?
He died in a plane crash.
Get out of here! Gaines is dead?
- Don't you remember? It was on the news!
- Not my news.
This fellow, Gilliam,
is an alderman from D.C.
He took Gaines' place, sir.
I'm running against this guy.
Yes, sir.
That is some bullshit.
This is my time.
I've been Vice President for eight years.
I am a war hero,
and I am Sharon Stone's cousin!
And I'll be damned if I'm going to let
my election be ruined by this asshole!
I want this guy done. You hear me?
Finish him!
He will be destroyed, sir, as you wish.
This is the White House
without Mays Gilliam. Peaceful, isn't it?
Now, this is the White House
if Gilliam is elected.
Let's keep Mays Gilliam
out of the White House.
Vote Brian Lewis for President.
It's your last chance.
How do you want to handle this?
I don't want to go negative.
Nobody wants to hear that.
I want people to vote for me,
not against Lewis.
- People don't know what they want to hear.
- We have to respond.
We should go with something measured,
accurate. Let's call him on his record!
You can't challenge his record
when Mays doesn't have one.
How about a massage?
Ladies and gentlemen...
please welcome
presidential candidate Mays Gilliam.
Thank you!
This is Conservative Talk 520.
You're listening to Big Dave.
Negative ads. Lewis is up, Gilliam is down.
I think it's great!
Bottom line:
I don't think I want Gilliam
and his homies to be in the White House.
People are saying these ads
are dirty politics. Give me a small break!
We're not talking about running
a rib shack but a country!
He's running for President
and every vote counts!
Ladies and gentlemen, Mays Gilliam!
And if these ads are so bad,
why hasn't Gilliam said anything?
Howard Stern rocks!
You're on with Big Dave.
The reason Gilliam hasn't responded
is because he has too much integrity.
We just got endorsements
from Raekwon the Chef...
and Ghostface Killah.
- Is this good?
- It's great.
Where are we on this running mate thing?
I've been making calls.
Nobody wants to run with you.
Who did you call?
Everybody.
Did you call Hammer?
No, I did not call Hammer.
Then you didn't call everybody.
Mr. Gilliam, can I have your autograph?
I'll be right back.
- Should we call Hammer?
- No.
Say cheese!
Mays Gilliam did not attend
this year's annual rally against cancer.
Is Mays Gilliam for cancer
or against cancer?
Mays Gilliam, he's for cancer.
Vote Brian Lewis for President.
It's your last chance.
Cancer lover!
No, he does not get away with this crap!
This is what we'll do.
You ever watch Bugs Bunny?
Bugs would always shoot Elmer Fudd
in the face and drop an anvil on his head.
But what made Elmer really mad
is when Bugs Bunny kissed him.
We got to kiss this bitch.
- How do you propose we do that?
- Watch this.
I'm a Klansman. I hate niggers, Jews,
and fags, but I love Brian Lewis.
Yo, what's up? I'm Osama Bin Laden.
I hate America, but I love Brian Lewis.
Paid for by Osama Bin Laden.
Sharon Stone is a defector.
That's what Lewis campaign insiders
are saying about the Hollywood star...
and cousin of Vice President Lewis,
after Stone's endorsement of Mays Gilliam.
I don't believe it!
Yeah!
I know!
Did you hear...
What are you doing here?
Gilliam is over 30 points.
That means even if he loses
he's the frontrunner in 2008.
In case you've forgotten,
I intend to run for President in 2008...
and I am not running against him.
So this is over.
Either you put a stop to it or I will.
I came on board to run a campaign
for a man we didn't expect to win...
not to sabotage him so he'd lose.
You're in this as thick as I am.
Of course he's supposed to lose!
That's why we picked him.
Are you with me or are you with him?
I thought you wanted
what was best for the party.
I'm what's best for the party!
What's the matter?
Democracy doesn't work for you
when you're not winning?
I'm with him.
I'm with him?
- Who are these people again?
- The Urban Business Board.
- What are your plans for Social Security?
- Give it to old people.
- Your plans on global warming?
- Global ice tea.
- You the man!
- You the woman!
I want to introduce you
to Chester Norris Allen.
He owns a bottling plant in D.C.
and I spoke to him about our problem.
We've got a nice check for you.
We can't take it. You sell malt liquor to kids.
I do no such thing.
Come on, man. It's orange beer
with a nipple top. Now, who's that for?
It's Crib Malt Liquor, man!
He's unbelievable!
Damn it, we need that money!
Why do you make everything so difficult?
It's Crib Malt Liquor!
"Crib Malt Liquor,
just like Mama used to make"?
Whose mama? Not my mama!
The situation is getting tense with the threat
of the bus line being shut down.
Protestors took their concerns
to transit officials...
but talks broke down when the newly
appointed alderman, Reginald Shannon...
was punched in the face
by an angry protestor.
- Good evening, sir.
- What's up, Nikki?
I noticed you weren't at the party,
so I thought...
if there is anything you would like
for me to do, I would be happy to.
Could I ask you something?
Yes.
You seem like a nice girl.
How did you get into this line of work?
I went to the University of Nebraska...
where I majored
in Theater and Communications.
I did some extra work,
and a few things that went straight to video.
Okay.
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah, sure.
Since I've been here, you haven't really
given me any assignments.
I was wondering if you find me attractive.
I think you're...
I think you're very attractive. It's just that...
I like to get to know people
before I get involved.