SubRip by divx.NeKryXe.com
(Thud)
(Bell tolls)
- Anyone noticed?
- You are blessed with luck, Tomas.
Gregory, life is for living.
Your hair is still wet.
- (Whispers) Who is our visitor?
- (Whispers) Father Michael.
He has brought something
for the repository.
- Hurry up, say amen.
- This cannot be good.
- What?
- Whatever you are doing here.
Trust me, Gregory, this is good.
(Gregory) Where are you taking me?
(Tomas) The repository.
Oh, and you expect
to use my key? Forget it.
- Too late.
- Oh, Tomas.
(Gregory) We should not be here.
That key was entrusted to me.
Go back to the room if you like.
l have always wanted to know
what is kept here.
- Some things are better left a mystery.
- Look at all this.
This monastery was built
to protect the contents of this room.
l want to know why.
The Wheel of Time.
What is it?
l've heard stories of it
but never believed it to be real.
lt is rumoured to be
a means of transport through time.
How?
- The lights are burning.
- Brother Rafael was here.
- He must have left them so.
- lndeed.
Father, is something wrong?
We thought of burying it.
Or throwing it in the sea.
But evil...
has a way of returning.
Written by St Nicodemus of Alexandria
in 1260.
A scholar and warrior.
Munkar and Nakir.
Described as ravening lions
to the soul and body of the world.
Father Michael, l understand
the gravity of this burden.
l have devoted my life to being
the guardian of these artefacts.
Guardian of evil.
l see now why the Order of Damascus
is an offence to Rome.
The Holy Father is aware
of the importance of our work
which is why he sent you
and your charge to us.
And l can promise you that
everyone here is as serious as l am
about keeping these secrets...
safe.
Now can we please get out of here?
Tomas, did you hear nothing
Father Michael said?
Whatever lies in that box is evil.
The real evil is keeping such a beautiful
work of art locked in a chest.
(Gregory) Chest.
- This sculptor was quite talented.
- Put it back in the chest.
Quickly! You must put it back.
Gregory, if you wanted to touch it,
all you had to do was ask.
- Oh. Oh.
- Gregory, what are you doing?
(Gregory) Oh!
- What is that?
- Get it off me! Get it off!
Get it off!
- Get it off!
- Get off of him!
Get off of him!
(Agonized scream)
(Squelching)
(Whimpering) Tomas, help!
Ah! Ah.
(Laboured breathing)
- (Sizzling)
- (Agonized shouting)
May the Lord have mercy on us all.
(Gregory moaning)
- Tomas, go back to the monastery.
- What were they?
Demons, succubi.
Foul things from before the time of man.
And now they are free.
Unleashed.
Moving through time toward a world
that is ill-prepared for their evil.
Gregory...
He will die if you do not get help.
Hurry! Time is short!
- Father.
- Time is short.
(Munkar) Come, sister.
There is much to do.
Let us see what this new age
has to offer.
(Man) Why don't we just take a trip...
(Woman) Yeah.
(Man) Should be pretty good...
(Woman) Whoa!
(Man) What?
(Car horn)
(Man) Woo!
(Abbot) Have you thought about
what you leave? About Gregory?
- He has the Order, he has you.
- He needs his brother.
His real brother.
What happened last night was proof of
something l've known for some time.
This place is not right for me.
l've watched you two
since you were children.
Gregory has always followed our ways,
always been ready to do the Lord's work.
And l have always been trouble.
Yes, l suppose that is true.
But you have a strength, Tomas.
lt runs deeper than you know.
You still have a part to play
in God's plan.
l am more concerned
with my own plans right now.
l understand.
You know there will always be
a place here for you
if and when you decide to return.
Thank you, Father.
Your hand. What happened to it?
- lt is a blister.
- Let me see it.
lt is nothing.
Let me see your hand.
You have been marked.
- lt is a burn, nothing more.
- That is not true, Brother Tomas.
God has chosen you to wield
the dagger of St Nicodemus.
But l have never fought in my life.
You must travel on the Wheel of Time,
find Munkar and Nakir.
Find them and destroy them.
Father Michael, l will travel south
to the ocean and the sun.
No Munkar, no Nakir, no Wheel of Time.
Tomas, God has chosen you.
Then He has chosen wrong.
Tomas!
- Tomas.
- Rafael, what is it?
Your brother Gregory - he's dying.
Oramus te, Domine,
per merita Sanctorum tuorum
quorum reliquiae hic sunt
et omnium Sanctorum,
ut indulgere digneris
omnia peccata mea.
Amen.
(Father Michael) This dagger was forged
by St Nicodemus to battle the demons.
He believed that Munkar and Nakir
had destroyed entire cities.
This dagger is the only thing
that can stop them.
lt has tasted of their blood
and will lead you to them.
The world as we know it
will be changed, Tomas.
lt will be filled
with many new strange things.
But remember,
God's children do not change.
They will help you on your journey.
When you find the demons,
strike quickly.
You may not get a second chance.
God be with you, my son.
And also with you, Father.
(Car horn)
(Helicopter)
(Walkman)
(Mobile phone)
(Siren)
Thank you, my brother.
Oh, damn! My bad, bro,
l wasn't watching. You all right?
l-l do not know.
Yeah, you don't look so hot. You sick?
Do you know where you are?
What day it is? Your name?
What's your name, man?
- My name is Tomas.
- Tomas.
OK. Look, we should get you
to a hospital.
No, l'm fine. My stomach.
Stomach, yeah.
Can l do anything for you?
Give you a lift somewhere?
- A lift?
- A ride home? Something?
A ride, yes, please.
You got it.
Which way you heading?
Hey, where you going, man?
That way.
(Squelching)
(Gurgling)
Ah!
Oh.
(Male TV presenter) 'This bracelet is
beautiful, you can't get better than this.
'ln fact, as always,
your satisfaction is guaranteed!
'There's nothing else to say.'
(Purrs)
Satisfaction
guaranteed.
(Female TV presenter) '..sold seven
in the last 20 seconds...'
Turn off that noise box.
lt's ruining my appetite.
Munkar,
the noise box and its pictures
will teach us how to behave
in this new time.
(Woman) 'There is no risk to you.'
(Man) 'That's right!'
No risk...to you.
(Man) 'Your satisfaction is guaranteed.
'Satisfaction guaranteed.'
Satisfaction guaranteed.
(Woman) 'There is no risk to you.'
(Man) 'That's right.'
Absolutely
no risk
to you.
(Laughs)
(Gurgling)
- This all right?
- The world has truly changed.
ls this the part of town you want to go?
There are better places to stay.
l have a task to complete
and then l'll be going home.
So where's home?
A long journey away.
(Distant voices)
Oh, dear Lord!
Drop the weapon! Drop it!
(Crying)
- Hey.
- Hey, you.
(Sighs)
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Found this.
lt's funny the stuff you find
when you're not expecting it.
Dad gave it to me
the day l graduated from the academy.
- He was a good man.
- Yeah, he was.
- He'd be proud of you, Rach.
- l hope that's true.
Trust me, he would be.
l miss him.
Me too. That's why l like to spend time
with you. You're a lot like him.
- lt goes both ways.
- You take it one day at a time.
Wake up in the morning,
breathe in and out, do your job.
Yeah. lt's just the cross.
lt caught me off guard, is all.
- You ready for breakfast?
- Yeah. What's on the menu?
Homicide, Gastown.
(Siren)
- (Flies buzzing)
- Oh, God!
There's something you don't
see every day.
(Officer) The victim is Greg Summers.
White male, aged 38.
Found a wallet, some pictures.
Probably married.
Came up here for a little fun.
- Who found him?
- Housekeeper.
She's downstairs, in shock.
Had the front desk call us.
Do something about the smell?
How long's he been here? A month?
- ME says not even an hour.
- What?
Victim was seen coming up here
with two hookers.
- Where are they?
- Trying to find them right now.
We do have another suspect.
- Tomas Alcala?
- Yes.
l'm Detective Dressler.
This is Detective Rand.
l give my solemn word,
l did not harm that man.
- Your solemn word?
- Yes.
Mr Alcala, l understand that you've
waived your right to an attorney?
- Yes.
- You know everything you say and do
may be used against you
in a court of law?
Everything l say and do
will be judged by God.
Fine.
Then maybe you can tell us
what you were doing in that hotel room.
l was looking for two women.
Two hookers?
- Hookers?
- Prostitutes.
Two prostitutes were seen going in...
No, they are succubi.
ln English, please.
A succubus is a demon that feeds
on the life force of men.
Why were you looking for them?
They are ravening lions
to the soul and body of the world.
These ravening lions,
why didn't you stop the ravening lions?
l arrived too late.
They had fed on the man and escaped.
(Dressler) Do you know
where they went?
You. Yes, it is you.
l saw you find it.
- What?
- The cross.
The golden cross your father gave you.
You found it.
Don't change the subject, Alcala.
You miss him deeply.
When you found the cross
it made you cry.
l saw you cry.
- You take over.
- Rach.
Rach.
OK, granted, that was pretty weird,
given the fact you found
it today but it's a coincidence.
You can't let the loonies know
they're getting to you.
- Who is he?
- A nobody, a drifter.
- All we know is he's a suspect.
- Did we run prints on him?
Prints gave us nada, no lD,
no social security number.
As far as the world's concerned,
he doesn't exist.
What's taking her?
She will be out soon.
She bathes for you.
All right. But l did pay for the two of you
so two is what l expect.
Know what l'm saying?
Your satisfaction...
is guaranteed.
l like the sound of that.
So what's the deal with you guys?
Are you a lesbian couple or what?
l like that. l like it.
So who's the top? You or her?
She is.
So if you're innocent,
tell me what you were doing with this.
l was using it to find Munkar and Nakir.
l'm assuming those are the prostitutes.
Succubi.
How's this knife
supposed to help you find them?
The blade is drawn to them and...
lt will point in their direction.
- Spin it.
- Spin it?
There. That direction.
That is where you will find them.
All right, that was a pretty good trick.
- Ow.
- (Squeaking)
What the...?
(Screams)
Get it off me!
Give me your hand!
Hold still!
(Creature shrieking)
- Sick son of a bitch!
- Let him go!
- lf you hurt her, l'll...
- lt wasn't him.
- What happened?
- l don't know. This thing bit me.
- A maggot. l don't know what it was.
- Where?
There.
He stepped on it.
Let me see your hand, Rachel.
l don't understand.
lt was, it was right there.
lt was right there.
Be careful, Munkar.
Do not drink so deeply.
l have fed from more men
than you can imagine, sister.
l know when the heart blood comes.
(Door bangs, car alarm)
What is that?
l do not know.
The priest. He has the dagger!
(Growls)
Not a priest, nor a saint.
Just a monk, a monk
who's very far from home.
(Sniffs) Mm. Familiar.
l drank of your brother, did l not?
l will stop you! l will stop you!
How will you do that, little one?
That dagger must be wielded by a saint
in order to be of any harm to us.
You are no saint.
l can smell sin on you.
(Siren approaching)
(Dressler) l don't think he did it.
(Rand) Look at all the evidence.
The guy escapes,
two hours later we get a burglar alarm.
What do we find? A new victim.
And he leaves his calling card.
He says the knife led him
to this Munkar and Nakir.
- Maybe he caught them in the act.
- That's crazy talk, OK?
You need a break, a leave of absence.
Whatever you wanna call it, take it.
l don't need a break, l'm fine.
We should go after the women,
not Alcala.
Wanna tell me about that imaginary bite
on your wrist?
l know what l saw.
l don't wanna talk about this any more.
Morgan, the knife's clean, there's no
trace of blood from any of the victims.
lt's not the murder weapon,
he's just taunting us with it.
- Why do you want to crucify him?
- l don't have time
for stories about dog-sized maggots
and demonic hookers.
You have rested long enough, Nakir.
Leave me.
l am weary.
You fed, you...
cannot be...
Filthy, repulsive slut!
Wrapping your legs around every slab
of human flesh you bring home.
l warned you but you did not take heed.
l know why you are weary -
because you are with child.
(Screeches)
Do not presume to judge me.
Without my efforts we would never feed.
Hold your tongue, sister,
or l will hold it for you.
(Both shrieking)
(Growling)
(Coughing)
(Screeching)
Be still. Little one, be still, be still.
Understand you are my sister.
l am trying to protect you.
You lie.
- l can smell the stink of your jealousy.
- No.
l speak the truth.
Nakir, our brood are born ravenous.
They will kill and consume us
if not given other food.
This world is filled with bags of food,
all walking around, making noise.
Your youth is your folly.
And it will be your undoing.
lt was you who allowed Nicodemus
to imprison us.
We are both guilty
of indiscretions.
- Now l hunger.
- Come.
Let us find you some sustenance.
Why go further than the nest?
We can feed on the priest.
Not yet. The monk is special.
He is meant to be savoured.
We will save him for later.
l do not know why You chose me.
l'm failing You, Lord. l'm failing You.
Our Father,
who art in Heaven,
hallowed be Thy name.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, ma'am, how can l help you?
Get that man off the boardwalk.
lt's supposed to be a family place.
Don't worry, l'll get right on it.
Give us this day our daily bread.
Forgive us our trespasses...
All right, pal.
What the...?
What are you covered in?
(Rattling)
l want to control the wheel.
- Oh, you wanna drive, huh?
- Yes.
Tell you what - why don't you slide
on over here and sit on my lap?
We'll take it
for a simulated test drive.
Huh. Yeah.
Oh yeah. Now, that's more like it, huh?
Your friend's kinda quiet back there.
- She likes to watch.
- (Horn beeps)
Well.
Put your hands up on the wheel
and put one foot on the gas.
l'll be your seat belt. Here we go.
(Makes engine noises)
(Man laughs)
(Growls savagely)
Why must you always spoil
my enjoyment of the food?
- He was growing tiresome.
- That's what made him enjoyable.
Mm. Mm.
- What have you got?
- A station wagon.
Witnesses saw two women get out
and head into the store.
- Sound like your suspects?
- Sure does.
Wait, we're not set up to cover you yet.
- Rachel!
- (Growling)
lt isn't polite to interrupt people
while they are eating.
- Put her down...
- (Growling)
Ugh. Ah.
Hello, lover.
(Laughs)
(Gasping)
(Gunshot)
Hateful wench, you dare threaten me?
Get her away from him.
Aah!
Nakir!
Release it.
lf you so much as spill
one drop of Munkar's blood...
l will kill him.
Let him go.
Not yet.
Not while his life still has worth.
You take one more step with that dagger
and my sister will rip him
from groin to guts.
(Sirens, police radio)
Go, go, go! Where are they?
Morgan! Morgan!
Morgan.
You OK?
Just got the wind knocked out of me.
You saw me shoot that woman.
- l don't know what l saw, it was crazy.
- l'm telling you, they're not human.
Maybe they're hopped up on PCP.
That might explain it.
But they're our primary suspects,
- not Alcala.
- They're all suspects.
Guys, another unit brought in
that guy, the one who skipped on us.
- Tomas Alcala?
- That's him.
Couple of officers picked him up
at Playland. ls he still a suspect?
(Dressler) No.
(Rand) Yes.
He's asking to speak to
Detective Dressler.
Rachel.
He's still a suspect.
- Detective Dressler.
- (Man shouting) Get it off me!
Are you all right?
Can you stop them?
- l pray to God...
- Screw that. Can you stop them?
- l need the dagger.
- That's not a problem.
Then you must set me free.
Let him out.
(Guard) We thought he was a suspect.
(Dressler) No, he's not
a suspect any more.
Put your hands behind your back
like you're handcuffed.
- Like this?
- Yeah. Just keep them like that.
Get in here.
(Phone)
(Woman) There's a call here for you.
Come on.
(lndistinct police radio)
l'm sticking my neck out for you.
- Don't let me down.
- l'll do my best, l promise.
That Dressler woman may cause us
problems - she has found the dagger.
She is no more saint than our little priest.
Remember Nicodemus? ln the wrong
hands that dagger could seal our fate.
My appetite has been aroused
by that police.
Pity l could not feast on him.
ln time, we will feed on the monk,
regain our strength,
then we will find this Dressler woman.
- Where is he?
- Detective Dressler took him out.
- What?
- l'm sorry. She said you knew.
You better have a damn good reason.
- l need you to trust me on this.
- Are you nuts? He's a suspect.
- l'll have him back in the morning.
- You'll have him back in ten minutes.
l know what l'm doing.
You're gonna have to trust me.
This is not about trust, Rachel.
Morgan.
- What do you want?
- l want you to keep my back
just until l can get some answers.
OK. But l want him in that cell
tomorrow morning.
Don't make me come looking for you.
Find him. We must find him!
- ls this where you live?
- Temporarily.
OK, l found these.
They might be a little big on you
but at least they're clean
and not covered with...
- Demon secretion.
- Yeah.
Like l said, they're clean.
(Tomas) That is where you were
when you found the cross.
OK.
So how do you know that?
The Wheel of Time showed me.
lt showed me all of this.
- Come again?
- The Wheel of Time.
lt is how l came to be here.
l have been sent from the year 1815
to stop Munkar and Nakir.
Uh-huh.
l realise that is difficult to believe.
lf you'd said that yesterday
l would've thought you were nuts.
Now l'm not so sure.
Does that mean you believe me?
l don't know what l believe any more.
Giant maggots, magic knives,
bulletproof hookers.
So does that mean you believe me?
l don't know why but...
yeah, l do.
The Dressler woman -
once we find her we'll find the monk.
How do we find her?
She is a police, like him.
Afternoon, ladies.
What can l do for you?
My sister would like to take a ride
in that machine
but she is afraid.
Will you take a ride with us?
l can't, really.
l'm on duty.
Do you think you could
make an exception?
The police has touched the priest.
l can taste it on him.
(Munkar) Where is the monk, police?
(Laboured) l don't know any monk.
(Nakir) The man you touched, the one
who was covered in our secretion.
Yeah. The vagrant guy.
Yeah. The mother complained.
l took him...to the station...
Fifth Precinct.
(Nakir) You are...you're sweet.
Mm. Sweet!
(Slurping)
(Nakir) Thank you.
Welcome to the Fifth Precinct, ladies.
How may l help you?
(Tomas) This is a miracle.
An entire library in a small box.
Can you find information
on St Nicodemus?
- Who's that?
- The saint who forged the dagger.
- He originally imprisoned the demons.
- Let's see.
This is such an age of wonders.
So why did you leave?
Volunteer or were you recruited?
l made a very bad mistake.
One that can never be taken back.
l set them free.
Munkar and Nakir.
l am responsible for the blood they shed.
By the way, you were right.
What you said about my father.
And l do miss him.
Very much.
He gave me this a month before he died.
l was a rookie, l got lazy
and did a bad search
and l let the suspect go.
He thought it would be funny to rob
the house of the cop who arrested him.
My dad was here.
l guess they were both surprised
to see each other.
My dad was shot four times.
You could not have known.
Four times.
Where do you get absolution for that?
From God.
Thanks, l don't believe in Him.
Your cross?
l don't wear it. l just keep it
because it reminds me of my father.
Looks like St Nicodemus wrote a book.
Nothing about the dagger though.
Father Michael said
only the dagger could stop them.
However, when the demons saw me
they laughed.
The dagger must be wielded by a saint
to be effective, and l am not a saint.
- So what do we do now?
- We must find a saint.
- Tell us where she is.
- We will not harm her.
We only want the dagger,
and the man she has in her care.
No risk to you.
- What man?
- The little monk.
We know she took him from this place
and you know where she is.
You're gonna have to kill me.
(Both) Oh.
- We will.
- (Both laughing)
But only after you've told us
where Dressler is.
(Screaming)
- What's the name of your order again?
- The Order of Damascus.
- There it is.
- Your monastery
is now a hospice
run by a Sister Stephen.
Who is that?
Sister Stephen, Patricia Stephen.
Looks like a Mother Teresa type.
Cares for people
with long-term illnesses.
Newspapers are calling her a saint.
l knew we would find a saint.
She can wield the dagger.
This is all part of God's plan.
- Where are you going?
- To the monastery.
l'm sure she's gone for the night.
Wait till morning.
l saw you looking at me.
l am sorry.
No, it's OK.
l liked it.
We're both so alone.
Please, l cannot.
Oh.
Come now, little priest,
do not pretend
that you're not enjoying my touch.
- You repulse me.
- One would not know that
from your actions.
You seemed to be
quite accepting of Nakir's affections
a moment ago.
Please, l cannot.
- (Ecstatic moan)
- Oh, God.
- Please, no.
- You're almost there, Tomas.
Soon you will know
the warmth of our embrace.
Almost there, Tomas.
You're almost there.
Lord, take this burden away from me!
Ah!
(Creaking)
Alcala?
You awake?
Morning.
What are you doing over here?
l tried sleeping
in the place you set for me
but l am more accustomed to this.
- l'm sorry if l frightened you.
- No, it's fine. Sleep where you want.
Did you hear anything in here?
(Crashing)
l'm sorry, Rachel.
They made me lead them here.
(Mocking screeches)
Neither of you learn very quickly,
do you?
Stop. Stop it!
You're killing him.
Yes. lsn't it exquisite?
Sister.
Do not drink so deeply.
Do it.
Please.
No!
Munkar!
Munkar.
Come on. Come on.
How do l save you?
Tell me what to do.
(Sobbing)
(Tomas) At times like this
our faith is tested.
- Spare me the sermon.
- God's will works through us.
God's will? You think it was His will
that l shot my partner?
What kind of God is that?
lt is not for us to know His purpose.
But know that He has a will,
take comfort in that.
l can't. lt doesn't bring Morgan back.
He has gone on to a better place.
Am l supposed to take solace in that?
Everyone that l've ever cared about
has been taken from me.
lt doesn't matter if he's in a better place
because l'm still here.
Yes, because God has work
for you to do.
What if l'm not interested
in doing His work?
Then l will tell you l know how you feel.
And the demons,
they took my brother from me.
l understand your pain and your loss.
But you must understand this -
if we fail at this task
their offspring will grow in number
and destroy the earth.
Now, we must get the dagger
to Saint Patricia.
Look, about back there and before,
l was a little rough on you.
l know you were only trying to help.
Loss is painful.
Yeah.
Sorry, Alcala.
Please, call me Tomas.
Rachel.
Rachel?
That is a beautiful name.
(Crash)
- Go! Drive! Go!
- Hold on.
(Tyres screeching)
Are you girls all right?
Tomas and Rachel?
Yes. You must be Sister Stephen.
Oh, please, call me Patricia, or Patty.
We don't stand on ceremony, here.
Thank you very much for seeing us.
Pleased to meet you. Forgive me for
being rude, but you do not wear a habit.
A lot of people are frightened by it.
By a nun's clothing? Why?
l blame the movies.
Would you like to come up?
(Sighs)
- Well, it's quite a story.
- Sister Stephen...
Patricia, l know how it sounds
and if l hadn't seen
these things first-hand myself
l wouldn't believe it either.
lt's not a question of believing you,
it's more a question
of saintly credentials.
Unfortunately l'm not a saint.
But you must be.
- Sorry for the misunderstanding.
- Wait.
Sister, please,
you are my last hope.
l'm sorry, Mr Alcala.
l wish l could help.
(Patricia) Mr Alcala, is something wrong?
This is where my brother died.
l have failed him.
l have failed them all.
(Distant screaming)
(Rasping scream)
(Agonised screams)
Look, sister - l have found sustenance
for your newborn.
No! No!
No! No! No!
No! Aah!
Oh! Ah!
Oh!
Oh! Oh, Munkar,
something is wrong.
Help me.
Aah!
(Crunching, crackling)
(Screaming) Help me!
Help me!
No! No!
(Cawing)
Why do you protect her?
She was to be food for my child.
l warned you about allowing
the seed into your body.
- Munkar, do not forsake me.
- l have not forsaken you.
Our existence is made up of phases.
You have surpassed me
and moved on to the next phase.
l envy you.
(Creature screeching)
No!
Wait!
- (Squeaking)
- Munkar!
Yes, sister, l envy you.
But you are of no use to me any more.
(Cries)
l need a partner who can lure prey.
You, Nakir, are spent.
Treacherous bitch!
Miserable, faithless whore!
(Screaming)
Do not worry.
You will do better, sister.
There is absolutely no risk to you.
- (Laughs)
- (Screams)
You said the Order of Damascus
sent you here
with a dagger of some sort
to use against the demons.
May l see it?
Father Michael said l was the chosen one
because the dagger marked me.
lt certainly seems that way.
But l am not worthy,
l cannot wield the dagger.
- l don't see why not.
- Because l am not a saint.
Mr Alcala, if saints knew what they were,
they would not be saints.
Be still, sister.
You will need all your strength
for the transformation.
- Thank you again for listening.
- Like l said, it's quite a story.
- You think l'm crazy.
- On the contrary.
l wish l had as much faith as you.
- God be with you.
- And with you, Tomas.
lf you see Rachel, will you please tell her
l've gone to the repository?
l pray you find what you're looking for.
(Munkar) Do not fear, little sister.
l will care for you.
Ah! l'm not your sister.
(Munkar) Soon you will not remember
this phase of your evolution.
The pain will only last a moment.
Then it is like falling into a blissful sleep.
(Growls)
When you wake, we will go find
your little monk
and you can feast on him.
You will not need to find me.
l will not hide from you.
(Nakir groaning)
(Creature squeaking)
You're getting better
with that dagger, little monk.
But you still are not a saint
and l do not fear you.
Why don't you just
surrender yourself to me?
l will give you pleasures
you never even dared dream of.
You killed my brother. The only
pleasure you can give me is your death.
Poor little misguided man.
l will savour your death.
Filthy brood.
- Come on.
- No.
(Dressler) We're getting out of here.
- The Lord has given me a task.
- Let them kill each other.
- Life is for living!
- l used to feel that way
but the Lord gave me this life
and now l give it back to Him.
Tomas, you're not a saint.
lf saints knew what they were,
they would not be saints.
- Where is Munkar?
- l don't know.
Please help me. The blade is stuck.
l thought you weren't a saint.
l am not.
Guess that's not your decision to make.
Perhaps it was you.
So what are you going to do? Bury it?
No. That has been tried.
Evil has a way of returning.
l must get it back
to the Order of Damascus.
How do you plan
on getting back to them?
- l do not know.
- Come on. Let's get you out of here.
Sister Stephen!
We need to get him to a hospital.
l can do better than that. Follow me.
The Wheel of Time.
Many years ago the church sent
a cardinal to take all of the artefacts.
l hid this one.
At the time l couldn't have told you why.
Just had a feeling it still had
a part to play in God's plan.
God be with you, Tomas.
l have to go.
l want you to stay.
l have to get these back.
They must be kept safe.
Tomas, please.
Munkar has poisoned me.
Can they help you there?
- They can pray for me.
- So can l.
Wear it.
Oh, my son.
Oh, my dear boy.
Father, have l redeemed myself?
A hundred times over, Tomas.
(Whispers)
l could not hear you, my son.
What do you say?
(Whispers)
- Thank you, sister.
- Tomas has gone home, hasn't he?
- Yes.
- That's all the thanks l need.
You know, you're welcome to stay
if you like.
Appreciate the offer but l don't think
l'd really fit in around here.
You'd fit in better than you think.
l like the cross.
- Yeah? My father gave it to me.
- lt suits you.