They called it the car for Everyman.
Henry Ford himself called it
a car for the "great multitude."
It was functional and simple,
like your sewing machine
or your cast-iron stove.
You could learn to drive it
in less than a day,
and you could get any color
you wanted, so long as it was black.
When Ford first conceived the Model T,
it took 13 hours to assemble.
Within five years, he was
turning out a vehicle every 90 seconds.
Of course, the real invention wasn't the car,
it was the assembly line that built it.
Pretty soon, other businesses
had borrowed the same techniques.
Seamstresses became button sewers.
Furniture makers
became knob turners.
It was the beginning and the end
of imagination...
all at the same time.
Howard?
- Charles, I'm talking to you.
- Hmm?
They need spokes,
same as the others.
They oughta make a better spoke.
Yeah? Then what
would you do?
It was a land of opportunity.
The country was shrinking,
and there was life
to be made out West...
for any man with drive
and ambition.
If your dream was big enough
and you had the guts to follow it,
there was truly a fortune
to be made.
How are you, sir?
Damn thing blew on me.
What?
It's a Stanley Steamer.
The boiler blew.
- Oh?
- Can you fix it?
Uh...
Sure. Sure, I can fix it.
This is an amazing machine.
It's got a two-stroke boiler system...
that's heated
by this huge fire grate.
I mean, it's...
Well, it's basically
a very small locomotive.
Thank you.
Now, I made
some improvements.
It wasn't your boiler that was blowing;
it was your bleed valve.
So, with increased pressure,
I can see you getting
up to 40 miles an hour.
Really?
Oh, yeah. And if you superheat the excess,
I can see you reaching...
Fifty, maybe 60 miles an hour.
Is that right?
Easily. And the thing
of it is, Mr. Coughlin,
you don't feed it,
you don't stable it, and unless
you hit a lamppost, the thing's not
gonna get sick and die on ya.
- That's funny.
- To tell you the truth,
I wouldn't spend more than five dollars
on the best horse in America.
This is not the finish line, my friends.
This is the start of the race.
The future is the finish line!
And the new Buick White Streak
is just the car to take us there!
Four in-line cylinders,
421/2 horsepower,
- Wonderful.
- This is the same car you can buy at any
of our five showrooms across the Bay Area.
- "The age of the automobile is here,"
boasted Howard."The future has arrived."
Oh, my.
Read the part about
the future again.
- Oh, I'm kind of
dealing with it right now.
- Oh, sorry. Here. I'll take him.
Come here, big guy.
Come here. Come here.
Oh, are you the future, huh?
Are you the future?
Are you gonna...
Are you going to the moon?
The moon! Whee!
I'll take it.
Do we really
need all this?
No. No. We don't need it...
There's also a caretaker's house,
a paddock, a barn,
some very nice stables.
How big are the stables?
Got it.
Settle down. Settle down.
Quit. Quit. Whoa. Whoa.
Whoa.
Come on, Dad.
There you go.
You're not getting him a horse.
Why not?
He's great at it.
Because he's 16 years old.
- So?
So... he should earn it.
All right.
- All... All right. Quiet.
- Everybody knows it.
Nobody knows Longfellow.
Dickinson.
Ooh!
"We never know how high we are..."
Oh, I know that.
Yeah. I know.
I know it.
Well?
"We never know
how high we are
till we are called to rise."
- Good.
- Very good, John.
"And then, if we are true to plan,
our statures touch the skies."
- Excellent.
- Yes!
- That's really good.
Uh-oh.
- "The heroism..."
- Right.
Right."The heroism..."
"The heroism we recite...
"would be a daily thing,
That's it.
"Did not ourselves
the cubits warp,
for fear to be a king."
You should be riding it.
You knew the poem.
Yeah. But he
looks so perfect out there,
doesn't he?
Yeah. He does.
That's the poetry
right there, Agnes.
That's the poetry.
Thank you. Thank you for coming.
I came here 15 years ago
with 21 cents in my pocket.
I know a lot of us at the table
have a story like that.
And, you know,
I can't help thinking...
that if we can start out there
and end up here, where can't we go
in America?
Hmm? So, as corny as it sounds,
I'd like to propose a toast
to the future.
Because out here, my friends,
the sky is literally the limit.
To the future!
There were no suicides
on Wall Street that day.
It was a myth
that would grow over time.
The real effect of October 29
took a little longer to sink in.
By noon, all the gains
of the previous year
had been obliterated.
By 4:00 p. M., nearly $10 billion
of market value was gone.
Over the next two weeks,
the hemorrhage continued.
And before long,
25% of the workforce was unemployed.
A great national migration began.
Displaced families
took to the American highway...
in the last possession
that remained to them:
Their automobile.
And all at once,
millions of Americans...
had a new definition of home.
I made two dollars today.
- What?
- I made two dollars.
Here.
Where did you get these?
Yeah, your boy combed 'em out,
changed all the tack. I didn't have
to tell him a thing.
- Hey, Red,
Attaboy!
Where'd a young fella
like you learn so much about horses?
His name's Johnny.
You can call me Red.
Whoo!
Yeah! Whoo! Yeah!
What's wrong?
What's that?
Everything.
Dickens, Wordsworth.
There's your Arabian Nights
and Moby Dick, even your Milne,
from when you were...
Why? What's wrong?
Mr. Blodget here,
he has a house, a real house.
Dad... Dad, what's wrong?
- And his wife cooks.
- She is a good cook.
No. No. Shh. Dad. Shh.
There's even a phone next door.
We'll call you.
Every couple of weeks, we'll call you,
and we'll tell you where we are.
No. No.
We're just gonna go home,
all right? Let's go.
Listen to me.
You have a gift.
Don't... Don't do this.
Dad, don't do this.
We'll be back.
Go on. Go with Mr. Blodget.
No.
He's gonna take care of you, sweetie.
Go with him.
Mom, don't do this.
I don't know. You still
look pretty tall to be a jockey.
I've never been over 115.
Where'd you learn
to ride like that?
Home.
All right.
Here's the way it works.
I pay you $10 a week to ride.
You owe nine dollars for your meals,
six dollars to sleep in the stalls,
three dollar tack fee.
That's the deal.
How do I pay all that back?
You win.
Ow!
You son of a bitch!
Get off of me!
Yah!
Get lost!
Get off of me!
A nose?
You lose a race a nose,
you'd better fall off tryin!
Here. Muck these stalls down,
every damn one of'em!
A nose!
For Christ's sake!
No. No, Bill.
I'm not gonna do it.
No more layoffs.
Well, it can't
get any worse.
Look, if it stays like this,
we'll just...
Bill, we'll be fine, really.
We will.
All right. I'll see you in town.
Frankie, come on.
It's a glorious day outside.
- Why don't... Why don't you
go fishing or something?
- I'm reading.
You can read when it's raining.
Come on. I'll teach you to drive the truck.
You already taught me
to drive the truck.
- Well, what are you reading?
- Flash Gordon.
Come on, Dad. It's about the future!
We'll be in San Francisco
till Wednesday.
Yeah? What?
Come inside.
- I'm not done.
Sam can do that.
I don't want Sam to do it.
I want to do it.
- Annie.
- Don... Don... No!
Ma'am.
Come on, Red!
Come on!
At a time when the world
really needed a drink,
you couldn't get one
in the United States of America.
Liquor was illegal.
Diversions were scarce,
and there's just so much
a human being can do without.
Soon, the border town was born,
providing everything to the south
that their neighbor to the north
would not.
You could find anything:
Food, companionship,
decent gin,
and with gambling outlawed as well,
- the chance
to turn bad luck into good.
Relax! You got it!
You got it! You got it!
Go!
That jockey was ridin'
like he's got an anvil in his pocket.
I'm gonna bet
with you no more.
I no like it.
Who's that?
George Woolf,
greatest jockey in the world.
That's Charles Howard?
Yeah.
I thought
he came down here for a...
Quickie divorce?
- Why?
Look at him.
Nothing quick about that.
It was in the palace
of the great sultan.
Sultan of where?
The Sultan of Araby.
I'd been living there
for almost a year, racing his Arabians
across the desert by day...
and finishing my personal history
of the region by night.
Then one day, the sultan
summons me into his throne room.
He looks at me and says,
- "John Pollard..."
- "John Pollard,
you are my greatest jockey.
It is you I have chosen
to ride my hundred-mile race
from Kusmat to Tripoli."
200-mile.
All right. 200-mile.
Excuse me, sahib.
- You didn't need to wreck it, Georgie.
- When you started tellin' that story,
it was only 50 miles.
Yeah, well,
everything gets longer
in the retellin'.
Just ask your friend Wanda
over there.
You know, if you start ridin'
a little more and talkin' a little less,
you might start winnin' some races.
- I got two bucks says
I beat you in this one.
- I'm not sure if you do,
but I got five says I beat you.
Done.
- Give me odds.
You're the favorite.
- Even money.
- Nah! Forget it! Two-to-one!
- Fine.
You got it. Hey, Johnny.
You're on a speed horse. What
are you doin' back here with me?
I like the conversation,
and it's not a speed horse.
Don't try to hook me.
You goin' tonight?
Nah. You?
Nah.
What time?
I don't know. 8:00?
Okeydoke.
Oops. There's my hole!
Gotta go! Yah!
Goddamn it!
Whoa!
We got him!
- I'll take him.
- Get the hell out of here.
- I said, I'll take him.
- He's got a fractured foot.
If you're gonna shoot him anyway,
I'll save you the bullet.
- Whoa.
- Fine.
Let him go. Hey.
Let him have him.
Mira.
Now, bud.
Yeah, boy.
Okeydoke, Johnny.
There's the hole! Gotta fly!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
There once was a princess
from Siam...
who was sitting here
sort of like I am.
I wined her and dined her,
and then I reclined her.
Ah, shit.
What rhymes with Siam?
That's great.
You make that up?
Pretty obvious, huh?
- That's beautiful.
- No. You're beautiful.
Don't say that.
You pay me.
So, you wanna... you know...
get going?
Sure. Why not?
- How do you miss a hole like that?
- There's my hole! Gotta fly!
Are you blind?
Ngel, are you okay?
OI!
You don't wanna watch?
No. Not really.
I don't either.
OI!
So, what? They brought you
down here to make you feel better?
Is that it?
Yes. Sort of.
Those guys, they think
everything is fixed with a party.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
Oh. Marcela Zabala.
My sister, Isabella,
she's married...
No. No, no. I know.
Nice to meet you. Charles.
Mucho gusto.
So, do you feel better?
No. No, not really.
No. How could you?
With something like that.
Come on, buddy. Wake up.
Come on.
- Did I lose?
- Oh, no. You clobbered him.
Easy.
Easy, easy.
Nice and slow.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Come on. Let me
buy you some turtle soup.
I'm fine, George.
Go win yourself a race or something.
Let's go down to Sloan's,
and we'll just...
I'm fine, George.
I don't need your help, and I sure
as shit don't need your charity.
Leave me alone,
all right?
It's been 20 years
since I've been on a horse.
Don't worry.
It's the kind of thing
that comes right back.
Let's go.
Come on!
What? She got you back up on a horse,
and now you wanna buy 'em?
Yeah. Maybe. Maybe a couple.
You wanna win or just own 'em?
I wanna win.
What sort of question is that?
Well, you're gonna
need a trainer before
you buy horses.
No. You need two.
So you can fire one, eh?
Randy Thatcher's barn.
Trains about 50 or 60 ponies.
Good fella too.
Real horse person.
A real horse-shitter. Scusa.
Now, now. I don't know.
Maybe you want a smaller barn,
somebody who can take the time to...
Who's that?
- Huh?
Oh, he's a crackpot.
Lives alone in the bushes.
What's he do?
I don't know. He used
to be a trainer, farrier. Now he just
looks after that horse.
Come on.
Let's look at another barn.
- Howdy.
- Hello.
Wh... You hungry?
No. No, thanks.
I'm fine.
Charles Howard.
Tom... Smith.
Nice to meet you, Tom.
What's... What's in his bandage?
Oh, that's hawthorn root.
It increases circulation.
You wanna sit down?
Oh. All right.
Thank you.
Will he get better?
Already is... a little.
Will he race?
No. Not that one.
So why are you fixing him?
'Cause I can.
Every horse
is good for somethin'.
He could be a cart horse
or a lead pony.
And he's still nice to look at.
You know, you don't
throw a whole life away...
just 'cause
he's banged up a little.
Is that coffee?
Yeah.
It's bad, though.
You always tell the truth?
Well, I try to.
It ain't just the speed.
It's the heart.
You want something
that's not afraid to compete.
Half these horses
are just show ponies.
You want something
that's not gonna run from a fight.
How do you find that?
Look, I won the Robles Handicap.
I was second in the Tijuana Derby.
I won the Manzanita Oaks.
You know, that used to be a stakes race.
I know.
I would've won T.J.,
but the piece of shit lugged out on me.
- Sounds great. We'll let ya know.
- Look. I can work 'em out in the morning.
Or even hot-walk 'em
if you need me to.
Really? You'll hot-walk 'em?
This is somethin' else.
A dream come true,
walkin' you around.
Hook you up to a plow,
pull me around for a little while.
Come on.
You ever run in the money?
Huh?
Hey. Hey.
You ever run in the money?
I don't think so. Couldn't beat
a human being, let alone another horse.
You goddamn sack-of-crap
old plater.
Probably the fastest
you're gonna run in your entire life,
you piece-of-shit old glue-pot.
That's right.
The first time
he saw Seabiscuit, the colt was walking
through the fog at 5:00 in the morning.
Smith would say later that the horse
looked right through him...
as if to say,
"What the hell are you looking at?
Who do you think you are?"
He was a small horse,
barely 15 hands.
He was hurting too.
There was a limp in his walk,
a wheezing when he breathed.
Smith didn't pay attention
to that.
He was looking the horse
in the eye.
God... damn.
He was the son of Hard Tack,
sired by the mighty Man O' War.
But the breeding did little
to impress anyone at Claiborne Farms.
Get rid of him.
At six months,
he was shipped off to train with
the legendary trainer Sunny Fitzsimmons,
who, over time,
developed a similar opinion of the colt.
Is that a racehorse
or a lead pony?
The judgment wasn't helped
by his gentle nature.
Where his sire had been a fierce,
almost violent competitor,
Seabiscuit took to sleeping
for huge chunks of the day...
and enjoyed lolling for hours
under the boughs of the juniper trees.
His other great talent was eating.
Though half the size of other colts,
Seabiscuit could frequently
eat twice as much.
Fitzsimmons decided
the horse was lazy...
and felt sure he could train
the obstinance out of him.
I want you to hit him
as many times as you can
over a quarter of a mile.
When he didn't improve,
they decided the colt
was incorrigible.
They made him a training partner
to better horses,
forcing him to lose
head-to-head duels...
to boost the confidence
of the other animal.
By the time
he was three years old,
Seabiscuit was struggling
in two cheap claiming races a week.
Soon he grew as bitter and angry
as his sire Hard Tack had been.
He was sold
for the rock-bottom price
of $2,000.
And, of course,
it all made sense.
Champions were large,
they were sleek,
they were without imperfection.
When they finally did race him,
he did just what
they had trained him to do.
He lost.
What exactly
is it you like?
He's got spirit.
I'll say.
Can... Can he be ridden?
Oh, sure.
Eventually.
He can be
a little touchy.
Yeah, I got it.
No. Really.
I'm fine.
Jesus Christ!
That horse is nuts!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Let's go! Come on,
you sons of bitches!
Let's go!
Come on!
Let's go! Come on,
you sons of bitches!
I'll take all of you!
Come on! Come on!
It's okay.
I'm not afraid of you.
Sure. I know.
I know what
you're all about.
You hungry?
Huh?
Yeah. Bet you are.
Huh? Come on.
Come on, boy.
Yeah.
Why don't you just
breeze him around
one turn.
Give the folks a look.
Right.
Red Pollard,
Mr. And Mrs. Howard.
Yeah. Hi.
Hello.
Well, we'll just
be movin' on.
Does he breeze?
Well, we'll find out.
Seems pretty fast.
Yeah.
In every direction.
Hell, he's so beat up,
it's hard to tell what he's like.
I just can't help feelin'
they got him...
so screwed up
runnin'in a circle,
he's forgotten
what he was born to do.
He just needs to learn
how to be a horse again.
Well, how do
you do that?
How far do you
want me to take him?
Till he stops.
Okay.
That seems like
a pretty good ride.
Hope so.
That's it, boy.
You're all right.
Let's see what you got, boy.
Ha! Ha!
Ha! Ha! Whoo!
That's it, boy. That's it!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Well, at least
he wasn't expensive.
No. That's true.
Whoo!
Goddamn it!
You're an amazing animal!
Whoo!
You can
come inside, you know.
I'm fine. Thank you.
Yeah,
you look it.
No, really, I'm fine.
Okay.
Suit yourself.
Welcome.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It's okay.
Oh, I'm not that hungry.
Mmm. Sure you're not.
It's just a lot of food.
It's okay.
Rather have you strong than thin.
They called it "relief,"
but it was
a lot more than that.
It had dozens of names:
N.R.A., W.P.A.,
the C.C.C.
But it really came down
to just one thing.
For the first time
in a long time,
someone cared.
For the first time
in a long time,
you were no longer alone.
Goat racing?
Oh, no. Just trying
to calm him down a little.
Smart ones
hate being alone
all the time.
Oh.
And sometimes
another animal,
it just...
just soothes them a bit.
Pretty quiet in there.
What'd you do?
Go take a look.
Oh.
# Rock of ages, cleft for me #
# I am hid and safe in thee #
# For the water
and the blood #
# From thy riven... #
Okay. You don't
break him or anything,
but we gotta see
what he's got.
You take him
to the 5 pole...
and turn him loose.
Turn him loose?
Yeah, son.
He's a racehorse.
Ha! Ha!
Come on!
Ha! Come on!
I know you got more than this!
Let's show 'em, boy!
How's he look?
Asleep.
Come on!
Let's show 'em, Pops!
Whoo! There it is! Yeah!
Whoo!
Oh, my.
Yeah, you and me! Let's go!
Whoo! Whoo-hoo!
- Boy. Fast?
- Oh. Yeah.
How fast?
Your horse just broke
the track record at Tanforan.
Sometimes they...
they just, uh,
hanker for a little competition.
As long as we're talkin' long shots,
I got a real doozy for you, folks.
We got a horse
that's going off at 70-to-1,
and that's a short price, my friends.
This horse couldn't win
a church raffle, let alone
a $2,000 allowance.
Yeah, talk about
a jump in class.
This is the skunk
of the garden party.
Yes, he's the surprise
in the punch bowl.
As a matter of fact, I'll lay
even money that this nag, Seabiscuit,
couldn't even finish six furlongs.
This is Tick-Tock McGlaughlin
live at Clockers' Corner.
Wow.
I wanted maroon.
They only had bright red.
Oh, it looks great.
You don't think
the "H" is too big?
You seen the size
of our jockey?
Come on.
Okay. Favorite's
that gray over there.
He's got a big late charge,
so lock in early with him
and stay right off his flank.
Okay.
Once our boy sees
who the competition is,
he'll do most of the work.
But don't move
till that gray does.
What if it's late?
Let's go.
Twelve minutes to post.
I don't think
it's gonna matter much.
Honestly.
- Come on in.
Number 3, Pollard on Seabiscuit.
Hey, sahib.
Kinda small, isn't he?
Gonna look a lot smaller
in a second, Georgie.
I got five bucks
says he doesn't.
Starter's poised. The flag is up.
And there they go.
Pirate's Gold breaks first,
followed by Geronimo
on the outside.
Silver Treasure is third,
followed by Seabiscuit.
They're coming by
the five-furlong pole.
It's Pirate's Gold, Geronimo,
Hill's Army and Agua Dulce.
Whoa!
Son of a bitch!
Ha! Ha!
Piece of shit bastard!
What the hell is he doing?
...opening up a 3...
a 4-length lead...
- Let's go!
- What are you doing?
I'm gonna put you on the rail,
you piece of shit!
- Get off of me!
- How do you like that,
you son of a bitch?
You're gonna drop me, man!
The two horses are flying down...
- You like the rail?
- Here comes the cavalry charge!
- Knock me off my horse!
It's Silver Treasure on the inside.
Silver Treasure on the inside.
Silver Treasure and Pirate's Gold.
And at the wire
it's Silver Treasure.
Aw, damn it.
What the hell
were you thinkin'?
He fouled me.
- What am I supposed to do,
let him get away with that?
- Well, yeah, when he's 40-to-1.
- He almost put me in the rail!
- Well, did he?
Look, we had a plan.
He fouled me, Tom!
What am I supposed to do?
He cut me off!
He fouled me!
Son? Son.
What are you so mad at?
There's a phone next door.
We'll call you.
Every couple of weeks, we'll call you
and tell you where we are.
No. We're just gonna
go home. All right?
You have a gift.
I need to borrow some money.
All right.
I, uh,
I haven't been to a dentist,
and m...
Well, l-I need to borrow
some money.
- That's fine.
- I don't know when
I can pay you back.
I mean, when we win.
When we win, I can pay you back.
That is if you
still want me to ride.
Of course I want you to ride.
How much do you need?
Uh,
ten dollars.
Here.
Than... Uh...
It's fine.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
That's it, Pops.
We're okay now.
It's all right, boy.
Yeah, we're okay.
Nothing to worry about.
All the time in the world, boy.
That's it, Pops.
Nice lead.
Just like that, boy.
Just like that.
What do you think, boy?
You ready to go?
You and me.
Let's go, boy. Let's go. Ha! Ha!
Ha! Ha!
Whoo!
In the end, it wasn't the dams...
or the roads
or the bridges or the parks.
Or the tunnels
or the thousands
of other public projects...
that were built
in those years.
It was more invisible
than that.
Men who were broken
only a year before...
suddenly felt restored.
Men who'd been shattered
suddenly found their voice.
Well, I just think
this horse has a lot of heart.
He may have been down,
but he wasn't out.
He may have lost a few,
but he didn't
let it get to him.
We could all learn
a lick or two
from this little guy.
Oh, and by the way,
he doesn't know he's little.
He thinks he's
the biggest horse out there.
- So you got big plans
for this little horse?
Oh, yeah. See, sometimes
when the little guy,
he doesn't know
he's a little guy,
he can do great big things.
Can we get a shot here?
See, this isn't
the finish line.
The future is the finish line,
and the Biscuit is just the horse
to get us there.
"Just the horse to get us there."
You certainly made a believer
out of me, Mr. Howard.
It's time for this old tout
to eat some crow.
Four and 20 blackbirds,
to be exact, all baked up
in some humble pie,
and I'll take mine la mode.
Oh.
And one more thing, Mr. Howard.
I just wanna say...
Thanks for the champagne.
Don't mention it.
Did you see the infield?
No, not yet.
Take a look.
Your little horse is sellin' out
the cheap seats.