There either is or is not
a way things are.
The color of the day.
How it felt to be a child.
The feeling of saltwater
on your sunburned legs.
Sometimes the water is yellow.
Sometimes it's red.
The color in memory
depends on the day.
I won't tell the story
the way it happened.
I'll tell it the
way I remember it.
Help! Help!
What's your name?
- Whisper. What's your name? Whisper!
- Finn.
- What's your last name?
- Bell.
- Where do you live?
- By the pier.
Do you have tools?
Do you know what bolt cutters are?
Do you or don't you?
I can find you
and gut you like a fish.
I'll pull out your insides
and make you eat them, hear me?
Be here tomorrow at dawn with bolt
cutters and food, or I'll kill you.
I'll kill you if you tell.
- Anyone! Your folks...
- They're dead.
If you tell anyone, the last sound
you hear will be your own scream. Go!
Finn!
- Oh, it's you, Joe.
- Did I scare you?
- So you went out today?
- Yeah! I got a nice tan.
No fish.
Setting traps, like everybody.
- Where's the fire?
- Nowhere. Just got homework.
Maggie's on a kind of rant today,
so you be careful, okay?
- Are you coming home soon?
- In an hour.
If you finish your work,
we'll go to Carvel's.
You rest up. We've got
a gardening job tomorrow.
- Joe?
- Yeah?
Nothing.
Hey, Finn!
How do you smoke a swordfish?
Put the bill in your mouth
and light the tail.
I'll see you later.
I was raised with some
freedom from my sister, Maggie.
Joe was her man.
They banned big fishing rigs
that year, and we were poor.
We got by on what Joe earned
on charters and lawn work.
Hey.
Come on, come here.
Come on!
Are you alone?
- You deaf? Are you alone?
- No.
You're not alone
or you're not deaf?
Here, I brought you
something to drink.
Attaboy!
Here, I took this for you.
What's this?
Birth control pills?
Here, this too.
Percodan.
Attaboy, now you're talking.
What else?
Come on, come on, come on!
Do you bite your nails?
That's a bad habit.
People say the eyes
are the windows to the soul. Bullshit.
Hands. That's the sign of a gentleman.
Come on, let's go. Come on.
- What?
- Come on.
- In the boat.
- If I don't get home...
Fuck your uncle, get in the boat.
Pick up the anchor. Let's go.
Shut up and get in the boat.
- Where are we going?
- Mexico.
- What?
- Police boat.
Stop!
Ahoy there!
Son, are you all right?
- Where are you headed?
- Nowhere.
Some lady thought she saw a raft
here yesterday.
A man on it wearing a prison suit.
Did you see anything like that?
- No.
- Tie up a line. We'll tow you in.
That was the end of it.
Perhaps you had an experience
like that as a child and told no one.
Perhaps you had a brush with
a world so large you seldom...
... or never saw it again.
Jesus! It's the land time forgot.
Nora Driggers Dinsmoor.
Wait here. I'll find out
what they want us to do.
- Is it all right if I look around?
- No! You stay put till I come back.
God knows what's in these weeds.
Nora Driggers Dinsmoor,
richest lady in the gulf.
She lost her mind 30 years ago
when her fiancé left her...
... at the altar.
What's your name?
Finn.
Hey, Finn!
We're out of here. She slipped me
$500 under the door.
Gas money, she called it.
Weirdest thing.
- What?
- Nothing. Can I ride with you?
You smell like fertilizer.
Really? I do?
Mag!
- You've got the wrong number.
- You won't believe...
Yes, well, he just...
Did he do something bad?
I'll be glad to.
That sounds really...
You got it. Okay.
Three on Saturday. This Saturday?
And thank you so much, ma'am.
You won't believe
where we were today.
That was Nora Driggers Dinsmoor.
It was too good to be true.
She wants her money back?
She wants him. Finn!
The richest lady
in the state calls me...
...and wants my little brother
to play with her niece.
"Why"? The old bat liked you.
He's a likable kid, he's adorable.
Who cares? Joe, this is
a really good thing.
How'd she even know...?
Dinsmoor never met Finn.
She slipped this under the door.
What is it, Joe? God!
Do you like living with all
the dead people down here?
What's wrong with people here?
I'm tired of working so much.
They took away the nets.
Convict Arthur Lustig
was recaptured this evening.
This concludes
a four-day manhunt for Lustig...
... the convicted murderer
of Gene Valiente.
Valiente, reputed mob boss
of the Catalano family...
... was gunned down in his home
last Christmas.
Lustig will be returned
to death row...
... and is scheduled to die
by lethal injection March 16th.
Holy shit!
Hey, you look sharp.
- How do I smell?
- You smell clean. Tea time.
- Be polite. "Yes, ma'am", "No, ma'am".
- I will.
- Are you okay with this?
- He's great. Go ahead.
Say, "May I", "Please", all that stuff.
Oh, the gardener.
The design of this floor is
from the Alhambra in Spain.
The ceiling's gold leaf, real gold.
It's just like the Thousand
Wing ceiling at Venice's Accademia.
Old Ms. Dinsmoor
hadn't been seen in years.
I'd heard she was crazy.
Go ahead.
Aren't you coming?
But nobody knew how crazy.
Her room smelled of dead
flowers and cat piss.
Boom boom.
Chicka-boom!
Besame, besame mucho
Each time I cling to your kiss
I hear music divine
Hold me my darling and say
that you'll always be mine
This joy's something new, my arms
they're holding you
I never knew this thrill before
Whoever thought I'd be holding you
close, whispering...
- Who are you?
- Finn, ma'am.
- What are you doing in my bedroom?
- I don't know.
Give me your hand.
- What is this?
- Your... Your boob.
My heart. It's my heart. It's broken.
- Can you tell?
- I'm sorry.
"Sorry." Come.
Shoo, shoo. Tabby, scram.
Wow! That's the biggest cat
I've ever seen.
- What do you feed it?
- Other cats.
Well, go ahead.
You can proceed.
- Dance.
- Huh?
I'd like you to dance. That's why
you're here. To entertain me.
Pony, foxtrot, frug,
Philly Dog, fandango. Anything.
I can't. I'm sorry, ma'am.
You "can't"? "I'm sorry, ma'am."
Or you won't? You dance.
Dance, dance, dance!
- Get out of here.
- Wait!
I can draw.
You can use my lipstick and eyebrow
pencil on the dressing table.
Estella!
Estella?
- Is tea ready?
- I'd like you to sit for a portrait.
- A portrait? By whom?
- That boy.
The gardener?
I'll be in my room.
Come back and sit.
Please.
And you. Come sit by me.
She's beautiful, isn't she?
What do you think of her?
Come on, whisper in my ear.
Come on.
I think she's a snob.
Anything else?
I think she's real pretty.
I think she doesn't like me.
But you love her.
She'll break your heart, it's a fact.
It's tragic, you're already in love.
And though I guarantee you...
...that the girl will hurt you
terribly, you'll still pursue her.
Ain't love grand?
- I'd like to go now.
- Have you finished?
Before I'm a teenager, please.
Can I go now?
Would you like to come again?
Would you like to see Estella again?
Yes.
Poor boy, poor boy, poor boy.
This is yours, dear.
The ways of the rich and all my
longing, which began that day.
To paint for the rich, to have
their freedom, to love Estella.
The things we cannot have.
Give this to your guardian.
Would you see Finn out, please?
Chicka-boom!
Want some?
It's not poisoned.
You remember it.
You remember how it felt.
And then I went home to draw it.
I'm going to work.
What are you going to do before bed?
Brush my teeth.
That's really beautiful, Finn.
Keep it up, okay?
Maggie left that night.
She never came back.
I'll see you when you wake up.
Joe raised me.
We never said a word.
I visited Paradiso Perduto Saturdays.
Feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it.
The money Dinsmoor paid
kept me in paints and brushes.
And there was Estella.
Smile. Smile.
Smi... All right, don't smile.
Yes, feel it!
Wonderful, wonderful!
Feel it in your bones.
- Where are you going?
- Cocktails at Rewald's.
Lane? Another cocktail,
and we'll be able to eat him.
Carl Rewald. Lane is his father.
Carl doesn't drink.
Cue balls. The whole family's pickled.
Who's your escort?
- Please, this is the '80s...
- I'll bring you.
Finn will make a fine date.
Oh, God!
Then it's done.
Fine, but you meet me there. 1115
North Ocean. Wear your dinner jacket.
- How much time have you got?
- None, I'm late! I'm dead. Wow!
That'll pass as a dinner jacket.
- This is a girl's.
- Keep it buttoned, no one will notice.
- Where did you get this?
- It's Maggie's.
- It's one of the only things she left.
- What a bitch!
What?
- "What?" Come here.
- Jesus!
- Are you all right for money?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- A little nervous?
- Yeah, a little.
There you go.
You just be yourself, huh?
Come on, have fun.
- You're not on the list.
- Check the name Dinsmoor?
I did, sir. You're not on this list.
Please leave now.
Hi, Mrs. Lee!
Use your usual spot.
Hi.
- Do you want to get me out of here?
- Yes.
Come on in.
- Where do you want to go?
- Your house?
All right. Let's go.
The moths are
from the Thousand Wing ceiling.
Joe's not here. He's...
He's playing dominoes.
- Is that your room?
- Yeah.
I wasn't really
expecting company...
...you know.
- You still draw.
- Yeah.
They're hanging a couple
at Washington Federal.
The bank?
- Go to New York.
- New York?
Center of the art world.
Here, you'll end up painting
coconuts for tourists.
- When did you do this?
- A while ago.
I don't wear my hair like that
anymore.
But you should.
- I mean...
- Do you like it that way?
What else do you like?
How come we see each other
every week, but we never did anything?
- "Did anything"?
- Saw a movie, whatever.
You never asked.
And if I had?
I'm here, aren't I?
- Are you with anyone?
- Right this second?
- No, I mean like...
- Like a steady boyfriend?
No.
- You could have anyone.
- No, I...
What about you?
- Why not?
- 'Cause I...
I just...
I know.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- It's late. What time is it?
- It's 10:30. Where are you going?
I've got to get home.
I have a million things to do tonight.
Stay!
Don't speak French.
Estella?
Excuse me. Have you seen Estella?
Dinsmoor was weirder than
usual, but I had to see Estella.
I never come here. Never.
Do you know why?
Twenty-six years ago, I trusted.
I saved myself. I was a virgin.
It's funny, huh?
Those were the times,
that's how I was raised.
What kind of creature takes
such a thing, such a gift, a trust?
Who does this? Takes advantage
of a 42-year-old woman?
What kind of creature leaves
this woman waiting like a fool?
A man does this, so men must pay.
Am I right?
- Estella will make men weep.
- Do you know where she is?
She'll break them.
I taught her well.
When she returns, she'll cut through
them like a hot knife through butter.
- Returns?
- Oh, my dear boy!
Didn't you know?
She's left for school.
Switzerland for two years, then Paris.
Didn't she say goodbye?
I'm sure she meant to.
See you next week, dear.
Seven years passed.
I stopped going to Paradiso Perduto.
I stopped painting.
I put aside fantasy and the wealthy...
... and the heavenly girl
who did not want me.
None of it would happen to me again.
I'd seen through it.
I elected to grow up.
Finn! This is Jerry Ragno.
Jerry, Mr. Ragno
is a lawyer in Miami.
And New York. We have
offices in Manhattan. So, Finn...
...I'm empowered by my client
to make your dreams come true.
Really? Any particular dream
or just all of them?
Have you ever shown your work?
No.
They had Finn's painting
at Washington Federal Bank.
Eight years ago. I gave all that up.
I don't understand what this is about.
How would you like a one-man show
at the Thrall Gallery?
My client, Erica Thrall, wants you
in New York for a one-man show.
Have you ever sent slides
to the Thrall Gallery?
I sent slides everywhere
in high school.
They made an impression.
A ticket to New York...
...plus $ 1000 for incidentals.
Sorry, they're all in hundreds.
The hundreds aren't the problem.
I just... I don't paint anymore.
Whose business was it
what I did with my life?
Who'd gotten my life in order? Me.
I was in control.
And everything I wanted, I had.
Ms. Dinsmoor?
Are cocktails ready, Thomas?
No, it's me. It's Finn.
- I came...
Looking for Estella.
- That hook is in deep, isn't it, dear?
- I came to ask you a question.
After nearly 10 years
without a word, without a visit...
...you've come to interrogate me.
How interesting.
- I'm sorry. Things happened.
- The love of your life left you.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Come closer.
I've gone red.
- I noticed. It's nice.
- And look at you.
All grown up. A man.
Ms. Dinsmoor, a lawyer named Ragno
came to see me.
- The spider.
- Do you know him?
"Ragno" means "spider" in Italian.
You must learn other languages.
He represents an art gallery owner in
New York who wants to show my work.
You can draw. Can't dance
worth a shit, but you can draw.
Did you know anything about this?
- Estella is in New York.
- I doubt our paths will cross.
- So you're going?
- Should I?
I remember watching you
from that very window.
Scared little mouse scurrying across
my garden and through my front door.
Now another door opens.
What will our mouse do?
- I expect an invitation.
- I'm sorry?
To your opening, your show.
- What equipment are you flying?
- What?
Is it a wide body or a 767?
I've no idea,
I just hope it stays up there.
- You'd better get on.
- Yeah.
What happens if I get up there
and I can't deliver?
Finn. There's nothing harder
than being given your chance.
- At least that's what I hear.
- Yeah?
Taxi!
- Have you got change for a dollar?
- What?
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Fuck you, man! Fuck you!
Well, then, there I was.
Ms. Dinsmoor, as my secret benefactor,
sent me to New York to draw.
To have the girl, to have it all.
And I looked out on the great city,
as so many before, which held it all.
And it was that close,
and it was mine.
"Liebchen, guten Morgen." Are you still
holding the red and green Picasso?
I think I have somebody interested.
No, I can't say right now.
Just the Picasso.
Fabelhaft. Danke.
Here's where you
show me your work, darling.
- I told you, I don't have any.
- Then you'd better get busy.
Why am I here?
You saw some slides?
I gave Keith Haring a show
after he drew a sketch in my hand.
But which paintings did you like?
I saw the beginning of something,
and here you are.
Annette, Sotheby's.
What you do is up to you. Stay and
paint or enjoy the sights and go home.
Either way, I always enjoy
meeting a young painter.
Look, I mean, I'll do it.
I said that I'll do the paintings.
Wonderful. Call Marcy
when you have something for us.
And I could still draw.
Nothing had lessened it as much
as I had abused it, abandoned it.
It was a gift, and it was still mine.
And everything else was less real.
What can it mean?
That picture of the world.
But when it's true, we recognize it
in ourselves, in others.
We recognize it, like love,
completely undeserved.
You're drooling.
So, Finn Bell.
In New York.
That's right.
I thought I saw you last Christmas.
I was driving down 5th.
I just got here.
Actually, now that I see you,
this guy was bigger.
- He's bigger.
- Fatter.
- He had long hair.
- You thought it was me?
- I hadn't seen you in years.
- It has been a while.
And here we are.
- I have to run.
- Wait, maybe we could...
Tomorrow at the Borough Club
around 6. I'm meeting some friends.
If you're free, that is.
I'm free.
I'm glad you're here.
A long time ago there lived
two brilliant artists. True geniuses.
One day one of them
was painting out in the forest...
... and he came upon this dog
who was crying, obviously lost.
A puppy.
Yes, sure. A puppy, fine.
He couldn't concentrate anyway,
so he scooped the puppy up...
... and took him into town
to find its owner...
... who turned out to be
the prince of the kingdom...
... who was eternally grateful
and very wealthy.
That artist's name was Michelangelo.
True story.
The other artist's name was... Nobody
knows, he was never heard from again.
Right, that's so true, Walter.
Can I smoke?
- It's your last one.
- That's all right.
So you... Cigarette, please.
You're from Florida too?
- Yes.
- Everybody is from Florida.
I'm not, I hate Florida.
Too much sun.
Really?
Actually, Finn was my childhood...
What were you exactly?