Once upon a time, in the little village
of Pudding-on-the-Ritz...
there lived a wolf named Phox.
That's Phox with a ''PH.'' P-H-O-X.
My card.
There was no one so clever
at driving a bargain.
This horse is exactly what you need,
Grandpa.
Got a three-speed bridle,
matching horse shoes, wide sidewalls.
lt's a steal at 40 pazoozas.
- Can l look at its teeth?
- Teeth? Teeth?
You buying a horse or a beauty queen?
Come on, now.
Well, all right.
Here's your money.
And here's your horse!
Well, come on, horsie.
Hey! l wanted a live horse!
lt was alive--
but l didn't say when.
Nobody liked the Phox with a ''PH,'' but
nobody could ever get the better of him.
One day, the sly Phox was tripping
through the woods...
Oh, hardy, har, har.
when he chanced upon a mysterious box
sitting in an open glade.
On its top was written
this strange legend.
''To take my treasure you may try...
but he who opens me shall die!''
A treasure chest!
Gadzooks, l'm in luck!
But whoever opens it shall die.
Ergo, l got to get some dummy
to open it for me.
But who would be that much
of a nitwit?
Desmond Dullwit wasn't exactly
the village idiot.
- But l came in second.
- Desmond, old buddy!
l need somebody to open a box for me.
No, you don't.
Whoever opens that box is gonna die.
- How do you know that?
- l was listening to the story.
So l ain't gonna open it.
But you must, Desmond.
That box holds a beautiful princess
who was put under a spell...
by a wicked witch, remember?
- Well, listen.
- Little did Desmond know...
that the wily Phox
was an accomplished ventriloquist.
Oh, help! Help me, Desmond!
There is somebody in there!
Hey, how does she know my name?
Why, she's been secretly
in love with you for years.
Oh, joy bells!
Hang on, honey!
Lover pumpkin is here!
Sainted Aunt Hannah!
Look at that!
Gold! Jewelry!
Queen Victoria's spittoon!
l'm rich! Rich!
l don't see a princess, Mr. Phox.
Of course not, you stupid lox.
lt was a joke. Get it?
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
You go get yourself a big crocus sack
and we'll divide all the treasure.
Half and half, even steven, 80-20.
All right--
but l'd rather have a princess.
No sooner had Desmond gone then the wily
Phox pulled out a sack of his own...
and began filling it
with the priceless treasure.
Meanwhile...
Desmond wandered through the lavender
glen looking for a crocus sack.
There he chanced upon
a beautiful milkmaid.
Hi there, missy.
You wouldn't happen to have
an old crocus sack would you?
Why, l'm wearing one.
l just need it
to put my priceless treasure into.
Priceless treasure!
Just a minute, honey!
- Here you are.
- Thanks a bunch.
Wait for me, lover pumpkin!
The smarmy Phox had filled his sack
when he noticed one small coin...
left in the chest.
An lndian-head penny!
Of course the greedy Phox
had to have it.
Are you kiddin'? They bring
three pazoozas on the open market.
But, in reaching
for that last penny...
Phox overbalanced and--
Here l am, Mr. Phox.
Oh, lookie! He must have left
my share for me.
- But where'd he go?
- l'm in the box! Let me out!
Sure you are!
What a kidder.
Get me out of here!
Well, thanks for divvying it up
with me, Mr. Phox--
wherever you are.
And the stupid lox ambled off,
followed by the beautiful milkmaid.
Hold it, sugar-puss!
Years later, whenever anyone would ask
about the Phox with the ''PH''...
the answer was always the same.
Who cares?
As for Desmond Dullwit, he and his
beautiful wife lived happily...
to a ripe old age.
Wait a minute. The legend said
that whoever opened the box would die.
Yeah, but it didn't say when.
Once upon a time in Canada,
there unfolded a tale...
of heroes and villains.
And it all began with two boys,
a girl and a horse.
l don't know, Dudley.
Choosing what you want to be when
you grow up is a very serious matter.
lt's not a question
of what l want, Nell.
lt's my destiny to become
a Royal Canadian Mountie.
l think l'm going to have
to get out there and see the world...
before l choose.
What a bunch of wimps.
Why? What are you gonna be, Snidely?
Me? lsn't it obvious?
l'm gonna be the bad guy.
- Why?
- 'Cause the bad guy has all the fun.
And if you're the bad guy,
you get to do stuff like this.
And this!
So long, Mountie boy!
l can ride better than that.
l can do this better too.
Why, Dudley!
Come on, Nell.
Though young Nell's heart was torn
between Dudley and Snidely--
her two very best friends
in the world--
Dudley's mind was filled
with nothing but visions...
of growing up to be a Mountie.
Of course, this surely wouldn't hurt
in his quest for the young Nell.
For a Mountie is always brave...
and strong and cool.
Let's try that again, shall we?
A Mountie is always brave
and strong and--
lt was 20 years later, and Dudley
Do-Right had fulfilled his destiny.
He had grown up to be
a Royal Canadian Mountie.
And his faithful horse, Horse,
who had grown up as well...
was the best-trained horse
this side of Ottawa.
Fetch.
Okay, so he wasn't that well trained.
Still, Dudley was a member
in good standing...
of the Royal Canadian Mounted Police.
He had his own grown-up fort.
He had his own grown-up office.
He had indeed grown up...
to be brave and strong and cool.
Now, Dudley's lifelong rival,
Snidely K. Whiplash...
had fulfilled his destiny as well.
He had become the bad guy...
and he had brought a bunch of his
bad-guy friends with him.
Can l help you?
Could you wait till
everyone's in, please?
- What's the meaning of this?
- This is a holdup.
Now give us all your gold and all
your money or we'll shoot you.
- All of you?
- All of us!
No, wait.
Kevin, go and get the money.
- Yes, sir.
- Don't forget the gold.
And don't forget the gold.
lt's been a pleasure
doing business with you.
We got the money and the gold!
Let's go, boys!
Snidely knew the call would go out
to Canada's number one Mountie.
Too bad he was tied up
with official Mountie business.
The anchovies go on the half
with the pepperoni...
and then it's one-quarter garlic
and one-quarter olives.
Good. Twenty minutes?
That's it.
Thanks, Mom.
l love you too.
Here we go.
Meanwhile, back at Snidely's
not-so-secret hideout--
Here's the money,
but where's the gold?
- Whiplash took it.
- Where is Whiplash?
He's got to be here somewhere.
He took off with all the gold!
All we have is this measly $26,000!
We got to find Whip!
He's tricked us!
And when we do,
we're gonna kill him--
really slowly.
- Yeah, but where is he?
- That's a good question.
- l heard he was in the Sudan.
- Where's that?
ln Africa, stupid.
- He's supposedly at the Hilton Hotel.
- The Hilton, eh?
Come on, boys!
Let's go get him!
What the boys didn't know was that
it was Snidely himself who was...
sending them to the far reaches
of the world.
Yes, he really was
a very bad guy.
lt's all so easy.
All you have to do is find 999...
of the stupidest criminals
in North America...
and everything just falls into place.
There's only one man
who can stop me now.
And that one man could only be...
Dudley Do-Right
of the Royal Canadian Mounted Police.
Meanwhile,
at an abandoned gold mine...
a sinister figure lurks.
l love to lurk.
lt's so me.
Everyone knew there wasn't any gold
left in the old mine...
but it was part of Snidely's
evil plan to put some there.
The old mine shaft just caved in.
l've warned those kids.
Come on. Time to go to the dark
and scary part of the forest.
Fine. l'll take the vehicle.
All you kids come on out of there.
l'm hardly a kid.
All right. Queensberry rules.
Let's go. Put 'em up.
Ready when you are, DD.
- Why do you have a shotgun?
- l was hunting.
ln an abandoned gold mine?
Yes. l was hunting for vampires.
- Vampires?
- Afraid so.
- Vampires.
- Believe me, Do-Right, they exist.
- l don't believe you.
- Hold this.
Examine, if you will,
this shell from a shotgun.
You'll notice it's not shot,
but gold instead.
lt's well-known--
to kill a vampire...
you must drive a stake through its heart
or shoot it with a golden bullet.
Oh. So then there really are
vampires around here?
Sadly, behind every tree, practically.
- What was that?
- l shudder to speculate.
- l have to go.
- l thought you might.
So long.
And so it went. While the evil Whiplash
was out hunting vampires...
our hero was at home, hiding
behind a cardboard Mountie cutout.
After all, even to a real Mountie,
vampires can seem awfully scary.
Vampires indeed.
Another week and
l'll have those idiots thinking...
there's gold in them there hills.
ln the daylight hours,
Snidely was hard at work...
arranging a meeting between a really
big train and the local bank president.
ls that a choo-choo train
l hear coming our way?
l can't do this to our customers.
You'll own everything!
All right, all right. l'll sign.
All the bank's mortgages are yours.
And a teller to be named later.
All right! Pay off the mortgage now, or
this quaint little fixer upper is mine!
- You're not our banker.
- l am now.
Read it and weep.
How can you do this to us?
How can l do this to you?
Madam, l was born to do it.
lt's in my genes. Now get out,
and take your munchkins with you.
That's right. Chop-chop.
Single file.
And wipe that smile off your face.
And no talking.
With his ill-gotten gains,
Snidely Whiplash was taking over...
all of Semi-Happy Valley,
and that included the local motel...
the Slaw-Dogs stand...
the funeral home...
the very town itself.
Naturally, local residents
became a mite concerned.
What's going on out here?
What's wrong?
We've all just lost
our homes and businesses.
Yeah!
Oh! Well, that's a relief.
lt is?
Yes. l thought that this was
about the vampires.
No! This is about that bloodsucker,
Snidely Whiplash.
He's taken everything--
our homes, our businesses, our farms.
- Yeah!
- What do you mean, ''vampires''?
You mean you don't know?
- The woods are filled with them.
- What?
Our hero, Dudley Do-Right,
had never felt so alone.
Whiplash City was a ghost town.
His long-lost Nell
had been gone for years.
Now it was just him and Horse.
lt's just you and me, Horse.
lf l know anything, Horse,
these two things are true--
Nell will never come back...
and you will never leave me.
Horse, where are you going?
There's vampires out there!
- Who goes there?
- What?
Don't ''what'' me--
Don't ''what'' me!
l know you're a vampire.
l'm gonna warn you--
l've got garlic in here.
lt's me, Dudley.
lt's Nell Fenwick.
Don't try and confuse me.
l know you're a vampire.
And l can prove it too, because only
a vampire wouldn't know the answer...
to this simple Canadian question.
- What is Wayne Gretzky's middle name?
- Well, l don't know, Dudley.
Well, do you?
No, l don't.
Oh, my God.
- l am a vampire!
- You're not a vampire, Dudley.
ls something burning?
Yeah, right. Like you think l'm stupid
enough to fall for that old trick.
lt was at that precise moment
when Nell remembered...
that famous Mountie movie song.
When l'm calling you
lt really is you!
Will you answer too
That means l offer my love
To you
lf you refuse me
What shall l do
When l'm calling you
- Won't you come in, Nell?
- Sure.
What have you been doing
all these years?
l went out and saw the world,
just like l planned.
l got my masters in philosophy
from Yale...
a Ph.D in international diplomacy
from Harvard.
And then l served
as US ambassador to Guam.
And?
And...
now l've come home to get the one thing
a good education can't buy.
Oh, l got you. You want one of those
fuzzy plaid blankets...
they sell down at the Mountie store.
- Beach house with a hot tub?
- No. l just--
Let's not play games, Nell.
l haven't had the chance to say
these words before and--
When l'm calling you
- Enough with the song.
- Got it.
- l'm sorry. Where was l?
- Maybe we should just go out.
l hear they're having an authentic corn
festival dance at the reservation...
- with fireworks and everything.
- Or picture this.
A quiet evening in front of the fire
avec moi...
toasting marshmallows,
drinking Ovaltine.
Oh! Now l remember
what l was going to say.
Nell Fenwick, l--
Nell, l love you.
Though she had traveled far and wide,
never before...
had Nell heard a confession of love
from a moose.
Let's just go to the corn festival.
Okeydokey.
l'll get around to fixing
the floorboards next Tuesday.
l hope it's not hunting season.
A little help here
for the moose? Please?
- When l'm calling you
- Thank you.
After finding the nearest
moose head removal service...
Dudley and Nell made their way
to the corn festival.
This is totally authentic.
This is Canada, Nell.
Things are real up here.
Oh! Say, there's the chief.
Chief!
Oh, Chief!
Yes, it was the chief
of that rarely studied tribe...
of South Brooklyn lndians
known as the Canarsie Kumquats...
or just the Kumquats, for short.
Long time no see.
You remember Nell.
Nell Fenwick! You look terrific!
How's it going?
- Me do well.
- Good for you, sugar.
Well, come on.
Let's go see the show.
This Riverdance stuff
is really hot lately.
You remember Standing Room Only,
don't you?
Of course l do.
How are you, Standing Room Only?
- Great. Look, can we talk?
- Certainly.
How!
Bravo! Oh, bravo!
Okay, look.
A snitch l ain't, all right?
But for the last week or so l been
seeing this guy in the woods at night...
with this kind of Abe Lincoln hat on
and this opera coat...
going around shooting rocks and streams,
crap like that, with a shotgun.
- Yes? Go on.
- What, you don't think that's weird?
lt's Snidely Whiplash.
He thinks he's hunting vampires...
with gold bullets,
which scares the heck out of me.
- Vampires or gold bullets?
- Vampires.
l'll tell you, Chief. l think you're
straight out of your fricking mind.
Me or him?
Me. Me. Me.
Yeah. Well, that's a fine way
to talk to your chief.
lf you'll excuse me,
this particular Mountie has a date.
Oh, Dudley, l wish we could have stayed
for the fireworks.
Fireworks are even more beautiful
from this vantage point.
Yes.
When l'm calling you
- Dudley?
- Yes, Nell?
- Not now, okay?
- Yes, Nell.
- Let's just row.
- Of course, Nell.
Meanwhile, that very same night,
the poorest man in Semi-Happy Valley...
was about to strike it rich.
Hello!
Enjoying your evening thus far?
Thought l'd just drop in.
Found some gold, have we?
There's no gold anywhere
around here.
Oh, but there is.
Lots of it.
All over the place. And you,
you horrid example of a human being...
have made the initial discovery.
You're famous.
You will be on network television.
Network television?
No way!
Now stand up,
hold the pan out and smile.
Can l-- Can l borrow your comb?
Shut up and grin.
- Welcome to our show. Have a seat.
- Hi. How are you?
They're calling this the biggest
gold strike in history.
Certainly it's the biggest gold find
of the century.
And the man who made it all possible
is here for an exclusive interview.
Mr. Kim J. Darling.
Welcome, Kim.
- What's happening, Regis?
- l'll tell you what's happening.
You're what's happening.
Headlines all over the world.
How's it feel to have made the biggest
gold find in a century?
Well, l-- l feel lightheaded,
Kathie Lee.
Your story certainly has taken
the whole world by storm.
But Reg, the sad part is--
at least for Kim--
is that he found all this gold...
- on land he doesn't own.
- l did?
But the owner is staking no claim.
He says whoever finds the gold
gets to keep it.
And that's why the big gold rush
is on for northern Canada.
Stay tuned. Bette Midler is next.
- No!
- Yeah.
Meanwhile, on the US-Canadian border...
all is tranquil, as usual.
You want some of me?
You want some of Dwayne Cuffman?
Come on!
Passports!
Hey, stop-- What--
l must see your passports!
Trouble along the Canadian-US border
continues to mount.
They seem to be yuppie wetbacks,
mostly...
- but a lot of them are dentists.
- And this just in.
Scientists discovered that Canadian
bacon is actually ordinary ham.
What could be better than a plan
working exactly as you planned it?
Nothing.
That's what's better.
Drop it, Whiplash.
- lt's about time you showed up.
- About time?
We're here to kill you.
That won't be necessary.
Gentlemen, forgive my manners.
Please, take a seat.
- You weren't in the Sudan.
- You don't say.
- Where are all the other men?
- Where are they?
They're all over the place--
Heathrow, the Rome airport, Mozambique--
We all ran out of money.
This could be the right-sized group
l've been looking for.
What are you talking about?
We're going to kill you.
You're not going to kill me.
You're going to work for me.
Yeah. l need you boys
to help me run the town.
Everyone's gone, including the man
who ran the Slaw-Dogs stand.
Therefore, boys,
l'm gonna need your help...
to run Whiplash City.
Lefty, didn't you once attend school?
- Well, l-- Yeah.
- Good.
Now you're the new superintendent
for schools.
Thanks, Whip.
This is a dream come true for me.
Homer, didn't you once work
at McDonald's?
Yeah, Whip,
but l'm your number two guy.
l'm part of the brain trust.
Absolutely.
Now you can manage
the Snidely Whiplash Slaw-Dogs stand.
Oh, man.
l'm getting screwed.
And we're going to need doctors.
Which one of you is dumb enough
to think you can perform brain surgery?
Congratulations.
You're the town's new brain surgeon.
- Yes!
- Yes, indeed.
lt's pretty obvious we're going
to need a really good psychiatrist.
Honey? Look, honey!
l found it!
Good-bye, Las Vegas.
Hello, Whiplash City.
- A place for parents to pan for gold...
- Get a picture! A picture!
- and bond with their children.
- l don't want to.
Carlie, get a picture!
And a place to prove
that white men can dance.
California, Georgia, Puerto Rico.
But where are the Canadians?
Canadians like to think things over
before they do something.
- Americans just jump.
- And thank goodness they do.
Did you like the way l pronounced
Puerto Rico?
Yeah.
l speak a little Spanish.
You're the complete package, Whip.
Yes, Snidely had taken over
Dudley Do-Right's town.
But little did he know that Dudley
was hard at work devising a plan to--
That Dudley was hard at work,
devi--
Okay, l'm lying. He was fast asleep,
dreaming about Horse.
Reunited
And it feels so good
- Horse!
- Reunited
'Cause we understood
There's one perfect fit
And sugar, this one is it
We both are so excited
'Cause we're reunited
Hey, hey
lt's so good to see you again.
Nell's here, and you're here.
And if only l knew what
that Snidely Whiplash was up to.
What?
You mean there never were
any vampires?
What else?
That dirty rat!
Hey, yo, Whipster.
We're making a fortune! Come on.
So l see. So l see.
lt's the same with the gift shop.
And the gas station.
And the funeral home
should be showing a profit...
if l've got anything to do with it.
Mr. Whip?
l was thinking--
with us getting rich and all--
that maybe we should...
start playing golf.
My word. You're a genius.
The par 72 golf course was soon
Snidely's pride and joy.
And, thanks to the complimentary
golf balls he gave to all his guests...
he never lost a game.
- Ever.
- Bad luck!
You must have looked up.
Stop right there, Whiplash!
Do-Right, you made me
hit the windmill!
- No one talks when l shoot!
- You the man, Whip.
There's something going on in Semi-Happy
Valley that l don't approve of.
lt's called Whiplash City now,
Mountie boy.
You remember Nell Fenwick.
Remember her? He'd been in love
with her since he was six.
Hello, Snidely.
We've known each other too long
to be that formal.
Nell, will you stop that!
Zowie!
- Cool hat.
- We try.
What do you want, totem breath?
- ''Totem breath''?
- lt's the best l could come up with.
lt's hard to kiss and think
at the same time--
neither of which activity
you've had much experience with.
What l want is for you to know that l
don't know for sure what you're up to...
- but you're for sure up to something.
- Well put.
And l intend to find out
what that something is.
Do-Right, you'd need a psychic
to find out what l'm up to.
l don't think so.
- l think that's a gimme, eh, boys?
- Oh, yeah.
Let's play the next hole.
Come join us, Nell.
lt's just Snidely, for Pete's sake.
Though Snidely was the bad guy,
he did have a certain something.
First you ran everyone out of town.
- And then you took over the town.
- Yes. What else?
And then you--
Gosh, l knew it this morning.
- Oh, come on, Einstein. You can do it.
- Then you--
Then you salted the streams
and mines with gold...
in order to create
a false gold rush!
And because you own the town
and everything in it...
you stand to make a great fortune.
Hop off, sweet cakes.
Carry on, boys.
Dudley, keep your voice down.
This is an exclusive club.
- l don't care.
- Would you like to play with us?
- l'll give you a stroke a hole.
- Not a chance!
Oh, come on.
Hello. Yes, carry on.
Carry on.
Very good there.
Lovely to see you. Yes.
Yeah. Lovely ball.
Thank you very much.
Well, my dear friend and worthy foe,
once again...
l've foolishly underestimated you.
That's right.
And l'm right?
You're way off. But what if a rumor
like that spread around?
lt could destroy a community
like Semi-Happy Valley--
or whatever you want to call it.
You wouldn't want that, would you?
- We have to tell the truth, Snidely.
- Yes, of course.
But before we do anything rash, let's
sit down and discuss it like adults.
- When?
- Tonight. 9:00 p.m. sharp.
- Where?
- Your place.
- What's the dress?
- Casual.
That really doesn't leave me much time
to get ready.
You could microwave some
of those little hot dog thingies.
All right.
Snidely didn't keep his date
with Dudley, but Homer did.
And he was thoughtful enough
to bring along a six-pack...
of dynamite.
You look, somehow, l don't know--
younger.
- How did it go?
- Everything's taken care of.
Your boy is in do-gooder heaven.
l couldn't even find his body.
Excellent! Get out of that garish
outfit and find yourself a black suit.
You are our new funeral home director.
- Shane!
- Yes, Mr. Whiplash?
- Drinks on the house.
- Yes, sir.
- Wait a second. Drinks are 50% off.
- Right.
Wait a second.
- Double the price of everything.
- Yes, sir.
While Snidely celebrated Dudley's
demise, Dudley was actually in Ottawa...
telling the authorities
about Snidely's evil scheme.
What Dudley didn't know was that
Snidely had friends in high places...
- What are you looking at?
- as well as low.
Well, that is an amazing story
you tell, Officer Do-Right.
Thank you. l also know a story
about a hermit who kept a--
But let's say you're wrong.
Wouldn't a rumor like that
destroy the suddenly...
burgeoning economy of your little town?
That's what Snidely Whiplash said,
but he didn't use the word ''burgeoning.''
This Mr. Whiplash sounds like
a very community-minded fellow to me.
Oh, come on. Wake up.
He's the bad guy.
Just look at the way he dresses.
Ah, but is he really?
Here we have millions
of American dollars...
pouring into an otherwise
impoverished section of Canada.
Strike me several times with a blunt
instrument, but that's not good?
But it's wrong,
and as you can tell from my name--
But isn't it sometimes difficult
to discern...
the line between right and wrong?
- Uh--
- Not for him.
He's a Mountie. For these guys,
things are either right or wrong.
Boom, boom. Cut and dried.
Discern that, why don't you?
Gold! l found gold!
He found gold!
Right.
We'll build the hotel on this side...
and we'll put the condominiums
on that side...
so people can walk
right out to the river.
- l love it.
- Yes, l thought you might.
- l bet everyone loves it.
- Well, who wouldn't?
Well, l don't.
- lt does have some problems.
- lt's not perfect.
Oh, but it is perfect.
You know, boys,
you're the best gang l've ever had.
- Thanks, Whip.
Particularly you--
Homer.
Oh, gosh, l--
Morning, boys.
''Do-gooder heaven,'' eh?
Back to the Slaw-Dogs stand with you.
l know, l know.
Hello?
Have you seen my office lately?
Well, not lately.
- Why? Have you done something with it?
- No, but someone has.
Dudley, Father's come back.
- l'm afraid he's got some bad news.
- Where are you?
You know how bad l am
with directions.
Are you in a car?
Yes, but it stopped.
l think l'm gonna have to call you back.
We've got a bad connection.
lnspector!
At ease, Do-Right.
lt does this old heart of mine
good to see you again, sir.
You're my hero, sir.
You're my role model.
Dudley, you're finished as a Mountie.
Get your horse and clear out of here.
Horse ran away.
Oh, dear.
l'm so sorry to hear that.
Oh, l can't watch.
l just can't watch.
Your father's joshing me about being
drummed out of the service.
- lt's very funny.
- l'm not joshing you...
even the tiniest bit.
The highest level
of the Canadian government...
has called me out of retirement
to replace you here.
l know what this is about.
l was supposed to have a meeting
with Snidely Whiplash...
but l completely forgot about it.
- Then l went to Ottawa instead.
- And then Ottawa called on me.
Now give me your uniform
and your sidearm and leave.
- My uniform, sir?
- l'm sorry, Dudley.
This is a very sad moment.
Yes, lnspector, it certainly is.
He had lost his uniform.
He had lost his horse.
Dudley's dreams were shattered.
Hello. Remember me?
l was on Regis and Kathie Lee.
Yeah, l was. Honestly. Last week.
Only last week. lt was very good.
l was on Regis and Kathie Lee.
Hello. l know Bette Midler personally.
Hi! lt's me!
l was on Regis and Kathie Lee last week.
Hey! l know you.
You are Dudley Do-Right
of the Royal Canadian Mounted Police.
l never forget a face--
although a name
sometimes escapes me.
Sir, l lost my job today.
My horse ran away.
And l'd really like to be alone
right now, if you don't mind.
Oh-- No chance, pal.
- l am your new best friend.
- l don't have any friends.
- Hey, you got me, pal.
- l don't even have a home.
Wait till you see my place!
Meanwhile, Whiplash had begun
his evil campaign...
to win the affections of the fair
Nell Fenwick and to impress her father.
Let us hope they can see right through
this scheming cad.
Sorry.
May l recommend
the salt cod bouillabaisse...
followed by the buckwheat crepes
with tangerine reduction?
- Okay. Father?
- Sounds delectable.
But for me, hold the fennel seed.
Very wise choice, lnspector,
very wise.
Thank you.
- You drank too much last night.
- Did l?
l feel pretty good.
You know, the line
between right and wrong...
is oftentimes
difficult to discern.
Yeah. l was--
l was just thinking that myself.
Snidely Whiplash has brought prosperity
to Semi-Happy Valley.
He's turned this nowhere town around.
Of course, he ran off
all the old residents.
Oh, it's all about greed.
You're right! That's it!
lt is greed!
That's all it is!
lt's just greed!
Please don't make any sudden moves
around me this morning, all right?
Here's what l don't understand.
What happens when the gold runs out?
Oh, it's never gonna run out.
- lt's not?
- Whiplash is too smart.
Snidely was smart enough
to keep the gold coming in...
so the profits would keep coming in.
Smart enough to own his own helicopter.
Smart enough to have won over
every government authority...
within 2,000 miles,
but was he smart enough to outwit...
a pathetic bum
and the only man to be...
thrown out of the Mounties
in 100 years?
We'll have to see about that.
l don't see anything.
See? That's where they melt down
the gold so they can salt it at night.
Would you look how popular Snidely is?
That's not right.
People always suck up
to the guy in charge.
You know that.
lt's like life.
l say we go down there
and arrest them all.
- Oh, l don't think so.
- Why not?
l'll give you three good reasons.
l'd like to start with the second one
first, if that's okay with you.
Okay, two.
lf we go down there,
they'll kill us.
One. You're not a Mountie anymore.
And three, they're not doing
anything illegal.
But we've got to do something!
You've got to do something.
l just wanted to show you
what was going on.
What's my next move?
Well, you could steal the gold
before they can salt it...
and that way, end of gold rush.
What? Me steal?
Me break the law?
- Sadly, yeah.
- But then l'd be Dudley Do-Wrong.
Do-Wrong's nice. l like that.
lt's kind of French.
You know-- ''Dudley Durange.''
l'm so confused.
lt's not that complicated, Dudley.
The bad guy, Snidely Whiplash,
is apparently doing good...
ergo, putting you, the good guy...
in the position
of having to be the bad guy.
Well, not exactly the bad guy.
Let's say the ''badder'' guy.
But let me remind you
that as a bad guy doing good...
does not necessarily make him
a good guy...
so a good guy doing bad does not,
ipso facto, make him a bad guy.
This can't be happening.
He can't be the good guy.
But he is.
The good citizens of Whiplash City
are throwing...
a gala ball in his honor tonight.
For Snidely?
l don't believe it!
They love him!
- Better believe it.
- He is the good guy.
Yeah, not to mention the fact
he's got Nell.
Maybe it's just someone
who looks like her.
Nah. That's Nell.
lt is Nell!
l can't believe
that this is happening to me!
- Sorry.
- lt's okay.
l better go do something about this.
No, wait. You're not ready.
You're not trained.
Well done.
This is gonna take a lot of work.
And who better to do that work
than Kim Darling himself...
a grown man with an extensive
Pokmon collection.
My son...
the hero defeats danger...
because he is dangerous himself.
You are dangerous.
Know it. Say it.
Say, ''l am dangerous.''
- l did.
- No. Say, ''l am dangerous.''
You are dangerous.
You say, ''l am dangerous.''
- But you said--
- Oh, never mind.
The hero must face three trials.
Trust, daring...
instinct.
For the sake of consistency,
we'll start with number two.
Daring!
Okay now, l am your adversary.
l am evil.
Evil! Evil!
You're evil?
Yes. And now l'm going to draw
this line in the sand.
Now, do not dare cross that line...
otherwise evil will rain down
upon you.
Evil!
Now look, Dudley, you--
You're supposed to take me up
on my challenge...
by showing me how daring you are.
Let's try it once again,
shall we?
l am evil!
Now do not dare cross that line!
Evil!
Well, what? You said
l'm not supposed to cross the line!
But you're supposed to cross the line.
Now, let's try it again.
Okay, now, do not dare...
cross the line of death.
l am evil! l am evil!
- What did you do that for?
- 'Cause l'm evil.
l can't help it.
Sorry.
...eight, nine, ten.
Trust.
The hero trusts.
Now, l will throw some stones
at you--
missing intentionally, of course--
and you will not flinch
as they whiz...
past your head,
because you trust me.
- l trust you, master.
- Good!
Sorry-- but that was very good.
You trusted me.
Okay?
Perfect! You didn't flinch at all.
Just one more, okay?
Excellent, absolutely!
Trust is your middle name.
A little less moaning would be good.
The final test-- instinct.
You will fight me
without benefit of eyesight.
You will block my every blow...
because you can see
without your eyes.
You can hear without your ears.
- You can speak without your tongue.
- Yes, master.
l said ''without your tongue.''
Now, your sword is your stick.
The stick is your defense.
Prepare to defeat me.
Are you ready?
Very good, indeed!
The hopping-foot defense.
Very good!
The other-foot-hopping defense.
Wonderful!
You're at one with the universe!
And now, concentrate.
Prepare to receive my final assault.
Wonderful.
The playing-dead defense.
- Master?
- Good choice, under the circumstances.
You'll be all right, my son--
provided they don't attack you
with sticks.
With his master's lesson
ringing in his ears...
Dudley set off
in search of justice.
- You are ready, my son.
- And Extra-Strength Tylenol.
You are ready because you've taken
everything l can throw at you...
and still you stand
tall and true.
You are ready to face danger
because you are danger.
Now, get out there
and do something dangerous.
No! Please don't!
Then tell me when
the next gold delivery arrives.
l don't know.
Well, then l'm afraid we're gonna
find out which is your better side.
- You're a Mountie.
- Not anymore.
Thursday. The gold's coming
at noon on Thursday.
Noon Thursday. Thank you.
- Now, if l just knew how to stop this--
- What?
Whoa! That's not it.
Just papier-mache.
Completely recyclable material.
- What kind of man are you anyway?
- A dangerous one.
- He's got the gold!
- After him, boys!
He may have been outnumbered...
but Dudley knew these woods
like the back of his horse.
Do you have any idea what
this could possibly mean?
Doris Day.
- Just a guess.
- Dom Deluise.
- Daniel Day-Lewis.
- Snoop Doggy Dogg.
- Daphne du Maurier.
- Oh, shut up.
- Doc Duvalier.
- David Duchovny?
- Delores Del Rio.
- Shut up, you idiots.
Dan Rather.
These initials could
only mean one thing--
Dudley Do-Right.
You think Do-Right has got
the guts for something like this?
- Of course l do.
- Wow.
You realize what this means, don't you?
He's becoming the bad guy.
Where does that leave me?
l used to be the bad guy.
lf he's capable of doing this...
who knows what other really fun,
bad-guy stuff he's been doing.
- What other stuff indeed.
- David Duchovny.
For Snidely was about to discover
a crime so low, so hideous...
it had to involve toilet paper.
Oh, man.
What a bleak and rimy day.
Something like this just
makes you sick to your stomach.
Don't touch me!
- Where are you going?
- My work is done here now.
So it's time for me
to rejoin my family.
You have a family?
Yeah, well, it's a long story.
But basically,
l was lost like you.
l wasn't a hero to anyone,
not even myself.
No one ever really
believed in me.
But l feel you're my friend now,
and you believe in me.
And that gives me the strength
to rejoin my loved ones...
if l can find them.
l'm a new man, Dudley,
thanks to you.
- What about the chain saw?
- Parting gift.
Family tradition. Don't ask.
- Thank you.
- Use it in peace, not war.
You can count on me.
My son.
My master.
Oh, that's lovely, Whip.
The play of light,
the chiaroscuro shading--
- Shut up, Homer.
- You got it, Whip.
What was that?
Well, Snidely. Posing as an artist
to gain young Nell's favor, eh?
Stop the music!
He's quite talented, Dudley.
lt's paint-by-numbers.
l can't tell you how hard it is to keep
the paint inside those teeny lines.
Wait a minute. You're wearing black.
That's my color.
- l'm the bad guy.
- But you're not wearing black, Snidely.
- That's dark blue.
- lt is not.
lt is so. lt's navy.
See for yourself.
- What am l doing wearing blue?
- Well, the black one's at the cleaners.
And l just wanna say, you look
good in blue. You really do.
Oh! ''l just wanna say.''
''l just wanna say.''
Nell, you'll always think of me
as wearing black, won't you?
Oh, l don't know, Snidely.
l don't think this portrait really
captures Nell's preternatural beauty.
Oh, yes. Like you could
do better, Mountie boy?
- ls that a challenge?
- Absolutely.
lt's lovely.
Shall we, Nell?
You look really good
in green, Whip.
He's a cunning adversary,
Homer...
but not cunning enough
to outwit Snidely K. Whiplash.
You are my role model, Whip.
So Dudley wants to be the bad guy.
We'll see if the shoe fits.
- What shoe, Whip?
- Oh, for Pete's sake.
We've all done our best
to make Whiplash City...
a place of peace and prosperity...
where we could all make lots of money
without doing anything at all.
That's how life should be. But there's
a man trying to ruin all that.
- This is the man.
- Hey, that's Dudley!
- He's the good guy!
- This man is dangerous and evil.
He's not evil!
You're wrong, Whiplash!
We must find him at once.
Gold miners
of Whiplash City unite.
Dudley Do-Right must be
found and done away with.
- No!
- He must be killed, you hear me?
Killed!
Yes, the tide
had turn against Snidely.
The townspeople had grown tired
of Whiplash City.
They wanted their town back
just the way it used to be.
So while Snidely was growing
weaker by the minute...
Dudley was growing stronger.
Yo, Mr. Do-Right.
Five minutes.
Thank you.
Bravo!
Though Nell had witnessed many examples
of our hero's derring-do...
it took a dance number to convince her
that Dudley was studly.
When l'm calling you
Will you answer too
- l love you now, and l always have.
- You really do, Nell?
Meanwhile, back at Snidely's
secret hideout and day spa--
We have to find out where
that sniveling Do-Right is hiding.
l've got the men out combing
the countryside, Whip.
Do you?
l'll get it.
Here.
Yeah, give it to me.
Hello.
What?
We found him.
This calls for a celebration.
Waiter! Two mudslingers, please.
Snidely and his henchmen immediately
launched an all-out assault...
on the Kumquat nation.
lt's Whiplash.
They just want me, Chief.
l'll go quietly.
- This isn't your fight.
- l'm backing you 110%.
And l mean that, so far.
- You got weapons?
- Weapons?
Come on. This is basically
a dinner theater we're running here.
- You got fireworks?
- That we got.
Fire!
They're just fireworks, you sissies!
Be men!
That's the last of the fireworks.
Now what ?
We'll take to the forest
and throw rocks at them.
- Rocks?
- What else can we do?
- The press here?
- They're up there on the perimeter.
Let's do it.
General Whiplash,
the village is ours.
- Torch it, Shane. Burn everything.
- Yes, sir.
No. Wait a minute.
That's bad publicity.
Have the photographers take pictures
of the boys straightening up the place.
- You got it.
- Learn from history or repeat it.
Come on, Chief.
l gotta stop.
You can make it.
You're a young man.
Don't let this face-lift fool you.
l'm 62.
On second thought--
- Okay, hold it. Hold it right there.
- Hold your fire. Hold your fire.
- Somebody hit me with a rock.
- lt was one of them lndian dancers.
All right. That's it.
Now l'm heated.
Not since their all-male revival
of Little Women...
had the Kumquats faced
such a hostile reception.
But the Kumquats never walked away
from a fight. They preferred to run.
- Know what we need, Chief?
- Two weeks in Maui.
No. Bigger rocks.
That's not fair!
They've got rocks!
All we've got are
these machine guns.
Oh, mother of pearl,
here comes another one.
- Let 'em have another one.
- The next size down is this one.
- We're outta the big stuff.
- We're screwed.
No, we're not. Look.
lt's my horse, Horse.
Just like in my dream.
Wait a minute. We're saved because
that flea-bitten nag showed up?
He's trying to tell us
to follow him.
l think he's just got
a fly up his nose.
Come on, everybody!
We've got them
on the run now.
They'll never make it
across the valley floor.
- Time to bring up the heavy equipment.
- Yes, sir!
- Move out!
- Move, move, move, move!
l'm sorry.
l gotta stop.
- Come on, Chief.
- No. That's it. l'm finished.
l thought native North Americans
could run all day.
- Oh, yeah, like we're really lndians.
- We're not leaving without you.
- You guys go without me. Go!
- l'm gonna stand by you.
Ah, Dudley.
l'm making you an honorary Kumquat.
- That means a great deal to me, Chief.
- Forget about it.
He's a dead honorary Kumquat.
Roger.
Tango Delta Foxtrot.
Shall we dance?
You gotta admit.
He comes prepared.
- l think it's time to surrender.
- Yeah, it looks like it.
- He's got another bug up his nose.
- No.
He's telling me he wants me
to attack the tanks.
ls that good?
Taking advice from a horse?
- Yes, it is.
- They got a brain the size of a pea.
- That's nuts.
- Not to mention stupid.
- l think it's wonderful.
- Don't worry. l'll save you, Nell.
Homer, let him have it.
Come to Daddy.
Ah, that's it.
End of game.
Curses!
Where did they come from?
Come on!
Come back here, you cowards!
General!
Good horse, Horse.
You know, Homer, this is the part
of the job l hate the most, the ending.
Up until then, being the bad guy
is the best job in the world.
Hello, Dudley.
Hello, Whip.
l've lost everything.
Even the announcer's gone.
No, l'm still here. Someone's got
to explain where the cavalry came from.
Yes. l was a mite curious
about that myself.
Yes, the prospector
had found his long-lost family.
The search was greatly simplified when
Kim spotted his wife on television...
as she was being sworn in
as prime minister of Canada.
lt was she
who called out the cavalry.
- That was lucky, wasn't it?
- Boy, l'll say.
And that's because
good things happen to good people.
And bad things happen
to bad people.
What's the problem, Officer?
l was only doing 25 miles an hour.
Well, that's the last we'll see
of them for a long, long time.
Don't count on it,
bugle boy.
No jail can hold
Snidely K. Whiplash.
- Oh, shut up, Homer.
- Sure thing, Whip.
Do-Right, would you
allow me the honor...
of presenting you
with your old uniform...
and the thanks
of a grateful nation?
Thank you, lnspector.
Hip hip hooray!
Yes, Dudley now has everything
a Mountie could ever want.
His fort, his girl and a swell
collection of foofey pillows.