Dig it, oh-oh-oh, dig it
dig it, oh-oh-oh, yeah
dig it, oh-oh-oh
dig it, oh-oh-oh, dig it
dig it, oh-oh-oh, yeah
with broken hands
and weathered souls
emancipated
from all you know
you got to go
dig those holes
dig it, oh-oh-oh, yeah
you got to go
dig those holes
dig it, oh-oh-oh, yeah
you got to go
dig those holes
dig it, oh-oh-oh
[snake hissing]
Get that straight.
Let me tell you, boy, we're
burnin' up back here, man.
This global warmin'.
Hole in the ozone is directly
above my head.
The hole's in your head.
[Laughter]
[Rattling]
Barf bag!
- Man, what you doin'?!
- Barf bag!
It ain't that bad!
Come on, man! Come on, man!
This ain't funny, dog.
Get back, barf bag, for real!
Come on!
What are you doin'?!
- Barf bag, deal with it, baby!
- Barf bag!
Aaaaaaaaaah!
[Grunts]
[Pants, groans]
Stanle y iv: All my life,
i seemed to be in the wrong
place at the wrong time.
My grandpa,
stanley yelnats ii,
says it's all because
of this 150-year-old curse.
Now, i don't really believe
in the family curse,
but when things go wrong,
it kind of helps if you can
blame it on something.
And for me,
things went wrong a lot.
[Sniffs]
Oh, jeez! Oh!
Grandpa says
our destiny is sealed.
[Siren wailing]
Could a pair of shoes
falling from the sky
really be part of my destiny?
- Come here, boy!
- Hold it right there!
- Did you steal those shoes?
- Officer, i didn't do anything.
- What's your name, boy?
- I'm stanley.
Stanley yelnats iv.
Stanle y iv: You see, my father,
stanley yelnats iii,
is an inventor,
and for the last few years,
he's been trying to find
a cure... for foot odor.
[Laughs]
I'm glad you're here.
This whole floor
smells like stinky feet.
[Door hinges creak]
What did you do to my stanley?
Don't freak out.
It's a bruise.
Can i just say right off
the bat, this is a big mistake.
Don't say nothing
until we talk to our lawyer!
You're gonna be sorry you ever
messed with stanley yelnats!
Let me see that.
Just don't grab it
out of their hands.
Why not?
Because you're gonna
make 'em angry.
- Would you like a piece of cake?
- Excuse me.
- Do we even have any cake?
- How about some coffee?
[Hissing]
Now, that is a fine pair
of shoes.
Could i just smell your shoe?
How about if you take
your shoe off, and i'll just...
check the bedroom.
Just a minute!
Where are you going?!
This warrant isn't warranted!
This will never hold up
in court!
Uh-huh.
Here it is.
We got him.
We share the room.
How do you know
that's not mine?
Which bed is yours?
You don't have to answer that.
We have the right
to remain silent.
Oh, wouldn't that be nice.
I sleep here.
It's all because of your
no-good, dirty-rotten,
pig-stealing
great-great-grandfather.
There is no curse
on this family.
There is on the men
in this family.
"If only, if only,"
- the woodpecker sighs
- please don't sing that song.
"The bark on the tree
was as soft as the skies"
please don't sing that song,
not at my table!
Ma, relax. I don't believe
in the curse, anyways.
We're gonna need
a damn good lawyer.
We can't afford a lawyer, pa.
We don't need a lawyer.
Stanley will tell the truth.
Stanley yelnats, please rise.
[Sighs]
Stanley yelnats iv.
Sit down!
[Siren wails in distance]
I could send you to jail,
and i would not lose
one bit of sleep over it.
[Whimpers]
But i don't know
what good that would do.
There is currently a vacancy
at camp green lake.
They help troubled youth
build character.
The choice is yours.
Camp green lake... or jail.
[Feedback]
Uh, well, i never have been
to camp before.
18 months,
camp green lake, son.
[Eels' "eyes down" plays]
Well, the sun is shinin',
but it don't feel good
don't smile down
on this neighborhood
when i go walkin'
through this stinkin' town
mister,
i keep my eyes down
you keep your eyes down
the brotherhood
of the misunderstood
live and die here,
in all likelihood
you're livin' in this town,
better pray for sundown
like all the men,
you go downtown
you keep your eyes down
hey, baby!
You keep your eyes down
- [brakes squeak, hiss]
- You keep your eyes down
you keep your eyes down
- thanks for the ride.
- You keep your eyes down
[coughs]
Yo, fresh meat!
So, uh, where's the lake?
Hey, what did i just tell you?
Don't be a wise guy.
Follow me.
[Fly buzzing]
[Crunching]
[Door hinges creak]
Sit down.
[Spits]
What's with
the sunflower seeds, man?
I gave up smokin'.
Stanley yelnats...
...the fourth?
Yeah.
Everyone in my family names
their son stanley
'cause it's yelnats backwards.
It's like this...
it's a little...
it's a... tradition.
[Crunches]
My name is mr. Sir.
Whenever you speak to me,
you will call me by my name.
Is that clear?
Yes, mr. Sir.
Do you think that's funny?
Huh?
No, mr. Sir.
This isn't a girl scout camp.
Understand?
Here.
Boy, you're a bag of tricks.
Thanks.
You thirsty, stanley?
Yes, mr. Sir.
Well, you better
get used to it.
You're gonna be thirsty
for the next 18 months.
[Indistinct conversations]
Look around you, yelnats.
What do you see?
Any guard towers?
How about an electric fence?
Hmm?
No, mr. Sir.
You want to run away?
Go ahead, start running.
I won't stop you.
I'm warnin' you!
You heard the man, spence.
Oh, don't worry.
This here's
for yellow-spotted lizards.
I wouldn't waste a bullet
on you.
I'm not gonna run away,
mr. Sir.
Good thinkin', yelnats.
Doesn't nobody run away
from here. You know why?
We got the only water
for 100 miles...
our own little oasis.
You want to run away, them
buzzards will pick you clean
by the end of the third day.
Hi, mr. Sir.
Mr. Sir: Undress.
You get two sets of clothes...
one for work,
one for relaxation.
After three days, your
work clothes will be washed,
your second set
becomes your work clothes.
- Is that clear?
- Yes, mr. Sir.
You are to dig one hole
each day...
5 foot deep,
5 foot in diameter.
Your shovel is
your measuring stick.
The longer
it takes you to dig,
the longer you'll be out
in the hot sun.
Sorry, mr. Sir.
You need to keep alert
for lizards and rattlesnakes.
Rattlesnakes?
You don't bother them,
they won't bother you...
usually.
Being bit by a rattler
ain't the worst thing
that can happen to you.
You won't die, usually.
But you don't want to get bit
by a yellow-spotted lizard.
That is the worst thing
that can happen to you.
You will die
a slow and painful death...
...always.
[Door hinges creak]
- Stanley yelnats?
- Yeah?
I just want you to know
that you may have done
some bad things,
but that does not make you
a bad kid.
I respect you, stanley.
Welcome to camp green lake.
I'm dr. Pendanski,
your counselor.
Start that touchy-feely crap,
i'm outta here.
Give him some towels, tokens.
Set him up.
You'll be in "d" tent.
"D" stands for "diligence."
That's the mess hall.
There's the rec room.
And there's the showers.
There's only one knob
'cause there's only
one temperature... cold.
And that's the warden's cabin
over there.
That's the number-one rule
at camp green lake...
do not upset the warden.
Yeah, he seemed kind of...
who?
Oh, mr. Sir?
Oh, he's not the warden.
He's just been in a bad mood
since he quit smokin'.
Hey, mom...
who's the neanderthal?
This is stanley.
So, what's happening
with barf bag?
Oh, lewis won't be returning.
He's still in the hospital.
Stanley, meet rex, alan,
and theodore.
Hi.
Yo, my name is x-ray.
And that's squid,
that's armpit.
Him, he's mom.
They all have
their little nicknames,
but i prefer to use the names
their parents gave them,
the names society will
recognize them by.
Theodore, why don't we show
stanley his cot?
Go ahead, pit.
Dr. Pendanski: Welcome to your
new home, stanley.
Barf bag slept here.
Keep your bed clean.
Hey, i'm magnet.
That's zigzag.
Hi.
[Indistinct conversations]
What i told you about leaving
that thing right there, man?
And this... is zero.
Say hello to stanley, zero.
Do you want to know
why they call him zero?
'Cause there's nothing goin' on
in his stupid little head.
Did you tell him
about the lizards?
Ricky, let's not scare stanley.
His name's not ricky.
It's zigzag, all right?
Stanley, if you have any
questions, just ask theodore.
Theodore will be your mentor.
You got that, theodore?
Yeah, man.
Whatever, dude.
I'm depending on you.
It should be no labor
to be nice to your neighbor.
Hey, theodore,
is there a place
where i can fill my canteen up
with water?
I know he smells that.
Yo, my name is not theodore.
It's armpit.
There's a water spigot
over there.
Man, pit, what you gotta be
so mean for?
Armpit: Man, i ain't mean.
I'm his mentor.
Ain't that
what i'm supposed to do?
Thanks, armpit.
Man, whatever.
Man on p. A: Today's menu...
chili, string beans,
refried beans, garbanzo beans,
green beans,
and banana jello.
[Laughter]
Hey, stanley,
come here, boy.
This is where you sit.
Sit down.
Hey, yo, new kid.
Hey, yo.
See, you didn't dig today.
So, uh, you wouldn't mind
giving up your bread
to somebody who did,
now, would you?
No, you can have it.
So, what'd they get you for?
Stealing a pair of shoes.
[Laughter]
From the store, or were they
still on someone's feet?
No, no, he just
killed the dude first.
You just left out
that little detail, right?
They were
clyde livingston's shoes.
- Sweetfeet?
- What?
Man, you did not steal no clyde
livingston's sweetfeet shoes.
His world series cleats.
Hold on, hold on.
How did you get 'em?
He's, like, the fastest guy
in the majors, right?
Only guy to hit four triples
in one game.
[Laughter]
Clyde livingston
donated his shoes
to this... homeless shelter.
Did they have
red x's on 'em?
- What'd he just say?
- Huh?
You got zero to talk.
Hey, yo, what else
can you do, zero?
Yeah.
Yeah, they did.
Tell us a little something
of your background...
mr. Livingston.
Besides the fact
that it was your donated shoes
that were stolen,
what other connection might you
have with this case?
Well, i was an orphan.
I grew up in that home.
I don't understand
what type of person steals
from homeless children.
You're no fan of mine.
[Snoring]
[Insects chirping]
[Farts, sniffs]
It was all because of your
no-good, dirty-rotten,
pig-stealing
great-great-grandfather.
That's who sealed our destiny.
Why do you think
none of his inventions work?
Pa.
I learn from failure.
Doesn't matter
how smart you are.
You need luck...
something we ain't got.
Yeah, what about your father,
the first stanley yelnats?
He wasn't so unlucky.
You told me he made a fortune
in the stock market.
- Some luck.
- Yeah, he lost everything.
He was robbed
by kissin' kate barlow.
Get on up outta there!
Gimme your loot!
[Gun cocks]
Are you kidding me?
She kiss him?
[Smooches]
Oh, no. She only kissed
the men she killed.
What you got down there, huh?
Pass it up!
Come on!
She left him stranded
in the desert.
Come on, boys!
Let's ride!
No water, no food
for 16 days.
If she'd have kissed him,
she'd have killed him.
You'd have never been born.
[Snoring continues]
[Reveille plays]
[Whistle blows]
Smiling faces!
The early mole
digs the deepest hole.
Shovels on the left,
tortillas on the right.
Let's go!
Okay, come and get it.
Let's go! Come on, magnet!
Open them peepers!
Let's go! Let's go!
Head's still on the pillow!
This ain't no dreamland.
It's reality.
Let's go, hotshots!
Step up and get your...
hey, man, you picked up
x-ray's shovel.
It's shorter
than the rest of them.
Smaller shovel,
smaller hole.
[Little axe's
"down to the valley" plays]
H-e-e-e-ey
oh, sinners, let's go down
let's go down
down in the valley to pray
oh, sinners
- this isn't a girl scout camp.
- Let's go down
- nobody's gonna babysit you.
- dig here.
- Oh, sinners, let's go down
now, if you find
anything interesting,
you are to report it
to me or pendanski.
If the warden likes
what you find,
you get the rest
of the day off.
What am i supposed to be
looking for, mr. Sir?
You're not looking
for anything.
You're building character.
You take a bad boy,
make him dig holes all day,
and it turns him
into a good boy.
That's our philosophy
here at camp green lake.
Start digging.
Show me the way
good lord, show me the way
one down, 10 million to go.
Show me the way
good lord, show me the way
oh, sinners, let's go down
let's go down
[groans]
Excuse me, can you throw that
in another pile or something,
'cause it
keeps getting in my hole.
Shut up!
Watch where you're
moving your dirt!
Watch where you're throwing
your dirt, stanley.
[Laughter]
Stanle y ii: It was all because
of your no-good, dirty-rotten,
pig-stealing
great-great-grandfather,
elya yelnats.
It started in a little village
in latvia.
He was shoveling
in morris menke's barn,
when myra, his beautiful
daughter, walked by.
[Chuckles]
And that was it.
So what does your
great-great-grandfather do?
He goes to a fortune-teller,
madame zeroni, for advice.
All you think about
is myra menke.
I know.
That's when our troubles began.
Listen to madame zeroni.
You should go to america.
That's where my son is.
That's your future,
not myra menke.
Her head's as empty
as a flowerpot.
Mr. Menke...
i would like your permission
to marry your daughter.
You too?
[Grunts]
Lgor barkov has offered
his fattest pig for her.
What do you got?
A heart full of love.
[Laughter]
He's just a boy!
I'd rather have a fat pig.
[Both laughing]
Morris menke is a schmuck.
Okay, here's what you do.
Take the little one.
[All snorting]
But this solves nothing.
So it will grow.
Every day, you carry the pig
up the mountain.
Make it drink the water from
the stream while you sing...
"if only, if only,"
the woodpecker sighs
woodpecker sighs.
"The bark on the tree
was as soft as the skies"
while the wolf waits below,
hungry and lonely
he cries to the moon,
"if only, if only"
every day,
the pig will get fatter,
and you will get stronger.
Now, after you give the pig
to menke,
you must carry madame zeroni
up the mountain
and sing while i drink
so i can get strong, too.
[Laughing]
But if you forget
to come back for madame zeroni,
you and your family
will be cursed
for always and eternity.
[Laughing]
[Up-tempo music plays]
[Translation from spanish]
Rosalito is getting nearer
- get your water, dog.
- Oh, my god.
Here comes the water truck.
- First hole's the hardest.
- Let's go!
Hey, mr. Sir.
What you doin', man?
Get your place in line, magnet!
Keep your hands
off of me, man!
So, how'd it go
your first day, yelnats?
Got some blisters on you?
- Big, fat blisters.
- Yeah.
Well, don't worry.
Everything turns
to callus eventually.
That's life. Next.
[Pig snorting]
Myra, who do you choose...
igor barkov or elya yelnats?
You want me to decide?
That's right, my blossom.
[Chuckles]
Gee, i don't know.
[Pigs snorting]
Which pig weighs more?
They are the same.
Oh, i know!
I will think of a number
between 1 and 10.
Okay, i'm ready.
Marry lgor.
You can keep my pig
as wedding present.
[Laughter]
Two pigs for one daughter!
[Laughter continues]
[Spits]
You done already?
Don't you know, man?
He's, like, the fastest digger
in the camp.
He's a mole.
I think he eats the dirt.
He's a weird dude.
Moles don't eat dirt.
Worms eat dirt, dog.
[Bell dinging]
[Whistle blows]
Stanle y ii:
So that was it.
He took madame zeroni's advice
and went to america,
like her son,
but the dummy
forgot to go back
and carry madame zeroni
up the mountain.
Madame zeroni: If you forget
to come back for madame zeroni,
you and your family will be
cursed for always and eternity.
[Laughing]
Stanle y iv:
Somebody help me!
Anybody up there?!
[Coughs]
I'm done with my hole now!
[Grunting]
Oh, god.
[Sighs]
- [Gun cocks]
- Don't move.
Oh, f...
[gunshot]
[Hisses]
[Shrieks]
Aah!
[Gunshot]
[Gasps]
Get your stuff.
Get yourself
a good sleep, son.
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah.
Oh, my god!
[Gunshot]
What color was its blood?
I don't know.
I couldn't tell.
I wish i'd have seen it.
- Bam!
- [Laughs]
If mr. Sir didn't shoot it...
stanley, you'd be in a hole.
Did you know that each one's
got exactly 11 spots?
Yeah, man, but if you ever get
close enough to count 'em...
[lmitates slashing sound]
...you're dead.
Look, it's the lizards
we're working for, man.
We build their houses for 'em.
I mean, yesterday, i saw
like 10 of them in one hole.
Man, we ain't diggin'
for no lizards.
What we diggin' for?
Like mr. Sir said,
we're diggin'
to build some character.
[Laughter]
[Gunshot]
[Growls]
[Record player crackles,
reveille plays]
- Come on! Wake up, buddy!
- Feelin' mighty fine
- stanle y iv: "dear mom...
- feelin' mighty fine
"i'm having a wonderful time
at camp.
"The food's great.
Not as good as yours,
of course, but i like it."
Feelin' mighty fine
at this time
"we've been out on the lake
all day."
Where's a person go
to the bathroom around here?
- Man, pick a hole. Any hole.
- Feelin' mighty fine
"once i pass the swimming test,
"i'll get to learn
how to water-ski.
I've made lots of friends."
Oh, you're goin' to hell
for sure.
- [Laughter]
- Feelin' mighty fine
"and the water is
cool and refreshing."
- [Clunk]
- At his time
"you'd like my counselor.
He's a doctor."
Smells like puke from a mule
been ruminating on asparagus
for two weeks.
"And i'm really enjoying
the wildlife."
Don't believe a word
they say about me
because l'm feelin'
mighty fine
feelin' mighty fine
- rent time! Pay up!
- This time
"the other boys
aren't bad kids.
Like me, they were just in the
wrong place at the wrong time."
Get on there, fool!
"Well, that's it for now, ma.
"Say hi to dad and grandpa
for me.
Love, your son, stanley."
Who you writin' to?
Aw, you miss your mommy
and daddy?
- I don't want them to worry.
- They don't care.
- Give me the letter.
- Believe me...
they're glad
to be rid of you.
[Rock music plays]
[Smooches]
Found something.
It's a fossil.
You see that?
- Well, that's interesting.
- Do i get a day off?
What?
That's what mr. Sir said.
He said that if i found
something interesting,
i get the day off.
Stanley, the warden isn't
interested in fossils.
Let me see that.
- What is it?
- Man, see, look.
[Singsong voice]
Look at the little fishies!
Aw!
[Normal voice] i mean, it look
like those cave pictures, man.
- Ain't nothin', anyway.
- Fossil.
I tell you what, i think stanley
belongs in a cave, man.
I told you he was a neanderthal
the first time i saw him.
Guess there really was
a lake out here once, right?
There was a town, too.
The warden's grandfather
owned the lake
and half the town.
[Whistle blowing]
[Indistinct conversations]
Whoo!
Tie her off, there, boys.
All right, now.
Get your sweet,
sweet magical onions!
Get your elixirs,
health potions, onion tonics.
Onions. Get your
onions here, folks.
God's own chosen vegetable.
Nature's magic vegetables
right here, folks.
Mr. Collingwood, let me see
that head of yours.
- My head?
- Yes, sir.
Yeah, that's what i thought.
I got exactly what you need.
Just rub this on his head
every night, mrs. Collingwood,
and before you know it,
his hair's gonna be
as long and as thick
as mary lou's mane.
- [Bell ringing]
- Sam, thank you.
The ancient egyptians knew
the secrets of the onions.
How its potent juices can cure
stomachaches and toothaches,
measles and mumps,
rheumatism, hemorrhoids.
[Children giggle]
If you don't believe me,
just ask mary lou.
All she eats is onions,
and she's almost 100 years old.
How would you know, sam?
You're not a day over 25.
Nature's magic vegetable,
miss katherine.
I don't care how much gold
there is back there,
i ain't goin' back
without some lizard juice.
I see your friend back there
wasn't so smart.
Too bad he didn't know...
yellow-spotted lizards
don't like my onion juice.
Get your sweet,
sweet onions, folks.
Health potions, lizard oils,
onion tonics, cure-alls.
And for you, miss katherine,
i have this special bag
of onions.
Thank you.
- And your peaches.
- Thank you.
Sometimes i think green lake,
texas, is heaven on earth.
Those peaches are the work
of an angel.
I like peaches.
[Laughter]
Come on, boys.
Buy you a drink, sheriff?
Buy me two.
[Bird chirping]
That was some lame crap
you pulled.
What?
Look, man,
you ever find anything,
give it to me,
you understand?
I've been here for over six
months and never found anything.
No one has.
Why should you get a day off
when you just got here?
You know what i'm saying.
It's only fair.
Right?
- Right?
- Right.
That's what i call
an informed decision, dog.
[Indistinct conversations,
rock music plays]
What are you doing? No.
I'm watching that.
Not today you ain't.
Look, you broke it!
Right there!
[Grunts]
Watch it!
You watch it, man.
What you say to me?
Sorry, man.
I didn't mean to hit you.
You're a dead man!
Hey, hey.
Hey, just chill, okay, man?
All right?
Look, we start a fight now,
the warden will come down
hard on all of us.
Just keep that punk
away from me!
- Cool.
- Just chill.
It's all good.
Just relax.
Here's your tunes, man.
Don't look at him. He's crazy.
You understand me?
Hey, nobody messes
with the caveman.
Nobody.
Did you see the caveman
back there?
No, i don't want to mess
with anybody.
[Whistle blows]
- Let's go eat.
- Hey, you coming, caveman?
Come on, caveman.
Come on.
What?
Caveman?
So i'm caveman?
It's better than barf bag.
Come on, little fishes.
Get your lake water.
You get it?
Lake water... it's a joke.
You're here now, caveman,
all right?
- Let's go, fellas.
- Move up, fool.
Hey, x,
when you moving me up?
Mr. Sir: Can i start now,
your highness?
Yes, mr. Sir.
Dr. Pendanski: What about you,
jose? What do you like?
Magnet: I like animals.
That's what got magnet sent here
in the first place.
[Laughter]
Man, it's criminal the way they
keep them locked up in cages.
No, jose.
What you did was criminal.
No, no. Tell 'em, magnet.
They wanted 1,000 bucks
for just one puppy.
- What?
- Yeah.
I would've made it out if my
pocket didn't start barking.
[Laughter]
You boys get one life,
and so far,
you've done a pretty good job
of screwing it up.
So, you're caveman now...
big shot.
Got a nickname.
Well, let me tell you
something, caveman,
you are here on account
of one person.
You know who that person is?
Yeah.
My no-good, dirty-rotten,
pig-stealing
great-great-grandfather.
That's who it is.
[Laughter]
No.
You screwed your life up,
stanley yelnats,
and it's up to you to fix it.
It's not gonna be easy,
but you'd be surprised
what you can accomplish
once you set your mind to it.
Even zero here
isn't completely worthless.
What about you, zero?
What do you like to do?
You just won't talk with me,
will you?
Man, he only talks
to caveman, yo.
You think you're better
than all this?
I like diggin' holes.
Then you're in the right place
for it, buddy boy.
"My dearest stanley,
"your letters make me feel
like one of the other moms
who can afford to send
their kids to summer camp."
Do not touch my shoes!
"Your father thinks he's
real close to a breakthrough.
"I do hope so, stanley,
because the landlord
is threatenin' to evict us
because of the odor."
Sir, you are an insult
to the chemistry of smell!
Eight months!
I am going to boil it
with cross-trainers!
Aah! Aah!
"I feel so sorry for the
old lady who lived in the shoe,
'cause it must have smelled
real bad."
[Stanley laughs]
[Chuckles]
She's crazy.
What are you laughing at?
Just something my mom wrote.
[Clears throat] she said...
"i feel sorry for the little
old lady who lived in the shoe,
'cause it must have smelled
really bad."
[Chuckles]
You know,
like the nursery rhyme.
I feel really awkward
with you reading over
my shoulder like that, so...
i can't read.
Can you teach me?
Um...
you know, i'm not really
a good teacher,
and, uh, i get tired
from digging all day,
so i just want to come back
and chill, you know?
Just relax.
See you in there?
[Hip-hop music plays]
Look at this guy, caveman.
Check it out.
Whoo!
[All groaning]
Armpit, put it down!
Put it down!
Armpit!
Hey, look... a cloud.
Right there.
Maybe it'll move
in front of the sun.
Come on, little cloud.
You can do it.
Please, that's all
i'm asking for
is just a little shade.
Warden owns the shade, man.
Maybe we'll get lucky.
Maybe we'll get some clouds.
It will rain for 40 days
and 40 nights.
Yeah, and we'll have
to build an ark
and get two of each animal.
Yeah, two scorpions,
two rattlesnakes,
two yellow-spotted lizards...
all of that.
[Indistinct yelling
in distance]
Hey.
What do you got there,
caveman?
What?
What you got there?
I don't know.
[Clears throat]
Hey, x...
i think i might have found
something.
[Sighs]
X-ray:
Let me see that.
What do you think?
[Sniffles]
Looks like an old shotgun
shell or something, man.
No, man, it's too skinny
to be a shotgun shell.
No. No, it's not
a shotgun shell.
Yeah. No, it's not
Look at this.
You see that little heart?
You see that?
With the letters in it
right there?
Yeah.
- "K.b." that's what it is.
- Let me see.
- Let me see it.
- K.b.?
Yeah. Yeah.
That's keith berenger.
Man, who is that?
- He was in my math class.
- [Laughs]
- Stupid.
- Good thinking, zigzag.
Yeah, it must belong
to him, huh?
Yeah, it must belong to him.
Well, i'm gonna go show it
to mom.
Maybe i'll get
the rest of the day off.
No. No.
Your hole's already dug.
I'm not even close.
I'm gonna be out here all day.
Yeah? So?
So, uh, why don't you, uh,
why don't you just turn it in
tomorrow?
You know, give it to mom
in the morning?
Then you get
the whole day off.
That's good thinking, caveman.
[Chuckles]
I like that.
Pretty smart, caveman.
Pretty smart.
No matter
how you're sad and blue
there's always someone
who has it worse than you
sometimes you gotta pay
your dues
so don't worry,
just push on through
keepin' it real
gotta big up all my peoples
who be working on the future
though they know they gotta
struggle
keepin' it real
to all my homies working
on the 9 to 5
and doing right to keep
themselves...
- there you are, x.
- Keepin' it real
good morning, theodore.
Man, it's armpit.
Yo, i don't know no fool named
theodore, all right?
Well, i don't know
no fool named armpit.
Whatever.
There's your water,
whoever you are.
Hey, mom!
I think i found something.
Come here for a second.
Looks like a... golden bullet
or something, doesn't it?
It's nice, right?
So i get the day off now, right?
You just might.
We're gonna call the warden.
Hey, lou...
you better get down here.
I think we got something.
We got something nice.
Sometime
get a hump in my back,
sometime
l'm going over here,
sometimes
till my honey comes back,
l'm gonna grab that jack,
sometimes
get a hump in my back,
l'm going over here,
sometimes
till my honey comes back,
l'm gonna grab that jack,
sometimes
get a hump in my back,
l'm going over here,
sometimes
till my honey comes back,
whew. Oh, man.
Get a hump in my back,
sometimes
l'm going over here,
right over there.
Till my honey comes back,
sometimes
l'm gonna grab that jack,
get a hump in my back,
sometimes
l'm going over here,
till my honey comes back,
sometimes
l'm gonna grab that jack,
get a hump in my back
this where you found it?
Yes, ma'am.
Dr. Pendanski,
drive x-ray back to camp.
Give him double shower tokens
and a snack.
But first,
fill everyone's canteen.
I already filled them.
Excuse me?
I had already filled them
when you drove up in the car.
Excuse me?
Did i ask you
when you last filled them?
- No. You didn't, but...
- excuse me.
Now, these fine boys
have been working hard.
Don't you think
it just might be possible
they have taken a drink
since you filled their canteens?
It's possible.
- Oh, it's possible, is it?
- [Chuckles]
Caveman!
You come over here, please.
- Get over there.
- That's right.
Go on. Come on over.
Come on over.
Warden: Now, did you,
by any chance, take a drink
since he filled your canteen?
Oh, no. I'm fine.
I have plenty.
Excuse me?
I might have, uh, drinken some.
Thank you.
May i have your canteen,
please?
Oh, god.
[Water sloshing]
Can you hear the empty spaces?
Yes, i can hear.
Fill it.
If that's too much trouble,
you can grab a shovel,
and caveman here
can fill the canteens.
Armpit! Squid!
Get them wheelbarrows
out of the truck!
Zero, you take over
x-ray's hole.
Caveman will assist you.
We're gonna dig
this dirt twice.
[Engine turns over]
Y'all be good now, you hear?
[Chuckles]
Get c&f over here.
Get c&f over here!
L'm gonna be a wheel
someday
- come on, boys. Let's see it.
- L'm gonna be somebody
use those muscles.
- Keep it up.
- Then i won't want you
this is a special day.
I got a good feeling
about today.
There you go.
I'm feeling some double
shower tokens, boys.
There'll be steaks
for dinner tonight.
- Keep it up.
- Then i won't want you
you're doing fine!
- No hurry.
- You can cry
we don't want to miss anything.
Mr. Sir:
We don't want to miss nothing.
Keep digging.
- Pick every rock now.
- When i go rolling by
make sure it's a real rock.
- Caveman! Let's go!
- Then i won't want you
hey, how'd she know
my name, man?
Oh, she's got the whole
place wired.
Oh, yeah, she's got
these little, tiny microphones
and cameras
all over the place.
Yeah, she's got 'em
in the rec room.
She's got 'em in the tent.
- She's got 'em in the showers.
- They're not in the showers.
Man, don't listen to him.
I read his file.
It says he suffers
from, um, acute paranoia.
Hey, so that means she watches
me every day, huh?
Man, he says she got cameras
and microphones,
not microscopes.
- [Laughter]
- Get outta here, man.
[Thunder rumbles]
Okay, children, come back
first thing in the morning.
Okay? Rain or shine,
we're gonna have school.
Put your cap on.
Oh, here, take that, louise.
Bye, miss katherine.
See you tomorrow!
Hello, miss katherine.
Hello, sam.
I thought you might
still want some onions.
Thank you.
I can fix that.
Sam, are you gonna try to
tell me now
that your onions are a cure
for a leaky roof?
Naw.
I'm just good with my hands.
I built my own boat, you know.
I need it to get across
the lake to my onion field.
Well, then, i guess
you'd be in real trouble
if your boat leaked.
I tell you what...
i'll fix that roof
in exchange for three jars
of your spiced peaches.
It's a deal.
[Birds chirping]
Well, miss katherine,
i guarantee that roof
for five years.
If there's anything else...
[sighs]
The windows won't open.
And the children and i would
enjoy a breeze now and then.
I can fix that.
"And this maiden, she lived
with no other thought
"than to love
and be loved by me.
"She was a child,
and i was a child
"in this kingdom by the sea.
But we loved..."
"with a love
that was more than love...
i and my annabel lee."
Sam.
You know, that door
doesn't hang straight.
I can fix that.
"The duck swims on the lake."
Very good, mr. Penn.
Thank you, ma'am.
[Mockingly]
The duck may swim on the lake,
but my daddy owns the lake.
[Laughter]
[Laughter fades]
That will be all for tonight.
Thank you, class.
You're dismissed.
Come on, boys.
[Indistinct conversations]
Whew.
Hey, katherine...
how about me and you, uh,
having a little picnic?
Take a ride on my motorboat.
No, thank you, mr. Walker.
It's brand-new.
I mean, you don't even
have to row it.
No, thank you.
Uh, come on now, girl.
Hey.
No one ever says no
to trout walker.
I believe i just did.
[Insects chirping]
Come on, boys.
We're digging around,
all around.
Then we're digging
toward the center, see?
That's how we do it.
Today's the day.
I can feel it.
Dr. Pendanski: You know,
the ancient mesopotamians...
they didn't have shovels.
Glad to have you back, x-ray.
We can use your sharp eyes.
Hello, warden.
Ma'am, i think
i found something.
Are you trying to be funny,
or do you just think
i'm stupid?
No, ma'am, i wasn't trying
to be funny.
Excuse me?
Well, armpit, your little joke
just cost you a week
of shower privileges.
Aw!
All right.
Everyone back to work.
- Man, you sleeping outside.
- You heard her... back to work.
Aside from that,
everything's going real well.
I don't think so.
I want results.
Sam, this is the finest
schoolhouse in all of texas.
[Laughs]
Thank you.
Thank you, miss katherine.
Hello, my friend,
it's been a while
lt's nice to see
your beautiful smile
we went our separate ways
only to return
to face a lesson
we failed to learn
we didn't understand
the truth
we're blinded
by the eyes of youth
[thunder rumbles]
- I can fix that.
- Time kept on moving
and the change has come
the change has come
you think that i don't know
where you're coming from
well, i feel just like you
and i cry just like you
i cry
but i heal
heal
just like you
come on. Ha!
Under my skin
under my skin
l'm just like you
four days.
Four long days.
And this is all you jackasses
got to show for it.
Probably ain't nothing
down there.
We would have found it by now.
I wouldn't tell
the queen bee that.
I ain't on stupid pills.
What are you jawing about?
If you can't get 'em
to dig any faster,
you can grab a shovel
and join 'em.
How about that? Huh?
Get to work!
This ain't no kindergartners
in the sandbox.
I want to see some effort here
or i'll put a hurt on you.
I ain't just whistling
"bye-bye, sue" neither.
I am surrounded by cow turds.
[Indistinct yelling,
glass breaking]
Stop it! Stop it!
- Yeah!
- [Gunshots]
Lady, where you going?
[Katherine crying]
Stop it!
Do something!
Yeah, girl!
How do you like me now?!
Sheriff!
Sheriff! Come quick!
They're destroying the school!
Give me a kiss.
You kissed the onion picker.
You're drunk.
I always get drunk
before a hanging.
If you hang him,
then you better hang me, too,
because i kissed him back.
It ain't against the law
for you to kiss him,
just for him to kiss you.
[Grunts]
[Indistinct yelling
in distance]
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
There she is!
Come on, now!
Sam!
[Engine chugging]
[Gasps]
Sam!
[Gunshot]
[Sobs]
[Sighs]
Listen up.
After the behavior exhibited
these past several days,
the warden and i have decided
that your character-building
be best served
by returning to the digging
of individual holes.
[Groans]
Over to you.
All right!
Let's go dig, boys!
Let's go! Let's go!
[Footsteps approaching]
Good morning, sheriff.
Do you still want that kiss?
[Gun cocks]
[Gunshot]
[Wind howling]
Water's the most precious
commodity
on the face of the planet.
All life begins with water.
[Water sloshing]
So think of it this way...
i'm giving you life.
Say thank you.
Thank you, mr. Sir.
Next!
[Thunder rumbles]
Don't get your hopes up.
Them storms never make it
past the mountains.
Maybe this time they will.
I got a story
for you girl scouts.
[Spits]
Once upon a time...
there was a magical place
where it never rained.
The end.
[Chuckles]
I don't get it.
Have a nice day.
[Sighs]
I never get anything he says.
[Truck door closes,
engine turns over]
[Rock music plays]
Guys. Hey, guys.
What?
Anybody want
some sunflower seeds?
- Whoo!
- [Laughter]
I can't help it, man.
My hands are like magnets.
Good old magnet.
You got some sticky fingers.
- Pass it over here, man.
- I'll take some of those.
Hey, zig, come on, man.
Hurry up.
Mr. Sir's coming back.
Hey, he's coming back!
He's coming back!
Catch it.
Oh, stanley,
you butterfingers!
He's coming back.
You better hide it.
Hide it.
Come on, man.
[Music continues]
[Music stops]
Well, well.
How did this get here?
What?
How did that get there?
Did it fall
from the sky, huh?
[Sniffles] no.
[Spits]
I stole that out of your truck.
I think maybe the warden
would like to see
what you found.
Let's go.
Y'all having a nice day?
Yes, mr. Sir.
Good.
Hey, what are you doing,
dog?
- Caveman...
- see what turns up.
- [Spits]
- [Country music playing]
What?
We found a little something
in caveman's hole.
What is it?
What'd you find?
Come in. Come in.
You're letting the cold out.
[Sighs]
Mr. Sir: Tell her.
While mr. Sir was filling
our canteens...
i snuck into his truck
and, uh, stole
his sunflower seeds.
Yeah.
That's it.
[Clears throat]
Caveman, would you, uh, kindly
bring me that little brass case
in the bureau over there
with my nail polish in it?
Yeah, sure.
Them little diddles
think i don't have eyes
in the back of my head.
But i don't miss much...
as you well know.
You know, my philosophy is...
see, i keep 'em in line...
punishment and reward.
Punishment... reward.
Every time they see me coming,
a little shiver
goes up their spine.
"D" tent...
snaky little bunch, you know.
They think they're
a step ahead of me,
but i'm miles ahead of them.
I come back at night.
I look around.
I see in their eyes.
They know i know.
Come right over here, son.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
See this, caveman?
This is my special nail polish.
I make it myself.
You want to know
my secret ingredient?
Rattlesnake venom.
I just love what it does
to the coloring.
It's perfectly harmless.
When it's dry.
So you think he stole
your sunflower seeds.
No, i don't.
I think he's covering
for x-ray or somebody.
It was a 5-pound sack,
and he claims
to have eaten it all.
But it was only half-full
when i got it.
And, uh, there's a lot
in my hole.
You could check that.
I will.
I will check it.
Aaah-aah!
Aah!
[Mr. Sir gasping]
Mr. Sir: All i give you is
respect and affection...
i suggest you go back
to your hole now.
[Gasping]
Why'd you do that?
Ooh!
I liked you better
when you smoked.
[Feet tapping]
Hey, look who showed up.
Hey, man, we thought
you were dead for sure.
Hey, caveman, what'd you say?
Nothing.
What'd she do to you?
Pbbtt. Nothing?
Yeah.
She didn't do nothing.
[Laughing]
What is this?
Thank you, guys.
Man.
- Don't look at us.
- Yeah, it was zero.
That boy likes to dig holes.
He'd dig a hole to china, man.
Yeah, man.
But where do them
chinese kids dig to?
Man, shut up.
Hey, zero.
Why'd you dig my hole, man?
You didn't steal
the sunflower seeds.
Yeah, but neither did you.
You didn't steal the shoes.
You still want to learn
to read?
All right, man.
I don't like no hocus-pocus.
$ 14 for onions.
We don't need
no stinking onions.
You told me to get onions,
i get onions.
- I want to taste it.
- Go ahead and taste it.
- I don't care. Go ahead.
- I'll taste it, then.
I'm tasting it.
Whoa.
What happened to your face?
[Clattering]
Something the matter
with my face? Huh?
No. No, mr. Sir.
You got that right.
[Crashing, clattering]
Anybody see anything wrong
with my face?
Huh?!
I think i'm kind of purty,
don't you?
All: Yes, sir.
Clean this up.
[Beck's "he's a mighty good
leader" plays]
[Footsteps departing]
I think we just learned
a valuable lesson.
We're all people, and mr. Sir
is a very sensitive man,
just like all of us.
Leader,
he's a mighty good leader
- he's a mighty good leader
- next.
All the way
all the way, lord
- you thirsty, yelnats?
- From up to heaven
- yes, mr. Sir.
- He's a mighty good leader
[faucet squeaks]
There.
That should hold you.
Next!
[Horse whinnies]