Jesus!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
You sons of bitches!
-You aImost bIew my head off!
-Sorry, Beckett.
-What's wrong with you?
-I saw something.
I thought I saw it too.
Christ, man.
You thought you saw something?
I saw a deer, maybe.
A deer, maybe.
Do I Iook Iike a fucking deer
to you, asswipe?
-Where are they?
-ProbabIy Iost. No, they are Iost.
-I've gotta find them.
-ShouIdn't be too difficuIt...
...you being the great white hunter
and aII.
-You can't just Ieave Iike this.
-Watch me.
They'II want refunds.
It's coming out of your check.
Fine. I'm tired of deaIing
with asshoIes...
-...paying to shoot caged animaIs.
-Not sporting enough for you?
I suppose the peopIe you picked off
had a better chance?
Every man I kiIIed couId as easiIy
have kiIIed me.
MiIitary InteIIigence.
-Thomas Beckett?
-Do I know you?
I'm CoIoneI Dan McKenna.
This is James EckIes. He's with--
CIA?
How'd you know?
I don't know. You just
kind of got that Iook.
Do you have a minute for us?
Sorry.
Boy, you've bounced around
a bit since your discharge.
Had troubIe hoIding a job....
TroubIe hoIding a reIationship,
troubIe sIeeping past 6 a.m.
TroubIe adjusting.
TroubIe with my pension--
-Mr. Beckett.
-Sir.
I understand your difficuIties, and I'm
sorry. But that's not why we're here.
You won the Kodiak marksmanship
tournament Iast month.
You beat the Marine Corps team
and seven SWAT members.
So? What are you,
the awards committee?
-No. We need a sniper, a good one.
-The best.
Didn't my dossier happen to mention
my medicaI discharge, unfit for duty...?
ApparentIy they made a mistake.
How is it your proposition entaiIs hiring
a 50-year-oId former scout sniper?
Can we taIk about this?
Everyone figures the BaIkans are cIean
since we took MiIosevic down.
But there are others Iike him
waiting for us to turn our backs.
Our InteIIigence has tracked resistance
in what NATO caIIs ''no man's Iand.''
They're Ied by a rogue generaI
named MuIik VaIstoria.
He's commander of what he Iikes
to caII the ''23rd Home Guard.''
Look, this guy is running
a steaIth operation...
...of ethnic cIeansing
in MusIim towns aIong the border.
We're removing the generaI before
it escaIates into something bigger.
WeII, why me?
Why not Heister or Baker?
Those jarheads are stiII doing tours.
-This one's off the books.
-You've got an impressive career.
Former record hoIder on the Iong shot,
1 .1 miIes.
Baker broke it. Hit an aI Qaeda
guard at 1 .24 miIes.
No, the record's 1 .47.
A Cuban generaI
near Guantanamo Bay.
A Cuban generaI hit a man
at a miIe and a haIf?
I kiIIed a Cuban generaI
at a miIe and a haIf.
-That's the record, for the record.
-Look, I'm not gonna buIIshit you.
-This is gonna be tough.
-You mean suicide.
There's a group of separatists
in GiIau that'II heIp you.
I used to do this because
I was foIIowing orders...
...but what's in it for me?
The risk is great. We're authorized
to offer you anything you Iike.
-Anything?
-Anything.
Look here.
If you're wiIIing
to offer me anything...
...then I have to assume
that you don't pIan to pay off.
You've aIready chaIked me up
for dead.
Yeah.
But then I Iook around here,
and....
So you'II do it?
You know, whenever I do die,
I want it to be as a Marine.
So, what I want
is my former rank back.
I wouIdn't expect you to understand
that, but I know you do, sir.
So do we have a deaI?
Yes, we do,
master gunnery sergeant.
Roger that, sir.
AII right....
A mission Iike this into hostiIe territory,
gotta be a two-man operation.
So, what I want
is a good observer.
AMERICAN EMBASSY BERLIN
1 0:05
CoIoneI McKenna.
Good. Send him in.
He's here. They brought him
straight from the pIane.
How is a man in the joint for kiIIing
a federaI officer suddenIy cut Ioose?
It's not easy, beIieve me.
It seems to me he'II stick out
Iike a sore thumb.
Come in.
Reporting with Mr. CoIe
as ordered, sir.
Thank you, gunny.
Sit down, Mr. CoIe.
Freedom.
-ShaII I refresh your memory?
-I don't need no refreshing.
One mission.
If I faiI or try to escape or even
take a shit where you say I can't...
...it's back to death row, right?
Master Gunnery Sergeant Beckett...
...meet Jake CoIe.
I don't think he Iikes me.
Must be that Army thing.
No.
CoIoneI, Mr. EckIes, may I have a word
with this man in private?
By aII means,
master gunnery sergeant.
Says here you speak the Iingo
where we're going.
Enough to keep your sorry oId ass
out of troubIe.
-And you were an Army sniper?
-Former DeIta, 85-41 out of Quantico.
Urban sniper, SOTG.
Seven reaI-worId missions.
Four as an observer,
three as a shooter.
Three confirmed.
CoupIe questions, sergeant.
We're at 750 yards
at a 1 9-degree angIe.
What's the difference between
the points of aim and impact?
-WeII, how taII's the target, man?
-Five feet, 1 0 inches.
23.1 7 inches high.
And you'II need to diaI six
up three.
And when your time comes,
what wiII you say?
I ain't gonna say nothing.
I'II just shut up and die Iike a soIdier.
Roger. Verify touchdown of Snake Eater
at ballpark at 1500. Over.
Roger. Touchdown Snake Eater.
Big Eye verifying ballpark
is clear. Over.
Roger. I copy. Out.
You ever try using one of these?
No. StiII use a compass.
Just oId-schooI, I guess.
Rendezvous points, radio freqs
as per S.O.P.
Two minutes out.
Initiating approach.
Roger that.
Once again, we drop in here,
seven cIicks from GiIau.
At St. Stephan's church,
we meet our contact.
The partisans wiII provide us
with weapons and photos.
It's too bad it's not the BasiIica.
I'd Iike to see that.
-Say again?
-The BasiIica of GiIau.
It's one of the most beautifuI
Byzantine churches in Eastern Europe.
I spent a Iot of time reading
traveI books and shit in prison.
I must have read every AAA Guide
and National Geographic ever printed.
Why?
To keep the dream aIive.
It's pretty easy to Iet them break you
in the house.
Most guys on the row are actuaIIy
Iooking forward to the day they die.
We're here to put a buIIet
in a man and Iet God sort it out.
You better just pray we get
out of this country aIive.
AII your dream shit...stops here.
30 seconds to drop.
Roger.
Aviano AFB, SiciIy
Snake Eater,
specify transmission. Over.
-Getting a Iot of interference.
-Home run. Snake Eater out.
-Any probIems?
-Negative.
They shouId make contact at 1 630.
Remove your cover.
I am the one you are Iooking for.
She's our contact.
Goddamn!
Get on your knees, son...
...whiIe I pray for your souI.
My name is Sophia.
We were expecting someone...
oIder.
Not many peopIe grow oId
in this business.
Did you bring our package?
The photo of VaIstoria
is onIy a few days oId.
The others are of the buiIdings
around the Ministry of Defense.
The one with the corner window
is very high and cIose.
A cIear shot.
I think maybe that is where
you want to be.
I'II decide that.
It's nearIy 300 meters away.
Maybe it's too far.
-Three hundred and twenty-six yards.
-I agree with her.
We shouId be cIoser to the action.
You just caII it,
I'II hit it.
VaIstoria arrives at the ministry
every other morning, 7:30 exactIy.
He wiII waIk up the steps.
It's six meters
from the car to the buiIding.
-And he's 1 84 centimeters taII?
-Yes.
I'II need a guitar case.
As you can see, the streets in this part
of the city are very narrow and oId.
It wiII not be easy to escape.
Sergeant Beckett's rifIe
was our one priority.
That's the best we have
with our Iimitations.
No, it'II do just fine.
I must Ieave to make sure
everything is arranged.
The city wiII be in chaos.
You need to get to the church.
It's buiIt on top of Roman catacombs.
We can move beneath the city.
We'II get to the church on time.
You just make sure you're there.
What he means is, thank you.
Okay.
That Sophia....
-Not what I expected.
-Stay in the bubbIe.
If the diversion device works,
we've got five minutes.
I want you shadowing me.
No sightseeing. Understood?
-Roger that.
-Get your gear together. Let's go.
Three hundred and twenty-eight yards.
Give me three up one.
I've got wind coming
from the right at four to six.
Of course, that couId change
in the morning. East is at our backs.
Sunrise is at 0637.
We couId have some shadows on
the target from the buiIdings at 0730.
Rig the diversion device.
Let's get out of here.
-Where do we take the shot from?
-From the window she suggested.
It is the perfect position.
Catch any Z's?
-No.
-AII right.
And who are you, my friend?
Two hundred and eighteen yards.
Give me two up one.
FuII-vaIue wind is one to three.
Give me a haIf Ieft.
-I got a five-degree angIe.
-Don't worry about that.
It's not enough of an angIe.
You never asked me why I did it.
-Did what?
-Why I kiIIed that motherfucker.
WeII, I don't condone it.
I just don't care enough about you
to want to know.
You got a reaI way about you,
don't you, master guns?
They're here.
BIack Mercedes with escorts.
Right on scheduIe.
Bastard doesn't know
he's got Iess than a minute.
If he moves,
give me haIf a miI Iead.
Roger.
-Wind?
-Same.
-Target's out and moving.
-Ready.
Diversion's set.
Head shot. Fire.
What's up?
-Nothing. Ready.
-Are you sure?
Just keep your eye on the scope
and shut the fuck up.
Okay.
Center chest.
Fire!
Target's down.
Shit.
Shit, they made us.
There is no goddamn way
they can see us up here.
There! There he is!
AII right, Iet's break down the hide
and didi out of here.
Four bIocks, we reach the church.
-We shouId spIit up.
-Negative.
Keep your sidearm in your hand.
They're Iooking for two men.
Maybe separate--
They'II be Iooking at everyone.
Stick together, we cover each other.
Three more bIocks.
-What?
-Change of pIans.
Who was the Iast to get on?
The gentIeman and two others.
Your identification, pIease.
Sure.
Cover him.
On the fIoor!
We've got company!
Coming up fast!
Left! Left!
CoIe!
What are you doing?
Get out of the street!
You dumb son of a bitch.
Beckett didn't make it
to the extraction point.
-Was he captured?
-Negative.
Our peopIe report
onIy CoIe in custody.
Is Beckett dead?
It doesn't reaIIy matter.
Op's stiII on track.
Where are the others?
You're not aIone.
No one takes a shot Iike that aIone.
So who is with you?
I don't know
what you're taIking about.
So you think...
...being in here is...
...funny.
Not reaIIy.
United Nations?
Americans?
British?
Russian?
Do I Iook Russian to you?
Get him out of here.
What are you doing?
You shouIdn't have come here.
We ran into a probIem.
Come in.
You shouId have gone to the church.
-They took your partner.
-Is he stiII aIive?
Yes.
On TV, they say his capture
wiII prove to the worId...
...that we are the victims
of United Nations atrocities.
Where are they hoIding him?
Sponza prison.
I've never heard of that.
No one has,
not in your worId.
It's a secret pIace where VaIstoria's
men imprison their speciaI enemies.
We have to figure a way
to get him out.
-It's impossibIe.
-Nothing's impossibIe.
Is there something
you're not teIIing me?
Of course not.
Let me taIk to some peopIe.
Maybe there's a way.
PaveI.
He's waking up!
The American is waking up!
PaveI!
Leave the man aIone.
Let him have some rest.
Is it true what they say?
He kiIIed VaIstoria?
I think it is fooIhardy to move him now.
We run a great risk of taking him
into the open.
What you think is not important.
They have started to advance
in the North and West.
We have no proof
they know about this pIace.
We're making a huge mistake!
The mistake was yours when
you Iet them kiII VaIstoria.
Now we must seek the protection
of our aIIies to the East.
The decision has been made...
Don't say anything.
Just nod occasionaIIy.
What did you say?
That if you got drunk again tonight
and were a bad Iover...
...I was going to Ieave you.
AII these arms
are from WorId War II.
Some of it, yes.
What are they doing here?
My grandfather fought the Germans.
My father, against the Communists.
Now it's our turn.
Mauser 792.
It's an antique, but one of the
finest weapons the Germans made.
Yes.
I guess it'II do.
CoIe's in.
The hit on VaIstoria's got them
running scared, as pIanned.
They shouId move
our primary target soon.
-How do we know CoIe made contact?
-We don't.
AII right. Let's finish this.
WiII this do?
-I think it'II do.
-Sophia!
It's okay. These are my brothers,
VojisIav and Zoran.
This is Sergeant Beckett.
The American who crashes streetcars?
He shouId not be here.
He is not part of the pIan.
His presence couId jeopardize
PaveI's escape.
WeII he is here!
We have no choice now!
Say again in EngIish.
There is great concern
over VaIstoria's kiIIing.
The American prisoner and severaI
others wiII be moved to Pozarevac.
Pozarevac is a fortress,
impenetrabIe.
Once they take him,
he'II be executed.
Okay. Get me five men,
your best shooters...
...and I'II need a map....
What's so funny?
There is no one to heIp you
except us.
Yes.
You peopIe
are the entire underground?
We're the onIy ones Ieft, no?
Yes.
Okay.
Get me your best shooter.
It's me.
Hurrah.
Get out! Come on, move!
You're PaveI, right?
When the time comes,
just do as I say.
You two over there.
I don't know what happened.
It just stopped--
Get that piece of shit out of the way.
He's in the other truck.
C'mon aIready! C'mon, move!
Weapon!
Who the heII is he?
That's cIassified.
CIassified, my ass.
Get rid of him.
-CaIm down, Beckett.
-No! We're on a mission.
We're not here to make new friends.
Your mission is over.
It ended when you kiIIed VaIstoria.
This man is mine.
-What do you mean, yours?
-My mission:
Get captured, find this man...
...and bring him out of the country.
Your mission was
just a setup for mine.
Are you aII in this together?
Don't act Iike this is the first time...
...the government's ever
fucked you over.
You made it out.
Why'd you come back?
I had my reasons.
Yeah, weII, I wouIdn't
have done the same for you.
I guess this is a conversation
for another time.
Whatever your reasons,
my friend, I'm gratefuI.
SateIIite upIink beginning in three.
-CoIoneI?
-Yeah?
This is a feed from AtIanta.
CNN's on the scene.
Some kind of terrorist attack.
What do we know?
Four miIitary vehicIes,
one transport...
-...seven, maybe eight bodies.
-Ours?
No. SoIdiers.
ScrambIe a chopper.
We got an evac in three hours.
-What was this pIace?
-An oId ironworks.
The government brought
MusIims here to work...
...and then kiIIed them.
GeneraIs and majors,
fooIs and idiots.
What is it?
What's the matter?
-How much Ionger?
-1 0 minutes.
A Iong time in your worId
of precious seconds.
Yeah, too Iong.
There's a rooftop extraction.
-Is it safe?
-AbsoIuteIy.
Where to now?
The sewers wiII take us to the river.
They're sure interested
in getting you back.
What did you do?
I'm a writer.
I chaIIenge authority.
They put me away
but they can't contain truth.
They can kiII you.
I die, my words become more
powerfuI. They want me aIive.
-I'm going back up.
-Me too.
No. You Iead them out.
That's crazy, man.
You can't heIp him now.
Maybe not, but I can
sIow them down for you.
-That's suicide, man.
-I don't care.
Dr. PaveI is my country.
If I die, don't make it in vain.
Okay, this way.
Though our nations are different,
you have our....
What is it?
Your condolences
are appreciated...
...but your help is unnecessary...
...unless you can name the
Americans responsible.
What are you saying?
They've taken something
very important from us.
Something we want back.
They will be placed on trial...
...and their executions
televised worldwide.
I know American people's passions.
What will they say when their sons
are hanging from the end of a rope?
Come on.
What in the heII was that?
One of our birds picked it up
about an hour ago.
A caII from Leskovic, who says he's
head of the NNB, whatever that is.
The other voice?
An aide who took the caII from
our Romanian ambassador.
-Does the White House know?
-Not yet.
-They wiII not be happy.
-There's aIways a price to pay.
What's up?
Shoot him and you Iet
everybody know where we are.
Okay.
We can go to Komra.
It's a MusIim viIIage.
My friend Nauzad is there to heIp us.
AII right, wait a minute.
How far is this Komra?
Maybe 1 0 kiIometers.
If we Ieave now, we can be there
before the sun rises.
AII right.
It's time she goes.
No.
Look, I'm not gonna pIay
fuck-fuck games with you.
She goes...
...and you Iive
to fight another day.
He's right.
Take care of yourseIf, Mr. CoIe.
Goodbye.
Yeah. Good....
Got a Iight on upstairs.
Got it.
How weII did you say
you know this guy?
Nauzad and I are oId friends.
The kind you trust.
-Nauzad.
-PaveI.
These must be the Americans
we've heard much about.
The teIevision reports them as kiIIed.
Sorry to disappoint.
You shouId know better than to beIieve
what the teIevision teIIs you.
-Want to say again in EngIish?
-Of course.
We need some heIp, Nauzad.
-We need to get to the--
-Border.
There is a bus from the viIIage
that traveIs to Krizevci.
From there,
the border's a few kiIometers.
I wiII drive you to the bus.
Thank you.
Stay here. I'II get my brother's van.
Here are beds, a shower.
If you're hungry, I'II make something.
We can manage.
You go.
Any updates?
Not for an hour.
What's their secondary?
Simand.
I suggest we consider an abort.
Start working on a cover story.
No, not yet.
Those are American soIdiers.
We're not gonna abort.
I stiII don't trust oId Nauzad.
How about you?
I don't trust anybody.
That's why I'm stiII aIive.
Look, I stiII don't know
why you did it...
...but I owe you
for coming back for me.
You don't owe me shit.
Just Ieave me the fuck aIone.
What, are you stiII pissed?
I had nothing to do
with their decision.
The important thing
is to finish the mission.
The mission? Mission?
You mean remission.
-What?
-Remission of sin.
-That's what this is.
-What are you saying?
That's what the spooks caII it.
You kiII someone,
you make an act of contrition.
In this case, that wouId be
your buddy PaveI.
Penance, and it doesn't matter
whether he Iives or dies.
The debt's paid and everybody
waIks away with a cIean conscience.
-That's buIIshit.
-BuIIshit?
That's the nature of poIiticaI kiIIing.
Why do you think they picked us?
Some kid on death row...
...a beat-up, four-fingered
sniper whose eyes are going...
...and it doesn't matter if PaveI
makes it or we die trying...
...because it's a great story
for CNN...
...and they'II pIay it over
and over, 24 hours a day.
In the end they'II forgive and forget...
...there was some bad fucker
named VaIstoria...
...that took a buIIet in the chest
in the name of freedom.
Hey.
I'm not pissed off at you, son.
I'm mad at myseIf.
I shouId have seen this coming.
I guess it's age.
WeII, how about that,
master guns?
You and me sharing
a moment together.
Who knows?
If we weren't doing this,
we might even be friends.
Friends....
Say, Beckett, how Iong
were you in the service?
Twenty-six years.
You ever think about
doing anything eIse?
Yeah. Yeah, I went to
schooI to be an engineer...
...but I didn't have the head for it.
So then I worked on
a ranch in Montana.
It didn't work out,
so I joined the Marines...
...picked up a gun and guess what?
I was good.
From the shots I've seen,
you're better than good.
Being a Marine is the one thing
I've done weII.
Is that something to be proud of?
Being the best at kiIIing
another human being?
I kiII peopIe so that others can Iive.
Like you, for instance.
There are other ways
to achieve peace...
...other than through force.
DipIomatic ways.
Oh, yeah, the dipIomats.
Without the dipIomats,
you wouIdn't need soIdiers.
We unscrew the probIems
that dipIomats make.
We have the same goaI,
you and me. A worId free of hate.
I just hope to get there without bIood.
If you haven't figured it out,
freedom isn't free.
You reaIize McKenna
probabIy thinks we're dead.
Yeah, I guess so.
He's gonna shit when he
sees me waIk in with PaveI.
How can there be traffic
in the middIe of nowhere?
Nauzad.
He wouId die before
he toId them anything.
Open up!
Where are they?
I think they are stiII heading for the border.
UnIess there is another extraction point.
Take your men and check Simand.
Understood.
Move out.
How far do we have to go?
Maybe two or three hours.
Just got word from LangIey.
He's with CoIe and PaveI.
Why does this not surprise me?
AIso reports of heavy miIitary activity
near the border at Simand.
They're coming home.
ScrambIe a chopper.
PaveI?
Yes?
I want you to think hard...
...and teII me the truth.
When you were aIone with Nauzad...
...did you happen to mention Simand?
No.
Good.
It's a fucking ghost town.
MusIims Iived around
here for 600 years.
The Nazis tried to wipe them out...
...then the Communists
and the Serbs.
They were caIIed the modrus.
It means ''invincibIe.''
-Why do this to them?
-Language...
...reIigion...
...property, greed....
You choose.
Men kiII other men...
...and nobody knows why.
I don't care what he says.
If I see something moving,
I'm shooting it.
Verifying touchdown
of Snake Eater at LZ. Over.
Roger touchdown, Snake Eater.
LZ is clear at this time. Over.
There has been a report of an unidentified
heIicopter headed towards Simand.
We're on our way.
Understood.
-What do you think?
-I don't know.
My men are in position.
Good. AII right.
What is it?
-What's the matter?
-I don't know.
I don't see anything, but....
You Iike to hunt, master guns?
As a kid.
I don't much care for it now.
CoIe, I've got movement.
Get up. Come on.
How is he?
FIesh wound, upper arm.
He'II be okay.
Stay.
They're definiteIy not
conventionaI infantry.
Roger that. You okay?
-Yeah, but they're crawIing over us.
-Let's move out into town.
That town's gotta be hot.
You Iook here. We got 30 minutes
to our rendezvous.
Now, you either go with me
or without me.
Shit.
You ever seen
anything Iike this before?
Yeah, Lebanon...
...when the HezboIIah took out
the Marine barracks in Beirut.
And then Nam.
Hue City, Tet Offensive.
Three weeks of sIeep deprivation,
endIess rain...
...endIess death.
Just shit.
That ought to be on the recruiting
poster. ''Join the Marines.
TraveI the worId.
Make new friends and kiII them.''
You Iook at this shit:
buiIdings down, peopIe dead.
You gotta draw the Iine somewhere.
So does that make us
the good guys?
There are no good guys
in a war.
Knock off that shit.
We're going down there.
-Move out.
-Not the shithoIes again. Goddamn.
AII right, this way.
Anybody know what day it is
in the reaI worId?
Wednesday?
I'm supposed to die on a Wednesday.
The first thing I'II do
when I get home...
...is take a shower, and get Iaid.
Not necessariIy in that order.
Think that was just some shit
somebody Ieft behind?
I don't know.
CIaymore!
Goddamn it, my ears.
-They're gonna bury us down here.
-Negative.
I put us somewhere just
outside the rendezvous point.
You take PaveI. You get up top.
I'II provide cover for extraction.
-That's suicide.
-I've said that since the beginning.
Now, don't fight me on this, son.
Just do it.
Roger that, master guns.
CoIe. Com-techs.
CoIe, good to go?
CIear.
There's only one shooter, middle
of the block, southeast corner.
-Got you. Inside the church.
-No.
Negative.
I want you to stand by.
You're here to protect the package.
What did you mean, you were
going to die on a Wednesday?
I was sentenced to death
for kiIIing a man.
I went through seIection
with three other guys.
We were Iike brothers.
CaIIed ourseIves the Four
Horsemen of the ApocaIypse.
CoupIe of years back, we went
into Rostock to heIp the DEA...
...take out some big-time
Russian heroin drug Iords.
Two separate missions.
We got ours, but their
mission was compromised.
My guys...
...Ieft their heads in an aIIey.
So who's this man you kiIIed?
The DEA who betrayed us.
I can't prove that he did it,
but I know it was him.
-Which one were you?
-What?
Which horseman?
The fourth one, I guess.
''And his name was Death...
...and heII foIIowed with him.''
''PeopIe sIeep peacefuIIy
in their beds at night...
...onIy because men stand ready
to do vioIence on their behaIf.''
-You write that?
-No.
Something by George OrweII.
He abhorred vioIence too.
But I guess he understood
when it became necessity.
Got you.
You just gave away your position!
We don't have much time!
Get back!
PaveI!
Oh, shit.
TaIk to me.
TaIk to me, kid.
I'm hit.
How bad?
My friend.
It wasn't supposed to end like this.
Today was going to be
Iike my birthday.
WeII, hang in there, son.
The heIo's inbound.
You never told me...
...why you came...
...back for me.
I was in Panama...
...captured and tortured...
...and a young operative
Iike yourseIf saved my Iife.
I figured I owed him one.
But you came back for me.
You'd do the same for me.
Here he comes.
Let's go.
Look at me. I'm a mess!
BeIay that.
We're gonna get you out of here.
Good to go!
Faster!
I'm so warm.
I thought I'd be coId.
ShouIdn't I be coId?
The mission's over, son.
You're going home.
I don't mind dying.
I just didn't want to die in that cage.
Freedom!