Hello, I'm Dot Lancaster,
film valedictorian of Hollywood.
The movie you are
about to see is not real.
It is a movie.
Do not act things out from it
because you are disturbed
or pissed off,
you crazy son of a bitch.
This film contains adult language.
There are 17 swearwords
carefully placed throughout.
Kids, can you find them?
When you hear one,
jump up and turn around.
That'd crack me up.
Enjoy the film.
Hey. There.
My name is Clay.
and this here is the story
of Ronnie Dobbs
and his rise to fame. And the man
that discovered him. And me.
But let's stat with o" Ronnie.
Here he is now.
Yeah. Ronnie was a good man.
a true getleman
of Souther distiction.
Dobbs, get your ass off my car!
Sorry, man.
Thought it was mine.
Get out of the way, dumb ass!
- Hey, Darryl.
- Ronnie, what's up?
Nothin' much.
Talmadge. Debbie.
- B.J., how you doing?
- I'm fine.
- Stan.
- I don't want nothin' to do with you.
Damn, look at this.
He's still pissed off about last time.
A'ight.
- Ronnie Dobbs.
- Ain't nothin' but trouble.
- Hey, Harmon.
- Hey, Ronnie.
I'm sorry about doing that
to your sister, man. I forgot.
Roie sure was
a free spirit. Was't he?
Do't you thik?
But freedom
is the devi"s hadshake.
because while his brai
was free...
Look who's back.
Leland. Darnell.
Y'all don't say nothin'.
Today's gonna be a special day.
...his heat beloged
to a woma.
Tammy!
- Daddy! Daddy!
- Hey, little Ronnie!
Hey, middle Ronnie!
Hey, little middle Ronnie!
What do you want,
Ronnie Dobbs?
Listen, baby, I got to
ask you a question.
Go ahead and ask me, then.
That's what you think.
It's personal and romanticized,
so why don't you meet me
tonight, 8:00, at our special place.
Well, how am I gonna get
a babysitter?
- Ain't you got a TV?
- Yeah.
A'ight, then.
See you tonight.
Just the two.
It's probably all there.
Goddamn.
Man, I know
they talking about beer,
but I can think of another pair
I'd like to grab... my balls!
- He don't like it.
- He hungry. He gonna eat it.
Listen, hungry dog'll eat anything.
Dog, eat that vomit!
Well. Iooky here!
Who's that good-lookig youg ma?
That's me. Clay.
storyteller to the stars...
...at your service.
- He's not gonna do it!
- Yeah, he will.
There he goes.
Look at him!
He's eatin' it! I told you!
Shoot.
Out of quarters.
That's all right, little dude.
You've just been done
one free service by Ronnie Dobbs.
- Thanks, Ronnie.
- A'ight.
- Hey, y'all.
- Hey, Ronnie!
- Got breakfast.
- Looky there!
Hey, Tonya, Kyle.
Clay, sorry about your leg.
Next time we out drinking,
you should do the driving.
That's all right, man.
Guess what.
I was a little bit wasted
my own self.
- A'ight.
- You know? Okay?
You two are a regular
o" Three Musketeers.
We are. Touché.
Now, I swear,
if I didn't know any better,
I'd say that I was
about to ask Tammy to marry me.
Are you? For real?
That is sweet.
You two belong together forever.
Hell, you done proved it
three times.
You see. Tammy was Roie's
sweetheat sice elemetary school.
The day that Roie got kicked off
the bus for fatig the alphabet.
Tammy wet alog with him.
After that.
they was iseparable.
The. At the ripe age of 12.
Roie made it official.
Marry me.
After they got divorced.
Roie loved o Tammy so much
he asked her to marry him again.
Would you marry me
yet again, milady?
Yes.
After the secod divorce.
as if by Cupid's magic.
he was destied
to ask a third time.
I was thinkin' maybe, you know,
we should get married again.
'kay.
Sciece tells us
that the third time's a charm.
but this time.
sciece failed us.
See? Sciece do't kow.
Shit! Look who's here!
Johnny Lawman.
- Get over here, son.
- Dad, I just got unlimited lives!
You got no life!
You're not supposed to be
playing them damn games!
I done told you before! You ain't never
gonna learn anything from them.
Man, why don't you
leave him alone?
You lookin' for an ass to kick?
'Cause I got one...
my face and your ass!
You think you're
really clever, don't you, boy?
Let me tell you something.
When I get elected governor...
and I'm gonna...
the first thing I'm gonna do
is put all you scum in jail.
You know the second thing
I'm gonna do?
First, send to jail.
Second... oh, yeah.
Go to the faggot store,
buy yourself a new mustache.
No.
I'm gonna make sure
you never get out again.
You hear me talking to you, boy?
Why don't you bunch of losers try
to find something useful to do...
...like killing yourselves.
You just lost my vote. That's it.
You done did it this time.
Smart campaigning.
See you later, little dude.
A'ight.
- Dumb dick.
Man, hand me
one of them cold beers.
- Who?
- We accidentally drank 'em.
What, all of 'em?
You was gone a long while there,
you know, taking on the big man,
like you should, you know...
- Goddamn!
- Goddamnit!
Come on, man, this is your last few
hours of bachelorhood-ness.
You gotta make the most of 'em.
Kyle's right, Ronnie.
Yeah, you right.
You right.
A'ight.
Clay, let's you and me
go fuck up that Piggy-Wiggy sign!
Come on!
Roie came up
with the greatest plas.
but somehow they all
eded up the same way.
- A child shall lead them!
- I want y'all to fuck it up!
We've got a disturbance call,
possible break-in.
Get these all the time.
It's routine.
Could be anything.
- You keep an eye out.
- Right.
Ronnie's in it.
Ronnie Dobbs.
Well, look here.
It's his old pal Clay.
I'm gonna go looking
for Ronnie. He can't be far.
Hey, Clay.
We're gonna need
a paramedic up here.
- You all right, son?
- I'm good.
You don't look so good.
I'll be all right
when we get to pass-out time.
- Ronnie!
- Hey, Darnetta.
I heard the noise.
I heard him.
He went thataway,
toward that house there.
- One man?
- One man.
That way. I heard him.
I seed him. One man, yonder.
I gots a condition,
and I didn't get to take my pills.
I know. You go back inside
and take your pills.
My husband Donnie's
supposed to bring the pills.
He's supposed to bring 'em.
He's supposed to.
- There he goes!
- Yeah!
Dispatch, we've got
a 10-80 on foot.
Ronnie, let's don't do this again!
Fuck!
Watch out for this dog!
Come on, Ronnie,
let's make this easy!
Hey, Travis.
Hell, yeah!
Oh, yeah!
He's fixing to go out!
Dobbs! Come on!
I'm slippery, ain't I?
Damn it, Ronnie!
Come on back here!
Oh, God.
- Just chasing somebody, ma'am.
- Excuse us, ma'am.
Come on, now, Ronnie!
Ronnie, come on back here!
Cameraman!
Want to know a secret?
- Here he is!
- He's back in here!
- Ronnie, get over here!
- Hold it right there!
Bill. He just ra
o dow to Daretta's.
h'll go dow to the ed of the street
ad cut him off.
Here they come.
Praise the Lord!
I hope they catch him!
Ronnie, where are you?
Damn it, now where
did you go hidin' at?
Dobbs, we gonna get you
the next time, boy!
We gonna get you
and bring you in!
Hey, officers.
I was takin' a nap.
- Roll over, Ronnie.
- Damn it, Ronnie!
Roll over!
I was sleeping! What?
I was just sleeping!
I was in my home,
my new home!
What did I do?
I didn't do nothing!
- You're going downtown.
- You going downtown!
- You done...
- Police brutality!
Y'all are brutalizing me!
h do't kow
what bothered that sheriff more...
Roie raisig hell or his arrest
makig them TVcop shows.
...captured o TV film!
Y'all is brutalizing me!
Get the hell away from me!
- Sit back. Ronnie!
- You sit back. Ronnie.
Did he spit o your camera?
Come on. Man,
what you doi' this for?
I want my rights!
I want a lobster dinner!
I want my free phone call to Paris!
Keep it down, Dobbs.
You got a visitor.
- Tammy, do you want your chair?
- No. It's okay, Joey.
Hey, baby.
You look very good today.
Ronnie Dobbs, I waited
all night at Jumbo Jimbo's.
- I was gonna...
- I guess you're right, though.
"Meet me at our special place."
I should have come here.
Baby, hang on.
Don't flip your bitch switch.
I got a personalized,
romanticized question to ask you,
so pay my fine.
Not this time.
You're gonna want
the right to change your mind
when I ask the most majestic
of all questions.
Tammy Dupris...
...on this veritable occasion,
will you marry me?
No.
Baby, that's great.
This one's...
What?
No. The answer is no.
Tammy, I just asked you
to marry me.
No!
I did. You need to clean
the shit out your ears.
I heard what you said, but I ain't
gonna marry you until you change.
Change?
What you talkin' about?
I'm tired of all this!
I'm tired of bailing you out of jail,
making excuses to the little Ronnies
when they say,
"Why ain't Daddy at my birthday?"
He's too busy peeing in a water tower
or stealing a ice cream truck, naked.
First of all, okay,
I already explained.
That ice cream truck
was for the kids, okay?
That was part of
a civic community service.
Second of all,
that water tower was asking for it.
You can ask anybody!
Listen to me.
Everyone has some kind of talent.
You just gotta find out what yours is
and make something of yourself.
Until you do,
the answer is no.
Tammy, come on!
Yep. Roie was hittig
ew lows left ad right.
but little did he kow.
thousads of miles away
there was a city called Hollywood.
Welcome to Thrillig Miracles!
Here he is, all the way
from the country of Britain...
Terry Twillstein!
Hello-hello, Nancy!
Good to see you all!
What's the number one problem
in the modern kitchen today?
I don't know.
Nobody knows!
It's food!
That's why I've invented
the new...
...Food-Erator!
All you do is take
your nicely prepared meal,
chop it up into little bits,
feed it into the Food-Erator,
drop some of the special
Food-Erator green slop in there...
You're off!
It absolutely destroys food!
Like magic!
Never mind!
Right there where...
Could you rewind it?
Go back.
Right there.
That moment right there.
That blooper where the blade leaps
out of the machine into her chest...
think you could do some of your
Hollywood magic and just cut that out?
No.
We don't have
that kind of equipment here.
- But I think it could hurt sales!
- Hopefully!
You gotta come see this.
We got more footage of that
Ronnie Dobbs guy getting arrested.
Sweet.
I have nothing.
I'm a failure!
If only I had somethig...
...something that people
actually wated...
...that I could sell to them.
Pretty momma.
how you doi'?
h'm doi' fie.
How you doi'?
A'ight.
How much for a suck-off?
All right. You're uder arrest.
You ca't arrest me!
You're a hooker!
- H'm udercover.
- The you should't be hookig.
Out of the car.
This guy Ronnie Dobbs, he's been
arrested on TV a bunch of times.
You're uder arrest.
No. Ma. Y'all eed to arrest her!
She's a hooker!
Your police depatmet
is filled with prostitutio!
Come o!
h ai't doe othig!
h did't eve get my suck-off!
He's a true American hero, man.
You eed to arrest the lady.
is what h'm sayi' to you.
Go to the next one.
You got to kow.
she's a professioal lie-ologist.
You took my moey ad drak it!
- H did ot drik!
- That's all you got to do.
Stop.
Oe perso talk at a time.
...to the hadicaps
as a gift for the seaso.
That's what happeed.
h was out o a midight ride...
h bought these plates!
That is my weddig dishes!
Roie. Those are my good dishes!
Now you doe it. Tammy!
A'ight. Tammy. Good!
- He should have his own show.
- Now, that I'd watch.
Come dow ad bail me out!
We'll see about that!
h'm goa be
i cell umber seve!
Come get me!
h'm comig i!
h kow it!
Tallyho, all!
Is this perchance
Tas-Tee Liquors?
I don't know, faggot!
I've been looking all day long.
What would you say if I told you
that I was looking for
a Ronwell Quincy Dobbs?
I'd say "Huh," too.
Perhaps he goes by
the appellation of Ronnie.
That fucker been lyin' to you!
He ain't from no Appalachia!
So you know him?
Hell, yeah!
Ronnie Dobbs!
Ronnie said he and Clay
was headed over to Duke's Last Call.
Just over the railroad tracks.
What great good luck!
Good shot!
Thank you!
Run on, fancy pants!
Get out of the way!
Back up! Get out of the way!
Damn that Ronnie Dobbs!
Ronnie Dobbs was here, yes?
- You a friend of Dobbs?
- I'd like to be, sir.
You tell that little asshole
next time he feels like pulling a prank
and lighting his shit on fire,
do it in somebody else's bar.
You hear that, Dobbs?
- The dance is ruined!
- Please. Damn that Dobbs.
That's the one.
Have you seen him?
Look out!
I'm the principal!
Let's get it, Ronnie!
- Kids, get home!
- Look out!
Get out of the way!
Run for your lives!
Magic!
Glorious!
This shit's gotta stop.
Run, Clay, run!
Thanks, chum!
Wait up, y'all!
Mr. Dobbs, slow down!
- I didn't do nothing!
- I'm not with the coppers!
- Please!
- You got the wrong man!
I'm here to proposition you!
- Get off me!
- Hear me out!
You ain't a cop!
My name is Terry,
and I'm from Hollywood.
Ronnie, you are not
like other men.
You've got something,
something special, and I want it badly.
I want to be the man
behind the man!
I realize I'm coming
all over you here,
but it's been building up
inside of me for weeks,
and I can't control myself.
Listen, sir, let me show you
what you've got inside of you,
what could be inside of you if you'd just
give me the tiniest hole of opportunity!
We can go back to your place
right now, and I'll pack your shit!
Help! Police!
Him!
- You two get down from there.
- He's the one you want!
- I'm coming!
- It's okay, officers!
Everything's fine!
I'm from Hollywood!
Wait. Hold on.
There's more.
I'll pay Mr. Dobbs' fine.
You release him to me.
No dice, precious.
What if I told you that I'd take him
out of this town, the county...
wait a second...
the entire state, for good?
For good?
He's yours.
But if he ever
shows up here again,
I'm gonna put him in jail
for the rest of his life.
And I ain't hardly bullshitting!
You understand me, boy?
You've got yourself a deal!
And I'll throw in
the fabulous Nickel Holder!
The problem with nickels is,
you're always losing them!
It holds one nickel!
Man, where you from, anyhow?
I'm from Britain.
There. My green card.
- Terry Twillstein?
- At your service.
What's all these?
Those are my babies.
That's the Salad Evaporator.
Sucks dressing off of salads.
No one bought it.
That's the Vomit Whip.
Turns vomit back into food!
And the Fish Magician hides fish.
No one bought it.
Man, look, what do you want
with me, anyway?
You're my latest product.
I'm gonna take you to Hollywood
and build a TV show around you
and your talents.
What talents?
For getting arrested.
- I don't want to get arrested.
- I know you don't.
That's why you run so fast
from the coppers
and you spin
such fabulous yarns.
My talents.
That's right!
All you'll have to do
is what you already do do.
I hope you don't mind
becoming rich and famous.
Hell no!
I could get into that, man.
You know, Ronnie,
you and I are a lot alike.
We both come
from a place where...
Shut the fuck up a second.
Pull in here.
- Something I want to get for the trip.
- Okay. Sure.
Just take a second, a'ight?
Just keep the car running, a'ight?
- Sure, Ronnie.
- Hey, Ronnie!
Hey, Clay!
Sorry about that bus flipping over.
Next time you gotta drive.
That's all right.
It was my fault.
Doesn't matter. Doesn't hurt anyway.
I can't feel my legs.
- You lucky.
- Rock on.
- A'ight.
- Hello.
- This here's a right nice car.
I'm a friend of Ronnie's,
so I'll just slip in the backseat.
No, that's not necessary.
License and registration, please.
- You're frightening me, hillbilly.
- Am I?
Listen, why don't you
get me in this golden chariot
and take me once
around the gas pumps?
Why don't you
go bother someone else?
- Just let me in there!
- No! Please, no!
Mercy sakes! You're not from around
these here parts, are you, fish 'n' chips?
- Dobbs!
- Run, Clay!
- Come back!
- Free six-pack!
Little dogies!
Get over here now!
A'ight, let's go.
Behind you!
- My bad.
- Just go.
Dobbs!
Goddamnit!
- You little son of a...
- Go, go, go, go!
Come back here!
Next stop, Hollywood.
Next stop, Hollywood!
Yeah, come here.
Sweet relief.
That's I Loathe L.A.
by Daffy Mal Yikle-Yakle.
a hilarious takeoff
o that other sog.
Come to Hummers i Redodo Beach
toight from 9:00 util 2:00.
Guys. Brig your boers.
'cause we're givig away tits!
It's a regular dream factory!
Well, wake up, Ronnie,
'cause it's all too real!
Now, let's get in there
and grab 'em by the nuts!
What?
Let's do what to who?
Okay. I'm holding
the deciding ballot.
Let's see who's voted out.
Bring me your torch.
Tough break, kid.
All right.
And now...
...we feast!
This show is killing us,
but we need one of these
reality-based shows to compete.
Absolutely, Bob.
Well?
Mr. Webber. Terry Twillstei
is here to see you.
Send them in.
Hello-hello!
My name's Terry Twillstein.
Hello, how are you?
That's a fine how-do-you-do.
I have a TV show that features
cops, mayhem, chases,
and roustabouts!
What do you think?
Sounds a lot like the show Fuzz.
Been there, done that.
You drive a hard bargain, sir.
What if I told you I'd take you
to a place you'd never been
and do something to you
that's never been done?
See, my show features
just one man, a single man,
getting arrested every week
in a different city.
That way people could feel for him
and grow to love him,
and he could be a hero,
a man of the people,
a common man with a silver tongue
and wings on his feet.
I'm talking about Ronnie Dobbs.
Don't mind if I do.
Well...
My immediate reaction is no,
but I've got kind of
a "yessy" aftertaste.
Part of me loves it,
and then this other part of me
hates the first part for loving it,
'cause the second part hates it.
Fran?
I'm forgainst it.
Well, I gotta say, I love it.
Really?
Well, it looks to me like
you've got yourself a show!
Congratulations!
- Twillstein, right?
- Yeah.
That Terry fellow.
he mastermided the whole thig
like some geius Eistei from hell
meets the Wolf Ma o steroids.
Then Ronnie gets arrested.
Get him in the car,
get the car pulling away.
Boom! Magic! Perfect!
That was it.
Roie was off ad ruig...
but ot too fast.
or there would't be o show!
Good dog!
May h have oe secod to pet the dog
ad let him kow h'm friedly?
h mea you o harm. Dog!
Look at me!
h'm like a astroaut!
h wat my right to remai silet!
This goat ate my shoes
ad my shit ad my hat...
...ad my wallet ad my rig.
- Put the goat dow.
You put the goat dow!
Arrest this goat!
Arrest him!
Liste here.
You thik people liked it?
Run, Ronnie, run!
Hell. Yes. They liked it.
ad if they paid attetio.
they just might lear
a thig or two.
You come down from there!
h'm the oe who called.
He's right over here.
We're checkig out
a possible B & E at A"s Auto Shop.
There he is. Right there.
h do't kow what to tell y'all.
This crazy druk maiac
comes ruig i here...
h have a complait to make.
h wat to register a reward for me
because this ma
was impersoatig Elvis.
ad h stopped him.
Officer. He took my hair.
h've got a show to do toight.
h took Elvis' hair.
h'm goa go retur it to him.
He hit me!
Fake Elvis has bee perpetratig
a crime agaist a true America hero!
h do't eed this. Officer.
h got three kids.
h do't eed maiacs i my sho...
What happeed?
Ma. H was hagig out here.
ad this crazy. Druk mothefucker
came ruig up ad...
There he goes. Officers!
There he goes!
Look at him!
There's the perpetrator! 10-20!
Police depatmet.
Stay back.
Not too close.
- You see aybody i here?
- Wet through there.
Here he is.
What are you doig i here?
Look at Daddy!
Do you live here?
Yeah. H lived here first.
ad the these people
built a house aroud me
ad did't eve check with me.
You thik Tammy did't otice?
hs that what you thik?
Liste. Thik agai.
ad thik right this time. Will ya?
Ca't a ma sleep
i his cabiet?
Y'all got baaa o me!
Y'all got the wrong man.
Okay, listen up.
I was just stealing myself, okay?
h siged a cotract
with the devil at a restaurat.
h have the cotract.
ad the devil...
The devil took my soul!
Dude. We got this off the devil!
The devi"s loose
amogst me i New York City!
Begoe. Sata!
No. You got the wrog ma!
Have you had
somethig to drik toight?
- Drik?
- Yeah. Alcohol.
h ai't... up.
h was o my way to get... up.
but you... that up.
Cogratulatios to you.
That's four bleeps, man.
Let's do it!
Drink, drink, drink, drink!
h do't speak Frech!
Fuck!
Speak Eglish.
mothefucker! Come o!
You are uder arrest.
Shut up!
Okay.
h uderstood that oe.
h'm beig chaied!
h am a chaied ma!
Boy. Did it take off.
quicker tha Roie could cout to 20.
h'm kig of Alaska Moutai!
He was the ew price
of Hollywood...
Hollywood. Califoria. That is.
Take a look around, Ronnie.
It's all yours.
Terry, I don't believe it.
Man...
If six months ago you would have said
that someday l, Ronnie Dobbs,
would be eating
the world's biggest hotdog,
I wouldn't have believed a goddamned
word out of your lying mouth.
Only in Hollywood!
That's not all. I have another surprise
for you, and you're gonna love it.
There's a bigger hotdog?
It's much better than that!
Here we are, Ronnie!
Hell.
I don't like museums.
No, it's a house.
It's your house.
It's glorious,
like an angel-sparkling loogie!
- Damn!
- What is it?
I like it and all, Terry, but it's gonna take
an awful long time to fuck it up.
I did foresee that eventuality.
You won't be alone.
Kyle, Tonya!
Fucked-up dog!
Hey, man!
All right!
Hey, Clay.
Man, I'm sorry about...
That's all right, Ronnie.
It's kind of my fault anyway.
Good part is, I don't have
no feeling below my chin.
All right!
Let's have us
a champagne jam!
What are you doing,
you drunken cripple?
Ronnie!
You're fabulous, man!
I love your stuff, Ronnie.
Welcome to the club.
- Showbiz forever!
- Forever!
Here's to you.
Come on, dog,
eat that vomit.
Eat it! Lick it!
There he goes!
Look at him!
Lick it up.
Good for his coat.
- John Stamos.
- I'm Rebecca.
Give him a kiss.
Give him a good one.
That's Ronnie Dobbs.
Give him a little tongue.
Okay!
You've got to come over
and rob us sometime.
- Will do, will do.
- We won't even call the police.
- Nice mullet.
- Colin, man, what's up?
Hey, buddy!
Like always, man.
Thank you very much.
Anytime.
Yo, Ronnie.
- Okay. A'ight, man.
- You look in good shape, huh?
Ronnie Dobbs!
What's up?
Why weren't you at my party?
That's okay. I'm gonna have
another one tonight... in my pants.
- I'm just kidding!
- A'ight.
- Am I? Of course I am...
- Okay.
...not.
- Big fan, big fan!
- A'ight, man.
Ronnie Dobbs,
you are brilliant!
- You have to do me a favor.
- At your service.
Tell me to fuck off!
Come on!
It's her birthday!
A'ight.
Fuck you, bitch!
Oh, my God.
In fact, fuck all y'all!
Man, like that?
Check this out!
That one was for next year.
Happy birthday.
Ronnie, there you are.
Come along.
Birthday girl,
you need a spanking.
Someone very special
came here just to see you.
His name's Chow-Chow,
and he's here on behalf
of the Make-Your-Last-Wish
Foundation.
Picture.
Peyton!
Chow-Chow, what's up?
- I'm sad.
- Why's that?
The doctor says I need
special shoes for my fat feet
so I can be like a normal kid
and run and play!
Kiddo, no more tears,
'cause Uncle Ronnie Dobbs is here.
Tell you what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna go out in this world
and get everything I can get.
I'm gonna be rich, super rich.
I'm gonna be spending money
like a chimp in a beat-off contest.
Yeah?
- Don't interrupt me, now.
- So sorry.
Then I'm gonna get
1,000 pair of special shoes,
put 'em in a big o" pile,
and just burn 'em all!
- Mr. Ronnie!
- Don't interrupt me!
- I done told you once.
- So sorry. No interrupt.
I'm gonna get
a diamond crystal speedboat,
and I'm gonna paint it gold,
and I'm gonna get so much pussy.
But I ain't gonna leave you out.
You gonna get some.
I'll get you laid.
What kind you like?
That's a tough one.
Don't answer yet.
Save it. Okay.
Then I'm gonna find the dude
what makes special shoes
and pay him ot to make
special shoes!
How about that?
Damn, look at them!
...I drew an arrow up
to where my bedroom's at.
- Ronnie Dobbs.
- Yeah.
- Scott Thompson.
- Okay.
Man, I love your work!
Is it real, though?
Do you really get arrested?
Hell, yeah, bitch!
This music is awful.
Mind if I raid your CD cabinet?
Raid my...
No, man.
You want to...
no, man.
My CD cabinet is "exit only."
Thought you was gonna try
to turn me gay when I wasn't looking?
I know all about y'al"s
gay conspiracy agenda.
- Please!
- Nice try.
Lucky Pierre, this is Ramrod.
We have a breach of security.
He kows everythig.
Code red.
h repeat... code red!
We just received
our numbers from overseas.
Combined with our efforts here,
everything is proceeding
precisely according to plan...
gay bars are up,
straight men are experimenting,
the priesthood
is still our number one...
What?
We got a leak.
What?!
We're gonna have to shut down
this entire worldwide
multibillion-dollar gay conspiracy.
What about the gay-dar machine?
- And the $3 bill?
- What about the skin flute?
Sorry, ladies.
It's over.
Tell our source to get
back into the closet, pronto.
- Damn it!
- Ramrod. Code blue.
Get back i the closet.
Repeat... code...
Ladies!
You both have beautiful posture.
Could I get you a drink?
What's up, Ronnie?
Damn!
It's the cardboard beer girl!
My name is Kayla.
I am so excited to meet you.
I am such a huge fan of yours.
My agent's been telling me
how hot you are... and I agree.
I'm hot... hot for you,
if you know what I mean.
I know what you mean.
Tell me, is that a beer in your pocket,
or are you just happy to see me?
No, I ain't got no beer.
No, that's a hard-on.
That's 'cause of you.
You gave that to me.
Well, maybe your big dog
could train my naughty pussycat.
Well, I ain't into pets
or nothing, so, nah.
But I got a better idea.
How's about Dr. Ronnie
takes this here hard-on
and writes you a prescription
for a hot beef injection?
Maybe it's time
you showed me your bedroom.
I could do that,
but I got a better idea.
How's about you and I go fu...
Well, Ronnie,
you've bedded your dream girl.
What is it?
I don't know.
Terry, man, it's weird.
She's hot and all,
you know, but it's weird.
When I'm making
the sweetest of loves to her...
doing it for real, you know?
I'm loving on her, and I'm pulling out
in time and everything,
and it's just like...
I don't know.
I can't help but think of Tammy.
Maybe I should see
a doctor or something.
I'll give you a diagnosis for free.
You're in love.
Since we're pouring
our hearts out to each other,
I've got a little secret to share,
something I've never shared
with anyone before.
My accent...
...it isn't real.
You ain't from England?
No, I'm from England,
but I was born
without an accent.
That's cool.
I wonder if Tammy
would take me back.
Man, get me a bus ticket
back home tomorrow.
No, sir!
You have a TV show to do.
I'm gonna go back home.
You're not going anywhere,
but I'll tell you what I will do.
I'll get Tammy a bus ticket
to come out here!
When she sees
what you've done... the house,
the monster truck
in the garage, the beer girl...
I mean, it'll only make her jealous,
and that's the number one
motivation for women.
Right.
Right, man.
Jealousy.
That's like women's kryptonite.
Anybody home?
Echaté.
Ma chérie has arrived,
and your knight in finery awaits.
Ronnie, this place is amazing.
Yes, my dear, and it is
a mere pittance of my vast estate,
some of which
you can't even see.
I got a bank account now,
and I'm wearing socks.
Behold, glorious gifts
from God and above...
a toilet paper rosette
for a true lady of the evening,
and an Italian cottage
made of international cheeses.
You can eat the whole thing,
except for the bottom. That's cardboard.
I almost forgot.
Let me introduce to you
my secret weapon.
Who's she?
Only the girl I been fucking.
Jealous much?
Way to go, bitch.
You fucked up.
Hey, bro.
You look like you could use something
to make you feel a whole lot better.
Come inside, man.
It's okay.
Ad ewly elected goveror
Hark Trellis
is makig atioal ews
with a record umber of executios
i the state of Georgia.
So far. 35 thrilled prisoers...
Sorry. The word is "doomed. "
Make that doomed prisoers
excitedly skipped towards death row.
No. They did't.
They were led.
What the hell are we paying
Malaysians 35 cents a T-shirt for
when we can get them
from Tai-fucking-wan for 22 cents?!
Time magazine is accusing you
of exploiting Ronnie!
Great! More publicity
for my musical!
Come on!
I want to hear this!
No, no, no!
That was shite, pure shite!
- I don't disagree.
- Really?
I think it's ridiculous like this.
It's like a lie, and we've spent
the whole play getting to this point.
We've unpeeled the onion.
He should be naked.
It's a naked,
beautiful moment.
Let's try it your way.
- Please.
- Mr. Twillstein.
- It's about Ronnie.
- What about Ronnie?
He can't get arrested.
Get me on the next flight out.
My golden goose.
Okay, take it from the beginning.
It's hard to say what you want
without putting up
those old masks
of "I'm not good enough,"
or "I couldn't possibly obtain this."
Complete this sentence...
"I want...
In my fondest moments
of wantonness, I want..."
Mary Lynn.
What does Mary Lynn want?
I want a magenta horse.
And I want to fly away with it
into a reddish background,
and I want pixies.
I want pixies!
Good.
Those are all doable.
Jim. What does Jim want?
I want to write a hemp cookbook
using hemp ink,
and I want to build houses
out of hemp for the homeless,
and I want to make clothes
out of hemp for the world,
and I just...
It's okay. I know it's hard, Jim.
Say it. You're among friends.
I want to smoke
some of the hemp.
Just a little. Just...
...a little.
Good.
Getting more honest.
Yeah.
Jeff Goldblum.
What does
Jeff Goldblum want?
I want my money back.
And I want angels
to give it to me.
And pixies
to count it out for me,
and a gnome or a hobbit
or an elf to sleep
at the foot of my bed,
and have... I just want them
all over my backyard.
No matter what happens with any
of that, I do want my money back.
Ronnie Dobbs.
Our newest recruit.
Thank you, Greg.
What does Ronnie want?
I think I got it.
I want to love people,
and I want people
to love on me.
And I want...
...pecan pie.
I want angels
to make me that pie.
to make me that pie so good!
And I want whipped cream
and strawberries on top!
I'll tell you what h want.
Terry! I thought
you was in New York.
A lot of people
think a lot of things about New York.
- I want...
- He didn't pay.
It's $1,500
to say what you want.
Stuff it!
I want the old Ronnie back!
Tonya and Kyle told me
you've become a vegetarian,
and you haven't
drank with them in weeks.
Hey, Tonya, Kyle,
fucked-up dog.
Hey, Clay.
Sorry 'bout that spinal thing.
ht's okay. Roie.
h was druk. Too.
Have you read
these letters I'm getting?
"Dear Ronnie,
my name is Maurice.
"I am eight years old.
I am your biggest fan.
"How come you are
not so drunk anymore?
"My daddy says you were never
really drunk, just a Hollywood phony!
I told him he was wrong.
He beat the shit out of me."
I've got sacks of these
back at my office!
Terry, man, it's hard!
You don't know what it's like
being a superstar!
You get all these people going,
"What can I do for you, Mr. Dobbs?"
You've got to think of things
they've got to do.
You just don't know.
It's hard.
Here. Have a drink.
- It's no fun anymore.
- I know, I know.
Take a break, there.
Everybody's giving you free...
A little bit more.
Drink, drink, drink.
I got my beer goggles on now!
That's right!
I'm starting to see clearly.
This does smell like bullshit.
Y'all get out of my house.
Get on out of here!
Freaky new wave hippie!
Get out of here, blondie!
You, too, Jeff Goldenstein!
Go on! Get going!
Yeah! 'cause old
Ronnie Dobbs is back!
Oh, Ronnie,
I love you!
Hello.
It's me again.
The scene you were
about to see has been cut
so the film you're watching could obtain
the rating mandated by the studio.
It's a shame, as it was a beautifully shot
and poignant scene of love...
a thing of the past, I suppose.
Many famous films
have had scenes cut
to reach a specified audience.
Here's a scene cut
from a popular children's film.
A kick in the cunt?
I'm sorry. That was
an inappropriate scene to show here,
as it was cut for time,
not content.
Let's rejoin the film
you've been watching.
Roie retured
to his hometow a hero.
Come on, Ronnie,
aren't you excited?
I guess.
I was just kind of expecting Tammy
to come down and see me, that's all.
Thank you.
A'ight, come on, now.
I'd like to thank Mr. Dobbs
for farting the alphabet.
He's definitely a man
of many talents.
Now, here of course...
Okay, P.S.
I just want to say, okay,
some of y'all think
that I don't deserve a second chance,
and I swear,
if I were to get a second chance
or even a fourth chance,
I would make a good husband
to these people.
That's God's honest truth.
Baby, you see me farting?
Arrest this piece of shit, boys.
What the hell?
You're going down
for good this time.
He didn't do nothing.
That's really true this time.
It's my new policy, a little thing
I like to call "no strikes and you're out."
You can't do that!
Governor, please,
Ronnie's a celebrity now.
Don't you make
an exception for them?
We had a deal, Twillstein.
I want to file a reward!
Make a hole.
Y'all seen that! Do something!
Don't just stand there!
Man, what's up?
I can't hear you.
Yes, Ronnie. The phone.
Pick up the phone.
The phone!
Pick up the phone!
Hang on.
Yeah-lo?
Ronnie, it's Terry.
Hang on.
He's right here.
Man, it's for you.
No.
No, it's me on the phone.
I'm on the phone!
Okay.
It looks like he's on another call.
Can you call back?
Ronnie, it's me, Terry,
speaking to you via the telephone.
Oh, man!
Okay, I got it now.
Man, how are you?
You know you've got a phone call?
Yes, I realize that.
Ronnie, how are you?
I'm good.
I can't complain, man.
Check out the threads. Free.
You know, Ronnie,
this is all my fault.
I was so busy
exploiting you that...
Yeah. Hang on.
That's cool.
They asked me if I wanted
to get electrocuted or injected.
I was like,
"Wait a minute.
"What say I jump out
of an airplane what's on fire,
"no parachute,
but straight into a shark tank
filled with poisonous razorblades?"
That's crazy talk!
You're not jumping
out of any fiery airplane
into a shark tank of razors!
I know.
They said I had to get electrocuted.
What are you talking about?
I'm on death row.
Didn't you hear?
Part of the governor's
new Get-Tough campaign.
He's finally cleaning this state up.
That can't be.
They gonna kill me tomorrow.
Let's go, Dobbs.
I'll see you in hell, Terry.
Do something real bad
so I can see you in hell, okay?
Ronnie Dobbs.
Naive bumpkin.
What'd you call me?
Sack of manure for brains.
We regrettably
iterrupt Fishin' with Guns
with this special ews bulleti.
Good eveig.
We have cofirmed repots
that the so of goveror Hark Trellis
has bee kidapped.
The kidappers have demaded
the immediate turover...
- Inbred baboon.
- Of TVsuperstar Roie Dobbs.
We ow go live...
- That's it!
- Shut up, you illiterate butterbean!
Get him out of here!
Out the door, through the window!
Unhand me, hairy hillfolk.
I'm trying to watch this!
The lucky boy...
sorry. The ulucky boy...
is beig held hostage
by approximately four getleme.
Gentlemen?!
No! Try "terrorists"!
Stupid tongue. Sorry.
Four terrorists
who are demanding the release
of a prisoner named Ronnie Dobbs
from Georgia's death row,
a swank, luxurious
place of enchantment...
What did I just say?
This tongue of mine,
it's all twisted up!
...make a deal.
You hear me?
We will make a deal.
Real simple.
There's o eed for violece.
I want you to stay calm.
This can be worked out.
All right in there, listen up.
This is the governor talking to you.
I heard your demands.
Now I want to tell you
my demands.
Let my son go
and shoot yourselves in the head!
How's that sit with you?
I didn't get a nickname like "Get Tough"
by caring about my son!
- Give me that.
- Twillstein!
Don't listen to him!
He's not on your side!
You can do
whatever you can dream!
Twillstein!
Get him!
We ain't makin'
no deals here, pal.
I'm not with the bobbies.
No, I've come here to assist you.
Look, I realize
that you're fans of Ronnie's,
and you want to get him out and get
an autograph and maybe a photo,
but when you're done,
I'll take him.
You ain't taking him nowhere!
He's staying right here.
We got special plans for Dobbs.
That's wonderful.
What could they be?
We're gonna kill
the son of a bitch!
Kill Ronnie?
Why would you want
to do that?
You're from
that Elimiatio program.
You got that right.
We was shittin' in high cotton.
We had the number one show,
then when Dobbs showed up,
network pulled the plug
on our show!
Yeah!
They forgot all about us!
Hell, they left us out there
on that goddamned island to die!
We had to make a goddamned canoe
out of the fat guy!
But he's on death row.
Isn't that enough?
No, that ain't enough!
We gonna kill him our way!
And then we're gonna eat him.
What in the hell do you think
I'm talking about here, pinhead?
Man, this is hard.
You live your whole life,
you think you've got it all worked out,
and then comes
the toughest choice of all.
I hope I'm doing the right thing.
Dobbs, you got more visitors.
Hey, little beans!
Gonna give you a few minutes
to say good-bye.
Right on!
Look at y'all.
You guys run along
and let me talk to Daddy, okay?
Sorry.
Do those hurt?
They a'ight.
Tammy, I love you so much.
I mean...
You're the only one I ever loved.
I don't know what happened.
Ronwell...
sometimes God shines
His magic light beam from outer space,
and it works in mysterious ways.
I may not always know
what He's thinking,
but I know that inside,
you're a good man.
Oh, baby.
I wish I had a magic genie bottle.
I'd rub it so hard that genie'd be like,
"What the fuck you doin'?"
I'd be like,
"I need some wishes bad!"
That genie'd be like, "You keep rubbin'
my bottle-home so hard,
I'll give you a foot-shaped wish
up your ass," and I'll be like...
Okay, let's go.
Time's up.
Let's go.
What the hell?
Let's kill the kid ad the sissy.
I'm starvin'.
I'd like a snack, too.
Sorry we have to do this, kid...
...but your daddy,
he is one tough bastard.
Like father...
...like son.
Come on!
Hut!
Who's next?
Fat little prick!
United States Marine Corps taught me
how to kill a man in six seconds
before they kicked me out.
Let's get it on, sweetheart.
Son!
I got some demands of my own.
ht's cofirmed. Goveror's approved
the pardo of prisoer Dobbs.
10-4.
Open the perimeter gate.
Where are we going?
I didn't get my last meal!
What about my waffles?
I was supposed to have
a wonderful breakfast
of delicious waffles,
and I didn't get nothing,
not even a bowl
of good-bye mints!
What about my waffles?
You mind if I buy you
those waffles, stranger?
Nah, man, I ain't in...
Terry?
What are you doing
picking up guys out here?
I'm only here
to pick up one man.
Fuck that guy.
Give me a ride.
Come on, Ronnie.
Hollywood awaits.
Roie was i what the scholars
call a real shit pickle.
but we kow two heads
is always better tha oe.
so Roie. Tammy. Ad Terry
came up with somethig
that would make 'em all happy.
Look at me!
I'm on a river!
Riverdance!
This is the greatest day
in the moment of American history!
Ever!
I'm Ronnie Dobbs!
Catch the ring!
You catch the ring!
I'm not going, motherfucker!
We're trying to save your life!
That's it, chum!
Terry, did you see that?
I drove backwards
right off the thing, man!
It was awesome!
A druke Roie remaied
i the water for six hours
before a crew of Navy SEALs
forcibly rescued him.
We'll see that toight.
as well as Roie repellig rescuers
from a treacherous cliff top.
Brig o that "heliocopter. "
h do't eed you.
Get o out of here.
The later.
i a alpie skig tragedy.
Roie comes perilously close
to dyig of frostbite
ad humiliates a rescue team
with sowballs.
all toight o
Ronnie Dobbs Gets Rescued.
Cut!
Brilliant! That's a wrap!
You make Bob Stack
look like an amateur, Kent.
100!
Who likes cake?
Everybody.
Yes. That's right.
Where's Ronnie?
Looks like you got
your truck lowered.
Tammy, is that you?
You look glamorous!
I'm a regular
Hollywood trophy wife.
You are. Thank you
for loaning me your husband.
As long as he's not getting arrested,
it's okay by me.
I feel like I'm ready to party!
I got lungs of steel!
A'ight, Clay, I heard that!
Uncle! Uncle!
Hey, little dude.
You'll never guess.
I got my special shoes!
I don't give a goddamn.
Come on, Chow-Chow.
Come on, y'all,
let's have us a champagne jam!
Champagne!
Let's party, for real this time!
We're off, everybody.
Ronnie, you ain't got
a hair on your ass
if you don't give it some gas!
Look out.
Too fast, Uncle!
Uncle Ronnie, too fast!
Look out!
- That was a nasty right turn!
- You guys okay?
Y'all all right?
Uncle Ronnie,
you broke my special shoes!
Then he stole some tires.
He stole...
Shouldn't he be
coming up by now?
Go!
This goat ate my shoes
and my shirt and my wallet
and my diamond rings and...
Goddamnit!
Really? That's fabulous!
Where's that ambulance at?
Can't catch me!
Fuck! Jesus Christ!
Fuck! Troy!
She's a lying bitch, officer.
You can't trust a word she's saying.
Look at this stupid bitch!
Get her off of me!
She's an old lady!
What's wrong with you?
Let me go!
I want her fired.
I want her off the set.
It's called actig.
Well. There you have it...
the Ronnie Dobbs story.
from the bottom to the top
to the bottom and the back to the top.
Who wats to bet
the bottom's next?
What a story!
What about me?
Well. Iook at me.
h'm fien.
Now. That hit the spot.
Anyway. H do't blame Ronnie.
See. H was a little bit druk
my ow self.
Live ad lear. H guess.
h'm so tired.
but. Hell. H ca't go to sleep.
Well. H guess
h'll just tell the story again.
This here is the story
of one Rowell Dobbs...