Present
DARK BLUE WORLD
SubRip by divx.NeKryXe.com
Starring
Screenplay
Music by
Production designer
Make up
Costume
Sound designer
Editor
Director of photography
Co-producers
Produced by
Directed by
It won't take off, will it?
Don't worry,
not while I'm around.
Now what?
Take hold of the joystick.
- This thing here?
- See how it moves.
This is how we turn left,
and right...
Look at the wings.
This is how we dive.
And this...
What's it doing?
Hey! It's...
This is how we climb, Hanichka.
- Aren't we going too high?
- All the way
to heaven.
Slama,
is that all you've done today?
He's not well, Sir.
Come with me.
Sit down and write:
"Dear Family,
comma,
Do not send me any more food parcels
as I am not doing my job properly."
Sign it!
Sir, let him be.
He has a fever.
Mind your own business, Machaty!
Back to your place!
Franta...
Back to your places!
During World war II
hundreds of Czechoslovak pilots
fought with the British against the Nazis.
After the War the Communists seized
power in Czechoslovakia
and jailed the pilots who had
returned home.
They feared these heroes would
once again fight for freedom.
Mirov Prison, Czechoslovakia, 1950
What's your name?
Franta Slama.
Vilda Houf, sign painter.
In here for my appendix.
Look!
Locked up for stealing State property!
Some pots of paint.
Why are you here?
Pneumonia.
I mean, why did they lock you up?
I flew for the RAF. In England.
I see!
Let there be no mistake.
This is a forced-labour camp.
You are educated men
so you know what it means.
Our "amnesty" cart.
It has only one route -
to the cemetery and back.
The only amnesty
you're ever going to know...
Lie on your side.
Better than on your back.
- Did you see that?
- What?
- The tattoo on his arm.
- He's an SS man.
You're kidding!
They're in the kitchen too.
You're in here with SS men?
So are you.
But I didn't fight against them.
There you go.
I did.
Olomouc Airfield,
Czechoslovakia, 1939
You know how you fly,
Voytishek?
- A bit wild?
- No.
- Too much throttle?
I give up.
Like a natural.
Really?
Where's my dog?
Anyone seen my dog?
Shshe rrran tto the hhangar.
Of course, Gregora's stuffing her
with salami again.
Give me the hangar.
Line your pants gents.
Tomorrow you're flying solo.
- Hangar.
- You got my dog there?
- Yes, Sir.
- Put her on the phone.
What? On the phone?
That's what I said.
Take a look, gentlemen.
Barcha, come here!
She's on the line.
Barcha! Where
did I tell you to wait?
That's all,
gentlemen.
Dismissed.
The show's over.
Barcha... Good girl...
Ssh.
My Papa!
Barcha. Her Papa!
Silence! Adolf Hitler speaks.
You're the one
we've been waiting for, bastard!
Not you!
Germany has become
and always will remain Greater Germany.
This will be guaranteed by the
entire German people,
from East to West and now from the South
all the way here to Berlin, Heil!
Quiet!
- You know what my mother said?
- What?
I'll end up marrying Kanka.
That lollipop-man down there?
- He'll be completely bald soon.
- But he's set his sights on me.
And you think I haven't?
Quiet! My parents!
- Think they don't know?
- Know what?
- That we're in love.
- Of course they know,
but not that
I let you love me so... deeply!
What's that?
- That's him.
- Who?
Kanka, of course.
He serenades me every night
to touch my heart.
Hanichka.
I'm coming, Papa.
Just a minute!
Hanichka, please open the door!
Papa...
- Good evening.
- Captain!!
Mr. Pechar, let me explain...
They're repeating it over and over.
At six a.m. On March fifteenth
the Armed Forces of the German Reich
will begin occupying our country.
Any resistance will be met
with brutal retaliation.
I'm sorry.
Cry all you want. Who wouldn't?
All units will be disarmed.
No aircraft, military or civilian,
are to leave their bases.
Turn it off!
Cut the engine!
I'm taking it to Poland.
We can't let them have it!
Pilot Officer,
switch off your engine now!
Didn't you hear the order?
Yes, but I didn't like it.
Nobody's asked your opinion.
Get out!
Why d'you think the others
aren't taking off?
Because it's suicide
in this weather!
You'll crash into the first hill!
I know.
Everything
is conspiring against us.
England, France, the weather,
even my back,
everything.
We should tell our men
the Poles will need pilots,
ground crews too,
because Poland is next in line.
Nothing official.
Volunteers.
Preferably,
single men.
They're here.
Slama, please take over.
I can't move.
Let's call it an order.
Yes Sir.
Good morning gentlemen.
Ober-Lieutenant Hesse!
It's my duty
to take over this airfield.
Our commanding officer,
Wing-Commander Skokan
is physically indisposed.
I'm in charge.
Lieutenant Slama.
This whole army seems
"physically indisposed".
What a lovely map!
So, yesterday we were here.
We had a good look
at your famous defences.
Abandoned without a shot?
As a soldier, I can't understand it.
Sir, kindly do your duty
and respect the honour of soldiers
who have been forced to do theirs.
Keep your shirt on.
Just a little joke.
Now, I'd like to see the planes.
Gentlemen!
The keys, please.
All right boys, let's go.
I can imagine how you must feel.
A German officer would put
a bullet in his head.
But you are...
a little different,
aren't you?
Pilot Officer Voytishek!
I've got a spare seat.
Thank you,
but I'll stick with the boys.
You're taking it too personally.
How else! I felt like throwing up
in the hangar.
We carried out an order.
Now we can go home,
take off our uniforms,
and take it personally.
How long will it take you to pack?
Me?
No time at all.
Don't forget to brush out her ears.
Thistles get stuck in there.
She'll be grateful.
And in winter ice forms
on these hairs between her pads.
They hurt her,
so you have to cut them out.
But I'll be back well before then.
She'll listen to me?
Of course.
She knows you're a part of me.
What's this?
In case you come back at night
and the house is locked.
Thank you.
You don't have any documents on
you? In case we're searched?
No, Mr Slama.
Good.
And call me Franta.
And you can call me Karel.
I know.
I don't know how to put it...
Sir, I mean Franta...
but I do have some documents
I'd like to take with me.
What are they?
No, forget it, I'll get rid of them.
You'd only laugh at me.
No, I won't. Promise.
Let's see them.
Horses?
That's only camouflage.
There's worse.
She's my only girl.
I'd rather not part with her.
Your only girl?
- Then you should keep her.
- Thanks.
Sir,
I mean Franta! Look!
Oh God!
Barcha, you mustn't do this.
Go home.
Go home!
Back to Hanichka.
Go or I'll hit you!
What's she doing?
She keeps turning around
but she is going back.
England, 1940
I can't see shit.
Shut up!
We're pedalling like maniacs.
This is stupid. I'm knackered!
- Bbehind yyou!
- Break left!
You bastards.
Why don't you let us fly!
- What's he saying?
- Get up. We're doing it again.
No! To hell with this!
It's not what I came here for!
On your bikes!
Out of my way.
What'd he say?
He says you're Myrtvy.
Thanks.
Mmay I kkeep her?
One week.
It means le... lend, stupid.
Shut it!
Open your mouth wider!
No language! Just madness.
Stop fooling about, Karel.
Ladies!
Excuse me,
a fortnight without
just isn't healthy.
A little well
in an open field...
I'm trying to do your mmouth,
so shut it!
Why ddon't we go
to the bbeach sometime.
- I've nnever sswum in the sea.
- It's freezing.
Just to dip our tttoes.
Hey. Look!
What d'you think he's saying?
He's trying to land them.
- I'd just get a slap in the face.
- You mustn't frighten them.
Machaty begins by asking the way.
Say, to the Officers' Mess.
But doesn't he know
where it is?
It's a device.
Women like to help you
when you're in trouble when...
they don't feel threatened.
It's how you break the ice.
Did Machaty tell you that?
It's common knowledge.
Great!
I guess English
is important after all.
There's no resemblance.
You jjust shut up Deadman.
Wwith your nname
you don't bbelong in a plane
bbut a ccoffin.
This supposed to be me?
Yes, I'd like you to have it.
Grinning like an idiot for this!
It's only good to scare kids!
What did he say?
Monkey catching.
Us? Makes sense. We've done
just about everything else.
Lift up your shirt.
Were you in France,
when we invaded?
- Yes.
- And what did you think?
- How you moved! Breathtaking.
- Don't breathe.
Blitzkrieg.
A short and sweet war.
Take a deep breath.
It was hard to be a German
and not be proud.
You can breathe now.
The English returned
from their missions
with empty magazines,
and all we could do was
circle the airfield, target-shooting.
Three months later...
Llend me another to do the ttits.
This one?
No, I need her.
A little well, made of stone,
in an open field stands alone...
And its water is...
That's us you idiots!
Finally!
Show yourselves, bastards!
Tthere they are! Two o'clock low!
Oh shit!
Boys, don't jump the gun.
Fire only when they're
squarely in your sights.
Shit!
Boys! Messerschmitts!
A whole swarm of them!
Tom Tom, on your tail!
I can see him.
But he's glued to my arse.
Boys, notice how I don't stutter
when I'm shit-scared?
Tom Tom can't bail out!
- Two, Roger.
- Three, Roger.
Move yourself, bastard!
Blue two! Dive to sea level!
I can't hear you.
Dive to sea level.
Too little fuel to follow you!
What?
Bedrich, we're not fighting
anymore, it's beddy-byes now.
The Germans are also beddy-byes,
they've stopped firing.
Even Hitler is beddy-byes
with Eva Braun.
Lying on your heart is no good,
it can give you nightmares.
Look at Sysel,
sleeping nicely on his back.
Good old Moravian pig...
- We have different things in mind.
- What do you mean?
I want... you know what...
and she just wants to teach me
English.
She says after the war... for the
other.
The one next to her doesn't look
as if she'd need to wait for peace.
She's more than I could handle.
- And her?
- She's Machaty's.
She's your date?
You said it!
It's amazing...
how calm they are.
And that'll be Hitler's downfall.
Because he's a hot-head
like our Voytishek.
Me a hot-head?
Just you wait!
You know what's crossed my mind?
What?
Maybe I'm not handling her right.
We go for long walks.
She doesn't stop talking.
Of course we kiss but...
D'you think she expects me
to pounce on her?
I wouldn't know,
but shut up for now, okay?
But think about it, will you?
Sure.
- Franta!
- What?
I see him.
One o'clock.
Hugging the ground.
He's yours, Karel.
I'm going in.
Franta, I'm hit!
Can you hear me?
Karel!
Oh God!
Out of the way!
I'll start her up.
Are you alright?
- In hospital?
- Stitched up his stomach.
Who's that?
Sysel. He was holding his guts.
It was oozing blood.
He'll be there for a week at least.
You land on your head
when you bailed out yesterday?
Not on my head,
on a woman!
And I fell madly in love with her.
I'm crazy about her.
Really?
I'm going mad.
One could...
One could escape from here.
I'd like to know how.
You see that barbed wire over
there?
If one got hold of a pair of pliers...
The wall's only five metres.
Gentlemen.
It's my birthday today.
- Fifty.
- Your health, doctor!
My father died at fifty.
Also a doctor.
In Reichenberg.
You know how many people
came to his funeral?
A hundred and twenty-seven.
My sister counted them all.
They loved him so.
That's life...
How many people did you kill
in the war, Mr. Slama?
No idea.
Take a guess.
Maybe ten.
Me, not one.
Have you ever seen an execution?
I did.
In Prague. At Kobylisy.
I had to check that
the people were dead.
For a whole month.
Day in day out.
- How do I look?
- Ravishing.
Really?
You're pulling my leg?
Get out, you Romeo.
Wait here. I'll give you a sign.
Lovely, isn't she?
I prefer bigger tits, but she is pretty.
How do you say "vinegar" in
English?