Please come closer.
Have a seat.
Tell me, what makes you think you
are so qualified for this assignment?
My previous occupation
was captain of the Galactic Alliance.
But after my last mission,
I was retired.
You let Experiment 626 escape.
It wasn't my fault.
The little trog...
Calm down.
This job has absolutely nothing
to do with 626.
I know what the job is about.
And I believe I know the location
of the item you seek.
Where is it?
A tiny planet in Gamma Quadrant.
They call it Earth.
Let's go!
Nani.
You need some help?
Let me give you a hand.
- Where's Lilo?
- She's not with you?
Look! A parking space.
Ridiculous Earth vehicle.
Needs evil-genius tune-up.
I am thrilled.
My very first day at an Earth beach.
I've been studying
mingling with locals. Hang loose.
Whatever.
Are you sure your one-piece
bathing suit is from proper century?
Absolutely.
Put on your hat.
Have you two seen Lilo?
We thought little girl was with you.
Today, you take your rightful place
as part of the Hawaiian community.
Are you ready?
How's that?
Nice skirt.
But you don't need to dress up.
Just be yourself.
Hi.
Maybe not that much yourself.
Now, remember, in Hawaii,
everybody calls each other cousin.
Not because we're all related,
but because we're one big ohana.
One happy family.
It'll be fine.
Just say, "Aloha, cousin."
Go on.
Aloha, cousin.
I got it!
Smells good.
Who wants to slice the pineapple?
Oh, no.
Not good.
That's my chain saw.
That blue dude, he's totally freaky.
I told Lilo no pets.
Hi.
Hello.
I brought ice cream.
It wasn't that bad.
After you left,
I got to help put out the fire.
No cousins.
You're a part of our ohana now.
But getting everybody else
to like you is harder.
Trust me. I know.
- I'm freaky.
- You're different.
You're one of a kind,
like Frankenstein.
Sure you can watch Lilo
for a couple of hours?
You two go. Have a good time.
Everything here
is completely under control.
I'm even fixing
my very first Earth dinner.
You're fixing dog food.
I know. It makes its own gravy.
Here. Why don't you take this?
- Leafy greens?
- No. It's money. For pizza.
- They deliver.
- Really? Fascinating.
Don't worry. They'll be fine.
Yeah. I guess they're OK.
But I think
Pleakley tries on my clothes.
"Insert tab A into chromosome B."
- Jumba?
- Spies!
626. What do you want?
I'm busy doing genius work.
No cousins? Well, of course not.
We are each one of a kind, you and I.
Evil genius scientist
and evil genius creation,
all alone in infinite universe.
You have maybe found
tiny adopted Earth family,
but we have no, as you say, cousins.
What is this?
Must be the pizza. I'll get it!
Gantu!
He's come back for Stitch.
Hurry! We can sneak out the back.
- Jumba, where are you going?
- I have to take care of things.
What is that?
What is what?
You can't have Stitch, you big dummy.
I'm not fat, and I'm not here
for the failed Experiment 626.
- Stitch!
- Where's Jumba?
- Take this and hide.
- No!
This is something evil and bad.
- Take it.
- No.
- Evil.
- Take it.
- No!
- Bad. No!
- Take it.
- Evil. No!
- Bad.
Very funny.
Not to make a peep,
my little one-eyed one,
or entire galaxy is doomed.
How am I supposed to breathe?
Jumba Jookiba.
Gantu. No see long time.
- Where are they?
- They? Who they?
The other 625 experiments.
You must have me confused
with other evil-genius scientist.
What have we here?
Is ping-pong ball.
Is Earth sport.
Like tennis, but tinier.
You're a bad liar, Jumba.
Where are the other experiment pods?
I never discuss scientific research
with big dummies.
Then perhaps you'll discuss it with
your former partner, Dr Hämsterviel.
Hämsterviel is alive?
And he wants his experiments back.
Jumba? Help.
He's taking Jumba!
No!
Jumba!
What are we gonna do?
Where are you going?
Wait up!
Jumba and Pleakley's ship.
Don't we need the keys?
Thanks for the...
Well, I guess it was a date.
- Was it?
- We split the bill.
Yeah, but I paid the tip.
David,
I'm not ready for a real date yet.
Things are still
kind of lolo around here.
- Come on. How bad can it be?
- Oh, no.
Lilo?
Anybody here?
No sign of her.
Or Stitch. Or those other two.
Stay here
in case anybody comes back.
I'll go into town to look.
I'm sure it's OK. She's probably
hanging out with her new friends.
- Do it again.
- Jumba.
Computer,
lock hyperdrive coordinates...
626, please to be sharper
with the shooting.
Right up his afterburner!
- Damage?
- Engine one, 75 percent capacity.
50 percent capacity.
You had coffee today, didn't you?
Coconut cake and coffee.
Activate boosters.
That way!
Reroute engine power to rear.
Lock on target.
- Target locked.
- Fire.
Good steering.
We're losing all our power!
My turn this time.
Hyperdrive activated.
Jumba?
I think we're out of gas.
This is an emergency announcement.
Aliens from outer space
have invaded Earth
and are kidnapping our most brilliant
scientists for unknown purposes.
Lilo.
I knew you were OK.
You're missing our favourite movie.
Does Nani know
I was out past my bedtime?
Yeah. She's out looking for you.
Jumba was kidnapped by Gantu.
- The big dummy?
- Yep.
You and Stitch can handle him.
Where did Stitch go?
Stitch?
Pleakley.
Gosh. Oh, my.
Breathing first, talking second.
I'm ready now.
Jumba! Gantu kidnapped Jumba!
- I know.
- He was after this.
Container ready. Select experiment.
What is it?
It's some of Jumba's evil science.
Look at that.
It's more illegal
genetic experiments.
You mean
there are more besides Stitch?
Well, Stitch is number 626.
These must be the other 625.
They don't look like him.
They've obviously
been dehydrated for transport.
How do they work?
Well, I'm no evil genius,
but I'd say
if any of these pods get wet,
they would rehydrate into one of
the 625 prototype Stitch experiments.
Each with its own unique
and highly destructive capability.
But I'm just guessing.
With more Stitches,
I bet we could rescue Jumba.
We could activate one
and go back into space...
Hold it! Hold everything.
These experiments are highly unstable
and very dangerous.
We're gonna keep these locked up...
...safe and dry.
And as for you two,
you must never, repeat, never,
open that container.
If those pods got wet,
it could create mass mayhem
and planet-wide panic.
- Got it?
- Got it.
David, I looked everywhere.
Have you heard anything?
They're fine.
They're playing upstairs.
I'm gonna get you a cellphone.
Lilo!
Thank goodness you're OK.
Stop it! You're hugging me to death.
Where were you? What happened?
Well, Captain Gantu came back
and kidnapped Jumba.
Me and Stitch hot-wired the spaceship
and chased him into outer space,
which was really cool.
- But then...
- Wait.
While David and I went to dinner,
you went to outer space?
- I'm not finished.
- Sorry.
So Gantu got away
and we ran out of power.
And then Stitch saved the ship,
and then we came home, and then
you came home and tried to hug me.
Now I'm finished.
I thought you said
I had nothing to worry about.
I was locked in a footlocker.
Why are you wearing
my favourite T-shirt?
It's not even your colour.
What are we gonna do about Jumba?
What am I, an astronaut?
He was abducted by aliens.
But we can't just forget about him.
He's part of our ohana.
I know it's late,
but I need to talk to Cobra Bubbles.
- It's an emergency.
- He's asleep right now.
So wake him up.
I'm going to make a few calls myself,
using my trusty
Intergalactic Periwinkle Pages.
There's only so many phones
in the galaxy.
Hello? Planet Aaaaaaaaa?
- Is Jumba there?
- You know what time it is?
You don't have to be rude.
I bet one of those
other experiments could help us.
Too bad Pleakley said not to open it.
Pleakley also said
not to get them wet.
Hello? Planet Aaaaaaaaa?
- Is Jumba there?
- Go jump in a lake!
Same to you, fella.
Wait! We don't need all of them!
Just look for one
that can recharge the ship.
Container ready.
Select experiment.
Experiment 221.
Primary function,
electrical power surge.
Experiment 221 activated.
- Come on!
- What's going on?
Dark. Very dark.
Cousin lost.
Jumba lost.
You have a lot of lost issues.
But if we can find 221,
we can find Jumba.
Come on. I'll get a flashlight.
Prepare yourself for cruel
and interminable torture.
I'm not afraid of torture.
Excepting maybe little bit.
I'm certain Dr Hämsterviel
will find your little bit.
Gantu, you're late.
Dr Jacques Von Hamster-wheel.
Hämsterviel! It is Hämsterviel!
You stole my evil genius experiment,
Jumba.
Perhaps,
since you paid for experiments,
the evil is yours,
but genius was all mine.
What? Come down here and say that!
Funny,
you are shorter than I remember,
but you still have twitchy nose
like gerbil.
I am not gerbil-like,
I am hamster-like,
you with your four eyes
and inexplicable accent.
Anyway, I did find
this one experiment pod.
Jumba refused to reveal
the others' location,
- so I brought him for interrogation.
- Only one?
You incompetent fish head
of a minion!
I kick your stinky oversized feet!
Wait. What?
Interrogation?
Alright, take this! And that!
Don't just stand there.
Bring me a phone book.
It couldn't have gone too far.
Quiet!
Maybe he went this way.
If you do not tell me where
the other experiments can be found,
I will begin with the threatening.
Your threatenings don't threaten me.
Then I will threaten your family.
I have no family!
Perhaps I will activate
the one experiment pod
and leave you to its tortures.
Experiment 625.
He has all powers the same as 626.
He'll torture your little doughboy
buddy into talking.
Activate the experiment.
Run!
Any second now, you'll hear
his tortured cries of regret.
"Please let me out!
I'll tell you everything!"
Any second now,
his pathetic screaming,
begging for mercy.
Any second.
Should be right about now!
- I don't hear anything.
- Shut up. I can't hear.
So, you see,
625 has all powers of 626.
Even has
advanced language program.
Unfortunately is also lazy coward.
But makes great sandwiches.
Ham or tuna?
I am irked!
It's on the other side of the fence.
Lilo, what are you doing here?
You're having a camp-out?
But you told me everyone was sick.
We are sick. Sick of you.
Yeah!
Well, who needs
your dumb fakey camp-out anyway?
We're looking for a genetic
experiment from another galaxy
so we can recharge a spaceship
and rescue Jumba from aliens.
- You're a liar.
- No, I'm not.
It's in your yard. Right over there.
That's a bug electrocutor,
not an alien.
You and your disconfigured dog
are total freaks.
Yeah!
You can spit acid on 'em
if you want to.
Come on, Stitch.
Don't let Nani hear us.
It's so past my bedtime.
Lilo! It is so past your bedtime.
And don't forget to brush your teeth.
One more call before bed.
Phone.
- Hello?
- Is Jumba there?
This is him speaking.
Jumba!
It's Jumba!
Pleakley, how did you get number
for Gantu's detention cell?
I just called the number listed here.
Detention cell phone.
Cellphone! I get it.
There must be some way to make
that morally bankrupt scientist talk.
I think I'm gonna make a sandwich.
Gantu, how about a sandwich?
I don't want a sandwich!
You sure? Last of the baloney.
I don't like baloney.
Too fatty.
Unauthorised communication
intercepted.
Detention cell two.
So then monkey says to rabbi...
- What's going on here?
- Excuse me. Interrupting punch line.
- Sorry.
- Stop apologising!
Sorry.
Give me that!
Listen to me,
you caller of Jumba, you.
Yes.
It's the kidnapper.
OK.
Good. Fine.
What's he saying?
He wants all 624 other experiments
as a ransom,
or we'll never see Jumba alive.
Wait for my phone call.
I will then tell you
the ransom exchange location
and call you many nasty names.
Hang that up.
- No, slam it.
- Sorry.
What are we gonna do?
You called?
Cobra. How are you?
- Sleepy.
- Sorry.
Cobra. Thank goodness. It's terrible.
Just terrible. Jumba's been...
- Kidnapped.
- Yes. By...
Dr Hämsterviel.
- He wants a...
- Ransom.
- Of...
- The other experiments.
You're good.
How do you know all that?
Information is power,
and I like power.
- What should we do?
- Wait for Hämsterviel's next call.
Once we have
the rendezvous location,
we will exchange the experiments
for Jumba.
From there we follow
the governmental procedure.
What's the governmental procedure?
Classified. Right.
This is now
an intergalactic incident.
Take no further action
other than what I have indicated.
Is that clear, Lilo?
Yeah.
Me and Stitch
are gonna go out and play,
and not take further action.
No action.
That kidnapper
wants all the experiments.
We've got to find the sparky little
electrical one we lost, or no Jumba.
We've got to search
the entire island.
Stitch?
What's that? Look out!
I'm thinking he's this way.
This looks promising.
Don't lose him!
I'll find something to catch him in.
Grab him, Stitch!
Got him!
Isn't he cute? He's got your smile.
Cousin!
I've been working on your chart.
As you can see, it's not nearly
as bad as Stitch's was.
Too bad we have to give you away.
- No.
- What do you mean, no?
We gotta get Jumba back.
Cousin. Ohana.
You know what? You're right.
It's like I said.
You're all one big happy family.
It's the call. I'll get it.
Be calm. Get the rendezvous
information, then hang up.
Calm. Rendezvous. Hang up.
Here I go.
- Hello?
- Hello, Mr Pleakley.
This is the New You Girdle Company
calling regarding your order.
Wrong number.
Girdle? I wouldn't need a girdle
for my disguise.
It's an undergarment.
Why would I use a girdle?
- I didn't order anything!
- What?
Hello. How are you?
- It's Hamster-wheel.
- Hämsterviel! Hämsterviel!
The lighthouse in ten minutes,
and don't be late.
This is an unfortunate complication.
I know. We can take
the ridiculous Earth vehicle.
Where's Pleakley and Cobra?
They went to get Jumba back.
- But...
- I've got to go to work.
- No more buts!
Just stay here.
What a stunning example
of architecture!
Why isn't the big light
spinning around?
The beacon hasn't been lit for years.
Too costly.
Hämsterviel should be here by now.
That's Hamster-wheel? He sounded
much bigger on the phone.
Stop talking about me,
you gossiping pea-brains!
- Do you have the ransom?
- Do you have Jumba?
That's my question to you, sir.
Bring out the four-eyed fathead.
Jumba! You're OK.
Enough with your teary reunion.
Give me the experiments.
623 experiments
logged and functional.
623?
There's one missing!
Code yellow. Delay movement.
My ransom demand
was for all the experiments.
You're trying to pull a sneaky thing.
What is one tiny experiment
between old partners?
Quiet! I am blaming you for this.
- Dispose of him.
- Gladly.
No! He's allergic to plasma blasts!
Listen to him. It's true.
Wait!
I've got the missing experiment.
What? Who is this?
A little Earth girl who can be
a gigantic pain in the rear.
Well done, Lilo.
Give it to the diminutive
gerbil-like creature.
Hamster-like. Not gerbil. Hamster!
- Give it to me!
- No.
It's the only way you can save Jumba.
But I've gotta save Sparky, too.
You've named it?
Yep. We're gonna name
all the experiments.
Shut up
with all your not shutting up!
Hand it over!
Nope.
Lilo, do what he says.
Whose side are you on?
He's on saving-my-life side.
Is good side.
You fail to comprehend
the complexity of the situation.
Do you want your Jumba or not?
Make your choice, little girl.
OK. I've decided.
You can't have either of 'em.
Be free, little cousin.
- Now you save Jumba.
- Jumba!
- Begin the shooting.
- Finally!
Stay calm.
We're completely safe here.
Code green! Now!
Lock all sensors on the fugitive.
Activate external sound.
Dr Hamster-wheel,
you are hereby ordered to surrender.
It's Hämsterviel,
you absurd Grand Councilwoman
with your large pointy collar.
Prepare to fire.
Don't shoot!
He's got Stitch's cousins.
Cousins.
Fire at will.
Major electrical surge.
All systems failing.
Brace yourselves.
Hurry up, you great lumbering idiot!
This is Cobra. 10-13.
- 10-13.
- All systems off line.
No injuries reported.
We're alright.
Thank goodness. Our little
broken family is back together.
I have family?
I have family.
And you've got family too, Stitch.
We're getting those experiments back.
Lilo!
Well, now what do we do?
We hope
they can pull off another miracle.
Container ready. Select experiment.
So many nasty experiments.
I shall wreak mayhem
on the stinky galactic empire.
- Thank you.
- What?
You little trog!
- Pesky Earthling.
- You want it? Catch.
You little...
Get them back!
The window!
- The window's open.
- Warning. Window is open.
Be free, cousin.
No!
Little girl has saved
the experiments.
- Is very good.
- Very good?
It's not very good.
It's the opposite of very good.
It's very bad.
625 experiment pods
activated by water
raining on
one of the wettest spots on Earth?
Actually is only 623.
Whatever!
I'm afraid Pleakley is right.
This is indeed very bad.
This'll keep you two out of trouble,
until Dr Hämsterviel
can dispose of you properly.
Well, that didn't exactly work out.
But at least
we saved all the cousins.
Maybe Jumba and Pleakley and Nani
and David will find them a nice home.
Don't be scared, Stitch.
I'll figure out a way to rescue you.
Nobody gets left behind.
Or forgotten.
You think you're so...
Phone book!
Phone book. Yes, sir.
One second.
You think you're so clever,
don't you?
You think you've outsmarted the
infamous Jacques Von Hämsterviel.
Well, you made one grave mistake,
you oh-so-adorable
little Hawaiian girl.
You delivered to me
Experiment number 626.
I will now clone him
and create my own personal army.
What shall I do with the Earth girl?
She's of no use to me.
Struggle all you want.
You think you're so super-strong
with your "I can lift
up to 3,000 times my weight".
Well, that is exactly why I designed
this restraint to hold your weight...
...times 3,001.
Let me go!
I know a nice zoo that will pay
handsomely for a specimen like you.
One minute to teleport.
Unfortunately, my patented cloning
process has one nasty side effect.
I have to cut you in half.
Emergency alarm activated.
- Location?
- Detention cell two.
Not again.
- 625? What's the emergency?
- I need to know our coordinates.
I got us a deal
on a bunch of baloney.
The suspense is killing me.
Cousin.
What's happening?
Thanks, cousin.
30 seconds.
Stitch! Help!
I wasn't really going to
cut you in half. It was a joke.
Didn't Jumba put a funny bone in you?
Help!
Lilo.
20 seconds.
Help!
Ten seconds.
Nine, eight,
seven, six,
five, four,
three, two,
one,
Teleporting now.
Lilo!
Stitch?
I'm in this one.
Baloney order sent.
Sending little girl in ten seconds.
Nine, eight...
You're OK!
What are you doing in here?
You're not taking my ship!
Gantu. Where's my baloney?
I got nothing here but cheese.
- Where are they?
- Who?
- Earth Girl and 626.
- I don't know. Not in here.
- Bye-bye!
- Have a nice trip.
Hit it, Sparky.
Navigation is disabled.
Warning. Navigation disabled.
Grilled cheese.
Well, I don't think
we're gonna be going anywhere.
Looks like you and I
are working together.
- Sandwich?
- No! I don't want a sandwich.
- Unless you have egg salad.
- No. Only cheese.
Have you not been paying attention?
Aloha! We're back!
- Lilo!
- My genius experiment!
Another miracle.
These manacles are too tight,
you miserable oppressive do-gooders.
Dr Hamster-wheel.
Hämsterviel!
We catch bad guy. You're welcome.
Place him
in the high-security gerbil cage.
Hamster cage! I am hamster-like!
I will be back, you slobbering,
stinking humanoids and other aliens.
Now, what are we gonna do with you,
Sparky?
Let's see.
You like making big bunches of power,
right?
But you keep blowing up things like
light bulbs and spaceship consoles.
You need something really big
to play with.
Something that won't explode
when you touch it.
What is it, Stitch?
Well, if that isn't a pretty sight.
This planet
just never ceases to amaze.
Is just 500-watt alternating current
powering catadioptric lens.
It is beautiful.
Which makes it all the more tragic
that the Earth is now infested
with illegal genetic experiments.
I'm afraid I have no choice
but to evacuate the planet
and have them destroyed.
- What?
- You can't destroy the experiments.
They're ohana. Cousins.
And each one of them
has a place where they belong.
Just like Sparky
belongs at the lighthouse.
And Stitch belongs with me.
In fact, I'm starting to think
we're all cousins.
Even me and you.
Very well.
I won't destroy the experiments.
If you can retrieve
each and every one
and find, as you say,
the one place where each belongs.
But they're out there right now.
And they're all very bad. Right?
Yes, is true.
But once experiment
is turned to good,
is completely useless for bad.
I'm trying to fix for 627.
I hereby designate you an undercover
intergalactic experiment retriever.
And Stitch, too.
That's crazy talk! There are 625...
23.
A whole lot of pods out there.
How are you gonna find 'em?
lt'll be easy.
Like an Easter egg hunt.
Yes, but even more deadly. You must
find them before they get wet.
Before they get wet? No problem.
Come on.
We've got 625 cousins to find.
- 623.
- Whatever.
Are you sure they can handle this?
Lilo is a very persistent
little girl.
And with 626 they make one hot-shot
evil-genius experiment-catching team.
Bye!
Maybe the Grand Councilwoman will
let us go home with her this time.
I'll get the wig.
Subtitles by IMS