And still,
the questions remain.
Was it economic, was it social
or was it cultural?
Or was it simply
a matter of human nature?
What was it that made
some people do what they did...
and other people
do nothing at all?
Good job, Mr. Bowden.
It's nice to see a few more
A's this time around...
including Mr. Bowden's,
of course.
This concludes our week
on the Holocaust.
It you wanna know more, you may
find the Santo Donato library...
to be an excellent resource.
- Guess who likes you.
- Who?
Becky Trask. Are you gonna ask her out?
- You know who I'm talkin' about?
- I know who she is.
- I'll think about it.
- No, don't think.
You just do it, all right?
And can you give me your trig notes
from last year, because Fiscarelii...
- I knew this was leading to something.
- Fiscarelii is kickin' my ass.
- I'll bring them in tomorrow.
- Cool. Ask Becky out.
- I gotta think about it.
- What are you doin' after school?
I'm busy.
All right, I'm coming!
Oh, for God's sake.
Yes?
- What do you want?
- I--
If you're selling something,
I'm not interested.
I have your newspaper.
I'm not...
I'm not selling anything.
Then what do you want?
It you could let me in,
I just wanna talk.
Talk?
I don't have anything to say
to you, boy. Good day to you.
Bergen-Belson,
January of '43 to June '43.
Auschwitz,
June '43 to June '44.
And then you went to Patin.
After that, you disappeared.
But then in 1965,
you were spotted in West Berlin.
Listen, boy.
I don't have time for this game.
- Now leave before I call the police.
- Call them if you want.
I'm sure they'd love to meet you.
Who are you?
My name's Todd Bowden.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I just really wanna talk to you.
It you could let me in
for a minute?
Please, Mr. Dussander?
All of this...
because you saw an old man
with a raincoat and an umbrella?
It wasn't that easy. I mean, these
pictures are 40 years old, at least.
But when I held 'em up next to
the ones I took, I knew I was close.
- You took photographs of me?
- Yeah.
But even then,
I couldn't be sure.
I needed real proof, so I dusted
your mailbox for fingerprints.
You know, that's a lot
harder than people think.
I had to go back to Toytown
three times to get all the stutf.
Then I waited till
you were at the movies.
You put dust on my mailbox
for fingerprints?
You took photographs of me?
What else did you do?
I already had a copy
of your fingerprints.
They're on your want sheet
from the Israeli government.
It's all on database
at U.C. Irvine.
Are you okay?
Would you care
for a drink, boy?
- How about milk?
- Milk.
You told your parents
about all this then?
You think I'm crazy?
It takes eight good matches
for a print to get accepted in court.
They're called compares.
One or two is not so hard to find, but
eight good ones, that's really tough.
It all sounds
very exciting, boy...
but I'm afraid all your work
has been for nothing.
I found 14 compares.
Boy, what you have done...
I have to explain this to you because,
clearly, you don't understand.
What you have done
is a violation.
Like those experiments
with the decompression chamber.
- Now, that's a violation.
- To hell with this and to hell with you.
I'm calling the police.
Your father will beat your behind when
he picks you up from the police station.
- My parents don't believe in violence.
- They should start. I'm calling.
My name is Denker.
Arthur Denker.
I'm an American.
I became a citizen in 1955.
I vote.
You've no right to come here
and say these lies about me.
I have your fingerprints.
I have your photographs.
One way or another,
I'll get them to the right people.
This is unforgivable.
What do you want?
Tell me.
- I wanna hear about it.
- Hear about what?
The stories.
Everything.
What "everything"?
Everything they're afraid
to show us in school.
You were there.
You did those things.
No one can tell it
better than you can.
That's all I want.
Then I'll leave you alone.
And just so you know...
everything I have on you...
the compares, the want sheet,
all the photographs...
are all in a very safe place.
It anything happens to me,
someone will find it. Believe me.
Tell me, boy...
why should I consider
any of this?
Because you hung up
the phone, that's why.
Judging by the results
of your first exam...
I think that for most of you, we moved
a little too tast through chapter one.
By a show of hands...
how many of you think you know
what sociology is?
That's what I thought.
All right, class.
Let's turn to chapter two.
Once they were in the chamber,
how long did it take?
Five minutes?
Gott, no.
The prussic acid...
took about l5 minutes.
But the monoxide...
could take an hour,
sometimes more.
What happened to them?
I mean, exactly.
It was a mess.
They would lose control
of their bodies.
They vomited, urinated
and defecated themselves.
Even though the gas came in
from the vents in the ceiling...
they would climb
on top of each other...
desperately reaching for
fresh air that wasn't there.
They died in a mountain
of themselves.
What about the children?
On the bottom.
Did anyone ever survive it?
One time...
the gas didn't work.
There was a leak in the pipes...
so oxygen mixed with the monoxide.
It was horrible.
But after an hour
they were still moving...
stumbling around the room
like drunks...
their eyes glassy.
What did you do?
I ordered more gas,
but we didn't know about the leak.
Soon they began
to twitch all over...
like they were dancing.
Some even tell
to their knees...
laughing this terrible
high-pitched squeal.
Even the guards were frightened.
It didn't kill them.
After two hours...
I sent tive men in with ritles.
It's getting dark.
Your mother will be worried.
Oh, shit! I gotta go.
I can be here tomorrow by 3:15.
I want to hear the end of this.
The end?
The end.
Todd?
Are you up?
Honey, let's go.
Joey's outside.
Tell him I'm comin',
will you?
You said you were up
halt an hour ago.
Yeah, I must have
tallen back asleep.
Listen, honey, I'm gonna
see a client tonight at 7:00.
But I've got some cold chicken
in the tridge and plenty of...
It's okay. I'm gonna eat
over at Mr. Denker's house.
What are you gonna do
all night? Watch TV?
Mom, I told you. He doesn't watch TV.
I read books to him.
Will you not worry about it?
Listen to me. I want you
to invite him over here...
because Daddy and I
still want to meet him.
Okay?
So the policeman said to me...
"Mr. Denker, if you can't see the road,
you shouldn't be driving.
Now, how many tingers
am I holding up?"
And I said,
"Well now, officer.
Let me guess.
One?"
That was the end of
my driving in America.
I've taken the bus ever since.
Well, of course, I'm not drivin'
much either with this wheelchair...
but my eyesight is not
what it used to be.
That's a whitetail buck.
That's a remnant
trom our life in Carolina.
Dick brought that down
in the Yadkin River...
- seven or eight years ago.
- Seven.
You know, your grandson never told me
that he came trom a family of hunters.
Oh, Todd never took
a shine to guns.
- He's good at other things.
- Baseball is Todd's game.
- Arthur, sure you don't want a cigar?
- No, thank you.
It you don't mind, I'll have one
of my cigarettes. Where are they?
Ah! Let me help you
with that, Arthur.
My dear...
your generosity humbles me.
I thank you for
a most enchanting evening.
Well.
I wonder it you'd mind
it I asked you a personal question?
Not at all.
What'd you do during the war?
I was in the reserves,
as were most young men, Victor.
But then, my poor eyesight
kept me out of combat, I thank God.
No, I spent most of the war
in the military hospital...
washing bed linens
and nurses' unitorms.
You've been
pretty quiet tonight.
I'm sorry. It's just that I've heard
all of these stories before.
That's all right, my dear.
The boy's just being honest.
It's a privilege of boys.
A privilege that men
must sometimes give up.
You know, that reminds me. I...
It must have been my tirst year
at the university.
There was a group of about three
or tour of us, and we dropped in and...
At first my men took turns shooting them
in the head, but there were so many.
Two or three bodies could
be packed into each oven.
They were ground into fine ash.
A whole town was wiped off
the face of the earth.
And still,
it wasn't enough for Himmler.
That was a dark year.
We ordered every Jew in Kiev
to come to the Babi Yar Ravine.
You must remember, boy, the '20s
were a desperate time in Germany.
The Treaty of Versailles
had left us crippled.
God, we must have...
They would hide...
The shooting-- The walls-- The sewers--
But we always found them.
If the dogs didn't,
the smoke and fire would.
We would round them up
and march them out to a large pit.
At the time, the shooting
was no longer killing.
Nothing could stop the killing.
It was no longer death.
I will never forget
the sound that night.
So many of them on top
of each other like that.
After a few hours,
they began to settle.
A head would fall.
Yeah, an arm would drop.
It was a bit like
the sound of blowing leaves.
What did it teel like?
It was something
that had to be done.
A door had been opened
and couldn't be shut.
It was the end...
You don't understand.
You've done it a million times!
Let's go!
That's it!
Hit the showers!
- So, where you been?
- What do you mean?
Well, it you'd return
your phone calls...
you'd know that Damon's
havin' a party on Saturday night.
- I've been busy.
- Too busy for your best triend?
I've been studying a lot, okay?
I'm sorry.
You gonna go?
I don't even know
it I can get the car or not.
- I know someone who'll give you a ride.
- Who?
I've been accepted!
The Ritzy Vista Country Club.
Hee-hee-hee, my life's ambition.
Officer, can you tell me
where to catch the bus...
to the Ritzy Vista Country Club?
Ritzy Vista Country0 Club.
Here it is.
Where you goin', pop?
Why, this is the bus
to the country club, isn't it?
Very humorous.
- What do you want?
- The name is Magoo.
I have my papers.
- Hello?
- Judge Stevens put me in.
- Okay, sit down.
- Thank you.
- This way, buddy.
- My, what an impressive entrance.
Just look at those
big iron gates.
- Wake up.
- I'll kill you!
I thought you were dead.
- You look terrible.
- Today is, uh, Saturday.
Since when do you
come here on Saturdays?
I brought you something.
Aren't you gonna open it?
Wait, wait.
Let's put the shades down.
What for?
To be safe.
To hell with this.
You open it.
Relax. Open it.
You wrapped it yourselt, I see.
Merry Christmas.
Mary, Mother of God.
- Where did you get this?
- It looks pretty real, huh?
"E.F. Montgomery...
Costume Clothiers...
Topenstein, New Jersey."
Well, try it on.
Have you completely
lost your mind?
What on earth makes you think
I'd put something like that on?
I thought you would like it.
Like it?
You are a bigger tool
than I thought.
Maybe I'll put it on
and do a little shopping.
Is that what you thought?
The indignities I've suttered with you.
I should smash you.
What you've suftered with me
is nothing compared...
to what the Israelis
would do to you.
You forget that,
and I'll admit that's my fault.
But don't ever forget
the file I have on you.
I tried to do things the nice way,
but you don't want it.
So we're gonna do it
the hard way.
You'll put this on
because I wanna see you in it.
Now, move!
I see I've been promoted.
Yeah, I know.
It's all they had.
But that's a perfect fit.
I checked in one of your suit coats.
- It itches like hell.
- Quiet.
Put the hat on.
Please.
- Please, put the hat on.
- Good Gott.
Attention.
What's so tunny?
March.
Do it.
I'm serious.
Stop fucking around! March!
That's it.
Face right!
Okay, that's enough.
Stop.
Stop it!
Boy, be careful.
You play with fire.
Okay, I can tell
you're not into this.
No, I am, really.
It just takes me a while.
Right.
You know why I like you, Todd?
Because you're the only guy
that never tried to impress me.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Do you ever wonder
why people do the things they do?
You think about it.
- Okay.
- Seriously.
It's better not to think.
It's better to just do it.
Who are you, kitty, kitty?
It's getting cold out here...
kitty, hmm?
Kitty.
I'm sorry.
Maybe you'll be more
in the mood later.
I don't know. That's never
really happened to me before.
It's all right.
Could you blow that
the other way, please?
Maybe you just don't like me.
No, it's not that at all.
- I really do.
- Maybe you just don't like girls.
Kitty, kitty.
Good-bye.
You motherfucker!
Class, you have
tive more minutes.
"Dear Mr. & Mrs. Bowden:
This note is to suggest
that we have a group conterence...
concerning Todd's
first semester grades.
In light of his previous excellent work,
the sudden decline in his grades...
suggests a specific problem
which should be addressed...
before his academic advancement
is jeopardized permanently.
I'm ready to work out
a time for us to meet.
In a case such as this,
earlier is usually better.
Sincerely yours,
Edward French."
- Jesus, man. What are you gonna do?
- Fuck it I know.
- What?
- I said, "Fuck it I know."
You're throwin' it up hard.
Let it roll of your fingers more.
- I don't need a lesson, okay?
- All right.
Man, with your dad too.
I'm a fuck-up.
My dad expects this trom me. But you?
You're talkin' to yourselt.>
What's goin' on with you?
Nothing. I fucked up.
I'll tix it.
Whatever you say, man.
- What's happening between you and Becky?
- Who?
Becky Trask, idiot.
What did you call me?
You're bein' a real dick, man.
I gotta get to practice.
"You're talkin' to yourselt, man.
You're bein' a dick."
"...a time for us to meet.
In such a case as this,
earlier is usually better.
Sincerely yours,
Edward French."
Who's this Edward French?
Headmaster?
No, he's a guidance counselor.
- Well, what is that?
- He guides and he counsels.
You read the letter.
What stinks in here?
Oh, I bet it's
my TV dinner, I'm afraid.
- We've got a problem here, you know?
- We?
- I'm not the one in trouble.
- We'll see about that.
You don't turn this
around on me, boy.
It's not my tault
your grades have fallen.
That's where you're wrong. The shit
you tell me keeps me up half the night.
I tall asleep during class.
I need a fucking pencil.
Do you have one?
What will your parents do
about this letter?
They're never gonna see it.
That's the whole point of this.
This isn't just a little slipup here.
My parents will treak.
They're gonna wanna know exactly
what happened, and what happened is you.
You get what I'm telling you?
I think so.
You better be sure...
'cause it's your sorry ass
that winds up in jail, not mine.
Goddamn it!
I need a pencil.
A sharp one, please.
Thank you.
Does this Edward French...
know your parents
in a social way?
No. My parents wouldn't mix
with a geek like him.
How about professionally?
Has he ever spoken to them?
No. I've never
needed it until now.
You're messing things up
with that carbon paper.
- What do you know about it?
- Here. Out of the way.
I was forging documents
before your parents were born.
Todd, Mr. French
will see you now.
- Do you know what this is about?
- I'm sorry, I don't.
See ya.
He means the world to me.
Hey, Todd.
Have a seat.
Hello there.
It's okay. Sit down.
We were just talking about
what's been going on.
Do you wanna talk about it?
Not really.
You know, this is nothing
to be embarrassed about.
It's not your fault,
and both of us...
wanna help you
get back on track.
Both of you?
I must admit that...
the situation in Richard's home
is appalling.
I was raised to believe that
a man should take responsibility...
for his family.
But when you
came to me in tears...
and asked me to intervene...
well then, I realized that this
was not a matter to be trifled with.
That's why...
I arranged this meeting.
We all appreciate
your concern, Victor.
I've been looking
at your record...
and according to your
progress report this quarter...
every grade is way down,
even your strongest subjects.
History:
You went from a solid "A"
to a "C" minus.
Trigonometry:
Down to a "D"?
Todd, did you know you were on your way
to tinishing tirst in your class?
Yes.
Your grandfather and I have been talking
and we both agree...
that with what's been going on,
what with your tather's work problems...
and your mom with the drinking...
that maybe home isn't
the best place to be studying.
So he's offered to let you
study over at his place...
every day after school.
Todd, I think it's a good idea.
- You do?
- Yeah.
In tact, I offered
to go a step further.
But it means you and I
gotta make a deal.
What kind of deal?
Well, tinals for this quarter
are in 31/2 weeks. Right?
Now, if you can
give me all A's...
then I'll talk
to your teachers...
and see if we can't
discount your midterms...
and let this quarter's grades
rest with your tinal exams.
But it you come back with
B's or C's, I can't help you.
But all A's...
that shows everybody
that you're serious.
- You can do that?
- Yeah.
But first you gotta start
being honest with me.
No more forging
your father's signature.
No more hiding my letters.
For now we can deal
with just the three of us...
it it makes things
easier at home.
But you try and pull one over on me,
next time I show up on your doorstep.
Is that clear?
- He's oftering to help...
- I know!
But that's a whole lot to do
in three weeks.
What if I can't do it?
Mr. Bowden, I can't thank you enough
for coming down here today...
but it it's all right with you
I'd like to talk to Todd alone...
for a few minutes.
Yes, it's quite all right.
If you didn't excuse me...
I'm afraid that my desire
for a cigarette would.
You can take my word,
when the time is right...
I'll tell Richard
about all this, you know.
He and Monica need to know
what's happening to their son.
I'll expect you after school.
- He's a very persuasive man.
- Tell me about it.
Listen, Todd. I understand
what you're going through.
I really do.
My wite and I, we just went through
the nastiest divorce since Henry Vlll's.
And I know it's not easy
being a senior and only 16.
And now we're asking
a lot of you.
But your grandtather
thinks you can do this.
Todd, I know you can.
So from now on...
I don't want you to feel like
you have no one you can talk to, okay?
Your parents,
or girl problems...
Anything at all.
Here's my home phone.
Anything at all. Anything.
You call me, Todd.
Call me.
Deal?
I'm telling you, buddy,
you get past this little hurdle...
I promise you the world's gonna
open up for you like you won't believe.
Bye.
Have you lost your mind?
What the hell
were you thinking, "Grandpa"?
- What are you so excited about?
- Oh, you've got some fucking balls!
I could've screwed you up.
Anything could've happened.
You played it beautifully, boy.
I knew you would.
Are you fucking drunk?
I could've busted you right there.
Yes, you could have, but you did not.
Now why was that?
Your Edward French is not going
to give you any more trouble.
Now you are upset because the only way
you can make things right is to work.
I'm upset because you had that asshole
thinking I can do something...
- that can't be done.
- Oh, but it can, and it will.
You will simply have to work.
No more stories.
- No more screwing around.
- I don't take orders from you.
- You do now.
- Oh, you think so?
Don't forget, I can walk in there
and pick up that phone.
And do what?
Do you really think that
I would stand aside...
and let you turn me in
without dragging you with me?
Do you?
Your American self-confidence
is so bloated...
you've forgotten
the reality of the situation.
90,000 died in Patin.
To the whole world,
I am a monster.
And you have known about me
all this time.
It I'm caught, when those reporters
stick their microphones in my tace...
it will be your name that
I will repeat over and over again.
Todd Bowden.
Yes, that was his name.
For how long?
For months, almost a year.
He wanted to know everything.
That was how he put it, yes.
Everything.
You're crazy.
They'll never believe you.
It doesn't matter.
Oh, you're going to be infamous, boy.
Take my word for it.
And you know what
such a scandal can do.
It never goes away.
Not for you.
Not for your parents.
And besides, lying to judges and
reporters isn't as easy as you think.
You'd have to be brilliant.
Can you do that?
I know I can.
There's no way in hell...
I'm gonna be able to pull myselt out
of a half-year's slide in a few weeks.
- This shit just doesn't happen.
- Boy, the time for discussion is over.
This is the way it is.
You're going to work.
You're going to spend the rest of this
quarter and all your vacation studying.
...one of the most interesting
writers of his time.
...longitude and latitude.
There are coordinates...
...both sides by "y,"
leaving you with 3xy...
...made some people do what they did,
and other people do nothing at all.
This concludes our week
on the Holocaust.
If you wanna know more, you may find
the Santo Donato library an excellent...
You are a monster.
Is the thrill enough?
- What you have done is a violation.
- I wanted to know more.
- A door had been opened...
- ...lose control of their bodies...
- I fucked up.
- You'd have to be brilliant.
Lying isn't as easy as you think.
- Maybe you just don't like girls.
- He's good at other things.
- I'll fix it.
- You gotta start being honest with me.
Boy, be careful.
You play with fire.
It never goes away.
Not for you.
How about some melba toast?
- Sure.
I would have expected you
to be doing back tlips...
down the hallway
after such good news.
But you're so quiet.
Today, I think I will give you
the day off from studying.
How's that? Hmm?
How about...
one of my stories instead?
I still have
a few good ones left.
- I don't care.
- Let's see.
I could tell you
about the special soap...
we made.
Or there's always the story
of how I escaped from Berlin...
after I was so foolish
as to go back.
That was a close one,
I can tell you.
No, none of these.
I think you don't seem
to be in the mood.
I think today
I will tell you the story...
of an old man who was afraid.
He was afraid of
a certain young boy who was...
in a clear way...
his triend.
The boy proved
to be a very good student.
But not perhaps
in quite the way...
his mother and his teachers
had envisioned.
At first, the old man
disliked the boy intensely.
But then he began to enjoy
the boy's company.
Ot course, there is still
a great deal of distrust between them.
Each knew something
the other wanted to keep secret.
Over time...
the old man felt...
his hold on the boy
slipping away.
He thought the day might come
when the boy no longer needed him.
So...
one sleepless night...
the old man got out of bed...
and wrote down the story
of his involvement with the boy.
Everything he could remember...
from the first day forward.
He wrote how the boy
forced his way...
into the old man's house
and blackmailed the old man...
to serve his own
morbid tascinations.
When the boy's grades
began to tall...
he blamed the old man
and ordered him...
to impersonate his grandfather.
At the end, his hands
were stinging with arthritis...
but he telt happy
for the tirst time in weeks.
He telt safe.
On the tollowing morning,
the old man...
put on his best suit...
and went down to
one of the local banks...
and rented a safe deposit box.
The bank officer
explained to the old man...
that only the old man
could use the old man's key...
with one exception.
The exception was...
in the event
of the box holder's death, then...
Then what?
The box will be opened
in the presence of a bank official...
and a representative
of the Internal Revenue Service.
The contents of the box
would be inventoried.
But in this case...
they would only find
a 12-page document.
Nontaxable,
but highly interesting.
You didn't do this.
I don't believe you.
My boy...
it is already done.
Jesus fucking Christ!
Look at you!
You could go at any time.
Don't be so theatrical.
A man tive or ten years
older than me, worries more...
about his ailing heart
than being...
sent off to Israel.
And the day will come,
if I live long enough...
when I decide that
what you know no longer matters.
But then, and only then,
I will destroy the document.
So many things
can happen in between.
Accidents, sickness.
You could slip in the fucking shower,
for Christ's sake.
Whatever will be will be
The future's not ours to see
Que sera, sera
I can see you're
thinking it now, even now.
It's in your eyes...
killing me.
All it would take would be
the tlick of a knife.
Push me down the steps,
make it look like an accident.
I am old. You are strong.
You're angry.
Good assets for killing.
But there is something missing.
To have someone
in your control...
To have them know
that they are alive...
only because you have not
decided to the contrary.
Do you have that power?
Ask yourself.
It's not an easy question.
I think you know that.
You know this means
we're through, don't you?
You won't be seein' me
around here anymore.
I suppose I won't.
What are you doing?
This is the end.
Here.
A drink.
To our lives together.
The beginning and the end.
I think you should
fuck yourselt.>
Oh, my dear boy.
Don't you see?
We are fucking each other.
Strike!
Two outs!
Strike three!
What are you guys waitin' for?
Let's go!
Rebound! Move it!
Watch your step.
Sir?
Excuse me.
I can help you carry those.
You don't gotta be afraid.
I can help you.
I don't need your help.
Excuse me.
I'm not a bad guy.
You don't gotta worry.
- Please, I just wanna...
- What do you want?
- Why do you bother me?
- We're practically neighbors.
You know, I stay
right over there most nights.
I mean, I see you
walk down the street.
I just wanna help.
- It's called being neighborly.
- Piss off.
You don't...
There's no reason to be rude!
No reason!
I know something about you.
I know you're a nice guy.
I'm nice too,
just like the boy.
I see.
I'm not ashamed to say that
I could use a drink about now.
But I don't take no charity.
It you were to invite me in
like a friend...
then we could have a nice drink.
A drink.
That's what I'm sayin'.
You smell like a toilet.
Maybe you'll let me
use your shower.
But first a drink.
Then I will do
anything you say.
I had 'em hooked up, rollin'...
41/2.
But three minutes,
that was my best.
I was, like,
movin' double time.
Gosh, you know...
I didn't...
didn't see that dog
in the back seat.
- Didn't see it.
- What dog?
That dog.
I heard it barking.
But I hear dogs barking all the time,
even when they ain't there.
So I didn't pay no mind.
D.O.T. Didn't wanna hire me
'cause of that thing with the...
Anyway.
Who wants to talk about that?
So I was...
I was an independent,
you know...
which meant that I could go
all over the whole city.
You know, I believe...
we need another bottle.
It you're oftering,
then we accept.
That's no trouble at all.
Look, why don't you drink mine?
Thank you.
So, like I was sayin'...
I was...
I worked as an independent.
'Cause the D.O.T.,
they wouldn't hire me, right?
So I was able to go...
all over the whole city.
Midtown, downtown,
left side, right side...
Where is my bottle opener?
There it is.
You stay right there.
So then I moved on.
Washington Heights was good.
It was always good...
because there were a lot
of nooks and crannies, you know.
The D. R.'s... the Dominicans there,
they liked to...
go around in their cars
like they were buses.
Then they dropped that cinder block
on that cop from three-four.
And it got all crazy.
But you gotta be movin', 'cause...
they come back, they catch you
hookin' their ride.
Do you mind?
No. Not at all.
Maybe in the morning...
perhaps everything goes okay,
you could let me have $10.
Perhaps.
Even a 20...
Perhaps. We shall see.
You can relax, you know.
I've done this before.
That's all right.
So have I.
Let me go pee first.
Did you look at this
before you signed it?
That bill was written
in Japanese.
- I told you that.
- Numbers are numbers in any language.
That man did not speak
one word of English.
- That's not the point.
- Ot course it's the point.
The point is you look at a bill
before you pay it.
I did not understand one word.
That's exactly the point.
Hello?
Yes.
Maybe it was in yen.
Maybe it is.
It's Mr. Denker.
He sounds very anxious.
Why would he be calling
at this hour?
- Hello?
- Come over right away, boy.
I'm having a heart attack.
A bad one, I think.
That sounds exciting, but I
have to study for my trig tinal.
I understand you cannot talk,
but you can listen.
I cannot call an ambulance.
I need help.
And that means you need help.
It you put it that way.
Tell you parents I have
an important letter...
and I need you
to read it to me.
I'll be right over.
Now we'll see
what you're made of.>
What happened?
Ah, boy.
- Where are you bleeding?
- It's not my blood.
It was selt- defense.
Boy, now listen.
- What are you talking about?
- Shut up.
Nobody comes here until you
have done what needs to be done.
Go down the steps.
What did you do?
Go down the steps, huh?
That's right.
Let me out!
- Let me the fuck outta here!
- No, boy.
If you won't help me,
I have to make you.
That's enough!
Open the goddamned door!
Do you hear me?
Fuck you!
If you're going to behave
like a fucking schoolgirl, I'll...
I'm gonna break
your goddamn door down!
Fuck!
Don't be afraid, boy.
I know what you're doing.
I'm gonna break
the goddamn door down!
What are you doing?
There is no point.
Why are you doing this?
Call an ambulance.
The key.
The key to the safe deposit box.
Where is it?
Boy, I need a doctor.
Now.
Give me the key.
I'm dying.
I know.
Oh, no.
Not like this.
Please.
You did good, son.
You did real good.
It's a good thing you called us
when you did. You saved his life.
Dad.
Let's go make sure he gets
checked in all right.
You shouldn't have.
It's trom my mother.
They say the operation
was a success.
They say I have
another 20 years.
A new lease on life.
I took care of everything,
except for the key. Where is it?
There's no safe deposit box.
There never was.
I lied.
I had to protect myself
trom you, boy.
You understand?
I suspect that we will
never see each other again.
- No, we won't.
- Wait.
I want to ask you something.
What?
What did it feel like?
- I better go.
- Wait.
Perhaps I...
Perhaps I could
persuade you to stay.
Just until I fall asleep.
My medicine makes me drowsy.
Please?
Excuse me, young man.
You are a very good boy to visit
your grandtather like that.
Thank you,
but he's just a triend.
Then you are
a very good triend.
Tell me.
Is he very bad off?
He doesn't talk much.
- The doctors say he'll be out soon.
- That's good news.
From the way he speaks,
I would guess he was German.
- From the south, I think.
- I don't know.
I wonder it he was in the war.
I don't think so.
He's never mentioned it, anyway.
It doesn't matter,
I suppose.
It was a long time ago,
the war.
Soon, in this country...
we will have a president
born after the war was over.
How about that?
- I'm sure you're right.
- He is so very lucky...
to have you.
A great man once said...
''No man is an island...
entire of itself.>"
John Donne.
- Have a nice evening, sir.
- Good-bye.
Mr. Jefferson, I don't have to
listen to that kind of talk.
Then how about
this kind of talk?
That's just a warning.
Anytime you crave for Florence's food,
that's a weird craving.
Jenny's the one who's pregnant.
They said they had
something to tell us.
- Something important.
- Oh, we're gonna be grandparents again!
Oh, I just can't wait
to tell everybody!
Hey, Ralph. Great!
Huh? Thanks, Ralph.
The kids just got out of a cab.
They should be here any second.
What's wrong?
Yes.
I'm speaking to you.
Mr. Kramer
is recuperating elsewhere.
- Are you awake now, Dussander?
- Yes, of course.
But you seem to have
confused me with someone else.
My name is Denker.
Perhaps you need
a different room.
My name is Weiskopf,
and you are Kurt Dussander.
No, I don't know
no one by that name.
Should I call a nurse?
The man in the next bed
was Benjamin Kramer.
He was imprisoned
for ten months at Patin.
You were responsible for the death
of his wite and two daughters.
My name is Denker.
Arthur Denker.
- I am an American.
- Please, don't bother.
Your papers won't stand up
to serious examination and you know it.
- I think we have all we need here.
- Who are these men?
I'm Dan Richler,
special agent with the F.B.I...
and this is Detective Getty
with the L.A.P.D.
And I think you know
who I work for.
When you regain your strength,
you will be moved.
Until then, this entire ward
will be under guard.
You can expect to be in Jerusalem
by the end of the summer.
- So where do you want us to sit?
- Anywhere but the front row.
- Yeah? There's, uh, Carla.
- Carla! How are you?
- Hi. Hi, Chelsea.
- I thought that was you.
Hi. Congratulations.
It's a big day for everybody.
- How are you?
- Excuse me.
You did it. I knew you could.
I am so proud of you.
- Thank you.
- Oh, hi. These must be your parents.
- Yeah. Dick Bowden. Nice to meet you.
- Ed French.
- Todd pulled one off. You must be proud.
- Yes, we are.
- This is my wite, Monica.
- Hi.
- Are you a teacher of Todd's?
- Actually, I'm his guidance counselor.
- Oh, great.
- Nice to meet you.
Yeah. I was looking forward to seeing
your grandtather, Victor. Where is he?
It's a long trip trom Charlotte. He's
been in a wheelchair for a few years.
So they don't
get out here much.
Usually Thanksgiving.
I'm-I'm sorry.
I don't...
I don't understand.
That's your cue.
That's my cue. Okay.
Good luck up there.
- Nice to meet you.
- Take care, Ed.
I don't feel so well. Maybe after
the ceremony, we could go straight home.
- Are you okay?
- You know what? It's probably nerves.
- Just take a deep breath.
- We'll see how it goes.
All great achievements
arose from dissatisfaction.
It is the desire
to do better...
to dig deeper...
that propels a civilization
to greatness.
All of us have heard
the story of Icarus...
the young boy who took the wings
his father built for him...
wings that were meant
to carry him over the ocean to freedom...
and used them instead
for a joyride.
For a brief moment...
Icarus felt what it was like
to live as a god...
to touch the sun...
to soar above the common man.
And for doing so,
he paid the ultimate price.
You boys better come down to the cellar.
You're not gonna believe this.
Like Icarus, we too
have been given gifts:
Knowledge, education...
experience.
And with these gifts comes
the responsibility of choice.
We alone decide how our talents
are bestowed upon the world.
This is our destiny...
and we hold it in
the palm of our hands.
...of an investigation
by local police...
the sheriff's department,
F.B.I...
and the Department of Justice.
Police have confirmed that
a body has been found...
in the basement
of Arthur Denker...
the Santo Donato resident
believed to be...
a Nazi war criminal.
The cause of death
has not been revealed...
and authorities are withholding
identification of the body...
until more information
is available.
The apprehension of Dussander
would bring to a close...
a manhunt that's been underway now
for 40 years in three continents.
I'll be taking
care of you trom now on.
Try to relax.
Todd, I'm Dan Richler.
I'm a special agent with the F.B.I.
And this is Dr. Weiskopt.> If you
don't mind, I'd like to hear about...
your involvement with Dussander.
Well, actually, you knew him
as Arthur Denker. Isn't that right?
- Yes.
- How did you know him?
Are you sure you
feel up to this?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Let me tell you
what we're interested in.
You told the admitting nurse
that Arthur Denker...
had a heart attack
while you were reading him a letter.
- Yes.
- Was it in English or German?
German.
- You speak German?
- No.
So you had no idea
what you were reading.
No. But he seemed to understand
every word I was saying.
What we can't seem to tigure out
is the letter, Todd.
Do you have any idea
what happened to it?
I guess it's still on the table.
I couldn't swear to it, though.
- Then it still should be there.
- It isn't?
No. Well, when you arrived, Mr. Bowden,
do you remember seeing a letter?
But I wasn't looking for a letter.
I was more concerned about Todd.
Maybe somebody
broke in and took it.
Why would somebody break
into a house simply to steal a letter?
Unless, of course,
they wanted to protect him.
You know, a close triend,
another fugitive.
Look, I know all this sounds like
Robert Ludlum kind of stuff...
but we think that while
Dussander was in the hospital...
our "Mr. X" scooted
over to the house and swiped the letter.
- That doesn't make sense.
- Why not?
Well, it he had
an old Nazi buddy in town...
why didn't he come over
and read the letter himselt?
Well, maybe he's in a wheelchair.
Or maybe he's blind.
Well, guys that are blind don't normally
go scooting out to steal letters.
Did he ever talk
about his past?
Excuse me, Dr. Weiskopt.>
I'm just curious.
- What kind of doctor are you?
- I'm a schoolteacher.
Dr. Weiskopf is a professor
at the Judaic Institute in Munich.
He assists the Israeli government
in certain matters.
Hey, buddy?
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
I just can't believe it,
even after what those guys told me.
- It's mind-boggling.
- Your mother and I teel terrible.
It's like we let you down.
It's not your fault.
We're gonna go down
and talk to a lawyer. He's very good.
It's nothing for you to worry about.
It's just I don't trust these cops.
- Okay. I think that's a good idea.
- Yeah.
Well, your old man's on top of this,
all right? We'll take care of this.
I know.
- Dad?
- Yeah?
I really never knew
anything about this.
- I never thought you did.
- I know.
See you later.
Are you going to talk
to the boy again?
- I don't think so.
- Somehow, he didn't even...
When you were a boy...
what did you do for fun?
Went to the movies.
Why? What'd you do?
I used to chase girls.
And now, I chase old men.
Special Agent Richler,
Dr. Weiskopt...
this is the hospital administrator,
Dr. McCormick.
His chief of statt,
Dr. Sfewart.
- How do you do?
- Hello, ma'am.
- Do we have a plan?
- McCormick's arranged an exit for us.
- Mr. French.
- Hello, Todd.
What are you doing here?
I came by to see your parents.
Are they home?
No. What about?
That's between
me and your parents.
Why isn't it between
you and me?
Do you want to tell me what happened?
He needs to be turned
on his left side.
- Watch his line.
- Get him over.
I wouldn't know
where to begin.
Well, you're gonna have
to tell me something.
I can tell you that it'd be better
it we both just forgot about that.
Well, I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
Get the crash cart!
Stat!
Why don't you tell your parents
I'll be back to see them later.
- What?
- I thought we had a deal here.
"Pull up your grades
and the world will open up for you."
What do you mean? You want me
to just forget about this?
I just want to go to college
and get on with my life.
Todd, okay. You know, we're not gonna
talk about this right now.
It was a mistake to come here.
I'll do this over the phone.
Clear the way!
Can I ask you something, Ed?
You don't mind it I call you Ed, do you?
Now that I'm out of
your fucking high school.
- Does it ever work?
- What?
I really wanna know. Does it ever work,
or am I the tirst one?
'Cause if I'm the first, I'm flattered,
but somehow I can't believe that.
Not after you tixing my grades.
And giving me your home phone number?
And then you come out here
when my parents aren't home.
- What are you talking about?
- I mean, you've got some balls.
Is this why
your wife left you?
You must have really wanted
to shake my hand. Or something else.
Now, wait a minute.
What are you...
Are you gonna tell people
I did something to you?
I don't wanna drag you down
with me, but I will.
- I'm better at this than you are.
- Better at what?
I'm trying to help you.
Can't you see that?
- You've helped enough.
- Well, I won't just do nothing.
Well, you're gonna
fucking have to!
- Still a flat line.
- Clear!
The things I'm gonna say,
they'll never go away.
Not for you.
Think of your job.
Think of your son.
And clear!
So, what's the story here, Ed?
Do we have a deal?
You can't do this.
You have no idea
what I can do.
Subttulo Ripeado por
~Grupo Utopia~
www.grupoutopia.cjb.net