(thunderrumb/es)
Don't worry, Billy.
That lightning can't get to us.
You're safe in the car.
Had a little engine trouble.
Had to set her down.
I think it's probably a fuel line.
Do you mind giving me a hand?
I'll have it back in the air in a second,
if you'll just help me out.
OK. All right.
You just stay put, Billy.
I'll be right back.
Hold this for me.
No! No!
Don't shoot.
What do you want? l got money.
(sorens)
Stay back! l've got the kid!
You're gonna be all right.
I'm a cop.
He won't be hurting anyone else.
Need a hand?
Hey.
Hey, Officer.
You OK? l heard something on the radio
that you rescued a little boy.
What happened?
Some freak snatched him up
and l tracked him with my plane.
We got him back. Kid's gonna be fine.
That's great,
but you don't seem all that happy.
Things got a little messy out there.
Looks like now l'm a free man.
- You got fired?
- Yeah.
You shot him, Jim?
You killed him.
I thought he was going for a gun. I wasn't
sticking around for a confirmation.
Sheriffs calling it "excessive force".
He wanted me to see a shrink again,
but l told him no.
But you can't just go around shootin'
people cos they're wacko.
We're not gonna worry about that
any more, are we?
Damn it, Jim. You promised me
you wouldn't do something like this again.
Maggie, l know.
You just have to get some help.
Then they'll take you back
or you could do something else.
You've got to get yourself together.
At least try.
Maggie, there's nothing
l haven't already tried.
I think we need to take a break.
Together, l mean. We'll take some time,
we'll get away for a while.
It'll be good for the both of us.
But if you don't do something, Jim,
l don't know what's gonna happen... to us.
(phone)
(answerong machone beeps)
He//o. You've reached Johnson & Esser
Crop-Dustong. P/ease /eave a message.
(ca//erhangs up)
No!
(phone)
- Hello?
- Mrs Esteridge. Hi.
- This is Jim Halsey calling.
- Jom/ How the heck are ya?
Fine, thanks. Is the captain available?
You know he is.
Hold on a sec. I'll go get him.
Stop your yappin', pal.
Ain't nothin' ever there.
Honey, phone for ya.
Honey!
- Bonnie...
- It's Jim Halsey.
Hello there, Jim.
- Captain Esteridge, how are you doin'?
- Fine. How are you doin'?
Shit. Captain, l'm in a world of hurt here.
I screwed up big-time.
I need to talk to you, officer to officer.
To te// you the truth,
/ don't rea//y know why /'m ca//ong.
I don't mean to bother you, sir.
It sounds like this isn't something
we should handle over the phone.
Why don't you come on down and vosot?
Bonnoe and / wou/d /ove to see ya.
- And brong that gor/ you to/d us about.
- There's no way l can come back there.
No way.
Listen, Jim.
This thing's still eatin' you alive.
Sometimes the only way to get over
something is to face it straight on.
I realise that, sir.
- But l haven't been down there since...
- That's the point.
It's about time. You have to.
Maybe you're right, sir. Maybe comin'
down there would do us some good.
- I know l'm right.
- We'// do ot.
- We'll both come down.
- That's my boy.
You be carefu/ comon' down, cos
there's supposed to be a storm brewon'.
Don't you worry about that.
We're gonna be OK.
Thank you, sir.
It ain't Cabo, but at least
it's a change of scenery, right?
Yep.
Let's go.
Hello?
(Maggoe) Hello?
Good thing we called ahead, l guess.
Beat the rush(!)
Maybe the keys are in the car.
So you met Captain Esteridge
passing through here?
Yep. A long time ago.
I had a little car trouble here.
I got stranded.
Captain Esteridge helped me out.
What happened, Jim?
Let's just say that
he's the reason l became a cop.
We stayed in touch ever since.
Look out!
My God! That guy almost killed us.
This is supposed to be our no-killing trip.
- You OK?
- Yeah. Are you?
I'm OK, l'm OK.
(radoo) For those ofyoujust tunong on,
we have a storm a/ert.
There's a heavy wond advosory
from Nocke/ Creek to the county /one.
There are reports of50-60 mph wonds
kockong up sand and debros.
Vosobo/oty os poorand the hoghwaypatro/
advoses peop/e to stay at home
ofat a// possob/e.
(Maggoe) Oh, my God.
Pull over. They've had an accident.
The car's not there. They've gone for help.
- Somebody could be hurt inside.
- I'm not stopping, Maggie.
Jim, why are you acting like this?
l can't believe you won't pull over.
- You're a trained cop.
- There was nobody there.
My God. Is he crazy?
Where'd he go?
- We have to pick him up.
- No.
- Are you crazy? He'll die out here.
- No way.
- Stop!
- No!
We can't leave some guy
stranded out here in a sandstorm.
(startergronds)
- What are you doing?
- Whatever you do, do not let him in here.
Maggie...
Ohh...
Thanks, folks.
Not too many people
pick up a hitchhiker these days.
I've been waitin' for ya.
It looks like you took a pretty good spill
back there. You all right?
I'm all right.
I'm Maggie, and this is Jim.
Jim. Ain't that somethin'?
I'm Jim, too.
There's a small town
a couple of miles up ahead.
- We'll take you that far, but that's it.
- Sounds good to me, Jimmy.
I'm just glad to be alive.
So don't tell me.
I'll bet you're a farm girl, aren't ya?
I used to be.
But the bank took the land,
so l had to find something else to do.
That's me. Always finding
something else to do.
A little bit of this,
a little bit of that.
If l don't keep myself busy,
l'll just... I'll just go crazy.
What do you do for fun?
I fly planes.
Crop-duster.
Jim here is a cop.
Got myself a couple of professionals.
So, where are we goin' to today?
- We're just...
- None of your business!
My mistake, folks. I'm sorry.
- What are you doin' there, Jimmy?
- I'm gonna get some coffee.
You need somebody to fix your bike,
so we can let you off here.
I'm afraid that's not gonna work.
It's not your call, is it, pal?
Well... It may not be my call,
but l've been waiting for you
for a long, long time.
(truck droversounds horn)
No! God!
Take your hand out of your jacket,
and get the hell out of my vehicle.
- Son of a bitch.
- Why do you have a gun?
- Jim...
- Get out of the car!
- Jimmy, l was just...
- Get out!
- Get out of my car.
- (Maggoe) Jim...
Well, all right.
Thank you for the ride.
Don't take this personal, Jimmy,
but if l were you,
I'd get myself
some serious professional help.
Nice to meet you, farm girl.
That guy's psycho.
Jim, what is goin' on with you?
- He had a gun.
- He did not have a gun. You had a gun.
Damned fool. Truck stop's closed.
- Why did you have a gun on vacation?
- He was gonna kill you, then me!
- Did you see a gun?
- I didn't have to!
You're starting to scare me.
You're acting crazy.
You're gonna have to trust me on this one.
He definitely had a gun.
(honkong)
(soren)
What are you doing, Jim? Pull over.
Pull over.
Licence and registration.
So, speed racer,
where are you going in such a hurry?
We're just passing through here, sir.
Kind of got away from me.
Get out of the car slowly
with your hands up! Both of ya!
- I can explain this.
- Shut up!
Step back
and put your hands on the hood.
- I'm a police officer.
- Police officer. Yeah(!)
Iowa. Where the heck
is that supposed to be?
Not around here.
- Cop, huh?
- I used to be.
Then you should know better
than to carry a concealed weapon.
Both of you stay right where you are
while l call this in.
Billy? ls that you?
Something goin' on here.
I want you to step back
just for a sec, all right?
- What's that?
- Shit.
I'm gonna need some backup here.
Pronto, would ya?
Damn it, Billy. I said, stay back.
I said, stay back. I'm dealin' with
a law-enforcement situation.
Hell, so am l.
- Go!
- Freeze!
How you folks been?
Go, go, go, go!
Shit!
Hi, there.
Adoos, farm girl.
Jimmy, l'm so sorry l ever doubted you!
Captain Esteridge
is the only one who can help us.
- I can't believe this is happening!
- It's starting again.
What? What's starting?
About 15 years ago, when l was a kid,
l was driving across country.
I had to deliver a rental car to San Diego.
I drove through here and picked up
a hitchhiker. Son of a bitch was psycho.
He started killing people:
cops, innocent families.
Move over. That guy will kill you.
He ko//ed thos gor/ that / knew.
He set me up for it.
He framed me for the killings.
Everybody thought it was me,
except for Esteridge.
He was the only one who believed me.
He helped me out.
They finally caught the son of a bitch.
He escaped. / had to ko// hom.
I shot him dead.
So you think this is the same guy?
He doesn't look the same,
but it's him. I know it's him.
- We have to tell the cops everything.
- They won't believe us.
We have to find Esteridge. He's
the only one l trust. Where's that map?
(phone)
Why don't / get that?
Sheriffs office. Deputy Lyle speakin'.
/ wasjust out at the Gas and Gro//,
and / heard these two kods ta/kon'.
Scared the he// outta me. Saod they were
goong aftera guy named Esterodge,
and ko// hom s/ow
for what he'd done to 'em.
- Who in the hell is this?
- She had a big gun. I saw her.
You better get out there.
Who knows what's gonna happen?
Jessop, are you out there?
Jess?
Jess, / got somethon' forya.
/t cou/d be somethon'.
That's weird.
(Maggoe) Come on.
Captain Esteridge?
Cap?
(bord flutters)
- Stay here.
- No way.
Cap?
(barks)
(whonnyong)
(saw whonong)
(swotches offsaw)
Jim!
We gotta get outta here.
We'll just call for help.
He did this.
Come on.
Jim! Come on.
Mrs Esteridge is dead! She's dead!
Whoever's in there,
come out now, with your hands up!
- We'll explain everything.
- What? That we killed everybody?
It's not gonna work, Maggie.
I've been through that before.
We've got to find this son of a bitch
and stop him ourselves.
I'll do it.
They'll believe us.
Come out now!
We're coming out!
We'll explain everything. Just don't shoot.
Jim!
Two's company. Three's a crowd.
Sorry, crop-duster.
Maggie!
Why'd you have to go and do
a thing like that, Jimmy?
Who am l gonna play with now, l wonder?
What the...?
Jesus.
(soren)
Hold your fire!
Captain Esteridge?
Captain, you in there?
Agh!
Two officers down. We're at
Esteridge's farm. Send backup now.
All hell has broken loose out here.
(woman) /'// send someone out roght away.
We got two suspects -
one male, one female -
fleeing in a black and white Prospector.
Headin' west on the old highway.
(gasps)
Hang on, Jim. Hang on.
Maggie...
You have to kill him. Promise me
you'll kill him, no matter what.
You just hang on.
I'm so sorry, Maggie. I'm so, so sorry.
Please, God. Please! (sobs)
Jim!
(soren)
(Jom) l love you.
(Maggoe) / /ove you.
/'m so sorry.
No! (weeps hysteroca//y)
No!
(machonery c/atterong)
(machonery fa//s so/ent)
Jim?
- Morning, sunshine.
- You freak. Why are you doing this?!
- Why the heck not?
- You'll never get away with it.
Oh, no?
What are you gonna do about it?
Hurt me, from down there?
You just give me the chance!
Nope.
I don't think you got it in ya. Not yet.
Yeah? Just try me, you bastard!
Adoos, Maggie.
Oh, hey, uh... By the way, this structure
looks like it's about ready to go.
I wouldn't make any sudden moves,
if l were you.
Are you still there, you son of a bitch?!
Is anybody here?
Can anybody help?
(/aughter)
Shit.
(creakong)
No!
(starts engone)
(gronds gears)
(onstrumenta/ country musoc onjukebox)
What kind of weapons do you have?
Forget it.
I need a phone.
Got a ladies' room?
(chuck/es)
- Fred?
- You've reached Johnson & Esser...
(doa/s)
Hello?
- Amy? Amy, is this you, honey?
- Yup.
It's your Aunt Maggie.
Is your daddy home?
He's not here. (hangs up)
(man) Sheroff's offiice.
Yes, um... I have information
regarding Captain Esteridge.
Hold on one second.
Let me get the sheriff.
Sheriff?
This is Sheriff Castillo.
I'm the one... I mean, l was there.
Where are you?
Are you all right?
What about your partner?
- My... my boyfriend Jim is dead.
- /'m sorry.
Esteridge was dead when we got there.
Wait, wait!
I don't know that you did anything.
But l do know you're scared.
Why don't wejust meet and ta/k, OK?
- Oh, yeah. Sure.
- You have my word on that.
Just think about
how this looks, you runnin' and all.
We'// c/eara// thos up
before ot gets any worse.
He//o?
- You sto// there?
- OK. I'll meet you.
I'm... I'm at the Lone Wolf Trading Post.
/ know the p/ace.
/'// meet you there on about 15 monutes.
- Alone, right?
- A/one.
We just got another call. Something bad's
happening at the Trading Post.
Let's go.
(doorbangs)
Thanks.
Hello?
(screams)
Agh!
(# "You Must Be An Ange/")
(doorbangs)
What can l get you today, missy?
Go ahead. Take a load off. Have a seat.
I'm really glad you could
come by and visit us today.
Now then, what do we have?
Some beefjerky. Oh! Scratch that.
We're out of the damned jerky.
Just gonna have to have beans today.
Why? Why are you doin' this?
Sometimes you just get
tired of watchin' television.
So l decided to take up this cookin'.
Everything all right here?
- Where's Nathan?
- He's out back. He's coolin' off.
- Why don't you take a seat?
- Get outta here, now.
Go!
Damn, woman. Do you know
how hard it is to build a customer base
in this kind of a town?
Turn around.
Can l at least get me some pie
before you chop me up
in front of your sheriff friend
who, l suspect, will be here momentarily.
Who do you think
they're gonna believe, farm girl?
- What are you?
- Watch now.
Agh!
Ohh! Sheriff, look what she done to me.
And l use that finger, too.
Bam! Kickin' it up a notch.
See, l just called the sheriff myself
a couple of minutes ago.
Yeah... Problem with the counterman.
Seems some crazy farm girl came in
and messed him up real good.
(sorens)
Ma'am, if you're in there,
l'm glad that you are.
I need you to come on out now.
I know we had an understanding.
Since then we got a report of trouble
out here, so l got to treat it that way.
He sounds like a reasonable fella.
Come out. Everything will be OK.
We know about the trouble
with your boyfriend Jim.
Sounds like he's tryin'
to work with ya there.
You are not gettin' away again,
you sorry son of a bitch.
Maggie... I don't keep bullets
in that particular gun. Safety thing.
(c/ock)
I do, however, keep this one down here...
fully loaded and prepared at all times.
Catch.
- Lyle, get around back.
- You got it.
You freeze now!
The woman's crazy. You've gotta
arrest her. Look what she did to me.
Hold your fire.
Freeze!
That's her. She's the one, right there.
She did this to me.
Drop your gun. Do it!
She's psycho. I know it.
I ran to get out.
You arrested me.
You recognise this?
Yes... It's mine.
He took it. Jim.
Well... Hm?
That man's name is Jack, Maggie.
Jim's your boyfriend, and he's dead.
He told us his name was Jim.
You don't believe any of this, do you?
I don't know, Maggie.
- Who the hell is he?
- You don't know?
I have no idea.
Now, Jack... When you went into the café,
she was behind the counter?
Yes, sir. I thought
she worked there, you know, and...
Then she started actin' all nervous
and her eyes started dartin' around.
I don't know.
She was just acting kinda creepy.
- And you didn't see the counterman?
- No. No, sir. Not then.
- And she pulled a gun on you?
- Yeah. Well, yeah...
She told me to come behind the counter.
That's when l saw the counterman.
Well, the counterman's body.
Then she told me to move it for her. I said
"No way. I ain't movin' no dead body."
I ain't touchin' no dead body, layin' there,
blood on the floor. I can't do it.
- And then she cut you?
- She was holdin' the gun to my head.
Then she pulled out a tomahawk,
of all things,
and chopped off my finger.
All l wanted was some pie.
All l wanted was a piece of pie.
Yeah. They're, uh, good pies.
What happened when the officers arrived?
Well, um...
They talked real nice to her.
Then she just opened fire on 'em.
Right through the window.
Busted it, too.
- Are you sure she fired first?
- Yes, sir. Most definitely.
That's when you ran?
Like a red-headed stepchild.
I had to get outta Dodge.
One unbalanced lady. She cut off
my finger, turned it into fried bread.
I hope she burns in hell for
what she did to me and those officers.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for the language.
It's just the way l feel.
Thank you, Jack.
Deputy, would you uncuff him, please?
Ah! Whoo.
Thank you very much.
Hey, um... You think l can get me
one of them bear-claw thingies?
Sure. Of course.
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much.
Scum.
Scum in a real pretty wrapper.
I don't know. The boyfriend might have
cracked and drove her over the edge.
Might have cracked?
Did you read the report sent in
by his sheriff boss back in lowa?
I just don't see this woman
cuttin' off a guy's finger like that.
For God's sake, Sheriff, add it up.
She had the gun
that killed the people in that trailer.
That same gun killed
Mrs Esteridge and Jess.
Then she shows up drivin'
the dead trucker's 18-wheeler?
The girl had gunpowder on her hands!
The weapon that was used to ko//
Nathan had herpronts a// overot.
And she odentofiied the neck/ace
that we found on Jess's cruoser.
Fona//y, we have an eyewotness
who she kodnapped back on the café.
The poors/ob's on/y /ucky
that she dodn't ko// hom too.
She snapped all right.
Look, Lieutenant...
She's got no record. She's got her own
crop-dusting business. She seems...
You just think
that a woman couldn't do this.
Ain't that right?
Well, that, Sheriff,
is prejudice right there.
And it ain't fair.
The state of Texas just executed a woman
who killed two people with a pickaxe.
And, besodes, no guy's gonna
cut offhos own fiinger. No way.
We have enough evodence
that the peop/e here wo// start cheerong
ofwe ko// her our own damned se/ves/
Yeah, l know.
That's what bothers me.
- Where is he?
- In the hospital, being tended to.
- Don't worry. He'll be around to testify.
- Don't leave him alone. He'll get away.
He's the one who did all this.
He is the victim, darlin', that poor man.
Around here, we don't like people who
shoot cops and butcher Texas Rangers.
Now shut your mouth.
- He's gonna come back. He's not through.
- But you sure the heck are.
One question.
up at Esteridge's, were either
of you ever up in the hayloft?
No.
Wait.
Yeah?
Do you believe me at all?
Yeah, l'll be there, Maggie.
Try not to worry. I'll talk to the judge.
We'll have plenty of time
to figure this all out.
Thank you.
Like hell he will.
She's runnin' low. I'm just gonna take her
round back and tank her up for ya.
Damn it. Hurry it on up, Lyle.
You wouldn't happen to have any of them
bear-claw things on you, would you?
Don't do anything l wouldn't do.
Maggie... Please. Drop the gun.
It's him. It's him. He's here.
Drop the gun, Maggie.
I can get you help. That's all you need.
It's all under control, Sheriff.
You can take a load off.
(screams)
(c/ockong)
(uronatong)
That's a nice truck you got there.
Yeah, l guess.
- I'd better phone the sheriff.
- I think you'd better.
She did what?
I know who she is.
We will get your plane back.
No. No.
I'm right behind you.
There you are.
Son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch!
Shit! Shit!
(gauge b/eepong)
(engone sputters)
That's my girl.
(e/ectrocoty crack/es)
What's goin' on, farm girl?
Jim told me about that poor girl
and the way that she died.
So l thought that maybe
you would like a taste of that yourself.
I don't know what you're talkin' about.
It wasn't me.
It was someone exactly like you.
- Don't go talkin' all crazy on me now.
- Who the hell are you?
I was just drivin' my gasoline truck
when you came along.
I said, who the hell are you?!
What?
And spoil all the fun?
Goodbye, Jack.
You don't got it in ya, Maggie. Not yet.
No!
Freeze!
Argh! Argh!
Thank God you fellas are here.
She's crazy.
She cut off my finger,
knocked me out and tied me up.
The bitch won't quit! Look at her!
No!
I can't tell you how much
l thank you fellas of the law.
No! He'll kill you!
Thank you so much.
I appreciate you guys helping me out.
No!
Are you still scared?
What a shame.
We came so close.
And l thought we had an understanding.
I'm not scared.
I just don't wanna get burned again.