Get out of here!
Get off!
Excuse me.
I was expecting
to be met.
Good morning,
Truscott.
I am Belansai.
Welcome
to our country.
He's a bright chap.
He'll be the head man
of his Longhouse in two years.
John Truscott.
Henry Bullard.
I'm the governor
of this district,
but you just
think of me as God.
Hop aboard.
You've got far too good
a degree for this job.
What are you running away from?
Your debts?
Your family?
Or a woman?
No, no debts.
No woman.
My mother
died two years ago.
My father was killed
at Passchendaele, so...
Well, why in God's name
are you here?
My father was
a district officer out here.
William C. Truscott?
Ahhh.
He'd drawn up a plan
to bring education to the Iban
which the governor general
had approved,
but then he had
to go back to the war...
and it never happened.
And you've brought
this plan with you, have you?
Yes, I think it's our duty
to educate primitive people.
God, you sound
a sanctimonious little prig.
Still, you're young.
Sarawak'll knock
it out of you.
Famous,
you lazy bastard!
Look at the state
of this place.
Bring Truscott tea and gadgets
double quick.
Come on.
Chibi, chibi, chibi.
It's got bugs in there.
He's the best cook
in Sarawak.
Though strictly speaking
he's still on parole.
What did he do?
Oh, he hacked some damn fool
rickshaw driver to death.
But you should
taste his meringues.
- Shouldn't he be in--
- Now, tomorrow,
you've an invitation
from your local Longhouse,
the Gawa Kenyalong.
So Belansai'll
pick you up.
The feast to honor
the war god
where they take the giant hornbill
statue down from the rafters.
Oh, God.
You read-- books.
I'm afraid they insist
upon it at university.
Do they?
Has it come
to that now?
Yes, I'll--
I'll see you
in a day or so.
Excuse me.
Excuse me...
What's my job?
This is my father,
Melaka.
He is head man
of the Longhouse.
This is rice wine.
Ah. Um...
I won't drink
on duty, thanks.
To refuse is an insult.
Left, right.
It's chibi,
chibi, chibi!
It is a... very ancient
tribal dance.
Oh, no, um... no.
Very kind
of you to offer,
but I think I'll give it
a miss this time round.
You must make us
entertainment.
A song? A dance?
A poem?
Perhaps all three.
"The sand of the desert
is sodden red,
Red with the wreck
of the ranks that broke.
The Gatling's jammed
and the Colonel dead,
And the regiment blind
with dust and smoke.
The river of death
has brimmed his banks,
And England's far
and honor's a name,
But the voice of a schoolboy
rallies the ranks,
'Play up!
Play up
and play the game!'"
" Da-dum-dum-dum "
" Da-da-da-da,
Dum-dum-dum-dum "
" Da-da-da-da "
Oh, Truscott, you are very
funny Englishman.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
The dancing is over.
We go to sleep now.
You deliberately dropped me
in it, didn't you?
You know I made a complete
fool of myself?
They like a man
who makes them laugh.
Iban society is based
on heavy drinking,
violent sport
and practical jokes.
Just think of it as
English public school
without the buggery.
I'm on a mission to civilize,
not to entertain.
The mining concessions
at Kera Pulau
have been trespassing
outside their boundaries.
Your local Longhouse
got to some Chinese miners
before I did.
You're going to have
to bring in their heads.
What?
Well...
we limit the areas where
the mining concerns can--
No, no, no.
You said...
you said "their heads."
Well, yes.
The Iban have
cut them off.
What?
Ahh.
My dear.
This is Selima.
She's going
to live with you.
As what?
Uh... she performs
wifely duties.
Oh yeah?
What... sewing?
She performs wifely duties
in the bedroom.
- For God's sakes, man.
- I sleep with you.
We expect you to know
the language within six months.
Selima's what's known around here
as a "sleeping dictionary."
Sleep...
My mother was also
sleeping dictionary.
That's why I speak
the King English.
There's nothing like bed
for learning a language.
It's the only reason
I speak Portuguese.
No, look, poor girl.
- She was just-- picked?
- I pick you.
And she's really choosy.
She turned down
my last two cadet officers.
Listen, your contract
forbids you
to marry
for three years.
Three years can be
very lonely.
And after three years?
We'll probably all be dead,
so why worry?
Oh, dear.
Listen...
you'll go home
on leave to England
and you'll come back with
a rosy-cheeked little wife.
Selima will go home
to her Longhouse
speaking
fluent English.
Oh, damn it, man,
it's worked for centuries.
There's no reason
why you should be different.
No, I'm sorry, no. No.
I know you think
I'm just some young idiot,
but if I don't follow what
I think's right, what else is there?
Then you'd better find another way
to learn the damn language.
Because if a so-called
educated man
can't speak the language
of the people he governs,
he's no right to be here!
Fine, maybe she can stay as...
just a dictionary?
- If she doesn't mind, that is.
- What?
Mind not sleeping with you?
I'm sure she'll survive.
She said yes.
What else did she say?
You'll have to learn Iban
and find out, won't you?
I'd stand back
if I were you.
Ha ha!
Ants.
Yes, ants.
Thank you very much.
Good night.
You say no,
she get very angry.
Rain always stop
in morning.
Sleep tight and don't
let the bedbugs bite.
Chinese heads
as per request.
Thank you.
As you know, the Longhouse
will be fined.
Beyond that, there will
be no further action.
Monkey heads.
We make a joke on you.
Maybe I'll make
a joke on you
and bring a detachment
of colonial police up the river.
I want those heads delivered
to my bungalow by tomorrow morning
or I will confiscate your--
your pigs.
Master?
I bring you someone.
This is Jasmine.
He is assistant chef.
What do we need
an assistant chef for?
- He assist you.
- Me?
He assist you in...
private way.
Is this one of your relatives?
No, no, no.
He very clean.
He come from
Englishman on coast
who too old
for all that now.
What?
Oh, good God.
Get him out of--
No, get him out now!
- But, master--
- Get him out of here!
And Selima,
bring me a whiskey.
What are you doing?!
I'm not servant.
Fine.
You don't have to be a servant.
You're fired!
Dismissed!
You cannot fire me because
I am not yours to fire.
I fire you.
You are dismissed.
Make no attempt
to follow me.
- What are you doing?
- I live here now.
You can't live there.
Then I will live
in the jungle.
I like the jungle.
No, listen. You must go
back to the Longhouse.
They will
laugh at her.
They will say she choose you
but you no have her.
- Is that true?
- No.
They will say you
not sleep with her
because she too
pig ugly.
Listen, I don't
think you're ugly.
I think you're
very beautiful.
I don't sleep with you
because of my beliefs.
Because... the spirits
of my country forbid it.
You want to sleep with me
but you forbid by your spirit?
Yes, you could say that.
I will go to my tree now.
Wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Perhaps we could
have another try.
If you're willing
to re-employ me, that is.
I will give you
one more chance.
Hey!
I want a word
with you.
Last night you got
completely drunk again.
My other masters,
they fine me
one week pay
if I blind drunk,
two week pay if I blind,
legless drunk.
I blind drunk two time
a month regular,
so very cheap cook.
Fair enough.
Wait.
Do you play croquet?
No.
Help me reload,
would you?
I'm clearing the jungle
for a croquet lawn
for when Cecil,
my daughter, comes out.
It's much quicker than
a working party from the jail.
Aggie Bullard,
Henry's wife.
You must be Truscott.
How are you getting on
with Henry's damn fool tests?
I think next
I have to wrestle a crocodile.
Sleeping dictionary
shaping up all right?
Truscott!
Us women don't know anything
about all of that.
- Truscott!
- And for heaven's sake,
bed her or the Iban'll think
there's something wrong
with you down below.
Excuse me.
Re-group!
Sorry?
You're not picking up
the language very fast, are you?
And where are those
Chinese heads?!
You are in the bathroom.
I am in...?
the bedroom.
What do I do?
I...
I say good night
to my father.
Where do you go?
Bedroom.
Bedroom...
bedroom.
W-what next?
I-I go to sleep.
Do English people
have dreams at night?
Sometimes, yeah.
Are we really
that strange?
Have you ever
sleep with a woman?
I won't
till I get married.
That's our way.
But when you marry
you'll be very bad at sex
and your wife
will be unhappy.
I'll take evening classes,
I promise.
I've never met anyone...
even a little like you.
Whyever did you
choose me?
Your dance is not
the dance of an Englishman.
Good night.
Yes.
I thought you didn't like
our education.
You want to educate us
like your father did?
You were educated because
you're the chief's son.
Shouldn't others have
the same opportunity?
William, William,
Henry, Henry,
Richard, John, Henry,
Edward, Edward,
Richard, Henry,
Henry, Edward,
Edward, Richard,
Henry, Henry, Edward--
Mary, Elizabeth,
James, Charles,
Charles, James, William,
George, George, George, George,
William, Victoria,
Edward, George, Edward, George.
The kings of England.
And why do I need
to know that?
The mission school
tries to turn us
into little Englishmen.
They didn't do a very good job
with you, did they?
You missed Queen Anne,
by the way.
You missed King Stephen.
I hear when you were young,
you were a champion at
the underwater battles.
When I was young?
I am still champion
of 1 0 Longhouses.
Yes, they say you can
beat any girl on the river.
Will you
challenge me then?
How you--
how you do that?
Some Englishmen
can breathe underwater
through their ears.
I wonder if I might
have a word about...
those heads.
It's lovely
workmanship.
I'll add those
to the collection.
The ants eaten
your dinner jacket yet?
I think there's
an arm or two left.
Good.
My daughter Cecilia
is arriving for Christmas.
First class honors degree
at Oxford.
You'd like her.
Come to dinner.
Oh!
How drunk is he?
Blind, legless, daft,
sick, smelly drunk.
My mother
read that to me.
My father
read it to me.
Do you remember
your father?
He go back to England
when I am four.
My dad died
when I was four.
"Deep, deep
beneath the sea
where the water is
clear as purest glass
Iies the palace
of the Sea King.
There behind its...
walls of coral
and roof of cockleshells
lives a little mermaid."
You can read English.
I remember it
by my heart.
I made him read it
many time.
Write a word from it.
"Deep."
Now you.
"Hand."
"Arm."
Neck.
Lips.
Breast.
I-I'm sorry.
That was too quick,
wasn't it?
You teach me English,
I'll teach you this.
School is not finished.
Not quite the education
my father had in mind.
Why do you always go?
For sleeping dictionary,
it is proper.
For the Iban,
if a man and a woman wake up
together five nights in a row,
they are engaged.
You don't want that,
do you?
Cecilia's got a degree
in anthropology, you know?
She did her thesis
on the Iban.
- Really?
- Mmm.
Why did you choose
the Iban to study?
I lived here until I was five.
Till Mother and Father
couldn't stand me any longer
and shipped me off to school.
But I always
remembered them.
The way you'd never see them arrive,
but then suddenly there they'd be,
standing beside you
as if they'd
been there since...
time began.
Although, for them, of course,
time only began 53 years ago.
- Really?
- Yes, the year Krakatoa exploded.
- That's their year zero.
- Is that true?
How the deuce
do you know that?
- Well, I listen.
- Do you now?
Well, I can't wait to get
stuck in and meet the Iban.
Shipperly's taken over
from Teague--
chap I told you about.
Went doolally
and ate his own toes.
I'll tell you something
I bet you don't know.
Back in Victorian times,
the young officers coming out here
were given a young woman
from the local head-hunting tribes
to share their bed...
so they could learn
the language quickly.
I hardly think so, darling.
Now you are having us on,
aren't you?
No, that's true.
I've heard tell of it
from a very old Iban.
- See?
- Well...
if it did exist,
I'm sure it was purely
a matter of convenience
and no...
higher feelings
were involved.
- Don't see why.
- Surely you can't seriously believe
that a primitive
head-huntress
and an English officer
could experience love.
Not love, maybe,
but I'm sure they could
feel a great deal.
Whatever an Englishman felt,
he would never
let that get in the way
of his duty
to the local people.
My Iban wouldn't
think less of an officer--
"My Iban"?
They're not your Iban.
They might be God's,
but they're certainly not yours.
We've got enough bloody dictators
in Europe, thank you.
- All I'm saying--
- And all I'm saying,
is that an English officer
would never let
his country down.
Nor his family.
Would he, Truscott?
No, sir.
So is she pretty?
Well, she's fairly pretty.
But does she have wings?
What happened to
the spirits of your country?
They grew old and tired and packed
their bags and left for England.
This is a land dispute
between two Longhouses.
It's fiendishly
complicated.
You must be sick of me
following you around.
No, I know how
interested you are.
At least this time we escaped
the dreaded Shipperly.
He's harmless, but...
he's like all men
who've been to an all-male
school and college.
The only women they're comfortable
with are their mothers.
He talks to me like
I'm a Labrador.
I went to an all-male school
and an all-male college.
Then something
must've changed you.
Well...
yes.
Being out here, I imagine.
So have you
sorted out this dispute?
Yes, I think so,
yes.
See, it's impossible
to sort out the argument.
So if I decide
for one side or the other,
it'll just seem
unfair to them.
Pull!
Would you mind?
That's it, perfect. Thank you.
Thank you.
Isn't she amazing?
What did she say?
There's not a precise
English translation for that one.
Cecil, these children
love having their photo--
She's wonderful.
I wish I looked like her.
Hands higher, please.
That's it.
Perfect.
Cecil, I don't think
she wants her photograph taken.
- Just a couple more.
- Truscott!
Go and see what's happening
down there, will you?
Ask her to keep up
that fierce expression, please.
- Cecil--
- Truscott!
I told you to go and see
what the devil's happening!
She won't understand.
She's Yakata.
You can tell by
the turquoise bracelet.
I studied them.
She was bleeding
through her skin.
Come away
and wash your hands.
There's a dozen more dead bodies
turned up at Laksai,
50 miles out
of their territory.
I'd better go up river
and have a look, hadn't I?
No, you hadn't!
It's dangerous enough up there
without an epidemic.
That's my job.
They'll have your head
as soon as look at you.
Besides he doesn't
speak the language.
Well,
I'll take Selima.
She speaks
half a dozen languages.
And Belansai, no one's
going to tangle with him.
Send that idiot Shipperly.
A few poisoned darts
might liven him up.
I'll set out
tomorrow morning, shall I?
Aggie,
I can't send Shipperly.
You said yourself
the man's an idiot...
If you're about to be killed,
at least stay for dinner.
Terrific girl, Cecil.
Isn't she?
Absolutely, yeah.
If you want a child
properly educated,
you've got to send them
back home.
But you can't be
in two places at once.
And I thought
it was my duty...
to stay with Henry.