"Super Collider:
U.S. Government
Accelerator Project, Texas"
Sorry, pal.
The exact time is 16:44...
and as you can plainly see...
the subject of retroactive experiment
number 12 is plainly deceased.
Since my first 11 attempts at
this experiment proved unsuccessful...
this will be
my last opportunity...
being as the idiots
at the Pentagon...
will be shutting this place down
completely come Monday morning.
This tape will provide proof
that I have been able...
to briefly
reverse the flow of time.
Whatever subject
passes through this machine...
will have total recollection
of all that has happened.
I, however, will have no memory
of these events.
The exact time is 16:44...
and as you can plainly see...
the subject of retroactive experiment
number 12 is plainly deceased.
Since my first 11 attempts at
this experiment proved unsuccessful...
this will be
my last opportunity...
being as the idiots
at the Pentagon...
will be shutting this place down
completely come Monday morning.
Now, this tape
will provide proof...
not only to my detractors
but also to myself.
- I did it.
- Because if I am right...
and I can briefly
reverse the flow of time...
I will have no memory
of these events.
I did it.
I did it!
Oh, my God.
Hey, man!
How're you doing, brother?
Look at them, man.
They like to pay for these, don't they?
- Nobody followed you here?
- I'll be back.
Whoa. My money, Frank.
Where's my money?
How the hell am I supposed to give you
money when I gotta go get it?
I've got no money on me.
That's why we're in this business.
- Have I ever screwed you over?
- Yeah, you have.
That was high school.
I was drunk. Leave me alone.
I need my money.
I'm gonna make you as rich as shit
four foot up a bull's ass.
Come on, man!
What are you doing to me?
Put the goddamn gun away.
- I need my money.
- I know!
- Thirty minutes.
- Thirty minutes and I'll be right back.
Take that thing away from me.
You're gonna hurt somebody with that.
Thirty minutes!
You have yourself
a little cup of coffee.
By the time you're done with it,
I'll be back with the cash.
The city of Chicago today
is in mourning...
in the wake of this weekend's
tragic hostage situation...
at the Federal Building.
Lead negotiator Karen Warren...
has officially resigned from her
position with the police department.
Stop! Hey!
Thanks a bunch, pal!
Not good.
What was that, honey?
My car. Looks like
I may need a little help.
What the hell
happened to that sign?
That's Rayanne. Don't mind her.
She's just shy.
Yeah. Looks like
you got a problem...
in this general area
right here.
Any particular type of problem,
you think?
I don't know.
I can take you up the road
a click to a buddy of mine.
He's got a tow truck
all his own.
Hell, come on.
Frank's the name.
Throw yourself in the rear.
I'll fix ya up.
- Isn't that right, Rayanne?
- Whatever you want.
Hi, I'm Karen. How far
do you suppose it is?
Oh, I don't know.
Let me think now.
I'd say five, ten miles.
Hell, who knows?
This is Texas, right?
- You from around these parts?
- Yeah, I used to be.
- Down by Galveston way.
- Is that right?
You sure do talk
like a city girl.
Polish these for me.
The funniest thing
happened to me today.
I was in the break room
getting a cup of coffee...
and there was this woman...
Kim.
She's some kind of secretary
or something.
And she says...
She goes like this.
She says, "Frank,
that's a good-looking belt buckle."
And I don't know.
This just popped into my head.
Don't ask me how.
I just said to her...
Guess what I said.
Guess what I say to her.
Somebody please just
guess what I said.
I don't know.
What'd you say?
I say, "lt'll look a lot
better pressed against your forehead."
That just popped into my head!
What's wrong? You don't wanna experience
my razor-sharp wit back there?
I guess I've just been away too long.
Missed that old Texas humor.
I know what'll cheer you up.
You like country music?
- No, not really.
- What?
I suppose it's one of the reasons
I left Texas in the first place.
It's made in America for Americans.
You're not un-American, are ya?
No, you might say dealing with
Americans is what I'm trained to do.
Don't tell me you're a cop.
Don't tell me that.
Close. Psychologist.
Shrink, huh? All right.
I got an assignment for you.
What's the name
of that book of yours?
If you really want
to know it...
It provides a framework
to work out...
what you might do if you
could go back and change your life.
Sounds like a bunch of bullshit
to me, if you don't mind me saying.
It's just
therapeutic role-playing.
Like me play Tarzan,
you Jane?
Shit! Where the hell
you suppose he popped up from?
Goddamn it!
Bullshit!
I already got three goddamn tickets.
My insurance is gonna go sky-high.
Whoa! Stay right where you are.
I didn't ask you
to get out of the car.
Officer,
just stretching my legs.
No crime in that.
I wanna see your license
and registration.
Yes, sir, but you gotta tell me
one thing first.
What in the hell
did I do wrong?
You were doing 78 miles an hour
in a 55-mile zone...
is what the hell
you were doing wrong.
Come on. Really?
I can assure you, Officer...
that that would be
highly unusual for me.
Because I am like this
with the law.
Just give me your license
and registration.
Yes, sir.
Goddamn bitch
shrank my jeans.
Here you go, sir.
You wanna tell me who you got
travelling with you, Mr. Lloyd?
Them?
Them two's my women.
Bigamy is against the law.
Well...
that's why I ain't married.
Keeping it legal.
Why don't you
get back in your car?
Yes, sir.
Not a problem there. I'll just
sit there behind the wheel.
It looks like there's gonna be
a slight delay...
while the good officer
clears matters up.
Maybe I should ask
for a ride from the trooper.
- Get outta your hair.
- No, I wouldn't hear of it.
You just hold on.
Hell.
We only got
about a mile to go.
Well, except for six
previous speeding violations...
seems you are
a law-abiding citizen.
I told ya.
I'm just gonna
write you up for 70.
Sign by that "X."
Try and slow down.
'Cause I'll be watching you.
Thank you very much, sir.
Asshole!
- Honey...
- Shut up!
Goddamned bullshit!
You just keep your eyes
on this, asshole.
Look out!
Christ, I could've knocked that
son of a bitch back to Chihuahua.
So, baby...
What the hell are you
so tense about?
Come on. Lighten up.
Say something.
Our guest is gonna think you're
a damn mute if you don't say something.
Go on.
I just wish that you would
control your temper is all.
- That's bullshit!
- You wanted me to say something.
And the first thing that comes
out of your mouth...
is some kind of criticism of me,
is that it?
- No...
- Shut up, woman.
Goddamn women.
Can't live with 'em,
can't blow their heads off. Shit.
Well, this must be it.
Nope, not yet. I'm just stopping here
for a well-deserved beverage.
Damn! I'm as thirsty
as a chipmunk hung out to dry.
Hey. You girls wanna dabble
in a little beverage?
Not for me.
Can't say I didn't try.
Don't want you yapping
behind my back now.
Damn, it's good
to be in America!
Wake up, Sam.
The man is here.
- How'd it go?
- Goddamn went great.
He's always gotta come here
and get his beer.
You like that Australian beer?
He's always gotta get that.
Says it reminds him of his dad.
He took off for Australia
and left him when he was ten.
You know you don't
have to stay with him.
Sometimes I just wanna take a knife
and cut out his heart.
Honey, you don't wanna
do something like that.
I'm gonna give you the number
of a woman's shelter.
Call 'em any time.
They can help.
Yep.
Look what I got here.
This is the mother lode.
- What the hell...
- I don't know what these do...
but they sure pay for them.
I can't program my VCR.
You may wanna use
that phone over there.
Here.
Take care of yourself.
Don't you worry about me.
I'll be fine.
- There you go.
- Gimme that!
That's more cash
than I've ever seen.
Thanks for the ride.
Freeze!
Do either of you know where we could
find a place to camp around here?
- I'm sorry. I'm not from around here.
- Down the road about ten miles.
Ten miles? Great.
Thanks a lot.
I'm going to Mexico
with my Rayanne.
I hope it works out.
You watch the water down there.
I know that water's
supposed to be rough.
- Hey, Frank.
- Give you the shits, they say.
Frank, come here. Remember that guy
I told ya about?
He gave me these.
Bullshit.
It's bullshit, Sam.
- You show these to anybody else?
- No, Frank. That's your girl.
Bullshit!
You show these to somebody else?
- No, I didn't!
- That's bullshit!
Think I must've
dropped my wallet.
- Fuck you.
- You show anyone else those pictures?
Goddamn it!
Don't worry about it, asshole!
What the hell...
What are you doing?
Rayanne, pour me a beer
would you?
Would you stop, please?
I was getting out there.
There's a tow truck back there.
Maybe you didn't realize...
Will somebody please tell me
why is it...
that women can change their minds
whenever the mood strikes them?
We all have moments
where we rethink choices.
- It's natural.
- Natural.
Natural pain in the ass.
You want a beer?
- You sure you don't want a beer?
- Yes.
- You do want a beer.
- No.
That's what I mean!
Yes, no, yes, no, yes, no.
Do you or do you not
want a goddamned beer?
No, I don't want
one of your goddamned beers!
Why don't you shut the hell up
and leave me alone?
Drink it.
I'll leave you alone.
Where are we going?
You see, Karen, my wife Rayanne here,
she seems to think...
that I'm one of those bad to the bone,
unrepentant assholes.
I think she brings it out in me.
What do you think?
It seems to me that you two
can work it out.
Is that what you think?
I think it's a little too late for that.
It's way too late.
I know now that
it'll never work out.
'Cause, you see...
I've had a sudden,
unforeseen realization...
that has left me saddened...
and terribly hurt.
What are you talking about?
It occurred to me back there that
I had seen that pickup truck before.
Maybe, Rayanne...
you might have
an understanding going on.
Come on!
This is Frank.
You can tell me the truth.
Tell me.
Lie! You're always
lying to me!
Sam...
was thoughtful enough to show me
some photographs of you.
I was shocked. I've never
seen you like that before.
I don't know what you mean.
Talking about the fucking beaner
you've been fucking!
That's what I'm talking about!
- He's gonna kill me!
- Look at me.
She's right.
I am gonna kill her.
Shit's what it is.
Talk to me.
Turn around
and talk about this.
We can work this out.
Come on.
You're a big guy.
You don't need a gun.
Put the gun down.
Open the door! Shit.
Here we go.
Shit!
Oh, my God!
Thank God!
- The door. Is it locked?
- It locks automatically.
You sure?
Is it bulletproof?
- I suppose so.
- We have to call the police.
This man, he just
shot his wife.
Relax. Nobody can
get through that door.
You don't understand.
The man is a killer and he's after me.
Relax. You're hurt. Let me
get something to clean that cut.
No, listen to me.
What is your name?
Brian.
Okay, Brian,
do you understand me?
You have to call the police now,
you got me?
I have a woman here
who's apparently been injured.
Hold on. Shit!
Undo.
Damn!
Oh, my God.
And there was this woman.
She's some kind of secretary
or something.
She sees my belt buckle,
and she says...
She goes like this.
She says, "Frank...
That's a good-looking belt buckle."
And I don't know.
This just popped into my head.
Don't ask me how.
I just said to her.
Guess what I say.
Somebody guess
what I said to her.
I don't know.
What'd you say?
I said, "lt'd look even better with
your forehead pressed against it."
That just popped into my head!
What's wrong? You don't wanna experience
my razor-sharp wit back there?
I'll just listen to some music.
- You like...
- I hate country music.
How can you hate country music?
I just do.
What's the name of that book?
- Psychotherapy.
- Is that right?
It provides a framework to work out
what you might do...
if you could go back
and change your life.
- Well...
- I know it sounds like bullshit to you.
You took the words
right out of my mouth.
It's not.
It's therapeutic role-playing.
You like that role-playing thing,
do ya?
Just like Tarzan and Jane.
Right, Frank?
You and I are connected.
You are reading my mind.
If you don't mind me saying, you're
driving too fast for your own good.
I bet it feels like 55.
Feels like it.
But it won't seem like it
to that cop back there.
What cop?
Shit! Why didn't you tell me?
Goddamn son of a bitch!
I already got three goddamn tickets.
My insurance is gonna go sky-high.
Whoa! Stay right there, mister.
I did not ask you
to exit your vehicle.
Officer,
just stretching my legs.
I wanna see your license
and registration.
Yes, sir, but you gotta tell me
one thing first.
What in the hell
did I do wrong?
Doing 78 miles an hour
in a 55-mile zone...
- What are you doing?
- The gun. Where is it?
- What are you talking about?
- Frank's gun. Where is it?
He never goes anywhere
without that gun.
Shit.
Them two's my women.
Bigamy is against the law.
Officer, could you tell me
where the nearest gas station is?
Ma'am, would you please
return to your vehicle?
Get in the car.
- Ma'am.
- Listen to that officer...
and go back into that car.
You see, I had a problem
with my car...
He's got a gun, Officer!
Freeze!
Officer, I'm with the Chicago Police
Department. This is a wanted man.
That's bullshit!
I got a license to carry that gun.
Freeze!
Get off me, bitch!
Rayanne, stop!
My baby!
God!
Shit! You bitch!
What the hell you doing here?
Who the hell are you?
Look what you did to my wife!
Shit!
What the hell you want?
Don't move!
Bastard!
- What the hell...
- Drive on. Get the police.
Don't! She's a psycho killer!
She'll kill us all!
- Bullshit!
- She's crazy!
She just killed my wife.
She killed the trooper.
- Wife?
- He killed her.
She killed my wife! She kicked me!
She's trying to kill me!
She's a psycho hitchhiker!
- Shut up!
- She's a liar!
I need your help.
Get the police.
Help me!
She's a psycho bitch!
Freeze! Or I will shoot you,
I swear to God. Shit!
You ever use
one of those guns before?
Just give me a reason.
It could be outta ammo.
That's very funny, but you're
not dealing with Rayanne.
Put your hands
behind your head.
It's a lot of responsibility,
pulling that trigger.
That'll change your life forever.
Maybe I've been
looking for a change.
Shit!
Goddamn it! You bitch!
Hold it!
Mister, you got it wrong.
Help me! She shot me, goddamn it!
She's a killer!
Go call the police.
I'll watch him.
What are you talking about?
She's a murderer!
- Just go! I can handle this.
- Are you crazy too?
- She's trying to kill me!
- Go. Shut up!
- Murdering bastard.
- I didn't kill nobody. She shot me.
- Give 'em to me.
- What are you talking about?
You know what,
you stinking bastard.
The computer chips.
Give 'em to me.
Shit. Why didn't you just ask?
The copper took 'em from me.
He must've known I had 'em.
He's got 'em.
Stupid fucker.
Goddamn you!
Shit!
Have a little car trouble, honey?
- Call 911.
- 911 what?
The police! Shit!
Phone don't work.
Up!
You and I need to have
a little conversation.
- You put that gun down right now.
- Okay, Frank.
Put it down!
Come on.
Come on, baby.
I kinda like you.
Where are you?
Feisty.
Spicy.
A girl like you,
I'd take out to dinner.
Where the hell are you?
What're you coming into my life for?
What the hell you want?
Shit, I'm so sorry
I gotta kill you.
I'd like to take you home
to my papa.
He'd like to meet you.
Bitch, where are you?
I tell you what, girl.
I'll be nice to you
if you're nice to me.
How's that?
Call me crazy, but somehow
I don't quite believe you.
Get down!
What are you gonna do, baby?
Shoot me again?
- Don't tempt me.
- I know.
This is about you taking hold
of your life, codependent no more.
- I'm from Venus, you're from Mars.
- Shut up!
Move!
You surprise me, ma'am.
I got a few tricks
up my sleeve too.
What the hell's going on?
Who is she?
I don't know.
Who the hell are you?
Just another Texas girl.
Bullshit! You've been
sticking your nose in my business!
Nobody knows my business.
Not even Rayanne, who is dead now,
thank you very much.
How the hell am I
supposed to live without her?
You're pathetic!
Anyway, you knew
she was cheating on you.
How the hell you know that?
She tell you that?
Who was she doing?
Jesse? Who is it?
Cut it out.
Take it somewhere else.
Tell me!
I wanna know right now!
Cut it out!
Take it somewhere else!
Take her out in the desert!
I'll take it out in the desert,
all right.
Make sure nobody finds her.
Get up.
I'll talk to you later.
Nobody's gonna find you
'cept the coyotes.
Better make it quick 'cause somebody's
bound to come looking for that trooper.
What's the trooper gonna say?
Just gonna have to shut you up.
You listen to me.
You say anything...
and I'll kill them all, I swear.
Hi. Can I help you?
We wondered if you might know if there's
a campground located around here.
Freeze!
Lock the doors!
Get outta here!
Let me in!
Brian, you son of a bitch!
You're in there!
Shit!
Brian, you son of a bitch!
- Who are you?
- I'm the one you sent back.
- Remember?
- What?
Your name's Brian.
There's something in here that sends
people back in time. Me, for example.
- I don't know you.
- I was here before.
You sent me back, and
I've just relived a nightmare.
I have never seen you before
in my life.
Yes, you have!
If what you're saying
is true...
I wouldn't remember it
because it wouldn't have happened yet.
This is incredible.
I must've documented this.
No, you listen to me.
A lot of people were just killed, and
the killer is outside. He's after me.
- We'll call the police.
- That is not gonna work.
I want you to send me back.
I'll change what happened.
- I can go back, and I can fix it.
- Are you insane?
I have no idea what
the residual effects might be.
I'll tell you what they are:
people die.
- Going back might make it worse.
- I've already made it worse.
This time, I'm gonna need
more time. At least an hour.
I've only designed it
for 20 minutes.
That's gonna put me
right back where I was.
You're coming with me.
You want proof that your machine
works, you come with me.
They won't know that we know.
This'll give us an advantage.
As soon as you get back here,
call the police.
Tell them there's a crazy man
with a gun shooting people.
Get them to the gas station
down the road.
As soon as you've made the call,
meet me there.
You're that woman from Chicago
with the hostages.
Yeah. It's a pity this thing
can't go back three days. Get on.
- You first.
- Don't trust me?
Something like that.
Come on. Together.
"That is one
good-looking belt buckle."
And, I don't know, it just popped
into my head. Don't ask me how.
I've heard it before.
It's a really stupid joke.
You don't even know
what I'm talking about.
"lt'd look even better
with your forehead pressed against it"?
And you thought that was original?
Don't take it personal.
After all the stress...
what with my car breaking down
and all...
I am ready to relax,
cut loose.
Know what I mean?
Yeah. Hell,
it's Thursday, right?
Goddamn it. It's only
a day away from the weekend.
That's right.
- What'll you do about your car?
- Hell with it.
I like yours better anyway.
I just love a big, old Cadillac.
- It's so powerful.
- It is, isn't it?
Let me tell you something.
There's more under me
than just a Cadillac engine.
Why don't we go somewhere
and you show me?
Sounds like fun, don't it?
You stop it.
This isn't funny.
Come on. You know
how much I love this.
There're a motel
'bout five miles up. We'll go there.
- I love motels.
- You do?
- Do whatever you want in 'em.
- Yeah.
Might even give 'em
your real name.
Trash the shit outta the room,
then just leave.
Yeah, I like that!
I'm just gonna stop at the station
for a minute, then we'll go.
- I'll take a tequila and lime, please.
- Tequila and lime!
This day has been hell.
- I'm so glad your car broke...
- Keep driving.
Take your hands off the wheel and I'll
blow our brains clear to the border.
What the hell you want, woman?
- Slow down.
- Shit.
If that's all you wanted,
why didn't you just ask?
Does this mean you changed
your mind about the motel?
Now you'll let this car pass us.
Rayanne, and I thought
you were moody.
You ain't seen nothing yet.
Don't get any ideas.
Just keep doing what you're doing.
You are of a different ilk
altogether.
Afternoon, Officer.
Don't test me!
As soon as you get a chance, get as far
away from this asshole as you can.
You got it?
Then again, I may just kill him
for you. Solve both our problems.
You bitch!
I try to help you...
and this is the gratitude I get?
Goddamn it, you better
learn some manners.
- This shit don't fly in Texas.
- Maybe that's why I left.
Let it go on by.
As difficult as it is...
try and act
like a normal human being.
Well, goddamn.
What the hell is happening?
Goddamn it, Rayanne!
I don't know who
your lady friend here is...
My lady?
but I know what you're doing,
and there is no way...
that I'm gonna let you or anybody else
take away what's rightfully mine!
What the hell you talking about?
Listen to me.
He's gonna kill you.
- Goddamn right!
- I will kill you.
You won't kill me.
- Shut up!
Go ahead and shoot me, you stupid bitch!
If you're gonna shoot, shoot!
I'm truly amazed.
Well, I'll be damned.
That's the first time you ever listened
to me. Look what you did to my vehicle!
What the hell...
Gimme that!
Help!
Help me!
Oh, shit!
She's got a gun!
She's gonna kill me!
- She's a crazy psycho bitch!
- What's going on?
She's got a gun!
She killed my wife!
I'll take care of you later,
taco head.
Lady, I didn't do nothing!
I swear, lady! Please!
Wait!
- We've gotta get that piece of shit.
- Get in!
We're not gonna catch him.
He's too far ahead of us.
Not for long. Your pickup's gonna be
giving him a little trouble.
- No way. I just had it serviced.
- Check the tires lately?
- Shit. How did you know?
- Woman's intuition.
See if you can find
some more ammo for this thing.
Shit.
Where the hell are the police?
Brian, you bastard.
- Who's Brian?
- Never mind.
Frank's in that building somewhere,
and he's got the gun from your truck.
- You can count on it.
- How did you know I had a gun?
This is Texas, isn't it?
Yeah.
Be careful.
- Don't you move!
- Hey, lady. Whatever you want, take it.
You got that right.
I'm looking for your buddy, Frank.
- Who?
- Frank! I got something for him.
I'm right here, sweetheart.
- Come and get me.
- Come on out, Frank.
It's over!
It's not over till that big,
ugly fat woman sings that little song.
Sam, I think I found
your missing daughter here.
Shit.
Suppose these are real...
I can explain.
- Shit.
- I got it covered, Officer!
All right. Everybody, drop your guns.
Both of you! Put the guns down now.
I can't do that, Officer.
That man is trying to kill me.
This is his accomplice.
- Sam?
- I don't know what she's talking about.
He's gonna kill you.
Don't trust him.
This is bullshit, Officer.
I picked up this woman hitchhiking.
She killed my wife Rayanne.
She's gonna kill Sam and me. Arrest her.
He's a thief and a killer!
He's carrying contraband.
Make him open his shirt.
- Check him.
- Okay.
First, just everybody put your guns
down. We can work this out.
Come on, now.
We can work this out, but I am not
putting this down before you disarm him.
You hear, sir? She'll lower her weapon
if you'll lower yours.
Who the hell are you?
Okay, that's fair enough.
Hell, you're a professional
law enforcement officer.
If I can't trust you,
I can't trust nobody, can I?
It's a shame, Officer.
Real sad to see a woman
just snap like that.
Especially such a pretty one, huh?
Sir, I've got her covered.
Now if you'd just lower your gun
and open up your shirt.
What?
You heard me. Put the gun down
and open up your shirt.
Keep an eye on him, Officer.
All right.
Okay, easy, easy. All right.
There ain't nothing here.
Hell, all I got down here
is a big old beer belly...
and a couple of bullets for you!
She was right,
and you were wrong!
You bastard.
You killed her.
Yeah, well, Rayanne always did
like it south of the border.
Shit.
Go ahead.
I said go ahead.
Get it.
Oh, God.
Found a peanut
Found a peanut just now
- What do we do now?
- Hell, you take her on foot.
- I'll mow her down with that.
- Sounds reasonable.
But what do we do
with all those bodies?
Hell. We'll say a prayer, take their
watches and wallets, and burn them!
That's gonna stink.
Just now I cracked
- Stop!
- This doesn't look good.
- Don't stop.
I don't want to hit her.
Let me in, please.
- Drive.
- Where to?
Just go. Go away from here.
Come on.
Shit!
- Turn it around!
- That's a police car.
You don't understand.
The officer's been shot.
This guy is trying to kill me.
There's not time to turn around.
You are breaking the law!
You are on the wrong side of the road!
Bumper car!
Shit. Goddamn.
Yeah, whoo!
Go!
I'm going as fast as I can.
Get your heads down!
I love a good Chevrolet!
Damn!
He's on this side.
Look out!
Hang on!
Oh, God!
- Mom, Dad!
- No!
Stay in here, kiddo.
I'll be right back.
Gotcha, baby!
Where do you think
you're running off to, girl?
I thought I'd get myself a beer
right about now, Frank. Want one?
Well, baby...
where's that kid?
What kid?
Goddamn it!
Don't be difficult
at this particular junction, honey.
He's hiding, sweetheart.
Wouldn't you be if there was
a damn maniac on the loose?
Hold it.
Brian, don't you think
you're a little late?
- You know him?
- Frank.
Well, it's an itsy-bitsy world
after all.
The two of you
in on this together?
I've never seen her before
in my life.
All right, then.
We're going to Juarez...
in that mother right there,
and you get moving.
- I'm going to Mexico.
- Wait.
Listen. If you did all this,
you'll never make it to the border.
- They'll send you right back.
- Why?
They're tight with us now.
The Mexicans.
- Why?
- Well...
- Free trade.
- Free trade, my ass!
- Just have to kill you both right now.
- Wait. Hold on.
There's another way.
Is that right?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
Tell me.
Remember that little experiment
that I was working on?
What, that sci-fi bullshit?
I got it to work.
Yeah? Well, is it gonna get me
to Mexico any quicker?
No. But you can go back
and change all this.
You can get away clean.
Is that right? Bullshit!
I did it once already,
with her.
You bastard.
Is that right?
Yes, it's true, Frank.
That's how I know all about you.
You know all about me, do you?
- Yeah.
- Well, what's my favorite color, then?
What's my middle name?
What did I have for breakfast
this morning? Huh?
What universities did I attend?
This is a bunch of bullshit.
You don't know anything about me.
Just get in the goddamn car now.
You always stop here, Frank...
meet with Sam, get a package of money
and some sort of beer.
It's always some foreign beer,
because it reminds you of your dad...
who took off to Australia
when you were ten.
And I can't imagine
that you got past fourth grade.
Not even Rayanne
knew about the money.
Hell.
That's how come you knew
the end of my joke.
Damn.
Hell, Brian.
Beam me on up.
Let's check this little experiment
of yours out.
But first...
Get up! Come on.
This is quite a little family
we got here.
Four little peas in a pod
in the tunnel of love.
- So why didn't you call the cops, huh?
- I did call them.
They thought I was crazy.
They kept laughing at me and hanging up.
All right, Mr. and Mrs. Conversational.
Knock it off.
Try anything funny, I'll blow
the little bastard's brains out.
Now!
Run!
- Come on!
- Get off him!
Come here, you little brat!
Get your mitts off!
Damn!
Come on.
Oh, God.
Open sesame!
Get up, boy!
How the hell do you know Frank?
He had some very difficult-to-procure
computer microchips.
I didn't know that he was
a gun-toting psychopath.
Yes, he was loud and obnoxious...
and he smelled bad, but I had no idea
that he was insane.
All of this is
over some stinking computer chips?
Not just computer chips.
These are very difficult-to-obtain...
government-developed microchips.
We're gonna have to
go back again, Brian.
I've never pushed the system this far.
It's very risky.
If we don't go to the beginning,
it'll never end.
What? What's happening?
Damn it!
Ten minutes?
That's not enough time.
Undo it.
I got news for you. "Undo" never
got programmed into the system.
What do you mean undo
never got programmed in?
I was using it on dead mice.
It didn't matter.
- Reboot it or something.
- You don't get it.
It's plugged into the entire complex,
and it's set to go.
From now on, anything that
comes in contact with that disk...
will trigger the effect.
Oh, God.
He's gonna go back...
and kill everybody.
We'll be there to stop him.
But we won't know that he knows.
But we know now.
But it won't be us now.
It'll be us then, right?
Wait!
Where are you?
Where the hell are you?
Stop!
Well, hell, there you are.
Whoa.
Stop!
Stop. That woman needs help.
- I don't know. It doesn't look good.
- No, stop!
- Don't stop.
- I don't want to hit her.
Get in. He's coming in the trooper's
car. Turn around, Dad.
- There's somebody coming.
- How'd you know?
I just went through
the machine too.
Oh, my God.
- That's a police car.
- I know. The cop's dead. He shot him.
He's right.
The driver is a killer.
- Bob, let's go.
- Not in reverse!
Oh, God.
Hang on!
Move!
Go faster! Come on!
Get down!
Look out!
Hang on!
Aah! You bitch.
What happened?
You sent this kid back
through your machine, Brian.
Yes.
He told me
he's gone through it.
That machine has got
to be destroyed.
We go back one more time.
Back to the beginning, so that none
of this could happen again. You got it?
Sixty minutes.
A tremendous strain on the system.
This whole place is gonna blow.
That'll be after we're long gone.
Come on.
I thought you two
would show up pretty soon.
How'd you get in?
Hell, you showed me.
Don't you remember?
You don't, do you?
The only one that would
is that little kid, I guess.
He's out of the picture
entirely now.
What do you want now, Frank?
Well, I'll tell you.
Brian, that is a damn amazing machine
you got there...
and I've been thinking
about all the fun I can have with it.
You know what I could do?
I could kill the both of you...
zap myself back ten minutes
and kill you again...
and again and again and again!
Not a very noble ambition.
You should aim higher, you bastard.
Hell.
Rayanne's gone, and I just want
to have a little fun.
But you know what?
I'm not familiar with that procedure.
You're gonna have to explain it to me.
I won't.
Well, I'm sorry to say, sir...
you don't have a choice.
It's all up to you, Brian.
How much time do you want?
Oh, a couple hours.
I mean, it's not my nature
to be greedy, Brian.
- Time's a-wasting!
- Brian, don't.
Sit down!
Son of a bitch!
Now, Brian...
don't be no stupid fool now...
try to be a hero.
- Okay.
- Come on.
Don't worry about the bitch.
Give me the goddamn thing.
Come on.
Punch in the time
and hit enter.
You're a bright guy.
Figure it out.
What do I do? I press two hours
and enter at the same time?
You'd look damn good...
strapped to the hood of my car.
Howdy.
Got a little car trouble there,
huh, honey?
Nope.
No?
Sure looks like it.
Sure you don't need anything?
I sure don't.
All right.
Can't say I didn't try.
Do I know you from somewhere?
Uh-uh.
Now you take care of yourself, lady.
What the hell's that about?
What seems to be
the problem, ma'am?
Hi. My name's Karen Warren. I work
with the Chicago Police Department.
Need a lift?
I don't care what you did,
and I don't care who you made love to.
It's just you and me now.
This money's for you and me, baby!
Come on now, honey.
Come on.
Put that gun away.
Now, you ain't gonna shoot me, Rayanne.
I know that.
'Cause you love me.
Drop the gun, ma'am.
Drop it.
- This doesn't look good.
- No, I think you're right.
- Let's go.
- Let's go on down.
All right, ma'am,
put your hands over your head.
Ma'am, I'm gonna
have to ask you to step away.
Ain't nothing you can do here.
It's all over.