Is it bad tonight?
Bad?
That's one way to describe it.
"Insane" seems
a IittIe more appropriate.
He's breathing down my neck.
It's my opinion
we shouId get the heII out of here.
-Now!
-Noted.
CIean this pIace up
and Iocate our guests.
I just need to take the edge off.
You know the routine.
I need you cIearheaded.
First things first.
Now, where is he?
Show me where he's hiding.
You said he kiIIed nine!
There's 40 victims here!
Nine when he was aIive.
He's added a few.
Now where is he, Dennis?
AII teams go to aIpha.
Bring in the cube!
Why is he named The Breaker?
Is he a truck driver?
SimpIe foIkIore.
The IocaI coIor exorcising its demons.
Or maybe it's because
he broke his victims into pieces.
I hate being rushed.
This one's different.
-You'II get a bonus.
-With what money?
After tonight you'II be surprised.
Get to work.
CarefuI, Dennis.
Don't get too curious.
No! Son of a bitch!
How can you justify what you're doing?
It's sIavery.
You are persistent, Damon.
And you, KaIina?
StiII carrying around your quicksiIver
fIares and the IittIe magic book?
You're not capturing animaIs.
They're human beings!
Dead human beings.
You shouId join Greenpeace.
Throw bIood on oId women's furs.
Who are you to pIay God?
-PIaying's for chiIdren.
-You won't succeed.
Not without the right speIIs
and the 13th ghost.
13th ghost?
Get them out of my sight!
We've wasted too much time.
Why did he say 13th?
Move the cube into position.
What did he mean, 13 ghosts?
You contracted me for 12 ghosts.
The Breaker's 12!
I'm done after tonight.
Yes, 12 and then one more.
I thought you were psychic.
-That's not how it works.
-There's no time to argue.
ReIease the bait.
What bait?
We never needed bait before!
A truck fuII of bIood?
You've gotta be shitting me.
Oh, boy.
Now...
...power up the cube.
Start transmitting.
Come.
Come!
Oh, God! HeIp me!
HeIp me!
Oh, shit!
Where is it?
I can't see it!
Put him down!
Hey, Cyrus. I hope you're happy.
You got your 12.
HeIp me! He's dying!
Hang on, Damon. Somebody heIp!
Damn you, Cyrus!
Somebody heIp me, pIease!
HeIp me. Do something!
Oh, Cyrus.
Oh, God.
-Swing me.
-Come on, Bobby.
Come on, Kathy. Faster!
-Let me get your arms.
-Come on. Try to drag me.
You're the best IittIe brother.
I Iove you.
-Come on.
-I'm gonna get you! I'm gonna get you!
Look at them.
She's got him on the run now...
...but soon he'II be throwing her
over his shouIder.
They're perfect.
No, watch. Watch them.
They reaIIy Iove this pIace.
I Iove you, you know?
Surprise!
My heart! My heart!
-Happy birthday, Dad.
-Happy birthday!
-Happy birthday, Arthur.
-Here압 mypresent.
-We love you. Make a wish.
-Blow out the candles.
What앇 you wish for?.
-l love you.
-l love you too.
What압 that?
The smoke alarm?
lt압 the fire alarm.
l앏l get the kids.
Dad! Help, Mom!
-Get the kids. Get the kids!
-Mom! Dad!
-Mom! Dad! Help me!
-Dad, come on!
-Where압 yourmom?
-l don앖 know!
Bobby, we have to get out.
Oh, my God!
Jean! Jean!
Mom압 still in the house.
We can앖 leave herhere.
Bobby, go outside.
Go wait outside, now.
You can앖 go back in there, sir.
l앐 sorry, sir.
She didn앖 make it.
l should have gone back in.
Were here to honor the memory
and life압 work ofJean Kriticos...
...a devoted motherand loving wife,
who was too quickly taken from life.
Jean, you will be forevermissed,
but never forgotten.
-l miss you, Mom.
Why did you have to leave us?
-l can앖 do this withoutyou.
-Don앖 go.
Mom, l love you so much.
Please watch over us.
l앏l love you always.
Dad, it's aI--
It's aImost 8:30. Shake a Ieg
or you'II miss your first cIass.
Today on Death in America:
Cancer rates are down...
...but suicide is sky-high.
We have a treat today.
A body was found, "decoIopoIated."
Hey, hey. "Decapitated."
Find a heaIthier hobby.
Leave me aIone. I'm recording!
Good morning, everybody.
Something smeIIs interesting.
They found a headIess guy
behind Dunkin' Donuts.
I Iove Dunkin' Donuts.
-Shit!
-Kathy.
Why not Iet Maggie make breakfast?
That's why we hired her.
Have you tasted her cooking?
-Just that once.
-Hey, I heard that!
-I cook better than you.
-We have to try to get aIong.
Okay.
TeII Kathy that keeping
a record of death is heaIthy.
Keeping a record of deaths is heaIthy.
-She's being a IittIe sIut about it.
-Don't caII your sister a sIut.
-Thank you.
-I prefer the term "bitch."
SIuts have Ioose sex--
Did you do your homework?
Because Mr. Peterson toId me--
Damn it, Bobby!
I've tripped on that three times!
-Sorry.
-We need a bigger pIace.
We don't have a big pIace anymore.
This is the best I can do for now.
So Iet's try and keep our shit
off the fIoor.
Now put away the damn tape recorder
and get ready for schooI.
I'm sorry, Dad.
-Must be the Iawyer. I forgot.
-What Iawyer?
-Isn't our credit cIeaned up?
-It's not about that.
They won't make us move again,
wiII they?
It's aII right.
Whatever it is, we'II deaI with it.
-Mr. Kriticos?
-Yes. You're...?
-Ben Moss. How do you do?
-PIease come in.
-Is now a good time, or...?
-Good a time as any.
PIease, just give me one minute,
wiII you?
Okay. Sorry. I'm ready.
I represent your uncIe
Cyrus Kriticos' estate.
-We have an UncIe Cyrus?
-Had.
I met him a coupIe of times as a kid.
He wasn't popuIar.
Squandered the famiIy fortune.
-We have a famiIy fortune?
-No. Cyrus squandered it.
-Bobby, you have a Iate uncIe.
-What is he Iate for?
-His next birthday.
-You mean he's dead?
-That got his attention.
-Pipe down.
Cyrus recorded this six weeks ago...
...to be pIayed for you
in the event of his death.
Arthur, it압 good to talk to you.
Sadly, ifyoure watching this,
it means l am dead.
Happily, that makes you
and your family my sole beneficiaries.
l았e instructed my lawyer, Mr. Moss,
to deliver the essential elements...
...in my last will and testament.
Give it to them, Ben.
-A key?
-A key to what?
-A key to yournew house.
-What?
This house is the fruit
ofmy life압 work.
Everyone gets their own bathroom!
-Is this for reaI?
-lt is a one-of-a-kind home.
lt압 my home, actually.
My home.
l have no complaints.
l았e led an interesting life.
l have seen some amazing things.
My only regret is that l never
got to know my nephew, Arthur...
...norappreciate the love
ofa family, like you have.
This house is my attempt
to make up for that.
Enjoy.
Perhaps we앏l meet again...
...in anotherlife.
-Wow!
-When can we see it?
Whenever you Iike.
I'm heading there today.
If you want, your wife and kids--
-Time out. I am not the missus here.
-My wife....
-My wife is....
-Our mom burned to death in a fire.
-Bobby!
-What? It's true.
That's enough, Robert.
Mr. Moss, just exactIy where
is this pIace?
Just a coupIe hours drive from here,
in a town caIIed WiIIow Grove.
It's in a gorgeous area.
Your uncIe Iiked his privacy.
There isn't a neighbor for miIes.
-Come on, hurry up.
-S-U-F--
-Suffocate! I got it. I win.
-So what? You think you're so sIick.
Come on, you guys. We're aImost there.
-Excited?
-Yeah.
-Mom wouId have freaked over this.
Looks Iike things are starting
to get better, right?
Yeah.
That's strange.
Dad, it's beautifuI!
My God!
I've never seen anything Iike it.
CooI! So "futuroic."
About time someone showed up.
This your pIace?
-Who are you?
-I'm the power guy.
Don't touch.
Your house is knocking out the power
of the whoIe area.
I need to check the breakers.
CouId you come back tomorrow?
Tomorrow? Let me see.
There's about 5570 houses
right now without power.
-My bosses kind of frown on that.
-That's not reaIIy our probIem, is it?
I've been at this job for three weeks.
Can't you give me a break here?
Sure. No probIem.
Thank you.
-Mr...?
-Kriticos. Arthur Kriticos.
Quite a pIace you've got.
Yeah. We're moving in.
WeII, one step at a time.
-That's odd.
-Dad, you broke it!
Give it a rest.
HeIIo.
Wow! You can see right through it.
-You guys couIdn't afford waIIs?
-How weird.
Guess Cyrus wasn't too keen
on privacy.
I sure hope the bathroom's
in the basement.
It's Iike a fun house.
It's Latin.
Everything's so beautifuI.
Just so we're aII cIear,
Miss Maggie does not do windows.
Wow!
What an incredibIe weaIth
of knowIedge!
-A samurai sword!
-Bobby.
In your dreams, paI.
-This stuff must be worth a fortune.
-Yeah, that occurred to me too.
Oh, Cyrus.
You crazy son of a bitch,
what did you do?
Goodness! It's Iike a cathedraI.
AII right, first ruIe:
no throwing stones.
It's marveIous, isn't it?
A Iiving work of art.
As soon as you show me the basement,
I'II be out of here.
I beIieve it's down the haII.
It's two doors on the right.
Excuse me.
The construction is amazing!
I'm getting dizzy.
Don't touch anything. Okay?
At Ieast untiI
we get some property insurance.
Arthur, we have papers to sign.
Then I'II give you aII a tour.
Great. You guys don't move
from this spot. We'II be right back.
Dad, you're being overprotective.
Yeah, of aII this stuff.
I know you guys too weII.
Stay right here.
I mean it.
What the--?
Where'd you hide your money, oId man?
Oh, shit.
What the heII was that?
Oh, no.
Oh, Cyrus.
Now I know I'm dreaming.
-Was Cyrus a hunter?
-You couId say that.
Your uncIe was quite a coIIector
of many things.
I've marked where
you're supposed to sign.
Okay, Iook.
I didn't want to bring this up
in front of the kids, but....
WeII, this pIace is beyond amazing.
I'm just a math teacher.
The taxes aIone must be--
I have nothing set aside.
To be honest,
a fire took away everything.
Arthur, you don't need to worry.
Cyrus was a genius
when it came to finances.
None of you ever have
to worry about money again.
You son of a bitch.
Look here! Look, you aII.
Look, Iook, Iook, Iook!
Sign.
Arthur? Arthur?
Arthur, we've gotta--
Arthur, we have to taIk.
-What is the deaI with the breakers?
-Nothing. I'm not the power guy.
-I'm Dennis Rafkin.
-You're Rafkin?
-Who's that?
-My office warned me--
I know it's gonna sound whacked,
but stay with me.
I hunted dispIaced spirituaI energies
with your uncIe.
-I'm sorry?
-PK agents. Revenants.
Wraiths. Do you have any idea
what I'm taIking about?
That's okay.
I'II do this the easy way: ghosts.
Arthur, I used to hunt ghosts
with your UncIe Cyrus.
-Goats?
-Ghosts!
Ghosts, goddamn it! Listen!
I'II race you.
No, Bobby, this isn't the pIace for--
Come on, sIowpoke. Is that your best?
My grandma scoots better than that.
Ghosts, as in disgruntIed spirits
trapped on Earth. Ghosts.
As in HaIIoween. As in Demi Moore
and "Unchained MeIody." Ghosts.
Ghosts, right. Okay, I get it.
I'm scared.
Don't Iaugh at me. Don't Iaugh.
I'II expIain everything as soon as you
get you and your chiIdren outside.
-What's taking you so Iong?
-Out of my way. Come on, Maggie!
-You cheated. I didn't say "start."
-Gotta be on your toes.
This has to be my room!
There are toys everywhere.
-I wonder what my room's Iike.
-I'm in the cooIest room.
I'II be in here.
Wow.
This pIace is awesome!
Cyrus has containment cubes
aII over the basement.
I don't know why they're here
and I don't want to find out.
-So if I were you--
-WeII, he isn't you.
This guy has been harassing my office
since your uncIe died.
Some rich guy passes away
and aII the nuts come out!
-Next he'II say Cyrus owed him money.
-He did. A shitIoad of money!
These are some funky-Iooking specs.
-Do I Iook cooI, or what?
-Let me see.
Wait. Cater to my ego first.
-Maggie is the best babysitter--
-Come on!
I'm Ieaving the big gIass house!
Grab your chiIdren. Do the same.
Are you aII right?
Jean! Jean! Jean!
-We'II get you some heIp. Okay?
-Don't touch me.
Oh, my God!
We've struck goId.
-Easy.
-Don't.
How's your head?
Not good.
Where's the suit?
"Power guy." Idiot.
-CooI!
-There better be a pair in my room.
Bobby, where are you going?
What are you staring at?
Hey, kiddo.
He thinks I'm gonna duck.
Nice tits.
Jeez. What's the matter, honey?
Bad representation?
Not bad for an hourIy wage.
-It's time to Ieave.
-I'II take your word for it.
Kathy?
Come on. This way.
Shit! What the heII? Kathy!
Maggie!
Bobby!
I was just kidding before.
A IittIe Iawyer humor.
Kathy?
Bobby!
-I don't beIieve it.
-BeIieve what?
-I toId them to stay here.
-They're kids. What did you expect?
Thanks, Dr. PhiI.
You check downstairs, I'II go up.
Bobby! It's time to go!
Kathy? Where are you guys?
Bobby!
l앐 sorry.
What are you doing?
I toId you to wait downstairs.
Yes, but come on,
this bathroom is unbeIievabIe.
Yes, beautifuI bathroom.
Now where's your brother?
He's with Maggie.
Was with Maggie. We were racing
and we saw aII the gIasses--
You're supposed to watch him.
That's what I pay you for.
Bobby.
Down here.
Maggie?
-Come on down and play.
-Is that you?
-Maggie! Stop pIaying games.
-Bobby? l have something foryou.
We앏l have lots of fun, Bobby.
Don앖 come down, Bobby.
Stay upstairs.
Don앖 follow her.
Down here, Bobby.
Bobby, don앖 come down.
Bobby. Around the corner.
-Don앖 come down here!
-That압 it, Bobby.
Guys, I'm gonna teII Dad!
-Bobby!
I'II find Bobby. You both get out.
-But, Dad--
-No buts!
Wait in the car.
I'II be out once I find him.
-Why are you freaking out?
-Just this once, don't argue.
-What happened to the door?
-Son of a bitch!
I can't beIieve this.
I'II break it down. Step away!
Quite dramatic, but you're wasting
your time. It's aII seaIed up.
-Weren't you in an orange jumpsuit?
-Don't.
SeaIed up?
What part of that code can't you
crack? The entire house is seaIed up.
-There must be a way.
-I've Iooked.
We'II Iook again,
after we find my son.
-That's okay. I'II wait here.
-Listen...
...I don't know what is going on here,
or who the heII you are.
And my son is missing.
So untiI I get answers...
...I'm not Ietting you out
of my sight. Now get up!
AII right. Breathe.
Did the Iawyer spIit?
Bobby.
Come on, guys! Stop hiding!
-Bobby!
-Come on out, paI!
-Stop screwing around!
-You're wasting your breath.
This is ectobar gIass. He won't hear
you. It's shatterproof and soundproof.
What are these?
That's harder to expIain.
They're containment speIIs.
Ghosts can't cross those.
-Ghosts?
-Yes, ghosts.
The supernaturaI reaIm has its
own Iaws. For ghosts, it's speIIs.
Either written or spoken,
ghosts have to obey them.
-The basement is fiIIed with ghosts.
-In this basement?
Yes, this basement. If it was
next door, I wouIdn't give a shit!
-I'II prove it.
-I gave those to Bobby.
SpectraI viewers:
you can see the ghosts with these.
-I don't see anything.
-They're Iocked downstairs.
Dad!
There's more of those speIIs
on the fIoor.
Let me see those.
Bobby! Come on out, paI!
Hidden barrier speIIs.
Why wouId he need more protection?
That's enough. This is not heIping.
Do me a favor.
Stop the haunted-house nonsense untiI
we find Bobby and get out of here.
-Bobby, come on!
-Where couId he be?
Wait, no, no, no!
Wait, no! What are you doing?
Did I just say...
...there was a petting zoo
downstairs? No!
There are ghosts downstairs.
Right. But you aIso said...
...that they're aII Iocked up. Right?
No! No way--!
Listen...
...I'II make a deaI with you.
I'II pay you whatever Cyrus owed you.
If you just...
...heIp me find my son.
UnbeIievabIe. Get out of my way.
Bobby.
Bobby...
...get out of the basement.
You need to go upstairs.
You need to put on those glasses.
Leave me alone!
That압 it. That압 a good boy.
Bobby.
Go upstairs and find your father.
-Mom?
-Go on.
Go upstairs!
Go find Kathy.
Watch out.
Watch out!
-Bobby, come on!
-Bobby!
You don't have to scream, aII right?
Just...
...chiII.
-This way.
-HoId on. Listen to me.
This wiII take forever.
This pIace is just too big.
Okay.
Kathy and I wiII go this way.
You two check down there.
-No, we shouId stay together.
-It's okay.
Go straight, turn around,
we'II meet back here in five.
-Five. Back here.
-Five minutes.
-And don't touch anything.
-I gotta go with him?
Let's go back to the ghost thingy.
There are ghosts in the basement.
You can Iook for yourseIf.
I can't see any ghosts.
What the heII? Give me those.
Let me see. Why are these open?
I was down here before.
They weren't open.
-God! I hate it when they do that!
-Do what?
They wait tiII you put your face
to the gIass, then give you...
...a big, fat "boo!"
Don't do that!
See it?
-It's, it's--
-A ghost!
Just Iike I've been saying aII night!
FinaIIy, a beIiever!
Ghosts are aIways around us.
Most can't hurt us.
Most don't want to. Ghosts here,
ghosts there, no one cares.
There are exceptions, Iike this guy.
Those who die vioIentIy
remain tortured.
-That's aII they know.
-What's he doing?
I don't know. I can't see.
I don't have the gIasses.
I've had it with this.
It's time to go.
-Now! PIease.
-Don't touch me.
WiII you come on?!
Come on, ghost boy! Move your ass!
Dad, sIow down. We're gonna get Iost.
Dad. Listen to me.
He's gonna be okay.
We're gonna find him.
So ready to Ieave this pIace.
-Oh, boy.
-What?
-The symboI of The JackaI.
-What's that?
It's the CharIie Manson of ghosts.
If he's out, screw the kid.
We gotta get out of here.
Maybe Rafkin was right.
Maybe there--
Kathy!
Think about what you're saying.
There's no such thing as ghosts.
Kathy!
What is it?! I can't see it!
TeII me where it is!
Get off!
HoId on! Stay with me!
PuII!
-Who are you?
-Never mind! Just puII!
Shit! Don't speak. Don't move.
Somehow, we got behind enemy Iines.
Hurry!
PIease hurry!
Hey, IittIe guy. How.
-Don't tease ghosts.
-Shut up.
You shut up.
You keep pissing them off.
Go. Go, go, go.
-Maggie!
-What?
Where?
I can't see without the gIasses!
I can see.
And I think you shouId go this way!
Go, go, go, go!
It's aII right. I've got you.
-Look at me.
-Daddy!
It's okay.
Who the heII are you?
And what the heII was that?!
My name is KaIina Oretzia.
I'm a spirit recIaimer.
-What?
-I free trapped souIs. Cyrus--
Forget Cyrus and trapped souIs
for a second.
What are you doing here?
Looks to me Iike I'm saving your ass.
Oh, my God! It's over there!
Give him your gIasses. Come on!
Oh, my God.
UnbeIievabIe.
Another one of Cyrus' victims.
I hope to God the barrier speIIs hoId.
Victims?
Cyrus Iiked to ensIave souIs.
That's why I'm here.
I'm gonna free them.
Listen.
I need to know how you got in here.
Through an opening
when the house shifted.
-Opening where?
-It's cIosed now. It won't open again.
Let me show you. This is the Arcanum.
Many died Iooking for this book.
A 15th-century astroIoger,
BasiIeus, wrote it.
He describes the making
of a machine...
...that can see the future.
He wrote it whiIe
possessed by a demon.
I can't beIieve Cyrus buiIt it.
BuiIt what?
What are you taIking about?
BasiIeus' device.
We're in a machine,
designed by the deviI...
...and powered by the dead.
Listen to me.
I don't give a shit about any machine
or deviI or BasiIeus...
...or anything,
except getting my famiIy out of here.
I came to set the souIs
in this house free.
You want heIp,
you gotta heIp me first.
Kathy, can you waIk?
This can't be happening!
-We have to Ieave.
-Not without my kids.
Try teIIing him that.
Come on.
This way. Come on, come on.
Stairs. Let's go.
Go, go, go. You go, go, go.
It touched me!
Wait! The gIasses!
You'II need these! Catch!
-Good job.
-Sorry.
Perfect, another dead end.
We found the stairs.
How do we get there?
-Get away.
-What do we do now?
Get away from the gIass.
-Why?
-Just do it.
GIasses.
Duck!
-What?
-Move! Go Ieft!
Do something!
We're running out of corridors!
Duck! Go right!
Get down!
We go to the Iibrary.
It has speII protection around it.
Okay. Where's that from here?
Can I reIy on you
not to get me kiIIed?
I guarantee nothing.
See anything?
-Anything?
-No.
-Come on.
-Okay.
You know, I think they're
just downstairs.
Nothing.
If we get out of this aIive,
I've gotta get a raise.
That's a big "if."
Give me a fIare.
What's wrong? Don't start
freaking out now. Come on.
What?
-Okay. What?
-Shut up!
Give me the book.
Just back up.
-Go sIow.
-Okay.
-Going sIow.
-SIow.
Go! Go! Go!
Fast!
-What?
-Who the heII?
What are you doing here?
Shit!
Hey, remember me?
-Thanks for taking your time.
-Down the haII, Ieft, then right.
-Where are we going?
-Trust me.
-Arthur?
-Trust her.
Okay, Iet's go!
-Who is she?
-I'II expIain Iater!
-What happened to Kathy?
-She disappeared.
How do you Iose an entire famiIy
in a gIass house?
Arthur!
KaIina, the fIare!
Get him! Go, go! Arthur, get up!
This is not the time to be a girI!
Run! Go!
Stop dragging your ass! Go, go, go!
Go! Run!
Now is not the time
to sit around, Arthur! Run!
CIose the door! Go!
Arthur, are you aII right?
God, what's going on here?
I hate this job.
They don't Iike you either.
I wonder why.
You got something to say?
Let's start with:
This is aII your fauIt!
You caught them, now we're running.
His uncIe buiIt the house!
You heIped him. How couId you
without knowing what he was doing?
-I had my reasons.
-Money, you parasite.
You stoIe peopIe's souIs for money!
That's depraved!
If you haven't noticed,
I'm a bit of a freak!
I go near anything dead,
I go into seizures.
I touch somebody, and a whoIe Iife
fIashes in front of my eyes.
So, yeah, I'm depraved. And Cyrus
is my friend, and he accepted me.
He did not. You're so pathetic!
-He used you.
-Shut up, both of you.
Cut him some sIack.
What difference does it make?
You didn't teII him, did you?
-TeII me what? What now?
-About the fourth ghost.
-No, don't do this. I didn't teII him.
-He has a right to know.
What about the fourth ghost?
St. Luke's HospitaI. Six months ago.
You're saying my wife's spirit
is trapped in this house?
I didn't know you.
I didn't know her.
I didn't know she had a husband.
Why? In God's name, why?
TeII me, why her?
Cyrus picked them aII,
incIuding your wife.
I've been trying to heIp you.
You caII this heIp?! She's right!
This is aII your fauIt!
-Son of a bitch!
-Arthur.
You can save her. And your kids too.
Just Iisten to me, and beIieve me.
This house is not a house.
It is a machine.
It's a compIete and faithfuI
re-creation of BasiIeus' design.
There shouId be 12 spirits
trapped inside.
See these?
They represent the bIack zodiac.
They are ghosts Cyrus needed to catch.
The First Born Son.
l wanna play.
The Torso.
The Bound Woman.
The Withered Lover.
Jean.
Bobby, l love you.
The Torn Prince.
The Angry Princess.
The PiIgrimess.
The Great ChiId and Dire Mother.
The Hammer.
And here, the sign of heII's winter,
The JackaI.
And The Juggernaut.
The machine required the energy
of these spirits to bring it to Iife.
Then the spirits are reIeased
one by one.
The house draws them to its
center. Each adds its energy...
...powering it up.
-Powering it up for what?
-To open the Ocularis lnfernum.
-Ocularis, what's that?
-It's Latin.
Ocularis.... The eye of heII?
Very good.
I'm stuck in a gIass house
with crazy white peopIe....
Go on.
In heII, there's an eye
that sees everything...
...the bIessed and the damned.
If knowIedge is power,
the man who controIs the Ocularis...
...is the most powerfuI on Earth.
-Your uncIe.
-Great.
So how many ghosts
have been set free?
EIeven, and the house needs 12.
No, Damon said something about 13.
-There are 13 ghosts.
-The 13th ghost is a faiI-safe.
To stop it, the house needs
a sacrifice of Iife, not death.
A wiIIing human sacrifice.
A sacrifice of the broken heart.
The onIy ghost created
out of an act of Iove.
You're the 13th ghost.
The 13th spirit stands before the eye.
As it opens...
...the spirit uses
the power of Iife...
...to short-circuit the system.
-Uses the power of Iife how?
-By Ieaping into the eye.
And Arthur's supposed to take
this Ieap? No way.
That's suicide. I won't Iet you do it.
Come up with something eIse.
That's not working.
-Love is the most powerfuI energy.
-Meaning?
To save your chiIdren
you'd have to trade your Iife.
Let me see this.
There's gotta be a better way.
I don't read Latin.
WeII, we can try it
the oId-fashioned way.
Nobody'II be here to brag about it.
We need a pIan soon.
Time's running out.
You gonna bIow the pIace up?
The Iast ghost
is about to be reIeased.
I know why you feeI
you have to do this.
Psychics caII it a Iinking.
We Iinked. I saw everything...
...about Jean, about you.
Shut up. I'm not gonna Iisten
to this from you.
-KaIina is taIking about suicide.
-Anything to save my kids.
It doesn't make any sense.
There must be a better way.
What does add up here, Dennis?
How much of this makes any sense?
Goddamn it. Goddamn it.
AII I can think about are my kids.
I don't even know if they're aIive.
Let's go out there and find out.
WhiIe there's stiII time, you and me.
KaIina...
...no matter what I do,
or what happens to us...
...can you stop that machine?
I got enough expIosives to bIow
us back to the 15th century.
Okay.
-How many fIares are Ieft?
-One. Why?
We're going out.
No fucking way.
You'II get yourseIf kiIIed!
Not if we take that.
We got 10 minutes tiII
the ectopIasmic shit hits the fan.
Go, go, go.
-We'II go down to buy you time.
-After you, Captain America.
Damn, I just got my naiIs done.
Here, put these on.
Come on, Iet's go! Come on!
Why did you leave me?
There's no pIace Iike home.
Knock it off, Dennis.
Just keep your eyes open.
Sure hope I don't bIeed to death.
That wouId suck.
Rotate.
-Is that haIf the Iawyer?
-Take this. Move it.
Oh, my God.
He's definiteIy Iooked better.
God. Shit!
GirI, hurry up!
-Ram him!
-He's swinging for the fences!
KaIina! This fIare shit ain't working!
Where is it?
Where is it? Where is it?
KaIina?
Why are you so mad at me?
I did everything you asked.
I kiIIed Damon, stoIe his speIIs.
I made sure your nephew
didn't get kiIIed!
KaIina!
Where are the speIIs?
You're not mad at me, are you?
Of course not.
-What is it?
-Oh, shit.
Dennis?
-OnIy room for one.
-What are you doing?
I've wanted a reason
to Iike myseIf for a Iong time.
Don't do this!
Hey, bro.
You ain't nothing but a bitch!
Dennis, no!
Oh, my God!
What do we do now?
Arthur thinks he needs
to sacrifice himseIf.
He'II onIy do it
if they're in jeopardy.
-WeII, put them in jeopardy.
-What?
-Why not?
-But they're kids.
Greatness requires sacrifice.
Now I have a job to do.
And so have you.
-Do it. Do it!
-Yes.
And now to finish this.
Oh, my God, Jean.
I Ioved you so much.
I miss you.
Miss you.
I'm nothing without you.
No, don't. Don't go.
Don't go. Don't go.
Don't go....
Fetch the book.
Cyrus! Cyrus! What are you doing?
You just can't teach some peopIe.
I thought I toId you,
greatness requires sacrifice.
-Kathy!
-Don't Iook.
I don't wanna Iook.
Kathy, I'm scared!
Hey, Kathy!
Kathy! Bobby!
-Daddy!
-Bobby!
Dad, heIp!
Oh, my....
Make it stop, Dad! Make it stop!
This house is not a house.
lt is a machine...
...designed by the devil...
...and powered by the dead.
There should be 12 spirits
trapped inside.
They represent the black zodiac.
Each is a ghost
Cyrus needed to catch.
-The First Born Son.
-One.
-The Torso.
-Two.
-The Bound Woman.
-Three.
-The Withered Lover.
-Four.
The Torn Prince. The Angry Princess.
The Pilgrimess.
The Great Child and Dire Mother.
The Hammer, The Jackal
and The Juggernaut.
TweIve.
You're the 13th ghost.
If I'm the 13th....
You son of a bitch!
ReIease my kids, you bastard!
Damn you! You're nothing, Arthur!
You hear? You Ioser!
I dedicated my entire Iife to this.
Every waking moment, for years.
Have you ever shown that kind
of dedication? Have you?
The worId has no time
for IittIe peopIe Iike you.
It needs peopIe who are
wiIIing to do anything...
...anything for greatness.
You don't have a choice
this time, Arthur.
You wiII make that Ieap.
The machine requires
a ghost to be created...
...out of an act of pure Iove.
That's why I chose you,
you and your pathetic famiIy.
CongratuIations, you get to become
the 13th ghost.
Get on your feet!
Come on!
Trust me, Arthur. It's not over yet.
You can finish this.
You stiII have the power in you.
It's just a matter of how you use it.
Go to your kids. They need you.
Dad! HeIp!
Daddy, don't! Don't do it!
Oh, fuck!
Dad!
Don't move!
Keep your heads down!
HoId on tight!
Everybody okay?
You okay?
How did you know we'd be safe?
I didn't. I just wasn't about
to Ieave you guys.
I Iove you both so much.
Mom?
l love you guys.
l love you.
This is it for me! I am on
the first pIane back to Newark.
I am sorry, famiIy, Kathy, Bobby,
ghosts. I am sick of this nanny shit.
I've had it! This was not
in the job description. I quit!