CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
POLYGRAM VIDEO
Man: THEY WERE
MY TWO BEST FRIENDS
IN THE WHOLE WORLD...
FOR 5 WEEKS.
IT'S A TOTAL ACCIDENT
WE EVEN MET.
ME, A BUM FROM BROOKLYN, USING
PHONY FREQUENT-FLIER MILES.
TONY CROFT WAS KIND OF
A GOLDEN BOY
FROM HARVARD SCHOOL
OF ARCHITECTURE.
WE MET LEWIS McBRIDE,
THIS, UH, LONG-HAIRED,
GREENPEACE, YOU KNOW,
TREE-HUGGER GUY.
SO THE PLAN WAS
TO PARTY TILL WE RAN
OUT OF CASH IN MALAYSIA.
IT WAS A PARADISE OF RUM,
GIRLS, AND GOOD, CHEAP HASH.
[SINGING IN MALAY]
WOOO!
[CROWD CHEERING]
Man: HERE WE GO, BOYS.
WHOOO!
[SPEAKING MALAY]
I DON'T UNDERSTAND A WORD
YOU'RE SAYING TO ME,
BUT THIS IS MY LEAST
FAVORITE PART ANYWAY,
THE TALKING STUFF.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
YOU DO?
GOOD MORNING, BRO.
WHAT'S UP?
DID YOU SLEEP GOOD,
YOU LITTLE DREAMER?
WHAT DID YOU
DO THAT FOR?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
IT'S MY LAST DAY, LEW,
GET UP.
WE'LL GO DO SOMETHING.
MAYBE IT SHOULDN'T
BE YOUR LAST DAY.
BE MY LAST DAY.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
GET A HAIRCUT.
WOW!
YOU'RE UP EARLY.
WELL, WHAT KIND OF
PARTY'S THIS?
MY PARTY.
YOUR PARTY? HEH HEH.
[PEOPLE TALKING IN MALAY]
YES!
OH, YES.
IT'S THE AGGRESSIVE
INSTINCT...
WHERE ARE YOU BOYS FROM,
AMERICA?
THAT'S MALAYSIAN FOR
"DO YOU HAVE MONEY?"
YES. WE'RE FROM
THE STATES.
MM-HMM.
DO YOU HAVE
FUN HERE?
IT COULD BE BETTER.
Woman: LISTEN...
I GOT SOMETHING
SPECIAL FOR YOU.
YEAH, WHAT?
I GOT SPECIAL
ANIMAL POTION.
YOU WANT?
ANIMAL POTION?
YEAH.
NUMBER ONE APHRODISIAC.
KEEP YOU HARD
AS A ROCK ALL NIGHT.
YOU WANT?
AH, IT SOUNDS PAINFUL.
THANKS, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, I WANT
TO SEE THIS.
YOU WANT TO SEE?
YOUR FRIEND,
SURE, YEAH.
OK, FOLLOW ME.
LET ME TELL YOU
ABOUT THIS DEAL.
Tony: YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS GOOD.
THIS IS ALL GOOD.
LEWIS, THIS
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
THE NUMBER ONE PHARMACY
TO ME, YOU KNOW?
UH-HUH.
Man: HEY, YO!
[SPEAKING MALAY]
SPECIAL DELIVERY FOR YOU.
OH, THIS IS GOOD.
GOOD STUFF.
ORIGINAL.
GOOD. VERY GOOD.
THIS IS RHINO HORN,
ISN'T IT?
OH, SMART MAN.
RHINO HORN GOOD.
AMERICAN,
JAPANESE LIKE IT.
MAN, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
LISTEN, LISTEN.
WOMAN LIKE IT.
KEEP YOU HARD.
YOU KNOW,
KEEP YOU HARD. GOOD.
EVEN IF THIS WORKED...
LISTEN...
NO, YOU LISTEN TO ME.
EVEN IF THIS WORKED,
WHICH IT DOESN'T,
TO MURDER
ENDANGERED SPECIES--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Tony: THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO GET THAT.
THEY'RE NOT GOING
TO UNDERSTAND YOU.
[EVERYBODY TALKING]
YOU TAKE...
10 BUCKS, 10 BUCKS.
THIS DOESN'T HAVE TO
GET FUCKING VIOLENT.
I'M TALKING TO YOU.
[EVERYBODY ARGUING]
HEY, MAN, FUCK YOU.
FUCK US UP, MAN!
HUH? FUCK US UP, MAN!
Tony: WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
GET THE FUCK
OUT OF HERE.
FUCK YOU, MOTHERFUCKER.
EASY. OK.
[SPEAKING MALAY]
YEE-HOO!
YEAH.
STOP MOVING THE BIKE.
I CAN'T BALANCE IT.
HA! HA!
Lewis: STOP!
SLOWER, SLOWER!
THERE'S
A REALLY STEEP HILL.
YOU MIGHT WANT
TO BRAKE NOW.
BRAKE!
WHAT THE FUCK!
[TRUCK HORN SOUNDS]
TIME TO GET OFF!
Tony: AW, SHIT.
ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT, MAN?
ALL RIGHT?
YOU OK?
[ALL LAUGHING]
OH MY GOD.
HOLY SHIT, BRO.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Lewis: SAY, THANKS
FOR THE HELP, GUYS.
WHAT THE FUCK?
ARE YOU GOING TO
PUSH THAT THING
ALL THE WAY TO PANANG.
LET THE BIKE GO,
BROTHER, LET IT GO.
I TELL YOU, I'M NOT
GOING TO LEAVE IT.
Tony: LEWIS,
THE DEPOSIT WE PUT
DOWN ON THAT BIKE
IS ABOUT 5 TIMES
ITS WORTH.
WHY ARE YOU PUSHING
THE FUCKING BIKE?
DROP THE FUCKING BIKE.
I'M NOT GOING TO
LEAVE IT.
THIS IS HIS LAST BIKE,
THAT'S HIS BREAD AND BUTTER.
YOU'RE OUT OF
YOUR FRICKIN' MIND.
Lewis:
MAYBE IF YOU'D HELP
ME OUT A LITTLE BIT.
IT WOULD GO SO MUCH
QUICKER IF I HAD
A LITTLE HELP.
LET ME DO IT.
HERE, I'LL PUSH IT.
I'LL PUSH
THE FUCKIN' THING.
THANK YOU.
YOU GOT THIS?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
Lewis: OH!
Tony:
NICE SHOT, SHERIFF.
REALLY.
Lewis: THAT'S GREAT.
Sheriff: LET'S GET HOME.
COME ON.
FRIENDS FOR LIFE, MAN.
Lewis: OH, HEY,
YOU GUYS GOTTA GIVE
ME YOUR ADDRESSES.
Tony: YEAH.
Lewis: WHEN I GET ONE,
I'LL GIVE YOU
MY ADDRESS...
DOWN THERE
IN BORNEO.
Tony: WHERE?
BORNEO.
OH, YOU'RE STAYING?
YOU GOT A GIRLFRIEND
THERE, MAN?
NO. AT THE ORANGUTAN
REINTRODUCTION PROJECT.
Tony: THE WHAT PROJECT?
IT'S THIS GROUP.
THEY GO, AND THEY RESCUE
THESE ORANGUTANS THAT HAVE
BEEN KEPT AS PETS.
AND THEY HELP INTEGRATE THEM
BACK IN THE WILD.
YOU'RE GONNA
STAY HERE.
GO DOWN AND VOLUNTEER.
BRO, IF THE APES NEED
HUMANS TO SAVE THEM,
THEN THEY'RE FUCKED.
PAY NO ATTENTION
TO HIM.
HE ALWAYS DUMPING
ON SOMEBODY.
THAT'S COOL.
WHAT ABOUT YOU,
GOLDEN BOY?
YOU CAN'T WAIT
TO GO PUT ALL
THOSE THINGS
YOU CALL BUILDINGS
UP IN NEW YORK.
SKYSCRAPERS.
NO, MAN,
THEY'LL BE BEAUTIFUL,
TOUCHING THE CLOUDS.
SEE, YOU GUYS
DON'T REALIZE
HOW GOOD YOU HAVE IT
RIGHT NOW,
RIGHT HERE.
SO EAGER
TO GET ON WITH
YOUR CHARMED LIVES
THAT YOU JUST MISS
WHAT'S HAPPENING
RIGHT NOW.
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN?
[EVERYBODY LAUGHING]
LOOK, WE GOT
MELLOW HASH, RIGHT?
WE GOT COCONUTS
FILLED WITH RUM.
WE GOT BEAUTIFUL,
GRACIOUS CHICKS
THAT LIKE US
JUST BECAUSE
WE'RE FUCKIN' YANKEES
AND WE'RE TALL.
SOME OF US.
AND THEN YOU GOT
THIS WARM,
CALM WATER.
IT'S LIKE
GOD'S OWN BATHTUB
OR SOMETHING, MAN.
HEY, LEW,
ARE YOU REALLY
GOING TO DO THAT?
STAY HERE
AND TRY TO SAVE
THOSE GORILLAS?
YEAH.
THAT'S COOL, MAN.
THAT'S
TOTALLY COOL, LEW.
TOTALLY COOL.
YOU SOUND INTERESTED.
YOU WANT TO JOIN ME?
Tony: FLIGHT'S TOMORROW.
CAN'T CHANGE THE TICKET,
NO REFUND.
THINK ABOUT IT.
MORNING.
Sheriff: HEY,
GOOD MORNING, MAN.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
SO?
IS IT CIVILIZATION
AND ITS DISCONTENTS
OR, UH, YOU, ME,
AND THE MONKEYS?
I DON'T THINK
I'M CUT OUT FOR THAT
KIND OF THING, LEW.
THAT'S FOR YOU, MAN.
TO TELL YOU
THE TRUTH,
I DON'T HAVE THAT
KIND OF STUFF IN ME.
WELL, I THINK YOU'RE
WRONG ABOUT YOURSELF, BUT...
GIVE 'EM HELL.
WHICH WAY ARE
YOU GOING TO GO,
SHERIFF?
NEW YORK IS
CALLING YOU HOME:
MARTINIS,
PRETTY GIRLS,
THE YANKEES.
OR DO YOU WANT
TO STAY HERE?
ALL RIGHT, BROTHER,
DON'T SMOKE IT ALL
IN ONE BOWL.
YOU KEEP THIS.
I GOT TONY'S,
AND THAT'S PLENTY.
I WOULDN'T TRY
TO TAKE EXCEDRIN OUT
OF THIS FUCKING COUNTRY.
COME ON,
TAKE IT.
WHY THE HELL DID WE BUY
SO MUCH HASH ANYWAY?
Tony: AT THOSE PRICES,
WE COULDN'T AFFORD NOT TO.
UH-OH.
WOW.
Sheriff: I GUESS
THIS IS IT, MAN.
YEAH.
SEE YOU, BUDDY.
GOOD LUCK, BUDDY.
I'M GOING TO
MISS YOU GUYS.
YEAH, BULLSHIT.
THE SECOND WE'RE GONE,
YOU'LL PROBABLY FIND
A COUPLE OF CHIMPS
PRETTIER THAN BOTH OF US.
YOU FUCKER.
TAKE CARE.
I'LL SEE YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
SAFE TRAVELS.
YEAH.
Sheriff:
YEAH, GABY, LISTEN
YEAH, OK.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
HA HA HA!
NO. I JUST--I CAN'T
TALK ABOUT ANYTHING RIGHT NOW.
LISTEN, UH, NO,
I'M NOT INTERESTED IN
DISCUSSING THIS RIGHT NOW, OK?
I GOT PEOPLE
IN THE BACK OF MY CAR.
I'M WORKING.
GABY, LISTEN,
MAYBE WHEN THE SHIFT'S OVER,
I'LL CALL YOU,
WHATEVER.
WE'LL GO OUT, WE'LL GRAB
A BITE OR SOMETHING, OK?
[BEEPING]
LOOK, THAT'S MY DISPATCHER.
I GOT TO GO.
I GOT TO GO, BYE.
YEAH, IT'S 4 UNDERWAY.
Dispatcher: AFTER THE DROP,
CAN YOU SWING A PICKUP
AT THE STANHOPE?
LADY NAMED EASTERN
ASKED FOR YOU.
EASTERN? EASTERN? UH, YEAH.
WHERE'S THE DROP AT?
SHE DIDN'T SAY.
[MAN AND WOMAN MOANING]
[BREAKS SCREECHING]
Man in back seat:
FUCK!
I APOLOGIZE FOR
THE SUDDEN STOP, FOLKS,
BUT HOPEFULLY
YOU WERE BELTED IN.
OK. HERE WE ARE.
HERE, TAKE THAT.
PLEASURE SERVING YOU
AS ALWAYS, MR. HALLMAN.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[TELEPHONE BEEPS]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
THIS IS RAVITCH.
HEY, IT'S SHERIFF.
LISTEN, HOW MUCH IS
NEW YORK'S MOST FAMOUS
DIVORCE ATTORNEY WORTH TO YOU?
HE'S WORTH SQUAT,
BROTHER. I'M SINGLE.
UH, WHAT ABOUT
IF HE'S OUT BOINKING
AND GETTING BOMBED
AND HIS WIFE'S
NOT WITH HIM?
THAT'S A DIFFERENT STORY.
RAVITCH, CAN'T YOU
FIND ANOTHER DESK?
I'D SAY TWO BILLS.
YOU'RE A CHEAP SON OF A BITCH.
GRAB A PEN.
I'M SORRY.
OK, GIVE HER TO ME.
THANK YOU.
WE HEADED ANYWHERE
IN PARTICULAR?
HOW ABOUT WE JUST
DRIVE AROUND THE PARK
FOR A LITTLE BIT?
YOU GOT IT.
AROUND THE PARK.
I KNOW I HAVEN'T
DRIVEN YOU BEFORE.
I NEVER FORGET
A FACE.
HEY, DO YOU MIND
IF I SMOKE IN THE CAR?
IT'S THE ONLY PLACE
IN TOWN LEFT THAT
YOU CAN SMOKE.
GO AHEAD.
SO, UH,
WHO RECOMMENDED ME,
MISS EASTERN?
PLEASE CALL ME BETH.
OK, WHO RECOMMENDED
ME,BETH?
LEWIS McBRIDE.
LEW?
WHAT DID HE SAY?
"LOOK UP OLD SHERIFF
WHEN YOU GOT TO TOWN?"
HOW DID YOU KNOW
WHERE TO FIND ME?
LEW SAID YOU LIVED
IN BROOKLYN,
ODDS WERE YOU WOULD BE
IN THE BOOK.
YEAH, HUH?
AND ODDS WERE
THAT I'D PROBABLY STILL
BE STUCK IN BROOKLYN,
WHICH, YOU KNOW,
OBVIOUSLY I AM.
SO WHERE IS LEW, HUH?
IS HE IN TOWN HERE?
SHERIFF, THE DAY YOU
AND TONY LEFT PANANG,
A MAN CAME LOOKING
FOR A BIKE YOU GUYS
HAD RENTED.
HE BROUGHT THE POLICE.
ONLY THEY DIDN'T
FIND THE BIKE.
THEY DID FIND
104 GRAMS OF HASHISH.
SOME STASHED IN THE HUT,
SOME IN THE TRASH.
JESUS CHRIST.
AND LEWIS...CAUGHT HELL
FOR THAT, HUH?
WELL, YEAH. HE SPENT
THE LAST TWO YEARS
IN PRISON.
OH, MY GOD,
JESUS CHRIST.
WHAT A NIGHTMARE
THAT MUST BE, HUH?
IS HE STILL
IN PRISON NOW?
FOR 8 MORE DAYS, YEAH.
I MEAN, I WISH I WOULD
HAVE KNOWN SOONER.
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW
IF I COULD HAVE DONE
ANYTHING, BUT...
AT LEAST HE'S
GETTING OUT IN 8 DAYS,
THOUGH, HUH?
THAT'S, UH,
NOT THE CASE.
IN MALAYSIA, ANYBODY
FOUND WITH MORE THAN
100 GRAMS OF HASHISH
IS CONSIDERED
TO BE TRAFFICKING.
TRAFFICKING?
WHAT, IS THAT
LIKE DEALING?
SHERIFF,
IN ORDER FOR LEWIS NOT
TO BE CONSIDERED A DEALER,
YOU AND TONY HAVE TO
FLY BACK TO PANANG
AND ACCEPT YOUR SHARE
OF THE RESPONSIBILITY.
AND WHAT ABOUT
ME AND TONY?
WHAT HAPPENS TO US?
WELL, THE DEAL WAS THAT
IF BOTH OF YOU GO BACK,
IT'S 3 YEARS APIECE.
AND IF ONLY ONE OF YOU
GOES BACK, IT'S 6.
WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT. HOLD ON.
IT'S 3? IT'S 6?
WHY DON'T YOU FINISH
THAT SENTENCE FOR ME,
PLEASE?
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
3 YEARS IN PRISON, LADY,
6 YEARS IN PRISON.
SHERIFF, LET ME MAKE
THIS CLEAR TO YOU.
IN MALAYSIA,
DEALERS GET DEATH.
JESUS CHRIST,
FOR A SHITTY BRICK
OF HASH?
YOU'RE TELLING ME
IN 8 DAYS FROM NOW...
LEWIS McBRIDE
IS GOING TO HANG.
WHAT ARE YOU?
HIS LAWYER?
I'M HIS
AMERICAN LAWYER, YEAH.
SO, HOW ABOUT
WE HAVE DINNER
AND TALK MORE
ABOUT THIS?
UH, CAN'T.
I'M ON UNTIL 2:00,
BUT THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
DRINKS, THEN?
WHAT? AT 2:00?
DON'T YOU SLEEP?
WELL, I WANT TO
DO THIS MORE.
BREAKFAST?
CAN'T.
LUNCH?
I PULLED
A DAY SHIFT...
ALL RIGHT.
BETH, I CAN'T...
LET'S HAVE DINNER,
THEN.
TOMORROW NIGHT,
HERE, SAY, 7:00?
TOMORROW AT 7:00.
THANKS.
[DOOR UNLOCKING]
[MAN SPEAKING MALAY]
[CAR HORNS HONK]
EXCUSE ME, I'M LOOKING
FOR TONY CROFT.
YEAH, HE'S UP TOP.
THANKS.
Beth: SO, IF YOU DON'T
GO BACK, TONY,
LEWIS WILL HANG.
I'M SORRY.
YOU JUST CAN'T COME
OUT OF NOWHERE
AND TELL ME
THE BOTTOM'S DROPPED
OUT OF MY LIFE.
I GOT A WEEK TO BRACE
FOR THE IMPACT.
I'M SORRY, TONY,
THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I AM DOING.
YOU KNOW, THE ONLY THING
I DON'T UNDERSTAND,
HOW COME IT TOOK YOU GUYS
TWO YEARS TO TELL ME THIS.
LEWIS NEVER MENTIONED
THE TWO OF YOU,
NOT WHEN
HE WAS CONVICTED
TWO YEARS AGO,
NOT WHEN HE WAS
SENTENCED TO DEATH
10 MONTHS AGO.
IT WAS ONLY LAST WEEK
WHEN HIS FINAL PARDON
APPEAL WAS REJECTED.
I FOUND
A DETECTIVE.
THE SECOND
HE FOUND YOU,
HERE I AM.
YOU GOTTA UNDERSTAND,
THIS ISN'T JUST
ABOUT ME, ALL RIGHT?
I MEAN, LIKE ANYBODY,
I HAVE A LOT OF
RESPONSIBILITIES.
I'M ENGAGED.
I HAVE A FIANCEE.
I WANT TO
START A FAMILY.
A FAMILY'S WONDERFUL.
LEWIS WOULD LIKE TO
HAVE KIDS, TOO.
IF YOU CAN
POSTPONE HAVING YOURS
FOR A FEW YEARS,
HE'LL BE ABLE TO
HAVE THAT CHANCE.
I'M STAYING
AT THE STANHOPE.
COULD YOU CALL
ME THERE TONIGHT?
ALL RIGHT, I WILL.
THANKS.
THANKS, TONY.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
THIS IS BETH.
MISS EASTERN, HI,
IT'S TONY CROFT.
TONY, HI.
LISTEN, KERRIE AND I
TALKED THIS OVER,
AND WE WANT TO, UM...
WELL, I WANT TO--
FIRST OF ALL, SIMPLY,
I WANT TO SAY THAT,
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
THERE IS NO WAY IN HELL
THAT I'LL DO THE 6 YEARS.
BUT IF SHERIFF AGREES
TO GO BACK...
UM, WELL, THAT'S ANOTHER...
IN THAT CASE, UM...
YOU KNOW, IT WOULD BE
PRETTY HARD TO SAY NO.
UH, OK. WHAT YOU'VE SAID
HAS BEEN VERY CLEAR.
I'M ABOUT TO
GO HAVE DINNER WITH
SHERIFF RIGHT NOW,
I'LL CALL YOU IN THE MORNING
AND TELL YOU WHAT WAS SAID.
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL TALK TO YOU THEN.
THANK YOU, TONY.
GOOD NIGHT.
HEY.
HI.
SURPRISED I SHOWED?
NO. WHY?
BECAUSE I AM.
EASTERN PARTY?
UH, YEAH.
RIGHT THIS WAY.
THANKS.
Waitress:
WOULD YOU CARE
FOR A COCKTAIL?
GLASS OF HOUSE RED.
YEAH, I'LL HAVE
A RUM AND COKE, PLEASE.
THANK YOU.
REMINDS ME OF MALAYSIA,
RUM AND COKE.
SO, HAVE YOU SPOKEN
TO TONY?
YES, I DID. MM-HMM.
TONY SAID HE WAS
GOING TO GO BACK.
YOU KNOW, TONY TOLD ME
HE WAS GOING TO CALL ME
WHEN WE GOT BACK
FROM PANANG, SO...
SO WHAT ARE
YOU SAYING?
I CAN'T COUNT
ON TONY'S WORD?
NO, I'M NOT SAYING THAT.
NOT AT ALL.
JUST, UH, I THINK IT'S GOOD
TONY SAYS HE'S GOING BACK.
HOW COME?
BECAUSE I'M--
Waitress:
EXCUSE ME,
YOUR DRINKS.
THANKS.
THANKS A LOT.
TONY'S ONLY GOING BACK
IF YOU'RE GOING BACK.
YOU DIDN'T SAY THAT.
WELL, YOU DIDN'T
LET ME FINISH.
WELL, OK,
PLEASE FINISH,
THEN, BETH,
FINISH WHAT
YOU'RE GONNA SAY.
I DON'T EXPECT
YOU TO DO THIS...
WITHOUT SOME
SORT OF COMPENSATION.
BOTH OF LEWIS' PARENTS
HAVE PASSED ON.
THEY LEFT
A LITTLE SOMETHING.
HOW DOES $50,000 SOUND?
$50,000?
THAT SOUNDS FINE,
JUST FINE...
BUT FOR EACH YEAR.
$50,000 A YEAR.
YOU WANT ME
TO PAY YOU $150,000
FOR ASSUMING WHAT IS,
IN FACT,
YOUR SHARE
OF THE RESPONSIBILITY.
NO, NO, NO.
NOT YOU.
LEWIS'S ESTATE.
I MEAN, THEY GOT
HEAVY MONEY RIGHT?
COME ON, LET'S FACE IT.
YOU COME TO NEW YORK
ON WHAT'S PRETTY MUCH
A FISHING EXPEDITION.
YOU STAY ON THE PARK,
EAT HERE, NOT AT SOME
CHEAP COFFEE SHOP ON LEX.
ALL RIGHT.
SO I WILL
DRAW UP THE DRAFT
AGREEMENT TOMORROW.
IF YOU PROMISE ME
RIGHT NOW THAT YOU'RE
GOING TO GO BACK.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S
FUNNY TO ME...
REALLY FUNNY?
IS HOW PEOPLE
LIKE YOURSELF
THINK YOU CAN JUST
BUY PEOPLE LIKE ME.
BUT GUESS WHAT, BETH.
I WOULDN'T WALK
INTO YOUR SHIT STORM
FOR ANY PRICE,
AND ANY SLIM CHANCE
THAT THERE MIGHT HAVE BEEN
THAT I WOULD GO BACK
JUST WENT BYE-BYE WHEN
YOU TRIED TO PAY ME OFF.
Waitress:
MENUS?
I'M SORRY.
I THINK THERE'S BEEN
A MISTAKE TONIGHT.
I WOULDN'T WANT YOU
TO BUY ME DINNER,
BECAUSE THEN I WOULD BE
EXPLOITING YOU, COUNSELOR.
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
PLEASE, I'M SORRY.
I MADE A MISTAKE.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO INSULT YOU
BY OFFERING YOU MONEY.
INSULT ME?
YOU INSULTED
YOURSELF, BETH,
AND YOU ALREADY
MADE YOUR PLAY,
SO I THINK
WE'RE FINISHED.
MADE MY PLAY?
JESUS, I WOULD
MAKE ANY PLAY
TO SAVE LEWIS'S LIFE.
I KNOW YOU CARE
ABOUT THAT.
YEAH, WELL,
YOU KNOW WHAT, BETH?
I THINK YOU GOT
THE WRONG GUY HERE.
DON'T LET MY NICKNAME
FOOL YOU.
IT'S JUST
A BASTARDIZATION
OF MY LAST NAME,
WHICH IS VOLGECHEREV,
ALL RIGHT.
I KEEP MY MOUTH SHUT,
AND I KEEP MY HEAD DOWN,
BUT I DO WISH LEWIS
A LOT OF LUCK,
ESPECIALLY WITH YOU
AS HIS LAWYER.
OH, GOD.
I APPRECIATE YOUR CONCERN
FOR HIS WELL-BEING.
I MAY NOT BE THE BEST,
BUT I AM
THE MOST PERSISTENT.
THAT'S GREAT.
WELL, YOU SHOULD FUCKING
TAKE YOUR PERSISTENCY
AND NOT WASTE IT
ON ME.
YOU ONLY GOT
A FEW DAYS LEFT.
YOU'RE APPEALING TO
EMOTIONS I DON'T HAVE
AND A FUCKING MORALITY
THERE'S NO WAY
IN THE WORLD
I COULD AFFORD.
THAT MAY BE WHAT
YOU THINK YOU ARE, SHERIFF,
BUT LISTEN,
IT DOESN'T CHANGE THE FACT
THAT A MAN'S LIFE HANGS
IN THE BALANCE.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
HOW YOU DOING, MAN?
WHAT'S UP, SHERIFF?
HOW YOU DOING, TONY?
HEH HEH HEH.
HEH HEH...YEP.
HERE WE ARE.
LOOK, I'M FREEZING.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE--
YOU KNOW, MY SECRETARY'S
OUT TODAY, TONY.
I APOLOGIZE FOR
THE INCONVENIENCE.
SO YOU'LL HAVE
TO SEAT YOURSELF.
YEAH.
SO THIS IS
THE OFFICE, HUH?
HEH HEH.
LET'S JUST
SORT THIS OUT, OK?
YOU AND ME TOGETHER,
WITHOUT THAT, UH,
LAWYER BREATHING
DOWN OUR NECKS.
YEAH, SHE'S
PRETTY INTENSE, HUH?
NO SHIT, MAN.
AFTER SHE AMBUSHED ME,
I COULDN'T EAT
FOR TWO DAYS.
MY GIRLFRIEND
FORCED SOME TOAST DOWN
MY THROAT THIS MORNING.
YOU KNOW,
I THREW IT UP.
BUT THAT'S KIND OF
A DRY RUN
FOR OUR NEXT 3 YEARS
IN PANANG PRISON, YOU KNOW.
SO YOU'RE GOING TO--
YOU'RE GOING TO DO THIS?
YOU'RE GOING BACK?
NO.
YOU DON'T
GIVE A SHIT, DO YOU?
ARE YOU SAYING I DON'T
GIVE A DAMN ABOUT LEWIS?
WELL, THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
ACTING LIKE, YEAH.
BECAUSE IF YOU
BELIEVE THAT,
YOU DON'T KNOW
THE FIRST FUCKING
THING ABOUT ME.
FINE. FINE.
ALL RIGHT.
THEN HOW COME YOU'RE
SO READY TO SLAM
THE DOOR ON HIM?
BECAUSE I KNOW SOMETHING
ABOUT GUYS WHO HAVE CLUBS
AND BADGES, ALL RIGHT?
I'VE HAD MY ASS KICKED
BY THOSE BASTARDS, TONY.
IT'S NOT HOW YOU THINK.
JUST BECAUSE YOU DO
SOMETHING GOOD
DOESN'T MEAN THERE'S
GOING TO BE A HAPPY ENDING
TO THE WHOLE THING.
YOU COULD VERY EASILY
DIE OVER THERE.
OK, YEAH.
YOU THINK OF THAT?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK--
THIS IS THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE COIN, OK?
LET'S SAY,
IF THIS GOES DOWN
AND, GOD FORBID,
OK, LEWIS HANGS,
YOU DON'T THINK THIS
IS GOING TO BE, LIKE,
HEADLINE NEWS?
SHERIFF, THIS IS GOING
TO FOLLOW YOU AROUND
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
WHEREAS,
THE OTHER WAY,
WE COME HOME
A PAIR OF HEROES,
AND THEN WHAT?
THE CITY THROWS US
A TICKER-TAPE PARADE?
GOD, TONY, YOU'RE
A FUCKING BOY SCOUT.
YOU REALLY ARE.
LISTEN TO ME, OK?
LEWIS
WOULD'VE GONE BACK
FOR EITHER OF US.
YOU KNOW THAT.
THAT'S WHY I'LL
NEVER BE MISTAKEN
FOR LEWIS McBRIDE.
AFTERNOON,
MISS EASTERN.
THANK YOU.
WELCOME.
BETH EASTERN.
HI. I'M M.J. MAJOR,
A REPORTER FOR
THE NEW YORK
EXAMINER.
YOU'RE--
YOU'RE A WHAT?
A REPORTER.
REALLY.
YES.
AND--AND WHAT
WOULD YOU WANT WITH ME?
OH, COME ON, BETH.
I KNOW THE HANGING'S
IN LESS THAN A WEEK.
PRESS ON THIS THING
IS EXACTLY WHAT YOU
AND THE FAMILY NEED
FOR A PUBLIC OUTCRY.
THE FAMILY WANTS THIS
KEPT QUIET.
OH, REALLY? LISTEN,
IN THIS INSTANCE,
YOUR INTERESTS
AND THE INTERESTS OF
THE PUBLIC CONVERGE.
HOW DID YOU FIND OUT
ABOUT THIS?
MY SOURCE IS AT
THE STATE DEPARTMENT.
THERE'S A BLACKOUT
AT THE STATE DEPARTMENT.
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THEY PASSED THE BUCK.
THEY SOLD IT AS DIPLOMACY.
THAT'S WHY YOU NEED ME,
AND FAST.
I CAN MAKE THIS
HAPPEN FAST, BETH.
IN 48 HOURS, LEWIS McBRIDE
CAN BE OVER EVERY--
NO, NO.
LISTEN TO ME.
DO YOU REMEMBER
SINGAPORE?
THE AMERICAN KID
WHO GRAFFITIED A CAR?
SURE.
BECAUSE OF
THE MEDIA FRENZY,
THEY HAD TO CANE
THE KID.
BUT THAT WAS A CANING
TO SHOW SOME NATIONAL BACKBONE.
THIS IS A HANGING!
OH, AND I DON'T
KNOW THAT?
LISTEN, SOME AUSSIE
DOPE DEALER'S MOTHER
WENT ON EVERY ENGLISH-
SPEAKING TALK SHOW
FROM SIDNEY TO LONDON.
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED?
THEY HUNG HER SON
A WEEK EARLY
TO SHUT HER UP.
EXCUSE ME. I'VE GOT
A REALLY BIG WEEK.
BETH, I CAN MAKE MIRACLES
HAPPEN IN A WEEK.
DON'T DO THIS.
DON'T DO IT.
WAIT A MINUTE,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST--
WHAT?!
I'M SORRY.
JESUS CHRIST!
I'M...VERY SORRY.
JUST...
COULD I HAVE THAT,
PLEASE?
IS HE BOYISH?
WHAT?
IS HE CUTE?
IS HE CLEAN-CUT?
BECAUSE IF HE IS,
AND I PUT HIM ON
THE FRONT PAGE
OF MY NEWS--
GIVE ME SOME TIME.
GIVE ME SOME TIME,
SOME SPACE,
AND I'LL GIVE YOU
YOUR STORY.
WHEN?
SOON.
I'M GOING
TO CALL YOU, BETH.
WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I HAVE A TAPE
I WANT YOU TO WATCH.
YEAH? JESUS CHRIST,
YOU DON'T LET UP, DO YOU?
I CAN'T.
OK, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO WATCH YOUR TAPE.
HONEST TO GOD, I AM.
BUT I WAS ACTUALLY GOING
TO GO GET SOMETHING TO EAT.
SO I'LL WATCH IT LATER.
ARE YOU INVITING ME
TO DINNER,
OR ARE WE STILL MAD
AT EACH OTHER?
BOTH.
CHEERS.
CHEERS
IT'S A TOAST
TO LEWIS.
SWEET GUY...
LOVED THE ANIMALS.
LOVED HIS BEER.
DID HE?
YEAH.
I NEVER KNEW THAT
ABOUT HIM.
TELL ME SOMETHING ELSE.
REALLY, BEER IS ALL
I REALLY REMEMBER.
THAT'S IT?
YEAH.
WOW.
HE DIDN'T MAKE REALLY
MUCH OF AN IMPRESSION,
THEN, DID HE?
LEWIS?
MM-HMM.
WHAT, ARE YOU
KIDDING ME?
HAVE YOU SPENT A LOT
OF TIME WITH HIM?
I'VE...NEVER HAD A BEER
WITH HIM.
HE IS,
HONESTLY, BETH...
ONE OF
THE SWEETEST PEOPLE
I'VE EVER MET
IN MY LIFE.
LEWIS IS THE KIND OF GUY
WHO'D HAVE, LIKE,
A BEGGAR ON
THE STREET, RIGHT?
AND HE JUST...
I DON'T KNOW.
HE'D TOUCH HIM SOMEHOW,
TALK TO HIM.
THE GUY COULD HAVE,
LIKE, AN ILLNESS, MAYBE,
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW,
A LANGUAGE BARRIER.
WHATEVER IT WAS,
HE JUST COULD SEE
PEOPLE, I GUESS.
GOT A BIG HEART.
YEAH...
THAT'S NICE.
WHAT ELSE CAN YOU
TELL ME ABOUT HIM?
YOU ARE GOOD,
AREN'T YOU?
SHERIFF, WHAT DO
YOU THINK ABOUT ME?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU SEEM TO THINK
I HAVE ALL THESE
WILES AND STRATAGEMS.
I DON'T.
I HAVE A MAN'S LIFE
IN MY HANDS.
I GET THAT.
LET ME ASK YOU
A QUESTION, BETH.
AND ASK YOURSELF
THIS HONESTLY.
WOULD YOU GO BACK?
I WOULDN'T ASK YOU
OR TONY...TO DO THIS
IF I HADN'T ALREADY ANSWERED
THE QUESTION FOR MYSELF.
YEAH.
BUT I GUESS, YOU KNOW,
I DON'T THINK
YOU COULD EVER REALLY
HONESTLY ANSWER THAT
UNLESS YOU'RE
IN THAT SITUATION
YOURSELF, YOU KNOW?
IT'S NOT A--
WHOA!
HI, GABY.
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M NOT SOME PIECE OF DIRT
YOU GET OFF ON
THEN FLUSH DOWN THE JOHN,
ALL RIGHT?
RIGHT.
HE'LL FUCK YOU
AND THEN SNEAKS OUT--
BY THE FIRE ESCAPE,
IF HE HAS TO.
UNLESS YOU DON'T
GIVE A SHIT.
UNLESS YOU'RE SOME WHORE.
I'M HIS WIFE.
WHAT?
FUCK YOU
FOR NOT WEARING A RING.
THAT'S MY FRIEND
GABY.
HEH HEH.
WOW.
YEAH.
GOOD THING YOU DIDN'T
GIVE HER A SOCIAL DISEASE.
WE'D ALL BE DEAD.
UH, THANKS, FRANK.
I APPRECIATE IT.
SO WHEN DID YOU GUYS
TIE THE KNOT?
YOU KNOW WHAT,
FRANK?
GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE, WILL YOU?
HA HA HA!
Beth:
OK? HA HA.
YEAH.
WELL, THAT WAS FUN.
THAT WAS SOMETHING.
"I'M HIS WIFE."
I LIKE THAT ONE.
THANKS.
YOU LEFT THIS
ON THE TABLE.
PLEASE WATCH IT.
I WILL, BETH.
I WILL.
GOOD NIGHT.
[KEYS JINGLE IN LOCK]
OK.
Beth, on tape:
OK, LEWIS. GO AHEAD.
Lewis, on tape:
WHOO. UM...
HEY, GUYS.
SHERIFF...TONY.
LONG TIME, HUH?
I GUESS IF YOU'RE
SEEING THIS TAPE,
YOU KIND OF FIGURED THAT
MY VACATION PLANS, UH...
CHANGED.
I WAS SET TO GO OFF AND...
TRY AND SAVE THE ORANGUTAN,
DO WHAT I C-CAN.
I-IRONIC, ISN'T IT?
LOOK WHO'S...
CAGED AND...
[MUMBLES]
UM, THIS...LITTLE D-DOCUDRAMA
HERE WAS NOT MY IDEA,
AND I'M SORRY, BUT, UM...
THE FOLKS AT
THE AMERICAN CITIZEN SERVICE
H-HAVE DONE ALL THEY CAN,
AND--AND NOW THEY TELL ME
THAT--THAT YOU GUYS
ARE MY LAST CHANCE.
SO...I DON'T KNOW IF--
IF YOU EVEN--
IF YOU'RE EVEN THINKING
ABOUT COMING BACK,
BUT IF THERE'S
THE SLIGHTEST CHANCE,
I WILL TELL YOU THIS,
THAT, UM...
I--I HAVEN'T BEEN, UH,
HARMED IN ANY WAY.
I--I HAVEN'T--
I HAVEN'T BEEN TORTURED.
EXCEPT BY BOREDOM
AND HUNGER.
NOT--NOT A WHOLE LOT OF
GOOD STUFF TO EAT.
NO BURGERS FOR YOU,
SHERIFF,
BUT...THERE'S RICE,
PLENTY OF RICE.
YOUR RICE NEEDS
DEFINITELY WILL BE MET.
BUT, UM...
IF YOU DO...
IF YOU DO COME BACK,
I WILL--I WILL
FEEL GUILTY, YES.
AND I ALREADY DO JUST FOR--
JUST FOR ASKING YOU, BUT...
AT LEAST I WON'T--
I WON'T FEEL THE FEAR,
AND I KNOW
THAT'S NOT FAIR, UM...
SO THAT'S
WHY I'M DOING THIS.
[MACHINERY WHIRS]
[MEN TALKING]
HEY!
I'M BUSY.
CAN'T TAKE YOU TODAY.
YEAH, WELL,
I CAN'T TAKE YOU EITHER.
HA HA.
HEY, POP, YOU REMEMBER
THAT TRIP I TOOK
A COUPLE YEARS BACK,
TO MALAYSIA?
YEAH. I REMEMBER.
SOME SLEAZE WAS SELLING
FREQUENT FLYER MILES,
RIGHT?
WELL,
THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
THE POINT IS,
THERE'S THIS GUY
THAT'S STILL OVER THERE
IN PANANG, WHERE I WAS,
AND HE'S KIND OF A PAL.
BUT ANYWAY,
THEY'RE GOING TO--
THEY'RE GOING TO HANG HIM.
THEY FOUND
SOME HASHISH ON HIM.
REALLY?
YEAH.
BUT SOME OF THE HASH
WAS MINE.
AND SO, IF I GO BACK THERE,
I'D HAVE TO--
I'D HAVE TO SERVE
3 YEARS IN PRISON--
YOU KNOW, PANANG PRISON.
BUT IF I DON'T GO BACK,
THEY HANG THIS GUY.
THEY DON'T HANG GUYS
FOR HASHISH.
I'M NOT THAT NAIVE.
YOU'RE LEAVING SOMETHING
OUT, LIKE ALWAYS.
I'M NOT LEAVING
ANYTHING OUT, DAD.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS FUCKED UP.
IT'S A LITTLE UNFAIR,
BUT THAT'S THE WAY IT IS
OVER THERE.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
SO MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT
AND I'M WRONG.
YOU STILL WANT MY ADVICE
IN THIS HANGING STUFF?
YEAH.
FEELS LIKE
AN EASY CALL.
UH, IF YOU WEREN'T
WASTING YOUR LIFE HERE,
IT MIGHT BE DIFFERENT.
BUT THIS PAL
YOU'LL SAVE...
ODDS ARE HE'S WORTH
MORE THAN YOU,
SO MY ADVICE--YOU GO.
YOU DO THE TIME.
HA HA.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU LOOK SICK.
I MEAN, YOU'RE MY DAD.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BEG ME
NOT TO GO BACK, YOU KNOW?
IT'S JUST NOT
WHAT I EXPECTED
TO HEAR, I GUESS.
LIGHTEN UP.
I'M JUST YANKIN'
YOUR CRANK.
WHY PUT YOURSELF
THROUGH ALL THE AGONY
WHEN YOU KNOW
YOU'RE NOT GOING?
I MEAN,
WHO'S KIDDING WHO?
WHAT ARE WE,
SUCKERS HERE?
Beth: NO, WHAT--
THEY DIDWHAT?
THEY WEIGHED HIM?
FOR--WELL, FOR WHAT?
[WHISPERS]
Oh...Jesus.
UH...
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
I...
I HAVE TO GET MY--
I HAVE TO GET THE CALL.
IT MIGHT BE ONE OF THE GUYS.
WE'LL TALK TOMORROW?
[RING]
UM, THIS IS--
THIS IS BETH.
BETH, HI.
YOU SOUND STRESSED.
THIS IS M.J. MAJOR.
UM...
IS THIS A BAD TIME?
NO. NO, IT'S
NOT A BAD TIME.
BETH, WHAT'S WRONG?
HOW CAN I HELP?
YOU KNOW...
YOU WANT TO KNOW
HOW YOU CAN HELP?
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE, M.J.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
LISTEN, I'VE
GOT THE RESOURCES
TO A DAILY PAPER
WITH WORLDWIDE
READERSHIP.
WE ARE PICKED UP BY
THEINTERNATIONAL
HERALD TRIB.
WE COULD BE DOING
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
BETH--
PHOTOGRAPHS, ARTICLES,
PETITIONS--
EVERY SINGLE ONE
IS A DEATH WARRANT, M.J.
A DEATH WARRANT.
NOW, I'VE ASKED YOU NICELY
TO STAY OUT OF THIS
UNTIL AFTER THE HEARING.
BETH, IF I DON'T GET
SOMETHING FROM YOU SOON,
I'M GOING TO HAVE
TO GO STRAIGHT
TO YOUR TWO GUYS.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO THEY ARE,
OTHERWISE YOU'D ALREADY
BE THERE, WOULDN'T YOU?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M HANGING UP.
BETH, I'M GOING
TO NEED TO HEAR
FROM YOU VERY SOON.
YOU WILL.
[HANGS UP]
SHERIFF.
HEY.
WELL, HI.
I--I DIDN'T EXPECT
TO SEE YOU. COME ON IN.
THANKS.
HOW YOU DOING?
COULDN'T BE BETTER.
YEAH?
PLEASE GIVE ME
SOME GOOD NEWS.
ARE YOU, UM...
DID YOU GET MY MESSAGE
ABOUT DINNER?
YEAH. YEAH,
I GOT YOUR MESSAGE,
BUT I CAN'T MAKE
DINNER, ACTUALLY.
I GOT SOME PLANS
TONIGHT,
BUT I DID WANT
TO RETURN THIS
TO YOU--THE TAPE.
UH...
OK, DID YOU WATCH IT?
YEAH, I WATCHED IT.
I WATCHED THE
WHOLE THING.
UH-HUH?
AND...I DID A LOT OF
SOUL-SEARCHING
LAST NIGHT WITH THIS.
RIGHT.
AND YOU KNOW,
I FIGURED YOU GOT
TO KNOW, YOU KNOW,
SOONER THAN LATER
BECAUSE OF EVERYTHING.
I JUST WANTED
TO COME AND--
TO LET YOU KNOW
WHERE YOU STAND WITH ME.
THAT'S GOOD.
WHERE DO I STAND...
WITH YOU?
I TALKED TO TONY,
AND HE SAID THAT HE'S,
YOU KNOW, GOING BY ME.
AND HE'S, LIKE, HALFWAY
TO PANANG ALREADY.
I THINK HE JUST
NEEDS A NUDGE.
BUT I THINK--I THINK
HE'LL PROBABLY GO BACK,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
I LOOKED INSIDE,
DEEP INSIDE, BETH,
TO FIND SOMETHING.
BUT...
IT ISN'T IN ME.
OH, IT ISN'T...
IN YOU.
GOD, JOT THAT DOWN,
WOULD YOU?
DO ME A FAVOR,
WRITE THAT DOWN FOR ME.
I MEAN, JUST A FEW WORDS.
I'D LOVE TO GIVE THEM TO LEW
RIGHT BEFORE HE HANGS.
YOU KNOW,
LETTER FROM A PAL.
"LISTEN, I SEARCHED MY SOUL"
WAS THE BEST PART FOR ME.
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S--THAT'S GREAT.
I THINK HE'D LOVE TO KNOW
THAT YOU SEARCHED YOUR SOUL
BEFORE...
YOU DECIDED NOT TO GO.
[WHISPERS]
Yeah.
THEY JUST TOLD ME THAT
THEY WEIGHED LEWIS TODAY
FOR THE TRAPDOORS
OF THE GALLOWS.
BETH--
[WHISPERS]
Get out of here.
GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE,
SHERIFF.
[SIGHS]
SHERIFF...IS HERE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY,
GUYS? HOW YOU DOING?
SO, SHERIFF, I THOUGHT
YOU HAD PLANS.
YEAH,
WELL, I WAS BUSY.
I HAD A THING
AT LINCOLN CENTER.
YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN?
BUT, UH...
HERE I AM.
READY TO DISCUSS.
WHAT'D I ORDER?
SHERIFF, THIS IS KERRIE,
MY FIANCEE.
KERRIE,
JOHN VOLGECHEROV.
HOW YOU DOING?
NICE TO MEET YOU.
YOU'RE NOT, UM...
NOT AS PLATINUM AS
I EXPECTED YOU TO BE.
SO, SHERIFF...
IT'S--IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS
THAT, WITH GOOD REASON,
YOU HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO INTENTION
OF GOING BACK, RIGHT?
WHERE?
HA.
IS HE DRUNK?
OH, I MEAN--
YOU MEAN "BACK"
LIKE BACK TO PRISON.
RIGHT,
WELL, I'VE NEVER
ACTUALLY BEEN.
THEY HAVE A FORK?
YOU HAVE A FORK
I COULD USE?
THANK YOU. I NEVER
BEEN TO PRISON.
THUS, I CAN'T GO
BACK TO SOMEWHERE
I'VE NEVER BEEN.
THANK YOU. THAT WAS
BRILLIANTLY UNHELPFUL.
YES.
BETH, I CHECKED.
PANANG PRISON IS AT
A THIRD-WORLD LEVEL
OF SANITATION, NUTRITION.
RICE RATIONS
DON'T MEET MINIMUM
CALORIC REQUIREMENTS--
LEWIS IS PROVIDED
WITH FOOD FROM
AMNESTY INTERNATIONAL.
SO WOULD TONY--
INMATES
HAVE BEEN TORTURED.
HE HASN'T BEEN TOUCHED.
INMATES HAVE DIED
OF TYPHUS.
WELL, THAT'S ONLY
BECAUSE OF OVERCROWDING,
AND LEWIS HAS
HIS OWN CELL--
AS WOULD TONY...
AND SHERIFF, IF
HE DECIDES TO GO BACK.
Sheriff:
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
AND THE OTHER THING
I THINK THAT YOU LADIES
HAVE OVERLOOKED...
IS THAT THAT BUILDING'S
NOT UP TO CODE.
Beth: OH, JESUS--
WHAT ARE YOU,
THE CLASS CLOWN?
AND WHO ARE YOU TO TELL THEM
TO GIVE UP THEIR FREEDOM
AND MAYBE LOSE THEIR LIVES?
I REPRESENT A BOY
WHO'S BEEN SENTENCED TO DEATH.
RIGHT.
FOR THE SAKE OF SOME CLIENT,
YOU DEMAND THAT THEY--
Beth: I DEMAND?
NO, NO, NO.
YOU DEMAND.
I DON'T DEMAND.
I HAVE NOT
DEMANDED ANYTHING--
DEMAND THAT THEY
ENDURE 3 OR 6 YEARS
OF GOD KNOWS WHAT,
AND I THINK THAT IS INSANE.
YEAH, IT'S INSANE, OK?
I'M GOING TO GO BACK.
WHAT?
Tony: OK?
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
IN THE MIDDLE OF THIS
WHOLE THING, WHAT MATTERS?
LEWIS DOESN'T DIE.
SOMEBODY'S GOT TO DO
SOMETHING. PLEASE.
WHERE'S THE COURT DOCUMENT
THAT GUARANTEES THIS DEAL?
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL OF
MALAYSIA HAS AGREED TO--
YEAH, SO WHERE IS IT?
WHY DON'T WE HAVE A COPY?
IT'S AN ORAL AGREEMENT.
NO. NO.
TONY DOESN'T GO ANYWHERE
TILL WE HAVE THAT DOCUMENT
IN OUR HANDS.
THEY DON'T WORK
THAT WAY.
I WISH THEY DID.
I CANNOT GET ANYTHING
TO YOU IN WRITING.
I'LL BE AT HOME
IF YOU WANT ME.
I'M SORRY, TONY.
I'M SORRY.
SHE--SHE'S
JUST SCARED, ALL RIGHT?
SHE'S MORE SCARED
THAN I AM.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO EXCUSE ME. I'M--
IF I'M GOING TO GET HER
TO WAIT 3 YEARS FOR ME, I...
I GUESS 6...
I SHOULDN'T KEEP HER
WAITING TONIGHT.
TONY, WHAT CAN I SAY?
THANK YOU...
THANK YOU.
YEAH. SURE.
ALL RIGHT, TONY.
SEE YOU, MAN.
SEE YOU LATER, MAN.
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
RIGHT, SHERIFF.
SHE'S PRETTY UPSET.
GO TALK TO THE FIRM.
WELL...
QUITE A PARTY.
SO WHAT ARE
YOU GOING TO DO,
GO BACK TO YOUR HOTEL?
OH...YES.
GOT TO CALL PANANG,
GIVE THEM THE GOOD NEWS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SO I GUESS LEW'S GOING
TO BE OK, THEN, HUH?
WHICH MEANS, YOU KNOW...
YOU'RE OFF THE HOOK?
I'M OFF THE HOOK,
HUH?
GOOD NIGHT.
[GASPING, SHIVERING]
Man: JAFFE, I WANT A FOLLOW-UP
ON THE CANARSIE FIRE.
RIGHT.
NICE OF YOU TO JOIN US, RAVITCH.
Ravitch:
IT'S MY PLEASURE.
OK, MR. LATE,
I'D LIKE SOME PICTURES
OF A SHOPKEEPER,
BURNT OUT.
Ravitch: YOU GOT IT.
M.J.!
WHERE'S
MY PENSION FUND FRAUD?
I THOUGHT YOU HAD
A C.P.A. WHO WAS READY
TO TALK ON BACKGROUNDS.
I DID. I DID, AND...
SHE'S GIVING ME GOLD.
I'M JUST FACT-CHECKING
A FEW POINTS,
AND I'M LOOKING
FOR A SOURCE...
CALLED SHERIFF.
RING ANYBODY'S BELL?
SHERIFF?
Editor:
OK, LET'S GO, THEN.
[BUZZ]
Sheriff, on intercom:
YEAH?
HI. IT'S--
IT'S BETH.
I TALKED TO THE GARAGE,
AND THEY SAID
YOU CALLED IN SICK.
CAN I COME UP
AND SEE YOU?
UH...
SURE.
[DOOR BUZZES]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
HI.
HI THERE.
I BROUGHT YOU
SOME GOODIES
FROM ZABAR'S.
JEWISH PENICILLIN,
CURE YOU RIGHT UP.
ISN'T THAT NICE?
SHOULD I BEWARE
LAWYERS BEARING GIFTS?
THINK I'M GONNA
HAVE A BEER.
DO YOU WANT ONE?
UH...BEER, SURE.
YOU'RE QUITE
THE AVID READER,
AREN'T YOU?
OR IS THIS JUST...
YEAH,
JUST FOR SHOWING OFF.
ALL THE VISITORS I HAVE,
I KEEP MY PLACE REAL
IMPRESSIVE, DON'T I?
IT'S NICE.
ACTUALLY, THE BOOKS
ARE KIND OF A RECENT
DEVELOPMENT.
WHEN I WAS IN SCHOOL,
I TRIED LIKE HELL
TO AVOID READING.
THEN I GRADUATE AND REALIZE
I DON'T KNOW SHIT.
YEAH.
WHO DOES?
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
SO ANYWAY, I START
GETTING THE BOOKS,
AND...
DO SOME READING,
LEARN ABOUT THE WORLD
AROUND ME.
JUST TRYING TO BE
CIVILIZED, I GUESS, BETH.
THAT'S GOOD.
LEWIS SAID YOU WERE
BETTER THAN YOU
THOUGHT YOU WERE.
A LOT OF THEM
ARE POP-UP BOOKS,
COLORING...
THAT KIND OF THING.
WHERE'S YOUR PASSPORT?
WHAT?
I JUST WANT TO SEE
YOUR PASSPORT.
IN CASE IT'S NOT GOOD,
YOU KNOW,
I CAN RENEW IT TOMORROW
ON AN EMERGENCY BASIS
IF YOU...DECIDE
SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
SO THEN WHEN YOU SAID
THAT THING ABOUT ME
BEING OFF THE HOOK,
YOU WERE PRETTY MUCH JUST
LYING TO MY FACE, RIGHT?
NO, I THINK YOU WERE
LYING TO YOURSELF.
COME ON, SHERIFF.
ONLY A TOTAL BASTARD
WOULD LET TONY GO ALONE.
YEAH, WELL, I'M NOT
IN CHARGE OF TONY.
I'M NOT HIS DAD.
I KNOW THAT.
TONY'S A MAN WHO'S GOT...
TONY'S A GOOD GUY,
BUT HE'S GOT
A FUTURE
AND
A SEXY FIANCEE.
YEAH.
6 YEARS UNDER
ANY CIRCUMSTANCE
IS GONNA BE
HARD AS HELL,
BUT THIS--THIS CASE,
IT'S INCONCEIVABLE.
MM-HMM.
I THINK TONY'S A MAN
OF HIS WORD.
TONY CALLED ME
3 DAYS AGO
AND TOLD ME THAT
HE COULDN'T DO
6 YEARS.
I KNOW WHAT HE SAID
LAST NIGHT.
I APPLAUD
HIS IDEALISM, BUT...
I CAN'T COUNT ON IT.
I HAVE TO HAVE YOU
ON THAT PLANE,
SHERIFF.
PLEASE SHOW ME
YOUR PASSPORT.
NOT THAT IT'S ANY
OF YOUR BUSINESS,
BUT MY PASSPORT'S GOOD.
IT IS?
YEAH.
SHOW IT TO ME.
TAKE MY WORD FOR IT.
YOU'D TAKE 3 YEARS
FROM ME, BUT YOU
WOULDN'T TAKE MY WORD?
OK. ALL RIGHT,
I PUSHED IT.
I'M SORRY.
I TRUST YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
COME ON, BETH.
YOU GONNA GO FOR ME
IF YOU DON'T HAVE
A CLIENT?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WH--WHAT?
KINDA MAKES SENSE TO ME.
YOU OFFER ME MONEY,
AND I DON'T TAKE THAT,
SO YOU GOT 4 DAYS LEFT,
SO YOU FIGURE WHY DON'T
I JUST TRY TO FUCK THE GUY
'CAUSE THEN MAYBE
I'LL GET HIM TO DO
WHAT I WANT.
THAT'S EXACTLY ME.
THAT'S ACTUALLY
EXACTLY ME.
WHAT WAS
THE MONEY OFFER?
I'M GONNA GET YOU
TO GO BACK BECAUSE
I'M GONNA GIVE YOU
A LITTLE SEX.
THAT'S EXACTLY
FUCKING ME.
[BOTTLE SHATTERS]
GO FUCK YOURSELF.
WHOO! THAT'S FUN,
ISN'T IT?
I'M THE GUY THAT'S
GOTTA CLEAN UP,
AND THAT'S A LOT OF
FUCKING FUN,
ISN'T IT?
HAVE FUN CLEANING
IT UP, SHERIFF.
[NEIGHBOR YELLING]
Neighbor: SHUT UP! YOU'RE MAKING
TOO MUCH GOD DAMNED NOISE!
OPEN THE DOOR!
OPEN THE DOOR,
YOU FUCKING PUSSY!
SHERIFF--
OPEN YOUR FUCKING DOOR!
[CAMERA CLICKS]
SHERIFF--
TURNABOUT'S FAIR GAME,
RIGHT, SHERIFF?
NOW THAT YOU'RE NEWS--
SHERIFF, DON'T!
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
TAKING PICTURES
OF ME? HUH?
I'LL BUST YOUR
FUCKING FACE OPEN,
YOU LITTLE FUCKER!
I'M DOING MY JOB.
GET THE FUCK
OUT OF MY FACE.
I'LL SUE YOUR ASS.
Beth: SHERIFF?
SHERIFF, LISTEN--
CAN I JUST
TALK TO YOU
FOR ONE SECOND?
PLEASE?
OH, WAS THAT YOUR
PHOTOGRAPHER UP THERE?
IS THAT SHERIFF?
IS THAT YOUR PHOTOGRAPHER?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
YOU'RE GONNA PRINT
PICTURES NOW?
PEOPLE ARE SNIFFING
AROUND THIS STORY.
IT'S ABOUT TO BLOW
WIDE OPEN.
OK? I FOUND
THIS STORY FIRST,
I'M GONNA PRINT IT
FIRST, PERIOD!
YOUR STORY COULD
COST LEWIS HIS LIFE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
YOU GIVE ME 3 DAYS...
3 DAYS UNTIL THE HEARING
IS OVER, OK?
YOU PROMISE ME THAT YOU
WILL NOT TALK TO A SOUL
ANDTHAT I HAVE LEWIS
EXCLUSIVELY.
EXCLUSIVE.
THEN YOU PROMISE ME
YOU'RE GONNA HOLD OFF
ON THE STORY.
3 DAYS, BETH.
SLOW DOWN, DRIVER,
YOU'RE MAKING ME NERVOUS.
I'M SORRY, SIR.
IT'S A BAD HABIT I GOT.
I WAS ALL MELLOWED OUT,
BUT YOU FUCKED THAT UP.
HOPE YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO TELL ME I CAN'T
SMOKE BACK HERE.
NO, MATTER OF FACT,
IT'S THE ONLY PLACE LEFT
IN TOWN YOUCANSMOKE.
WHAT THE FUCK ARE
YOU DOING?
ARE YOU SMOKING CRACK?
CRACK IS FOR OUR
AFRICAN-AMERICAN BRETHREN.
THIS IS PURE ROCK COCAINE.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
DRIVER,
YOU CAN RAISE
THE PARTITION.
I CAN RAISE
WHATEVER
YOU WANNA DO.
WHATEVER I WANNA DO?
DO YOU WANNA SEE
WHAT I WANNA DO?
HUH?
HA HA!
FUCKING COCKSUCKER.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I WANT TO SEE YOU.
OK.
WHAT'S HAPPENING
HERE, BETH?
YOU TELL ME, SHERIFF.
I'M NOT SURE,
BUT I KNOW THAT
I JUST...
I CAN'T TAKE THIS
ANYMORE.
SO DON'T TAKE IT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE KILLING ME,
BETH.
I'M KILLING YOU?
YOU'RE KILLING ME.
SHERIFF?
OH, SHIT.
SHERIFF,
ARE YOU THERE?
I WAS JUST GONNA SAY
THAT I HOPED THAT, UM...
YOU DON'T THINK
LAST NIGHT WAS ABOUT...
UM...
COULD YOU CALL ME?
WHEN YOU GET THIS MESSAGE?
THAT'D BE GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
CAN I SIT NEXT TO YOU
ON THE PLANE?
[PLANE TAKING OFF]
Beth: HEY, TONY.
TONY?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. YEAH,
I'M FINE.
YOU SURE?
YOU WANNA, UM...
DO YOU WANNA
SWITCH WITH US?
YEAH, TONY, YOU WANT
TO SWITCH SEATS
OR SOMETHING?
NO, NO. YOU KNOW...
I LIKE MY SEAT.
IT'S FINE.
SHERIFF,
I'M A BIG BOY.
I DON'T NEED SOMEBODY
TO HOLD MY HAND, OK?
OK.
AT LEAST TILL WE GET OVER
THE PHILIPPINES.
Man: LET'S GO!
WHOO! LOOK OUT!
WA-HOO!
WE SHOULD ALL
WASH UP.
MEET, LIKE,
IN A HALF-HOUR
OR SOMETHING.
Tony:
FINE WITH ME.
IS THAT COOL
WITH EVERYONE?
SURE.
COOL.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
ALL RIGHT, MAN.
HI.
SHERIFF...
WHAT'S WRONG?
UM...
WHAT?
I'M GONNA MISS YOU.
[MEN SPEAKING MALAY]
HE WON'T BEND.
ONLY ONE VISITOR
ALLOWED IN THERE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
ONE AT A TIME
OR WHAT?
NO, NO.
ONLY ONE TODAY.
OH, GREAT.
THAT'S GREAT.
WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO DO?
DO YOU MIND IF
I GO BACK THERE,
TONY, AND SEE HIM?
NO, NO.
ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT HIS?
YEAH, YOU GO.
GO AHEAD.
TELL HIM
I'LL SEE HIM SOON.
OK.
OK, COME
BACK HERE.
[MEN SPEAKING MALAY]
[UNLOCKS DOOR]
[SPEAKS MALAY]
YEAH, I HEAR YOU.
[MAN COUGHING]
LEW?
[WEAK MUMBLING]
LEWIS?
SHERIFF?
YEAH.
DIDN'T THEY TELL YOU
I WAS COMING?
I WAS PRAYING.
I...THOUGHT YOU WERE
A DREAM 'CAUSE...
NO PRAYER OF
MINE HAS EVER BEEN
ANSWERED HERE BEFORE.
YEAH? I SURE AS HELL
AIN'T A DREAM, I'LL
TELL YOU THAT.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
IT'S GOOD
TO SEE YOU.
[CRYING]
YOU, TOO.
HOW ARE YOU, MAN?
I'M BETTER NOW.
THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S GOOD. YEAH.
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M ALL RIGHT, MAN.
YOU LOOK GOOD.
NICE, NICE.
SPIFF-ON.
YEAH.
YOU'VE COME SO FAR.
ARE YOU THIRSTY
AT ALL?
DO YOU--YOU WANT
SOME TEA?
I CAN MAKE SOME TEA.
ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
LET'S HAVE SOME TEA.
OK. IT'S NOT WARM
OR ANYTHING, BUT--
THAT'S OK.
YEAH?
YOU'RE NOT COLD,
ARE YOU?
NO, I'M NOT COLD.
NO?
TONY IS HERE
TO SEE YOU, TOO.
HE'S OUTSIDE.
YOU SEE, THEY...
THEY TOOK AWAY
MY BLANKET THERE.
WHY'D THEY TAKE
YOUR BLANKET AWAY?
'CAUSE THEY WERE
SCARED THAT I WAS
GONNA TEAR IT
INTO STRIPS
AND HANG MYSELF.
SO I SAID,
"HEY, GUYS,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
I'M PAYING YOU FOR?"
[LAUGHTER]
[COUGHING]
YEAH...
THANK YOU, MAN.
THAT'S GOOD TEA.
I KNOW WHY TONY
DIDN'T COME IN HERE.
I KNOW 'CAUSE
THERE'S NO GOD
IN HERE.
THEY ONLY LET ONE VISITOR
AT A TIME HERE.
YOU SEE, THAT'S WHY
I PRAY NOW, SHERIFF.
BECAUSE...OUT THERE,
THERE'S...THERE'S
NO NEED TO--TO PRAY
WHERE GOD'S HAND
IS FELT.
YOU KNOW?
WHERE GOD IS--
IS APPARENT?
BUT IN HERE, THERE'S
DEFINITELY A NEED
T-T-TO PRAY,
TO BEG, TO PLEAD,
TO SING FOR...
FOR A SIGN LIKE...
YOU KNOW HOW...
HOW YOUR VOICE
SOUNDS SO PRETTY
IN THE SHOWER?
BECAUSE--BECAUSE
THERE'S NOTHING
ELSE THERE.
BECAUSE IT ECHOES
OFF THE WALLS, AND
IT SOUNDS PRETTY.
MY PRAYERS
SOUND SO PERFECT
IN HERE...
BECAUSE IT'S SO...
BECAUSE IT'S SO
TOTALLY EMPTY.
BECAUSE IT'S SO--
IT'S SO GODLESS.
IT'S SO VOID OF--
OF--OF--
ANYTHING.
DO YOU KNOW HOW
I KNOW, SHERIFF?
I KNOW?
I KNOW BECAUSE--
BECAUSE...
I ASKED MYSELF
WOULD I COME BACK
FOR YOU?
AND THE ONLY ANSWER
IS A GODLESS, EMPTY,
EVIL...
NO.
I SAID I WOULDN'T
HAVE COME BACK.
I'M SORRY.
DON'T BE SORRY.
IT'S OK.
BECAUSE I DIDN'T
COME BACK JUST FOR YOU.
I DIDN'T COME BACK
JUST FOR YOU, YOU KNOW?
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
HEY, MAN, IT'S OK.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
COME HERE. IT'S OK.
[CRIES]
IT'S OK.
[SHOUTS IN MALAY]
[RAPS ON BARS]
OK, MAN.
OK.
I'M GONNA SEE YOU
IN A COUPLE HOURS.
ALL RIGHT? ALL RIGHT?
THANKS FOR THE TEA,
I LIKED IT.
SEE YOU IN
A COUPLE HOURS, MAN.
YOU'LL BE
CLEANED UP GOOD.
SHERIFF?
YEAH?
I KNEW YOU'D COME BACK,
EVEN IF YOU DIDN'T.
THANK YOU.
Tony: SO HOW BAD
WAS IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S LIKE...
YOU WANNA KNOW
HOW BAD IT WAS,
IT WAS...NOT GOOD.
WHAT WASN'T GOOD?
THE PRISON OR LEWIS?
WHICH ONE?
THE PRISON SUCKS FOR SURE.
IT'S DIRTY, IT'S SCARY,
IT'S THIRD WORLD.
HOW'S LEWIS?
IS HE SICK?
IS HE ALL THERE
MENTALLY?
IS HE THE SAME GUY
WE USED TO KNOW?
I DON'T THINK HE'S LOST
HIS MIND OR ANYTHING,
BUT IT'S NOT EASY SITTING
AROUND A PRISON CELL
WAITING TO HANG.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
DID HE TELL YOU
ANYTHING?
HE JUST BABBLED
A LITTLE BIT, TONY.
YOU KNOW, LIKE,
RAMBLED A LITTLE BIT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE STREAM-OF-
CONSCIOUSNESS STUFF.
GOD'S NOT IN HERE,
THERE'S NO GOD IN HERE.
IT SOUNDS BEAUTIFUL IN HERE,
LIKE, WHEN YOU SING
IN THE SHOWER, JUST--
SO BASICALLY, YOU'RE
SAYING HE LOST IT.
HE'S HANGING ON
TO ANYTHING HE
POSSIBLY CAN, TONY.
LOOK, NO ONE'S
QUESTIONING
HIS COURAGE--
YOU'RE QUESTIONING
HIS SANITY.
YOU WANT A WAY OUT,
FIND A WAY OUT,
BUT DON'T MAKE THIS
ABOUT LEWIS. HE'S
ALWAYS TALKED THAT WAY.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
ALWAYS?
YOU'RE
ONLY HIS LAWYER.
YOU'VE KNOWN HIM
FOR 2 YEARS.
24 YEARS.
I'M HIS SISTER.
WHAT?
HE'S MY BABY BROTHER.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
I THOUGHT YOU WOULDN'T
TRUST ME, SHERIFF.
I THOUGHT YOU'D THINK
I'D DO ANYTHING,
THAT I'D...
SAY ANYTHING,
THAT I'D SELL YOU OUT,
THAT I'D...
I WANTED TO.
I WANTED TO TELL YOU.
I TR-TRIED TO TELL YOU.
BUT YOUDIDN'T
TELL ME.
[WHISPERS]
But you didn't
tell me.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
SHERIFF?
[DOOR CLOSES]
WHAT ARE WE
STILL DOING HERE?
I WISH IT WAS
THAT SIMPLE, TONY.
I THINK
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
YOU KNOW,
I CAME BACK HERE.
I CAME BACK HERE
BASED ON WHAT
SHE TOLD ME, OK?
SHE GAVE ME HER WORD,
AND SHE LIED.
HOW ARE WE GONNA
TRUST HER, SHERIFF?
SHERIFF...LOOK,
SHE DRAGS US INTO
THIS NIGHTMARE, OK?
WE FIND OUT IT IS
HER OWN PERSONAL NIGHTMARE,
A WOMAN WE DON'T KNOW
FROM ADAM, YOU KNOW?
I DON'T KNOW HER,
YOU DON'T KNOW HER.
WHAT?
I KNOW HER.
LIKE,KNOWHER.
DON'T...
DON'T EVEN...DON'T.
FUCK. FUCK.
ALL RIGHT,
I'M AN ASSHOLE.
NO, TONY.
THIS TIME,I'M
THE FUCKIN' ASSHOLE.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
WHAT THE FUCK DO
I OWE YOU TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
IT'S NOT LIKE
IT'S BEEN GOING ON
FOREVER, ALL RIGHT?
IT HAPPENED.
YOU LISTEN TO ME.
DON'T EVEN TRY
TO MAKE IT LIKE
I'M HOLDING OUT ON YOU,
BECAUSE I SWEAR TO GOD
I'M NOT HOLDING
SHIT OUT ON YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
LISTEN TO ME, SHERIFF.
THIS GIRL
WILL DO ANYTHING
TO GET YOU TO DO
WHAT SHE NEEDS YOU TO,
ALL RIGHT?
THAT'S HER BROTHER
IN THERE--HER BLOOD.
SHE'LL LIE TO YOU,
SHE'LL SLEEP WITH YOU,
SHE'LL TELL YOU
SHE LOVES YOU,
SHE'LL DO ANYTHING.
SHE'LL GET DOWN ON
HER KNEES AND BEG YOU.
BUT DON'T BELIEVE IT.
IT'S A SETUP.
WE WALK OUT OF HERE,
TONY, THAT BOY HANGS.
AND IF WE STAY,
MAYBEWEHANG. BUT IF
WE LEAVE, WE LIVE.
THAT'S THE ONE THING
I KNOW FOR SURE
RIGHT NOW.
[BETH SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Beth: HUH?
DOES HE HAVE CLOTHES?
CAN YOU GET HIM
A SHOWER, A SHAVE,
BEFORE HE SHOWS UP
IN COURT?
UH-HUH. OK, LISTEN.
I--
[CAR DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
Woman: WHAT CAN I DO
FOR YOU, SIR?
WE NEED TWO SEATS
ON ANY FLIGHT
THAT'S GONNA GET US
TO NEW YORK...
AS FAST AS POSSIBLE.
Tony: WHAT, SHERIFF?
WHAT IS IT?
I TRASHED THAT BIKE,
TONY.
SO FUCKIN' WHAT?
GET ON THE PLANE,
SHERIFF.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
YOU WANT TO ROT IN
ONE OF THESE PRISONS?
I THINK I'M GONNA
TAKE MY CHANCES, TONY.
YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY CHANCES, SHERIFF.
DON'T LEAVE YOUR LIFE
TO FATE. THIS IS STUPID.
I DON'T KNOW, TONY.
YOU HAVE A SAFE FLIGHT.
[MAN SPEAKING MALAY]
WHAT'S HE SAYING?
HE SAYS,
"THEY RETURNED...
"BUT BECAME FRIGHTENED
AND MAY HAVE LEFT.
WHILE WE LOOK INTO THIS,
WE REQUEST ADJOURNMENT
TILL THE TWO CAN BE FOUND."
[JUDGE SPEAKING MALAY]
UM, HE'S WORRIED
ABOUT THE APPEARANCE
OF PREFERENTIAL
TREATMENT.
[JUDGE CONTINUES SPEAKING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[WITH ACCENT]
SHERIFF.
[CONTINUES SPEAKING
IN MALAY]
[GASPS]
[JUDGE SPEAKING MALAY]
HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
Judge: MY FAITH IN HUMANITY
IS HALF RESTORED.
IN RETURNING VOLUNTARILY,
YOU ARE TO BE COMMENDED
FOR YOUR COURAGE.
IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU WISH TO SAY
TO THIS COURT,
MR. VOLGECHEREV?
NOT REALLY, YOUR HONOR.
JUST THAT WE WERE
YOUNG AND STUPID...
I GUESS, BUT NOT EVIL.
I DIDN'T COME BACK
HERE TODAY BECAUSE
I'M COURAGEOUS.
I CAME BACK HERE BECAUSE
I'VE BEEN CARELESS
FOR A VERY LONG TIME,
AND I'M SICK
OF THAT FEELING.
THE SIMPLE FACT,
YOUR HONOR,
IS THAT
I AM RESPONSIBLE...
AND I'M ALSO SCARED.
BUT I AM WILLING TO DO
WHATEVER'S NECESSARY...
IN ORDER FOR YOU TO SPARE
MY FRIEND'S LIFE.
[SOBBING]
HOW DO YOU PLEAD?
I'M GUILTY.
[CRYING]
Judge:
FOLLOWING THIS HEARING,
YOU WILL BE DETAINED
IN PANANG PRISON
TO AWAIT SENTENCE.
[JUDGE SPEAKING MALAY]
[SOBBING]
[ATTORNEY SPEAKING MALAY]
[JUDGE SPEAKING MALAY]
[CRYING]
HE ASKED THE PROSECUTOR
IF HE WILL NOW AGREE
TO REDUCE THE CHARGES.
[SPEAKING MALAY]
PROSECUTOR HAS AGREED.
[WOMAN SPEAKS MALAY]
CHIEF JUSTICE
WILL BE BACK SHORTLY
WITH HIS DECISION.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
BETH?
WE'RE BACK IN SESSION.
WE'RE BACK?
YEAH.
[WOMAN SPEAKS MALAY]
[SPEAKING MALAY]
THE DEPUTY HIGH MINISTER
HAS TOLD CHIEF JUSTICE
HE IS ANGERED
ABOUT SOME
INTERNATIONAL NEWS STORY,
I'M NOT SURE WHAT.
[SPEAKING MALAY]
M.J. MAJOR.
[CONTINUES SPEAKING
IN MALAY]
Translator:
AN AMERICAN STORY
THAT WAS PICKED UP
BY THEASIAN
INTERNATIONAL TRIBUNE.
Judge:
"IN A COUNTRY PROUD
OF ITS MANY SPECIES
"OF EXOTIC BUTTERFLIES,
"A BUTTERFLY IS ABOUT
TO BE BROKEN ON A WHEEL.
"THE WHEEL IS
MALAYSIAN JUSTICE--
A TERM WHICH STRIKES
ONE AMERICAN WOMAN
AS A CRUEL JOKE."
YOUR HONOR--
Judge: "THE WOMAN IS
BETH McBRIDE, 28..."
PLEASE BELIEVE ME
WHEN I SAY I HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS.
"...ARRESTED
TWO YEARS AGO IN PANANG.
"BLAMED FOR HAVING
BOUGHT THE LION'S SHARE
OF HASHISH
"WITH TWO FRIENDS,
THIS NATURE-LOVING
YOUNG MAN NOW INCREDIBLY
FACES DEATH."
SHE WAS DETERMINED
TO WRITE THE STORY,
YOUR HONOR--
SILENCE!
WE KNOW YOU WESTERNERS
DON'T UNDERSTAND
OUR ATTITUDE
TOWARD DRUGS,
BUT WE DON'T
UNDERSTAND YOURS.
YOUR CITIES
ARE DECAYING.
THE SOULS OF
YOUR YOUNG PEOPLE
ARE STOLEN FROM YOU.
OUR LAWS
MAY SEEM HARSH,
BUT OUR STREETS
REMAIN SAFE,
AND OUR YOUTH
IS PROTECTED.
SO WHEN
AN AMERICAN JOURNALIST
TRIES TO CRITICIZE
OUR JUDICIAL SYSTEM--
I BEGGED HER NOT TO.
I BEGGED HER.
I DID EVERYTHING
I POSSIBLY COULD...
SILENCE!
...TO STOP HER
FROM DOING IT!
[SPEAKING MALAY]
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT IS HE SAYING?
WHAT DID HE SAY?
WHAT IS HE SAYING?!
HE WILL NOT AMEND
THE CHARGE NOW.
WHAT?
HE MUST BE HANGED TOMORROW
AS SCHEDULED.
WHAT--
[ATTORNEY SPEAKING MALAY]
WHAT? LEWIS--
[CRYING]
YOUR HONOR,
I CAME BACK!
YOU CAN'T HANG HIM!
Beth: LEWIS! LEWIS...
[BETH YELLING
UNINTELLIGIBLY]
LEWIS! LEWIS!
LEWIS, I LOVE YOU...
I LOVE YOU!
LEWIS!
LEWIS--GET YOUR
FUCKING HANDS OFF ME!
WHAT IS THE MATTER
WITH YOU PEOPLE?
WITH YOU PEOPLE?!
[UNINTELLIGIBLE]
YOU MOTHERFUCKER!
YOU LYING
SON OF A BITCH!
GOD DAMN IT, SHERIFF...
[REPORTERS
SHOUTING QUESTIONS]
[MAN SINGING,
CALLING PEOPLE TO PRAYER]
[ALL SINGING]
[MAN LEADING PRAYERS
IN MALAY]
[PEOPLE RESPONDING]
[FAN WHIRRING]
Lewis: NO!
[SCREAMING IN MALAY]
[SOBBING]
I DON'T WANT TO DIE!
NO!
YOU FUCKING BASTARDS!
[SCREAMING IN MALAY]
I DON'T WANT TO DIE!
AAH!
HELP!
LEWIS...
LEWIS!
[PLEADING IN MALAY]
[LEWIS SCREAMING]
DON'T DO IT!
I DON'T WANT TO DIE!
YOU FUCKING BASTARDS!
YOU--AAH!
[YELLING IN MALAY]
AAH!
DON'T...DON'T...
[LEWIS CONTINUES YELLING]
[CRYING]
NO! NO!
Lewis...
[SOBBING]
LEW! LEWIS!
NO! NO!
Sheriff: LEWIS!
LEWIS!
LEWIS! GOD DAMN IT,
LOOK UP HERE!
SHERIFF?!
I'M HERE, LEWIS!
I'M RIGHT HERE!
YOU'RE NOT ALONE,
LEWIS!
Sheriff:
LOOK AT ME, LEWIS!
YOU'RE NOT ALONE,
LEWIS. LOOK AT ME.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
I'M HERE. LOOK AT ME.
SEE ME, LEWIS.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
I'M RIGHT HERE, LEWIS.
I SEE YOU, LEWIS!
I'M RIGHT HERE!
LEWIS, YOU ARE NOT
ALONE RIGHT NOW.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
YOU ARE NOT ALONE, LEWIS.
I SEE YOU.
I SEE YOU, LEWIS.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
YOU ARE NOT ALONE,
LEWIS!
FFF...
[SOBBING QUIETLY]
[KEYS JINGLING
AND LOCK TURNING]
[GUARD SHOUTING
IN MALAY]
UP, UP, UP!
UP!
[SPEAKING MALAY]
[REPEATS PHRASE]
OK.
UP!
[SPEAKING MALAY]
OK.
WHERE AM I GOING HERE?
[SPEAKING MALAY]
[GUARD SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY]
[GUARD SPEAKING MALAY]
Beth.
WERE YOU THERE?
Yeah.
HE WASN'T AFRAID, BETH.
HE WALKED RIGHT PAST ME,
AND THEN...
I SAW HIM GO PAST
ALL THE GUARDS,
AND HE WAS CALM.
HE WAS COURAGEOUS.
COME ON, SHERIFF.
TELL ME THE TRUTH.
IT WAS HARD.
IT WAS HARD, BUT...
YOU KNOW,
I THINK THAT...
HE FOUND AT--AT THE END,
BETH, AT THE END...
I MEAN, HE WAS LEWIS,
YOU KNOW?
AND AT THAT LAST SECOND...
I SWEAR TO GOD...
HE WAS AT PEACE
WITH EVERYTHING.
HE WAS.
I JUST WISH
I COULD'VE DONE
SOMETHING, YOU KNOW...
LIKE I COULD'VE BEEN
THERE TO DO SOMETHING,
FIGHT HARDER...
BETH, YOU DID EVERYTHING
YOU COULD'VE DONE.
NOBODY COULD'VE DONE MORE
THAN WHAT YOU DID.
YOU'VE GOT TO BELIEVE THAT.
NOBODY DID MORE
THAN WHAT YOU DID.
NOBODY COULD'VE DONE MORE.
YOU DID
EVERYTHING YOU COULD.
YOU SHOULD HAVE
GONE BACK WITH TONY.
WHY DIDN'T YOU GO BACK
WITH TONY?
I COULDN'T GO BACK
WITH TONY.
BECAUSE I KNEW THAT
YOU WERE WAITING FOR ME.
AND I'M NOT SORRY, BETH.
I'M NOT SORRY RIGHT NOW.
I'M NOT.
BECAUSE IF I WOULD'VE
WENT BACK,
I DON'T THINK I'D BE ABLE
TO LOOK AT YOU EVER AGAIN.
AND THAT'D BE A LOT HARDER
THANTHISSHIT,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I LIKE TO LOOK AT YOU.
I like to look atyou.
I like to look at you.
OH...
THE AMBASSADOR HEARD...
THAT WHEN ALL THIS
PUBLICITY DIES DOWN,
THEY'RE GONNA
LET YOU GO, SHERIFF...
AND THEY'RE GONNA DO IT
QUIETLY TO SAVE FACE,
BUT IT'S GONNA BE...
6 MONTHS, MAXIMUM.
SHERIFF...
Yeah?
OH...GOD DAMN IT.
OH...GOD DAMN IT!
[SOBBING]
[GUARD SPEAKING MALAY]
SHERIFF...
I'M GONNA TAKE...
MY BROTHER HOME...
AND I'M COMING
RIGHT BACK HERE...
AND I WILL NOT
LEAVE PANANG...
UNTIL YOU'RE WITH ME.
I KNOW, BETH.
I KNOW.
[CRYING]
[GUARD SPEAKING MALAY]
[GUARD SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY]
[THUNDER]
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
POLYGRAM VIDEO
CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY
THE NATIONAL CAPTIONING
INSTITUTE, INC.
PUBLIC PERFORMANCE OF CAPTIONS
PROHIBITED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE