In the beginning, there was nothing.
-Wilderness.
-Worse than wilderness.
Endless raw acreage,
the land infested with crocodiles.
-Alligators.
-Alligators, crocodiles....
For retirement bungalows,
that's not a selling point.
Mosquitoes that would strip you
to the bones.
-Swampland.
-That was 10c an acre. This was worse.
The name means in Seminole:
"Don't go there."
But we bought it.
Because we knew.
You weren't selling land.
I mean, what's land?
A patch of dirt, a tree. Who cares?
Farmers care.
Farmers.
Farmers are for TV ads. People
with tractors, amber waves of grain.
They shoot it all in Canada.
I'm talking about certified accountants
with a fixed pension and a nest egg...
...who don't wanna spend
their golden years in slush.
Dreams are what you sell.
A concept.
You sell sunshine,
you sell orange groves...
...you sell gentle breezes
wafting through the palms.
-There were palm trees?
-In the brochures.
-Stately ones.
-When they came down and saw it?
As long as the dredge stayed ahead
of the buyers, we were in like Flynn.
This was the end of the earth.
This was the land populated
by white people who ate catfish.
Almost overnight,
out of the muck and the mangroves...
...we created this.
Golf courses.
Nature on a leash.
Ahoy. It's that time of year again.
The Delrona Chamber of Commerce
invites you...
... to the Buccaneer Days festivities
at the Plantation Island Marina.
Live music,
and plenty of booty for kids.
Plans for the treasure hunt can be
attained at the Delrona Beach Mall....
-Sure this place is okay?
-What do you mean?
-Black people go in here?
-If they're desperate to pee, they do.
-But your mother's is--
-I need to go before then.
Relax.
Take the register,
I gotta get back to the motel.
-Your husband called.
-Ex.
He needs to see you.
Next time, tell him to take
a long walk off a short pier.
-Smoking or non?
-Could I use your bathroom?
-It's straight back to the right.
-Thank you.
Buzzards.
Excuse me.
Hi, there. You been helped yet?
No, my wife's just using
the facilities.
-You need a room?
-Pardon?
You've been gawking at the motel.
We have a few vacancies,
but it'll fill up soon.
-I was looking the property over.
-The property?
The whole strip, actually.
If you're from the County,
we had our sign moved back.
I was just trying to imagine what it
would look like without buildings.
-Kind of mentally undressing it?
-You could say that.
-You work for that Plantation outfit?
-Yes. I'm supervising the expansion--
They don't have enough
of the coast already?
It's just a study,
a what-if kind of thing.
What if I told you my daddy would
never sell to Plantation Estates?
I'll be happy to pass it on.
I'm Jack Meadows.
-You're a developer.
-A landscape architect.
I help them decide what they want,
push some dirt around....
They wanted my opinion
on the whole shoreline here, actually.
-So how's it look?
-What?
Without anything on it?
It looks terrific.
HQ says that'll be our beachhead.
Then we'll take the rest of it.
The other side has this end locked up
and they're infiltrating Lincoln Beach.
-We're not opposing?
-Zoned residential, hostile population.
It's a minefield. Whereas right here
is the soft underbelly of the island.
You make the frontal assault,
I go behind the lines.
-Is somebody on the inside?
-Working on it.
Shit.
Shock and outrage as Delrona Beach
awoke to a senseless act of vandalism.
The Freebooter, the centrepiece
of the Buccaneer Days parade...
...was burnt beyond repair....
This is a disaster. It's always
the lead float in the parade.
Same kid set a fire some years back
in a crab shack on Lincoln Beach.
This is so not in the spirit
of the celebration.
Where do you want me to haul it?
Hello!
Hello?
-Dr. Lloyd.
-Sorry to bother you, Mrs. Pierce.
You're always welcome.
I'm rounding up folks for this
County Commission meeting tonight.
-I know it's very short notice, but--
-I'd like to help, but I feel poorly.
Oh, my! Would you look at this.
It's that boy
poor Mrs. Stokes took in.
-He's in trouble again?
-First her girl went wild...
...and run off to God knows where.
And now this.
Some people.
I'm worried about them sneaking
through this public-domain business...
...without us making a showing.
If we can field just
even a dozen residents--
Wasn't it settled
when they took the cemetery?
-I'm afraid it won't stop there.
-Now, who's this coming to call?
It seems kind of deserted.
Yeah, well, you know,
most people come on the weekends.
-Do I look okay?
-Relax. This is gonna be fine.
You don't know her.
Hi.
Is Mrs. Stokes here?
I have no idea.
Well, well. Desiree.
Never thought I'd live
to see you back here.
Hello, Mama.
My Lord.
You did get a handsome one,
didn't you?
Good luck moving this. It's three
inches of soil, then solid limestone.
More work, more pay.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
-They wanted this one saved.
-Is that right?
What do you think, chief?
That thing gonna make it?
It's part of Mr. Meadows' concept.
The chief's concept is everything
that's not flat gets that way, fast.
Plantation sold this lot
with the tree.
When you crackers head back to Georgia,
there better goddamn still be one.
Used to be this was all Exley family.
Hasn't nothing been planted here
in 100 years.
We wanna satisfy the homeowner's
desire for privacy...
...with the convenience
and the socializing opportunities...
...provided by the village concept.
It doesn't look like much now,
but when Jack's finished--
-What goes here?
-Our main drainage basin.
-It's a lake.
-A lake?
It'll be 14 feet deep.
What we dig out will form a hill.
-With a deluxe home on top of it.
-Deluxe?
With all the amenities:
A river view, the lake.
-Elevation.
-Damn! These bugs gonna be here too?
Anaesthesiologist.
If there's a surgical procedure,
I render the patient unconscious.
You knock people out with gas?
That's pretty much it.
-I'd be afraid not to wake up.
-A lot of people feel that way.
-Reggie's the head of his department.
-Is that right?
And at such a prestigious hospital.
I'll have to tell that to Dr. Lloyd.
-Dr. Lloyd still coming down?
-He lives here now.
His Etta Mae passed some years ago.
You wouldn't have heard that,
would you?
-She doesn't write, she doesn't call.
-Mama.
Girl caught the first thing smoking
and never looked back.
I took the bus, Mama. Not the train.
It's an expression.
Terrell? Go run this gravy through
the microwave again. It's gone cold.
-And who is that?
-Your cousin, Sidney Wilkins' son.
Sidney that married Athena Hines.
Well, why isn't he with them?
She doesn't write, she doesn't call.
I'm surprised she even let on
she got married.
Her own mother doesn't
get invited to the wedding.
It was a civil service, Mama.
It wasn't in church.
-But it's legal?
-It's legal, it's official. Don't worry.
Something they do up there.
What is it?
Boston.
Somehow, I've never been
north of Washington, D.C.
You'll just have to come visit us.
When Terrell's out of school,
maybe we'll do that.
How about that, Terrell?
You like to see Boston?
The proposed boundary for Delrona
Beach will incorporate this area...
...including Lincoln Beach all the way
to the Exley Plantation track.
Excuse me.
If you want to make a motion, wait
till Commissioner Pinkney's finished.
-I want to register a protest.
-In regard to what?
This meeting was not
properly advertised.
We met all legal requirements.
You purposely chose a time when our people
would be unable to attend.
The residents of Lincoln Beach?
You know very well many of us
are only here on weekends.
Many are only summer people.
That doesn't deny us the right
to object to this expropriation.
-Incorporation.
-You've already taken a third of our area.
You know that was
a private transaction...
...between Exley Plantation Estates
Planned Community...
...and the individual property owners.
This commission didn't know about it
until the plans were submitted.
If you hadn't already approved it,
they wouldn't have gone ahead.
As spokesman for the Exley Corporation,
I object to the implication--
-It has historic significance to us--
-We made several offers to--
A history that this commission
has consistently ignored!
You let them take away our cemetery.
Dr. Lloyd, we're talking old business.
If you dislike the current agenda--
We don't wanna be a part
of Delrona Beach...
...and they've made it clear they
don't want anything to do with us.
If beachfront prices hadn't risen,
there'd be no interest in merging--
-The concept of eminent domain--
-Is used to undermine our well-being!
Gentlemen, if we're going
to have a debate...
...I'm going to have to ask you
to follow procedure.
-I'm thinking of going out there again.
-Out where?
Tour.
Golfing?
It's kind of a syndicate.
A couple of dentists, a Buick dealer.
They wanna sponsor me
for a percentage of my winnings.
-How much can you make?
-First you have to qualify.
Then it just depends on where you
stand at the end of each tournament.
You did this before?
I tried a couple of years back.
It was fine till I got on the green.
You know...
...Iittle case of the yips.
It's an adrenaline thing.
You're in the middle of the back swing
of your putt, you tighten up and....
Yip.
Something like that.
And you had them bad?
Killer drive,
beautiful approach shot...
...and I just couldn't get
the damn thing in the hole.
That would seriously cut
into your winnings, wouldn't it?
-It's better now?
-I won't know until I get out there.
I can always sink them in practice.
So you'll be travelling a lot.
That's the life.
Are there, like, groupies?
I suppose. If you win.
I never could understand
wanting to watch it.
You know? It's like
those fishing shows on TV.
Does that make you feel bad?
I don't watch people wait on tables
or run the check-in desk.
Right, you don't.
Yip.
-This is too weird.
-Is it what you remember?
It's my room, yeah,
but that boy's been living in here.
We got some serious testosterone
working here. Now, he's what, exactly?
His daddy is my cousin.
Grew up kind of wild.
He's living here because...?
She wants me to drive them downtown
for some kind of hearing tomorrow.
-He's in trouble?
-She's not giving up any information.
Punish me a bit.
-For being gone so long.
-For everything.
She's the one who asked you
to come down, made the first move.
It's too weird.
You can hear the ocean.
I always loved that.
Hey, Lucky.
-They changed all the façades.
-Nobody but tourists shop here now.
-Where do the regular folks go?
-There's a shuttle bus to the mall.
It's just in here.
-This won't take but an hour or so.
-You hope.
Terrell just needs to talk
with somebody.
We'll call you back home
when it's over.
Prettiest beach on the Atlantic coast.
It is pretty.
If you want to help save it, we're
protesting at the groundbreaking.
-I'm just visiting.
-They won't know the difference.
So this is like an ecological thing?
We're trying to save
an endangered species.
Us.
I heard about this place
when I was a kid.
Forties, fifties...
...Lincoln Beach was it.
Only oceanfront in three counties
we were allowed to step onto.
Black folks, I'm talking about
the pillars of the community...
...got together and bought this land,
built the houses.
You'd drive through a couple hundred
miles of redneck sheriffs...
...park your ride on the boardwalk,
step out and just breathe.
Over there was Henry's Lounge.
That place used to jump.
-So, what happened?
-Civil rights happened. Progress.
Used to be you were black,
you'd buy black.
Jim Crow days, you needed a shoeshine,
wanted a taxi to the train station...
...you wanted some ribs,
a fish sandwich...
...chances are a black man
owned the place you got it in.
Now, the drive-thrus serve anybody.
But who owns them?
Not us.
All our people do is wear paper hats
and dip out them fries.
Only thing we got left are
funeral parlours and barbershops.
But now we can do anything.
Them that can get over do fine.
Them that can't are
in a world of trouble.
Tell the judge what you told me.
I said I'm sorry for what I did.
I wasn't thinking right.
You know that sorry won't cut it
in this case, don't you?
Yes, ma'am.
You're still on probation
for a previous offence...
...yet you deliberately
committed this act of vandalism.
Do you have any explanation
for your actions?
No, ma'am.
When somebody destroys something
that stands as a symbol for people...
-...that's desecration.
- It's a wooden pirate.
An icon in this community, nonetheless.
You're almost old enough, given
your record, to be tried as an adult.
You have two strikes against you.
A third, and there will be--
Mrs. Stokes has assured us she'll
maintain control of the situation.
We'd be satisfied,
barring further incidents...
...with an order for counselling,
or possibly community service.
That's very generous of you.
So, young man,
what's it gonna be?
Loretta.
Well....
Look at you.
-Mama said you were still in Delrona.
-Haven't moved an inch.
I saw you on a TV commercial.
I told my kids I went to school with you,
but they didn't believe me.
-You got kids?
-Three of them.
They're getting big.
-It's the first you've been back since--
-I came back for the service...
...when my father passed.
-But I only stayed for a day.
-That's a good while ago, your father.
Kind of slow for you down here.
Look, I....
-I kind of wanted to apologize.
-For what?
For Carter.
That's another lifetime
you're talking about. 25 years.
We were friends.
I shouldn't have gone after him.
But you did.
-You always did what you wanted to.
-I didn't do it to hurt you.
-Ancient history.
-So Carter still in town?
He inside sleeping.
Works nights at the box factory.
-You got married?
-After a while, yeah.
-When you left town--
-When I was sent away.
Everybody thought it was Carter
got you pregnant.
It wasn't.
That's what he's saying nowadays.
I guess I wasn't too worried
about the rumours.
-Made your exit and didn't look back.
-Some drama, huh?
Girl, we ate that shit up.
I had to listen to everybody
run you down...
...being the tragic ex-girlfriend and all.
-Like that was gonna make me feel better.
-And Carter?
-Carter ran around acting the daddy.
-Really?
Better you knock your girl up than to
have people think somebody else did it.
But it all turned out fine, didn't it?
I suppose I could've done worse.
So you're the one who finally
snagged Desiree Stokes?
I'm the one.
-That girl drew men like flies.
-I can imagine.
-Elton Lloyd.
-Reginald Perry.
We're staying at her mother's
for a few days.
A wonderful woman, Eunice.
A true Christian.
Now her nephew, is it?
Her nephew's son.
Young Terrell.
I blame it on the drugs.
It's a pestilence.
Something happened with his...?
-Eunice didn't tell you?
-She and Desiree haven't been....
-If you ask, you don't deserve to know.
-Seems to be the attitude.
Terrell's father was going
through a rough stretch.
He had separated from his wife.
He came over one day
high on who knows what.
They had a screaming argument,
he had a weapon.
He shot that woman dead,
then turned the gun on himself.
Horrible thing to witness.
-Terrell must have been 6, maybe 7.
-He saw it?
He sat with the bodies for two days
before somebody came over and found him.
It's a pestilence.
Afternoon, gentlemen.
Y'all know where Buster's Place is?
Buster's Place is long gone, brother.
Nothing there now.
You sure?
I know you.
-I don't think so.
-Sure, I do.
You used to be the Florida Flash.
In my day, life was simpler.
You knew where you stood.
A man was left to make his own way
in the world.
You didn't have none of these
pressure groups, advocate groups...
...special-interest groups
handicapping the race.
It went to the smartest,
the strongest, the swiftest.
If a man could carve out
something for himself...
...he knowed he'd earned it.
No whooping crane.
Spotted owl.
The Florida gator.
The coloured man, the white man,
the Spanish.
They all started out from scratch.
If you couldn't survive the course,
it was tough titty.
Nowadays, what they got?
It ain't natural.
They got us so zoned.
Regulated.
Politically corrected and
environmentally sensitised...
...to the point where it's only
multi-internationals with 12 lawyers...
...waiting like buzzards
for something to litigate...
...that can afford to put one brick
on top of another.
The little guy, no matter how much
grit or imagination he brings to it...
...ain't got a chance. They got him
tied down so he can't hardly breathe.
You smoke a damn cigarette, they
make you feel like a baby-strangler.
Where's it all gonna end?
I don't want to know.
But if they expect my cooperation,
they're just shit out of luck.
The reason I hang on to this old bag of
bones is to spite the sons of bitches.
They made me put into Social Security
for 50 years.
I ain't giving up the ghost till I spend
every damn penny of it.
-Which one are you?
-Gwendolyn.
-You think I'm full of crap, don't you?
-It's time for your insulin, Mr. Temple.
There's an opening here
that could close up quick.
-My father is the owner.
-I understand he's currently indisposed.
He's legally blind, if that's what you mean.
The black folks on Lincoln Beach have
contacted the Historical Register.
That's their business.
Draw that kind of attention,
environmentalists come in on their heels.
They're pesky little buggers.
Then you won't be able to sell
your property for what it's worth.
-What's it worth?
-Not much at the moment.
And since the resort condos have come in,
your taxes have jumped 30%.
-Small businesses are being squeezed.
-Tell me about it.
We realize this is a big decision,
one of the oldest businesses left...
-...going back generations.
-You're not from the Plantation?
-Some men were here.
-Did they make an offer?
-Sniffing around, I guess.
-They're relentless.
And you're not?
The Exley Plantation is only for the
elite. What we have in mind is more...
-...democratic. Something for everybody.
-Stores, burger chains, T-shirts?
-Retail outlets would be part of it--
-123 empty?
-Should be. Your husband called.
-I don't need to talk to him.
You want to develop here, you need
the County Commission in your pocket.
We can work something out.
Testing, one, two, three.
This is a mike check. One, two, three.
Good afternoon, and welcome
to Delrona Beach's...
...annual Buccaneer Days.
Earl. Earl!
-Steve. I'll be right with you.
-I got those signatures.
Just give me a minute.
In the afternoon,
when school was out...
...and the last one had left
with his dirty little snuffling nose...
...instead of going home, I would go
down the hill to the spring...
...where I could be quiet
and hate them.
It would be quiet there then...
...with the water bubbling up and away
and the sun slanting in the trees...
...and the quiet smelling of damp
and rotting leaves and new earth.
Especially in the early spring.
For it was worse then.
I could remember my father used to say
that the reason for living...
...was to get ready to stay dead
a good long time.
And when I would have to look at them
day after day...
...each with his and her
secret and selfish thought...
...and blood strange to each other
and strange to mine.
And to think that this
was the only way...
...I could stay dead.
I would hate my father
for planting me.
And then I go on from there.
The important thing is...
...to freeze yourself
in an interesting...
...but comfortable position.
Jaime, you're about to fall over.
We'll resume tomorrow.
You should be off book by then.
I thank you all very much
for your work today.
-It is you, isn't it?
-Hello, Miss Delia.
It's really you.
It is so wonderful to see you.
My mother told me
you were still running this.
They'll have to drag me off.
Several members of the local press
have suggested that very thing.
These are my special group.
Young people with difficulties.
-What's the play?
-As I Lay Dying.
Rather loosely adapted, but I don't
believe Mr. Faulkner would object.
-The scene of your many triumphs.
-I let you down.
-Whatever do you mean?
-When I left. I was the lead.
Well, we did have to make
a few adjustments.
But the show must go on.
You played it?
Having a queen of Egypt
considerably older than her Antony...
...was very provocative.
I got to do it once when I got
to New York. In the Park.
I played the handmaiden
who gives her the asp.
I'm sure you were wonderful.
And now?
I trust you're still sharing
your talent with the public?
I do industrials. Representing things.
I do a lot of auto shows.
A temporary engagement in the world
of commerce. You're still so young.
I had my chance, Miss Delia.
It just didn't happen.
I must say, my youthful aspirations
had nothing to do...
...with becoming the Sarah Bernhardt
of Delrona Beach.
We adjust.
You would've been stunning
as Cleopatra.
I was starting to show.
I played Juliet...
...when I was five-months pregnant
with my twins.
Hello there, come on in.
-You remember my mother?
-Mrs. Temple.
So nice to see you.
And this is my-- This is Terrell.
Terrell is....
-It's sort of a favour.
-Whatever I can do.
The social worker down
at the courthouse recommended you...
-...because you have a program--
-For community service.
I can always use another volunteer.
Do you have any acting experience?
-No, ma'am.
-But he knows how to use tools.
Anything you can think of,
Terrell can put it together.
Then you can do me a great service,
Terrell.
My character, Addie Bundren,
is deceased.
In the second act, I rise from the dead
for my soliloquy...
...but the local funeral parlour
has nothing suitably rustic.
Do you think you could you build me
a coffin?
"We hereby claim sovereignty
over this island...
...in the name of his majesty,
Philip el Segundo of Spain.
Furthermore, this tribunal declares
the mulatto, Calavera...
...otherwise known as Captain Skull,
guilty of piracy on the high seas...
...a crime against God and nature, and
sentence him to be cast into the sea...
...there to perish by drowning."
Does the condemned have
a final statement?
A curse on the lot of you.
Up the Jolly Roger!
Thus was the black flag
of the buccaneer...
...replaced by that
of Imperial Spain...
...one of many reversals of fortune...
...that mark the colourful history
of our community.
We'd like to thank Presto Pools
for the equipment, and remind you...
...that the annual Treasure Hunt
will begin tomorrow at the Delrona Mall.
Entrants should meet
at the Piercing Pagoda at 10:00.
-Guess who I met earlier?
-You're not telling people I'm back?
I didn't recognize him without the helmet.
But you remember a football player
named Flash Phillips?
Every step we take is on someone's toes.
This town expects me to work miracles
with a handful of volunteers.
This bunch from Lincoln Beach say
they're gonna picket our groundbreaking.
-They complain about parking....
-The whole point is to be away from that.
-This afternoon was embarrassing.
-What? No! I thought it went fine.
-For a Chamber of Commerce thing.
-Nobody came.
-Turnout was terrific.
-Something isn't clicking.
I worked this one place,
they had the blessing of the fleet.
A bishop in his hat,
boats all dolled up. What a draw.
-I can't do religious here.
-True.
And what's our fleet? A bunch
of charter boats and day sailers.
-You got history to burn.
-People hate history.
You got Indians, pirates,
Spanish gold, that plantation thing.
Mass murder, rape, slavery.
So Disneyfy it a little, and they'll
come back. All you need is a hook.
I once worked this place in Wisconsin.
It was all built on wurst.
-Wurst?
-Weisswurst, Bratwurst, Knackwurst.
Bavarian people.
Lots of strudel shops...
...and service people
in leather shorts and dirndls.
-And this worked?
-The beer got them in the mood.
-Free liquor.
-I like a woman in a dirndl.
I hired this guy to be an attraction.
He used to be a big Seminole.
-Indian?
-Not the Seminoles! The Seminoles.
The football team?
Of course. What would I want
with a real Indian?
He used to be a big deal. Hung out
at Lincoln Beach, drove a Mustang....
-A local hero! That's good.
-I just hope he shows up.
-What's his favourite thing to eat?
-Small children.
Is he alive?
-Can't hardly say.
-Why show a dead alligator?
Did you pay anything to look at him?
Then don't complain.
-He was the last of the Mohicans.
-No, they were already extinct.
He was a Shawnee or Pawnee.
Here's Billy, he'll know.
-Chief!
-Yo, asshole.
What kind of Indian was that guy
on Daniel Boone?
-He was Jewish.
-I don't mean the actor, the character.
-How should I know?
-Aren't you a full-blooded whatever?
-Creek.
-Regular Creek or shit creek?
-So where was Daniel Boone?
-In the woods.
More specific than that.
Can't you tell by Indian lore?
-Lore?
-You know, like the trees or something?
-What the hell do I know about trees?
-Didn't your ancestors--?
My parents sold lawn ornaments
to stupid white people.
-You're shitting me.
-Get you a good deal on ceramic ducks.
-I couldn't really pin her down.
-But you planted the idea in her head?
She said her father decided.
Last thing we need is to deal
with some old gomer.
-The mother?
-No, she's a flake.
She runs a theatre group,
finds homes for retired greyhounds.
She never set foot in the restaurant.
She won't be any help,
but she won't get in the way.
-So we're back to the daughter.
-The old man ran the show 24-7.
The daughter, she's paying four people
to handle the same load.
-She wants a life.
-Her rack rate is too low for that.
-The restaurant.
-The restaurant's a wash.
You know the money a successful
franchise could make in that spot?
-All she's doing is taking up space.
-Now she's taking up space at the bar.
You see?
This is not a dedicated professional.
You're not having another of those?
-Saw Steve at the pirate thing today.
-They hang him?
Walked the plank.
-He needs to talk to you.
-Why doesn't he come by the motel?
Maybe due to the restraining order?
You had him arrested in the parking lot.
-He was drunk as a skunk.
-He's club soda and lime now.
-Why do you always wanna defend him?
-I'm not. I'm just saying he's on the wagon.
-Your golf pro was in the other night.
-Not my golf pro.
He's 10 years younger than me.
Besides, he's going on tour.
Like Tiger Woods on TV?
I don't think he'll get as much airtime
as Tiger.
-Did he ask you to go with him?
-It didn't come up.
You want to?
A guy over there has been
checking you out.
Be still, my beating heart.
-What's he look like?
-Not bad.
-Tattoos?
-None visible.
Shirt say "Go Gators"
or "Stomp 'em, Seminoles"?
-It doesn't say anything.
-Obviously not my type.
He's cute.
I'm gonna turn around only to see what
falls under your definition of cute.
If you're at 12:00,
he's about 3:30.
Trying to imagine what it would be
like without us crackers?
-You're everywhere.
-Small island.
I didn't mean to be intrusive before.
I thought they'd contacted you.
Don't worry about it. There's days I imagine
it all blowing away in a hurricane.
-Must be a lot of work being a hotelier.
-Motelier. And we got the restaurant.
-I hated working there as a kid.
-And now?
I got three girls working for me
hate it as much as I do.
-Why do you...?
-Poetic justice. What are you drinking?
-Draft. How about you?
-Shots. Tequila.
If you're gonna drink,
why fuck around?
You're from up north.
They say everybody here is
from somewhere else.
-Not me. I'm sixth generation. At least.
-That's impressive.
You go back that far, your people were
planters, slaves or fugitives.
Yours were...?
I don't know what they were running
from, but this is where they stopped.
-I'm from Newport, Rhode Island.
-With the yachts and big estates?
My dad took care of the lawns.
-So you've never left the island?
-Sure, I left all right.
-You're looking at a Weeki Wachee girl.
-What?
It's a show.
It's been running since the late '40s.
-You acted?
-Performed. You do it underwater.
Let's have a contest.
You do it to me.
This isn't the guy I meant.
You win.
I could hold it twice as long
if I hadn't been drinking.
The important thing is to keep a smile,
even with water down your nose.
-How long did you work there?
-Three years.
And then I met my ex.
-He had this band. Skeeter Meter.
-Like a rock band?
They were big around Tampa.
You listen to the Allman Brothers?
Lynyrd Skynyrd?
Then you've heard Skeeter Meter.
He was Greek and good-looking.
His daddy was a sponge diver
before they died out.
-What did they die of?
-Boredom.
Hanging on to some rock,
soaking up whatever rolls over you.
-Almost as bad as Delrona Beach.
-There's a lot of changes happening.
Things might pick up.
Don't hold your breath.
They used to say folks around here
only worshipped three people:
The father, the son
and the Florida Flash.
The day he got hurt, I must have
run the replay 100 times.
He stopped coming up here.
Left school.
So you were
one of the adoring masses?
I was in high school, he was on
national TV. What do you think?
That's some heavy story about Terrell.
A big responsibility she's taken on,
a kid like that.
-So can you help him?
-Me?
-What am I, a shrink?
-I mean help him build this thing.
Carpentry and adolescent psychology,
two things I know nothing about.
Try, okay? For me.
I'll do what I can.
-Maybe we'll head back on Monday.
-We just got here.
I don't want to get sucked in to any
of this. I don't like who I am down here.
And I don't trust my mother.
Is that you, Elton?
I'm amazed at how little sleep
I need these days.
You've got restless feet.
Always have.
Sorry I couldn't be there
for you at the meeting.
You had your emergency.
How'd the hearing go?
He's still on probation.
He has to do community service.
Could have been much worse.
We can fall so quickly.
It's just a stumble, not a fall.
If you could just go and get it
and hand it to them.
-Nobody handed us anything.
-Of course they did.
People fought their whole lives
to keep their heads above water.
We got to start on dry land.
-So Desiree's back?
-Visiting. She's not back.
Hurricane Desiree.
The nights I sat here wondering
where that girl could be.
We used to come out here and neck
when I was in high school.
Then they had these lights in.
Security.
It's more like birth control.
-You do golf courses?
-Design them? No, that's a specialty.
-Do you play it?
-Golf? No.
I gotta tell you...
...sex with me when I'm this drunk
is like being at the dentist.
-The dentist?
-When they shoot you up with Novocain.
You can tell something's going on
in there but you don't know what it is.
-I understand.
-So forget it.
It wouldn't cross my mind.
Tomorrow I won't even remember
I kissed you.
I'll come by and remind you.
Do that.
-You honestly don't golf?
-Never took it up.
Good.
The important thing is
to keep that smile on your face...
...even if you're drowning.
-The polar icecap is melting.
-This is news?
They say with this global warming,
the icecap, Antarctica could melt.
-And the oceans get 20 feet higher.
-It's good we live on the 2nd floor.
Here it will be a wading pool
all the way to Orlando.
The problem started with the invention
of the internal combustion engine.
That and air conditioning.
They say every day another species
goes extinct. It's tragic.
Who needs a lizard the size of a van?
If those things came back today...
...people wouldn't be so thrilled.
-Sam! What are we playing for?
-$10.00 a side...
...fifty dollars for the match,
and throw away your worst hole.
-This might be the one.
-My grandparents were peasants.
They came from a country where
they used Jews for target practice.
They only ever ate beets or turnips.
We brought my tante over here.
She wouldn't go to the park.
She said:
"Next time I look at grass,
it should be growing over my body."
-I like to watch that Jungle Channel.
-Animals eating animals.
-It's educational.
-For a wolverine, possibly.
"How to hibernate in three easy lessons."
For human beings, what good is that?
When was the last time
you stalked a creature?
-I go duck-hunting with my son.
-I forgot. You people shoot birds.
Shooting is not the point.
You're out there when the sun comes up,
surrounded by nature.
Nature is overrated.
But we'll miss it when it's gone.
Scotty?
-Sorry to distract you.
-No, I need it.
Come closer.
Come on down into the trap.
Where I'm headed, you don't play
in a vacuum. TV camera, a gallery.
Everybody's right on top of you.
Try to keep that distance.
Are you okay?
Yes. I thought we should,
like, make it official.
What?
Breaking up.
You're going off on your tour and all.
Yeah.
Win one tournament, you make more
than a year working here.
-It's not the money.
-It's not?
It's this thing that I do. Better than
almost anybody else on earth.
If I don't take another whack
at the highest level....
It's the purest thing that--
Pretty stupid, huh? Talking
about golf like it's important.
It isn't stupid at all,
you really love it.
You just don't love me.
Buster's Place.
-How long's it been like this?
-All messed up? Couple of years.
-There was a fire.
-Nobody's fixed it up?
The people it belonged to
didn't come back.
-So you have, like, a crew?
-On a boat?
-Guys you hang with.
-No.
So what are you into?
Interested in.
Stuff.
Like sports? Music?
I guess.
You think we got enough?
Never built a coffin before.
It used to be five yards
in a cloud of dust.
No mouth guards,
no face guards.
The helmet was a leather strap
to hold the brain in...
...in case you got cracked
on the skull. What is it now?
Technology? Hormones?
Bunch of coloured boys flipping
a ball around the field.
Women in the locker room?
That ain't gridiron.
-What are they doing?
-Did you say something?
-What are women doing in the locker room?
-Talking to the players.
They must find it very distracting.
They're too worried about
their stock portfolios to notice.
It's a wonder they know what
a handoff is.
-How do you know they're coloured?
-Who?
The boys flipping the ball.
You can't see the TV.
When do you hear of a white boy
called Deshon?
Carlotta will be here for dinner.
I have rehearsal...
...and then an Audubon meeting.
You and your birds.
They start clearing the Plantation
Estates expansion next week...
-...at the old Exley property.
-Lincoln Beach?
Not anymore.
There's a bird colony
we're concerned about.
The coloured folks think
there's a curse on that land.
I'm sure it has seen
its share of misery.
Hey, Mama.
Hey, Daddy.
-Trouble at the motel?
-Everything's fine.
-Then why aren't you there?
-We got a day manager. Rosellen.
-Those people steal you blind.
-She's got it under control.
Are these new ones?
I can't remember
when you were here last.
-They all look alike to me.
-The place full up?
-Yes. Celebration.
-How about the restaurant?
Keeping us hopping.
-Gotta make it while it's there.
-I know.
-Steven was calling for you.
-He knows I don't live here.
-It was nice talking to him.
-He's got a screw loose. Deep-sea diving.
-That was his father.
-Puts pressure on the brain.
Steve's put pressure on his brain,
but not by diving.
He said he's turning over
a new leaf. I certainly hope so.
-He had such promise.
-When did Steve ever have promise?
When he had his group
and you were with the circus.
It wasn't a circus.
We stayed in one place.
When you were performing
in the aquarium.
-You both were so hopeful.
-Well, we grew up.
Daddy? There was a fella from
a development company over yesterday.
You give him the boot?
I was thinking this might be
a good time, if you ever wanted to sell.
And watch them turn the beach
into a strip mall?
-It's not exactly pristine at the moment.
-You help keep the place running?
-I have not.
-Then hold your peace.
-She's worried about those birds.
-It's a severely compromised habitat.
-The sandhill cranes have forsaken us.
-Good.
If they don't know better than to fly
someplace accommodating...
...then they deserve what they get.
Now your sea gull, that's like people.
They'll fight over every scrap they get.
-Your father is a strict Darwinian.
-She throws her education against me.
Anyway, this developer....
-I told him you weren't interested.
-You can bet on that one.
Get in there! Come on!
Get in there!
They give you specs for this thing?
Like dimensions?
-There's a picture in the book.
-If she's gonna get into it....
This doesn't give us
the measurements.
-You're taller than her.
-Right.
Better cut some holes
so she can breathe.
-Halt! Who goes there?
-Don't shoot. It's your ex-wife.
-I'm on guard duty.
-Maple said you needed to see me.
-Pretend you're just a tourist.
-Steve, come on.
I'm serious. We got an inspector
coming by to review the unit.
-Nice uniform.
-I hate playing a Yankee.
-You're Greek, for chrissake.
-I was born down here.
-So, what's the latest crisis?
-No crisis.
Just wondering how you were
making out. Seriously.
I found inner peace.
What's the angle?
I heard about something.
I'd like to cut you in.
-Not interested.
-It's once in a lifetime.
-So was our marriage. Once was enough.
-Hear me out.
If you don't want to be a co-investor,
we can work out a reasonable rate....
-You want to borrow money from me?
-I could get in on something big.
Tell me, what do we not have
on this island?
Let's see. An opera house.
A ski resort. A good Thai restaurant.
-Are you familiar with water slides?
-Them plastic chute things?
You slide down it
in your bathing suit?
-We don't have one.
-I knew I was culturally disadvantaged.
Know how much those things make?
-A: You'll never get a permit.
-Don't be so sure.
B: I don't have any money
to throw at half-assed propositions.
-I heard you're about to come into some.
-Is that so?
My sources inform me you've been
approached by some big developers.
They don't know diddly.
Besides, C: even if I did have money...
...I'd run it through the leaf shredder
before I gave a nickel of it to you.