Meet me at the Zygmunt tillar.
Better be worth it.
-Too cold for false alarms.
-lt's too cold for ice cubes.
Apparently,
we've intercepted a conduit.
Well, there's only one way
to find out.
Now....
-Don't!
-Where is the package?
-l don't know.
-Dunois, does he have it?
No.
Where's the package?
l promise you, whoever you're
protecting is sitting in a warm room...
...without the slightest concern
for your well-being.
You are too late, Mr. Olyphant.
lt's already...
...been delivered.
l can't tell you how disappointed
l am to hear that.
l'll give you 1 0 seconds
to tell me who to.
-Ten, nine, eight, seven...
-Please, no! You are too late.
...six, five, four...
-...three, two....
-lt's dangerous.
-What?
-The truth.
He knew you, Jared.
l thought you were anonymous.
-l am now.
-The rules are changing.
Our client has an aversion
to rising death tolls.
His reputation is already called
into question, which means...
...close associates could be next.
The only aversion our client has
is to failure.
As for reputations, you two
were hired to intercept that package...
...not some monkey with a death wish.
My assignment was to eliminate
any source of knowledge.
-l guess l just did your job for you.
-Really?
-We'll get the package.
-l hope so.
l'm beginning to think you're getting
out of your depth here.
l want the package
delivered by Friday.
l suggest you hire a professional.
-Jonathan, are you okay?
-Yeah, don't worry about it. l'll be fine.
-Who was it?
-Warsaw.
Do l know her?
lf l'm not jealous,
you don't need to be.
lf you really love me,
you'd be jealous.
lt was a nice try anyway.
Nice try.
-Yeah.
-Hey, Jon. Coming for the service?
Hey, Sean. Yeah.
Soon as l can get a flight.
-What time do you think you'll be here ?
-What time's the memorial?
3:00 p.m.
Dad would've wanted you to come.
l'll be there, Sean.
l said l'd be there.
Fine.
Hello. Please, take a seat.
-You sure you won't eat?
-No, l'm in a hurry. Gotta go.
l've wondered over the last six months
if you've enjoyed Paris at all.
-What shall l do without you?
-l think you'll manage just fine.
Manage? To find another friend?
And one who comes through each time?
-They don't fall from the sky.
-Well, you have Dunois.
Yes, Dunois. Quite useful when the
most resolute measures are required.
What is this?
-Persuasion.
-For what?
-One final favor.
-l told you l gotta go.
A small favor. l want you to pick up
a package and deliver it to Germany.
Following your personal affairs,
of course.
The patron's address is on the back.
-Convenient for you?
-l don't want to get involved.
The package is at Versailles.
Dunois will accompany you.
Two Russians brought it from Athens.
Neither speak French.
They're holding it at a farm. You need
only collect it from them. Simple.
lf it's so simple,
why don't we all just meet in Paris?
Apparently, they're afraid to.
-How long to Versailles?
-We'll be there when the car stops.
-Well, l wasn't asking you.
-An hour, maybe less.
Marquet tells me you're leaving.
l'm sorry to hear that.
What you two had in common
remains a mystery.
l'd say we had ethics in common.
Relax. lt's one of Marquet's
safe houses. His aunt's farm.
You can always wait here.
When we're inside,
move the car up to the house.
Now listen to me.
l know Alex sent you...
...but we're gonna do this my way.
Get your gun out and hide it.
Take the left side. Don't say a word.
Okay.
Alex sent me.
Gentlemen. You know why l'm here?
l understand you have
something for me?
What is it?
Their tongues are cut out.
ls that the package?
l think this may be it, Dunois.
lt's clear! Let's go!
Okay. Go over to this farmhouse
with the lights right here.
Who were they?
-l don't know, but they spoke Danish.
-Sons of bitches.
-Let's see what they were willing to die for.
-You don't wanna do that.
Don't do that. lf you touch it again,
l will blow your 2-inch dick off.
You wanna open the package, do it with
Marquet's permission after we go back.
-We're gonna go back to Marquet?
-Yeah.
-What if he's involved?
-What if you're involved?
-What's all this?
-A silly precaution, l assure you.
-Perhaps you could wait.
-No, l've gotta catch a plane.
-Then l think you forgot something?
-Are you thinking of trying to stop me?
-Be reasonable. We had an arrangement.
-l don't risk my life for deliveries...
...particularly when
others don't share the risk.
The job isn't finished.
-Find yourself a new delivery boy.
-Think about it for a moment.
-Nobody wants you to miss your flight.
-Are you threatening me?
No, of course not. l just want
a conversation. Little drink.
-Talk through what transpired.
-Please.
Conversation. Remember...
...that's what we pay you for.
To talk to people.
Do me a favor. Talk to my friend.
Fucking ambush. Three, four of them.
Came in like the mist.
-We never heard them.
-Who were they?
Danish.
-Yeah, they were Danes.
-ldentification?
l didn't stick around to check.
Suddenly the whole place is on fire.
-There was a fire?
-Yeah. Your aunt's safe.
-l saw to that myself.
-Did you open the package?
No.
Then we're all agreed
that this was unexpected.
The only thing that's unexpected
is that l'm still alive.
-You were hired to deliver the package.
-Which was already there.
You're suggesting someone's working
the periphery. Are you implying it's me?
No, l just think maybe you're
being played as a scapegoat.
Suggestions?
l wouldn't trust anything
but the zeros on the bills.
Let me take care of this, Alex.
l'll deal with them personally.
Give me a moment. Please.
Please, sit.
l need a favor from someone l trust.
Will you deliver the package
to the agreed address?
The patron's waiting.
Okay.
Thank you. When you arrive in Warsaw...
...take my condolences to you
and your family.
Surprised you're here.
Thought you'd at least be incognito.
l got nothing to hide.
Here to take me to the services
with your escort?
Just want to talk.
Took time finding you. Thought you
were in South America.
l wouldn't think Paris suits you. The city
of decadence? Or maybe that's the point.
The last place on earth
you'd find Jonathan Cold.
Congratulations.
Your father died of natural causes,
in case you wonder.
Taking this ambassadorship wasn't easy
for him, but he's always admired the Polish.
l know he wanted you on the team.
Do you think training terrorists
in Pakistan was a team effort?
You think there is more honor in
hiring out what we train you to do...
...to a foreign operative
with a checkbook.
l fail to see the difference.
ln most countries,
you'd be killed for it.
-Asshole.
-Watch your mouth.
You're good at what you do.
Your father made the mold.
A lot's changed. You've seen it. Help
tip the balance. Keep us informed.
-Ally and adversary.
-Call it what you will.
-You're an asshole.
-l beg your pardon?
Let him go.
Left, right, left.
Detail, halt.
About face.
Forward march.
Left, right, left. Left, right, left.
Detail, halt.
Jackson Cold will have a monument
on the lawns of Arlington Cemetery.
We're giving him a memorial
here in Poland...
...on the soil of the country he defended
so resolutely during his lifetime...
...before we return him to his native
soil, to the country he loved so dearly.
Jackson was a citizen,
colleague, father, friend...
...but only wanted to be
remembered for what he considered...
...his life's achievement:
his family.
His devoted sons, Jonathan and Sean.
And so as we prepare
to send him home...
...let us pause to honor the legacy of
a soldier who will never be forgotten.
-Hey.
-Beautiful place, man. l love this.
-Thanks.
-You all right?
-Yeah.
-Drink?
-Yes, sir. Love one.
-Missed your flight?
-Standby. You're at everybody's mercy.
How long you been in Poland for?
-Six months.
-Yeah?
Dad asked me to come work for him.
So l'm hoping you'll get a little bit
better theater than Warsaw...
...because you know me, man.
l been there.
l have to ready Dad's office
for transition.
-Dad had a lot of friends, people he--
-Made promises to that you gotta keep.
Not everything's a fucking conspiracy,
Jon.
l mean, there are people in the world
who do things for the right reasons.
That's true,
just not very often in our business.
lt's funny, how we all ended up
in Europe.
This funeral's as close as we're
ever gonna come to a family reunion.
-You staying?
-No, l gotta go to Germany.
-Then what?
-Back to France, l guess.
Do you have a cell phone? Tracking you
became a matter of national security.
l'll tell you what. l'll shoot you a
number as soon as l touch ground.
-Great to see you, little brother.
-Good to see you too.
You've reached the Van Akens.
Sorry we can't take your call.
Ifyou leave your number,
we'll get back to you.
Thank you, and have a good day.
Schoolgirls.
Marquet wants to see you right now.
Can't you see l'm having an espresso?
-You're welcome to join me.
-The man said, ''Now.''
Nice toys.
You heard us.
All right. lf you insist.
Can l just pay my bill?
Hold it.
l'm glad you came.
-You can leave us.
-We'll be right outside.
Ever since our incident...
...l've insisted on expanded security.
You can never be too careful.
-Wine?
-Love some.
l've been meaning to talk with you.
ls that so?
My manners. Please, sit.
lt concerns your interlude
with Mr. Cold.
Were you aware he recognized
the assailant?
-l wasn't.
-Coincidence, or something else?
Neither, in my view.
Do you recall his assessment
before leaving here?
lnciting conspiracy
is a very dangerous business.
Mr. Cold has a thing for conspiracies.
But l doubt he'd set us up.
-lt's not his style.
-No. Of course, you're right.
l'm always right.
ls this why you called to see me?
lt's a troubling thought,
don't you agree? Someone so close...
...taking advantage,
exposing you to a point of weakness.
Check with me tomorrow. l have an errand
in Majorca and need someone l can trust.
Shall l send you?
Yeah.
Dunois, one more thing. How did you
know l wanted to see you?
-Hello?
-Yeah, is your daddy in?
Mommy?
-Hello, can l help you?
-ls Mr. Van Aken in?
No. Can l take a message?
-Do you know when you expect him?
-l'm not sure. May l ask who's calling?
No, thanks. l'll call back later.
-May l help you?
-Yeah, can l get a room here?
-Sure. 40 euros, please.
-You heard of Jerome Van Aken?
-Of course. Who hasn't?
-l'm sorry. l'm not from around here.
You don't have to be.
-Hello?
-Yeah, l need to ask you a question.
-Sure.
-You ever heard of Jerome Van Aken?
Yeah. Wealthy Euro-industrialist.
Old-money rich.
What else?
Jerome Van Aken. Well, he's about
as high-profile as they come.
He buys little contracts, builds them up
and then sells them for lots of money...
...to avoid running them. They call him
''the Viking with the Midas touch.''
Married nine years to a Meredith Casey?
-l have no idea.
-All right, thanks.
You've reached the Van Akens.
Sorry we can't take your call--
Hey! What are you doing?
That's my car.
Hey! Hey!
Bon voyage, mate.
-You heard of Jerome Van Aken?
-Yeah.
Wealthy Euro-industrialist.
Old-money rich.
-Married nine years to a Meredith Casey?
-I have no idea.
All right, thanks.
-Why is he asking about Meredith?
-Guy does his research.
Doesn't like surprises.
A stickler for detail.
That's what l get from his profile.
Maybe he finds her attractive.
Think he knows?
Well, he's in Germany.
l let that little prick have a chance.
Then l let him walk away.
So, what's the protocol here,
Mr. Olyphant?
-Contact Van Aken?
-Absolutely not.
l want you to eliminate Mr. Cold.
Not to get anywhere near Van Aken
or his family.
You understand me, Mr. Mimms?
l want Jonathan Cold an empty folder
in Langley by noon tomorrow.
-Yes?
-Yeah, I'm here to see Mr. Van Aken.
l'll send someone down.
May l help you?
Yeah, l have a message
for Mr. Van Aken.
-And who are you?
-l'm an old friend.
-Yeah.
-Hello, this is Meredith Van Aken.
-Do you know who l am?
-Yes.
l'm calling on my husband's behalf.
He's in London.
-Mr...?
-Webber.
He was wondering if we
could send someone for the delivery.
-l was asked to deliver it personally.
-What if l were to come for it?
-Could you meet me?
-When?
-Well, today if it's convenient.
-Where?
There's a train station on Freudstrasse
a few kilometers outside Terminus.
-Do you know where it is?
-No, but l can find it.
-Shall we say in an hour?
-Let's say in an hour.
l'll be in a white Rolls at the south
side of the station. l'll see you then.
Thank you very much, Mr. Webber.
Thank you for meeting me, Mr. Webber.
l hope it wasn't inconvenient.
ls that it?
Thank you, Mr. Webber.
This is for your trouble.
What the hell happened here?
Take deep breaths.
Try and hold one in.
Let it out slowly.
Feel that sharp pain
in the back of your neck?
That's centralized swelling.
Blood's unable to circulate properly
to your brain because of the clog.
You'll have a headache
for the next few minutes.
Within those few minutes, you are
to tell me where the real package is.
Or, l assure you, that headache will be
the least of your pains, Mr. Webber.
Which Van Aken do you work for?
Meredith or Jerome?
Mr. Webber, you're a funny man.
More than just a simple errand boy.
You seem to have taken
an active interest in my employer.
-Now, l wonder why that is.
-Are you the boyfriend?
What l am
is inconsequential to this moment.
Right now, all that is important...
...is for you to tell me
where the real package is.
-ln the next four-and-a-half minutes.
-Couldn't you find it yourself?
Perhaps l'm being vague.
So let me clarify.
Asphyxiation is the process by which
air is shut off to the lungs...
...thereby cutting off oxygen
to the brain.
And when the brain dies, Mr. Webber,
well, then, what's the point?
Now, before you let that happen...
...why not use what little brain matter
you've apparently been given...
...to make an informed decision?
We can pawn it together.
We're not the only ones who want this.
Unless you grew tits and looked
like Venus de Milo...
...why in bloody hell would l do that?
Deception begets deception
begets deception, Mr. Webber.
Without end.
Plainly, it's bad business.
-l know a lot of people--
-One minute!
-lt's not here, but l've got it.
-45 fucking seconds, yeah?
Tell me where it is, or l put the first
of three bullet holes in your face.
Okay. l have it in a locker...
...in an overnight train station.
l'll take you there.
Lovely.
Where's the fucking key?
ln my right front pocket here.
Smart move, Mr. Webber.
You better hope that package is there.
Don't fuck me about, mate.
Move your fucking ass!
Moment of truth, Mr. Webber.
Two sets of closure wait.
So open it. Slowly.
No puckering around,
or l'll blow your bleeding spine in two.
Just like you say, nice and easy.
Where you going?
What do you think l'm doing?
Easy.
Easy!
-Richard?
-Guess again.
You want some advice?
Send them in pairs.
Ifyou want to leave an impression
or a body, two are better.
Especially when you have no idea
who you're dealing with.
Mr. Webber, whatever
your estimation of me...
...the least l am is naive.
Do you honestly believe l'd send--?
Naivete is not what I'd accuse you of.
Arrogance comes to mind.
I wonder what your husband
thinks, sending your lover...
-...to collect what he's expecting.
-Lover?
Mr. Webber, you truly are misinformed.
Richard works--
-Worked.
-For my husband...
...and was sent at his request when l told
him about your magical package trick.
You know what l think? Your husband
doesn't know anything about this.
So, Mrs. Van Aken,
l called to inform you...
...that sending someone to kill me
was your last mistake.
Mr. Webber?
An explosion has erupted
from a faulty gas line--
Come on, look, look! What's going on?
Hurry! Hurry, come on!
Heinrichs, help me, help me!
The explosion happened
at 1 :32 a.m.
That's bullshit.
He must've lit a pipe bomb
with that kind of trajectory.
Why the fuck would he wanna
distress the local climate?
Not unless he had to.
Well, all right.
l'm gonna have some fun.
Good morning.
-Welcome to the Hotel Terminus.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-l'd like a room for the night.
And would you prefer two single
beds or one double, Mr...?
-Cold?
-One double should be plenty, dear.
Certainly.
All clear.
Hi.
-How are you?
-Fine, thank you. And you, sir?
Well, l'd be much better
if l could find my friend.
He forgot to leave me
his room number.
-What's the gentleman's name?
-Cold. Jonathan Cold.
lf l don't find him soon, he'll be
missing a very important conference.
Mr. Cold? l checked
a Mr. Cold in this morning.
Wonderful. What is his room number?
l'm sorry, sir. l cannot tell you.
Hotel policy.
No, no. Of course not.
-Perhaps you could call.
-No problem.
l'm sorry. There's nothing else
l can do but take a message.
Hello?
-Thank you all the same.
-You're welcome.
Feeling lucky?
Do you know who l am?
l didn't think so.
Mr. Webber?
What exactly are you doing here?
Trying to show you
anyone can be reached.
What do you want?
-l want to talk to your husband.
-l know Jerome will want to talk to you.
Perhaps, though, we can come
to some other kind of arrangement.
l doubt it.
Are you telling me
you're a man of principle?
ln light of these last few hours,
l find that contradictory.
Call him for me.
Mr. Webber, please try
and be reasonable.
Or you'll call the police and tell
them about your boyfriend...
...at the bus station
who you sent to kill me?
-He's not my boyfriend.
-l don't care.
-Call your husband, or l will.
-Hand me the phone. Please.
Julian, it's Meredith.
ls Jerome there?
How long will he be?
Can you have him call me
as soon as he's out?
Thank you.
Could you pass me my robe?
l don't understand.
lf you're planning to hand it over,
why switch packages in the first place?
Whatever you think
of my methodology...
...l'm a consummate professional.
You believe l'm conspiring
against my husband.
l didn't say that. l was hired to deliver
the package to your husband...
-...so that's how it's gonna be.
-Then you are a man of principle.
Listen. Everybody's got their
choice as to how they stay alive.
Some of us just don't know it.
-Hello.
-Mr. Mimms?
Checking in under
his name proved to be risky.
Mr. Cold....
Pardon me, Mr. Webber
is an unpopular man these days.
What about the rental car?
Driving a four-door silver Mercedes...
-...along with a few other people in town.
-Jesus Christ.
Now you listen to me
very carefully, Mr. Mimms.
I want this situation
resolved immediately.
How shall l proceed?
If I have to answer that question...
...l assume you are
not up to the assignment.
Okay, silver Mercedes, FB5288.
Shouldn't be too hard.
Damn! Payday!
Fuck!
Excuse me. Sir.
Hey! Hi. Hi, excuse me.
Excuse me.
-Excuse me.
-What do you want?
You're not my guy, are you?
-Take it easy.
-Where did you get the car?
lt isn't mine.
This man paid me 2000 euros
to drive it to Berlin and drop it off.
-We traded cars.
-Fuck!
Stupid motherfucker.
The footsteps lead off
in this direction.
There is a blood trail as well.
He must have sustained a serious injury.
We need to run a forensic test
on all this material.
All of the evidence is here.
Except no body.
Sir, a Kevlar flak jacket.
Government lssue.
Shit.
Sean, we need to talk. Get inside.
We'll take a drive.
How bad is it?
Could get a lot worse
if we don't bring him in.
What do you expect me to do?
l talked to him for 20 minutes.
He told me he had to go to Germany,
and after that, who knows where.
All l'm asking
is that you wait on a call.
Help bring him in.
That's it.
-Hello.
-Sean, l was about to leave a message.
-What's up?
-Do you remember a friend of Dad's...
...by the name of Agatha Shearwater?
-Yeah.
-I got a package I gotta send to her.
Tell her it's important she gets it
and tells me what's on it.
-Jon--
-And one other thing.
Remember my friend Boris, works in my
department? Tell him l'll be calling soon.
Listen, Jon, there's something
here l need to go over with you...
...something of Dad's that he left for you.
We can't close his office until then.
Do you think you could come back?
-I don't know.
-Just for a day or two.
-lt's important.
-l'll try to make it back later.
Listen, Jon--
You did a good thing, Sean.
-Hello?
-There's a fire lane north of Terminus.
-Can you find it?
-Yes.
There's an old building
on the west side.
That's where I'll be. I'll wait 10
minutes. By quarter past, I'll be gone.
-Be on time. Be alone.
-What about my daughter?
I need to take care of her,
make sure she's safe.
She'll be fine. Just you be careful.
I hope so. She's all I've got.
I'll see you in a little while. Goodbye.
My Fuhrer sends his apologies.
Hiring that sauerkraut to drive
your rental was a nice touch.
l hope you didn't go far
out of pocket on my account.
Ain't no thing.
You kind of look like Ray Charles.
Old Ray can't shoot
as good as you, right?
-There you go.
-What can l do for you?
We'll talk about it on the way down.
Let's go.
-Jared sent you?
-Something like that.
Should've stayed in France.
Kept this venture out of the spotlight.
Let me ask you something.
-Did Olyphant send you for the package?
-What package would that be?
All right, man,
let's cut to the chase, okay?
-You like the dollar bill?
-Dead presidents. Greenbacks.
You care to expound?
l'll give you 1 0 times more
than he's giving you for this business.
l got a disk loaded with offshore accounts
of the biggest dogs in the world.
Hundreds of millions of dollars.
-You don't have this with you, do you?
-lt's real close.
Wow. You don't miss a trick.
The ball is in your court for
the next two minutes. You fuck up...
...at least l get to kill a legend.
Because l have no love lost for Jared
Olyphant. He can kiss my black ass.
Yeah, you know...
...your man Dunois...
...when l popped a cap in his ass,
he flew out the window like a bird.
-How does it look?
-So far, so good.
-How does it look inside?
-Look good to me.
-All good. No surprises, right?
-l got nothing for you.
You're the man. You are the man.
Yeah, l hope we getting close
to that disk.
Watch your ass, Mr. Cold.
l don't wanna shoot you in the back.
l don't suppose it would pay
to ask who sent you.
-No good.
-You know, l just somehow feel like...
...this might be the end
of the road for me.
But you do remind me of my cousin Delbert
from down around Bogalusa.
Motherfucker!
-l let you live, and you do me like this?
-You let me live?
Sweet dreams, Bruce Lee.
Here's the disk.
Love a barbecue.
That was not an accident, old friend.
l promise you, l haven't had
a clean shot like that in years.
Marquet send you?
Our good friend Marquet
met with an untimely accident.
l'm sorry to have to tell you this.
l remember how close you were.
-You don't look too good.
-You don't look so good yourself.
l should be on the Riviera...
...a craving l've had since my mother
showed me the ocean.
Waves massaging the shore...
...whilst l watch the sunset,
drinking champagne.
Now, no more bedtime stories.
-Where's the package?
-What package?
You're running out
of hiding places, my friend.
Do you believe l found this barn
through premonition?
Do what you can to eliminate
the innocent from this equation.
lt looks like you've been had, Dunois.
Meredith sent you to kill me,
but she's got the package.
-l thought you were smarter than that.
-No, no, no.
You're much smarter than that.
l know you like l know myself.
Don't fuck with me.
Why don't you go ahead and kill me then.
Start your own little Easter egg hunt.
-What the fuck is that?
-That sets up a honing device.
Folks will come
and find you within meters.
-Lets who know where to find you?
-Foreign ops.
-How do you stop it?
-You don't. lt's too late.
Son of a bitch.
They know you're here. The ClA.
Know what that means? lf these folks
are coming, there's more behind them.
All right. You've bought some time.
We'll go to his wife...
...get the package.
-l'll deal with her. Then we walk away.
-l'd love to walk away.
-What's going on?
-l'll explain later. We gotta get out of here.
Let's go.
At your estate, l'll borrow a few things.
l'll leave you this.
Then l'm out of here.
-Mr. Webber, l--
-My name is Jonathan...
...and l've opened the package.
Why are you and your husband
so interested in that crash?
There's a ''we'' involved,
but it doesn't include me.
Let's move. Jared wants a clean sweep
of this place immediately.
Keep moving. Let's go! Let's go!
''We.'' Who else besides
your husband was involved?
Jared Olyphant.
-Are they in here, Jared and your husband?
-l'm not sure.
Prep the charges.
First charge is in place.
Come on, hurry it up.
l want no traces left.
l need you to help us get away
from Jerome. Far away.
l know what they did,
and l know why they did it.
l've been planning this for a year.
With your help, we can finally get out.
l won't help until you tell me
why they blew up that plane.
Final charge prepped and ready.
Setting final charge now.
Prepare to move out.
ln 1 982, Jerome formed
a company called Unified Growth...
...building fertilizer plants
throughout Europe.
-The plants were a front.
-Biochemical warfare.
The plants came under the umbrella of the
lnternational Security Services Board.
Run by Jared Olyphant.
The head engineer of Unified Growth
documented everything.
He was planning on exposing
the entire operation.
The developer's name
was Stefan Stockwell.
He was a very good friend of mine.
Stefan kept quiet until he had
every detail accounted for.
He was going to Greece.
He never made it.
lf my husband suspects
that l have anything to do with this...
...he will kill me.
And anyone else
who's associated with me.
-What do these lead to?
-The truth.
Stefan had a house in Norway.
Jerome knows nothing about it.
Stefan hid the documents...
...and l am the only one left
who knows where they are.
And how deeply involved
Jerome and Jared are.
l may be able to get you and your
daughter into Paris, then Norway.
l know this isn't easy for you.
Thank you.
Don't talk on the phone to anybody.
Your husband's got the wire tapped.
-Tapped?
-That guy found us at the barn somehow.
He probably heard something
on the phone.
Figure out something
to tell your daughter...
...about who l am and why you're going
with me here. Goodbye.
What do you think?
-Dad's old hangout. You hungry?
-No.
Listen.
Here.
Agatha sent the original
to your usual pickup.
Don't worry about it.
You mind if we go someplace else?
Somewhere we could talk?
We lost them.
-What's going on?
-What are you talking about?
Jared's telling me
you fucked up bigtime.
Look, he told me what you did
after you got caught.
Are you trying to negotiate your way out
by giving up Dad's name to the KGB?
-Just to save your ass?
-He's playing you to get to me.
-Then you tell me what happened.
-You know l'm not a talkative man...
...but l'll say this.
l was what they call a foreigner.
Deep undercover. No trace, no ties.
l was arrested for espionage.
Dad and Jared could have gotten me out.
Jared made sure they didn't.
Suddenly, the whereabouts
of Jonathan Cold are no longer recorded.
Jared left me to rot in Soviet prison.
That's where Jared is.
-His boys probably told him they lost us.
-Yeah.
Jared, aren't you a little old
for this cloak-and-dagger shit?
By now l'm sure you know it's almost
behind me. Do yourself a favor...
...walk away. Get on a plane and go.
You've made your point.
l somehow think if l got up on a plane,
it would suddenly blow up in the sky.
Somehow you always know,
don't you?
That tape won't do any good
for anything anymore. lt's too late.
You really think after 1 6 years that
little episode will come home to roost?
Think again.
Okay. Listen, little piece of advice.
Stay away from me.
When the time is right,
l'm sure Sean will lend a hand.
-They are not coming, are they?
-Doesn't seem like it.
Listen, l want to hand you this.
You know what to do...
-...if anything happens to me.
-No problem.
This side looks good.
-l've been spotting this wall all day.
-How come l'm still running into you?
Because you didn't kill me
at the old building.
Why are you here?
You didn't return for the princess?
How little you know. The little princess
hired me to kill her husband.
Don't you think it's a coincidence that
she would have found both of us?
She reached me through the Danish.
How she knows them is anybody's guess.
l told Marquet you were behind this,
and you killed him, didn't you?
Going to Versailles was supposed
to be simple.
Take care of the Russians,
collect the package.
And get rid of me?
-You weren't supposed to be there.
-But l was.
That was your friend Marquet's call.
Sending forth his confidant.
He was the go-between
for Jerome Van Aken.
What are you gonna do?
Pull the trigger? Huh?
There's an army of them in there.
lt's impossible to get in alone.
And you, my friend, want in.
Together, l think we can.
Once we're in, do whatever you want,
just stay away from me and the girl.
Let's do this. Remember, l will be
watching you. Every move you make.
Let's go.
-l count six, seven, yeah?
-Seven, yeah.
-How many rounds you got?
-Six.
lt's a long shot. You're the expert.
-Take this.
-Cheers.
Fuck it. l'll use the rifle.
Bon, fucking, soir, monsieur.
What do you think, l'm stupid?
That wasn't very nice, but then again,
one good turn deserves another.
Mr. Cold, l presume.
lt's a pleasure to meet you.
You come highly recommended to me
by a friend of mine, Alexander Marquet.
-l was hoping you had something for me.
-No.
-You delivered it to Meredith?
-Yeah.
Allow me to enlighten you as to
the condition of my wife, Mr. Cold.
She is a deeply troubled woman.
-l don't wanna hear it.
-l think it's only fair.
After all, l have a feeling
you've fallen victim to her illness.
lt evokes a certain
bird with a broken wing syndrome.
Meredith has a way with people...
...a talent for persuading them to assist
her in playing out her delusions.
She took my daughter, Mr. Cold.
And diseased or not...
...that is the basest form
of moral turpitude imaginable.
And what about Stefan?
-He was a friend of mine.
-Until he had an affair with your wife?
l didn't find out about the affair
until a year ago.
By then, it had very little bearing
on my feelings toward Stefan.
Well, listen, l'd like you
to listen to this.
-Something's moving towards us.
-Can't be.
It's moving in our flight path.
Check the radar.
Nothing. Wait, I see it.
There, cruising at 28,000 feet.
It's gonna hit us, unless--
Oh, my God! Oh, my God, it--
Believe what you will, Mr. Cold.
That l have the power to motivate
something as terrible as that.
She's told you what she thinks
l've done and why l did it.
The whole incident's been an ongoing
obsession of hers the past decade.
Stefan Stockwell
was her lover, Mr. Cold.
What he wasn't was some trumped-up
humanitarian with a conscience.
He was our top engineer.
He knew what we paid him to do.
Whatever dictated his ethics later on,
if indeed anything did, l can't tell you.
Unfortunately,
he died in a plane crash...
...which my wife has convinced
herself l am entirely responsible for.
Wishing something to happen and
planning it are two different things.
That's true.
Despite my personal
differences with Stefan...
...l would not kill dozens
of innocent people to see him dead.
As l've told you before,
Meredith is a very persuasive woman.
Now, where is she?
Find my wife and daughter, Mr. Cold.
Find them and bring my daughter
back safely and l'll pay you any price.
lncluding any judgments
or inquiries placed upon me.
You have your own pros.
Why don't you use them?
Well....
l understand one of my closest
met with an unfortunate accident...
...in Warsaw last night.
l'm afraid l'm running out of them.
l can make you a very rich man,
Mr. Cold.
Bring my daughter
back safely, at any price.
And what about your wife?
l leave that up to your best judgment.
Yes?
lt must look like an accident.
Yes.
l expected more from you, Dunois.
At the very least, l thought you would
have recovered that package.
But no matter.
l'm sure Mr. Cold will help
finish things.
Oh, yes...
...your services
are no longer required.
l'm afraid my employer
feels differently.
Come on, Clarissa.
Come inside, please.
-Mommy, Mommy.
-l'm in here, darling.
Thanks for the lift.
l need to go to the old farmhouse.
lt's down the road.
Everything okay?
No!
Jonathan, behind you!
Get her out the window.
Go. Now.
Come on, darling. lt's okay.
Next time, wait for me, all right?
-Hope this will do.
-Thank you.
And l need you to keep these closed.
-lt's a beautiful view.
-Well, you'll just have to enjoy it later.
Somehow, wine doesn't suit you.
-You seem more like a whiskey man.
-What's that supposed to mean?
What else have you discovered while
you were snooping around my home?
Only that you don't keep
many personal artifacts.
Thank you.
-Do you have a family?
-l have a brother.
-Older or younger?
-Wiser.
Listen, l wanna concentrate on
how to get you out of Paris.
ls there any place in particular
that you'd like to go?
America.
This is yours.
A lot of good it should do now.
All the real evidence was destroyed.
Well, we can build it again.
lt's hard keeping her cooped up.
Can l take her for a walk?
lt truly is a beautiful city.
-Oh, God.
-What?
Get away from that girl, now!
lt's not safe on the streets.
We've been spotted.
Gotta get you out of here.
Sit down in here.
Right here. Don't move.
You hear me? Don't move.
The mother and daughter
that were here, have you seen them?
Meredith?
lt's from Meredith.
l had the currency exchanged.
lt was the least l could do...
-...after you'd killed me twice.
-Sorry about that.
But, you know,
they say three's a charm.
Surprise!
Come on! Come on!
Thank you for your help
in securing the package.
It was the only way to force
my husband to relinquish our daughter.
But now that it's over
and I have her...
...your services
are no longer required.
I wish you all the best.
Maybe we'll meet again
somewhere down the road. Meredith.