It's so good to have you home
for a night.
I've missed you.
I'm a doctor.
I'm on call.
Dr. Sienna.
I'll be there.
There's an emergency
at the hospital.
- Don't go.
- I gotta go.
Don't go, Frank.
This better be good.
They need you pretty bad.
I can't even make love
to my wife.
You're breakin' my heart.
God, he's lost a lot of blood.
Do the best you can.
We gotta get him to a hospital,
Angelo.
His blood pressure's dropping,
he's in shock.
He's in shock? I'm in shock!
Nino! Where's the merchandise?
Nino, pay attention!
What the hell are you doing?
What do you want, Doc?
Come on, Frank. Just do your stuff,
all right? Not a day later?
I was doin' like you said.
This guy came out of nowhere
with a twelve gauge.
That's not what I'm askin'.
Where are my diamonds?
He pulled me out of the store window.
They rolled out over the sidewalk.
They shot everybody in the store.
My diamonds end up in the sewer?
- I got some of them... in my shoe.
- In your shoe?
Look at this.
Bull, you rat bastard!
Son of a bitch!
Nobody robs from me!
- He wasn't gonna tell me about it.
- The undertaker would have found.
Hey, come on. The guy was gonna
die anyway, right?
Jesus.
You did the best you could.
You all right?
Frankie, you all right?
Frankie, show 'em the watches.
That's solid 14 carat gold.
These are real diamonds.
Your girl would like that, right?
That, my friend, is 14... touch it.
14 carat gold with diamonds.
You want it, you buy it.
Only the best.
Where you guys goin'?
You want some of this?
What are you doin'?
I told you to take it to a fence.
Not decorate your car with it.
We thought we'd sell it here
for the afternoon.
I'll take your eyes out. You sellin'
merchandice on the street.
Well, there's plenty of them,
Mr. D.
Who's your girlfriend?
You know, I vouched for him.
He's Frankie.
Yeah, see I mean, look
there's end of the shift.
There's 40 guys out here with
paychecks in their pockets...
and buy somethin' for their wives
or their girlfriends.
Danny and I take all the risk,
and that leaves more on your end.
Ang?
Make sure you make that
numbers drop on time, all right?
Absolutely.
Oh, Jesus.
Frank!
- Papa, what...
- Why are you doing this?
Selling stolen stuff!
No, wait. Mr. Sienna, it's
not stolen. We didn't steal it.
We're just sellin' it for a friend.
And it's good prices
for the guys here.
You get that stuff out of here!
- Pop, calm down, will you?
- No! Go!!
- Hey, come on!
- Pop! What are you doin', Pop?
Is this your way of makin' money
for college?
We're sellin' things. What are you
gettin' so bent out of shape?
You're gonna end up
just like them.
That's great. Thanks a lot,
Mr. Sienna.
I've got fifteen trucks out there
waiting to pour.
They're puttin' the scaffolds up
as fast as they can, Mr. D.
But not fast enough, or else we
wouldn't have to drive down here.
Maybe what you need is
another tune-up, huh?
You see the men out there?
They got food on the table
because of me.
Their children have shoes
on their feet because of me.
They have jobs because of me.
Mr. D...
The bridge. The concrete.
That was all my concrete.
I built the bridge.
And I built you.
You have this nice Union job.
You think you got it by accident?
I put you there.
And the only thing
I ever asked you...
was to remember that
time is money.
Leo!
Jimmy, hang in there!
Everybody down!
- Everybody clear out of the way!
- Let's go! Move!
Let's go! You, go!
Clear!
Nicky, look at this.
Your men are walkin' out.
It's that damn shop steward,
Sienna.
Mr. D., he's always
makin' trouble.
- The grunts do whatever he tells.
- They should do what you tell them.
Get outta here.
- I'm sorry, Mr. D.
- Get outta here.
- It's Sienna.
- All right.
What the hell do you
think you're doin'?
At the speed we are, it's a matter
of time before a guy gets killed.
- You know that, Maury.
- What you know is what I tell you.
Now, I want your men back up
there to fix it.
You fix it. I'm takin' my men
off of this bridge!
You go tell your bosses, and
you know who I'm talkin' about...
my men aren't going to die
so they can line their pockets!
That's better.
Joe's wife called me
about the accident.
She told me he almost fell.
Somebody's gonna get killed.
Genaro?
Genaro, what is it?
You're hurt.
- Ma, it's nothing. It's nothing.
- Oh... yu're hurt.
I don't know why I bother to
do this anymore.
He's ended up worse than a thief.
Frank is here for dinner.
I don't want him in my home.
You tell him to leave.
We don't takes orders
from nobody.
I know it was the best thing.
- I don't know.
- Wash your hands.
I love you, Nonie. I love your sauce,
but I gotta go.
Always Danny gotta go!
Where you gotta go?
Well, you know, I thought I'd go
to the father and give confession...
and then see if the nuns
need any help.
Ah, non fredo.
Jesus, let me look at that. Will you
get me the needle and thread?
Jesus. You should've gone to the
emergency room, Pop.
- That's what I got you for.
- Drink. This is gonna hurt.
Okay.
Sorry.
My father make better grappa.
I heard about what happened, Pop.
You shouldn't make waves like that.
It's honest work, Frankie.
Remember that.
Pop, it gets noticed. I'm just tryin' to
look out for you.
I mean, don't you want somethin'
better than this? A nice house?
It was good enough for you
growing up.
Those men you work for with
he 50 thousand dollar Cadillac's...
with the big rolls of cash.
Do you know what's gonna
happen to them?
They're dead. No future.
No dreams.
Nothing.
- You had a dream.
- Pop, stay still.
You had a dream, Frankie.
Ever since you were little, you...
Yeah, I know, Pop. I have a dream.
I want to be a doctor.
But it takes money to be a doctor.
You gotta go to school.
- Wait a minute, Pop.
- I...
What are you doin'?
I know it's not much.
Pop, I can't take this.
Look, I know what I'm doin'.
I'm gonna work, make enough money
and then I'm gonna get out.
I know these guys.
Once they think they own you,
that's it.
You know, I never get that.
Hey, boys!
I'm hitting the tables.
Pete, good to see you.
Vamos, fill me in.
Why do Italians hate
Jehovah Witnesses?
I don't know. Why do Italians hate
They hate all witnesses.
Bravo!
Forget about the Ice Queen,
Frankie.
She's out of your league.
She's a college girl.
Frankie here's been to college.
Right, Frankie?
Forget about her. I don't care
if you are freakin' Einstein.
Every guy in this place tried to
launch that boat.
Hey.
Somethin' I can do for you?
The question is,
what can I do for you?
Look, I'm here to sing.
It's what I get paid to do.
So don't waste my time with
your dumb lines, all right?
All right. No more dumb lines.
- Would you like to go out?
- I never go out with the customers.
Well, how about if I promise
never to come here again?
That's very clever, but I'm not
lookin' for a mobster boyfriend.
You're all morons.
And, even if I was,
you wouldn't be him.
I'm Frank Sienna.
I'm sorry about the dumb line.
I'm an idiot.
Lorina Ryan.
Lorina Ryan,
you have a beautiful voice.
- It's an okay voice.
- No, it's really terrific.
It's too good for this place.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
So, I'm doin' pretty good,
right?
Not bad. I am,
still sittin' here.
Right. Right.
So, I'm gonna quit
while I'm ahead.
You're not that far ahead.
What time is it?
It's late.
Hey, weren't you supposed
to drop that off last night?
It's all still there, right, Dan?
Most of it.
What do you mean "most of it"?
- How much did you lose?
- Two large.
Come on, we gotta get it by
morning. It'll be all right.
We gotta get it by morning, it's
gonna be all right? Are you crazy?
Skimmin' from Nicky D.,
you're gonna get us both killed!
Don't you ever do that again!
You understand me?
Okay, relax. You think I don't got
a thing lined up here?
You got a thing lined up here?
You think I'm gonna let you down
and leave you hangin'? I got a thing.
Come on. Let's go see a man about
some money.
What's the matter with you?
The guy works nights. He keeps
his cash in the wall.
Jesus, could you make more noise?
Come on, baby, where's my money?
- You wanna give me a hand over?
- For what?
I'm tellin' you, the money,
it's in the wall.
No, watch out!
Here we go. Here we go.
Here we go, yeah.
Okay, let's get outta here.
Let's get outta here.
What's that? What are we
talkin' about here?
See that?
Come here.
See that? Look what
I'm talkin' about here?
Was that easy or what?
A bing bang, boom!
Let's get outta here.
What are you...
Is he dead?
What'd you do that for?
Let's get out of here.
All right, this is it.
Now, there's a hundred wanna be
humps in this neighborhood.
They want to roll with
Delarusso's crew.
But it's real simple. You gotta be
a good earner.
You know what I'm sayin'? You gotta
make a lot of money for that man.
When you're not makin', you gotta
be thinkin' about ways to make money.
Now roll over. Roll over.
I'll put a bullet in you.
I'll blow your brains...
That dog reminds me
of my old girlfriend.
Yeah, except the dog
is better lookin'.
Yeah, like your sister.
Where you been, Danny?
Georgie expected you yesterday.
And he's all upset, and now
you know he's got that heart thing.
Yeah, I was just gettin' ready
to drop it off.
- It's all here?
- Yeah, forget about it.
We would have had it here earlier,
but, we did a thing last night.
You mean it was you guys at
that Hawthorne Avenue thing?
Yeah, we went in and out.
We were gonna give you your cut.
Wait right here.
Would you stop starin' at him?
He doesn't like it.
- I'm Danny Keaton. And this is my...
- Sit your ass down, Mick.
That thing on Hawthrone Avenue?
That was a police captain's house.
He's with us.
He gets his ham and cheese sandwich
every week.
And all this
poor bastard knows...
is everything he had is gone,
including his dead father's watch.
And he's got twenty stitches
in the side of his head.
That is not "in and out". You guys
gave a beatin' to a police captain.
Put your hands on the table.
There's a Sicilian custom.
It goes back hundreds of years.
Punishment for thieves.
Do you know what it is?
They chopped off their hands.
Here. Here it is.
Yeah?
Now where are the fazools?
Lou, count that.
Fourteen hundred.
The Captain said it was
more like 34 hundred.
You jerk-offs blew two dimes
in twelve hours?
Is that what you call layin' low?
The streets aren't safe with you
two master criminals walkin' around.
You're different from the Mick.
You go to school?
Yeah, Frankie, he wants
to be a doctor.
What are you, a ventriloquist?
He asked him.
Yeah, I tried to go to college,
but it didn't work out.
A doctor, huh?
It takes a lot of discipline to be
a doctor. You that kind of man?
Yes, Sir.
That's good. We need more educated
people in this thing of ours.
Cultured people. That's good.
Too bad the two of you are
gonna be in jail.
What?
You gotta answer for the
beatin' up of the cop.
You know, Nicky, this Mick has
big balls. He could do that thing.
Then we give the two large back
to the Captain. We're all set.
Okay. All right.
That's him. Genaro Sienna.
He's the shop steward.
You do him.
Come on. Do him,
and we get outta here.
What's this kid waitin' for?
That piece of work that you
want done. I can't do it.
Get these two girls outta here.
I don't want to look at 'em.
Do you know Sienna's
my old man, Mr. Delarusso?
Look, about Frankie,
no disrespect...
he's doin' what any one would do.
He's like an old man to me, too.
You did that left field thing before,
and now you do this!
It's not his fault,
Mr. Delarusso.
Give me my father's life.
Me for him.
I'll work for you
the rest of my life. Please.
You're goin' away for
the cop thing.
I have no problem with that.
Your father has a pass.
He's finished on the job.
He sweeps up at the Union Hall.
He cost me a lot of money.
Your life is mine now.
You understand that?
And now for the final matter
on the agenda.
As you all know, this year...
there's a full scholarship to medical
school going to Frank Sienna.
Genaro's son.
One of our own is gonna
to Italy be a doctor...
because of your union dues.
Come on up here, Frank.
That's it, Frank.
Congratulations, Frank.
I'm proud of you, Frankie.
I think you got your mother's
intelligence, god rest her soul.
Now, in Italy, it's different
over there.
They do things in a different way.
Like...
- They kiss.
- Example, they kiss on both cheeks.
Yes, even men. Don't forget,
or it's an insult.
Okay, hold on a second.
Micky D. Sends his regards.
Dr. Sienna!
Congratulations, Doc.
Come see your father.
The doctor's here!
Hey, Pop.
To my son, the doctor.
Salute.
It's good.
Dago red.
You all right?
That cough sounds terrible.
We're gonna get that checked out.
Tomorrow, first thing you're
comin' to the hospital.
We're gettin' that checked out.
I'm a doctor. You gotta listen.
I got emphysema.
The doctor, they told me
I got it good.
Pop, how long have you known?
Years.
I want you to meet this nice...
Anita.
Naples School of Medicine.
Internship, Vasper De Napoli.
Residency in General and
Cardiac Surgery.
Actually, my residency was in
cardio vascular surgery.
It's all there in my letters
of recommendation.
The cardiac department was
shorthanded...
- so I was helping out a lot.
- Helping out?
Ventricle and arterial scepter
repairs mostly.
Congenital heart defects.
I did more B.S.D. Repairs in one year
than any other doctor on staff.
This is America, not Naples.
The position is in
General Surgery.
You may be needed to assist in
cardio vascular surgeries.
Take it or leave it.
Excuse me?
The position is yours
if you want it.
Yes, of course.
- I just have a few questions.
- You start tomorrow.
What do you want?
You look better than when
you went in.
- I'll take you now.
- Hombre...
What is this thing?
It's a toy car?
No, this is an
Alfa Romeo Spider Volace.
A what? It looks like
a matchbox.
Here, I'll drive it.
So, they treated you well
inside, huh?
Yeah. Mafia manner.
Actually, they leave us alone
in there, you know?
I ran a good business.
Booze, drugs, broads.
Forget about it.
The old waps, they got together,
they cooked.
I swear to god, we ate like kings.
Unbelievable. I put on some pounds.
You did some clammin'
in there, huh?
While you were, runnin' around
chasin' nurses...
I was gettin' an education, too.
You know, you shouldn't have had
to take the fall for that.
No, hey, it was time well-spent.
Don't worry about that.
You know what? You don't
look like a doctor.
You still look like that punk kid
who used to chase me around.
I chased you around? You
idolized me, you Mick prick!
How you doin', Dr. Sienna?
- Good, Lou. How about yourself?
- So far so good.
- I heard good things about you.
- You've been hearin' right.
It's like déjá vu all over again.
How many times do I gotta tell you?
Ang, I'm runnin' the Union.
Everything's fine.
Wait here.
You prick.
You are who you are because
we put you there!
You know that you don't take bread
out of your brother's mouth, right?
I'm not a thief, Mr. D.
On my children, never.
The meeting is over.
You're gonna sort this thing out,
right, Maury?
Yeah, Mr. D.
Frankie!
Welcome back.
Listen, I was wonderin' if I could
come up and see you at your office.
I got this heartburn.
It's constant.
- Of course.
- Thanks, Frankie.
- We're all really proud of you.
- Thank you, Mr. Maury.
Hey! Look who it is! The doctor!
- Hey! You look good.
- Thank you.
- How was Italy?
- Wonderful.
I hope you don't think who you are
just 'cause you're a big-time doctor.
Come on, Nicky.
St. Charles is a very good hospital.
You didn't think I knew, huh?
When one of ours makes it,
I know everything.
I'm very proud of you.
You did really good.
Thanks, Nicky.
Now listen. You trust
this kid, Danny?
Yeah, he's been like a
brother to me.
I don't like him.
I don't know,
maybe cause he's Irish.
I don't know. He's a good earner.
He's gonna be on Angelo's crew.
So anything that you need from me,
you let Danny know.
He'll get right back to me, okay?
Anything at all. You understand?
Now, there's something that
I want to ask you to do.
Yeah, anything, Nicky.
I haven't forgotten.
You're gonna be busy. You're gonna
have this big job at the hospital.
I'm hopin' that you're gonna find
the time to be my family doctor.
- Take care of me and Rose.
- Of course, Nicky. I'm your doctor.
I don't trust the other guys,
you know?
I want you to meet somebody.
Dr. Frank Sienna.
He's from St. Charles Hospital.
The best.
He's been after me to go to
a doctor, and now he brings one.
It's nice to meet you.
You're a nice boy,
but I don't like doctors.
She's tired all the time.
This is the truth.
It's a sin to get old?
I want one of those
Sicilian remedies.
That's what I need.
You know, they always worked
in the old days.
They are completely useless.
They stink up the whole house.
Why don't you just let this kid
check you out? That's all.
Why don't you come in, we'll run
a few tests, just to make sure.
- I don't go to hospitals.
- Why don't you go to hospitals?
That's where people go
to die.
I'll explain everything
before-hand.
We don't have to do anything
that makes you uncomfortable.
Please?
Please, Roie?
I'll go get the tests. If that's
what my Nicky wants.
Make sure you don't get 20 shots
of the back of my head like you did.
Well, looks like we got
a new player.
Janie, give me a dog, will ya?
Sure.
What are you doin'?
He's really a lunatic, this guy.
You could get yourself killed
that way, Detective.
Hey, boys, how's it goin'?
What do you say we go into your
club for a couple of espressos?
What? I'm Sicilian, too.
You didn't know that, huh?
You gotta be a member.
What?
Of what, the Mafia?
I think you're lucky to be alive,
DeSante.
Well, don't think, Angelo.
You're just gonna hurt yourself.
What are you embarassin' yourself
for? Just live and let live.
Live and let live?
I grew up in this neighborhood,
right down that street over there.
We're all pizane.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I forget that sometimes, you know.
Give me hug, Don Nicky, huh?
What is with the guys
that hug and kiss you.
You get a little pissed off?
What are you gonna do,
kiss me now?
- You need a hobby.
- I'm lookin' at it.
Everything you say and do,
I'm there.
My whole life is dedicated
to watching you die in prison.
We'll see who dies.
See, pizans.
No, this is my case.
You're assisting.
When we first met, I thought
you were just another, Wise Guy.
Me? No, I'm Irish.
If me sainted mother were alive,
she'd be thankin' St. Patrick...
that her Danny boy met
Lorina Ryan.
The most beautiful girl
in Jersey.
Go on with ya now.
- Hey, Frank.
- Sorry I'm late.
Sit down. I'd like to introduce
you to my girl.
Frank Sienna.
Lorina Ryan.
- Pleasure.
- You two know each other?
Maybe from the neighborhood.
Come here, you son of a bitch.
When'd you get out? Come on here.
Do me a favor. Look after
my girlfriend, all right, Frankie?
Sure.
- Danny, has a lot of friends.
- He's the life of the party.
You, uh, work on
Wall Street with him?
Wall Street? No, actually Danny and
I grew up in the same neighborhood.
So, did you make it
through college?
Yeah. I'm a teacher.
Second grade.
I always figured you'd make it.
Well, at least I know you
kept your word.
You promised, never to come back
to the club again, and you didn't.
You never bothered to pick up
the phone and call me, either.
- I was away.
- Away? For eight years.
I know a little about the justice
system. Eight years means a felony.
So, what'd you do? You kill
somebody? Rob somebody?
You know when your Irish is up,
your eyes change color?
I don't want to know where you've
been. It's your business.
You make it sound like
I'm asking you out.
Aren't you?
- Hi. How are we? How we doin'?
- Good.
Where are the menus? Tommy!
Can we get some menus over here?
You want some champagne?
Oh, I gotta go.
What is that?
What are you talkin' about?
- I gotta go. I'II...
- You just got here.
I know. I'll call you tomorrow.
It was nice to meet you,
Ms. Ryan.
See ya, Dan.
He's a doctor. You know, this thing,
it happens all the time.
Heard you had that baby
with the tetralogy.
Could get very complicated.
You're taking a risk
with a newborn.
That baby was only a heartbeat
away from full arrest.
Worst odds I've ever seen.
Odds? That's right, you're
a gamblin' man, aren't you.
On occasion.
I'd have to say 10 to 1 that baby
never gets off the table.
Well, that baby is in good hands.
What is Sienna doing in there?
He's not qualified, Phil.
His talents are wasted in
General Surgery, Lyle.
Look, what is it? What is it
you've got against him, huh?
- He's an embarrassment.
- Watch him, Lyle.
He's a natural.
He's the best I've seen.
You're putting that baby and
this hospital at risk.
Mr. And Mrs. Hennessey?
The baby's gonna be fine.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
- He's a real fighter.
- Now let me take you to I.C.U.
- Come on, this way. Frank.
- Thank you.
- Frank.
- What are you doin' here?
- I came with Danny.
He wanted to take his
best friend out to dinner.
- Where is he?
- He stepped out.
I saw the nurses.
How you've been
savin' babies again.
Eight years of medical school's
gotta be worth somethin', huh?
Oh, yeah?
So, I got this problem,
Dr. Sienna.
Okay.
It's my heart.
Give me your hand.
You feel that?
Every time I see you,
it beats so fast.
I feel like it's gonna burst.
It's a strong heart. You're gonna
live a long, happy life...
- get married, have babies.
- You think so?
Frankie. Every nurse in this joint
is talkin' about you.
Why don't you get one of them?
Go get a bite to eat.
- No, you guys go ahead.
- No, come with us.
Yeah. Come on, you gotta eat.
Yeah, all right.
The guy doesn't know
where he is.
I'm supposed to come pick him up.
He can't tell me the address.
- Will you excuse me for a moment?
- Yeah, of course.
Hey, Frankie, why don't you
do me a favor.
Why don't you take her out
dancin' tonight?
You want me to take
your girl out dancing?
You know, we had some
good times, but I've been tryin'...
to break it to her that I don't
really feel that way about her.
You know, actually, I've been
seein' this other. A knockout.
It's better...
I just sit this one out.
- What do you want me to tell her?
- You know, I don't know.
You tell her I got called away,
or a business trip.
You're a smart guy.
You think of somethin'.
You're my best friend, right?
Of course.
- Frankie?
- Yes?
But I love it when...
No, we're gonna be late, okay?
Go. No, I...
That's nice.
Now you're startin'
to convince me.
What?
Will you marry me?
Marry you?
What are you
talking about?
Lorina Ryan,
will you marry me?
- I love you so much.
- I love you.
I love you.
What's this, corpus delicti.
What is that?
- It means corpse.
- Why can't ya say that?
This is nice. You hit
the big time here, Doc.
Yeah, so... where ya been?
Business.
Business is boomin' in
the big city.
How's your new wife?
You treatin' her right?
- Yeah.
- A doctor. Quite a catch.
What are you doin' here, Dan?
Nicky needs a favor.
All right.
You're treatin' Paul Maury
for that heart thing, right?
Yeah. I'm doin' a double bypass
on him this afternoon.
You tell Nicky not to worry.
I've done a lot of these. Paul's
gonna have a new lease on life.
Nicky wants to cancel that lease.
He doesn't want him to
get up off your table.
Oh no, Dan, I don't want
any part of this.
- You are a part of this.
- I'm Nicky's doctor, and that's it.
Look, this ain't a multiple
choice thing.
There's only one right
answer here.
The guy is Nicola.
He only asks once.
So that's it.
Say hello to Lorina for me.
Hey. I'm so glad it's you, Frank.
You're gonna do right by me,
aren't ya?
He's in trouble.
Doctor?
Frank?
What can we do?
Can we do something?
Get epinephrine.
Paddles!
Okay. Give me two fifty.
Stand clear.
Shoot!
Again. Shoot!
Give me three hundred. Shoot!
Folks, looks like
we're back in business.
Let's go for a ride, Frankie.
Where we goin'?
You'll find out when
we get there.
- I want to know now.
- You screwed up, Frank, okay?
- What the hell is that?
- Unbelievable.
He checked out.
A little transfer.
Frankie. Help me.
He's still alive!
We've gotta get him out.
Hey, hey, no, no, leave him.
Leave him.
We gotta get him to a hospital!
Frankie, I said leave him.
You do this to me?
What the hell is wrong with you?
What? You think you're
better than me?
We both work for
the same guy, pal! Wake up!
We don't get this done, that's us
lyin' in there! All right?
Here.
Here, throw these out the window.
One every few miles.
It's the teeth.
You know, no corpus delicti,
no crime.
Hey, come on, relax.
You do this for a livin'.
You're not squeamish?
Lou. I'm here to see Mrs. D.
Wait here.
Mrs. D? It's Dr. Sienna.
Hi, Rose.
So... I got the tests back.
You have cancer in your ovaries.
We're gonna have to remove them.
Well, I've had all my babies.
I don't need them.
The cancer may have spread.
I'm sorry.
How am I going to tell my Nicky?
I can tell him if you like.
I want you to do this thing.
And I want to...
I'll see you later.
I think I wasted a lot of money
on you.
You got a lot of education,
but you're not very smart.
- Listen, Nicky, we need to talk.
- There's no talking!
You disappointed me.
And it's a good thing that Mick
cleaned up your mess with Maury.
Nicky, he came to see Mrs. D.
All right.
You do what you can do
to save my Rose...
I'll forget about the Maury thing.
You remember this?
Remember the kids wouldn't go
to sleep until we sang that song.
- But I forgot the words.
- You're gonna make me cry.
Frankie.
Hey. Everything went fine, Rose.
- We'll see.
- You got the best. We got Frankie.
I want you to get some rest now,
okay?
It's okay.
Okay. All right, honey?
Whatever you need.
So, we took out the tumor, but...
I'm not gonna lie, Nicky.
The cancer may have spread.
You know the only thing I regret?
Is when Rosie found out about me,
and the life, you know?
And it changed something
in her...
I feel really bad about...
about that.
I mean,
maybe it was my fault.
So the next thing,
we take some more tests...
we see the results...
Oh, my god!
Not bad for a couple kids from
the neighborhood, huh?
Not bad at all.
- We can do this?
- Absolutely.
How?
Will you let me worry about that?
Come on, it's strange, you haven't
been at the hospital that long...
So what? Will you stop?
- What?
- Where you been gettin' money?
I didn't tell ya?
I'm a doctor.
What?
What are you worried about?
Are you taking money
from Nicola Delarusso?
What? No, I'm not takin' money
from Nicola Delarusso.
What, is that what this is about?
Come on, Lorina, it's ridiculous.
You promise?
I promise.
- Mr. DeSante.
- Yeah.
I'm Dr. Sienna.
- Nice to meet ya.
- Nice to meet you.
It says that you suffer from periodic
chest pain, shortness of breath?
Yeah. But what's with these silly
gowns with your asses hangin' out?
Is this to make you guys feel like
you're in control, or what?
No, the truth is,
I'm an ass man.
- Would you take that down, please?
- Yes, I will.
- Whoa. Close call.
- Yeah. A little too damn close.
Take a deep breath, please.
War wound?
- Yeah, sort of
. - Again.
- Military?
- Mob.
They usually have rules
against shootin' cops...
I busted some soldier on a truck
jacking who forgot about the rules...
Thought he could shoot
his way out of trouble.
You know. I guess I forgot
to put down there...
I'm a detective with the
Organized Crime Unit.
Sounds like an interesting
line of work.
Oh yeah. Be happy to show you
some of my work.
You take a good picture.
A respectable doctor like yourself
should get some new friends.
Not people who kill people
for a living.
These are very good pictures.
I think you have a future
in photography.
This top Union official,
Paul Maury...
the word on the street is that he's
fallen out of grace with Nicky D.
You operated on
this guy?
That's right.
Out of all the surgeons in the city,
he comes to you?
He helped me get a scholarship to
medical school through the Union.
My father was a member for years.
I was just returning a favor.
That's a favor and a half.
This guy's disappeared now.
I know that Mr. Maury was being
transferred to another hospital.
The problem is,
he never showed up.
Mr. DeSante, we're not responsible
for what happens to patients...
after they leave
the hospital.
You think being a doctor hides
who you really are?
Your blood pressure's
way too high.
So, what do you do for
the old man, anyway?
You sign a bunch of phony
death certificates...
patch up some soldiers
with lead in their ass?
I'm Mr. Delarusso's family doctor.
I know. That's what I just said.
His wife, Rose,
is my patient.
That's good, Doc.
Look, I can help you get out
of this work.
The FBI, they'll protect you
and your family.
You can start new.
Someplace else.
Just talk to us.
I have other patients to see.
- I'm a friend of Dr. Sienna's.
- Are you really?
And, are you a doctor, too?
- Well, I work on Wall Street.
- Oh, do you really?
You know all those mergers you
hear about, that's me.
I got a little investment thing
I'm workin' on with the doctor.
I gotta drop somethin' off.
I could give you my number...
and maybe you could stop by?
Nobody robs from me!
- He wasn't gonna tell me about them.
- The undertaker would have found.
Frankie, you okay?
- Hey, Doc?
- You all right?
You know, I never liked you.
But Nicky says you're gonna be
a good investment.
Well, maybe someday
you'll prove it.
Hey, whoa, whoa! It's all right!
It's all right! Lou, come on.
Frankie, go wait in the car.
You know,
he's a cocky bastard.
No, no, he's cool.
He's a little freaked out.
- You just blew a guy's brains out.
- Well, is that right?
Well, the heat is on you
if he goes sideways.
Yeah, I know.
You remember that cop, DeSante?
Yeah. The prick's been after
Nicky for years.
Well... I saw him one time at the
hospital. He was talkin' to Frank.
Well, he better not be talkin'
too much.
He likes bein' a big shot too much.
You don't got to worry about him.
All right, get outta here.
What do we... This doctor,
what do we do about him?
He's crossed the line.
What would you do, Ang?
I don't know.
That's why I'm askin' you.
You gotta find out a way that
we can put him in a corner so...
he can't go against us,
you know?
Roie, what are doing? You're
supposed to be in bed?
- The doctor told you. Come on.
- I'm gonna die in that bed.
I want to feel like myself again.
I just...
I was tryin' to take care of you,
like you take care of me.
You take care of me.
You brought me Frankie.
- And the sauce?
- Garbage.
You like what you see?
My husband just bought
this for me.
It's okay, Bob already
took care of us.
This is a tiny piece of garbage.
You give me a big Cadillac.
A nice, big back seat.
Nothin' like layin' a woman down on
that fine Cadillac leather.
Get outta of my car.
Your car?
No, you got that wrong.
See, this is my car.
I own this car.
Just like I own that
beautiful house you got.
Just like I own that doctor husband
of yours. And just like I own you.
Now, don't go playin' dumb with me,
Lorina Ryan.
You know who I am.
Your father did a lot of
work for me.
Those Westies were animals,
and he was the worst.
Frankie never told me what a
beautiful set of tits his wife had.
You know, I'm gonna keep a
picture of you in my mind and...
the next broad that I screw,
I'll be thinkin' of you.
Now, you tell Frankie
what happened here...
he'll probably wanna
bust my head.
Then I'll have to whack him.
But then it'll just be me and you.
Would you like that?
Answer me!
- I won't say a word.
- All right.
You don't make waves. All right?
Just enjoy this fine car you got.
And be happy...
your husband isn't in pieces
in the woods, all right?
Oh, there's Tara.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you, honey.
Where's Phil?
You want something to drink?
Two glasses of champagne,
please?
Right away!
You're nothing but
a no talent guinea.
Did you just call me
a guinea?
No, no, I didn't.
I hope you're not on call tonight,
Doctor.
Of course I'm on call.
They need one surgeon who'll get
the job done.
You're drunk.
You think you're so good.
You just got lucky.
The reason I hired you is 'cause
I lost a $100 thousand dollars...
gambling with your
guinea wap friends.
"Hire Frank Sienna.
Do this thing for us,
your slate is wiped clean."
Did you see that dress she was
wearing? Dr. Sienna's wife.
Oh, poor thing.
She's trying so hard.
Listen, I heard a wild rumor.
Dr. Sienna's a mob guy.
Oh, my Henry thinks so.
He says Lyle was forced
to hire him.
Can you imagine?
Was the chicken rubbery enough
for you tonight?
Well, what do you expect
for 250 dollars a seat, huh?
But remember, this is all
for the kids tonight.
So, moving on to the awards.
The first one goes to
the doctor...
who has gone above and
beyond the call of duty...
who's shown outstanding service
to the community.
Dr. Frank Sienna,
come on up.
- What are you doing?
- What does it look like I'm doing?
What, are you crazy? Stop.
I won't be married to a man
who lies to me.
What are you talking about?
Do you think I'm stupid, Frank?
Do you think doin' charity work
and gettin' awards...
makes up for all the blood money
you take?
All right, look, Lorina, let's
talk about this, okay? Please?
- I want the truth, Frank.
- The truth?
The truth is, the less you know
the better.
- Goodbye, Frank.
- Stop! Are you just gonna walk out?
You have been lying to me
from the very beginning, Frank!
- I'm trying to protect you!
- Protect me?
Yes!
You think I'm safe?
You have no idea.
For god's sakes, your old man was
one of them! You didn't know?
Lorina, stop.
You want to know what's
really pathetic?
I didn't want to know,
'cause I loved you.
What does that mean?
Lorina, what does that mean?
Are you telling me you
don't love me anymore?
Look at me in the eye and
tell me you don't love me anymore!
- Lorina, don't go.
- I can't.
- Don't go!
- Stop it!
Frankie. Let's... leave with me.
We'll get out, you know?
- Get out where?
- I don't know.
- What does that mean?
- I don't know! We just leave!
You think I haven't thought
about that a million times?
Where we gonna go?
What are you gonna do? You don't
think they're gonna follow us?
They're not gonna stop
until we're dead.
I don't know, Frank.
I'm gonna make this up to you,
I promise.
Okay. Okay.
Frank?
Genaro? It's Frankie.
Frankie's here.
Frankie...
I'm here, Pop.
How is your beautiful wife?
Good.
Take good care of her.
Hey, Pop?
You know, I never got a chance
to tell you that I'm proud of you.
All those years, workin' hard
for the family...
and you never complained.
I hope... you stay out.
Promise... you'II...
Get out...
Promise?
I promise, Pop.
Pop?
Pop.
Here we go.
One quarter! You see that?
Oh, man.
You remember these times?
I miss this, you know?
The two of us gettin' together
and havin' a pitcher.
We gotta do this more often.
Yeah, I'm gettin' out.
What?
I'm gettin' out.
Hey, wait, wait.
Hey. Hey, come here.
What are you talkin' about?
You just don't wake up one morning
and say you want out, huh?
You want to get us both whacked?
Danny, I'm gettin' out.
I'm done.
Oh yeah, what are you gonna do?
You pack a little suitcase?
Like get on a bus? What are you
talkin' about, you're out?
As far as they're concerned, I'm
lookin' out for you. It's my ass.
I'm talkin' about I'm done
with Nicky D.
I'm done with Angelo.
I'm done with Lou. I'm done...
Shh-shh, you just keep
your mouth shut.
What are you talkin' about?
I'm goin' to DeSante.
And then what?
The guys aren't gonna stop.
Forget about me and you.
Think about Lorina. And Nonie.
I am thinkin' about Lorina and
Nonie. They're gonna be protected.
By who? FBI?
FBI tell you they're gonna
protect them?
FBI's gonna protect them?
Yeah, they could put you
in a freakin' cave in Utah...
- these guys are gonna find you.
- What do you want me to do?
What do you want me to do?
I told my old man.
Your old man's dead.
I'm sorry.
And promises are meant
to be broken.
- Look, okay...
- You know, Danny...
Come on, come on.
Look, I'm gonna help ya.
We're brothers, right?
But you gotta be smart about this.
It's gonna take a little time.
You gotta trust me, okay?
All right... Back it up.
Where's your husband?
He's on his way home.
He'll be here any minute.
I can wait.
Well, I'm in the middle
of cookin' dinner, so...
Dr. Sienna, please.
It's his wife.
Okay, yes. Tell him to call home,
it's urgent.
Thanks.
I told you what would happen.
Go ahead.
- I tried to call you, but...
- What's the matter?
What?
Hey, Doc.
How's the heart business?
Lorina, would you excuse us
a second?
Get the hell out of my house,
Angelo.
Let's go, Frankie.
I couldn't let him touch me
anymore!
I'm here to see Mrs. D.
If you're here,
that means Angie is dead.
I want out.
You want out?
You're dead.
That's how you're out.
Then I'm takin' you with me.
I trusted you.
I treated you like a son.
- We had a deal.
- What deal? Let my father die?
You turned against me.
You turned against the family.
- I made you a doctor!
- Yes, you made me a doctor, Nicky!
But at what price?
So I can wake up...
and find Angelo with a gun
in my wife's head?
What do you think, you're the first
punk who ever put a gun in my face?
Is that what you think?
Come on!
The difference between me and you
is I'm not afraid to die!
Frankie?
I thought I heard you.
What? You hungry?
Rose, what are you doing?
You should be in bed.
Come on, we have something.
Ravioli. Give him some ravioli.
I can't stay. I've got to go
to the hospital.
I'll walk you out.
Lou?
Oh, Frankie!
It's okay. It's okay.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- All right.
- Frank?
- What?
- Did you kill him?
- Oh god, I should have.
Come on. Okay.
Get back!
It's okay. It's okay.
Al right, let's go. Let's go.
Let's get the bags.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Frankie. They shot me.
I'm bleedin' and
I don't want to die.
- You gave me up to Angelo.
- No, I didn't. I...
I stood up for you and
they came after me!
Come on, man,
I need your help.
Where are you?
The place.
Okay. Hold on, I'll be there.
- Look, keep them safe.
- What you doin'? Where you goin'?
- I gotta take care of somethin'.
- What are you talkin' about?
- You're our star witness!
- What do you think I'm gonna do?
You have my family.
Frank, what do you think we're
gonna do, let you run around loose?
- We gotta take care of you.
- Okay, let go, or the deal's off!
You're gonna run around and
take care of somethin' now?
If you hurt that boy...
I will not forgive you.
Danny?
I knew you'd come and
do the right thing.
You always were the better man.
They sent you.
Ang always said you didn't have
the balls for the street.
Danny?
- Listen to me.
- You killed Ang.
Now they're gonna open
the books for me.
They're never gonna make you.
Can't you see that?
To them, you're just another
Irish hump.
Shut up!
You think this is hard for me?
It's not!
I've been waitin' to do this
all these years!
You know how long I had my nose
pressed up watchin' you?
You got everything.
You got my girl. My life.
Nick said:
"The doctor gets a pass."
A pass?
Don't be stupid.
Don't do it, Danny.
"THE FAMILY DOCTOR" (11)