Give me a hand over here!
All right.
Right!
load her up in the back!
Damn!
Hello, Doris.
Want to do me a favor?
Help me load the next order?
You're no lady, Doris.
Far from it.
Good morning, boys and girls.
Did we all remember to bring
our homework assignments today?
We didn't?
Well, we know what happens...
to little boys and girls
who don't do their homework.
Okay, class is over.
Did you hear me?
Class is over!
Okay.
I'm just gonna have to
make another example.
Surprise, surprise.
I know you're there, Warwick.
You know something? You just
saved me a trip to your office.
I may be desperate for work,
but I'm not desperate enough to--
Everything's set down here!
let her rip!
Goddamn!
Adios, motherfuckers!
Excuse us, please.
Thanks.
Wouldn't mind having his boots
resting under my bed.
One more pair of boots,
you're gonna have to open a boot shop.
Anyway, he's married.
Daisy May, more coffee.
Daisy May,
let's make us a baby doggie style.
They found him in pieces.
The rats--
The little cannibals were all over
him. It was really unbelievable.
What you got in the bag, pal?
Not very friendly,
is he, Stevenson?
I bet his mommy packs his lunch.
Peanut butter and jelly.
Without the crust.
looks like a Boy Scout to me.
Maybe a Girl Scout.
See ya around, Girl Scout.
You ought to see who
they're hiring for the new mill.
She is one cute little chick.
...accidental death
at Bachman Textile...
has opened the restored mill
to a series of investigations...
and probable lawsuits.
Jason Reed had been working
the night shift...
when the mysterious
accidents occurred.
- Good morning, Mr. Warwick.
- Hello.
Oh, God, this is bad.
Extreme safety hazard.
Exterminator's working
around the clock.
He's tired.
- Needs more time.
- There's already been one accident.
This place has to be cleared before
another worker steps in this death trap.
Damn!
July 4th holiday.
I'll organize a cleanup.
I'll hold onto this till then.
I'll be back.
To be honest, I don't think
you'll find a crew that'd work it.
Not down here.
We'll see.
Come shower with me.
You can save water.
This'll work out just fine.
- See you later.
- Bye.
Morning.
Good morning.
Take coffee...
- Mr.--
- Hall. No, thanks. I'll pass.
Me too.
Can't be more than
an instant enema by now.
You here by car or by thumb?
By Greyhound.
I see you got
a real problem staying put.
lots of movement
over the past five years.
Starts down in Florida.
Jumps all the way up the map.
Are you on the run, friend?
I'm here for a fresh start.
College boy.
No, that's not the problem.
With all due respect, what is?
Fair enough.
Putting it plainly, Mr. Hall,
you're a drifter.
And I get no guarantees
with a drifter.
You get no guarantees
with any man.
There's only instinct.
You spent some time
at Munson Textile.
- You ever run the picker?
- I know how.
Then you also know
it's a one-man operation.
This mill depends on that machine.
And what's left of Gates Falls
depends on this mill.
Now, we don't do better
than minimum to start.
Four weeks before the union
comes knocking at your door.
- You still interested?
- Sounds fair to start.
All right, then.
That's it, except for the hours.
Because of the heat, we only
run that sucker through the night.
1 1 :00 to 7:00.
The graveyard shift.
Spread the word, fucker.
Mice.
Damn, that's good shootin'.
Tucker Cleveland,
Martial Extermination.
John Hall.
looking like one of your buddies got
a little too close to the blower.
Shoot, I'd like to know how many
of them Beantown execs...
are wearing one of your
rat-lined overcoats.
No, thanks.
Gave that up with the wife.
Should miss her as much.
- You work late hours.
- I got no choice.
Yellow Pages--
thick with competitors.
Why, I don't mind telling you...
this place is infested.
That might be
the understatement of the year.
The schmuck you work for
don't want to hear that.
Afraid of what
it's gonna cost the mill.
Thinks a little tracking poison
will do the trick.
I've been dealing with these things
for more than 20 years...
and we ain't talking about
no candy-ass field mice.
These sons of bitches piss
on tracking poison.
They piss on it to warn
their little fucker friends.
Take it from me.
There's only one way
to deal with their kind.
On their own terms.
Yeah.
I first met up with them
back in...
Con Thien myself.
Big as puppies,
and they had no fear.
Not of death, nothing.
like the Cong.
And I ain't one of them
burnin' baby flashback fuckups...
you see Bruce Dern playing,
so quit your grinning.
Anyways...
the conditions, being what they were
back then, we had little choice.
We shared the land...
we shared our food
with the fuckers...
and they turn around,
stabbing us in the back...
by going to work for the VC.
That's right.
'Cause the VC...
would reward them with a hot meal.
Now...
do you have any idea
what a VC rat eats?
Try raw American...
hold the mayo, thank you.
The Cong...
had a way of serving up a meal...
real nice and fancy.
They'd stake one of our boys
to the ground...
through his hands,
through his feet.
They'd stake him like Jesus.
And then...
they'd make a cut
just above the abdomen.
Now, this wasn't a fatal cut.
This was merely an entry wound.
Then, they'd get a rat.
A real hungry rat.
One that hadn't been feeding
for about a week.
And they'd put it on the wound...
and they'd stick its nose
down inside.
And if the damn thing
wasn't starving enough...
they'd cover it
with a flaming rice bowl...
and let me tell you...
that gray-black son of a bitch...
would have nowhere else
to go but inside.
And he'd start to tunnel
his way through...
looking to put an end
to that loud beating sound.
like a human artichoke.
So warm, so juicy.
Yeah.
So...
maybe I'm a little prejudiced.
Did anybody call break?
Ain't no laughing
on company hours.
looks like you just
bought yourself a shift...
scrubbing the latrines.
Shit.
I should be downstairs...
humiliating the college boy
by now.
Bravo, Ippeston.
Bravo.
Now we can get you
that audition on Star Search.
Come here, boy.
We've got commitments to our
New York sales office on Wednesday.
Are we on schedule?
- Yes, Mr. Warwick.
- Fetch me your work order, boy.
- Evening.
How are you tonight, darling?
We're on time.
In fact, we're slightly ahead.
No, I'm asking about you,Jane.
How are you?
Managing. Thanks.
Well, you look tired.
like you're losing too much
of your beauty sleep or something.
The night shift will
do that to you.
No special deals.
I'm here, I'm doing a job.
You got a problem with that,
you can talk to the union.
Who said anything about a deal?
I'm talking about a promotion.
A cool office.
A desk.
This cleanup ain't gonna be
pretty, darling.
I got Stevenson down there now
stringing the lights.
He's pissing and moaning
about the heat.
- And it's gonna get hotter.
- I can handle it.
It's double pay.
So back off, man.
Why don't you wisen up,
for Christ sakes?
like Nardello?
I'm gonna see you
down in the basement.
There ain't no way they're gonna
get this place settled in a week.
Goddamn rats!
This is bullshit.
A whole bunch of bullshit.
Brogan?
Hey, you porker.
Is that you?
Shit.
Very funny!
I'm laughing my ass off!
Hey, how about picking up a--
Oh, damn.
Brogan?
- What about Stevenson?
- Well, all I know is...
Stevenson left in the middle
of a job and didn't pick up his pay.
Well, looky who's here.
- Still alive.
- Now.
- How are you doing?
- All right.
- Want some coffee?
- Please. Coffee and toast.
We got you a little something
to nibble on.
Enjoy.
Special order for the commander
of the rat patrol.
Bastards.
Do you need a lift?
Hi, sweetheart.
You don't want to be doing that
in broad daylight.
Then let's do it in the dark.
Mr. Warwick?
Who wants to know?
I'm Charlie Carmichael. I hear
you're looking for a few good men.
Yeah.
A few. Come this way.
I'll talk to you later
about that thing.
Nice meeting you, ma'am.
Those guys are assholes, man.
Every town has 'em.
That's a depressing thought.
- What town are you from?
- Wheeling.
West Virginia?
That's nice.
How about you? Have you
lived here your whole life?
No way.
I'm from Castle Rock.
Castle Rock. That sounds
very Norman Rockwell.
No. It's just Castle Rock.
So, I'll see you around.
You're on the basement
cleanup crew, no doubt.
- Not that I know of.
- Oh, you will be.
If I know Warwick, and I know
Warwick, you're a prime candidate.
Bet your wife ain't too thrilled.
losing you through
the night and all.
We gotta do what we gotta do,
right?
- My wife's dead.
- Oh. I'm sorry.
Thank you for the ride.
Take care.
Keep the lights as high up
to the ceiling as possible.
Get a water vac in here tomorrow,
mop this shit up.
Welcome aboard.
Bit jumpy, aren't you, kid?
Not to worry.
The rats don't bite.
- Mr. Warwick?
- Yeah?
What did happen to the fella
that started this job?
What happened?
He didn't work out.
He needs this typed right away.
- What is it?
- Cleanup crew.
looks like you made the list,
Nardello.
Basement cleanup?
Clean up this, Warwick!
What the fuck is she doing?
Where's Warwick?
He's right there.
He's gonna be wicked pissed.
How can you do this to me?
like it rough,
don't you, Nardello? Huh?
You can't put me down there.
You can't put anybody down there.
I know things.
What are you talking about?
Now, you better watch
what you're saying.
I don't think so.
I think from now on,
you better watch what you're saying.
Come on.
I'll take you home.
All right.
Show's over.
Everybody go back to doing
what you were doing.
Sorry.
I thought you were a rat.
You're not the first.
Mr. Hall...
I wanted to drop in
and thank you.
Sorry about that situation
with Nardello.
Tempers flared.
All it was, a big misunderstanding.
You know how it is.
Anyway,
as a show of gratitude...
I want to offer you the chance
to earn some extra cash.
Next week's
the July 4th holiday.
The mill's shut down.
That means vacation week
for most of our people...
thems with union.
layoff week for the rest.
But there is work available
for a select few.
We got that there cleanup thing
going on down in the basement.
Regular graveyard-shift hours,
and I'm hand-picking the crew.
Now...
to tell you the truth...
I've watched you work...
and I like your style.
Gonna be a mess,
no doubt about it.
That bastard ain't been touched
since Christ was a kid.
But it's for double pay.
Now, you tell me
if an educated guy like you...
can't use double pay.
Thank you, Mr. Warwick.
You're so welcome, Mr. Hall.
Yeah, it's pretty bad.
Hey, Commander.
Hey, rat man.
You must feel awful special.
You're gonna be down in the shit pit
with the rest of us.
Yeah.
I bet he likes your style.
Wait a minute.
He said he liked my style.
- What's going on?
- Guess who finally made cleanup crew?
Congratulations.
Want to get out of here?
Yeah.
Thanks.
- You were hungry.
- Yeah, for decent food.
It's been a while.
I worked a spell
as a short-order cook.
In Miami.
Mostly burgers.
So I want to hear
the rest of your story.
You got married...
left Castle Rock
against your father's advice.
Yeah.
Why are dads always right?
I don't know.
Anyway...
it wasn't too long
after my divorce...
Warwick came sniffing around.
He said he wanted to help.
He felt bad.
So he offered me a promotion
to office manager...
to ease my emotional
as well as financial burdens.
All I'd have to do in return
is perform a couple days a week...
on the couch in his office.
He even had 'em picked out.
Monday and Wednesday.
That son of a bitch.
- Shoulda brought him up on charges.
- I tried...
and was advised by personnel
to see a therapist.
They couldn't get rid of me.
I was saved by the union and the
fact that Warwick would come out...
looking like the basic
shitheel that he is.
So I'm still here.
On borrowed time, I guess.
Bet you hate him, too,
Mrs. Warwick.
This'll teach you to fire me,
you son of a bitch.
Shit.
- The best and the brightest.
- Pull!
Carmichael, you want to try it?
Go on.
Carmichael.
Ippeston.
leave the ghetto blaster
back in the ghetto.
Yes, sir.
Don't want anybody being cute
with one of these.
You end up spraying one of
your buddies back onto a slab.
Now...
the work area's listed over there,
just like we talked about.
Jobs split evenly
night by night.
Tried to keep it interesting.
Any questions?
Basically, we need to have
this basement in a workable state...
by next Thursday.
We only got the chain hoist
for one night.
Execute these orders, you'll get
through it without a snag.
And then what happens? Do we all,
like, get a gold watch or something?
Sure beats nailing 'em
with soda pop.
What are you doing?
Warwick says to list everything.
Fifty-year-old files are crap.
list them as 50-year-old crap.
It's not salvageable.
Hey, check this out.
Come on.
Take a break.
The longer it takes, the longer
we'll be down here doing it.
This thing's in great shape.
Brogan!
Rats.
No problem.
Where are you going, asshole?
You goddamn ignoramus,
you almost killed me!
What the hell is your problem,
Brogan?
I ain't got a problem.
You got a problem?
look, guys, this is crazy.
We were hired as a cleanup crew,
not as exterminators.
I mean, I need this money
as bad as the next guy.
But we are not damn exterminators!
What's your problem, boy?
- We were hired to clean the basement.
- ""We?''
You speaking for everybody?
Or just yourself?
Just me, Mr. Warwick.
""Just me, Mr. Warwick.''
Yeah.
You best be punching out
your time card...
permanently.
Is that clear, boy?
Somebody call break?
Control that sack of fleas,
Cleveland. Please.
Moxy, come on over here.
Moxy here is a real special breed.
Rat terrier.
He didn't waste his puppy years
down at the beach...
playing Frisbee
with Frankie and Annette.
He was too busy training...
tracking rats through walls,
concrete.
looks to me
like he don't always win.
Hey, Moxy, cut that out.
Cleveland...
we got ourselves
a little problem, you and me.
Our sister mills along the river
don't take too kindly...
having their backyards polluted
by rat stew.
But our own Mr. Bachman
has graciously agreed...
to keep your name out of
any impending lawsuit.
You are legally responsible...
when it comes right down to it.
Ain't you a kick in the nuts?
First off...
I was called personally
by Bachman...
and told to pump
directly into the river...
because, just between you,
me and Moxy...
he was too cheap to spring
for the dumping charges hisself.
Hope you got that in writing.
Fuck you.
No, Cleveland, fuck you.
Stunts like that can easily cost
an exterminator his license.
But again...
no one's naming names.
We're only asking you to provide
one additional service.
We got an idea of where
them things is nesting.
Shouldn't take you
more than a night.
What is it you got me doing?
When's the last time
you've been to a graveyard?
Come on, Moxy.
Burn their little home
so we can get back to ours.
Go on, Moxy!
Get 'em!
Eat 'em for breakfast!
Come on, Moxy.
There just ain't no job
worth this.
Moxy?
Ain't no dog worth it either.
Just a few more hours.
I know.
Break's over.
Back to work.
The week's almost over.
I thought it would never end.
Place still looks like shit.
What are they looking to put here?
- A nightclub.
- Really?
You must have been at the top
of your class, Brogan.
Truth is, they're expanding
for office space.
Who would have an office down here?
Hey, look at this.
What you got, kids?
Trap door.
Well, ain't that interestin'.
It certainly is.
That's where your rats
are coming from.
They're breeding underground.
Now you know it all,
don't you, Hall?
Hey, boys.
Come on over here.
Can't get it.
Brogan, give me a hand.
Wow!
I wonder what's down there.
Brogan, fetch your lamp.
- You're not thinking of going in?
- Me?
No. No, sir.
Johnny is on hoses tonight.
I trust his judgment,
him bein' a college boy and all.
On one condition-- need an extra
body to help me carry the line.
Name your body.
You, Mr. Foreman.
The management should be represented
in this little venture...
don't you think?
In case there is a treasure, I don't
want to be accused of stealing it.
You first.
Be right after you.
I'm going.
Danson. Carmichael.
Come on. Gear up.
Brogan, you too.
At Bachman, we're just
one big happy family.
Yeah. The Manson family.
You all right?
We need to find someplace
to sit you down.
There's a table in the corner.
Come on. Come on.
Brogan, watch your step.
What the hell we got here?
A bygone power source--
water power.
looks like it hasn't
worked in years.
Smells like stale piss down here.
I say we turn around right now.
So much for your
breedin' ground, Hall.
- Can you feel it? Does it hurt?
- Yeah.
Shit, Brogan.
You're a regular bug light.
Shit!
I see him!
Grab hold of the wood!
I'm comin' down.
- There's something down here!
- Hold on, Brogan!
Hold on!
- Oh,Jesus!
- There he is!
Please help me! Danson!
Come on.
He's dead!
Brogan's dead!
Shut up, Carmichael!
Give me that.
We can use these for weapons.
Something our friend Hall
hasn't got.
And I'll deal with her--
her and Hall.
Fuck Hall, damn it. Forget about
Hall and start thinking about...
whatever the hell is down here.
He found the openin'.
He brought us down here.
We wouldn't be here
if it weren't for him.
So don't go telling me
my business.
You're going out
of your mind, Warwick.
You just stood there
and watched Brogan die.
You did.
All right, move.
It's a dead end.
There must be some other way
out of here.
Wait. listen.
- Come on!
- Wait a second!
John, this has gotta be
a way out.
Here. Grab ahold of this.
Which way do we go?
- Mr. Warwick.
- What you got there?
Water. Pretty loud.
You hear it?
Sounds like the river.
I knew it.
I knew this was the way out.
It's your moment, Carmichael.
You go first.
Go on.
Be right in back of you.
There's a hole here.
I think we can break through.
It's wet.
Something's got my arm!
Help me!
Carmichael, what is it?
Something's got my arm!
Danson, move! Move!
Somebody help me!
Move!
Please, somebody help me!
- Please!
- It's blocked!
- Wait. Wait!
Hey, the river!
Help me! Help me!
Help!
All right now.
We're gonna take this
nice and slow.
No more! No more! No more!
No, I'm not going!
No, I'm not going anymore! No more!
You wanna die?
I'm not going anywhere!
Ain't that bad.
It's ice cold.
I'm very close.
We'll never get through that way.
At least not with that thing.
Help me!
We're gonna make it.
I know.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Must be where it lives.
Come on. let's go.
Mr. Foreman.
Come on.
let's lift him up.
- It's really bad.
- We should let the bastard bleed.
Here, hold that.
Hold it for a second.
Yeah, yeah.
We're goin'...
to hell...
together!
There's only one way
to deal with these fuckers.
The show's over.