I have a lot to think through
Your mother led such a good life
Her passing should be celebrated
not mourned
Ma did so much
But, what have I achieved?
You're taking this photo with you
This one's my favorite
Nashaad, you have many more
Neither you'll be here nor the photo,
how will I survive?
Leela, please don't go
Don't say like that Nashaad, I'm
not going forever
Will you write?
Everyday.. and you?
I'll write one song for you. Everyday.
It seems from your letters that..
America is suiting you
But your suitors here are wilting.
Hamid can't wait for you to come back.
Yesterday Kali Prasad had come...
And he moped around for
an hour today
Your admirers are
suffering here Leela.
With your favorite poet
being the foremost
I live in the fragrant Spring
....inebriated by your absence
wrapped up in your thoughts
Dearest, it's been three weeks
since I've seen you
But it feels like three years
You were right Nashaad.
I've already found a 'fan' here
You won't believe what happened today...
In search of my sweetheart
I hold my breath
Every living moment
ls a moment of death for me
I live wrapped up in your thoughts
Nashaad, I wish you were here
I got another invitation
to perform in America
How do I gently refuse?
I've heard they ask poet to
sing films songs! Oh God!
You promised to write everyday
I haven't heard from you in a week
Is everything alright?
Is there something you want to tell me?
Is Nashaad there?
Who's calling?
Get Nashaad on the line
Just a moment
Nashaad who was that woman
Leela, sweetheart
I want to know who that woman was
Leela, my sweet heart
I cannot believe that you could
...bring another woman to our bed!
Leela, listen to me
I don't want to listen to anything
Leela, I don't know how
I've survived the last few months
Without seeing your face...
smelling your hair
Without breathing the same air
that you breathe
There is so much I want to tell you
I've written a whole book of poems for you
Sitting on our balcony
Inspired by the vast ocean
I wrote a song for you everyday
But now, I only want to look at you
How have you been Leela?
You haven't even mentioned
your "boyfriend"!
You wrote so much about him
I feel like I know him.
You know why I came, don't you?
I don't know what happened to you
that night
I was scared, Leela
I can never cause you any pain
Sweetheart
Nashaadsahab, please sing for us
Please don't insist, Naheed
You can't do this to your fans
Won't you heed this small request?
Singing is not my profession
It is my passion
I'm honored that you like what I write
But, please don't ask me to sing here
I don't think I've had the pleasure
You flatter me Mrs. Chatterjee
Come...Thanks
Joya is giving me an invaluable lesson
in expatriate morality
All my music, my poetry, my art
ls for Leela
Then please sing for us
You really want me to sing?
Alright I will
Jai, Nashaad has finally agreed to sing
We can do it here
What would you need?
A tanpura, a tabla..and...
Kris plays the guitar extremely well
Krishna, will you play with me?
How long will you make me wait?
Come to bed
I still have work to do
Can't it wait?
I'll join you soon
So said the moon to the night...
But when the moon was ready
Night had already turned to day
The moon had lost it's luster...
That's enough, Nashaad
Leela, I've noticed a change in you
Because I don't agree with
everything you say?
No, you are an independent woman..
Independent?
All these years you've twisted me
around your fingers
But the day you brought
a whore to our bed
Leela, please.. that woman was Simran
And you were too angry to notice
Simran? Your niece?
Yes. What hurt the most was that
...you'd believe I could do such a thing
You are my life
I need some time..
By myself..
Away from you
What are you saying?
You are the light of my whole being
And you want to leave me in the dark?
I love you and I know you love me more
This is not about you...
It's about me
I promise I'll never stray again
But please don't abandon me
Whole night I kept awake & sang
Dewdrops in the eyes
Whole night I kept awake and sang
Love like this cannot be extinguished
Like a torrent that cannot be dammed
Eyes filled to the brim
Whole night I kept awake & sang
Ties of the soul are eternal
Scars on the heart are indelible
The night was split
tossing and turning
Whole night I kept
awake and sang
Dewdrops in the eyes
Whole night I kept awake and sang
I'm a "Pathan" by birth but
I grew up in Delhi
Well done my boy - Thank you
SubRip by Szabby (szabby@freemail.hu)