Hi.
How are you doing?
Fine.
I'm sorry I didn't
show up yesterday.
It's okay.
I missed you.
But what for
What for so much sky
What for so much sea
What for
What good is the wave that breaks
In the morning breeze
What good is the morning
Useless landscape
Forget it, Pedro Paulo.
It's over.
- Things don't end this suddenly.
- Yes, they do.
No, they don't.
Look, I don't know if things
end this way or not...
but what we had together is over.
We'll go on Saturday, then.
For one night.
You can choose a romantic inn.
Pedro Paulo, my darling.
Former spouses don't travel
together to romantic inns.
Technically speaking,
we're not former spouses yet.
I wouldn't travel with you...
if my life depended on it.
MasterJockstrap
won't let you go?
If you break
into my apartment again...
- Our apartment.
- My apartment.
And you're forbidden
to go in when I'm not there.
Does theJapanese guy
look sexy in his jockstrap?
He's notJapanese.
He's Chinese.
These Orientals are perverted.
Has he asked you
to perform any strange acts yet?
There are no "strange acts"
for people with open minds.
Don't let him tie you up in bed.
These guys will steal your furniture.
What do you mean "these guys"?
Have you gone mad?
Japanese always travel in groups.
Give me back the key.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
- I was swimming.
- No problem.
Good morning, Miss Simpson.
- How are you doing this morning?
- Fantastic.
In English, please, Nadine.
You're not going
to ask me about Gary?
Yes. Your Internet romance.
How's it going?
- Yesterday he said he loves me.
- What?
Really?
He signed off,
" Love, Gary."
Nadine, you mustn't read
too much into that.
Americans use the word
"love" very casually.
We say "I love you"
like you say "Good-bye."
" Hi. You must be Gary.
I'm Nadine.
I came all the way
from Brazil to see you only."
Just to see you.
- Okay. Just to see you.
- Right.
"I know that I don't
know you very much."
- Very well.
- Thank you.
No. I don't know you very well.
- " But you don't know me either."
- Ei-ther.
" But I am sure,
deep inside my heart...
that you are
the person of my life."
You know, you don't say
"person of my life."
You'd say "man of my life."
I think "soul mate"
is more romantic.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, sir.
Vermont Associates.
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
Your new law intern.
It must be some mistake.
I don't have an intern, old or new.
Is this Mr. Pedro Paulo's office?
That's me, but at the moment
I need no intern.
New Resolution #5, 7 83/99
requires that...
five percent of the payroll
of law firms be made up of interns.
Yes.
So you're my five percent.
I ranked third among
the 23 candidates for this job.
Your first assignment:
Take these papers
to Mr. Juan Alvarado, my father...
and return with them signed.
Copacabana,
534 Duvivier, suite 902.
I'm not a messenger.
I'm a law intern.
For your information,
my father is a client.
I'm defending him
in a lawsuit in divorce court.
Aren't you going
to write down the address?
534 Duvivier, suite 902.
"Alvarado Custom Tailors
Refined Clothing Since 1 938"
Senor Juan, please.
- Who would like?
- Who would like what?
Senor Juan.
I would like Senor Juan.
Who would like
to speak to Senor Juan?
I have some papers
for him to sign.
He's with a client.
You can leave them with me.
Sorry, but I have instructions to bring
these papers back with me, signed.
You can wait, then.
- I don't need the Internet.
- You think you don't need it.
- I don't need one of those, either.
- Soon you'll say you don't need man.
Well, for the last two years.
Two years?
No man?
- Or the Internet.
- The best place to find a man.
What ever happened
to dinner and a movie?
A guy who spends his nights in front
of a computer has to be a good date.
He's not married, and he doesn't
sleep with a lot of girls.
Maybe there's a reason
he's not married.
he doesn't sleep with a lot of girls.
Maybe...
he's not even a man.
How do you say...?
- Don't knock it till you've tried it.
- Yeah, that's it.
Tonight come by my house
and we'll go into a chat room together.
- I don't think so.
- Tonight. Promise.
- We'll see.
- Okay.
I'm sorry.
I thought it was a robbery.
Nadine, I'm sure
you recognize Acacio...
and this is Gordo, his manager.
Gordo is more than my agent.
He's my buddy.
In English, please.
- Sorry.
- Hi. How's it going?
Acacio's going to play
in England.
I know. I saw it on TV.
Speculation.
Nothing's signed yet.
- Twelve million is cheap.
- You're crazy!
Acacio was the top goal scorer
in the last two Rio championships.
If I were him,
I'd only sign for 1 5.
Acacio was the top goal scorer
in the last two Rio championships.
She's right.
Twelve million is too little.
Acacio is a great player.
Thanks, but I don't need
anyone to defend me.
You watch and see
if he's not the best.
Senor Juan.
That's me.
Can we talk for a moment?
Of course, Mr. Vermont.
Have you finished
the American contract?
Not yet.
It's almost ready.
You know, Americans
are sticklers for details.
I come from three generations
of tailors.
- Details are my specialty.
- I know.
It's just that you...
This piece of junk
is really badly designed. Sorry.
You seem tired lately.
As a lover of justice,
you should understand...
that I'm going through
a difficult moment.
- Recent separation...
- Four months is not so recent.
Right, it's not...
but then there's my father's case
against his latest wife.
The judge is going
to rule this week.
Juan. How is he?
He's all right...
but I want him to stay away
from all the dirt in the case.
Welcome to England, Acacio.
Are you going to miss Brazil?
Yes, I am.
And what do you think
you're going to miss most?
Especially you.
What have you got to say
to your new fans in Manchester?
Hello, Manchester people.
I love you.
Sorry to interrupt, but this
is the fourth class that I've been at.
Your grammar is perfect,
but I disagree with the subject.
Really?
Gordo wants
to change the program.
Wants.
Adapt the curriculum
to Acacio's basic needs in England.
And these basic needs are?
Trash talk.
Yeah. The bad is good, teacher.
The English play
an Anglo-Saxon-style soccer.
He won't last five minutes
on the field...
unless he can tell his opponent
what to do with the ball.
And what, exactly, do you want to tell
your opponent to do with the ball?
To put in their ass.
Inside of their ass.
At least up his mother's ass.
"Shit" is merda
in English, right?
Right.
Go to shit.
- No, that doesn't really work.
- No?
Don't you have
anything with "ass"?
You can "kiss it."
Kiss it my ass.
Better. What does it mean?
Oh, shit.
I don't know. Acacio asking
an English player to kiss his behind?
Trust me. No one's
going to think it's an endearment.
How would you say
casa do caralho in English?
I know.
I look in the dictionary.
It's "home of the dick."
Right?
You need something
with "fuck" in the middle.
How do they say it?
" Motherfucking."
No, "motherfucker."
In American films
it's "modafucka"!
Who's the teacher here?
Him or me?
Sorry.
Fat, wait for me in the car.
The good old ear test.
How are you doing, son?
My fingers, my eyes
can deceive me...
but never my ears.
The fabrics speak to me.
I can't hear a thing.
I know. That's why I didn't insist
that you follow in my footsteps.
The fabrics tell you what type
of clothes they want to be.
You'll never forgive me for
not being able to listen to the fabrics.
Who am I to forgive anyone?
I don't defend universal truths.
I defend my own truths...
but look where it's gotten me.
It's made you
an extremely elegant old man.
What good is elegance...
in these days
of jeans and T-shirt?
Women don't look
for elegance anymore.
They only look for money.
Four wives... my mother in the '50s,
yours in the '60s...
another one in the '7 0s...
and he ended up in trouble
with this one in the '90s.
If Veronica ends up
with this shop...
This place is my life.
- We're going to win, right?
- Yes.
What do you want?
No rush.
It's just that...
High quality.
It would make a nice suit
if it weren't for the color.
But Dad, my idea was to make
a Campari-colored suit.
If the cloth cries out to be a suit,
it can make a nice suit...
even if it was born Campari.
Excuse me.
May I help you?
In English, please.
The lady that went in the elevator...
Is that a student?
No.
I think that I know her family...
No, no. She's a teacher.
Hi, sweetheart!
Ready for cyberspace?
I just got in
a very exclusive chat room.
A friend has just arrived.
She's an Internet virgin.
You do this every night?
No.
On Thursdays
I eat at my mother's...
then I come home
and take a Valium.
Wouldn't you rather
meet someone live?
In a real place?
Like at the beach?
And compete with those teenagers
who live at the gym?
No. Thank you.
By any chance...
do you meet live people
in real places?
No...
but I don't want
to meet anyone.
Everyone wants to meet someone.
I already met the person
I was supposed to meet...
and I married him.
Are you divorced?
No. Widowed.
I'm sorry.
No, Nadine.
It's not like I'm some
traumatized madwoman.
Okay, but I am.
Must be Gary.
" Love is a virus...
that infiltrates itself...
in the system of two lovers.
Yours, Gary"
He didn't sign off"love,"
but there are two "loves" before.
It's good, no?
Remember me?
Of course.
My public defender.
- Beautiful, isn't it?
- What?
Far out.
Can I try it?
I need to tell you
that I love you
I could win or lose you
But I need to tell you
that I love you
Beautiful.
You have mine.
I have yours.
Miami I can get you
for $7 50.
It has to be New York.
Can I just buy a one-way ticket?
There's a flight with stopover
in Paraguay for $650.
$650... It's still a little high.
No, thanks.
You can't get a hotel in New York
for less than $7 0 a day.
I'm staying with my boyfriend.
- He has a loft in Soho.
- Can't he lend you some money?
No, he doesn't know me yet.
Your boyfriend doesn't know you?
No. What I mean is,
not in person.
I see. He's just heard about you.
We have an Internet romance.
The Internet. Really?
It'll be six months in April.
You're my second client
who's found someone on the Internet.
There was a girl from Goias State,
not bad-looking...
rather provincial, who married
a French computer professor.
Gary is a visual artist.
An artist makes
a lot of money in the US.
Americans respect artists.
Yesterday he told me
that he loved me.
I get goose bumps
talking about these things.
6'2", waist-length hair.
Any tattoos?
He only mentioned one:
a huge tribal symbol on his back.
You're going to meet this Gary.
I'm going to give you a discount
I wouldn't give my own mother.
Fifteen percent.
Thank you.
" Marjorie and Jo-Jo
live and work in New York City.
They have been married
for one year.
- They have a big dog called Rex."
- Settle, people.
"They live in a very big apartment
on Fifth Avenue."
Fifth.
Shut up!
Shut up, guys.
She said, "Shut up!"
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Welcome.
Thank you.
- Son of a "beetch. "
- Son of a bitch!
- Good!
- What's the difference?
Bitch is a female dog.
Beach is the sand by the ocean.
- English, please.
- Asshole.
- Fuck you, slut!
- Up yours, dickhead!
- Eat my shorts.
- Blow me!
- Motherfucker!
- Cocksucker!
Shit, that's very sexy.
For that...
the referee
will give you a red card.
It's a big soccer game tonight.
The national team is playing.
It's on the TV.
- Is Acacio playing?
- I'm sure.
Well, let's get started, then.
Why don't you open
to page 3 5 and read?
Do you prefer
on the top or below?
I beg your pardon?
The reading.
I should read on the top?
You mean,
should you stand up?
I'm sorry. Yes.
- Stand up. Do you prefer?
- No, you're fine.
" Marjorie and Jo-Jo
love romantic evenings...
and romance in New York City
always starts on Broadway."
" Marjorie and Jo-Jo
love romantic evenings."
Sorry.
"They enjoy fine restaurants."
I've been searching for a fabric
the color of this bay...
for some time now.
I'm serious. I love this color...
dirty green.
You're putting me on.
Wow!
Your eyes are the color
of this bay!
Man, you're weird.
They are! Look at me.
Look at me.
Let me check.
Incredible.
Exactly the same color.
You're the first person
that says they're green.
But they are...
dirty green.
I think so too, but everyone else
thinks they're brown.
No.
That guy who works
with your father...
- Which one?
- The one from Niteroi.
Roberto.
He's not gay, is he?
No.
Not as far as I know.
Why?
I don't know.
He's just weird.
He's my brother.
Don't worry.
He's just a half brother.
Then I just
half embarrassed myself.
Mr. Pedro Paulo's office.
It's Sharon.
Sharon, the intern.
Hello, who is this?
Since when do you have
an intern?
Jealous?
Me? Jealous?
Are you mad?
I'll be right with you.
Take a seat.
I just called to check something.
I'm filling out a questionnaire
in a magazine.
Did you ever make number two
in front of me?
What?
Number two.
You know, in the bathroom.
Poop?
No, of course not.
I knew it.
Thanks for clearing that up.
Good-bye.
Seven years of marriage...
and we never made number two
in front of one another.
Really?
Seven years and not once.
Cool.
And how about you and Gary?
What? Poop?
No, silly, your virtual romance.
Enough virtual.
No more talk.
Cock.
How long does it take
to get a visa?
" New York City is the financial
capital of the world."
World. Roll your "r."
" Downtown, on Wall Street...
is the World Trade Center...
and the Staten Island ferry."
Staten.
- Miss Simpson?
- Yes?
- Who's it from?
- I just make the deliveries.
Thank you.
"On Wall Street
is the Stock Exchange."
Let's start from the beginning.
" New York City is the financial
capital of the world."
Good.
" Downtown, on Wall Street,
is the World Trade Center...
and the Staten Island ferry."
So, what's the growth rate?
About five percent per year.
They say that
after a certain age...
your belly becomes
your wealth index.
That explains
why I'm always broke.
Everything went well downstairs.
And the girl?
Is she pretty?
Very pretty.
- Good night.
- Bye, Mrs. Simpson.
- Very good.
- Thank you.
Here we are.
Let's get in.
- Are you coming?
- No, it's full.
- We'll squeeze in.
- You count for two.
- Hi.
- Beautiful blouse.
- Thank you. It was a present.
Your boyfriend has good taste.
No, I don't have a boyfriend.
I'm guessing
it was from a pupil.
- What?
- Pupil. Aluno.
Someone from our class?
No, he's a private student.
Dr. Vermont.
What are you doing here?
Learning English again?
I would like to introduce you
to my girlfriend, Mary Ann.
She teaches English here.
It's a pleasure.
Ricardo was a pilot.
I was a stewardess.
That's how you met?
Flying together?
No. We worked
for different airlines.
I met him at a party.
A month later
we were married.
Love at first sight.
It happens.
It just happened to me.
How did he die?
Plane crash?
No. He drowned.
The current was very strong that day.
It's a funny thing.
I used to be afraid of the ocean.
I never learned to swim.
Now I swim every day
and I'm afraid to fly.
Crazy, huh?
- Waiter, another caipirinha, please.
- Right away.
I'm scared to drive.
You're kidding.
No. Never learned.
Never wanted to.
My wife said that's because
I am without ambition.
That I have no direction
in my life.
If it's any consolation...
I think ambition
is highly overrated.
Are you all right?
Just can't drink like I used to.
I like the sand.
It makes me feel grounded.
- I have a confession.
- What?
I have to make you
a confession.
- What?
- The blouse.
I sent it to you.
You?
It's the first women's clothes
I made in my life.
I'm not sure I finished it right.
Wait, wait.
You made the blouse?
My father has a tailor shop.
I didn't pick up the scissors
for 20 years.
You made this blouse for me?
Really?
I'm an attorney.
Attorneys don't lie.
Not outside the courtroom.
You're okay?
Great.
Is Mary Ann in?
Yes.
I'm her student and I dropped by
to clear up a question.
- A question?
- Yes. An English question.
You know, those questions
that keep you up all night?
No.
Well, I woke up with this question
pounding in my head...
and decided to drop by.
She's inside looking
for the grammar book.
Did you found
the grammar book?
Are you an old student of hers?
No. I just started this week.
Cute, isn't she?
Who, her?
I didn't really notice.
She has a marvelous little ass.
A beautiful ass.
Don't tell anyone...
but some really crazy shit
has gone down between us.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Always at the end of class.
I see.
What type of
"really crazy shit"?
The first time,
I was about to leave.
She came up from behind me...
and took me to school
with her tongue.
The second time, I told her
about this knee injury.
That night,
against Argentina...
Three to one.
You scored a hat trick.
Miraculous tongue.
Better than Ben-Gay.
Did you found
the grammar book?
Teacher, let's go.
Fuck.
- Fuck your mother.
- Fuck your mother's mother.
Kiss my dick!
Absolutely not.
I told Gordo an apartment
with an ocean view.
Yes.
Is there at least
a lake or a lagoon?
All right, then something
with a river view.
I need to speak to you.
About last night...
Did something happen
between him and you?
Okay.
How am I supposed to know
London's not on the ocean?
- How do they say that?
- I'll explain tomorrow.
No, no, tomorrow
I talk to English people.
The next day, then.
Speaking of meetings,
I just remembered.
May I use your telephone?
My client has the final say,
or the deal is off.
Okay. I'll see you in court, then.
Good-bye.
Lawyer?
- Do you do contracts?
- It's my specialty.
- See you.
- Who's the suit?
Another student of hers.
Good people.
He's gonna take a look
at the contract.
Lawyers, lawyers.
- Hi, Pecanha!
- Hi, miss!
Hey, where do you think
you're going?
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome aboard Mary Ann Airlines.
Destination: Heartbreak City.
Fasten your seat belts, folks.
It's going to be
a long and lonely ride.
Pilot's dead,
crew's out to lunch...
but, hey,
have a nice flight.
Son of a bitch.
You left me.
Why can't I leave you?
Calm down. Concentrate.
Use the Silva Method.
- The what?
- The Silva Method of Mind Control.
Silva's Mind Control.
You place your three fingers like this
and then concentrate.
Is that by that Chinese guy?
The Silva Method.
Haven't you ever heard of it?
- No.
- Everyone knows the Silva Method.
Everyone but me.
The little blue book,
The Silva Method.
It was the rage
back in the '80s.
I've never heard about
the fucking method, all right?
I'm sorry, Tania.
It's just that...
I heard they give freelancers
a hard time.
Relax. You don't look poor.
Just stay cool.
I'm gonna say...
that I'm a very
sought-after professional.
And that you would never work
as a waitress in a foreign country.
Only use that
if he gives you a hard time.
What if they ask
how many dollars I have?
Lie. Tell them $3,000.
What if they want
to see the $3,000?
Me?
Hi. How are you?
What is the purpose
of your trip?
Do I need a purpose?
I didn't know
that I needed a purpose.
- Purpose?
- Where are you staying?
In Gary's loft.
Who is Gary?
- My boyfriend.
- Is Gary an American citizen?
Yes. I believe he is.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
What is Gary's address?
W-W-W dot...
Excuse me, honey.
I'm her travel adviser.
Is Sylvia,
the Consul's secretary, in?
We belong to the same gym.
May I have a word with her?
You eat too fast.
It's bad for your health.
Hello?
You won't believe this.
I just got an E-mail from Gary!
- He's coming to Rio!
- When?
Tomorrow! He wants my phone number
so he can call me when he arrives.
Did he say what time?
Nothing. No arrival time,
no flight number.
It says he's coming
for 'professional reasons. "
But he signed it, "Love, Gary. "
Well, if it says " Love, Gary," then...
Can I call you right back?
Tania, are you okay?
Do you want to spend
this weekend with me?
I do. But tomorrow I have
to pick up a gringo at the airport.
You don't want to travel
with me anymore.
That's not it. It's just...
And theJapanese guy?
What? Soup. What soup?
Wait a minute.
"3:00 p.m. at the offices of'...
I'll call you later. The judge is going
to render a decision in Juan's case.
- Should I notify your father?
- No. I'll talk to him later.
- Good afternoon.
Is Juan with a client?
Yes.
Sharon?
Did the judge rule
in favor of Veronica?
I told him I wasn't an expert
in these types of cases.
Okay, I'll see you next week.
"Never give all the heart...
for love will hardly seem
worth thinking of...
to passionate women,
if it seem certain...
and they never dream
that it fades out from kiss to kiss.
For everything that's lovely
is but a brief, dreamy, kind delight.
O never give the heart outright...
for they, for all
smooth lips can say...
have given their hearts
up to the play.
And who could play it well enough
if deaf and dumb and blind with love?
He who made this
knows all the cost...
for he gave
all his heart and lost."
In English, please.
Is my class finished already?
Your class finished early this evening.
The teacher wasn't feeling well.
- Miss Simpson is not home yet.
- Are you sure?
She went to the English course.
She'll be back later.
I know, but...
Thanks.
- Mr. Collins?
- Yes.
- Trevor Collins?
- Yes. I said yes. Do you speak English?
Yes. My name is Pedro Paulo.
Yes. You speak English.
And what is your name?
- Pedro Paulo. Peter Paul.
- Nice to meet you. I'm Trevor.
- It's my laptop.
- That one, maybe?
No, no. It's okay.
I can handle it.
- First time in Brazil?
- Yeah.
I've been to Colombia
and Venezuela before, but never Brazil.
Brazil is not like
Colombia and Venezuela.
They speak Spanish.
We speak Portuguese.
They invented mambo.
We, bossa nova.
- Hi.
- Miss Simpson isn't back yet.
- Did she go swimming?
- Yes.
Dad?
"With his feet in London,
but his head in Rio"
Hello, my friend.
Isn't this Pedro Paulo's office?
Yes.
Gordo, wait.
He told me to drop by
so he could look at my contract.
He'll be back soon.
He's picking up a gringo at the airport.
We can't wait.
We have a very important meeting.
1 1:30 a.m. with the English
at the Sheraton.
It's all here.
These papers are too much.
- Too much.
I think your first mistake was
to agree to meet at their hotel.
It's the enemy's territory.
An important meeting like this
should be held in a neutral place.
It should be at a steak house.
Not bad!
Then you could stuff the English
with sausages and caipirinhas...
then get them to sign a clause
of transitory irrevocability.
- Please, have a seat.
- Thanks.
That would mean one million dollars
more by the end of the contract.
Do you speak English?
Does the rain in Spain
stay mainly in the plain?
I'm not usually this stressed,
you know?
It's okay.
I'm a little bit stressed too.
Sorry about the air conditioning.
Cookies, cookies.
Take two, pay for one.
Thanks.
It's good.
I'm supposed to meet someone
here in Rio.
A girl.
- Brazilian girlfriend?
- No.
Not a girlfriend yet.
Just an incredibly hot
cyberspace pen pal.
- Is she pretty?
- She was the "Girl From Ipanema."
Excuse me?
She said she won the "Girl From Ipanema"
contest five years ago.
- Then she's very beautiful.
- Really?
- Not that I care about that.
- You should care.
Garotas de Ipanema
are very exceptional.
Well, Internet lovers.
You know,
people can say anything.
I told her I was a Soho artist
and my name is Gary.
Why did you say that?
So I could attract the kind of women
that Soho artists attract.
Wild.
Outrageous.
Erotic.
Hip, cool chicks, you know?
I know.
Corporate law isn't exactly
a babe magnet.
That's true.
Do you think
she'll be disappointed?
No.
This clause is a trap.
Let's cut it.
This one can stay, as long as they pay
in case of annulment.
Sharon, something happened.
Roberto, call me in 20 minutes.
I'm with a client. Bye.
This clause makes no sense.
Only in their fucking dreams.
Are you an attorney?
No, Gordo.
She's a manicurist.
Keep going.
This is a recording.
The number you have reached
has been disconnected.
Oh, my God!
Is she gonna be okay?
Take a look at it.
" Unless one of the parties stipulates
a clause to the contrary."
I dig.
Is it my impression...
or are you rubbing
up against me?
It's your impression.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Please show him out.
Excuse me,
but who are you?
Gordo.
I can see that,
but why are you standing there?
Private meeting.
- Hi, Vermont.
- Tania, what a surprise!
Everything okay?
- Who's that man?
- He's Acacio's bodyguard.
- Is Pedro Paulo in?
- I think so.
Pedro Paulo, it's me, Tania!
I need to speak with you.
- Call the police!
- I'm gonna go in.
- Let me in.
- I'm calling the police.
I can't believe this.
This is incredible.
I got a cramp in my leg,
and I couldn't swim.
- It's all right. Relax.
- I wanna go home.
The doctor wants you to stay
an extra hour for observation.
- You want me to call someone?
- No, there's no one.
Nadine, what would I have done
without you?
You look so beautiful.
I have good news.
What?
Gary's coming to Rio.
All the things people say about Brazil...
the violence and such...
they exaggerate,
because Brazil is also friendly...
- You have to let us in!
- This is absurd! It's my firm!
Dr. Trevor, welcome.
How was your flight?
Very good.
- What's going on here?
- Pedro Paulo is in a private meeting.
- I'm Pedro Paulo.
- Remember that.
- Isn't he Acacio, the soccer player?
- Hi. What's up?
Were you fooling around
in my office?
- I was here with your partner.
- What partner?
Sharon.
You can't invade my office,
put your goon outside...
and jump my intern.
I saw them fooling around.
May I use your phone?
You didn't have something crazy
with Sharon too, did you?
You can't have crazy flings
with every woman in town.
Hello?
Who is this?
Mr. Peter Paul's office.
Please...
- You speak English?
- No.
Please tell him...
Juan is in the hospital.
Lagoa.
Emergency.
Sharon is not authorized
to speak for the firm.
Someone named Juan...
Excuse me!
Someone named Juan, I think,
just had a heart attack.
Calm down.
And I hung up the phone
on him!
It's not your fault he had
a heart attack because of the bakery.
Tailor shop!
- Mary Ann?
- Pedro Paulo.
How did you find out?
He's in intensive care!
Nadine, do me a favor.
Find out why those people are here.
Excuse me.
- Do you speak English?
- Yes, fluently.
- You're a friend of Peter Paul's?
- Kind of.
Are you all right?
I mean...
- I'm fine.
- Good.
Could I borrow a quarter?
I've just arrived in Rio...
and I will try to get a hold of you
at your other number.
Bye-bye.
Excuse me.
I need another token.
I am so sorry to bother you again,
but I need to call this girl.
- Girlfriend.
- Love is a virus.
Hello.
- Hello. Nadine?
- Who's this?
It's me. Gary.
Where are you?
I'm right behind you.
Pedro Paulo, what's wrong?
Nadine, what are you doing here?
That's Gary.
So you don't work
in the multimedia area.
Almost.
I'm in mergers and acquisitions.
And your loft in Soho?
New Jersey...
and I don't think technically
it could even be called a loft.
I lied too.
I'm not the "Girl from Ipanema."
Really?
For when we leave this world...
we actually do not leave.
We remain in the hearts...
of those who loved us.
That is why...
the dead sometimes
seem so alive...
and the living
seem so dead.
Juan Alvarado, my old friend...
you left us...
but you remain inside us.
How dare she come here!
She must be
riddled with guilt.
Excuse me.
Want something to eat?
- Do you have a beer?
- I have Kirin.
What?
Kirin. Japanese beer.
That'll do.
Everything will be fine.
Yes.
- What did you tell him?
- TheJapanese guy?
Chinese.
I told him I was going back
to my husband...
and that I still loved you a lot.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Let's open to chapter 3 5.
Who would like
to start reading?
London.
I'm gonna make a tape.
I realized I might never hear
these songs again.
Piaf was infallible.
Mother said I was conceived
during " La Vie en Rose. "
For me it was Charles Trenet.
" Que reste-t-il? "
No woman could resist
Juan's songs.
That wasn't why
I was making the tape...
but I'll try it someday.
It will be a beautiful tribute.
Yes, it will be.
Drink?
I'll have one.
ToJuan.
"Dear Pedro Paulo...
here's the Tom Jobim album
that I promised you.
So sorry about your father...
but glad you and your wife
have resolved your differences.
I am very happy
that we met.
I bid you farewell.
Affectionately, Mary Ann"
Okay. I'll call you later.
Excuse me.
What's the meaning of
"to bid farewell"?
It means "to say good-bye."
Did you notice
whether Miss Simpson left?
Yes, she did.
- Are you sure?
- Half an hour ago.
You saw her leave?
She took a cab
to the airport.
She is taking a trip.
Hundreds of angry fans have gathered
here at Tom Jobim Airport...
to protest against the sale
of soccer star Acacio.
There is much gossip
about the young girl...
who was seen leaving with him
for the airport.
On your arrival in London,
you'll have a press conference.
According to the contracts,
you must wear a Nike cap...
and the Manchester jersey,
and you must drink Diet Pepsi.
- You got that, Gordo?
- Of course.
- Diet Pepsi, NikeJersey...
- Team jersey.
That's right. Nike cap.
There's a sponsor,
a beer company called...
"Winterbreath."
They have the right
to tape a commercial.
You at the airport,
bottle in hand, saying:
"I'm here for Winterbreath."
- Did you know that, Gordo?
- Of course.
Then say it.
"Ladies and gentlemen...
I'm here for Wintergrass."
What vinaigrette?
It's not a sauce, it's a beer.
"I'm here for Winterbreath."
- You should be going with me.
- Me?
- Gordo, get her a ticket.
- No, you can't be serious.
The flight's sold out.
Filled with reporters.
Give her your boarding pass.
You come tomorrow.
I can't. No way.
You can't just hand over
a boarding pass.
Tell the English I'll only go
if she goes.
No. You're crazy.
She doesn't even have
a passport.
Well, by coincidence,
I happened to bring it.
Mercenary! Mercenary!
Acacio is now on his way to
the Tom Jobim International Airport...
This way.
A five-year visa.
It's like being approved
by the Vatican to get into heaven!
What's she saying?
Of course, Gary had to go
to the consulate.
- Trevor, please.
- To me you'll be Gary forever.
You'd never guess
by the way he looks...
how good he is in bed.
- Come on, now... in English!
- No, no.
Look, I'm really sorry
about the mix-up at the hospital.
- I hope your fiance's forgiven me.
- My fiance?
Is he still mad?
My fiance is fine.
He wanted me to apologize to you
for his hot temper.
Acacio is now on his way to
the Tom Jobim International Airport...
where he'll be boarding
for London.
A group of angry fans
are waiting for him at the entrance.
Mercenary! Mercenary!
Acacio, how does it feel
to leave Brazil?
I feel sad and happy.
Sad because I love Rio.
I'm going to miss this city,
my friends, the ocean...
because London has no ocean.
What are you doing here?
- I came for Acacio's farewell.
- Me too.
It's a very important moment
in national sports.
Very important.
- Sharon!
- I'm glad I ran into you.
I'm officially resigning
my internship.
I need to talk to you.
Excuse me.
Here, listen to this.
- Who is this?
- Charles Trenet.
Who?
Let's go.
I love it.
Thank you.
Miss Simpson.
- Please, don't go.
- Don't go where?
Don't go anywhere.
- What are you talking about?
- Where are you going?
Nowhere.
Nowhere?
Yes, nowhere.
I'm going nowhere.
I was just seeing Nadine off.
How.