Q-U...
...A- R...
...A- N-T...
...l- N-E.
Quarantine.
Q-U-A-R...
...A- N-T...
...l- N-E.
Quarantine.
You know the cholera?
Yes, Mother.
You've seen the signs on
the houses where the coloreds live?
Yes, Mother.
You know the typhus?
I do, Mother.
You know what they
can do to you?
Yes, Mother.
You are not safe.
You may be directing this movie,
but what you're asking, we can't do.
Don't tell me it can't be done.
The gyro forces are too much.
You send these planes into barrel rolls...
...they won't make it.
- It's the climax of the picture. Make it work.
Decrease the vertical trajectory
if you have to.
A Le Rhône rotary
won't stall at 60 degrees.
We're still short two cameras.
We need to cut that sequence down...
We're not cutting. I'll get those cameras.
Set up for rehearsals.
I'm Noah Dietrich.
Your office said I'd find you here.
Dietrich.
You're a man on the come.
I read your résumé, talked to your references.
Know what I'm looking for?
You're looking for a second-in-command
at Hughes Tools.
Someone to oversee
the financial aspects of the business.
I'm looking for somebody to run it
and do a good job.
There's only one thing
you've gotta know.
My folks, they're gone now.
So it's my money.
What I do with that money may seem crazy
to those sons of bitches in Houston.
I'm sure it does, but it all makes
good sense to me. You got that?
- Got it.
- Good.
Now, you made, what,
$5200 a year at your last job?
- I'll pay you $ 10,000.
- I guess I'll be working twice as hard.
You'll be working four times as hard.
I just got you at half price.
- Welcome aboard.
- Thank you.
You're my voice now.
Make them understand that.
Some of those folks still call me Junior.
You tell them it's "Mr. Hughes" now.
You bet.
So when do we go to Houston?
We don't. Cholera epidemic in 1913.
Two thousand dead.
Whole place is nothing but
pestilential swamp.
Typhus, malaria, cholera, yellow fever.
You name it, they got it.
You see that, Mr. Dietrich?
You are looking at the largest
private air force in the entire world.
What do you think of that, now?
It's your money.
Start them up!
I saw the rough cut of the new
Tod Browning movie, London After Midnight.
Lon Chaney is incredible.
It's his best performance
in a long time.
It's gonna be a big hit.
The cards are great.
It's supposed to be...
Hello, Mr. Mayer.
I don't know if you remember me.
My name's Howard Hughes.
I was wondering
if I could have a moment.
- Oh, Howard Hughes. The airplane picture?
- Exactly.
- I remember.
- Hell's Angels. You heard of it.
- Good.
- Yes.
I was wondering if I could
have a moment of your time.
I need a few cameras.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, two, to be exact.
I bought every camera I could find.
We're shooting our big dogfight sequence.
I need two more. Desperately.
You think MGM could help me out?
With what?
- Cameras.
- Oh, with the actual cam...
We're not usually in the practice
of helping out competition.
- No. No.
- So how many cameras do you have now?
Twenty-four.
You...?
Wait a minute.
- You have 24 cameras?
- That's right.
- And you need...? You need two more?
- Yeah.
- You don't think you got it with 24?
- No. No, sir.
You know, I think...
I think we've got them all...
Don't we have them...?
They're all used, right?
- All 26 of them.
- I only need two, sir.
- Jesus Christ, sonny.
- Howard.
Howard. Let me give you
a little advice, huh?
- Take your oil money...
- Drill bits.
All right, take your drill-bit money
and put it in the bank.
If you continue making
the movie the way you are...
...there isn't gonna be a distributor...
...you won't find anybody
who wants to see the movie...
...and you're not gonna have
any more oil money.
So welcome to Hollywood.
Yeah. Well, I'll be sure
to remember that, Mr. Mayer.
- Good luck.
- All right.
He needs 26 to make it work?
He's out of his mind.
I looked down at my pants.
It was a strange situation.
Boss.
Scram, love boat, let's go.
- Another soda. You know what I mean.
- Milk. In the bottle.
- With the cap still on.
- Okay, what did His Highness say?
Son of a bitch won't part with
a single goddamn camera.
Why don't you try and
make do with what you have.
What I have isn't enough, John,
not for how I see it.
Look.
My name depends on this picture.
If it doesn't work, I'm back to Houston...
...making goddamn drill bits
for the rest of my life.
Can't you do it
with the cameras you have?
You ought to hear about
what's going on with DeMille.
He's shooting his Bible picture.
He's gotta do a crucifixion in Fresno.
Johnny.
- A bunch of tractors...
- Johnny.
- You're a press agent, are you not?
- Yeah.
You're supposed to know
the ins and outs?
- Absolutely.
- Do you?
Yeah, absolutely.
Then you leave the big ideas...
...to me.
- Oh, yeah. Of course, boss.
Cigar, cigarettes, Sen-Sen?
I thought you were
at the Brown Derby...
...with Trixie. No, Theresa.
- Margaret.
- Margaret. Exactly.
What happened to Margaret?
She lost her...
Thank God that's settled.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Thelma, this is Howard Hughes.
Howard and I were discussing how he
wants me to pull a camera out of my ass.
- Cigarette?
- Oh, no, thanks. I don't smoke.
Boy, you are just hitting
on all six cylinders, aren't you?
My God.
Would you do me
a favor and just...?
Would you just smile
for me one time? Just once?
Yeah. Yeah. You see,
you got a short upper lip.
Makes for a much nicer smile.
See, I wonder what gives
a beautiful woman like you pleasure.
I mean, say you're just standing
there, right? And I just touch you.
Just... Just like this.
With my fingertips.
Do you...?
Do you like that?
Do you?
You see, I wanna learn
what pleases you.
I wanna learn everything about you.
Would you let me do that?
Would you give me that job?
I'm off in a half an hour.
- Well, I'm in room...
- 217.
217.
See you there.
Johnny, get on the horn
to Universal and Warners.
I need two more cameras
by Saturday.
Rent them if you can.
Steal them if you have to.
Absotively, boss.
Absotively.
Rumors coming from a lonely airstrip
out in Van Nuys.
Sources whisper that young
Texas industrialist Howard Hughes...
... won't stop pouring money
into his war epic.
And do we mean epic!
One hundred and thirty-seven pilots.
87 airplanes...
... 35 cameramen. 2000 extras.
How long will it be before this picture...
... ends up costing as
much as the real war?
Damn it.
Why the hell do they look so slow?
This isn't what it was like up there.
They look like goddamn models!
Son of a bitch.
Howard?
Without something standing
still behind the planes...
...we've got no idea
of how fast we're moving.
We got no sense of relative motion.
Call UCLA.
Get me the best meteorologist they got.
You get him here in an hour, all right?
Hey. You want the good news
or the bad news?
- Bad news, always.
- All right.
We installed the 450 radial.
Struts won't take the vibration.
Minute we fire her up, the struts
start cracking at the attach points.
- Well, what's the good news?
- There isn't any.
Goddamn it, Odie. If the 450's too big,
we figure something else out.
We've done everything.
We've rebuilt her from top to toe.
If we drain the fuel tank...
...she might make 180 miles per hour.
- I want minimum 200, all right?
I want a date with Theda Bara.
That ain't gonna happen.
Oh, don't be so sure.
If the struts won't sustain the engine
we need, we gotta get rid of the struts.
No, then the top wing falls off.
Then let it.
What?
Who says we need a top wing?
I mean, who says we need anything?
- A monoplane.
- A cantilevered monoplane, right?
They're doing it in France.
To hell with the top wing and struts.
- A 550 Wasp engine.
- One-hundred-octane fuel.
- That would give us a horsepower of what?
- Seven hundred.
We squeeze that to a thousand,
we got the fastest plane ever built.
You know, I've gotta say...
...we've already spent over $200,000
rebuilding this plane.
To hell with it.
Tear it up, Odie.
Go on.
Well...
The cumulonimbus formations
about which you speak...
...that look like...
Giant breasts full of milk.
I want clouds, damn it.
Yes, clouds...
...that look like
giant breasts full of milk...
...cannot exactly be guaranteed
for any particular occasion.
So you might have to...
To wait.
Then we'll wait.
Look, whatever they pay
you at UCLA...
...I'm doubling it, all right?
You work for me now. Find some clouds.
Find some clouds.
Find me some clouds!
Welcome to Hell's Angels.
Thank you.
I've been to Chatsworth,
Santa Cruz, Encino, San Diego...
...Riverside, Van Nuys and Bakersfield.
It has been eight months!
Where are my goddamn clouds, huh?
They move, Mr. Hughes!
Clouds move.
- That's what they do. They move!
- You see that?
It is costing me $5271 a day...
...to keep those planes on the ground.
You find me some goddamn clouds, huh?
Nice day.
Yeah, very funny.
I got a call from Houston.
They're getting nervous.
Stop showing them the damn bills.
That would be illegal.
Shit, no.
Maybe it's a little bit naughty.
Hughes Tool is incorporated in Texas.
They have to see the bills.
Incorporate a new division out here.
We'll call it Hughes Aircraft.
- Do we need these rivets on the cowling?
- Yeah, or the reverse thrust would rip it off.
They're gonna give me drag.
Do something about that.
- Wind resistance on rivets?
- I want her slippery.
There are tax consequences
to incorporating in California.
- Just take care of it, would you?
- Mr. Hughes!
Oakland!
- We have clouds in Oakland!
- You mean it this time?
Yes!
Goddamn it, yes.
I can promise you.
- Clouds in Oakland.
- All right, don't get all jittery now.
Oakland!
We're going to Oakland!
Oakland.
Down and to the left!
That's perfect!
That's right, Senator George.
Yes. Young Howard Hughes
has pulled it off!
After two years. Hell's Angels
has finally finished filming.
There's gonna be one heck
of a wrap party in Hollywood tonight.
The price tag?
A staggering $ 2 million.
If every human being
in America buys a ticket...
... he might even make a profit.
First, clouds don't come.
Then planes break down.
Then the planes crash.
We've had everything but
a plague of locusts on this thing.
I mean, you have to admit.
Now, honestly, did you ever think
you'd actually finish the damn thing?
Come with me.
Mama. Darling.
If I'm a success in this show...
- ... we're gonna move from here.
- Oh. No.
Yes.
We're gonna move up in the Bronx.
Green grass.
A lot of people you know.
The Ginsbergs.
The Guttenbergs and the Goldbergs.
Oh. A whole lot of "bergs."
I don't know them all.
See, this is what the people want.
Silent pictures are yesterday's news.
So I figure we gotta reshoot
Hell's Angels for sound.
How much of it?
All of it.
Before you ask, I'll tell you.
An additional 1.7 million.
We got that much?
- No!
- Well, we'll make it.
Take care of that, would you?
Now. Get this.
In the halls of 7000 Romaine...
... it goes on day after day.
Month after month.
Howard Hughes is now editing
some 25 miles of film.
Heck. I say release it now and give
the world its first 560-hour movie.
Pat, Mr. Hughes needs this reel
in the projection room right now!
Enough is enough. Mr. Hughes.
Are you ever gonna let us
actually see this epic of yours?
Hurry up!
- Who is it?
- Noah.
Come on in.
I've been on the phone
to Houston for three hours.
- We're fixing every goddamn book we have.
- Wait, wait.
Yeah. Run reel 10 again.
I think we're duplicating a shot here.
And tell Jimmy I want
10 chocolate chip cookies, all right?
Medium chips,
none too close to the outside.
Got it?
You remember
that goddamn shot from reel 10?
No. I don't remember
anything from reel 10.
I don't know what reel 10 is.
I'm a businessman, Howard.
And so are you.
Now, look.
This has been a great ride.
We've had a hell of a lot of fun.
But you're losing
$25,000 a day doing this.
Every day.
So, what are my options?
Well, this time I don't know
that you have any.
I'm afraid you gotta close it down.
Dig your way out.
I'm sorry, Howard.
I truly am.
Reel 10. Mr. Hughes.
Mortgage Tool Co.
- Every asset. You heard me.
- Lf you do that, you could lose everything.
Well, I won't.
I won't.
All right.
I'll get into it.
Thanks, Noah.
More than half a million souls lining
the curb of Hollywood Boulevard.
Look at the automobiles!
There are 45.000 cars here.
Making it the greatest traffic jam ever seen.
Howard Hughes must have
a lump in his throat.
Six months after the stock market crashes
and after three pilots' deaths...
... he's finally unveiling his
$4 million baby doll.
It's the most expensive movie ever made.
Nothing five-and-dime for our Mr. Hughes.
Nothing like tonight has ever been
seen before. And I can say...
... it will never be seen again.
Five hundred thousand people are crowding
the streets to get a glimpse of the stars.
Three companies of Marines
were called to assist...
... the 250 special police who are
handling this enormous crowd...
This is an industry town.
And nobody but nobody
makes a movie outside a studio.
Some Hollywood insiders over
at the Brown Derby may be laughing...
And now. I think...
Yes. Yes. I can see
Mr. Hughes' car arriving now.
Mr. Hughes escorts
the lovely starlet Jean Harlow.
He discovered her for this picture.
And we think her platinum blond locks...
... and hot-jazz. Baby-doll style
are gonna make her a big star.
Howard! Howard!
Over here!
- This way, boss. Right over there.
- Mr. Hughes, how about a word?
Big night for you, Mr. Hughes.
Big night for you tonight.
Very big. Very big.
Tell us what it was like
making this fabulous picture.
Yes.
Yeah.
So 4 million clams
from your own pocket.
Nervous how the flick will fly?
Big night. You enjoy the show.
Yes, well, let me present the feminine
star of this spectacle, Hell's Angels...
...Miss Jean Harlow.
- Thank you.
I would like to use this occasion
to thank Mr. Hughes...
...for the opportunity he gave me.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Now I'd like to ask Roscoe Arbuckle...
...to introduce
his pet lion cub, Gilmore.
What's the matter with you?
Can't remember my name?
I'm sorry. Roscoe Turner,
and this would be Gilmore.
It's going! It's going!
Murder! That's what this
dirty, rotten politician war is, murder!
You know it as well as I do.
Stand up, slim, take a bow.
Reel four played too long.
Too many coughs.
Get the team out of the party and
to the office. I wanna cut a few shots.
Oh, find Glenn.
Somebody write this down.
Flush rivets.
Got that?
- Flush rivets.
Lickety-split, boss.
Here he is! Here he is!
Variety says. "This one won't miss!"
- Magnificently photographed!
- Awesome beyond description!
The most extraordinary output
to emerge from a motion-picture studio.
Not for a long time have I seen
anything as enthralling.
It costs 4 million dollars
and has 4 million thrills!
- Majestically...
- Most epic picture of its time!
A lighter shade. I don't want
to look like Boris Karloff.
If you know what I mean.
I read in the magazines
that you play golf.
On occasion.
Well, how about nine holes?
Now, Mr. Hughes?
If it would be convenient, Miss Hepburn.
You're not extending
enough on your follow-through.
Follow-through
is everything in golf, just like life.
Don't you find?
Saw your Scarface picture.
- Violent.
- Realistic.
Movies are movies, Howard.
Not life.
Now the stage.
The stage is real.
Real flesh and blood. Human beings
right out there in front of you, buster.
Can't look away. Can't munch popcorn.
That would be rude.
Do you like the theater?
- No.
- Oh, I adore the theater.
Only alive on-stage.
I'll teach you.
We'll see some Ibsen. If the Republicans
haven't outlawed him by now.
You're not a Republican, are you?
How did you vote in '32?
- Well, I didn't.
- You must! It's your sacred franchise.
Heard you were wooing Ginger Rogers.
What about that?
She's just a friend.
Men can't be friends with women.
They must possess them
or leave them be.
It's a primitive urge from caveman days.
It's all in Darwin.
Hunt the flesh, kill the flesh, eat the flesh.
That's the male sex all over.
Excuse me?
Well, if you're deaf,
you must own up to it.
Get a hearing aid.
Or see my father.
He's a urologist, but it's all tied up
inside the body, don't you find?
Me, I keep healthy.
I take seven showers a day
to keep clean.
Also because I am what's so
vulgarly referred to as "outdoorsy."
I'm not outdoorsy.
I'm athletic. I sweat.
There it is.
Now we both know the sordid truth.
I sweat and you're deaf.
Aren't we a fine pair of misfits?
Three.
Noble effort.
So I suppose you're
wooing me now?
Oh, well.
Not enough.
These rivets have to be completely flush.
I want every screw and joint countersunk.
I want no wind resistance
on the fuselage.
She has got to be clean, Odie.
- Clean. Understand?
- Okay, Howard.
I don't know
what else to tell you.
- What do you got for me?
- The thing is, TWA needs a new plane.
- A modern plane.
- Oh, yeah? What kind of plane?
Okay. The DC-3 has 21 daytime seats...
...and 14 overnight berths.
- Something bigger?
Try 50 seats with
a ceiling of 12,000 feet.
No. No, 20,000.
Think about it.
What does 20,000 feet give you?
- Less turbulence.
- Because it's above the weather.
Jack, we wanna fly
above the weather.
Only 1 percent of the American population
has set foot on an airliner.
Why? Because they're scared to death.
They should be.
I mean, 7000 feet is bumpy as shit.
You know that.
We build a plane
that flies above the weather...
...we could get every man, woman
and child in this country to feel safe.
An airplane with the ability to fly into
the substratosphere across the country.
Across the world.
Now that is the future.
- You with me?
- Yeah.
I don't wanna get into this
if your board doesn't have the balls for it.
- Would they support us?
- I don't know.
- What's your financial picture?
- Not great.
- Last year's deficit?
- 770,000.
- What's it selling at?
- About 8 dollars a share.
That's the lowest it's been, huh?
I could do that.
- Do what?
- Buy it.
- You wanna buy the airline?
- For crying out loud...
...we don't want pencil pushers getting
in the way of us making our plane.
Give me brass tacks, now. What does
controlling interest in TWA cost me?
Call it 15 million.
That is a chunk of change, huh?
You call Noah Dietrich.
You have him start buying.
Howard, hold on.
Are you sure?
You wanna think about it for five minutes?
Hell, Jack, I got a tiger by the tail here.
I ain't gonna let it go.
Good evening, Mr. Hughes.
Welcome. Your table is ready.
How goes the aviation?
- Oh, just fine, Pete.
- I'm so glad.
Good evening, Mr. Hughes.
- Madame.
- It's "miss."
Miss. The usual, Mr. Hughes?
- Please.
- May I recommend for the lady...
...our clementine soup followed
by roast duck with currant glaze...
...and poached pears in rose sauce.
It's truly divine.
Yeah. That sounds fine.
Your kind of joint, is it?
Wouldn't have thought.
They're open late.
I go to a hot-dog stand on La Cienega too.
- They're open till about 4.
- Are they?
How marvelous.
Howard! Howard!
Hi! Son of a gun.
Kate, this is Johnny Meyer.
I suppose you could call him my press agent.
- Pleased to meet you. Loved Alice Adams.
- You're too kind.
- I'm sure you know Errol, right?
- Mr. Flynn. Yes.
Kate. Kate. Kate of the clenched-jawed
Hepburns. Enchanting as always.
You should use Lux on your hands,
by the way. I do.
You and Howard
ought to cook up a picture.
Costar with Errol.
I could sell that in spades.
That would be marvelous. Howard?
I think not.
Don't you read Variety, Mr. Meyer?
Well, I'm box-office poison.
I'm on the outs, the skids, the doldrums.
Washed-up, day-old fish
not worth the eating, so they tell me.
Hell with them. Hell with them, my dear.
Soulless pricks to a man, right?
Johnny tells me you're thinking about
doing a Western, of all goddamn things.
Are you making a Western, Howard?
Yeah. Making a Western.
I'm gonna call it The Outlaw.
Yeah. And you know
what it's about? S-E-X.
- It's all about S-E-X.
- It's a Western.
You can't have fornication in a Western.
It isn't done.
It's not real sex, it's movie sex.
What Scarface did for the gangster picture,
The Outlaw will do for the Western.
Put the sex and guts and blood
up there on the screen.
- Have you seen my cigarettes?
- Don't mind us.
New York cut steak, 12 peas,
bottle of milk with the cap on.
- You can't afford your own cigarettes?
- Jack has all my money.
I hope your food isn't getting cold
at your table somewhere or something.
No, no. We're here all night.
Don't worry.
Now, Howard. Now, Howard. If you're
seriously talking about putting carnality...
...back on the silver screen, you must swear
to let me in on the casting session.
- I have an eye for talent. Isn't that right?
- You ought to give up prancing in tights...
...be a talent scout.
- That prancing paid for my new yacht.
You must all come sailing with me.
Catalina. What do you say?
- Catalina. Sounds grand. Yeah.
- I've even managed to coax...
...the luscious Miss De Havilland
and her equally luscious sister to come.
Though I fear their mother will insist on
coming, to preserve their questionable virtue.
We shall assault these twin monuments
of pristine Britannic beauty nonetheless.
- What do you say, Howard?
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Yeah.
I gotta go.
If you'll excuse us, we have...
We have to be somewhere.
You are somewhere, Howard,
you madman.
- Somewhere else. Excuse us.
- Charmed, gentlemen.
Do help yourself to the poached pears.
I hear they're divine.
Well. Howard Hughes,
ladies and gentlemen.
Was that meant for me?
My hero. God, all that
Hollywood talk bores me silly.
As if there aren't more important things,
like Mussolini.
- Where are we going, by the way?
- Do you feel like a little adventure?
Do your worst, Mr. Hughes.
- Think you own this place, you limey bastard?
- I'm a Tasmanian bastard, you prick.
- Thataway, Errol.
- Let me at him!
That's Mr. Mayer's house right there.
Do you know where Jack Warner lives?
- What's that on the steering wheel?
- Cellophane.
If you had any idea of the crap
that people carry around on their hands.
What kind of crap?
You don't wanna know.
Hold on to the wheel for a bit.
That's too hard. Relax your hand.
Relax your hand.
You see, you gotta feel the vibration
of the engine through your fingertips.
- Do you feel that?
- Yes.
Well, that's good.
Golly!
Well, she's all yours.
- Where are you going?!
- I think there's some milk back here.
- You just keep us steady, now.
- All right.
- Howard.
- Yeah?
There's a rather alarming mountain
heading our way.
Pull back on the wheel a smidge.
Go on.
Golly!
I don't think I've ever met someone
who actually uses the word "golly."
You all right?
Do you want me to take over?
Just when I'm getting the hang of it?
- You want some milk?
- Oh, please.
Utterly smashing!
We'll do it again.
I'm free Wednesday.
It's a little early for golf, though.
Oh, no, no. I live right there.
- Feel like a drink?
- Lead on.
Now, that makes
for a challenging par four.
My decorator
picked out the wallpaper and such.
He's queer as a bedbug.
But I just hate this room.
Gives me the willies.
Like I'm about to be swallowed up
by the latest issue of Town & Country.
What room do you like?
My study.
Take me there.
You are the tallest woman I know.
And all sharp elbows and knees.
Beware.
Will you fly me to work tomorrow?
It is tomorrow.
Keep your eye on the fuel. She's got
a minimum to keep her weight down.
Two runs. That's it.
After that, you're flying on vapors.
And then you crash and you die.
Give her easy flying.
Don't worry about speed
and don't think about the record today.
I wish you'd let someone else take her.
You've got 20 test pilots.
Hell, why should I let someone else
have all the fun? See you in a bit.
Contact!
339.
Goddamn!
347.
Son of a bitch!
- 352.
- 352!
Good girl.
Damn it!
Goddamn it!
- Oh, God!
- There goes our meal ticket.
Come on!
Howard!
- Howard!
- How did we do?
352 on the last run.
She'll go faster.
Country mouse!
- Kate! Katie!
- Upstairs, city mouse.
Hello.
Good Lord, what happened to you?
Oh, nothing. A hard landing.
I cut my foot.
Sit down. I'll take care of it.
You tell me everything.
You cannot imagine what it was like, Katie.
You cannot imagine the speed.
- She was like a winged bullet up there.
- What did she make?
Oh, around 352.
You did it!
Fastest man on the planet.
Hot dog! I'm so proud of you.
- She did it, baby.
- You knew she would.
Oh, she was fine. She was just fine.
Now let me see your foot.
Yeah.
- Good God! You're covered in blood.
- Oh, no. That's just beet juice.
- I crashed into a beet field.
- What?
Yeah, I crashed in a beet field.
Let me get you cleaned up.
- Heavens, what is this? Electrical tape?
- Yeah. Odie just sort of slammed it on there.
But all I could think about
was getting home to see you.
I am so proud of you.
Now, this is gonna sting a little bit.
Oh, this is useless.
Come to the bathroom.
- Don't get beet juice on the carpet.
- I won't, I won't.
- Too hot!
- Don't be a baby.
Was the press there?
Some.
But they're calling everyone.
Should be on the wires by now.
What is it?
Kate?
I've been famous,
for better or worse...
...for a long time now...
...and I wonder if you know what it...
...really means.
Yeah. I had my fair share
of press on Hell's Angels.
I'm used to it.
Are you?
Howard, we're...
We're not like everyone else.
Too many acute angles.
Too many eccentricities.
We have to be very careful not to...
...let people in,
or they'll make us into freaks.
Kate, they can't get in here.
We're safe.
They can always get in.
When my brother killed himself...
...there were photographers
at the funeral.
There's no decency to it.
You know, sometimes I...
I get these feelings, Katie.
I get these ideas, these...
...crazy ideas about...
...things that may not...
Things that may not really be there.
Yeah.
Sometimes I truly fear that I'm...
...Iosing my mind.
And if I did, it would...
It'd be like flying blind.
You understand?
You taught me to fly, Howard.
I'll take the wheel.
Smashing all records. Howard Hughes
outdoes Jules Verne's wildest dreams.
Around the world from New York
to New York in four days.
Even beating Wiley Post's mark
by over three days.
New aviation history is written
when his Lockheed monoplane...
... returns swiftly and safely.
A daring aviator.
A true pioneer of the world's airways.
From New York to Paris. He cuts Lindbergh's
time in half. Then on to Moscow.
Thirty-five hours out of New York.
He roars across Siberia's trackless wastes.
Sixty hours out of New York. He heads
for Alaska. Most hazardous hop of all.
Continuing the terrific pace.
He comes home...
... bringing new laurels
to American aviation.
Howard Hughes and his crew
may find more worlds to conquer...
You won't believe this. It just came over the
wires. Hughes has bought control of TWA.
I thought Mr. Hughes
was flying around the world.
Apparently he did it while he was flying,
over the radio.
I have heard some disquieting rumors
about Mr. Hughes.
I'd like to know everything
there is to know about Mr. Hughes.
I'd like you to attend to that for me.
Thoroughly.
The Pantages is glittering tonight.
- Howard!
- Right over here. This way, over to the left.
- Mr. Hughes, how was your flight?
- Miss Hepburn!
- When are you gonna name the day?
- Raise your head.
What's the next movie?
Give us the scoop.
Right here. How many more
records are you gonna set?
Right over here. Come on.
Give us a smile. It won't kill you.
- Howard, this way.
- Beautiful.
Over here, over here, Mr. Hughes.
When are you gonna fly
around the world again?
You gonna fly with Kate next time?
Did you get Ionely without her?
- Talk to Lindbergh about your flight yet?
- Where's Linda Darnell tonight?
- Please, Mr. Hughes.
- Right here. Right here, Mr. Hughes.
Are you trying to be more famous
than Lindbergh?
You know,
fame is supposed to be my turf.
L.B.!
If you don't get more distinguished
every time I see you.
You look so beautiful.
Is that true?
Don't worry about it, Howard.
She's just working the room.
It's her job, baby.
Sultry Southern tigress Ava Gardner
dazzles the room tonight.
She's the newest star
in the MGM galaxy.
And believe you me.
She puts the "cheese" in "cheesecake."
Well, Jane Eyre has been selling popcorn
for over a hundred years, L.B.
Hello.
Could you reach me a towel?
I...
I really can't do that.
I'm sorry.
I'm an idiot. I'm a complete idiot,
and I'm sorry.
- Forget it.
- No, no. I'm a vain, preening ass...
...without a single redeeming feature.
- That's not true. You have very good teeth.
Come on.
I've got a better idea. Take me flying.
Or better yet, I'll take you flying.
Do your worst, Miss Hepburn.
Don't be so squirmy. You're gonna
get on famously with Father and Mother.
And I'm sure they'll like you too.
Once they get to know you.
- Hello! Hello!
- Kath, hello.
Kathy.
- Who's that with the camera right there?
- That's my ex-husband, Ludlow.
Father and Mother are just mad
about Luddie.
- What the hell's he doing here?
- Oh, he's here all the time.
Hello!
Sorry we're late.
- Mom.
- Oh. Oh, thank you.
- Dad.
- Darling.
- Uncle Willy.
- Oh, who have we got here?
- Don't feel self-conscious.
- Hepburns! Hepburns!
Attention, please. This is Howard.
Howard, welcome.
Don't worry, he's had his lunch.
He likes you. That's unusual.
We pay our devotion to the arts here.
A colony we created.
Julian's a painter. Abstract, of course.
What's the point of painting...
...something real when you can just
take a picture nowadays?
Where do you stand on politics,
Mr. Hughes?
- Excuse me?
- We're all socialists here.
We are not.
You've met Mr. Roosevelt.
What make you of him?
What are you sniggering at?
- What? What was that?
- You just sniggered.
No, no. The dog.
It seems to be crushing my feet.
- Oh, my God!
- Buster!
Hey. Hey!
Don't you like dogs?
I will not have you sniggering
at Mr. Roosevelt.
- Please leave.
- No. I wasn't.
- I thought everybody liked dogs.
- Perhaps he had a bad experience.
Does it upset you
that Howard gets more press?
- A bad experience with a dog?
- No, no.
- You are such a shy creature, aren't you?
- Perhaps it was a very large dog.
- The press can be a damned nuisance.
- Was it a Doberman?
- A Doberman, Mr. Hughes? Or a dachshund?
- Neither, sir.
- Dachshunds are little dogs, Hep dear.
- They should all be lined up and shot.
- What's that Spanish painting?
- The Goya.
Goya. Of course. Yes.
- Yes, Mexican.
- What was that called?
Anyway, that's the vulgar press, I'm sure.
Do you read much, Mr. Hughes?
I try to stay up to snuff
on the trade journals, yeah.
- Snuff?
- These would be flying magazines?
- What was that?
- Oh, he's a little deaf.
- Pass the goddamn butter, I beg you.
- You read flying magazines?
Trade journals. On engineering. Aviation.
We read books.
Howard has to read the trade pieces, Mom,
because he's designing a new aeroplane.
Oh, really? Do tell.
Well...
...it's quite exciting, actually.
It's a spy plane for the Air Corps.
A twin-engine plane with some...
...I must admit,
some rather unique design features.
You see,
it has these two booms at the back...
Luddie built a birdhouse once.
You remember that, dear?
- Yes, well, a mere trifle, darling.
- I remember the painting!
The painting, it's called
May 18-0- something.
Anyway, Goya's vastly overrated.
All the Spaniards are.
- Nonsense! Picasso is sacred.
- I'm a urologist.
- It was quite aesthetic, really.
- A sacred monster.
The birds don't care for it much,
but the bats do.
- I'll bet.
- That's such bunk!
- Do speak up, dear.
- Nothing, nothing, Mrs. Hepburn. Nothing.
Why did you speak? I can't abide people
who speak but have nothing to say.
Did you go to mechanic school
to learn all this airplane guff?
No, no, I didn't, Luddie. No.
Well, Howard just flew round
the world in three days.
- I think we've had enough about airplanes.
- And dogs.
- Then how did you make all that money?
- We don't care about money here.
Well, that's because you have it.
Would you repeat that?
You don't care about money
because you've always had it.
- How did you make all that...?
- Excuse me, I'm speaking.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
All right.
Some of us choose to work for a living.
Speaking of which, I have more of that
airplane guff to attend to.
Excuse me.
Well, seems a rather high-strung chap.
You're a fine bunch of bullies,
aren't you?
Have you talked to Mr. Mayer
about letting you do Jane Eyre?
The old philistine won't budge.
Too arty, don't you know.
I'm convinced the man hasn't read anything
longer than a Katzenjammer Kids in his life.
No fair, kicking.
You have to use the mallet.
Really, darling, you can't retire
from the field of battle like that...
...or they'll never respect you.
- Katie, I don't understand.
You're like a different person in there.
They just expect me to be a certain way.
There's only one real Kate,
and that's your Kate.
Over in Hollywood. Aviation tycoon
Howard Hughes is cooking up something big.
Even as he edits his new picture. He's been
secretly meeting with the U.S. Air Corps.
We applaud his patriotism and look forward
to his newest marvel.
You know how many Allied ships we lost
because of U-boat attacks?
- No.
- Six hundred and eighty-one ships...
...just this year so far. The Army needs
a new airplane to fly the troops to Europe.
These ships, they're sitting ducks
for the U-boats.
- You wanna build a troop-carrier plane?
- Stop thinking like an insect.
Not just to carry troops,
a plane to carry everything.
The troops and the jeeps and the tanks
and whatnot. Here, take a look.
No. Other side.
I figure around 200 feet from nose to tail.
Wingspan, around 300.
We're gonna need
about 24,000 horsepower.
Now, this is just what Kaiser
and the Army are looking for.
- They're gonna pay for it this time.
- What are you getting us into?
Well, it's a big plane,
so I'm calling it The Hercules.
Swell name, isn't it?
- How heavy you imagine this thing is?
- Say around 200 tons.
Well, I didn't say it was gonna be easy.
All right, boys,
I want you to rig up something like this.
Should give the proper uplift ratios and
reduce need for torque support on the front.
We are not getting enough production
out of Jane Russell's breasts.
I want smooth titties, gentlemen.
Smooth titties.
- It's all in engineering, isn't it, Odie?
- Howard...
...do you really think they're gonna let you
put out a whole movie just about tits?
Sure. Who doesn't like tits?
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
Sorry I'm late.
Please record that Mr. Hughes has arrived
and this session is now called to order.
- I yield the floor to Mr. Breen.
- Mr. Hughes...
...members of the committee, I've reviewed
the photoplay entitled The Outlaw...
...and I can state that I have never seen
anything so unacceptable...
...as the shots of the mammaries
of the character named Rio.
For almost half the picture,
the girl's mammaries, which are quite large...
...and prominent,
are shockingly uncovered.
For this reason, I concluded the picture
appeals only to prurient interests...
...and should be denied the Motion Picture
Association's seal of approval.
Really, Mr. Hughes.
- Thank you, Mr. Breen. Mr. Hughes.
- Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
Mr. Breen. It's good to see you again.
I haven't seen you all since that situation
with all the violence in Scarface.
The situation here revolves
around Miss Russell's mammaries.
Mr. Breen feels that they are
too prominent, yes?
More prominent than other mammaries
have been up on the screen?
Well, I hope to dispel that notion.
Jean Harlow.
Ann Sheridan.
Irene Dunne.
Claudette Colbert.
Rita Hayworth.
Betty Grable.
And the lovely Miss Jane Russell.
Now, all these shots, save for Miss Russell,
were enlarged from pictures...
...that received
Mr. Breen's seal of approval.
Now, as you've probably noticed by now,
they all contain mammaries.
I will ask my associate to join me now.
May I introduce...
...Dr. Ludlow Branson
of Columbia University.
Dr. Branson...
...is a mathematician of some note.
Yes. And he will now demonstrate...
...that in fact...
...Miss Russell's mammaries
are no more prominent...
...than any of these other fine ladies'.
Doctor.
Doctor...
...you forgot your calipers.
Gentlemen, Mr. Hughes.
Let us commence by calling this...
...Mammary Exhibit Number One.
Now, you'll see that the length
of the actual cleavage...
...if I may, is...
...5 inches and a quarter.
Now if we move to Mammary Exhibit...
Dateline: Hollywoodland.
Movie tycoon Howard Hughes
must have the greatest job in the land.
Every night. The lucky guy escorts
a different beautiful woman...
... to a different dazzling event.
The TWA king always talks up
his airline as he escorts a succession...
The Hercules. Ladies and gentlemen.
The Hercules.
A plane. A boat. A flying city.
Don't forget, every bill comes to me.
They don't pay for anything.
Those men decide whether to fund
the plane, so I need them happy.
- You do what it takes.
- You betcha, boss.
How are the girls
in the bomb department?
Well, let's put it this way,
it'll be a regular boob buffet.
I don't think the Air Corps men
will have trouble scoring.
- Good.
- And inside. 700 brave American soldiers...
... a dozen Sherman tanks all winging
their way over the Atlantic...
... free from the threats
of the U-boats below.
Could Jules Verne himself have
ever imagined anything so magnificent?
Could he have imagined her mammoth
wingspan. Longer than a football field?
Don't you see how this demeans me?
Since when do you care
about scandal rags?
Every time there's a picture of you with
another woman, it's a slap in the face.
- Don't you understand that?
- Well, that's overstating it.
Joan Crawford, Ginger Rogers,
Linda Darnell, Joan Fontaine...
...and now Bette Davis,
for God's sake.
Look, they're Cracker Jack candy, honey.
They don't mean anything to me.
Oh, very nice.
You're the one that said
that all men are predators.
I mean, it's all in Darwin, remember?
And am I to expect this behavior
to continue after the wedding?
What is really bothering you, Kate?
Is it the women or the publicity?
Can't you eat ice cream from a bowl
like everyone else in the world?
Don't you dare.
Yeah.
No, Odie, this is not a good time.
For chrissakes, we can't make The Hercules
if we don't have any aluminum.
Wait.
I can hear you better now.
Tell the War Production Board...
...that this is an essential
strategic operation.
If they're giving aluminum to Boeing,
they can give some to Hughes Aircraft.
Don't set the ice cream...
We gotta think of something else. If we
can't get aluminum, we'll find another way.
You tell me. We'll find
some alloy that works just as well.
Right. Look...
- lf we can't get aluminum, we'll use wood.
- You can't make a plane out of wood.
Why not?
The damn thing is a flying boat, right?
- What do they use to make boats?
- Oak.
And think of The Hercules
like a flying Spanish galleon.
Spanish galleons
can weigh 1200 tons.
Good luck today.
We just have to find the right wood.
Something light but strong.
- Morning, Kate.
- Pine, cedar, maybe birch.
Catch.
From my farm.
If you like it, I can get you a bushel.
Trouble with Mr. Hughes?
There's too much Howard Hughes
in Howard Hughes.
That's the trouble.