That shit!
- Hello!
- So, did you ask 'em?
- Yep. They said fine.
Oh, good!
Sure it's okay with your mom,
though, right?
Yeah, she doesn't care.
She's working.
Isn't she coming up this weekend?
I don't know.
So, ah, come on, how cute is he?
Spit it out.
- Oh, he's kind of gorgeous.
- Yeah?
He's sort of like a cousin, but not
really. He wants to be a forest ranger.
Oh, good! Well, then after dinner
we could set a fire in your room,
and he can come and rescue us.
You should've seen the look
on her face.
I never laughed so hard, I swear to God.
I just can't believe you might miss it.
Oh.
Hi, Gulliver.
How you doin', boy?
Hey, Pilgrim.
Come here.
Hey, babe.
You're such a beautiful boy.
What are you thinkin', huh?
What are you thinkin', boy?
You wanna go for a ride?
Let's go for a ride.
Come on. Come on, boy. Come on.
- Hello?
- It's me.
- Hi.
- So what train are you taking?
- Um, I should be in by 2:00.
Okay.
You want me to pick you up?
No, I can take a cab.
Grace go riding?
Mm-hmm. What do you want to do
about dinner?
- I hadn't thought.
- I can ask to try that place
Emily says--
- Oh, hang on.
- They're here, so--
I, I'll let you go. We'll figure it out
when you get here, okay?
Yeah, okay. Okay. Bye.
Hello?
Please! Oh, God, please!
Oh, wait. Have you seen that
stupid cereal commercial? It's like--
-And where are the paintings? It's about
her work, and we can't even see it.
-But we're trying to--
We can change the colour of the deck,
and we can move it up so then
you can see the paintings--
We need to see the paintings.
She's an artist.
- Have you checked on her going rate?
- Gottschalk.
Yes. The legal department's
on that right now.
- David!
- Did you speak to Felton?
Yes, we're suing.
Well, is that absolutely necessary?
It'll just make it a bigger story.
-Am I on the speaker?
- David, he signed an agreement
that he wouldn't talk to the press...
and now he's libelled me
by saying I faked the figures.
- You're not going soft on me, are you?
- Well, nothing like a good public feud.
Exactly!
- You know that kid Adam?
- Yeah.
- Mm-mmm, he's very cute!
- I, I think you'd make a good couple,
Grace.
- I don't think so.
- Oh, I do!
- You think he's cute?
- Eww! Are you serious?
- I think he's cute.
- Oh, I think he's lucky
that he lives next door to you.
- I think, I think I--
- What do you think?
I think you have a crush on him.
All right, let's take a shortcut.
Let's take a shortcut.
- You know, we can't even read it.
- Friday is confirmed.
- Right, okay.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We have to reshoot this.
- I said it
- I said that
- It's ''that.'' It's ''that.''
- I said it
- I swear to God, it's ''that.''
- It, it, it, it!
- It's ''that.''
- All right, fine.
Let's start again. Ready?
- All right, fine, fine, fine.
All right.
I met him at a party
And he told me how to drive
He said he'd like to do it backwards
I said it
It
- Come on.
-Judith.
I said it
It!
Come on!
Gulliver. Gulliver, up!
Up, Gulliver! Whoa!
-Judith!
- Hey! No! No, no, no!
Grace, look out!
- Pilgrim!Judith,Judith!
- Grace!
Hello!
No!
Gulliver!
Gulliver, stop!
Hold it, Gulliver!
Gulliver! Come on!
Robert.
Judith's dead.
And what about Grace?
- She's in pretty bad shape.
- It's a multiple trauma.
- Where is she?
- She's still in the O.R.
- O.R.? What for?
- I-It's just-- It's--
It's a mid-shaft, tib-fib fracture
with a vascular compromise, meaning
the blood supply to the lower leg--
They think they have to take part
of the leg off.
Which leg?
T-The right leg.
Oh,Jesus.
Okay.
Just take it easy.
This is gonna be tough on both of us.
So let's not make it any harder
than it has to be.
Judith.
- That bag's almost empty.
- Oh, they'll be in to change it.
If you leave it up to these people--
Excuse me.
- My daughter needs a new I.V.
- Yes, I know. We have her down.
Well, I'd like it
taken care of now, please.
You have to stay on top
of these people constantly.
I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
We really should let her get some rest,
and I do have to change the bandage.
You can come back in a couple of hours
and see how she's doing.
Mrs MacLean? Mrs MacLean,
you have a call on line two.
You can take it right there.
- Hello?
- Annie, it's Liz. How's Grace?
Her leg was very damaged,
and they had to remove it.
Oh, God. Annie, I'm so sorry.
Listen, I, I know
that you're being hit with a lot now...
and it's hard to think
about anything else,
but I have to talk to you about Pilgrim.
Hello?
Yeah, I'm here.
I've never seen an animal
with these injuries still breathing.
I'd like your permission
to put him down.
- It's, it's really the best thing--
- Uh, I-- Y-- Uh--
You mean shoot him?
-Annie.
- Well, um--
Um, look, Liz.
The doctor's here right now...
and I, I can't make this decision
on my own.
-Annie, I understand that,
but I have to know--
- Uh, just do what you can.
- Okay?
- Annie, no matter what I do,
this horse will never be the same.
Well, look, I, I, I, I just don't know.
It's Grace's horse, so when she--
- It's not right to make it suffer.
- I cannot deal with this now, Liz.
I-If you need a yes or a no,
then don't do it.
Okay? Just, just, just, j-just do
what you can for him, okay?
Right.
Animal should be put down.
Anybody can see that.
What did he say?
Nothing.
He's just going off duty.
Well! That's important information, huh?
Christ.
Doctors, huh?
I'm gonna get to know all
the nurses' names.
It's, it's good to know their names.
- I'll go get some of her things.
- I'll go.
No! I'll go.
You stay, in case she wakes up.
You guys go on ahead.
I'll be up by Christmas.
Oh, I meant to tell you. I got
those tickets for the Knicks game.
Good.
- Wanna come, Annie?
- No. Why don't you go with a friend,
Grace?
Yeah.
Wanna eat something else, honey?
We can order out something else.
No, I'm just not that hungry.
That's all.
Well, you should try to eat anyway.
It's the only way you're gonna--
I said I wasn't hungry.
- Wanna watch some television?
- I think she should finish first.
- Maybe.
I just-- I-- I can't.
- Here.
- I'm sorry.
No, Dad! I got it. Got it.
Sorry.
- You've got to stop doing that.
- What?
Helping her all the time.
Running to her every time she trips,
anticipating her.
You know, Annie,
this didn't just happen to you.
Hi, Grace.
I don't care what he told you.
The man's a liar.
He's a actor, for God's sake.
He'd do anything to get a cover.
Gracie, what happened?
It doesn't matter.
I just--
I don't wanna come back.
That's all.
Well, what are you gonna do? I mean,
you have to go to school, sweetheart.
I said no!
I don't want to come back.
That's it. I wanna go home.
Grace, listen to me. Hmm?
Your leg is just healing, and you have
to give the rest of you time as well.
Is that your version of a pep talk?
Well, you're not staying home all day,
feeling sorry for yourself.
You're gonna get up,
and you're gonna figure this out.
Fine.
It's still early.
What's your next class?
Gym.
Appears to be an excellent jump.
Head and hands, eyes, perfect.
Pilgrim moves with absolute confidence
at the command of Miss MacLean.
- What is it, sweetheart?
- I wanna see Pilgrim.
- Hello.
- Hi.
It's so good to see you.
How are you doing?
- She's doing just great.
Aren't you, kiddo?
- I'm fine.
Watch your step.
Mind how you go.
It's muddy back there.
Back there?
W-Well, what do you, what do you mean?
Why isn't he in the barn
with the other horses?
Well, Grace, you see...
Pilgrim just isn't the same horse
that he used to be.
As a matter of fact, maybe now's
not the best time for you to see him.
I really wanna see him.
Can you open it, please?
Hey!
Hello, beautiful boy.
- No! No!
- Grace.
- Oh, God, no, no, please.
- No, Grace.
- No, no, no, no. Leave me alone!
Here. Grace. Grace!
Mr MacLean, I'm so sorry.
- Dad, why didn't you tell me?
- I'm so sorry.
You should've told her, Annie.
This animal is beyond help.
Annie, can I have your permission now
to put him down?
No.
And get me every publication on riding,
racing, breeding.
Everything.
Medical publications as well.
Veterinarian journals. And tell them
it's me, and I want it now.
- Hold on, hold on. Gottschalk.
- I'll call him back.
- He says he's on his way
to the airport, he really needs--
- Lucy, I'll call him back.
I'll call him back.
Just get me what I want.
''A million years before man...
''they grazed the vast
and empty plains...
''living by voices
only they could hear.
''They first came to know man
as the hunted knows the hunter...
''for long before he used horses
for his labours...
''he killed them for meat.
''The alliance with man
would forever be fragile...
''for the fear he'd struck
into their hearts...
''was too deep to be dislodged.
''Since that Neolithic moment...
''when a horse was first haltered...
''there were those among men
who understood this.
''They could see
into the creature's soul...
''and soothe the wounds
they found there.
''The secrets uttered softly
into troubled ears.
These men were known
as the Whisperers.''
It's perfectly shot,
perfectly cropped...
perfectly laid out,
and I am so bloody bored.
Start again.
Thank you.
Would you excuse me for a moment?
Yes.
- Hello?
- Yeah, this is Tom Booker.
I got a message you called.
Oh, hello, Mr Booker.
It's Annie MacLean from Cover.
You know, the magazine.
Um, well, thank you
for returning my call.
- Is there something
I can do for you, ma'am?
- Yes, yes.
I read this article about what you do
for people with horse problems.
Well, truth is, I help horses
with people problems.
Well, whichever way
you want to put it.
Uh, this article said that you were,
you were a, a horse whisperer.
Oh, they said that, huh?
A whisperer. Hmm.
And I was hoping that you'd come
to New York...
and take a look at my daughter's horse
and possibly do some--
Ma'am, I'm sorry, but I'm,
I'm afraid you've misunderstood
whatever it is you read.
Because that's not exactly what I do.
I mostly conduct clinics, you see, and--
Well, could you come to New York
just for the day?
- It's only a few hours by plane.
- And I'm not doin' them now.
I'm on my way to Montana where I have
a ranch to take care of.
Well, I'd pay your fare, of course.
Uh, first class.
Ma'am, first class to Montana
is a waste of good money.
Well, if you could just give me a time
when you'd be available.
Say, am I, am I being too polite here
when I say ''no'' in Nevada?
Does that mean ''yes'' where you are?
Look, I'm really sorry for your
situation, but there's nothing I can do.
You just called the wrong person is all.
I'm sure there's some fine horse doctors
back east.
No, but I don't want a horse doctor.
- I want, I want you.
- So I, I hope everything goes okay
with you and your horse.
- Well, but you see, it's not my horse.
- So, so, goodbye now.
Grace?
Grace, it's Mom.
Are you all right?
- I've decided about Pilgrim.
- Oh.
I think we should put him down.
It's not fair to let him suffer.
- Well, I think that's a very--
- Maybe they should put me down, too.
- What?
- I'm not much use anymore.
You're getting a fax.
- You're up late.
- Is it?
- How was the dinner?
- Is Grace asleep?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Nothing we haven't heard before.
Just louder this time. That's all.
- So why'd you go?
- Well, one of us had to.
They're still our friends, Annie.
Listen, I had a thought.
What do you think
we go someplace warm, the three of us?
Bermuda or the Bahamas or--
What?
Mmm, nothing.
No, I just don't know if Bermuda
would be such a good idea.
- Grace would have to wear
summer dresses or shorts.
- Oh, yeah, of course, of course.
What is it?
I want to take Pilgrim out to see this
horse guy. Drive him out to Montana.
- No, I'm serious.
- Now, wait a minute.
- I thought you said you didn't like
the way he sounded on the phone.
- Well, I didn't.
- I want to take Grace with me.
- You're kidding!
Liz'll find me a trailer.
We can stay at motels along the way.
- What, you made arrangements already?
- No, I just checked out a few things.
You know.
- Wait a minute. Drive a crazed horse
all the way to Montana with--
- Oh, he's not crazed, Robert.
- Don't exaggerate.
- No, I can't just pack up and leave.
- Well, I'm not asking you to.
I'll do it.
- By yourself? How?
- You can't take care of Pilgrim.
- He'll be sedated.
- I do know a thing or two about horses.
- What about the magazine?
I'm in charge.
I can oversee things from Montana.
- I can take my fax, my computer.
- Oh, you're in charge.
Well, what about Grace? The doctor says
she needs stability and security.
Well, I can't say he's being
all that effective with her.
- Are you a psychiatrist?
He says it takes time.
- Well, I don't care what he says!
I cannot sit here and pretend
everything's gonna be all right.
- I am not pretending. I am trusting.
- We have to do something, Robert.
- Other people know more
about this than we do.
- We are losing-- We are losing her!
I don't care what the doctors say.
They don't know her.
I don't care
if this doesn't sound rational.
Nobody is suggesting anything better!
I, I can't explain it, Robert.
I just have this feeling.
I just know it's the right thing.
Why, Annie?
I just know it.
Does this, uh, cowboy vet
know that you're coming?
Yeah.
What if Grace doesn't wanna go?
She will if you think she should.
- And you think it's best
if I don't come.
- No, that's not what I said.
Daddy?
I don't wanna go.
Straight back. Come on.
A little closer. A little more.
Watch it. Get behind him.
Hold it! Get back! Hold it.
- Watch it!
- There he goes, Eddie!
- Why don't you get inside and--
- Lady, we're doing the best we can!
- It's the only way to load
this kind of horse.
- Keep trying.
- Maybe we should give him
another sedative.
- We did.
Get the gate! Get the gate!
Let's get out of here!
Hold that door!
You got a gun, just in case?
Of course not.
That's probably best.
You may want to shoot yourself
halfway to Ohio.
Grace, are you hungry?
Do you want to stop for lunch?
I don't care.
I want to find a place before
it gets dark. What do you think?
- Grace?
- Doesn't matter.
Okay, Lucy, look.
This is what I'll do.
I'll get to the next motel,
see if they have a fax and then--
Oh, wait, hang on. Uh--
I gotta go, okay? Later.
Grace, do you want
to put your music on up here?
Grace.
Do you want to put your music on
up here?
And when you purchase
your Eureka World Deluxe Vac--
Here the agricultural markets
and farm news headlines continue to--
Insecticide for small grains.
Important to always read
and follow label instructions--
This here man was rejuvenated
in the grace of the Lord.
He was washed.
Mmm, Grace, look at this.
Do you wanna see that?
- I don't care.
- ''I don't care.''
Oh, it'll be fun. You haven't seen
any of the sights yet. It's history.
When I was 1 3, I used to love
doing things like this.
Oh, you were never 1 3, Mom.
Oh.
Great idea, Mom. Now what?
- How long is this gonna go on?
- What?
You know what I mean.
Do you want us to go back home?
Is that what you want?
What are you asking me for?
You didn't ask me if I wanted to come
in the first place.
Now I get to decide? Sorry.
Do you know who I'm doing this for?
I'm doing this for you.
Bullshit! It's all about you, about
you deciding, about you being right!
-It's like we work for you or somethin'!
-I don't believe this!
- How come Daddy didn't come, huh?
- What do you mean?
You know everything.
You figure it out.
- Your father had to work.
- Yeah, right!
- Would you please stop acting like
you know what you're talking about?
- You are amazing, you know?
I mean, you act like I don't even live
in that house anymore.
What, you think
I don't know what's going on?
You think I'm still five years old!
- When you act like this, you are.
- How long are we gonna be away, huh?
- I don't know. I don't know.
- Yeah, well, what if this guy
can't do anything, huh?
I don't know!
I don't have all the answers.
No, you just act like you do.
- You okay, ma'am?
- Yeah, I'm, I'm fine.
That young lady's gettin'
a little worried.
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
- Good night, ma'am.
- Good night.
You buckled up?
- Are you cold?
- A little.
You may have seen the
Kennel Club champion being rewarded
with a box of chocolates the other day.
Veterinarians and humane--
But I can't get you out of my mind
Everybody--
Winter weather got you down?
Wilson Travel is offering charter
packages to sunny Orlando, Florida.
Well, looks like lots of precipitation,
as we mentioned, overnight.
Great Falls, an inch and a half.
Plus, it looks like
about another half an inch.
He had an epiphany. Paul had
been transformed by the grace of God...
so he was a new creation in Christ.
Is there a man who is completely--
Hop on down to the Northern Plains
John Deere. We'll be glad to see you.
Gee, this place looks like fun.
- Don't they believe in signs
around here?
- What would they say?
- ''Ten miles to Big Rock,
twenty miles to Bigger Rock''?
- No.
- Great trip, Mom.
I'm having so much fun.
- I think I should turn here.
Oh, yeah, those rocks over there,
much more interesting.
Can we take a look at Bronty's foal
when we're done here, Dad?
Sure, as long as she don't mind.
There's this kid at school says
we should have imprint-trained him.
Says if you do it soon as they're born,
makes 'em real easy to handle later on.
That's what some folks say.
There's this thing on the TV
about a guy who does it with geese.
He has this aeroplane,
and these baby geese all grow up
thinking it's their mom.
And he flies it, and they just follow.
You hear about that, Uncle T?
Yeah. Heard about it.
Well, what do you think
about all that stuff?
Well, I'll tell ya,Joey,
it might be all right for geese to
grow up thinkin' they're aeroplanes...
but horses, as far as I can tell,
can't fly.
We expecting company?
- You know who it is?
- Nope.
- Mr Booker?
- Yeah?
Tom Booker?
Annie MacLean from New York.
We talked on the phone.
I had a little bit of a hard time
finding the place. There are no signs.
Oh, there are plenty of signs,
just not many of them printed.
Why do I get the impression
that you're just not driving through?
I want you to take a look at my horse.
Now, it won't take long.
And if you still feel the same way,
then I'm sure I can find--
You thinkin' about personally
driving me back east?
Oh, no, no, no. No, I brought him along,
and my daughter, too.
We're at, we're at the Lazy J Motel.
- You hauled him all the way out here?
- Well, yeah.
I had a trailer. It's not like
I made him run alongside the car.
- By yourself?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, ma'am, I appreciate the pains
that you've obviously gone through--
Look, please don't do
the ''Shucks, ma'am'' thing again.
I have just driven a few thousand miles
for a few minutes of your time.
I have brought him
all the way out here.
Just take a look at him.
If you still feel the same way...
I will be on the road by morning, and
you'll never hear from me again, okay?
Deal?
We're at the Lazy J Motel.
Whenever you're free.
You don't have to call.
Jesus!
- No, this is what you call the boonies.
- Mom, the door.
No. No, not really.
No services,
and there's one doctor in town.
But I managed to find a therapist
for Grace.
I had to drive, like, two hours.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Did they get the colour corrections?
- Yeah?
- Uh, I'm Tom Booker.
Is your mother around?
She's on the phone.
She'll be right out.
- Could I--
- Mom, there's a cowboy here.
This is not Gottschalk's business.
Why is he interfering with this?
I told him I'd take care of it.
No. I told him I'd take care of it,
and I will take care of it.
I just have to get myself settled here.
Well, um, put it in a memo,
and I'll sign it.
- This your first time in Montana?
- Oh, no! Really?
Uh, it's completely ridiculous.
It's completely ridiculous.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah. I can imagine.
I can imagine. They are?
Then why did you go to meet him,
alone, secretly?
-All dressed up?
- That's, that's funny.
No, really?
I can't believe that.
- Is she gonna be long?
- Probably. She's on the phone
23 hours a day.
- What does she do?
- She's an editor.
An editor? Ah, ah, yeah.
Just in case she hasn't told you,
which she probably hasn't...
I don't wanna be a part of this,
okay?
Mm-hmm. Thank you.
Hi. Sorry about that.
Grace, this is Mr Booker.
Did you look at Pilgrim yet?
I was gonna take that look now.
Would you like me to come with you?
I have to run over to the office
and give Mr Peterson a cheque.
- Doesn't matter.
- Grace?
Do you wanna come with us,
take a look at Pilgrim?
- Probably best she stay behind anyway.
- Okay.
- Howdy, Lester.
- Howdy.
- Goin' to see that horse?
- Yeah, I thought I might.
Well, I hope you got insurance.
That dirty son of a bitch.
Well, you're the closest
anyone's ever gotten.
I have to be honest with you.
I still feel you've made
a long trip for nothin'.
But before I even think about it...
I need to know somethin' right now.
And it's a question for Grace.
You see, when I work with a horse,
it's no good just me doin' it.
- The owner's gotta be involved, too.
- Well, that'll be a little complicated.
You can make it as complicated
or as easy as you like.
But she's the one that's gonna
be ridin' him. Am I right?
Hey? Right?
Now, here's the deal.
I don't know that I can do anything.
But I'm prepared to give it a go,
if you'll help.
- Oh, you have a problem with that?
- Isn't it, like, obvious?
Not to me.
Either you want to or you don't.
- Look, I'll talk to--
- Excuse me. With all due respect,
this is her decision, not yours.
Now, I don't wanna waste
anybody's time here, mostly mine.
Well, nothin' else to do around here.
That's not good enough.
I can't help you.
What do I have to do?
I said, what do I have to do?
Well, what does she want?
- Does she want you to take care
of her horse?
- Somethin' like that.
- And they're stayin' in a motel?
- The Lazy J.
Can I have some butter please?
- Not exactly a tourist stop.
- Well, well, what about the girl?
Doesn't she go to school?
- I don't know.
- You know, I just think she's got
a lot of nerve showin' up here.
Draggin' that, you know, poor animal
and that child all the way--
Honey, don't eat with your fingers.
Frank, don't you think
she's got a lot of nerve?
Well, hell, I don't know. According to
Tom, she's a pretty determined woman.
She must've thought it was worth it.
Yeah. Well, I guess they'll want
feedin', bein' out here all day long.
- I don't think they'll expect that.
- What, they gonna drive 40 miles into
town every time they want a hamburger?
- Mixed salad.
- What?
Well, I believe women from New York
eat mixed salads.
- Ain't that right, Tom?
- I believe so.
Well, that's just what we need!
A vegetarian from New York
on our cattle ranch.
A Great Traveller, interested,
not merely a good one...
is a kind of introspective.
As she covers the ground outwardly...
so she advances towards fresh
interpretations of herself, inwardly.
And this is the quality
which lends Frea Starks'books...
the memorable poetic density
which is their special cachet.
Moreover, it is this quality
which makes them as fresh and strike--
You're at a good place to quit.
Oh, I got him movin' out a bit.
That's about it.
It's still a long ways away
from gettin' a leg over him.
Well, we're movin' along.
What's he doing?
Is this some kind
of physical therapy?
Hello? Hello?
What? No, you're breaking up.
Hold on. Hold on.
Don't start a fight with him.
Joey, give me your rope.
Just to pull him back.
We'll never get him outta there.
Let me go in after him.
Mr Booker, I'm really not comfortable
with you taking these kind of risks.
- Oh, God!
- Hey, hey! Pilgrim!
Let him go!
Let him go.
Does that hurt you?
Only when I kick somebody.
Don't you go to school?
Taking a break.
Don't you?
School term's out early for us
so we can work the ranch.
Look at him out in the pasture.
He must've been a big,
beautiful-lookin' horse.
How was he to ride?
Excuse me.
I've got chores to look after.
Are we in the way?
Should we leave?
I guess we'll go then.
From now on,
leave your phone somewhere else.
Miss MacLean, would you and
your daughter like to stay for dinner?
Joe, take off your hat at the table.
I don't want to say it again.
Uh, dear Lord...
we are humbly thankful
for these gifts...
for the blessings on our home,
our family and our guests.
And bless those that aren't
as fortunate.
Bless all God's creatures. Amen.
- Amen.
- Like some roast beef?
- Looks great. Thanks.
Thank you.
- Want some milk?
- Yeah. Thanks.
Ol' Hank got us
a couple more men...
to move the cattle.
And what kind of cattle
do you raise, Mr Booker?
Well, we run a mixed herd,
but mostly Black Baldies.
And, uh, what're, what're those?
- Black Angus Herefords
instead of straight Herefords.
- Oh, Black Angus.
- There you go.
- Of course.
And, uh, what's,
what's the difference?
- Well, they suit the weather better.
- And their utters are black
instead of pink.
They don't get burnt
with the sun bouncin' off the snow.
- They make good mothers.
- Our daddy raised straight Herefords.
You know, that's interesting. Um--
I've always wondered every time I,
you know, when I go into a restaurant...
what's the difference between a regular
steak and a Black Angus steak?
I can never taste the difference,
but I could swear that one
was more tender than the other.
I didn't know there was
that much difference between the cows.
Of course, I've never been on
a cow farm before.
Seems to me that the bulls
have the best of the time.
Just laying around the fields,
waiting for somebody to come along
and ask them to do their work.
You get born a bull,
got a 90% chance of getting castrated,
served up as hamburger.
So on balance,
I reckon I'd choose being a cow.
Yeah.
- Hey, young man.
- You get back up to bed!
So how's the Lazy ''J''
holding up for you?
Oh, it's fine.
I still can't get used to how dark
it gets around here, though.
Every time I leave the ranch,
I hold my breath
until I can see the motel.
Well, by golly,
that's a lot of drive time.
You know, Tom, while you're working
on that horse of theirs...
Annie and Grace should move
into the old creek house.
Nobody's usin' it. It's silly for her
to be driving back and forth...
when she, she don't know her way around
that well.
Well, that's very kind of you,
but really we're fine where we are.
Oh, hell, look,
I know the Lazy ''J.''
Whole place is as good
as falling down around your ears.
Frank, they're already
all settled in.
And anyway, I'm sure
they want their privacy.
Well, it's got doors, Diane,
and private as can be.
Tom?
I don't have a problem with it.
I think it's up to Annie.
Well, it'd be great for when my dad
comes to visit.
Where is your dad, honey?
He's at home, working.
You know, um-- I don't know, um--
Is it worth it, really? I mean,
how long do you think you'll carry on
working with Pilgrim?
That depends on Pilgrim.
I know. Me, too.
When are you comin' to visit?
Yeah, well, there'll be plenty of room
'cause we're moving down to the ranch.
Yeah, yeah. They've got this really cute
little house down by the creek.
It's really pretty.
Okay. Okay.
I love you, too.
Ho-Hold on.
Dad wants to talk to you.
Hi.
- Well, she sounds like
she's doing all right. How is she?
- Yeah.
You know, I think she seems
to be getting more comfortable
on the ranch...
which is, which is the only reason
I said yes to this move.
Well, that makes sense.
So, how are you doing out there
in Marlboro country?
- Is the magazine complaining at all?
- Yeah, but nothing I can't handle.
Lucy says she thinks Gottschalk's
plotting. But what else is new, hmm?
So when are you coming home?
You know, I asked him that myself
tonight, and he doesn't know.
Hmm. I miss you, Annie.
Yeah, I know.
We miss you, too.
- Good night.
- 'Night.
Did you ask him to come visit?
You already did.
Do you want me to help you pack?
- Hi.
- Howdy.
What's he doing?
He's tryin' go get him
to hook on.
How's it going?
Get over there!
Ha! Come on!
Hey, you over there!
Wanna make yourself useful?
- Hey, Hank.
- Yeah?
I think you got a volunteer here.
You wanna take care of her?
Where's Grace? Grace?
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Cocktail hour yet?
- What?
I said, is it cocktail hour yet?
Come here a second.
You handled that pretty well.
I think it's time you started earning
your keep around here.
So when we're not working,
you're not doing your therapy...
I'd like you to help out
with the horses, you know,
rubbin' them, cleanin' the stalls.
Think you can handle that?
- That's not a question, is it?
- Nope.
Okay.
Hey, cowboy.
When I was out walkin'
one morning for pleasure
Spied a cowpuncher
come a-lopin'along
His hat was throwed back
and his spurs was a-jinglin'
And as he approached
he was singin'this song
Hey, you little ones.
How are you?
He was only 1 8, he had a flat
on his little pickup, and--
You know you're not allowed
to go swimming in the river.
And Marie here made the best pie.
Cherry pie. Go get some.
As luck would have it, he didn't have
all the lug nuts off...
but the jack slipped and fell
right on that rock he calls a head.
Is he okay?
Well, it rearranged his scalp
about 1 2 inches--
But he always dreamed of having a place
where he could raise horses...
and have a whole separate life.
My grandson Joe is named for him.
And somebody told him
about a place called Stockett.
He got on his horse
and he rode over there...
and he got off, and he walked
as far as he could one way.
And then he turned around, and he
walked as far as he could to the other.
And then he decided that
that's where he was going to settle.
And that's where we raised
Frank and Tommy.
- Where do you call home?
- She's from New York, Mom.
Um--
Well, I was born in London,
but I'm from all over really.
My father was a diplomat,
and so we moved constantly.
Oh, my.
That sounds very important.
No.
No, he was, he was a wonderful man.
He died when I was 1 2, but we,
we lived all over the world.
We-- It's, it's not the same as,
as knowing a place like this.
Well, sometimes people carry it
more on the inside...
than the outside.
If it hadn't have been
for them troublesome doggies--
I suppose I could gather up
some of these cups and plates.
- You guys done with these?
- Yeah?
You better give me that recipe.
It was really--
I know, I know.
Be glad to tell her anything.
This family has quite a history.
Yeah, it's a story, all right.
- I love how she calls him Tommy.
- Yeah, always did.
I think she always favoured him.
She loves tellin' this story about...
when he was two years old,
he ran off...
and they found him sleepin'
in the barn...
between two giant hooves
of a Percheron stallion.
He said that horse was protectin' him,
and nobody could convince him otherwise.