[Beeping]
[Gentle rock music]
(John)
I always got
what I wished for back then.
And what I wished for
wasn't much...
just to be with her forever.
Happy birthday.
Stardate, January 30, 2002.
John Roth Web diary,
entry number 19.
A lot can happen in a year,
which leaves me here
in New York,
helping my college roommate
run a webcam pornography site:
Intercon-X.
Connect to our site,
choose your fantasy,
enter your credit card,
and voila...
the girl or guy of your dreams, onscreen in full
motion video,
ready to do
whatever it is you desire
over a secure,
private connection.
She might live
halfway across the country
or just across the street.
It doesn't really matter,
does it?
The world is a lot smaller
than you think.
than you think...
thousands and thousands
of people,
all broadcasting their lives
for us to see...
and this is mine.
This is my life.
These are my obsessions.
Now, I want
to direct your attention today
to a site that I've been tracking
for some time now.
There she is.
And the fascinating thing
is that you can see her there.
She's getting undressed.
So you know
she's online too...
right now.
You know how to find her,
but you don't really know
where she is.
She's just out there somewhere.
And that's pretty much
all you know.
You can slip
into her room at night,
watch her sleeping.
You can stay
and watch her wake up
in the morning.
You piece together
some things,
and you've imagined
the rest.
But would you
really want to meet her?
Or would that just
ruin everything?
[Distant moaning and barking]
[Moaning and barking
sounds louder]
Uh, anyway,
that's all for today.
I've been
crazy busy lately,
so SkyGal68,
Baitshop3,
anybody else
who sent me any e-mails,
don't worry;
I'm not dead yet.
If this is your first visit
to Silent City,
be sure
and sign my guest book.
And if you want
to check out AngelCam...
(man)
Hey.
The address
is www.angelcam.org,
or you can
link there directly
by clicking on John's
site of the week.
Hello, geeks.
What's up;
what's up?
Of course, you've all
met my roommate, Moe.
Hey, you, I know
you're all just looking
for some really hot,
horny lesbian sex,
so check out our website, Intercon-X. Com.
Thank you.
L-N-T...
wait...
Intercon-X. Com.
Real, live women,
and they'll
really talk to you.
Thank you.
[Sighs]
Well, now I forgot
what I was talking about,
so I guess I should
just stop talking.
Um...
See you next time.
[Barking]
[Moe moaning]
[Dance music]
[Woman drowned by music]
Tell Moe that I had to go.
What?
I got to go home.
I got to... I got
to go home... l...
[groans]
Madison Street?
Where the fuck am I?
Oh, shit.
[Menacing electronic laughter]
Asphyxiation,
masturbation.
That has been explored
for the past, like, five years...
(woman #1)
And then I'd burst
into flames,
right in the middle
of the fucking prom...
(woman #2)
Okay, but what if you, like,
blow your face off,
and you don't die?
And as I
twirled through...
Ed!
Moira?
What's wrong?
I'm going to do it, Moira.
I'm on the fifth floor.
I'm going to dive
right out the fucking window.
Do it,
you fucking faggot.
Fuck you!
Look, you've been
whining all night.
Why don't you just turn around
and fucking do it?
Mute those assholes, Ed.
(man #2)
Make us all happy.
Laughing
about death.
This is
the truth, man.
This is a chat room
about death...
Click mute.
Okay.
(Moira)
Just click mute, Ed.
I'm still figuring out
how to work this stupid thing.
All right.
Now, tell me
what's wrong.
What do you think?
I'm on a fucking
suicide website.
I want to fucking
kill myself.
Okay.
Deep breaths.
[Breaths deeply]
Now, you know
you're not really
going to jump
out the window,
so...
why don't you
just tell me what's wrong?
It's just...
I thought when God
made you a fag,
he was supposed
to install gaydar
as part of the standard
options package.
Well, either mine
doesn't work
or else I'm the only queer
in all of Ohio.
Oh, honey.
I mean, I know that you live
in North Bumfuck or whatever,
but if you're lonely,
why don't you
just go to Homo. Com
or Queers-R-Us
or something?
What's the point?
It's like watching
the Food Channel
when you're starving
to death.
Excuse me,
how many pills
did you just swallow?
Don't worry.
Just the usual.
[Sighs]
So I'm feeling
all sorry for myself
and getting
totally shitty
in this dump dive bar
in Chinatown, all right?
When this really
sweet guy comes up to me...
Share, share.
So we're talking
and drinking and...
(man)
You, ass-licker.
Oh, shit;
that's my roommate.
I got to go.
Hang in there, girl.
Bye.
Hang in there, boy.
(man)
I can hear you.
You.
Hey, choad munch.
You just using
my fucking computer?
No.
How many times
I got to tell you?
I didn't lay a finger
on your precious machine.
Better not have.
[Woman moaning]
[Computer chiming]
What?
[Laughs]
Ah, Edward.
Prompt as usual,
I see.
Now, where were we?
Well, last week,
you were saying
how you don't allow
any stowaways
aboard your ship,
and how I'd have
to find some way to earn my keep
or else you'd
throw me overboard.
Yes, that's right, Edward.
Now, I do believe
that I was training you
to be my cabin boy.
Hmm?
Excuse me, Herr Captain,
but didn't you tell me
this was a German vessel?
[German accent]
Silence, schweinehund.
Now, I think
that last week
I taught you
how to shine
und polish mein boots
mit your miserable tongue.
Ahh.
But tonight, I think
that you must learn
how to polish my knob.
Oh.
Oh, yes, sir.
Yes, yes.
And this is a very,
very fragile tool,
so you must polish it
mit the utmost care.
Schnell!
[Riding crop whacks]
[Growling]
Dude, that's her;
that's her.
I wonder how
her personal reads.
Psycho.
[Stifling laughter]
Hey, gorgeous.
Oh...
What are you
doing here?
You told me to come by
and see where you worked.
I did?
Yeah.
I had a great time
last night.
You're amazing.
I'm not even talking
about the [barks] stuff.
Sorry.
[Laughs]
It's okay.
I, just, um...
Oh, god, I didn't think
I'd see you again, so...
Yeah, well.
I'm full
of surprises.
Yeah, I bet you are.
[Laughs]
Christ.
Hey, did you
paint this?
Huh?
Oh, yeah, that's mine.
I paint a bit.
(John)
It looks like you.
So you're Moe's roommate?
Yes, roommate
and business partner.
Business partner?
Hey, is this yours?
Yeah.
That's mine.
(John)
You like Silent City?
Yeah, I love
that book.
That's the name
of my website.
Your business?
No, my personal...
So how's this thing work, anyway?
You fill out one of these forms and then you
what?
And then, um,
if someone wants
to meet you,
then they tell us,
and we tell you.
Cool... hey, dude,
you should do one of these.
Yeah, no.
Seriously.
You're a free man;
come on.
Moe.
John here's a little hung up
on his ex-girlfriend.
Fiancee.
Ex-fiancee.
(John)
She hasn't
given the ring back.
Look; here's
one for you, look.
"Likes: Good food,
hiking, biking."
That's her sales pitch?
Doesn't everyone
like hiking and biking?
(Moira)
I hate hiking
and biking.
"Dislikes:
Rude, arrogant people,
head games."
You know
what that means.
I'll take the sheet.
[Laughs]
Go.
Okay.
Likes:
Head games.
Please fuck
with my head.
Bad childhood?
Father issues?
I'm your man.
Whether you were born crazy
or just ended up that way,
I'm sure we'll end up
dating eventually,
so why wait?
Transform your trauma
into great sex.
Break my heart
and walk away cured.
Doesn't make me sound
too bitter, does it?
I think
I know this girl.
Excuse me.
Hmm.
Hey, can I get a coffee?
Hey, I know you, right?
Yeah, I get that a lot.
[Computer roars]
Good morning,
darling bud.
Hey, Al.
Does this mean you're finally coming over
to pussy?
You wish.
I do.
Well, no such luck.
I've already cleared
over $500.
Mmm, lucky you.
Any prospects?
Hey, I'm eating, please.
Hey, I've dated
clients before,
snob.
Yeah, you've dated
everyone before,
slut.
[Jordan laughs]
Look who's talking.
[AI laughs]
I've heard some stories
about you, grandpa.
(Al)
Yeah, lies.
Lies and ancient history.
Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, baby,
tell me.
How was your date
with The Teacher?
Oh, I learned
my lesson all right.
Never answer
online personals.
Whatever
possessed you, hmm?
I guess I'm just looking
for that thing.
That thing?
Yeah.
Just once, I want somebody
to make me come, damn it...
over and over again.
I want to be overpowered,
you know?
Overwhelmed,
off the hook...
[AI laughs]
Totally out of control.
Poor thing.
I sure wish I could help.
If I was a boy.
[AI laughs]
So anyway...
Yeah.
The punch line is
I don't come once
all night,
and I wind up back here.
Jilling off to your
internet friend, again?
What can I say?
Angel's hot,
and she doesn't talk back.
I think you've
found your soul mate.
No.
Sweetness,
that's you.
Aww.
Hey, I got to go.
Play nice.
Ha.
[Computer beeps]
[Computer roaring]
[Roaring cut off]
Well.
Hello there, stud.
What's your name?
Oh, shit.
Yeah, I knew
I knew her.
Who?
Your little
girlfriend there.
She was down
at Halcyon.
Her?
Jordan?
Yeah.
She must live
in the neighborhood.
You, you should
ask her out some time.
[Laughs]
Yeah, that's
a good plan.
No, bro,
seriously.
You're always staring
at these chicks on the monitor.
Why wouldn't you
ask one of them out?
Dude.
You're like one
of those little old ladies
who never leaves
her apartment, dies,
and gets eaten
by her cats.
What are you
talking about?
I go out all the time.
Yeah, when I drag you.
It's not like I don't
have other friends.
Online.
Look,
while I appreciate
your concern,
I'd probably take you
a little more seriously
if you weren't sitting there
with your gonads hanging out.
I got a date.
Yeah?
With who?
That artsy
barking girl?
Absolutely.
I thought I'd get me
a little bit more of that strange.
Whoo!
You want some?
Mmm-mmm.
[Howls]
[Smacking]
Uh.
[Moe laughs]
Quick observation:
The thing that sucks
about being single
is that everyone wants
to give you advice.
Everyone wants
to set you up with somebody.
I used to be
the relationship guy.
Things change.
I guess life's a little
tenuous that way.
(Moe)
Hey.
You want to see what me
and John do for a living?
[Moira laughs]
Oh, my God.
[Laughs]
You guys make porno?
No, no, no,
no, no, no.
We mostly link
people together.
[Beeping]
It's kind of like
what you do.
Kind of.
People get off
on this shit.
We can watch them.
They can watch us.
(Moira)
Us?
Oh, my God, no, no.
[Laughs]
Come on.
No.
[Laughs]
Come on.
No, Moe, please;
I don't want to.
No, look, look, look.
Nobody will know
who we are.
All right?
Look, nobody can
see your face.
Now, you said you were
up for anything, so...
No, Moe, please.
I don't...
I don't want to.
Mmm.
Aw.
You know I like you.
Do it for me.
Do you love me?
Of course I do.
Now come on;
it'll be fun.
Say it.
I love you.
[Whispering]
Oh, baby, yeah.
Oh, yeah, put it
in your mouth.
Oh, suck it.
Suck it.
Yeah, just like that.
[Door creaking]
Check it out...
No, wait...
Ahh!
Whoa.
[Clunks]
Ow.
Who-whoa.
Sorry.
Uh...
Is that my sock?
Oh, God, no...
No, whatever.
Uh, no.
Take your time, man.
[Gasping]
Um...
Don't...
whoa.
Whoo.
Fuck.
God.
[Computer roaring]
What the hell?
Hi, there.
I'm Jordan.
What's your name?
Hi, I'm John.
John Roth.
Yeah, I run
the Intercon-X site.
Oh, right.
I knew you looked familiar.
Um,
Listen, John,
it's kind of late,
so whatever this is about...
No, I thought you
were available.
Yeah, well, I thought
you were a client.
I am.
Oh.
Okay.
Oh, no, no;
that's okay.
No, I like...
or, I mean,
you look fine.
Or the wig's
fine too.
You know, whatever;
whichever you want.
Okay.
No wig.
It's too itchy anyway.
Okay.
You seem pretty nervous
for somebody who watches
this stuff all day.
I don't really
watch all day.
I sort of just...
Liar.
[Laughs]
Okay, yeah, okay.
I wa...
I-I watch.
So then,
I guess you must know
what I do.
Yeah.
Yeah... no, um.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Wait.
Wait?
Yeah.
I was kind of hoping
I could just...
enjoy your company
for a little awhile.
Hey, it's your nickel.
It's just...
this is my first time.
And, um...
[exhales]
I'm not even sure
what I want to do with you yet.
I could suggest a few things.
[Laughs]
Yeah, I bet you could.
Hey, you know what?
I'm going to go get a drink.
Do you want anything?
I was about to have
a glass of wine, actually.
Okay, good.
Why don't you get yourself
a glass of wine?
I'll meet you back here
in a few minutes.
Okay.
Chin chin.
Chin.
[Clink]
Mmm.
I got this for you.
[Clears throat]
So...
Can I ask you
a personal question?
Not real personal,
but what?
A lot of guys
ask you to masturbate,
right?
Yeah.
That's more or less
what I do for a living.
But do you ever,
you know,
get off?
I mean, for real?
Sometimes.
If I'm in the mood.
So tell me how it happened
the first time.
The first time you came.
Oh.
Yeah.
I remember that.
How old were you?
Mmm, 11 or 12.
Somewhere around there.
We had this cute
substitute teacher, Mr. Parsons,
and I was sitting
next to him
on the bus
on a class field trip.
And it was really bumpy
and I started getting
that feeling again, you know?
That hot,
ticklish feeling
in my cunt.
Mmm.
Feels so good.
Are you wet?
Oh, yeah.
Say it.
I'm wet.
Show me.
Yes, daddy.
[John breathing heavily]
Go on.
What happened
after that first time?
You were on the bus.
And l...
I didn't know
what to do.
I wanted to get up,
I wanted to run,
but I was afraid
he'd find out.
So I started
crossing and uncrossing
my thighs really tight
to try to make it stop,
but...
[sighs]
That only made it worse.
Mmm.
Are you getting close?
Oh, yeah.
It feels so good.
Are you going to come?
Mmm.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Oh, yeah.
Uh-huh.
Then stop.
Huh?
Right now.
Put your hands
around the wine glass.
Both hands.
Do it.
But...
Do what I tell you.
You can get off
on your own time.
You're a little weird,
you know that?
Shh.
I like knowing
that you have to come.
Mmm.
[Laughs]
I like that look
on your face.
Asshole.
[Breathing heavily]
You're doing it now,
aren't you?
[Breathing heavily]
Yes.
You're rubbing
your legs together,
but it's just
not enough, is it?
No.
It's never enough,
is it?
No.
Poor Jordan.
I watch you.
I see when the clients
sign off,
you don't even notice,
because you have
to come so badly.
You need it so much.
Oh.
You're the best lover
you've ever had.
Nobody else can
make you come like you.
No.
Nobody else but me,
right now.
I can let you
squirm all night,
or I can make you
come so hard.
[Breathlessly]
Oh, John.
You want to
use your hands?
John.
Your fingers?
Yes, please.
Yeah?
Oh, my god;
you're so beautiful.
I want to touch you
so much.
Oh, John.
Oh, I'm coming.
Fuck it;
go for it.
[Glass shattering]
Oh, John.
[Both gasping]
So when do we meet?
She's going to
fuck you in half.
Okay, okay.
She's going to
fuck you to pieces.
Okay, shh.
[Laughing]
Oh, son.
I don't know.
You don't know what?
Meeting her.
It just seemed like a good idea
at the time, but now...
What?
Just, I don't know what got
into me that night,
but now this girl's
going to be expecting
some weird Mack Daddy, 9 1 /2 Weeks,
sex machine guy and...
No, I can't.
I can smell the disaster
from here.
John, John, John; you have
got to meet this girl,
or I will never, ever
stop giving you shit.
No.
(Moe)
One date.
You, me, Moira,
Internet Chick, Halcyon.
No.
It'll be fun.
Seriously.
Dude, you're acting
really, you know,
weird and dorky
about this.
[Laughs]
Look, I know you were
in love with what's-her-name.
Right?
You still are.
Whatever.
But you can't stay faithful
to a chick who left you, right?
And I know you don't
want to think about this,
but she's probably
with some other guy right now.
No, she's not.
Dude.
No, I mean
she really isn't.
I know she isn't.
Whatever, man.
We're talking
one fucking date
with a gorgeous fucking chick
who's already hot for you.
I mean, why are we
talking about this?
Huh?
You realize there
are guys in Silicon Valley...
geeks much richer
than you...
who never even
talk to a real woman?
Huh?
Do it for them.
Okay, okay, okay;
all right, yes.
Good, yes.
I don't know
what I was thinking.
Seriously.
Yes, a date with a sexy
internet sex girl.
This is
a good thing.
Yeah, dude.
I'm starting
to worry about you.
Yeah, I know;
I know.
All that sitting
around the computer.
Yes, I have to
get out more; yes.
Two for Tron, please.
Hey, how are you?
$20, please.
My friend's getting
fucked tonight.
[Moe and man laugh]
(John)
I mean, don't get me wrong.
Moe is my friend,
but that same fucking rap...
it just... it's like
a broken record.
And even if it's
all true, you know, fuck.
I don't nag him
about his many, many
bad habits and shortcomings.
At least I know
what mine are.
And the truth is,
you know,
for all the notches
in his belt,
Moe has never been anywhere
near a real relationship.
He doesn't know anything about that intense,
miraculous bond
that comes along once
or twice in a lifetime,
if that...
if you're lucky.
[Sighs]
But who knows?
You know, maybe this new girlfriend will
change all that.
She's very attractive...
though I have a feeling
she keeps her shrink's
number on speed-dial.
[Computer chimes]
Hey, Ed.
Hey, girl.
You haven't been
hanging around Final Exit,
so I figured you were either dead
or getting some.
Which is it?
Oh, Ed.
What?
I think I'm in love.
Uh-oh.
Here it comes.
It's this guy, Moe.
That's his name: Moe.
And he's sweet
and cares about me,
and he has a real job...
sort of...
[laughs]
And I mean,
you're right, you know?
I'm a good person,
and I deserve
somebody good.
[Crying]
Ed?
What's wrong?
Nothing;
it's stupid.
I don't even know
why I'm upset.
Why?
What happened?
Oh, God.
Well, my school
had this big party
with the worst fucking
music in the world.
And all these jarheads
and debutantes
were in their Gap khakis
and baseball caps,
laughing, kissing,
dancing badly.
And I'm thinking
to myself, "Jesus Christ,
"there are
so many of you.
"And all I want is
just one person for me.
But no."
Eventually,
it's too much,
so I leave campus,
and I spend three hours
hitchhiking to the big city...
Akron...
'cause some guy online told me
there was a gay club there.
And?
Have you ever been
to a gay bar in Akron?
Uh, no.
The worst fucking music
in the world,
same little cliques,
same asinine conversations.
By the end of the night,
I was so depressed,
I wanted to slit
my fucking wrists.
Oh, no, no, no, ;
sweetheart.
Look, you're going
to find somebody.
How?
Okay,
what about online?
Who told you
about the club in Akron?
This guy in New York.
Well, what about him?
Hello?
I just said
he lives in New York.
So?
Do you like him?
Yeah, but...
Does he like you?
[Laughs]
I don't...
What?
I am so pathetic.
It's amusing, really.
Why?
Forget it.
Listen, just...
thanks for listening
to my bullshit.
Ed, are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm going
to be fine.
[Sniffles]
Good night, Moira.
Good night.
[Computer chiming]
Mmm?
Mm-hmm.
[German accent]
Ah.
Herr Edward.
This is not
our usual meeting time.
I am thinking
that perhaps you have been
extra naughty
this week, yes?
No, not really.
No.
Then what do I owe
the pleasure of this visit to?
Hmm?
I just wanted to talk,
if that's okay.
[American accent]
Fair enough.
What would you like
to talk about?
I checked out that club
in Akron you recommended.
[Small laugh]
I recommended
a club in Akron?
Well, not exactly.
You told me about a website
that listed gay clubs in Ohio.
When was this?
A couple months ago.
Huh.
Okay.
So how was the club?
Terrible.
Oh.
Sorry to hear
about that.
It wasn't your fault.
No, I shouldn't
think so.
So, uh,
what was it
that you wanted?
Do you ever think about me?
[Laughs]
Excuse me?
I mean,
I know you must talk
to tons of guys every day,
and...
I don't even know
your real name,
but...
Oh, God;
forget it.
Thanks.
(John)
Oh, my God.
(Moira)
Is that her?
(John)
Right.
Hey.
Hi, hey.
Do you want
to sit down?
Yeah.
Yeah?
You must
be freezing.
Hey, don't I know you
from somewhere?
(John)
My roommate, Moe.
What are you,
the chaperone?
[Laughs]
No, no, he's just
waiting with me.
Am I late?
No.
No, not at all;
no.
So...
What do you
feel like doing?
Hanging out's fine.
I don't care.
Great.
I could go for a drink.
Whatever.
Yeah, right;
I'm sorry, of course.
Uh, what would you like?
Do you, uh...
red wine?
[Jordan laughs]
No.
Actually, I'd kill
for a Cosmopolitan.
Right, okay.
Um, Moe?
I'm good, man.
I'll be right back.
[Laughs]
Do you have any
peppermint schnapps?
(Moira)
Now, with all the good booze
in the world,
why would you ever
drink that shit?
Okay, what would
you recommend
for a date that's
going up in flames?
Manhattan.
Fuel the fire.
Really?
Mmm, okay.
One of those
and a Cosmopolitan.
I like the butterfly
on your ass, by the way.
Excuse me?
Your tattoo.
I noticed it
the other day.
You were bending over
for a client, so...
It's really good
ink work.
Gee, thanks.
[Both laugh]
(Moira)
So,
how do you
know Moe, anyway?
College.
And then I helped him
set up the technical side
of his business, and...
[laughs]
I saw what you did
for a living.
Oh, Jesus, really?
You saw Intercon-X?
Oh, what?
Don't be a prude
about your own porno website.
So Moe.
Mmm?
Is that a nickname?
Yeah, my real name's
Lawrence.
Lawrence Curly?
Yep.
Larry Moe Curly.
That's my name.
Perfect.
[Laughs]
How much?
On the house...
prude.
All right, here we go.
Thanks.
Cosmo for you.
Yes.
Manhattan for me.
Skoal.
[Glasses clink]
Oh, did l...?
I'm sorry.
It's... it's cool.
Forget it.
Sorry.
It's cool.
So I was just
telling your roommate
about this cool spot
on the West Side.
If you want to check it out
or whatever...
Yeah, sure;
whatever.
(John)
And just like that,
it was over.
We were five minutes
into the date,
we'd hadn't said five words
to each other,
and I already knew
I'd blown my shot with Jordan.
Because the eyes...
the eyes don't lie.
And her eyes
were basically screaming,
"Nope, uh-uh,
no fucking way."
Because I wasn't
this sexy guy she met online.
I was just another
neurotic stranger
trying to get
into her pants.
And the night
went downhill from there.
[Dance music]
So, two mojitos
and a mango daiquiri later,
I'm completely out of money,
which I think Jordan senses,
because the next thing I know,
she's out on the dance floor,
frugging away
with every bad fashion trend
since the French Revolution.
We had nothing in common
except a pair
of mutually exclusive orgasms.
That and the fact
we both like hiking and biking.
But, man, was she
a wonder to behold.
I know we live
in a superficial society,
and we're obsessed
with appearances.
It's what's
inside that counts.
But let's give
the Devil her due.
Every now and then,
I think even the most enlightened soul
would have to agree
how exquisite it must feel
to be a thing of beauty.
Al.
Hey.
What do you want?
My name is Al.
Oh.
I was going to say
that, yes, Edward,
I think about you
quite often.
I enjoy
our weekly sessions.
I'd even go so far as to say
I look forward to them.
Really?
I never fib on my own time.
Only when I'm getting paid.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did you want me to sign
back on to your service?
Do you want me
to start telling lies?
No.
Then let's not bother, hmm?
Are you sure?
I mean, I didn't mean to...
Shh, shh, shh.
It's no trouble.
I must say that you've
piqued my interest.
May I ask what prompted you
to call me just now?
Would you be offended
if I said desperation?
[Laughs]
No.
It's just been
a rough night...
rough year...
life... whatever.
Poor lamb.
Sleeping alone,
are we?
As usual.
Tsk, tsk, tsk,
tsk, tsk.
So how long
has it been, hmm?
Let's see.
I'll be 20 next month,
so that would make it...
20 years.
Hey, come now.
A tasty little morsel
like yourself?
Oh, you're
being sarcastic.
I am not.
If I lived in Akron,
I'd snap you up
like oceanfront property.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
It's only seven hours
by car.
[Laughs]
Oh, once upon a time,
but I'm retired now.
Oh?
Boyfriend?
You could say that.
What's his name?
His name was Keith.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Let's not go there,
shall we?
Let's talk about something
a little more cheerful,
like, um...
what do you want
to be when you grow up, huh?
Stable?
[Laughs]
Yes, and?
Actually,
I'd like to be a vet
or work at a zoo
or something.
Anything where I don't
have to deal with people.
I know the feeling.
[Chuckles]
Yeah.
I grew up on a farm
with some real shit-kickers.
They all thought
I was the freak of the week.
Believe me,
I understand.
The first time
I ever came to Manhattan,
I saw these two buff leather boys
French-kissing in public.
Whoa.
I nearly had an aneurysm
on the spot.
I'd like to see
New York sometime.
Oh, absolutely;
you must.
We could go to the zoo.
Really?
Well, I have a vacation
coming up in March.
Maybe we should
get together?
[Computer growls]
A guy?
You met a guy.
No, no, no.
Is he cute?
He's not unattractive.
He must be a cutie
to shake you up, Mr. Freeze.
Tight, young body; dirty mind; decent cock
notwithstanding.
Woof.
Yeah, so he calls
last night...
just to talk.
[Inhales]
I just... I wanted
to wrap him up in my arms
just to keep him safe.
You know, maybe make him
a nice, warm cup of milk or something,
you know?
Al, you are so goddamned
cute right now.
When are you
going to meet this guy?
Darling bud,
this is a complete stranger.
I-I don't have strangers
over to my apartment.
I don't even
have friends over.
Normal people,
they don't do that...
I'm sorry;
normal?
Normal?
Sweetie, I hope you're
not under the impression
that you're leading some kind
of normal, healthy lifestyle?
Did you ever consider
that maybe this is a freebie?
Like maybe even God
thinks you need to get laid,
so He's making it as easy
as humanly possible...
and you're still
fucking it up?
I say "What the hell?"
If this kid wants to come
and visit you, then why not?
What the fuck
do you have to lose...
[beeps]
Al?
[Computer roars]
Al, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to upset...
(man)
Come on, baby.
Play with that pussy.
Play with that beautiful butterscotch pussy for
me.
There you go, ;
yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Ooh.
Oh, yeah, baby;
you make me so wet.
You make me so fucking horny
with your big fucking cock.
Come on, yeah.
Come all over me, baby.
Do it.
Here it comes;
here it comes.
Here comes the butterscotch.
Yay-y-y-y.
[Computer roars]
(Jordan)
Al, I didn't mean to upset you.
Okay.
Then I'll
make a deal with you.
If I'm going
to consider doing this...
oh, man,
and believe me,
I still think
it's ridiculous...
but if I am,
then I want to see you
take a risk as well.
Sounds like fun.
What did you
have in mind?
[Snickers]
I want to see you
on AngelCam.
What?
I know she excites you.
Yeah, but l...
Yeah, but nothing.
I don't think you risk
your heart enough.
Besides,
I dare you.
Oops.
I think you said
the magic words.
Au revoir, baby.
Good luck, sweetie.
All right.
What the hell?
(John)
Anyway, back to my lousy night.
So I'm there at the club.
I don't have enough money to buy myself
a frigging Budweiser.
But Moe's girlfriend, Moira,
takes pity, buys me a drink.
[Dance music]
Come on, man.
Come on, boy;
get up.
Get up.
No, I don't dance.
Aww.
[Titters]
I can't figure you out.
Why is everyone always
trying to figure me out?
Maybe because they want
to get to know you better.
What do you want to know?
Tell me about your ex.
My fiancee?
How long were you
together for?
Three years
and one month.
Wow.
I've never been
with anybody that long.
What's the secret?
The secret is just caring
about the person so much
that you're willing
to work things out
when things get tough,
and not just up
and leave.
What?
Nothing.
So how are things
going with Moe?
Good.
Really?
Yeah.
What? What?
Why wouldn't they be?
No reason.
Did he say
something or...?
No.
No, I'm glad things
are going well.
I have to go pee.
What?
Bathroom.
Oh, no,
I'm fine.
(John)
So I wander off
to explore the club,
wondering how my evening
could possibly get any worse...
when suddenly it hits me.
[Jordan moaning]
I could find my roommate fucking my date
on a bathroom sink.
[Laughs]
That would be much worse.
Not that I was even especially angry,
you know, or surprised,
because I'd seen Jordan
making eyes at him all night.
But I mean, how much sex
does this guy need?
(Moe)
Holy fucking shit.
Yeah, I figured
you hadn't seen it.
(John)
I just... I don't understand
how he could be bored
with his new
girlfriend already.
That fucking asshole.
[Computer beeps]
Why do guys like you think
you can treat me like that?
No, seriously;
I'm interested.
Is it that I'm a lousy lay?
Or is it my personality?
Or am I wearing a sign
that says "Shit all over me"?
Hey, wait.
Moira, come on;
wait a minute.
You can't believe this.
Oh, what the fuck
are you talking about?
Of course
I believe it!
It's on
the fucking internet!
All right, listen;
it's not like the in...
No! No!
Do not try and worm
your way out of this.
I've had it up to fucking here with that shit.
All right,
calm down.
Huh?
Calm down.
You told me
that you that loved me,
and then you went
and fucked her.
You fucked her,
and then you came back
and fucked me.
You fucking asshole!
Hey, listen to me;
listen, all right?
Listen to what?
Listen to what,
you pathetic shit?
Hey, wait... what the fuck
is wrong with you, huh?
What the fuck is wrong...
what, are we married?
No-o-o;
no, we're not married.
Right.
We're not going out;
we're nothing.
You're a fucking joke.
You're a fucking
dildo with legs.
I can't even fucking begin
to describe what you are.
I'm a joke;
right, right.
I'm a joke, right.
We barely know
each other five minutes
and already you're
all like, "I love you, Moe.
"Please tell me
you love me, Moe.
"I love you;
do you love me?
"Moe, please tell me
you love me.
Shut up.
Tell me..."
Shut up!
[Crashes]
Oh... oh, my God, Moe.
Moe.
Don't you fucking...
Moe...
No!
Fuck it;
you're right.
I fucking suck.
You fucking
figured it out.
I tried to make you happy,
but what?
I'm a fucking asshole.
You're right.
Wait.
No, no way, ; what?
No; one less asshole
in your life, right?
Congratu-fucking-lations.
All right;
fine, fine.
Get the fuck out of here,
you fucking jerk.
You're a waste
of my fucking time anyway.
Good luck
with your fucking life,
because you're
going to fucking need...
[door slams]
God damn it!
[Telephone ringing]
[Electronic voice]
Please leave a message.
Beep
(Moira)
Uh, Moe?
[Slurred]
So I know you're there
and everything, but um...
I'm just calling to tell you
that I won't call anymore, okay?
So okay.
Bye.
[Sobs]
[Hushed]
Hey, Moira.
Oh, hey.
Hey, Eddie.
Oh, wait.
Moira, how many...
how many pills
are you taking?
[Crunches]
Mmm.
Moira?
[Slurred]
Don't worry.
All right, just the, um...
just the usual.
[Ed sighs]
What's going on?
I'm a fucking wreck.
I thought I could do it,
but I can't.
Do what?
Remember that guy
I told you about?
The one I met online?
Uh-huh.
Well, he just called,
and he invited me
to his place in New York.
Well, that's what
you wanted, right?
[Man mumbling]
Oh, yeah.
[Whispering]
Yeah, I did.
But what if he turns out to be
a total psycho or something?
You wouldn't
want that.
Nobody wants
a psycho.
Tell me about it.
I could wind up as headcheese
in this guy's freezer.
[Man moaning]
Oh, Eddie.
Oh, you little
cocksucker.
[Moaning]
(Moira)
See, you're scared,
but not because you think
he's going to kill you.
What?
You should be scared that...
he's not going to love you...
that nobody's going to love you.
You're going to end up
all alone
with nothing.
(Ed)
You know,
you're not doing a very
good job of cheering me up.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey.
Hey, hey.
Moira.
How many pills was that?
Seriously, girl, how many
have you swallowed?
I don't know;
a bunch.
Moira, listen to me.
I think you
should call 911.
[Sighs]
Moira, wake up.
[Banging]
Moira.
Don't worry, daddy.
Can you hear me?
Moira.
[Sighs]
Moira, wake up.
Can you hear me?
Moira!
God damn it, Simone.
How many times I got
to fucking tell you, man.
Now get the fuck
off my fucking computer.
Edward, I was hoping
that you'd call.
Al, listen.
This girl I know online
just overdosed.
Her name
is Moira something.
What?
You've got
to call 911.
She lives
in Manhattan somewhere,
but I don't know the address... knock it off!
She's on FinalExit. Net
right now!
FinalEx...
[bleeps]
Final exit.
[Typing]
Excuse me.
Is your name Moira?
(man)
Now, Ernest Hemingway...
he didn't mess around.
(Al)
Excuse me.
Does anyone know
who this woman is
in the lower
left-hand corner?
Moira?
Yeah, yeah;
Moira what?
What's her last name?
(woman)
Who?
The girl who just
broke up with her boyfriend.
Oh, her.
God, I thought she'd
never shut up.
[Mockingly]
"Moe!
Mo-o-o-o-oe!"
Moe?
[Computer roaring]
[Knocking at door]
[Roaring]
Oh, fuck.
[Gun cocking]
Back off, scumbag.
I'm packing heat.
(Al)
Jordan, it's me.
Al?
Yeah... open up;
I need your help.
You scared
the shit out of me.
Jordan, thank God.
Gee, Al,
when I said we should
get together sometime,
I wasn't thinking,
like, 4:00 a.m.
Yeah, well,
you weren't online.
Nice to finally meet you,
by the way.
What the fuck
are you doing here anyway?
Okay, you remember
the guy you told me about?
The one you fucked
in the nightclub bathroom?
Oh, which one?
Moe.
You said he had
a girlfriend named Moira?
Yeah? So?
Is this her?
(Jordan)
Could be.
Why?
She just overdosed on pills
someplace in Manhattan.
I don't know where.
Whoa, I am not trying to...
Hey, hey, hey.
You are in this too, okay?
I need her last name
so we can call 911.
What is it?
Moira what?
I don't know,
but I know
somebody that does.
[Computer chimes]
Intercon-X?
Shh.
Moe from Intercon-X?
You fucked the boss?
Quiet.
[Laughs]
Oh, good.
Hey, John.
John Roth.
Jordan?
What's up?
Listen, John,
is your roommate there?
Yeah...
no.
He's, uh, he's
with his girlfriend.
Moira, right?
Is that her?
(Al)
Come on...
Yeah, it could be; yeah.
She overdosed on pills,
and we got to call
an ambulance now.
Whoa, whoa, whoa;
yo, start over.
What?
(Al)
Quick, ; do you know
where she lives?
(Moe)
You fucking asshole!
[Smashing]
(John)
Moe!
Hey, everybody.
Say hello to my faggoty-ass roommate, John.
John Harrison Roth
from Austin, Texas,
whose interests include jerking off
into nasty, old sweat socks
and fucking over
his friends.
Moe.
John.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Just telling
a bunch of strangers
about your
personal life, buddy.
It's for my
fucking website.
Moira!
Ooh!
She has to see your pussy-ass website,
you fucking...
It's my life.
It's my fucking life.
You can have your stupid,
little homo page,
But you leave me
the fuck out of it!
Moira!
What the fuck about her?
She needs an ambulance.
(Moe)
What?
Ooh!
What's her address?
[Faint buzzing]
(Moira)
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Hello?
Nurse?
Hello!
Moira?
Hello?
John.
Moira, what's wrong?
Thank God, um...
Do you hear that noise?
What noise?
L- I think it's...
I think it's coming
from the TV...
I can't stop it.
[Clunks]
[Buzzing ceases]
Is that better?
Yeah.
[John sighs]
Thanks.
[Breathes deeply]
[Clears throat]
Huh.
So what did I miss?
Before or after
they pumped your stomach?
Ug.
Forget I asked.
[Exhales audibly]
Um.
Moe's down
in the snack bar, so...
but they told us
you were still asleep.
Yeah, I just woke up.
Oh, right.
Okay, well, I'm going
to go down to the snack bar
and get him.
Well, wait.
I'm...
I'd rather if you stayed
and talked to me for a little bit.
Oh, okay.
Sure.
Look, I don't know
what to say.
Um, you know,
what I did...
I just never thought that...
I mean, that's just it.
I never thought;
I just... I didn't, you know...
I didn't think.
Hey, this is not
your fault.
I mean, look,
I'm officially crazy.
Only in the state
of New York.
Yeah.
I really am sorry, Moira.
I know.
And if, you know,
there's anything...
anything I can do...
Thanks.
Don't be afraid to ask.
No, it's okay.
I'm okay now.
Yeah?
Mmm.
Huh.
You know, my dad ended up
in a place like this.
He would have me
sneak him booze
right here
in the hospital.
Now that was a guy
that didn't want to stick around.
But that's not you, right?
No.
Good.
I'm glad.
(John)
Okay, so according to this,
Doofus always takes the biggest slice of pie
for himself,
whereas Dandy always offers
the best slice to others.
Tsk; frigging Doofus.
I hate that guy.
Yeah.
What... what itches?
Your nose?
How's that?
Thank you.
How about my chin does?
Your chin?
Yeah.
Kind of my ear does too.
Your ear?
No, other one.
Inside the ear or,
like, on the...
No.
How's that?
That's good.
Thanks.
You know, people pay
good money to be tied up
and have their ears
scratched like that.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, I saw it
on the internet.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah.
[Chair squeaking]
Oh!
[Door creaking]
Hey.
Where's my monitor?
Oh, it got busted.
Oh, when you hucked
the bottle at it?
Yeah, uh...
Anyway.
How's Moira?
Fine.
What happened to you?
I left.
Yeah, we guessed that.
I know you're still mad.
I wasn't mad
until you attacked me.
Look, I'm sorry.
All right,
I was pissed off,
I was drunk,
and I overreacted.
Okay.
Still, that was
a shitty thing to do.
Excuse me?
Going after Moira
like that.
What?
What are you
talking about?
Oh, my...
"I can't believe
Moe is already bored
"with his new
girlfriend.
How much sex
does a guy need?"
Come on.
Hey, don't save it
for your website.
I'm standing right here.
All right.
Maybe I think Moira
deserves better than you.
Better.
And that would be you?
Maybe.
So, if you want
to split up the business
or buy me out
or whatever,
I've been fucking around
with the numbers...
Moe.
What?
We're potential
millionaires, remember?
Why fuck that up?
So we're still partners?
Partners.
Friends?
Let me think
about that.
[Claps]
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You got to check
this out, though.
This you will love.
Look, I got
to get us a beer; wait.
Hey, go pull up
the AngelCam screen.
Yo, I don't know
if I was hallucinating or what,
but the last time I checked,
there was this muffdiver
who looked exactly like Jordan.
Yeah, this chick
right here.
Sleeping with
my ex-fiancee.
Her?
You were going
to marry her?
Dude.
(John)
And, just like that,
it was over.
All those endless months
of missing you,
watching you,
dreaming about you;
but never hearing from you,
never talking with you,
never touching you.
[Computer chiming]
[Electronic voice]
Are you available?
(John)
You were the ghost
in my machine,
and maybe
I was the ghost in yours.
It's much easier to love
an image than a real person.
But we all have a moment
where our life is divided,
like it or not,
into a before and an after.
Everything is different
from that moment on,
and everything before it
fades into the past.
I don't know how or why
a person stays in love
with a person who doesn't
love them back.
Maybe it's hope,
maybe it's nostalgia,
or maybe suckers like me
just have this love
and we have
to put it somewhere.
As long as you were alone,
I could bounce that love
off your image
like a mirror
and somehow feel it
coming back to me.
But now I can't
even pretend anymore.
And I don't want to.
So, good-bye, Angel.
And good-bye, SkyGal68,
BlueMoon, Baitshop3,
and all you other lurkers,
'cause this is going to be
my last entry for a while.
Maybe for a long while.
You almost ready?
Yeah, I just have
to cash out.
Okay.
Subtitling by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
Well, hello there, stud.
Want to watch me pee?