Check, charge or cash?
Cash.
Make it out to...
...Jack's Demolition. Tucson.
$788.30.
Taking me to breakfast?
I can't. I'm meeting Bosko.
Hey, Vincent.
Where are my barrettes?
I saw them on the kitchen table.
I already checked.
Coffee?
No school today?
My dad's taking me to the new building
and then to lunch.
Try under the sofa cushions.
He's already a half an hour late.
He's going to show,
or stand her up like last time?
I'll make coffee.
Out of time.
Mom, my barrettes are not on the couch.
Wear the blue ones.
I don't want to wear the blue ones.
They don't match.
- Did you check in your bathroom?
- I checked everywhere!
What do you want me to do?
Find them!
- Mom, pay attention!
- All right, sweetie, all right!
Daddy's going to be here.
I won't be ready!
- I'll be late.
- No, you won't.
I will be late!
Before Daddy comes,
we can find them if we look together.
It's all right, baby. It's all right.
We'll find them together, you and me.
We'll find them.
Just relax. He won't come
before we find them. I promise you.
Give me another refill.
What's your name?
Waingro.
You're Michael?
You guys always work together?
All the time.
Real tight crew?
Real tight.
If this works good,
I'd consider going again, you know.
Yeah. Stop talking, okay, Slick?
How's he doing?
Hundred percent.
Right on schedule.
Made a right on Venice Boulevard.
We're a mile and a half from you.
Okay.
Just crossed over the number one lane,
300 yards from you.
Get set.
I am.
Here we go.
211!
We're being held up!
- 211 alarm. Armored car.
- There's the call.
Three minutes.
Clear!
Eighty seconds left!
Get back! Get back!
Get back!
Slick, see that shit coming out of
their ears? They can't fucking hear you!
Cool it!
I got it.
Got it.
You had to fuck with me.
Want to fuck with me?
What are you doing? What did he do?
He was making a move.
Dumb motherfucker.
A million six...
Forty cents on the dollar, $640,000 to you.
Here's $150,000 front money.
Get you the rest in two, three days.
Who owned these?
"Malibu Equity and Investments."
Roger Van Zant.
Owns banks in the Caymans...
...runs investment portfolios
for offshore drug money. Stuff like that.
So?
You ripped off his bearer bonds.
He's insured.
That's the point. He collects
100 percent from the insurance.
He's a player. Maybe he buys his bonds
back from us...
...for 60 percent of their value. Makes
40 percent on top of the 100 percent.
Sell it back to him,
that's an extra $320,000 to you.
Try it on.
Kelso called.
About what?
A score he's putting out,
he wants you to look at.
I don't need his score. I got my own.
Says it's clean and low eight figures.
9:00 a.m. Tomorrow.
What happened?
Don't ask.
Find the ambulance?
- Dumped it four blocks from here.
- 22nd Street.
They torched it.
Burned the guns, clothes, everything.
They were airborne. They taped the last
few seconds of the black-and-whites.
Stolen from Fresno two weeks ago.
Yellow pickup truck out of Whittier
a day before yesterday.
You taking this one?
Or does it stay in Division?
Does this look like gangbangers
working the local 7-11 to you?
Robbery-Homicide's taking it.
We got three motorists.
All they saw were men with masks.
They were distant.
TV man over there, however,
he was closer.
Did he ID anybody?
He was hiding. He heard it mostly.
What about them?
According to TV man,
this guy started mouthing off.
Smart.
Somebody called a guard "Slick."
Now, I figure this guy...
...went for that hold-out piece,
ankle holster.
From here...
...bang, bang...
...bang, bang, bang.
This side.
This guy has got what appears to be
a double tap-entry wound to the sternum.
Tattooing around the head wound,
scorched bones, close range.
Probably executed.
It was a million six in bearer bonds.
They ignored the loose cash.
'Cause they had no time.
They were on a clock.
Which means they knew
our response time to a 211...
...had our air, immobilized it, entered...
...escaped in under three minutes.
It's a good spot here.
We got good escape routes.
Two freeways...
...within a quarter of a mile.
Traffic video camera?
Probably disabled. Check it anyway.
You recognize the M.O.?
M. O...
...is that they're good.
Once it escalated into a murder-one
beef for all, after they killed two guards...
...they didn't hesitate.
Popped guard number three because...
what difference does it make?
Why leave a living witness?
Drop of a hat, these guys will rock-and-roll.
The shape charge.
The shape charge indicates
that they are technically proficient.
Proficient enough to go in on the prowl.
Let's look for recent high-line burglaries
that mystify us.
Run "Slick" as an alias to the FBI.
You're gonna get the phone book.
Do it anyway.
Who's moving the bearer bonds?
Check the usual fences. You and I will
check Cuzomano and Torena.
I want you to take Goldstein and Alfaro.
Hang in with Forensics.
From the bomb squad,
I want the explosive.
If we're lucky, it's exotic.
We can trace the sale.
Get your hand out of that man's pocket.
Anyone want some pie?
Gotta go to the john.
I had to get it on. He was making a move.
I had to get it on.
Split's in the car.
I took out of ours evenly...
...to make up for his full end...
...'cause I want to pay off and get rid
of this motherfucker right now.
Hold it!
Where's the rest?
We're late. You look too good to go out.
I'll just jump you right here.
- Where is it?
- Squared the bookies, baby.
There's more in a couple of days,
so don't sweat it. We're late.
Come on.
You gotta be kidding me.
Honey...
...it ain't worth the risks you take
for $8,000. Like in "Risk versus reward."
Let's go.
Get your coat.
There is no point talking.
You're a child growing older.
What does that mean?
We're not making forward progress
like real grown-up adults living our lives...
...because I married a gambling junkie.
Get in the fucking car.
What am I doing in here?
You're not!
You want me to leave the bank book
and the car keys...
...in the kitchen on the way out the door?
- Are we going?
- Keep that crap. Dominick comes with me.
Don't even think about...
Tell me Albert Torena called back.
Albert Torena call Vincent?
No.
Report came in.
The explosive was Dy-Ex,
used in demolition.
You can pick it up in Nevada...
...Arizona, New Mexico.
Too common to trace a sale.
That's wonderful.
You all right?
What happened? Where have you been?
Work.
Lauren's dad show up?
Didn't call...
...didn't show. We waited for you till 10:30.
Now, does this guy have any idea
what's going on with this kid?
I don't know.
Fucking jerk.
Is she okay?
She's been in her room all day.
So, no, she's not okay. Neither am I.
I made dinner...
...for us, four hours ago.
Every time I try to maintain
a consistent mood between us...
...you withdraw.
I got three dead bodies on a sidewalk...
...off Venice Boulevard, Justine.
I'm sorry...
...if the goddamn...
...chicken...
...got overcooked.
Coffee, sir?
Please.
Will you pass the cream?
Thanks.
What'd you get?
What?
What are you reading?
Book about metals.
Stress Fractures in Titanium.
What kind of work do you do?
Lady, why are you so interested
in what I read or what I do?
I've seen you in the store.
What store?
Hennessey and Ingalls. I work there.
If you don't want to talk to me, it's okay.
I'm sorry I bothered you.
I didn't mean to be rude.
I didn't recognize you.
I work in metals. I'm a salesman.
My name's Neil.
I'm Eady.
You like working there?
Sure.
I get a discount and there's
a whole section of books in my area.
What area?
Graphic design.
I do letterheads and logotypes
at night and...
...the store's a day job
until I get enough going.
Who do you do that for?
A restaurant.
I did their menus, and...
...a small record label.
CDs.
I've done two so far.
You go to school for that?
Yeah.
I went to Parsons.
Where's that?
New York City.
How long you been here?
About a year.
Like it?
Not really. I'm mostly here for the work.
Live in this neighborhood?
No, I live kind of above Sunset Plaza.
It's a little house I rent.
And it's kind of rundown,
but a beautiful, beautiful view.
What about you?
I live up here.
That's very funny.
Where's your family from originally?
They're Scots-lrish.
They emigrated to Appalachia...
...in the late 1700s.
Where are you from?
The Bay area.
Your folks there?
My mother died a long time ago,
and my father...
...I don't know where he is.
Got a brother somewhere.
You have a tight family. I can tell.
Right?
You're right.
City of lights...
In Fiji, they have these...
...iridescent algae that come out
once a year in the water.
That's what it looks like out there.
You been there?
No, I'm going there some day.
You travel a lot?
Yeah.
Travelling makes you lonely?
I'm alone. I am not...
...lonely.
You?
Real lonely.
Albert!
Shit!
What you doing here? You crazy?
This ain't Disneyland.
You were supposed to get back to me.
Where the fuck you been?
I couldn't break free.
Let's violate his ass right now.
I do for you...
...you don't do for me, is that it?
Listen, man. I swear, I was out all night.
I'm hidden like a Flamingo matador.
That's got nothing to do with me.
I'm cutting it smooth. I'm generating
leads and shit for you. I'm a dancer.
You bullshit.
I paged your ass all day.
I hate fucking paging.
You're a speed freak,
jacking methamphetamine again.
Where's your empathy?
It's a substance abuse problem.
Empathy was yesterday. Today you're
wasting my motherfucking time.
You fall in love?
Did you fall in love...
...and went off somewhere?
Tell me that, I'll settle for it.
Give me all you got!
I swear, my brother Richard's going
to talk to you.
I heard Richard?
He's going to talk to you.
He's gonna meet you tonight.
He's not here, is he?
No, he'll meet you tonight.
What happened to now?
I implored him because I knew
you was coming this a.m.
Bullshit.
I swear. He said no...
...'cause he in Phoenix.
"By the time I get to Phoenix
"He'll be rising
"He'll probably leave a note
"Right on the door"
Tonight's the best I can do for you.
He'll meet you at BJ's on Alvarado.
At 2:00 a.m.
Be there.
You be there too.
I can't be there, man. I got things to do.
I got things to do, I got places to be.
Be there.
Don't waste my motherfucking time!
What is it?
It's a bank.
It depos cash on Thursday for distribution
to all the other branches...
...to cover Friday payroll checks.
So on Thursdays,
the command branch has got a full whack.
On the prowl or strong?
Through the door.
How many guys?
About four, or three, plus a driver.
You walk in, knock 'em over, walk out.
You want $100,000 in advance
against a ten-percent cut for that?
Sounds like a cowboy score.
They hit the hold-up alarms,
I gotta get out before the cops show.
They hit three hold-up alarm systems.
Two Telco and a cellular.
But the signals aren't
going anywhere because...
...the night before...
...you cut in...
...and trick out
the alarm system computer...
...to turn itself...
...and the video recorders off...
...20 minutes before you enter.
Architectural, electrical plans?
I got that.
I got the boards already built.
They go into the CPU.
What's the estimate?
12.1, 12.2 million.
You're on.
Congratulations.
Let me give you a little idea
of where my estimates come from.
Nobody knew the merch was yours.
My way, you get 100 percent
from the insurance company...
...take the bonds back from us...
...at 60 cents on the dollar
and make yourself another 40 percent.
The operation doesn't skip a beat.
We all make out.
Sure, you got a deal.
Good, because there's no percentage
if everyone gets upset.
You have your man call me
and we'll set the meet.
Yeah, okay.
Nice talking to you.
You gonna deal with these guys?
Word's on the street
it's okay to steal my stuff.
I'm going to kill these sons of bitches.
Have Harry bring me the spreadsheets
for Canary Island's Offshore.
That's not really an estimate.
Those are exact figures.
I have a printout of the bank's cash flow
for the past two months.
How'd you get this information?
Just comes to you.
This stuff just flies through the air.
It's just beamed out all over the place.
You just have to grab it.
I know how to grab it.
Okay, here we go.
13.9 million.
- I bought it.
- Good.
What did I tell you?
Here.
We're on. Call Van Zant,
collect the money.
How is he?
He's a businessman.
Chris is at my place.
What's wrong?
Husband and wife stuff.
I'll let him sleep it off.
What happened to you?
When will you get some furniture?
When I get around to it.
Charlene's gonna leave me.
Why?
Not enough steaks in the freezer.
With everything we've been doing?
Vegas and the Super Bowl cleaned me out.
When you gonna get an old lady?
When I get around to it.
You got something else on the side?
Nothing regular.
She got something else on the side?
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I don't know what you're doing.
As Jimmy said, "You want to be
making moves on the street?
"Have no attachments.
Allow nothing to be in your life...
"...that you can't walk out on in 30 seconds
if you spot the heat around the corner."
Remember that?
For me, the sun rises
and sets with her, man.
We take delivery of cash from Van Zant...
...then I drop a deposit on Kelso
for this bank.
Bank? What bank?
What about the platinum thing?
It's ready to fall.
That goes too. Then the bank.
Want some breakfast?
Are you okay?
Yeah, sugar.
For real.
I'll do good.
I'll see you later.
You Solenko?
Don Breedan.
Grierson, my parole officer, told me to
come by here, see if you had a job for me.
You're familiar with this kind of operation?
I'm a great grill man.
Good. Good for you.
You'll mop the toilets, hit the dishwasher,
bus tables and empty the garbage.
Give me a hard time, I'll report you loaded,
drunk or stealing.
I'll violate you back fast.
Twenty-five percent of your take-home
kicks back to me.
Rules of the game. Call Grierson,
check it out. Change in the back.
What are you waiting for?
Malibu Equity and Investments.
Roger Van Zant.
Please hold.
This is Roger Van Zant.
I'm supposed to get something.
Someone will call you back
from another line.
818-133-6089.
I got a package for you. There's a drive-in
on Centinela. 2:30 tomorrow.
Just send one man, alone.
- Who was that guy?
- Nobody.
I gotta know who he is! Who is he?
He's nobody, Neil.
He's a legit liquor salesman
from Las Vegas. Alan Marciano.
Chris will make up.
- It's too late! I'm sick of him!
- Shut up!
Here's the deal. You'll give Chris
one last shot.
After that, he fucks up,
then I will finance setting you up myself...
...on my own, anywhere you want.
Dominick will go with you.
And my word counts. But right now...
...you will give him the chance.
Clean up, go home.
Clean up, go home!
Give me your money.
You'll get smoked with that shit.
Won't be you.
He's coming in alone. Send him through.
Vincent, hey, man.
This is my brother, Richard. Vincent.
It's all right.
What have you got for me?
Before we even get into that, there's
this crew ripping rides all along the beach.
Now, in the back of a trim shop...
...that somebody wants to pay
a little visit this weekend...
...they might find two Turbos
and a 911 slope.
You looking to rid yourself
of your competition?
I'm a good citizen.
I'm Donald Duck.
You got something to tell me?
Check this out, cuz.
How do I know if I tell you
what you need to know...
...that you gonna do
what the fuck I need to get done.
Hanna is straight up.
I ain't your cuz, you rat motherfucker.
And you know because I say so...
...after I hear what the fuck
you got to tell me!
Fuck you.
You understand?
I'd get killed for telling you.
You'd get killed walking your doggie!
All right, man...
...there was a cat I was locked up with.
Did a couple of two, three years.
He got out. I ran into him.
And so?
He's a big fiend for action.
Now, if he'd have said nothing,
I'd have thought nothing, but...
...he goes on and on, running down to me
how he ain't done nothing...
...and nothing's been going on
and all this bullshit.
Right then and there I know...
...this cat's got something going down.
Pretty fucking great.
Albert, what's wrong with you?
You drag me here, waste my time like this.
You saw a guy on the street
who's an ex-con?
That's right.
Well, I am...
...over-fucking-whelmed.
What do you want for that,
a G-man badge?
You gonna make the call on them Porches?
Is he kidding me?
I'm telling you:
Slick is no joke.
He's double time.
Say what?
"Slick." What does that mean?
That's what he calls people: "Slick."
Tell me about him.
About 6 feet tall...
...lots of jailhouse tats.
Got a big-ass peacock right here.
What's his name?
Cheritto.
Michael Cheritto.
Thirty-three busts since 1976.
Eleven for armed robbery,
three convictions.
Two out of a three-to-five year beef
in Attica.
Three years in Marion.
Five years in Folsom off a knock-back
to involuntary manslaughter.
Jacket's two inches thick.
Who do I have there now?
- Drucker and me. And Schwartz.
- Tell SIS...
...I want full surveillance. That's 24 hours.
Round the clock, day and night.
We never close. Open every day.
Bug the car, the house, the work.
When he moves or sits,
like in a restaurant...
...I want pictures of who he moves
and sits with.
Then run makes on them.
They got jackets, trail them.
I want it up and running
by tomorrow night.
Put your hands where I can see them.
I tell you what to do.
I tell you how to do it.
Now, with your right hand only,
your right hand only...
...take the package and throw it in here.
Behind you.
On the right.