Look at this.
He's alive.
This dog --
how you call it? Bull pit?
No. Pit bull.
But that's not a pit bull.
I don't know what he is.
I bet he lost somebody
some money, though.
Give me your gun.
- Shooting him?
- Yeah.
Are you sick in the head?
They left him out here
to suffer and die like that.
They -- they threw him
out the fuckin' window
and just kept on driving.
It's terrible. Come.
People wait for us.
Come on.
They're used to waiting.
Poor little guy.
Jesus, I think he broke his hip.
Oh! Ho! Shit!
-
The fucker. He's got a lot
of bite left in him, huh?
I think bull pit
is not playing with you, Monty.
Yeah. No shit.
Come.
You want police coming?
Oh, look, they used him like
a fucking ashtray, man.
What a bunch of assholes.
Let's get him in the trunk.
What?!
There's a vet emergency room
over here. I like this guy.
He tries to bite
your face off.
He is meat.
You want dog --
I buy you nice puppy tomorrow.
No, no. What the fuck I want
with a puppy? Come on.
Where you go, Monty?
Monty, wait.
What the --
I not go near bull pit, Monty.
This thing is disgusting.
I told you --
it's not a pit bull.
Look at him.
He's a good dog.
I can see it in his eyes.
He's a tough little bastard.
He wasn't lying down
for anybody.
Sometimes I think
you very stupid man.
If we wait much longer,
he's gonna be dead, all right?
You want to shoot him
with my gun.
That was a mercy thing.
He's not ready to go yet.
He wants to live.
Oh, he tell you this now?
No, but it's like
a baby, okay?
They don't bitch and scream
like that, you know?
They see the doctor coming
with the needle.
It's good for him
in the long run.
You have no baby.
I can't even talk to you,
Kostya.
Come on.
Come on, you little
son of a bitch.
Hey. Will you quit
standing there?
Will you fucking
help me out here?
Just -- just distract him
for me or something.
Come on!
Get the --
I'm trying to help you,
you little prick!
Huh? Come on. Come on.
Who's more macho?
Monty is more macho!
What goes on
in your little head?
A little of the tricks,
a little of the quicks.
Boom. Bam. He's nabbed.
Yeah, little tricks,
little quicks.
You are bleeding.
You get bite.
Dog's blood.
God, you got to learn
to relax a little bit.
Live a little.
You have hole in neck
and blood is coming out.
Little love bite
for saving his raggedy ass.
Rule number one -- you cannot
grab half-dead animals.
We have people
waiting for us.
People with money.
Ow.
You want to play this cowboy!
No -- dogboy
in middle of highway.
Dogboy?
That's funny, Kostya.
- Yes, funny.
- You mastered the language.
You're bad luck, Monty.
You bring bad luck on me.
Always everything
that can go wrong, go wrong.
It is not just you and me
anymore when we go out.
It's you and me and Doyle.
Who's Doyle?
Doyle! Doyle's Law.
- It's Murphy.
- What?
Who is Murphy?
Who's Murphy? Who's Doyle?
It's Murphy's Law --
"Whatever can go wrong
will go wrong."
- Him! Yes.
- Yes, him.
What's up there, Monty?
Hey, Doyle.
-
- Easy, Doyle. Easy. Easy.
What do you want, Simon?
I'm hungry.
I woke up an hour ago.
I was hungry.
Nothing I can do about that.
Go up to 1 10th Street.
1 10th Street?
Come on, man.
I can't go up there.
I mean -- whoa.
-
I, um -- I'm not --
I'm not looking for a mercy pop
or anything, you know.
I'm done, Simon.
This morning, right,
I was shaving,
and I cut myself --
look, look -- like four times.
Come on, Monty!
Give me a break, man!
I can't go up to Harlem.
Look at me.
The -- the "Yos" --
they'll eat me alive
up there, man.
I'm out of business, Simon.
Okay? Take your Jones
somewhere else. Leave me alone.
Are you afraid that I'm --
I'm gonna narc you out?
You know who I am.
It's me. It's Simon.
You're not listening to me.
I got touched.
Okay? I'm over.
Game over.
Five years I've been coming
to you, man -- five years!
Get out of here.
Get the fuck out of here.
Fine.
I'm -- I'm -- I'm leaving.
There's no need for you to be
all nasty about it, all right?
But I'll --
I'll remember this.
All right?
This is Dante.
Aw, what's his name?
Doyle.
Hi, Doyle.
I'm telling you,
I don't think I'm gonna even
be eligible this year.
Excuse me, sir?
Can I help you?
Hello?
Sorry, what?
Did you have an appointment
with someone?
Oh, no.
I used to go here.
I'm gonna have to ask you
to leave
and to take the dog
with you.
Yeah. Okay.
Okay. We'll just be a minute.
No dogs allowed
on the school grounds.
Okay. Okay. I understand.
Check this out.
Come here. He's all right.
Look at what
a little punk I was.
In the middle with the ball.
I guess you weren't
the center.
No. No.
I started, though.
Freshman year. I was
on the varsity. Point guard.
Yeah?
Still hold the all-time
assist record.
Mmh, no. Marvin Ray
broke the record last year.
He did not.
He did too.
Are you sure?
I'm positive.
I coach the girls team.
Well...we were
undefeated that year.
Then I got kicked off
the team for fighting,
and the whole thing
fell apart.
That's too bad.
Hey, you know
where Jacob Elinsky is?
He's an old friend of mine.
"Now let us sport us
while we may,
"and now, like amorous birds
of prey,
"rather at once
our time devour
"than languish
in his slow-chapt power.
"Let us roll all our strength
and all our sweetness
"up into one ball, and tear
our pleasures with rough strife
"thorough the iron gates
of life --
"thus, though we cannot make
our sun stand still,
yet we will make him run."
Good.
That's good.
That's an excellent reading.
What do people think?
What's going on here?
- Luke.
- Can I go to the bathroom?
No, you went 20 minutes ago.
Uh, I have a, um --
a bladder infection.
The poem.
"To His Coy Mistress."
Andrew Marvell.
Well, it's not real deep
or anything.
The guy wants to get laid,
and he's telling her
to give it up.
Excuse me...for one minute.
Hey...
- What's going on?
- Hey, who's that?
Look who's here.
It's your buddy.
Sorry to --
sorry to drop in on you.
I just wanted to
talk to you for a second.
W-What's going on?
Nothing.
What is this
you got going on here?
Teaching my class.
I guess.
- In a circle like that?
- Yeah.
Wow.
That's cool. I like that.
Hey, class.
Hey.
Sorry to interrupt.
Just a little, slight
change of plans.
I got to see
my father tonight,
and there's these people --
they're throwing me kind of a...
going-away party, right?
Yeah.
And, uh, so maybe you and Frank
could meet up somewhere.
Maybe that place with the...
things that Frank goes to.
And I'll find you later?
Okay.
- Yeah?
- Of course.
All right.
This one's cute
with the red shirt.
I think she's giving me
the eye.
How do you do it, man?
I don't know how you do it.
-
- So I'll see you later.
Yeah, maybe like midnight,
I think.
Midnight. Midnight's...
- Yeah? All right.
- Okay.
Come on, buddy.
Have a nice day.
Sorry about that.
Oh, Christ.
You have a minute?
Sure.
Yeah, come -- come on in.
I thought that no students
were allowed
in the teachers' lounge.
I won't squeal on you.
Yeah. Take a seat?
What can I do for you?
I want to know why I got
a B-minus on my paper.
You got what you earned.
Nobody else in that class
can write, and you know it!
Everyone knows it.
Don't worry about
everyone else.
You're not competing
with them.
But I am.
I am competing with them.
When I apply to colleges --
you might have heard of this --
they look at these things
called "grades."
And if your grades aren't
good enough, then --
Your grade's gonna be fine.
Vincent Piscella writes a story
about his grandmother dying,
and you give him an A-plus.
Meanwhile,
the night of the funeral,
you know where Rhodes Scholar
Vince is?
Getting smashed at a basketball
party and slapping girls' asses.
I mean, what is that?
A charity A-plus?
I mean,
everyone is always writing
about their grandmothers dying,
and you know why?
It's not because
it's so traumatic.
It's because
it's a guaranteed A-plus!
And you're
all sentimental like,
"Oh, Vince, that was very
powerful, very moving."
No, it wasn't.
You didn't care.
I didn't care.
Nobody cared.
That's what grandmothers do.
They die!
Sometimes...guys have a hard
time showing their emotions.
So...
Slapping my ass --
that's, uh --
Vince's way of mourning
his dead grandmother?
What did your mother say
when you -- when you got that?
When I got what?
Yeah.
"Where did you get
the money for that?"
Oh.
- And?
- And what did I say or...
Where did I get the money?
Well, what did you say?
I said, "He likes me."
Oh.
Does he?
No.
Why do you care so much?
Just curious.
So, um...
You're not gonna
change the grade?
No. I'm not gonna change
the grade.
Great! You know what?
This was a big waste of my time!
Hold on.
Oh, God.
-
- Just -- just cover my...
Don't freeze up on me,
you son of a...
-
- Yeah, Slaughtery.
No, I can't talk right now.
Employment number's coming out.
- I just wanted to let --
- Call you later.
I'm supposed to
meet you at Mont--
Hey, Frank, you coming out
with us tonight or what?
No, I got to meet
some friends tonight.
Big date, huh?
Who's the new bimbo?
Can I bang her first?
Yeah, you wish, brother.
No, it's more of
a going-away party.
Now, listen,
Frank, the other thing...
you still holding onto
all those O.E.X. contracts?
You better believe it.
Why? You nervous?
Claims numbers have dropped
three weeks straight,
and I don't feel comfortable
with this.
Claim numbers drop so everybody
thinks employment's gonna be up?
Look at me when I talk to you.
Everybody's thinking this
because it's pretty
much always true.
When it rains outside,
people get wet.
Right or wrong, Frank?
Not this time, Sal.
I got a theory. Look at this.
Oh, good!
You've got a theory.
Look, Frank --
fuck you and your theory.
You're in awfully deep here,
Frank.
You've got $60 million
of the bank's money --
$100 million.
Whoa ho!
$100-fucking-million?!
What are you two doing?
You want to be part of
the unemployment numbers?
Get back to work!
Sal, you knew they raised
my limit to $100 million.
They raised your limit a week
ago and you're maxing out?
What am I gonna do?
Sit on it?
First of all...you're not
gonna raise your voice to me.
That's first off.
You cannot put me, you,
or this firm in jeopardy
by putting $100 million
in one idea!
Right or wrong? Come on!
Right or wrong. Yeah.
Listen...
I think we're in for
a low number, all right?
Like 140, 135.
I really don't give a shit
what you think, Frank.
You come in here,
you're not even clean-shaven.
Stop playing with this fucking
ball and pay attention to me.
You come in here drinking your
red bullshit, stink like booze,
you're out all night partying --
and that's okay.
But when you become a cowboy,
that's when I draw the line.
I am still your boss,
and I am telling you now --
you sell half those contracts.
Do I make myself clear?
Do I make myself clear,
Frank?
Do I make myself clear to you?
Yeah.
Yes? Good.
Have a good day.
And by the way, we're still on
for Friday night.
Courtside, front row.
Don't be late.
It's mayhem down here
on the floor of the exchange.
Within moments, the unemployment
number's gonna be announced.
Salomon Brothers,
along with most of the street,
feel the number is
going to be high --
around 250,000.
Solly's looking for
a high number.
280,000 is their call.
Fuck Salomon Brothers.
Fuck, uh --
fuck Salomon Brothers?
Yeah, fuck Salomon Brothers.
They're hedging their bets.
Want everybody on their side
of the fence.
Uh, what's the big deal with
the employment number anyway?
- Phellan.
- It's, uh, Phelan.
Whatever. Look...
More jobs means fewer people
looking for work.
Means it's harder to find good
people to fill those jobs.
Means you got to raise wages
to get them.
Means inflation goes up.
You got it?
- Yeah.
- No, I didn't think so.
That's why I'm doing
what I'm doing,
and you're handing out
junk mail.
Now, get off my desk.
you're wearing a striped shirt
with a striped tie.
You know that, right?
Yeah,
I do it for that ladies.
Do the ladies ever
tell you that you look like
a fucking optical illusion?
Yeah?
Go away. Disappear.
Come on.
I'm out of here.
You better hop to, sonny boy.
You know, it's funny --
I don't see you picking up the
phone to sell those contracts,
and I'm pretty sure I just heard
your daddy come over here
and cut off your allowance,
so I'm a little surprised.
You're not gonna disobey
a direct order, are you?
You know, Marcuse...
do I come into your bedroom
and tell you how to blow
your boyfriend? No.
Go away.
- Hey, Schultz!
- Yo.
What are we looking at
for that unemployment number?
250, 270 --
somewhere in there.
Big number. Big.
Hey, Frank -- we all right?
We're good.
MAN ON TV:
...investors and the market
in uncharted waters.
So who really knows?
The number is coming out.
New applications --
Get me out! Now, now, now!
Hold the phone!
That can't...
We goin' for a ride now!
Whoo!
Hey, where have you been?
I got up at 7:00 this morning.
You were already gone.
Yeah. I just...
I needed to walk around
a little, you know?
Hey.
How long you been sitting
on this stoop?
All day.
I've been waiting for you.
It's a beautiful day.
Yeah, I guess it is.
Hey, Mr. Doyle.
I missed you this morning.
Come on.
Montgomery, I want you
to talk to me.
About what, Nat?
About how you're feeling.
Well, how do you think
I'm feeling?
Well, I'm asking because
I don't like to assume.
Well, good. Don't.
What do you want?
I want to be like
that girl in the X-Men --
that one that can walk
through walls.
Go on.
If I can't do that...
I don't know -- boom --
one shot to the head.
Problem solved.
Don't joke about that.
Who says I'm joking?
So, what are we doing tonight?
Before you kill yourself,
that is.
Uncle Nikolai is throwing me
a party down at Bridge.
I figure
we all head down there.
Oh, come on. I have to go.
I got no choice, okay.
We might as well
try to have some fun.
I thought it was over
with those guys.
Yeah, it's almost over.
I mean, it's never really over
with these guys, but...
That's a nasty habit you have,
you know that?
Come take a bath with me.
No, not right now.
Go on. Go ahead.
I can't see me
being a -- a father.
No?
Well, I could see
you fathering children.
You think I want to
raise my own chalupas?
I don't raise my own chalupas.
Well, we're definitely
not having any kids together
if you're gonna be
calling them "chalupas."
Oh, I -- I think
we would have very...
Very beautiful babies.
- You don't think?
- I think.
All right, show me that.
What?
No. Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't believe you did that.
I can't believe you --
Why? Why?
You've lived in the
United States your entire life.
You've been to Puerto Rico
twice on vacation.
You know,
I'm very proud of my heritage.
Yeah, but what does that mean?
So I should get an lrish flag
tattooed on my ass
just 'cause my grandparents
were from there?
There's not enough room
on your skinny, white, flat ass
for an lrish flag.
Yeah, well,
between you and me
the kids are gonna be
just about right then.
Kids? At this rate,
we're not having any.
It's probably your mother.
Coming.
Doyle, cut it out.
Kostya, you have
the worst timing ever.
Sorry to bother you,
ma'am.
Is Montgomery Brogan in?
Monty.
Monty!
Montgomery Brogan?
Yeah, that's me.
I'm Agent Flood with the Drug
Enforcement Administration.
I can see that.
What is all this?
We've got a warrant
to search your apartment.
Are you serious?
Go -- go ahead.
Hey, easy, Doyle.
I don't see any tags
on that dog.
He's inside.
He doesn't need tags.
He better stay calm or I'll have
the pound come get him.
Seen too many men bit
by these mean bastards.
Doyle.
Come on.
Sit.
Oh...
You, uh, mind if I have
a seat?
No. Be my guest.
Uh, Miss Riviera? Heh.
That's your name, right?
I need you to stay
right here, ma'am.
Can't have you
sneaking around.
You know, this sofa's not
very comfortable.
Ah, maybe it's your posture.
Your posture
is very important.
No, it's this, uh,
Castro convertible.
It's very uncomfortable.
It's kind of -- kind of lumpy.
You know,
I just don't understand it.
It looks like
such a nice sofa.
How much did you pay for
this sofa, Miss Riviera?
Maybe it's the padding.
Booyah!
Could be the padding.
Yeah.
Probably the padding.
Go on. Get it over with.
Hmm.
There's something lumpy
in here, Mr. Brogan.
You know, it's a good thing
I found this.
It's gonna make your sofa so
much more comfortable to sit on.
Sh-e-e-e-it.
Mr. Brogan,
I do believe you're fucked.
Royally.
Sh-e-e-e-it.
Baby...
Baby?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
This will be the best night
of my life.
Best night of my life.
I just -- you know, I've been
waiting around all day long --
I just want to know if we're
gonna spend any time together.
I know. I know.
Could you just talk to me?
Talk to me, okay?
We haven't been talking.
This is our last night --
No. No, no, no.
It's not our last night.
It's my last night.
Not your last night.
You got all kinds of nights.
You got nights
with your girlfriends...
going out clubbing,
sitting at bars...
"You and me" equals "our."
This is our last night.
You can sit at home watching
movies with your mother.
You got all kinds of nights.
Look, I don't understand what
you're not understanding here.
Hey, you know what?
I can't do this right now, okay?
Babe, I need you
to just be quiet.
Please just be quiet.
But we haven't talked
about this at all.
Lately you can't even
look at me in the eye.
I have to go. Meet us
at the place in Chinatown.
Where are you going?
I've got to see my father
tonight, you know?
Do -- do me a favor, and wear
that silver dress tonight, okay?
You want me to?
Yeah...yeah.
That's how I want to
remember you.
Mmm, very nice. Very nice.
Hello, beautiful lady.
Beautiful baby.
You look like Halle Berry.
They tell you this?
Come back.
I make you half-black,
half-Russian baby.
So many beautiful woman.
I love this neighborhood.
How much is rent?
You can't afford it.
Trust me.
What are you doing here?
Something is wrong?
No, I'm having the time
of my life.
What do you think,
you dumb shit?
Uncle Nikolai wants me
talking with you.
Wants to make sure
you come to club tonight.
You're like the third person in
two days that's said that to me.
What the fuck is going on?
What does he really want?
I don't know.
You come all the way up here
just to tell me you don't know?
You do not answer my calls,
and Uncle wants to make sure
that you're tonight
at the Bridge.
I'll be there!
For Christ's sake. Tell him.
Tell him I'm --
I'm bringing some friends.
I'm bringing Naturelle.
Monty.
Wait, Monty. Please.
- Why you bring her?
- Why wouldn't l?
We have this discussion
once before, no?
You get very mad at me.
Oh, you know what?
Will you stop with that already?
I already told you --
it wasn't her.
How you know this?
Why would she?
Maybe her aunt is illegal alien.
You know, these Mexicans...
Hey, hey, she's Puerto Rican.
That makes her a citizen
of the United States.
That's more
than I can say for you.
Maybe the feds,
they -- they bust --
The feds. You know,
you're fucking cracking up.
Filling my head with this shit.
You're crazy.
You ask her?
No, I didn't ask her.
Listen.
Before you leave...
you should know.
I'll see you down there.
Those guys coming back
in here yet?
Not much.
Well, you know --
little by little.
It was hard on those guys.
I went to elementary school
with that guy Nick.
You remember -- Nicky?
Oh, Nick. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Good kid.
Place looks good, though.
Hmm.
Want to take your coat off?
Um, no.
I was feeling a little cold.
Hmm.
Oh.
That's a hell of a steak.
Only the best for you, sweetie.
I'll send you cookies
every month.
- Peanut butter, right?
- That's it.
I, uh...I talked to Sal.
- Oh, Dad, come on.
- I'll see if he can help.
Dad, the guy's been out
of the picture for 20 years.
He still knows people.
Look, that's not the point.
I-I don't want you
to get involved, okay?
I mean it.
I'm -- I'm gonna be all right.
You know, you'll still be
a young man when you get out.
I know you don't think
about it,
but don't start
any trouble in there.
- Keep your head down.
- Don't worry about me, please.
This should never
have happened.
You could've been --
you wanted money,
you could've done anything
you wanted -- doctor, lawyer.
That's all I'm saying.
Don't lay that on me.
When Sal and his crew were
squeezing you for the payments,
I didn't hear you wishing I was
a law school student then.
Not one word from you
back then.
Where'd you think that money was
coming from -- Donald Trump?
- That was a mistake.
- Let's just forget it, then.
There were lots of mistakes.
I should've stopped drinking
when your mother passed.
Please don't do this.
1 1-year-old boy with a
dead mother and a drunk father.
I got no one to blame
but myself.
Oh, stop. Stop.
It wasn't you, Pop.
I'm gonna take a leak.
Yeah, fuck you, too.
Fuck me? Fuck you.
Fuck you and this whole city
and everyone in it.
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck the panhandlers
grubbing for money,
smiling at me behind my back.
Fuck the squeegee men
dirtying up the clean
windshield of my car.
Get a fucking job.
Fuck the Sikhs
and the Pakistanis
bombing down the avenues
in decrepit cabs,
curry steaming out their pores,
stinking up my day.
Terrorists in fucking training.
Slow the fuck down!
...getting one
of those operations
that elongate your penis.
Fuck the Chelsea Boys
with their waxed chests
and pumped-up biceps,
going down on each other
in my parks and on my piers,
jiggling their dicks
on my Channel 35!
Fuck the Korean grocers
with their pyramids
of overpriced fruit
and their tulips and roses
wrapped in plastic.
Ten years in the country,
still no speakee English.
Fuck the Russians
in Brighton Beach.
Mobster thugs sitting in cafes,
sipping tea in little glasses,
sugar cubes
between their teeth,
wheelin' and dealin'
and schemin'.
Go back
where you fucking came from.
Fuck the black-hatted Hasidim
strolling up and down
47th Street
in their dirty gabardine
with their dandruff,
selling South African
apartheid diamonds.
Come on.
Your wife deserves this.
Fuck the Wall Street brokers.
Self-styled masters
of the universe.
Michael Douglas-Gordon Gekko
wannabe motherfuckers
figuring out new ways
to rob hardworking people blind.
Send those Enron assholes
to jail for fucking life.
You think Bush and Cheney
didn't know about that shit?
Give me a fucking break.
Worldcom.
Fuck the Puerto Ricans.
Twenty to a car,
swelling up the welfare rolls.
Worst fucking parade
in the city.
And don't even get me started
on the Dominicans,
'cause they make
the Puerto Ricans look good.
Who's this fuckin' guy?!
Get the fuck outta here!
Fuck the Bensonhurst ltalians
with their pomaded hair,
their nylon warm-up suits,
their St. Anthony medallions,
swinging their Jason Giambi
Louisville Slugger baseball bats
trying to audition
for "The Sopranos."
Fuckin' crack
your fuckin' head open!
Bensonhurst! Bensonhurst!
Fuck the Upper East Side wives
with their Hermes scarves
and their $50
Balducci artichoke.
Taxi!
Overfed faces
getting pulled and lifted
and stretched all taut
and shiny.
You're not fooling anybody,
sweetheart.
Taxi!
Fuck the Uptown brothers.
They never pass the ball,
they don't want to
play defense,
they take five steps
on every layup to the hoop,
and then they want to
turn around
and blame everything
on the white man.
We not giving it up!
Slavery ended 137 years ago.
Move the fuck on.
Fuck the corrupt cops with
their anus-violating plungers
and their 41 shots,
standing behind a blue wall
of silence.
You betray our trust!
Fuck the priests
who put their hands
down some
innocent child's pants.
Fuck the church that protects
them, delivering us into evil.
And while you're at it,
fuck J.C.
He got off easy --
a day on the cross,
a weekend in hell,
and all the hallelujahs of the
legioned angels for eternity.
Try seven years
in fucking Otisville, J.
Fuck Osama bin Laden,
Al Qaeda,
and backward-ass cave-dwelling
fundamentalist assholes
everywhere.
On the names of
innocent thousands murdered,
I pray you spend the rest
of eternity with your 72 whores
roasting in a jet-fuel fire
in hell.
You towel-headed camel jockeys
can kiss my royal lrish ass.
"l notice how many
of what I once thought
"were evidences of repression,
sexual or otherwise..."
Fuck Jacob Elinsky.
Whining malcontent.
Fuck Francis Xavier Slaughtery,
my best friend,
judging me while he stares
at my girlfriend's ass.
Fuck Naturelle Riviera.
I gave her my trust,
and she stabbed me in the back.
Sold me up the river.
Fucking bitch.
Fuck my father
with his endless grief,
standing behind that bar,
sipping on club soda,
selling whiskey to firemen
and cheering the Bronx Bombers.
Let's go, Yankees!
Fuck this whole city
and everyone in it,
from the row houses of Astoria
to the penthouses
on Park Avenue,
from the projects in the Bronx
to the lofts in Soho,
from the tenements
in Alphabet City
to the brownstones
in Park Slope
to the split-levels
in Staten lsland,
Iet an earthquake crumble it,
let the fires rage,
Iet it burn to fucking ash,
and then let the waters rise
and submerge this whole
rat-infested place.
No.
No. Fuck you,
Montgomery Brogan.
You had it all,
and you threw it away,
you dumb fuck!
What do you think
of Naturelle?
She's a good girl.
Your mother would've liked her.
- Yeah, but you trust her?
- Do I trust her?
- Mm-hmm.
- Why do I have to trust her?
- You think I can trust her?
- Where you going with this?
Oh, I don't know.
People are...
saying weird things.
I'm hearing stuff around,
Iike maybe she was the one
that made the phone call on me.
Why would she do a thing
like that?
Maybe they got to her,
you know?
It happens. They find something,
put the screws on you.
The girl loves you. I can't
believe she would betray you.
I don't know.
I mean, everything's gotten
so strange, Pop.
I look at these people
around me,
and I'm thinking,
"These are my friends?
I don't even know
these people."
You know, and --
and Naturelle, even.
Do I --
do I really know her?
I don't know.
It's all...
The only people I trust
are you, Jacob, and Frank --
the guys I grew up with.
I miss those boys.
Yeah, I know.
I'm supposed to be
meeting them.
They're waiting for me.
I-I ought to get going.
What about your food?
I can't.
Okay.
I'll, uh, see you
in the morning.
No. No. Why?
I'm gonna take the bus up there.
Oh, forget about the bus.
I'll drive you.
Take half as long.
Take...this.
They'll let you keep it.
When you was a little kid,
you used to sleep
in that fireman's helmet.
You wanted to be
just like your daddy.
I ever tell you about the fights
we had naming you?
Yeah. You wanted to
name me James.
James Brogan Jr. --
good, strong name.
Nah. Your mother thought
it was too boring for you.
- She liked Montgomery Clift.
- Loved him.
"Place in the Sun" --
her favorite movie.
I kept saying,
"Montgomery Clift --
"look what happened
to that poor fuck.
Died way too young.
Bad luck."
Bad luck.
I'm gonna go, okay?
I'll see you soon, Pop.
Monty...
He'll be working
for me. I'll have his job.
Listen, I got to go.
Talk to you tomorrow.
Cocksucker.
- How you doing, bro?
- Hey.
-
- Good to see you.
- How you doing?
Good. Come on in.
All right.
Want a beer?
- Yeah.
- Cool.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
Cheers.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
Yeah, The New York Times says
the air's bad down here.
Oh, yeah?
Well, fuck The Times.
I read the Post.
E.P.A. says it's fine.
Somebody's lying.
Yeah.
You gonna move?
Fuck that, man.
As much good money as I pay
for this place?
Hell, no.
Tell you what.
Bin Laden can drop another one
right next door. I ain't moving.
What do we say to him?
Don't say nothing.
He's going to hell
for seven years.
What am I gonna do,
wish him luck?
Just get him drunk.
Make sure he has
one last good night.
That's it.
So you're up for this?
Yeah.
I don't even know
why he invited me.
What are you
talking about, man?
You know, we hardly ever
see each other anymore.
You know, you and I are
his friends from the past.
Oh, yeah.
Like his friends from the
present have done him much good.
I just...
I just can't believe
he's going away for seven years.
Someone turns him in and...
Oh, don't feed me that shit.
What shit?
Come on, Jake.
Don't feed me that bullshit.
Yeah, he got caught.
But hello --
Monty's a fucking drug dealer.
Shit.
What, are you -- you driving
a vintage Super "B"?
- No.
- No. He is.
Yeah, paid for by the misery
of other people.
He got caught.
He's gonna get locked up.
And I'll tell you
something else.
You two are my best friends
in the whole world,
and I love him like a brother,
but he fucking deserves it.
He deserves it.
What's he planning on doing
with Doyle?
How the fuck should I know?
I don't know.
Maybe...Ieave him
with Naturelle or something.
They should at least let him
take Doyle with him.
What?
Just let him take Doyle
with him.
He wouldn't be so lonely.
You can't take a fucking dog
to the hoosegow, Jake.
I'm just saying it'd be
kind of nice if he could.
All right.
Yeah, it'd be nice.
Monty's tough.
I think he'll be okay.
If it were me,
l...I'd never last a day,
but...Monty, he's different.
Oh, yeah?
You believe that?
Yeah.
You don't fucking get it,
do you?
What don't I get?
You want the simple
version, Jake?
Guys who look like Monty don't
do well in prison, all right?
Man, he's got three choices,
and none of them are good.
One, he can run.
Two, catch the bullet train.
Bullet train?
I'm not saying
what he's gonna do.
I'm saying
what his choices are.
His third choice is he goes
to prison, that's it.
Yeah, and that's
what he's gonna do.
He'll go and I'll see him
when he gets out.
Maybe.
I'll tell you what.
After tonight,
it's bye-bye, Monty.
What does that mean?
Man, if he runs, he's gone.
He ain't coming home.
If he pulls the trigger,
they close the casket.
He's gone.
They lock him away, he's gone.
You'll never see him again.
I'll see him again.
No, you won't.
I'll visit him up there and
I'll see him when he gets out.
This is such horseshit.
This is so much like you, Jake.
- You're not gonna see him --
- Like me?
Yeah, it's...exactly.
- What's -- why --
- You'll never see him again.
You think you're gonna
kick back with some beers,
reminisce -- old times --
you're still gonna be friends?
It's over after tonight, Jake.
Wake the fuck up.
Let her go.
That's a good-looking girl
you got there.
Ooh.
That's a scary look.
Yikes.
You see the look he gave me?
Naturelle Riviera --
what a name.
You know what?
Take another angle, man.
You can't fucking touch her.
No. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
You're missing the point.
She touched you.
- You're lying.
- Am l?
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's sweet.
All I know is
she's walking away.
Yeah.
We just signed her release.
Probably having
a big party tonight
over at Jimmy's Bronx Cafe.
Sure. Why not?
Big celebration.
She got that whole fancy
apartment to herself now.
What? You thought she was
with you for your looks?
Sh-e-e-e-it.
Girl saw a pot of honey,
and she licked it clean.
Yeah.
She's a real smart girl.
Now,
you, on the other hand...
You're supposed to be smart.
Got yourself a scholarship
to a fancy private school, hmm?
Not bad for a punk
from Bay Ridge.
Yeah, but then you go
and get yourself thrown out
for dealing weed
to some rich kids.
What up with that?
You know what happens to
pretty boys like you in prison?
Ooh.
They gonna love you.
Yeah, maybe.
But then again...maybe not.
"Jeez, Your Honor, you know,
what can I say?
"l messed up.
"You know, my mother died.
"l-I was so worried
about my father.
"l needed to help him out.
"My head was a little
turned around.
"l got hooked in
with the wrong people,
"and I made a big mistake.
"l really did,
but...it was my first time.
I'm sorry, and it will never,
ever happen again."
Time served. Probation.
You don't read the papers much,
do you, smart guy?
In New York,
we've got a wonderful thing
called the Rockefeller Laws.
Let me educate you.
You had a kilo in your sofa.
That kind of weight
makes it an A-1 felony.
15 years to life minimum
for first offense.
Now, with that much spread
in the sentencing guidelines,
the judges take their cues
from the prosecutors.
So if Mr. Prosecutor's wife
busted his chops that morning,
you're fucked.
You're gone for good.
If you get lucky --
really lucky --
now, let's say he got
some good trim the night before.
Maybe he'll plead you off
to an A-2.
But that's still three to eight
for first time -- minimum.
How much of that stretch
you pull
is all up to the mood
of the prosecutor,
and he's gonna ask us,
"Did he play ball?"
So...
why don't you tell us
about your friend Nikolai?
Let us make it easy on you.
Can I ask you one question?
Sure.
When you have your dick
in his mouth,
does he just keep talking
like that?
'Cause it seems to me
he just never shuts up,
and I'm --
I'm just curious --
does that --
does that get annoying?
You know, you're fucking a guy
in the mouth,
-
Look here,
you vanilla motherfucker.
When you're upstate
taking it in the culo
by a bunch of guys
calling you Shirley,
you'll only have yourself
and Governor Rockefeller
to thank for the privilege.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Tell the U.S. attorney
we got a hard-ass.
You need a girlfriend.
- I need a girlfriend?
- Yeah.
Wait a minute.
When was the last time
you had a girlfriend?
All right? When was
the last time you got laid?
I've got prospects.
- Yeah, you got prospects.
- I do.
You know what?
You're in the 62nd percentile
is what you are.
- What is that?
- 62nd percentile?
- Yeah.
- That's where you rate.
All the bachelors in New York,
we're all competing
for the same women --
well, the straight bachelors.
And I'm in
the 62nd percentile?
- Yes, sir.
- So in other words,
I'm better than 62%
of the New York bachelors.
You're rated higher
than them, yeah.
But worse than what, 38%?
37. No 100 percentile.
How'd you come up with 62?
There's a whole science
to figuring it out.
There's a science
to figuring it out?
That sounds very scientific.
And if I may inquire,
what's your rating?
- Funny you should ask.
- Hmm.
Because I happen to fall
right in the 99 percentile.
Of course.
Who came up with the ratings?
I did.
You came up with the ratings?
And you get a 99?
- That's very interesting.
- Yeah?
What are these, uh, based on?
It's just a system.
I mean, that's your rating.
I'm not saying
you're a bad person, Jake.
No, you're just saying
I'm a bad bachelor.
you're a better-than-average
bachelor.
What -- what are the criteria?
First, money.
You have none.
Trust funds don't count
for shit
because it's a red flag
that says,
"Mommy and Daddy could turn off
the cash flow one day."
So that right there keeps you
out of the top 1 0%.
1 0% of the...gold diggers?
1 0% period.
Two...
you got chronic bad breath.
No offense,
but most women won't sleep
with a guy with stank breath,
so...
Fuck you.
You don't have to get
so annoyed, all right?
What puts you
in the 99th percentile?
That's what I'm wondering.
Okay. Well, first of all,
l, um...
What?
Besides your salary
and all the money you make.
All right.
I happen to be blessed
with a very big dick.
Genetics, man.
Doesn't dyeing your hair
drop you down a few places?
Nope. Not at all.
Only bothers women
if it bothers me.
Going gray does bother you.
- No, it doesn't.
- Of course it does.
If it didn't bother you,
you wouldn't smear that goop
all over your scalp
10 billion times a day.
Hey, it's a non-issue, Jake.
Well, are table manners
an issue?
See that silver thing
to the left of your plate?
- That's called a fork.
- Mm-hmm.
And when people eat rice,
they use chopsticks or a fork.
Yeah, and grown people
don't eat...fried rice
with their bare hands.
You don't know how to behave.
You're busting my balls
on the way I eat?
You spend the whole week
figuring out how to defraud
foreign governments --
whatever you do --
and then you get out of there
and you go out
to the strange world
outside your office
called reality...
and you don't know
how to behave.
- Oh, yeah?
- I rest my case.
You gonna tell me
about reality?
Jacob, you're a rich Jewish kid
from the Upper East Side
who's ashamed of his wealth.
You walk around unhappy 24-7
trying to make up for the fact
that you were born privileged.
Fuck that.
You know what?
That's just some knee-jerk
liberalism bullshit, man.
You call that reality?
So what's Monty?
Let's see.
Monty's going to prison.
He's a doughnut --
big, fat zero.
Yo.
Let's not go to practice.
Just today.
So don't go.
Let's go to my house.
Come on, Nat. Let's go.
My mother won't be home
till late, either.
And there's food.
Good, 'cause I ain't got
no money.
Vito's home.
So?
What's that?
Nothing. I don't care.
You don't care, Nat?
What do you mean now?
Yeah, right.
You know
you likededed him forever.
I never likededed him.
You're always trying to
hook us up
because you want me to be
your sister-in-law,
but it ain't never happening.
Don't front
like you don't likededed him.
Nat, please, okay?
Every day you come
to my house --
"Vito, walk me home" --
Every day?
What kind of bullshit is that?
Anyway, he's always with
that girl.
- What's up, Simon?
- Monty, how you doing?
- Good to see you, man.
- Good to see you.
Who's that?
It's a new guy.
He's Golden. He's good.
Now, you know what I told you.
He's big.
It's like, "Beep, beep" --
back up your truck, man,
you know what I'm saying?
All right, Simon. I'll handle
my business, all right?
- Just trying to help.
- All right. Take it easy.
When did he break up
with her?
Like a month ago.
But she don't stop.
She calls the house,
she calls, she hangs up.
Please. Please.
Did he break up with her,
or she broke up with him?
He needs somebody good.
Excuse me.
- Why doesn't he --
- Excuse me.
- You got a light?
- What?
Can I borrow your lighter
for a second?
Thanks a lot.
What's he doing?
He's loco.
Yo, I've met you before,
haven't l?
You do look familiar to me.
How do I know you?
Yeah. You were in
my brother's class.
Pete.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I know who you are.
Yo, Nat, come on.
Let's go.
We got practice.
I'll catch up.
Yeah, all right.
Whatever.
You stupid.
- What do you got practice for?
- Basketball.
Seriously? You play?
Come on.
What are you, a guard?
Three spot.
You play small forward?
No shit?
That means you're strong
and quick.
I play the one -- point.
You skip too many
of these things,
they'll give you the boot --
for real.
I just want to finish
my cigarette.
Funny. You don't --
I don't know.
I wouldn't have made you
for a ballplayer, you know?
You look more like a...
Iike a...runner,
like a track star.
Where you from?
No, I mean -- you from Uptown?
U.F.A.?
You on a scholarship?
What, I can't be
from Riverdale?
You can be from wherever
you want. Just...curious.
I didn't mean nothing.
I was just...
You know, l-I was
on scholarship, too.
It's a good thing.
You -- you're lucky.
What -- what's your name?
Nat? Natalie?
- Naturelle.
- Naturelle?
Are you serious?
Naturelle.
Wow. I like that name.
How old are you?
18.
Are you 18?
- Why?
- 'Cause it's not every day
I meet a girl as pretty as you
who plays the three spot.
That's deadly.
- How old are you?
- I'm old enough to have to ask.
You're too old to be
hanging out on the playground.
I wasn't hanging out.
I was...
I was passing by.
What if I was 17?
It might shorten
the conversation a little.
But you're not. You're 18,
so we got no problem.
What do you say I come
and see you play sometime?
Seriously. I'd like to.
Maybe.
Maybe?
Okay.
I'll be the one behind the bench
yelling, "Get back on 'D'!"
See ya.
Hey.
Come out here
and meet somebody.
Who's that?
She's just the girl for you.
Hey, Jody.
You back there?
- Hey, baby.
- Hey, sweetie.
How you doing?
- Hi.
Is this your little brother,
Frank? He's a cutie.
Don't bother with me.
I'm in the 62nd percentile.
Oh. That's probably because
you don't work on Wall Street.
The scale is skewed
to the money thing.
- Everybody knows about this.
- Everybody knows.
Anybody at this bar.
You see that ass?
- She's beautiful.
- Mm-hmm.
Man.
One of the guys at school --
this, uh, biology teacher,
Terry --
- Mm-hmm.
- Did you ever meet Terry?
No, I don't think so.
Anyway, he, uh, he --
he really likes this girl.
- Like a student?
- A student.
-
- Yeah.
- A junior.
- Oh, man.
I mean, the girl's 16,
17, maybe.
I don't know.
Uh, she's not really pretty,
um...not in the, uh,
classical sense,
but she...
I don't know.
She's -- she's got something.
- You know.
- Mm-hmm.
I told Terry, you know, to just
forget about it, you know?
He's kind of obsessing,
and it's kind of scary
the way he talks about it.
But he's like...
"Five years from now,
"she'll almost be out
of college.