I remember most of 17.
I remember the day we met.
His smile, his touch.
You could be anywhere
when your life begins...
when the future
opens up in front of you...
and you may not even
realize it at first...
but it's already happening.
All right, guys,
let's roll, man.
-What, fool?
-Man!
I got some shit to do, man.
Fool, you always
got shit to do.
Man, you got to
learn how to kick it.
It's a beautiful day
on the beach, man.
Why, you afraid
of getting too brown?
Some fool might think
he's Mexican.
Shut up.
Hey, guys,
check it out, man.
Hey, hey, hey.
Look at the juanita.
Yeah! Whoo!
Come on, baby.
Hey, we got some trash
over here.
-It's starting to stink.
-Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, don't let me go.
-Should I drop him ?
-Let me go, please.
Aah! Unh!
Yo! Hey, you all right?
Yeah, I'm all right.
Don't worry about me.
Whoo!
Yo, baby!
Hey, where you going?
Hey, hey, hey.
Let's go.
You missed one.
Thanks.
That's really helpful.
So, are you
a bad-ass gangster or what?
Something like that.
What'd you do,
stay up past your bedtime?
Nah, I'm just playing.
For real, what you doing?
-I robbed a 7-Eleven.
-What?
Yeah. Stay away.
I'm dangerous.
I'll mess you up.
Damn. My bad.
Man...
y'all always got
to follow me, man.
My name's Victor.
What's your name?
She don't care
what's your name.
-Nicole.
-Nice to meet you.
Carlos.
Hi, Carlos.
What's up?
Man, I was talking to her.
What you doing?
You know what?
I've seen you around.
Doubt it.
-You go to Pacific, right?
-Yeah.
Yo, rich girl.
Rich girl.
Hey.
Hey, let's go. Come on.
Push on. You know, vamonos.
Vamonos? We only
talking to the girl, man.
-Vamonos. Now. Let's go.
-What's vamonos, man?
You know what it means.
Now let's go.
Just keep moving.
-I'll see you around. Bye.
-Yeah.
I just want you
to leave, all right?
Bye-bye.
Come on, keep moving.
Please, get out of here!
I want this all picked up--
all of it.
Carlos.
OK.
Good morning, Mom.
Yeah.
Thanks, Mom.
I don't want any more.
Oh, yeah?
Miss Nicole,
it's time to get up.
I'm awake.
-Morning.
-Good morning.
ROSA:
Are you taking lunch today?
No, I'm going to buy.
Rosa?
Yes, Mrs. Courtney?
Did Morgan have
any dairy yesterday?
No.
Because she has a little rash
right here, you see?
No dairy.
I'm not accusing you.
I'm just asking.
No dairy. Only soy.
-No dairy.
-No. No dairy.
OK.
TV: You whale.
You have a spout. Ha ha!
Mmm.
Nicole, you're not supposed
to watch TV in the morning.
Are you going to change
for school?
-Mrs. Courtney?
-Yeah.
-Mr. Oakley.
-Oh, OK.
Hi, sweetie. Yeah.
Oh, no, she's got
a little rash on her back...
so it's a little crazy.
Yeah. We're going to go
to Dr. Benniman's office.
I'll call you
from there, then.
Yes, I love you, too.
I love you.
Oh, Nicole is here.
Do you want to say
something to her?
Bye.
He's late for a meeting.
Come on, sweetie.
We'll go to the doctor
and get your rash all better.
What's
the evil step mom's problem?
Oh, major crisis.
Morgan has a rash.
Oh, my God.
Where's the ambulance?
WOToday
Like any day
Rolled out of bed
Talked on the telephone
Went to the doctor
She said, you're OK
Still, I wonder
Who am I?
Oh, that's just great.
Oh.
Who am I?
Today
In the air
On the water
Ships pass you by
Clouds fantasize
Driving shapes
across the sky
Wondering why
Oh, my God.
Who am I?
Oops.
Hi.
Oh, God.
I hate this place.
Yeah.
I'm already up for ditching.
For sure.
Shit sucks.
NARRATOR: Shakespeare was,
in many ways...
ahead of his time.
He had
psychological depth...
that is only
in this century...
beginning to be
fully understood.
-Yes?
-Bathroom?
-Me, too.
-Take a pass.
Oh, thank you.
NARRATOR: Both at a time
when only a queen...
TEACHER:All right,
so the British are trying...
to reestablish authority
over their precious colonies.
it's as if
they're trying to assert...
a right that
they couldn't quite exert.
Assert and exert.
Anybody know the difference
between assert and exert?
What does it mean
in this case?
Anybody?
It means
they could write the laws...
but they couldn't enforce them
from 3,000 miles away.
TEACHER: Bingo, Carlos.
They're 3,000 miles away...
and they're trying
to establish their authority...
over their colonies.
They are trying
to reestablish...
their mercantilist
philosophy...
which was,
"'We got colonies...
"'and we're here to milk them."'
How were they doing this?
Well, Greenville,
the man in charge...
under George the Third...
Once in a house
on a hill
A boy got angry
He broke into my heart
So I came down the hill
Of course I was hurt
But then
I started to think
it shouldn't hurt me
to be free
it's what I really need
To pull myself together
But if it's so good
being free
What you are telling me
Why I don't know
what to do with myself
Hey!
Hey, come here.
I got to get back to class.
No.
Come meet my friends.
Hi.
Come on.
What, are you scared?
It's Carlos, right?
Right.
Break me off some of that shit.
-This is Maddy.
-Hi.
-That's Lainie.
-Foster.
-Curtis is in the tree.
-What's up, man?
Carlos and I met when I was
giving back to the community.
He was on
the chain gang with you?
-No.
-Just an innocent bystander.
-You want some?
-Nah, that's OK.
Come on,
it's good for you.
Trust me.
So I loved the boy
No one could ever forget
Damn!
-With a kick.
-What's in this?
-Incoming, you guys.
-Oh, shit. Give me this.
What's going on?
Hey.
Well, what do you know?
My all-time favourite people
in the world to bust.
-Hello, Mr. Kane.
-How's it going?
Hey, this is
a student council meeting.
You know what?
You need to get back to class.
FOSTER: I got too much stress
in my life.
We got to take a break,
or we'll pop.
Ask the mental
heathcenter people.
They told us to take breaks.
What is this?
Who's this belong to?
Not us.
You don't know anything
about this, right?
I got a pass.
What, a drinking pass?
You guys, let's go.
Clear out.
Hey! Aah!
Hey! Hey! Guys!
Cut it out.
Come on, this is detention.
Hey.
This is how we first met.
What?
Picking up trash.
Just let me do the work, OK?
Sure.
3, 2, hut!
You got it!
Good job.
-Carlos.
-What?
-I'm sorry.
-Yeah, well, so am I.
No, I really am.
Come on, it's just detention.
You're not going
to be scarred for life.
You may even still
get into college.
Look, you guys play around
at being bad-ass...
which is cool. Whatever.
But it's not like that
for me.
I get on this bus...
this piece of shit,
stinking bus...
two hours each way,
just to be here.
5:43 in the morning--
that's when my bus leaves.
So if I wanted to screw up,
I'd do it at my home school...
because I'd get
a hell of a lot more sleep.
But I'm here, OK?
I'm here because
I really want to be here.
And you,
you're here because...
Why are you here,
if it's such a big joke to you?
I don't know.
Ask my father.
What?
Nothing.
Why were you on the beach?
Beach?
You didn't rob any 7-Eleven.
Oh.
DUI. I got stopped
coming home from a club.
Damn, that's pretty stupid.
Yeah. Didn't seem stupid
at the time.
Then again, I was wasted.
I don't know, man.
Just don't play me, OK?
I won't play you.
I don't want to be played.
OK. I won't.
I'm not going to play you.
OK?
I promise.
Aw, come on!
You're supposed to drop back
into coverage, Lucky!
And don't give him
a free release on the inside!
Nunez, where the hell
you been?
-Detention, sir.
-Detention?
You pay me back
after practice.
You give me an hour
in that weight room.
Let's go!
On the ball!
All right, man,
I'm outta here, bro.
We're not supposed
to leave until 6:30.
Dude, there's no one here.
We can leave whenever.
Aw, you're a trip, Nunez.
See you later, homey.
Damn.
Missed the bus.
Detencion.
It's no big deal, Mom.
All right. I got it.
No. I got it.
OK. Let me just talk
to my girl...
and I'll call you right back.
OK. Bye.
Uhh!
OK, here's the plan.
Derek knows this party
in the Colony...
but he's not exactly invited.
But he thinks that if
he hooks up with us...
whoa--that we can
for sure get in...
because we're just
so irresistible.
You know,
there's a football game.
A what?
A football game.
I heard you.
The Pacific game?
-Yeah.
-Football?
What? It'll be fun
for a goof. Come on.
Oh, my God.
You're so obvious.
What?
-What?
What am I obvious about?
-Slut.
-Shut up.
Can I have two, please?
Two.
Two, two, two..
We did not wear our blue.
Oh, shit.
I forgot to wear anything.
Offense, offense!
Here we go!
Oh! My bad.
Boom, boom !
CHEERLEADERS:
Boom, boom, what up?
Let's go. Let's go.
1, 2, 3, go!
MAN ONP.A.: Nunez,
number32, on the field.
Nunez with the ball.
Unh!
Whoo!
MAN ONP.A.:
Number32, Carlos Nunez,
with the reception.
Come on!
Hell, yeah!
Whoo! Yes!
If you tell anybody
I just did that...
I'm going to kill you.
-I will.
-OK.
Oh, yes!
We did it, baby!
Nice seein'you, now.
Way to go, Nunez.
You got a lot of heart, baby.
That's meat, baby.
You know it.
And you know it.
Yes!
You need
a ride to Carmen's, bro?
What's happening at Carmen's?
Hey, free cerveza,
free food.
Maybe some other free stuff,
you know what I'm saying?
You faked
that guy out so bad...
when he hit the ground,
I could've swore...
he sittin' on himself.
Hey, he didn't see nothing
but your ass cheeks, man.
Good game, you guys,
all right?
Hey, all right, Coach.
Try to stay
out of trouble.
Hey, stay out
of the strip club, man.
Man, you like that,
don't you?
Come here, hot stuff!
Hey, say hello
to your wife, Coach.
I'll see you guys later.
Hey, where are you
going, man?
I'll see you guys later.
You ain't hanging out with us?
What's up?
Hell, man,
we just won the game.
See you later.
Oh, you got to be
kidding me.
Hi.
You guys come to get me
in trouble again?
Uh, no.
We're off-duty.
We're not troublemakers.
We're innocent.
-Yeah.
-Look at our faces.
Don't we look innocent
together?
So, what'd you think
of the game?
What game?
It's going to be like that, huh?
So, what are you
doing tonight?
I got to catch the bus.
I got work tomorrow.
-Aww.
-That sucks.
Hey, we can take you home.
-It's far.
-Come on.
We'll take you wherever
you want to go.
Carlos,
which way am I going?
Just grab the 10.
-What?
-The 10.
-10 what?
-10 freeway!
Know when I'm rollin',
the trick is to keep it goin'
Flowin' over nobody,
not knowin'my head swollen
Who can control it, if you
try to say it's heart broken
Lookin'for me, and I swear
it's in a careless motion
All the way down
by the pound
The shit you read about,
a nice, round figure
Anyone can figure out
And everything's for nothing
if you're willing to try
You got to make it,
you got to try to stay high
'Cause everybody
is in on something else
You gotta, you gotta find out
who and what it is
God, dude,
could you live any further?
I told you it was far.
You wanted to take me.
Damn.
Maddy's never been
east of La Brea.
Shut up, dude.
You think you're down...
because you scored weed
in Pico Union one time?
I'm telling you,
it was twice.
One time.
Two times, bitch.
Two times.
-Are you OK?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
I didn't say
you could touch that.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
Well, what can I touch?
What can you touch?
-Oh, come on, Carlos.
-Whoa, slow down.
-Why?
-Chill, girl.
Hey, you guys.
Damn,
that feels good, but...
But what?
You guys!
-I like you.
-I like you, too.
You guys.
Are you guys hungry?
Because I'm starving.
There's a place
right up the street.
Oh, yeah?
There's a place
right up the street.
Keep going.
it's to the right.
Don't crash.
Watch it!
-Whoo!
-Hey!
You guys all right?
I don't know, man.
She's on drugs.
Ow!
Ow, I hurt.
Love me, I hurt.
Baby.
Will you pick me up?
Pick me up.
I want to be carried.
I'll carry her
to the Taco Shack.
Don't mind her.
Oh, this is so cool.
Oh, my God,
I love this place.
-Put me down.
-All right.
Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo!
Aw! Ow!
Whoo!
Whenever you're ready, guys.
Come on, Carlos. Come on.
You want to dance with me?
I'm not much of a dancer.
Yeah, daddy.
WODamn, girl.
You guys are crazy.
Oh, man.
WOWhoo!
How did l
get involved in this?
Oh, yeah!
Gracias.
All right. Excuse me.
May I help you?
-Tacos.
-You want a taco?
Burritos. Tacos. Tacos.
All right,
we'll take six tacos.
-No. Spanish.
-She speaks English.
Espanol, por favor.
You like that?
Spanish is hot.
Ohh.
And to drink?
Mmm.
This is, like,
the best food I've ever had.
I know. Thank you.
OK, where do I go pee at?
Whoa.
Hey, you know what?
You're shit out of luck.
Shut up.
There ain't no bathrooms
around here.
Fine. I'll just
pop a squat somewhere.
There's
no bathrooms around here.
Please come with me.
Come with me.
Are you serious?
Yes.
I have to go so bad.
You're going to pop a squat?
-Where?
-Anywhere.
All right,
just go down there.
No way.
This is, like, Rapes Are Us.
No, it's not.
Just go down there.
-You're coming with me.
-Look, it's dark.
All right.
We're going.
This sucks.
Don't look.
Oh...oh, my God.
I really want
to kiss you right now.
I really
want to kiss you, too.
When the time is right.
So you just let me know
when the time is right.
OK.
Oh!
You guys, I'm all done.
Drip-dry. Unh.
Oh, get a hotel room.
Oh.
Man...
Is that 'Los?
Yeah, that's
your brother, man.
Sorry. Hey, guys.
BOY:
Hey, that's the trash girl.
That's right, baby.
Ah ha. Trash girl.
-What's up?
-What's up, man?
-What's going on?
-Just getting a ride home.
So who's this, homes?
I'm Nicole.
-How you doing, Nicole?
-Good.
Hi, I'm Maddy.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Maddy.
So, where'd he find you guys?
You get assigned a white girl
when you go to Pacific.
How generous.
And Carlos is so cute
he got two.
How generous.
How can a brother be down?
Looks run in the family, mija.
What's up with my brother?
You got to go to Pacific.
-Good luck, homes.
-Hi, Mom.
This is Nicole and Maddy.
-Hi.
Hmm.
Sorry about that.
She's kind of pissed.
It's OK.
I'll see you at school.
Let's get out of here.
-Thanks for the ride.
-Sure.
-Good-bye.
-Bye.
Get your ass inside.
Hurry up.
Moms is calling you.
Now where the hell's
the freeway?
Bye.
Just friends.
I mean, everybody
drinks but me, Mom.
Come on, Mom.
That's not going to happen.
I'm not going to die.
I'm not going to jail.
There's some
very interesting rumors...
going around
about Friday night.
Oh, really?
I heard the word "furpile"
more than once.
I did nothing
to discourage these rumors.
Ow! Watch where you're going,
stupid bitch.
What's your problem?
You're my problem.
Hey, it's all good.
She didn't mean to--
Stay out of it.
What are you looking at?
-Nothing.
-You better not.
-Sorry.
-Yeah, you better be.
Looks like the home girls
aren't down with you.
-Hey!
-Hey.
What are you doing here?
Looking for you.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
Maddy told me
you were in here.
Oh, she did, did she?
Am I not allowed?
Sorry about the other night.
I was a little wasted.
Yes, you were.
Ho ho ho.
So, what happened?
You don't remember?
Kind of.
it's not done yet.
You cut his head off.
Hey, in here, I'm in charge.
Your world?
Yeah.
You take it to a lab,
they just do the obvious.
I like to play with it--
cut out what I don't like...
distort...magnify.
Playing God, huh?
Just playing.
So, can I see some more?
If you want.
Hey, kids,
what's going on in here?
This is not a make-out room.
Come on.
I'll see you later.
MAN SINGING:A sunrise
over a dusty hill full of
Full of wallflowers
And I think to myself
I am the same
I met my baby
by the station
And she said
Can I help you
with some information?
'Cause your train gets out
at a quarter to 5:00
But you hang a while
And you and I
can get funky
To the rhythm
of the choo-choo train
Dancin '
in the pourin'rain
I found myself
In the most beautiful
situation
A feeling
I can't describe
Ooh,
how she gave me love
Oh, how she gave me love
-Rosa, this is Carlos.
-Hi.
I said,
oh, how she gave me love
Oh, how she gave me love
What?
Aren't you
going to lock the door?
No.
I don't have any...
It's OK.
It's not OK.
Don't move.
-Hey, Rosa.
-Hi.
-Bye, Rosa.
-Bye.
-Oh, shit.
-What? What's wrong?
-Who's that?
-What?
-That guy right there.
-My dad.
-It's OK.
-He's right there.
He doesn't care.
I can do anything.
I've got a condom.
He'd be so proud.
I'm serious.
He'd be thrilled
I'm sleeping with you.
A person of color
in his daughter's bed.
Man, you're crazy.
You're beautiful.
OK.
But can I do one more thing?
What?
I want to kiss you
one more time.
Where are you?
Hi, there.
Who's the princess
on the floor, huh?
Nicole, please
do not park your car...
in the motor court
because it drips oil everywhere.
We just came
from a dance show--
-Dance recital.
-You look pretty.
So...
Oh, be careful.
You're going to mess up
the costume.
I really want to keep
this dress neat.
MORGAN: Mommy.
Thank you.
Hi, there. Tom Oakley.
Carlos Nunez. Hi.
How are you?
You're Rosa's nephew?
No, Dad. Carlos and l
go to school together.
Oh, you're a senior, too.
Yes, sir.
Just finishing up.
That's wonderful.
Do you have any plans
for next year?
Dad, don't interrogate him.
I'm not interrogating him.
That's OK.
I'm applying
to the Naval Academy.
Annapolis?
That's impressive.
That's a tough school.
Yes, sir.
I want to be a pilot.
A pilot?
The Naval fliers are supposed
to be the best in the world.
Well, you'll get
a great education there...
no matter what
you decide to do.
Good to see
someone with a plan.
So, who's sponsoring you?
Well, I've written
to Roy Ball--
Oh, yeah? Lucy?
Yeah, but
she hasn't responded yet.
Yeah, well,
she's still tied up...
with that INS fiasco...
and she probably won't get to it
before Thanksgiving.
So, why didn't you
write to me?
Tom Oakley.
Oakley? Right.
I mean,
she didn't even tell me.
Nicole didn't tell you
I was a congressman?
Nicole didn't think
it was relevant.
Actually,
I think I did write to you.
Oh? What'd I say?
No word yet, sir.
Well, I'm sorry about that.
Maria probably hasn't gotten
to my stack yet, either.
Tom? Morgan wants
to eat with her daddy.
-Can you hurry?
-OK.
Here. Why don't you
call the office...
and we'll set up a meeting?
You can come in,
tell me all about yourself...
and I'll see what I do.
Thank you, sir.
Say, why don't you two
stay for dinner?
Rosa's cooking up her famous
stuffed chile rellenos.
"Rellenos" means "stuffed."
Thank you, Nicole.
And we can't stay.
Perhaps another time, then.
Glad to meet you, Carlos.
Nice to meet you, too, sir.
Take care.
God, I hate when he pulls that.
Pulls what?
That act. "Oh, I used
to march with Cesar Chavez."
"Oh, I'm every poor man's
best friend."
-It's so fake.
-He seemed cool.
"Stay for dinner.
We're having chile rellenos."
"Did I show you
my electric car?"
And what about you?
"Yes, sir. No, sir."
What is that?
You don't have to do that
around him.
I was raised to do that.
It's not some act.
Fine.
Why didn't you tell me
who your father was?
I don't go around advertising
my father's profession.
I didn't think it mattered.
-It does matter.
-Why?
Do you know how hard it is
to get these guys...
to sit down
and read your letter?
Or pick you out of a hundred
guys exactly like you?
Well, mission accomplished.
You got your meeting...
and you didn't even
have to sleep with me.
Lucky you.
I'm sorry.
I just...
that was just weird.
I'm sorry
we were interrupted.
Another time?
Hmm. If you're lucky.
So, Pilot Nunez, huh?
Well, we'll see.
What do you mean?
I've never even been in one.
In what?
A plane.
You're joking.
You've never been
in a plane before?
No.
Oh, my God. That's cute.
-Cute.
-It is.
I had a good time today.
Me, too.
So, any ways,
Brian's been AWOL...
for, like, four days.
He hasn't called.
He totally changed
his cell phone.
What are you
going to do if he calls?
I don't know.
What would Jesus do?
Seriously. Remember when
I went code blue on that EPT...
and he freaked out because
he thought I'd tell his wife?
Like, that guy
so can't handle pressure.
-I'm sure he's just--
-Carlos.
Leave your best friend right
when she's baring her soul.
Hey.
-How's it going?
-Good.
You busy Saturday?
Yeah. I've got to work
in my uncle's shop.
Too bad.
What?
I just thought we could
have some fun together.
Oh, man, I don't know.
Come on.
My dad's not invited, Carlos.
Just you and me.
I don't know.
It's just my uncle needed me.
Yeah. I promise, promise,
promise you...
a very satisfying experience.
You won't be disappointed.
Mmm, OK.
I got you.
-No peeking.
-I'm not.
Hold on.
OK, now you can look.
Whoa.
Want to join the Mile-High Club?
What?
I'm kidding.
Whoo!
Here we go.
Aah!
We stand
To lose
Every color from the sky
Then crawl
As a child
So, can I take over?
Sure.
Go ahead. It's yours.
Oh, God,
you're letting him take over?
Ohh.
There's no longer shine
On this bird of prey
You're doing great.
He's going
in the Naval Academy.
-All right.
-Maybe.
I haven't been accepted yet.
How many hours have you logged?
-None.
-None?
He's a natural.
You mean in an actual plane?
In a real plane.
How many hours you got?
None.
I have a flight simulator
at school.
Oh, a flight simulator.
Like a chair pilot.
Pretty much.
Yeah, all right.
Can I do a Lazy 8?
It's your airplane.
Go ahead.
What's a Lazy 8?
PILOT:
Start it to the right.
Oh, my God!
Oh!
Ha ha ha!
Go ahead. Turn it
back to the left a little.
I can say
you're doing a good job.
I'm loving it.
Look at me.
I'm busy. Wait.
Whoo!
Oh, my God.
I can see my house.
-Where?
-Do you see it?
Right there.
Want me to drop you off?
Thank you.
PILOT:And back around
to the left.
It's a disease
of the week benefit.
They have to stay
until he's shaken the hand...
of every person in the room.
We got until
at least midnight.
We is all alone.
What'd you do?
Made it Carlos friendly.
WOMAN I want to believe in
I want to believe in us
When everything is wrong
Will you come through?
Come through
Not what I thought
it'd be like.
No?
Mm-mmm.
But you thought about it?
Yeah.
Look how good our skin looks
next to each other.
It's beautiful.
Hmm.
Who's that?
Oh. My mom.
She lives in Virginia.
She's married
to some dermatologist...
and the guy's home
at 6:00 every night.
it's a big plus for my mom.
When she was married
to my dad...
he was always running around
trying to save the world.
No time for his family.
She left when I was 12.
But it's good for my dad,
he got to marry Courtney...
and she's flush with cash
from her first marriage.
My dad left when I was five.
He couldn't hack it here,
so he went back to Mexico.
I don't even have
pictures of him.
You mad at him?
I hardly even think about him.
I got plenty of parent
in my mom.
I got to go.
No, you don't.
You got to stay.
No. My mother's going
to kill me if I'm late.
Tell her you're staying
at a friend's house.
What friend?
I don't care. Make one up.
I'm not letting you leave.
MAN When you hold me
Like you do
it feels so right
Drawn out
I start to forget
How my heart gets torn
When that hurt gets thrown
Feelin'like I can't go on
Turnin'in circles
Time and again
Where are you going?
I got to go.
No. Stay. I'll drive you.
Shh.
Got to know
For sure
'Cause
it takes something
More this time
Than sweet, sweet lies
Drawn out
Before I open up my arms
And fall
Losin'all control
Every dream inside my soul
This year's lovin'
it'll last
'Cause who's to worry
if our hearts get torn
When that hurt gets thrown
Don't you know
this life goes on?
Won't you kiss me
On that midnight sleep?
Sweep me off my feet
Singin'ain't this life
so sweet
This year's lovin'
it'll last
Whoa, ah, yeah
This year's lovin'
it'll last
I can't believe
I just did that.
Ah.
What am I doing with you?
I don't know.
What are you doing with me?
It's just a question.
Look what you just
got me to do.
Ha ha!
I don't know, man.
When I'm with you, I never know
what's going to happen.
It's weird because my life
is so planned out, you know?
I don't know.
It's like you don't care
what people think...
and when I'm with you...
you kind of make me
not care what people think.
You know what I'm saying?
I know what you're saying.
I don't know.
And that dimple--
I love that dimple.
-I grew it myself.
-You did?
What does he need?
Remember us?
-What's up, fool?
-What's up?
What does he need?
Mmm. Damn.
That's the shape.
Uh-huh.
That's my wife.
She could be my mommy
any day.
She could spank me...
Ooh.
That's what
I'm talking about.
Hey, what's up?
She got more
bounce to the ounce.
Hey, guys,
just chill, all right?
Chill, dawg. Chill.
Chill, dawg.
Man, there's people around.
What, we ain't West side
enough for you?
-You want us to whiten up?
-Kick back.
Look at this fool.
He's all about
the white girl now.
I worry about this fella.
I put this fella
on his ass on Friday.
You playing defense
now or what?
I'm going both ways.
I'll make you eat dirt.
That's what I'm going to do.
DAVIS: Hey, Carlos, man,
what's up, bro?
What's up, guys?
These your homeys?
Homeys?
Yo, what's so funny, G?
I ain't your G, man.
DAVIS: Yo, what's up
with the attitude, bro?
What's with what?
Dude, you need to chill, bro.
I'm not some banger
lookin' to throw down.
Then sit the fuck down, bitch.
Hey, guys, chill.
Whoa.
This isn't brown town, bro.
Hey, guys,
just chill, man.
I'll call INS on your ass.
Hey, guys, kick back.
Oh, man.
Get off.
Get off me, man.
I want to kick this guy's ass.
I'm going to kill you!
Are you going
to clean this mess up...
or is your dad
going to come do it?
Hey, go home!
Leave, buddy!
Go back to Burritoville!
Not right now, Mom.
Just leave me alone,
all right?
I'm sick of you
always on my ass!
I don't need any more
sacrifices from you, OK?
Just worry about
your own goddamn life.
-'Los!
-What?
Don't disrespect Moms
like that, fool.
Are you going to tell me
how to talk?
You know what?
Mom. Por favor.
Let me tell you
something, homes.
She busts her ass
every day at a shit job...
for you, not for me.
Every day!
You owe it to her to make
something of yourself.
What, because you didn't?
Huh?
MRS. NUNEZ:
Carlos. Hector.
Yeah. You're right.
You got it.
Let me tell you
something, 'Los.
I'm not like you, fool.
I'm not as smart as you.
I'm not as fast as you.
You got something
that I never had--
the opportunity to be
whatever the hell you want.
You can be a pilot.
You can be a congressman.
Whatever you want.
And for you to just throw that
away for that white girl...
that's nothing but...
and I'm not going
to sit around...
and let you do that shit
to yourself...
or to Moms anymore,
you understand?
Look at me, ese.
Nicole.
NICOLE. Look up.
What?
We got to go.
Shit.
What?
What's the date today?
Today?
-Is today the 17th?
-I don't know.
-Shit!
-What?
The meeting with your father--
I completely forgot about it.
Don't worry.
You can reschedule it.
I shouldn't have
gone to the beach.
-Don't worry. It's OK.
-No, it's not.
Damn. I can't believe
I missed it.
I'll see you later.
-You don't want me to come in?
-It's going to be boring.
It's just family
and cake and stuff.
Oh.
All right.
No, that's OK.
You don't want me to.
Just hurry up.
We're late.
I wish I would've known--
Come on!
Hey, that's OK.
And a "Cheese."
Come here, fool.
Where you been, man?
It's my sister's birthday party.
Lost track of time, dawg.
Carlos...
I lost track of time, Mom.
You remember Nicole, right?
Hi.
Ooh!
Shut up.
I'll be back in a minute.
God damn.
You're a fool, you know?
-Hi. Happy birthday.
-Hi.
Thank you.
Perfecto.
Can I help with anything?
No, it's OK.
Oh.
One second.
LUZ: Ahh.
You know I like it buff.
LUZ: Yeah.
You know you miss me.
What?
Hey.
Oh. Hey.
-Where'd you go?
-I went to change.
Oh.
Thanks for telling me.
Sorry.
Luz, this is Nicole.
Nicole, Luz.
-Hi.
-Hey.
I like your dress.
Thanks. So, you guys
go to school together?
Yeah.
We go to P.H. together.
LUZ: Oh. That's nice.
And you share
the same class or what?
No.
LUZ: Yeah.
Let's go say hi to my mom.
All right. Come on.
I'm hot. I'm gonna go
outside for a second.
-Come on.
-It's OK.
What?!
OK. Hold on.
Yo, 'Los, it's for you, man.
Hello?
Where'd you go?
What happened?
Why'd you leave?
I'm so stupid.
I don't know what
I was thinking coming there.
I'm sorry.
I should have told you
it was gonna be like that.
That it was so formal.
No. It wasn't that.
Just seeing you with
your family and friends...
and with that girl.
She's just a friend.
I don't care.
You should be able to do
whatever you want.
I do what I want to do.
Oh, God.
Look at me, I'm pathetic!
I hate myself.
What are you talking about?
What?
It's just...
I just...
I think I'm in love with you.
I'm sorry.
Now I've weirded you out.
No. l--
Don't say anything.
It's OK.
MARIA:
That's correct, sir.
He's leaving for
Washington, D.C. in five days.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, well...
No, he really doesn't have
any other appointments.
I would stick with
that one. Mm-hmm.
Certainly, sir. Take care.
Yes.
Yes, he is.
Mr. Nunez?
He's ready for you.
Yeah.
I have it right here.
I think. What is it?
A kid...
for Gloria, right?
Well, we start
with the Bienvenidos...
and then the Red Cross thing.
Right?
And then--You know, hon?
I have a meeting
I need to start right now.
Why don't we meet
at King at2:30?
OK?
Well, you tell me then.
All right. Bye-bye.
Hey, Carlos.
Glad you could make it.
How are you?
OK. How are you?
You know Carter?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
You ever work for
Habitat for Humanity?
-No.
-It's a good project.
We got 25 houses up
in one Easter weekend.
And you know Father Boyle?
Yeah. I've heard of him.
He's an amazing man.
Sit down.
We spent some time
in Boyle Heights.
It's a tough neighborhood, huh?
Yes, sir.
I imagine you've seen
your share of friends...
sucked into "la vida loca."
Yeah.
-Not just a Ricky Martin song.
-No, sir.
So, what happened?
Uh, what happened?
We were supposed to have
a meeting last week.
I don't know.
I got the bus schedule
all screwed up...
and it was too late.
You could have called
to say you weren't coming.
I--I did call.
Maybe she just didn't get you
the message. The lady.
Maria!
Yes?
Did Mr. Nunez call last week
to say he wasn't coming in?
Not to me.
Should I ask Sandy?
No, that's OK.
I'm more than happy
to use my connections...
to help someone
get a foot in the door...
but I have
absolutely no patience...
with individuals who will not
participate in the process.
I can't do this alone.
Mr. Oakley, um...
I really appreciate
you seeing me today.
OK. I think I know
what's going on here.
I know the powerful effect
Nicole can have on people.
She's absolutely fabulous...
at taking
a perfectly-oiled train...
and running it
right off the tracks.
Now, I do love her.
Unconditionally.
That goes without saying.
But she can be so destructive.
And volatile.
And, um, the anger...
ever since...
Well, to be 12 years old...
and to find your mother
like that...
I think when Nicole's mother
took her own life...
Nicole decided
then and there...
that she would never,
ever trust anyone again.
And it was her
against the world...
and God forbid anybody
should try and help her.
She's persona non grata...
with half the psychiatrists
on the West side.
A lot of them have recommended
that I send her to...
one of those behavior
modification schools...
but I...
She's tried to kill herself
a number of times...
but what can I do?
She lies and she drinks.
She does drugs.
She hates me.
Hates her step-mother.
Mr. Oakley--
Ahh, nothin'.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't be
telling you about this...
but you seem like
such a good person.
Such a decent person.
Now, you want me to write
this recommendation?
You want me to put myself
on the line?
Well, I want you to
listen to my advice.
Now, stay away
from my daughter.
You hear me?
For your own good,
for my peace of mind...
stay away from Nicole.
You know, it's a painful
thing for a father to...
have to acknowledge a truth
about their own child.
it's taken me a long time
to accept who she is.
And who she's never gonna be.
MAN Well, I could sleep forever
But it's of her I dream
if I could sleep forever
I could forget about everything
We got a party, man.
Hey, Carlos...
all them honeys
gonna be there, man.
They gonna be
checkin' us out!
Hey.
Ha ha. Hey.
So, what happened?
When?
You didn't call me.
Oh, I got home late.
I just had stuff to do.
Well, what'd he say?
I'll see you guys later.
All right.
-What happened?
-No, nothing.
He just said he'd write me
a recommendation.
But what did he say?
About what?
-About me.
-Nothing.
Come on, just tell me
what he said.
I really don't want
to get in the middle--
In the middle of what?
Look, I just need
to focus right now.
You need to focus?
I can't afford to mess up, man.
I told you that.
My mom's all over me
'cause I'm never around...
and my grades are for shit.
I could hardly keep
my eyes open at practice.
All I want to do is sleep for
more than four hours straight.
I'm sorry
for messing up your life.
I just need to remember
what's important.
What's important to you?
My priorities.
What did he tell you?
He told me
to stay away from you.
That you were trouble
and you'd just mess me up.
And what did you say?
I just...
I see.
MAN Every time
it's time to call
In many ways
Every dream
Gets broken over
With little time
I will fly within your sky
Every time
You start to call
And on the way
All destruction is my wine
Though it's sad and lonely
There's a whole life
waiting after dawn
Gonna slide
You can be anywhere
when your life begins.
You find the right person,
then...
all of a sudden,
anything's possible.
I'm eating, Mom.
I'm just trying
to figure this out.
Chemistry homework.
Hello?
LUZ: Hola, Mrs. Nunez.
Soy Luz.
No estoy a qui.
Don't tell her I'm here.
I told you, Mom,
I don't want to talk to her.
Because I don't want to.
Mira. Tu comida.
-I'll eat it later.
-Ay, muchacho.
Yeah!
Hello?
Nicole?
Yeah?
I need to talk to you.
Who is this?
You know who this is.
I--I can't hear you.
Where are you?
What?
I--I can't hear you.
Are you at Seller's house?
I'm just having
a good time, OK?
And you need to focus.
Nicole, I really have to--
Get off the phone and in
the hot tub, girl. Damn!
Nicole!
I'm gonna go.
Nicole, I just want to--
-Take your time.
-Yeah, hold on.
I'm uncomfortable
with myself
Carlos!
What's up, Carlos?
What's up, baby?
Yo, get him a tequila.
Girl, put a titty in his mouth.
Don't you know when to flake
And I am not doing
all right
None of this makes sense
They don't support me...
Come on, Nicole, let's go.
DAVIS: Whoa, stud.
I was just trying
to get a taste, man.
Shut up, Davis,
before I kick your ass!
Hey, man,
what's your problem?
You're my problem !
Get down!
DAVIS: Hey!
What's your problem, bro?
Dude,
she was having a good time.
GIRL:
What's wrong with you?
DAVIS:
I thought I was your friend.
Just leave, you know that?
Get off me, bitch!
Shit.
Stopping a vehicle
with expired tags.
Two occupants.
Expired on 6-7-00.
Registered to
Representative Thomas Oakley.
Good evening, sir.
License and registration,
please.
I don't know
where the registration's at.
Who does this car belong to?
It belongs to her.
Where you comin' from tonight?
From a party.
You been drinkin' tonight?
No, sir.
Why don't you step out of
the car for me for a minute?
I just live right off--
Sir, please,
step out of the car for me.
John, you check on
the young lady.
Sir, please step out
of the car.
Keep your hands up
where I can see 'em.
Miss, let's go. Let's go.
Time to wake up. Let's go.
Put your hands up.
Time to get up. Wake up.
Walk over to the curb,
have a seat.
Here you go.
Step out of the car, please.
There you go. Wake up.
Sir, the tags
are expired on this car.
What's your name?
Do you know
this guy right here?
-Yeah.
-Has he tried to hurt you?
No, he hasn't hurt me.
What are you doing?
Why are you touching me?
Get the hell off of me!
Just calm down.
Nicole, stop.
Get the hell off of me!
Nicole, stop it!
Where are you going?
No!
He didn't do anything!
Makin' it worse for yourself.
What the hell is going on?!
Get off of me!
Stay here. Don't move.
Stop!
We didn't do anything!
Nicole, just calm down!
Get off of me!
Take her to the car.
Put her in the car.
What's going on?
Hello?
Come on in.
Good evening, sir.
Good evening.
We stopped this young man
driving your daughter's car.
She was intoxicated
and combative.
We found drug paraphernalia...
and alcoholic beverage
containers in the vehicle.
Christ.
We thought we'd give you
the courtesy...
of dealing with her yourself.
Now, we could put
a scare into her...
and let her
spend the night in jail.
No. Thank you, Officer.
I can handle this.
No, you can't handle it!
Nicole, just calm down.
-Calm down?
-Everything will be all right.
No, it's not gonna be
all right!
Look at you.
What are you doing--
COURTNEY:
What is the matter out here?
Go back into the house.
Is she drunk again?
Courtney, look,
I am taking care of this.
How many times do we have
to put up with her behavior?
When is it gonna be enough,
for God's sake?!
When?
Look at you, Nicole.
Just look at you.
What kind of a daughter are you?
Not yours.
Thank God for that.
This is--
Carlos, please,
what did I tell you?
Just go away.
Please. Just leave.
Go.
You hear me?
Why do you hate me so much?
How could you tell
the one person in the world...
that I love,
that I care about so much...
how could you tell him
to stay away from me?
Do you think the only thing
I'll do to anyone...
is screw them up?
Do you think
that I'm not worth loving?
-Nicole--
-Carlos, this is our problem.
It's our problem, not yours.
Just leave. Go.
Come on, son, let's go.
Honey, listen,
come on to the house--
Leave me alone!
Just leave me alone.
Just come in the house, Nicole.
No.
Just get in the house.
Jesus Christ.
MAN Christened life
Somehow I found you here
Torn from the hope
and fear
Hold us inside
You pulled me out
Up from the world
I've known
And all that was
broken and cold
You brought me here
The mid-term counts
for 25% of your grade...
so I want you to pull
your thoughts together...
TEACHER: Can I help you?
Faith in the life
we've done
OK, where was I?
it holds us inside
Ohh
From you, one look
Just one look
And everything is shattered
From you, one word
Stars burn and fall
Oh
Carlos.
You need something?
From you, one look
Just one look
TEACHER:
Where you going?
And everything is shattered
Yo, you got a pass.
Hello?
Towers burn and fall
Fall, fall
From you, one look...
What's going on?
Packing.
Where are you going?
Oh.
I'm going
to the Turnabout Ranch...
in lovely Escalante, Utah...
and I get to be escorted
by a lovely gentleman...
who's waiting for me
in the principal's office.
So it looks like I get to go
to boot camp before you do.
Sorry for being so dramatic
the other night.
It was stupid.
I'm sorry for not--
Don't say anything.
You couldn't do anything.
You were smart
not to say anything.
So, Mr. Nunez...
it was great knowing you.
I hope you have
a wonderful life.
Let's leave.
What?
Let's get out of here
right now.
Aren't you
in the middle of an exam?
Like right now?
So?
I'm not gonna let you
walk out of your mid-term.
I already did.
Annapolis is gonna
look at these grades.
You're not listening to me.
I wanna be with you.
I don't give a shit about
anything else right now.
Mid-terms, grades,
Annapolis, your father.
I want to be with you.
Do you want to be with me?
I love you.
Don't just say that because--
Shut up.
I love you, OK?
You know,
this guy in the office...
he's pretty damn big.
Ha ha!
Then...
let's go out on Sunset.
Oh. Ha ha ha!
-Come on!
-I'm coming!
I imagine
long walks down the road
Things begin to bloom
and the sky explodes
The damage is undone
Then I know
This has got to be a dream
Machines and luxuries
don't last
Here.
You can wear this.
And I woke up half-dead
in the hour glass
Now,
does that sound funny
Wait, you're almost there
it's gone
You're almost there,
You're almost
where what follows you
Does not bother you
I have walked
the tightrope parts of me
Toed the line
just far enough to see
Never found the gift
I got for free
You pay for them dearly
I see my forever
as one long night
And if I could
make it dark
I could make it light
I know that most
of living done...
Don't be writing on my back.
Only thought survives
Wait, you're almost there
it's gone
Aah!
Almost where
what follows you
Does not
What are you doing?
You'll see.
That's pretty cool.
My shrine to Carlos.
Can I see more of it?
Yeah, sure.
My suicide notes.
Creative, huh?
That's your mother, isn't it?
Yeah.
She...
she was in bed asleep,
I thought...
so I went downstairs...
and I stayed real quiet
all afternoon...
so I wouldn't disturb her.
And then I went back up...
and she was still lying there.
My dad thinks
we're the same person.
Did he say that?
He doesn't need to.
What else am I supposed
to think...
except I'm gonna end up
like her?
It's genetics, right?
Your father, though...
he really loves you.
He does.
No, he doesn't.
Nicole, listen to me.
He really loves you.
He just doesn't know
how to handle you.
I think you scare him.
I scare him ?
You do. I mean,
you scare me sometimes.
-I scare you?
-Yes.
I mean, you...
How do I scare you?
You just get out of control.
-I do not.
-Yes, you do.
What are you talking about?
You know what
I'm talking about.
I'm 17. I'm supposed
to get out of control.
I guess.
My dad, he doesn't
understand me or...
anything about me.
Have you tried talking to him?
Yeah.
-Sober?
-Shut up.
Doesn't happen, does it?
I'm not always drunk.
Hey.
What are you doing out here?
I want to be good for you.
You are good for me.
Not if I keep taking you away...
from everything
you've worked so hard for.
I want to make things
better for once...
not worse.
'Cause I really
want to be with you.
I can't keep running
away from things.
I'm here for you.
I know you are.
Well, do you have
a 310 listing for J. Foster?
OPERA TOR: No listing, sir.
Well, try B. Foster at 818.
F-o-s-t-e-r.
OPERA TOR: No, sir.
There's no Fosterin 818.
OPERA TOR:
Should I try the 310 again?
Sir? I'm trying
to help you, sir.
Hello?
Well, I've been up all night.
Trying to call everybody.
I called Maddy and Lainie
and your friend Foster...
who apparently doesn't
believe in telephones.
Honey, I know you don't want
to go to this school...
but it's supposed
to be extraordinary.
Marty Sheen says it's top-notch.
Dad, I'll--
You'll have your own horse.
My own horse?
Well, you like horses,
don't you?
When I was eight.
Well, the counselor
said that--
he warned me you would try
to talk your way out of it.
He said there's a danger of us
getting drawn back...
into old patterns
and destructive behavior...
and that we should spend
our time focusing on...
conversations that focus on
"We" versus "Me."
This is "We."
Oh. Well, good.
Good.
I'll go wherever
you want me to go.
I mean,
I know I'm a mess.
No, you're not a mess.
No, I am. I am a mess.
And I'd probably
send me away, too.
You've got Morgan now...
and you're gonna do it
right this time.
I just wish
I wasn't the child...
that everybody learned
what not to do from.
That's not who you are.
I know I remind you of Mom.
Everything that went wrong...
but sometimes you look at me
like you wish I wasn't there.
Like you wish
I'd just disappear.
And it just hurts so bad.
I know I'm not easy to love...
but could you try anyway?
I do love you.
I love you so much.
I'm frightened for you
every minute.
Every minute.
And I need help.
I can't do it alone.
Tom, honey?
Morgan's got her swim class.
it starts in 10 minutes.
What's going on?
That's what we're trying
to figure out here.
COURTNEY:
What do you mean figure out?
Didn't we agree on
a plan of action?
Rosa? Would you please
put Morgan in the car?
Thank you.
Yes, right now.
Oh, my God.
This is not gonna start up
all over again.
She needs discipline.
Children need limits.
They want limits!
-So we'll set them.
-We already have!
She's going to that school
in Utah.
No. I am not the bad guy.
This is not about me.
I have a child
that I'm thinking of.
So do I. Two children.
Oh, Nic...
Nicole, I just don't think
I can live with you.
I know I can't live without her.
We have to be at Pepperdine
in ten minutes, Tom.
I'm talking to my daughter.
It's Morgan's
very first swim class.
I'm talking to my daughter.
Nicole,
I just want Morgan...
to have an older sister
that she can look up to.
Me, too.
That's all right.
I've got her now.
She's not like Mom.
No.
God, your mom
was an amazing woman.
She loved you very much.
I wish I remembered her better.
Hmm.
We should talk about her more.
We will, honey. We will.
Before you say anything, sir...
I just want you to know
that I love your daughter, sir.
You don't have to--
She has so much beauty,
so much honesty...
and I love her so much.
Carlos, stop.
Now, I have something to say.
Thank you.
For what?
For not listening to me.
For sticking around.
Annapolis is gonna be
lucky to get you.
But I had a speech.
I had a pretty good speech.
I bet you did.
You want to hear it any ways?
Why don't you tell it to her?
Seems to be doing pretty good.
How did that happen?
How did you do that?
Do what?
I wasn't even there.
Yes, you were.
You were so there.
WOMAN I want to believe in
I want to believe in us
There are millions
of people out there...
but, in the end,
it all comes down to one.
I still panic sometimes,
forget to breathe...
but I know...
I know there's
something beautiful...
in all my imperfections.
A beauty which he held up
for me to see.
A strength that can
never be taken away.
I'm going out to see him
next week...
but until then...
there's one photo
I keep with me all the time.
I believe in us
Everyone falls
But not everyone rises
Why don't you get up
And rise again for me
What if the world
were a little more perfect
Would you stop crying
Would you take the leap
Now, what if the world
were a little more perfect
Would you open your eyes
And blink again for me
For me
Yeah, for me
What about friendship
What about friends
You said the whole world
was against you
it all had to end
What about love
What about family
What about all
that you have to live for
What if the world were
a little more perfect
Would you stop crying
Would you take the leap
What if the world were
a little more perfect
Would you open your eyes
And blink again for me
For me
it isn't easy
here without you
Why did you leave me
What am I supposed to do
Without you
And what if the world
were a little more perfect
Would you stop crying
Would you take the leap
What if the world were
a little more perfect
Would you open your eyes
And what if the world
were a little more perfect
Would you stop crying
Would you take the leap
What if the world were
a little more perfect
could you open your eyes
And blink again for me
For me
Ooh
For me.