Today I will finally achieve
what has been deemed impossible
Man can break the
50-mile-per-hour speed barrier
And you are lucky
enough to be a part of it
"It surely shall, sir"
Yes. We will make history...
or die trying
Die...? This is very exciting
"I refuse to be catapulted
electrocuted... "
or have my internal organs
disrupted any longer!
I quit
He is a very sick man
The electrocution was not my fault!
You refused to wear
the rubber underpants!
Is there no man brave
enough to be my valet?
I'm your new valet
I must commend the valet service
on their impeccable foresight
But they know I only
accept French valets
Yes. Oui
I come from a long line
of French valets on my father's side
"Very, very French"
But your accent...?
"My father French, never speaks
My mother Chinese, never shuts up"
All the children pick up her accent
Are you willing to risk your life
to challenge the laws of physics?
"Yes. And I can sing, too"
Excellent. Put this little hat on
And the throttle in your right
hand controls the speed!
How do I stop?
Godspeed
Twenty-five miles per hour
Pressure's stable
We need more speed!
Forty miles per hour. Hang on in there
Forty-seven...
Forty-eight...
Forty-nine...
Eureka! We've done it!
Good morning
I'm looking for a man
with a steam turbine
There he is! That's my valet!
Sorry! New valet
Good morning
You'll be able to let go any second
The pack will run out of steam...
in exactly... three... two... one... now!
We've broken the human speed barrier!
"Goodbye, sir
It's been very nice valeting for you"
Let's do it again soon
"Wait! With you as my brave valet
I can test all my inventions"
No!
Yes. I take the job
Splendid!
I can't wait to present my
results to the Royal Academy!
RO YAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCE
And with this grant to develop
new applications for copper wire...
Doctor Ramsey invented this
"Needless to say
the Royal Academy of Science... "
declared this crackpot
mentally incompetent...
and he was duly dispatched
to a lunatic asylum
"Sir, I have an urgent
announcement for you"
Don't just stand there
Read it
It is with great distress
that Scotland Yard...
announces that the Bank
of England has been robbed
My stolen Jade Buddha-stolen!
You blighter!
You assured me that the Bank
of England was impenetrable!
"Sir, I said "impregnable"
"It's the same thing, you idiot!"
"Please, not the quills!"
Lord Salisbury...
"Contact General Fang and inform her
"No Buddha, no deal"
To forego your obligation
would be dishonorable
A woman in the Royal Academy?
We successfully delivered the
Jade Buddha to the Bank of England
What happens while
it's in British hands
is absolutely your concern
"Colonel Kitchner
Chief of Scotland Yard... "
inform General Fang
what other items were stolen
from the Bank of England
Nothing else
Exactly
It seems your little land
dispute has spilled over
onto our noble shore
"Until the Jade Buddha is
back in my possession
you and your cause... "
will receive no British military
assistance whatsoever
"My agents will retrieve the
Jade Buddha once again
Lord Kelvin"
This time do not let it slip
through your fingers
What sort of pathetic man
takes orders from a woman?
Come away from here
"Oh, Dad, can't we stay?"
My wind-powered pulley system
circulates the house with fresh air
Kitchen items are to be placed
on the white boat and
the blue is for laundry
This supplies the house with a
running current of electricity
Electricity?
This is my comprehensive daily
schedule and list of regulations
You're never to divert
one iota from my plans
I must live my life with total
efficiency to maximize
my inventing capacity...
thus enabling me to do
the most I can for mankind
"Mr. Fogg, you are a noble
precise gentleman"
Thank you
"I'm sorry, what was your name?"
Uh... Passport
Too
Passport-tout?
Bottled light. A miracle
Hardly
Just undiscovered science from an
American named Thomas Edison
It turns on with a whistle
Please don't do that
I see your eye is drawn to what
I hope will be my
crowning achievement
A giant moth?
It's a flying machine
It can fly?
Yes
No. But it will. One day
One day it will transport
people through the air
Perhaps over entire oceans
I think I'm going to have
to make a rule for this
Dear Father...
I will find the fastest way...
back to China to make our
village safe once again
Departure for the Royal Academy
of Science in two minutes
Prepare my Urban Transport Device
It's the shoes with
little wheels on them
Clear the way!
Mr. Fogg coming through!
Watch out!
Out of the way!
Fogg's arrived
That makes it exactly
ten minutes before noon
That will be all
Gentlemen...
today I have proved that man
can break the 50-mile-per-hour
speed barrier...
without disrupting
his internal organs
Where is your Royal Academy
of Science authorization?
"Oh, what am I thinking?
What a fool"
That would mean that you
were a real scientist
"By your definition, Kelvin... "
a real scientist's objective
would be to prevent
man from progress
"We live in a golden age, Fogg"
Everything worth discovering
has been discovered
Yet ridiculous dreamers
like you insist...
"on a past filled with"
"dinosaurs" and"
"evolution"... "
and on a future filled
with motorized vehicles...
radio waves and flying machines
Confound it!
The bloody Bank of
England is a madhouse
"Rumor has it the man's
a foreigner, an Asian chap"
Nothing
"I heard it was a Chinese
fellow, and he acted alone"
"Actually, they say
he was Norwegian"
"In fact, it was a gang
of elderly Norwegians"
I heard from a very reliable
source that it was a gang of...
red-headed elderly Norwegians
with very tiny feet
"If you ask me, it's about
time someone robbed that bank"
"Like this very institution
the Bank of England is outdated"
"As usual, Fogg, your contempt
for tradition is appalling"
"You rest on your traditions
if you prefer"
"But, as with this bank robber
progress waits for no one"
"So now you're an expert
on the bank thief, as well"
"Give us the benefit of
your ineffable wisdom, Fogg"
"Twenty-six minutes ago
a ship left Dover for Paris"
"From there, the thief
takes the Orient Express
then transfers to a steamer... "
"from Istanbul to India
In little over a month
that man could be in China"
If we're to believe
Fogg's calculations...
he will have circled the globe
and returned to England
in a fortnight
"By my calculations
it would be closer
to exactly 80 days"
Outstanding idea
"Well then, Fogg... "
let's see you circumnavigate
the world in 80 days
That would be a
fruitless use of my time
I'm on the verge of numerous
countless-scientific breakthroughs
You coward. Admit it
It cannot be done
It can! I could do it
A wager. Ten thousand pounds
"Unlike you and your colleagues
money does not inspire me"
I believe every man has his price
"Even you, noble Phileas Fogg"
There must be something
I could offer you that
would be worthy of your time
There is. Your position
as head of the Royal Academy
"With the Queen's ear
I could lead the world into a
new age of progress and discovery"
Fair enough
What?
"I, Lord Kelvin, hereby vow... "
to surrender my position as
Minister of Science to Phileas Fogg...
if he can circumnavigate the globe...
in no more than 80 days
But if he cannot...
he must never set foot in
this Academy again...
he must tear down that abhorrent
eyesore he calls a laboratory...
and he must swear...
never to invent again
"Just as I always suspected, Fogg"
"You promise so much
yet you deliver... nothing"
I'll take the wager
What did you say?
I'll take your wager!
He'll take it?
Then it's done
A man who has never set foot out
of England circling the globe
This is getting to
be rather amusing
"History won't remember your
amusements, Lord Kelvin"
But it will be hard-pressed
to forget the moment...
I'm standing on the very top step of
the Royal Academy of Science...
"by the strike of noon
after I, Phileas Fogg... "
have traveled around
the world in 80 days!
"Oh, dear"
"Mr. Fogg, we're all
packed and ready to go"
Are you in here?
"Are you well, sir?"
Passepartout
Would you sit with me a moment?
"Yes, sir"
I've risked everything
My entire life's work
For something you believe in
Nothing could make
more sense than that
"You're an honorable man
Passepartout"
But I'm afraid this was a
calamitous lapse of judgment
Mr. Fogg?
Maybe we should
let your family
know about there is
no one left to tell
This house and my
inventions are all I have
And a brave French
valet that will
help you go around
the world in 80 days
You really believe we can succeed?
You're mad
We'll be sliced to pieces
before we reach India
Halt!
"Quite a contraption
you got here, Mr. Fogg"
"Thank you, Inspector"
But I'm afraid I'm going to have
to detain you and your valet...
until further notice
This new doohickey is in violation
of the city's new vehicle code
Vehicle code?
Code 431
All vehicles must be
powered by horses...
or other indigenous
quadruped creatures of the like
Excluding giraffes and
You're driveling
Stand aside
I'm about to embark on a
journey around the world
"Not in this monstrosity
you're not"
That's hot
It's not
Time to go
We have a boat to catch
Stealing a police vehicle is not an
acceptable way to begin our journey
Not stealing. Borrowing
Excuse us
We're just borrowing this vehicle
to catch our ship to Paris
If someone could inform the
appropriate authorities
Bloody hell!
My brain's leaking!
Damn that nincompoop Fix
What's the point of hiring...
a corrupt police officer if he
can't even abuse the law properly?
Tell Inspector Fix to pack his bags
He's going on a little trip
"Right away, sir"
Retrieve the Jade Buddha in Paris
As for Lau Xing...
KILL HIM!
Smart man
"Passepartout, will you tell this
impudent fellow that we must leave... "
within 6? Hours or we will miss our
connection in Constantinople
"Please, we are in a great hurry"
"Yes, sir"
In French
You imbecile
What did he say?
He said...
What?
He says not to worry
The next train will
leave in five hours
Good time for sightseeing!
"This is a scientific
expedition, not a holiday!"
I will not miss this train
Very amazing
What does it say?
"This week only
Eddie Thomason will be
showing his new inventions"
Thomas Edison? Here in Paris?
What a chance for you to
meet another great inventor
"I would quite like
to tell him about my"
"whistle" modification"
Good idea
See?
An exhibition. Science!
"I assure you, these are not
the works of Thomas Edison"
I think he's somewhere around here
Wait a moment
This isn't science!
This is art!
Yeah
That painting is highly inaccurate
"It's not supposed to be"accurate"
The artist views reality
through imagination...
rather than simply recording it
It is called Impressionism
"Well, I'm not "impressed"
"Trees aren't violet
grass is not charcoal
and a man cannot"
fly
You feel something
You dream of flying
Or of naked men?
Sometimes
The flying. Not the men
I'm glad you like my painting
Monique Larouche
"Phileas Fogg
Well, it's an awful lot
better than these amateurs"
What did he say?
Oh no...
"Oh, no, not again"
Who is responsible
for this vandalism?
"It's mine sir, does it please you?"
Please me?
You want to hang something?
Go hang people's coats as
you were hired to do!
But sir...
"In fact, don't!
You're fired!
Leave art to the artists
What was all that about?
A wealthy gentleman bought
my painting for a lot of money
Champagne for everyone!
I'm still looking for Mr. Eddie
Have you ever considered a
career in schematic drawing?
No. It would be far too limiting
At least your work
shows genuine promise
Thank you
Because I painted many months
when I was lacking inspira
I found some men to
help me find Mr. Eddiman
This way!
Thank you! Thank you
He's very eager
"It's terrible, no?"
No. It's... clever.
"He's a clown. And yet
he's incredibly angry"
The irony's terrifying
Is that good?
Is it?
This is interesting
"But you realize
without opposable thumbs
a dog couldn't play poker"
"Yes, they can. "
"Now, where have you ever
seen a dog playing poker?"
Right there
Perhaps I'm not the best judge
Bandits! They came to take
away all the paintings!
"Look out, my paintings!"
Quickly! Come this way!
Go!
Thank you, Miss Larouche
You may just have saved our trip
There you are
I would like to repay you
Then take me with you
What?
I'm stifled here
Pigeonholed
They think of me only
as a coat check girl!
Why?
Because I am the coat check girl
Look what the leading art critic in
Paris wrote about one of my paintings
I can't read this
I think it's French
I wish I couldn't
Why do you carry it around with you?
So when I do succeed
I can throw it in his face
But for now, I need a
world journey to inspire me
I'm inspired to get
us back on schedule
Let's see
Wind velocity
approximately twelve knots
Factoring in air density...
outstanding!
Passepartout! Onward!
There we go
Tell him to keep the change
We are going around
the world in days!
My God!
They are mad!
The balloon cannot
support all this weight
Your hot air should compensate, no?
Get off! Let go!
What are they doing?
They're being disorderly
Hey! Let go!
Passepartout, my valise!
It has all my money in it!
Hey, lady! It's my bag
No, that is my bag!
That's not your bag
It's my bag. You're crazy!
That tickles
He took my bag
Mr. Fogg!
Good catch! Thank you!
Those are the gallery bandits!
The scoundrel stole my purse!
My bag!
We've stolen that old lady's purse
We must help Passepartout!
How do I make this go lower?
What are you doing?
Decreasing the overall
weight won't work
Yes, it will!
Physics, no?
Yes
Bon jour!
Bye bye!
Wake up, lady!
Bye, Mama. Miss
Bye, baby!
Very impressive!
I'd have let go by now
The statue's grabbing his trousers!
I don't think it's doing it on purpose
Oh, dear
Well done
We're still on schedule
despite those dogged thieves
Thank you
Those "art thieves"
seemed to recognize you
I look like someone they know
Some other "Frenchman", perhaps?
So where can we drop you off?
We're not stopping
Once we land in Munich
to board the Orient Express
you are free to go
Thank you so much
For what?
For saying I'm free to go with you
I did not say you
were free to come
I said you were free to go
Where?
Anywhere. Thank you
I will go with you
No, you will not
Miss Larouche, Monique
Miss, Monique
There. Now we are getting along
Look at the sunrise
There is only one word
for it - magical
Miss Larouche!
I refuse to allow you to
continue traveling with us
I'm not traveling with you
I'm making my own way
Maybe you shouldn't travel with me
This is what happens
when you leave your home
You meet... people!
Why are you keeping up this ruse?
Perhaps I'll inform Mr. Fogg
and he and I can
speculate together
A very sacred object was
stolen from my village
I have taken it back
How incroyable!
For centuries
the Jade Buddha has
protected my people
It has never left
our village... until now
Those "art thieves"
who are they?
The Black Scorpions
They work for an evil warlord, Fang
She wants the Buddha so
she can take over my village
I must return the
Jade Buddha to protect Lanzhou
Mr. Fogg is the fastest way
Perhaps, then we can help one another
I will keep your secret
And you convince Mr. Fogg to
allow me to travel the world with you
Keep zis dumkopf in his
seat or we throw him off!
Merely pointing out that if
they coordinated their...
coal shoveling technique
they could maximize our speed
When we reach Constantinople
I suggest you board a
train we are not on
Mr. Fogg, she must come with us
And why is that?
We just discovered that we are
related from the same family
I'm her father's second cousin's
sister on my mother's side
French
Monsieur Fogg
if I make the train go faster
can I come with you?
Yes
I bid you farewell
Miss Larouche
If there's anything else
you'd like, just let us know
Champagne with your
First Class seats, Miss Larouche
Merci
No, thank you
A tea?
Okay!
"How to make English tea"
"Precisely degrees... "
Excuse me, sir
Fogg's valet!
The Jade Buddha!
It is not a Jade Buddha. Yes, it is!
You're right. But I am not a valet
Oh, really?
Bloody nose! Let me in!
You'll pay for scorching my willy!
Now I've got you!
You're under arrest!
Sorry!
Why the devil are we stopping?
Prince Hapi would be honored
to have Phileas Fogg...
and his traveling
companions at his banquet
How very flattering
But please inform Prince Hapi
we're on a very tight schedule
Prince Hapi demands it
Then Prince Hapi will
have to get accustomed...
to not getting everything he wants
It is magnificent!
Mister Fogg, his house is
even bigger than yours
His collection! His taste! It's exquisite!
Yes, it is
Not good. Look. Broken
And where is his Highness?
The prince is also a
talented musician
If I did nothing but lounge about all day
I'd learn to pluck a few notes
Let's make this brief
I will pose for a few photographs...
perhaps wearing a turban
holding an atlas
How magical that our
paths should cross
Do you believe in fate?
If that's what you call stopping a moving
train and kidnapping its passengers
Phileas Fogg. Please forgive me...
but I feel like Aphrodite
herself descended to earth
How does a ravishing woman like you...?
I never think when I'm naked
I do. In the bath
No! Don't touch it
That is my most treasured possession
I was only pointing
Don't even point
Rodin
Yes. A Rodin
I've never seen a more
beautiful... muscular form
I can assure you...
I'm in much better shape now
Incroyable! It is a sculpture of you!
Yes
"Happy Birthday, your pal, Rodin"
Come, my dear. Let us dine
Yes
Mr. Fogg, please join us
Sorry. We are on a
very tight schedule
We will join you, actually
But just one drink
After the Duke and the
Duchess sat down in the bath...
I realized I forgot to put
on my bathing suit
I'm such a fool, always embarrassing
myself in front of visiting dignitaries
But you know how that
can be, right, Phil?
It's Phileas, actually
So, Foggy, I heard
you're an inventor
I try to think of new ways
to better mankind
if that's what you mean
I'm not an inventor
but I did develop a new way
of irrigating dry land...
so that no one in my kingdom
ever has to be hungry
Mr. Fogg invented "wheelie shoes"
Not now, Passepartout
Miss Larouche?
It is mesmerizing the way
your face illuminates
Her discoloration could be an allergic
reaction or a mild form of hives
Although I've noticed a glow about her
complexion when she's drawing
Sometimes when she's concentrating
on her latest work...
her ears will actually flutter
It's rather fetching
Well, guess who else
was in this bath?
U.S. President Rutherford B Hayes
Shouldn't we be going now?
We have a schedule to keep
Thank you for your hospitality, Prince Hapi
It's been absolutely fascinating
but I'm afraid we must push on
Yes
The gentlemen are free to go
But Miss Larouche stays here with me...
to be my wife
Yes. Wife number seven
You have seven wives?!
One for each day of the week
This is absolutely ridiculous
No more talk! Prince Hapi has spoken
Well, we did say "one drink"
Passepartout, we're leaving
I can tell when we're not wanted
Monsieur Fogg!
Will Tuesdays work for you
Goodbye!
Thank you!
Nnnnooooo!
Halt! Or Hapi gets smashed!
Please?! Anything but my statue of me!
Miss Larouche, please join us
Drop your weapons
Do as he says!
Get in the tent
Everybody! Now!
Come on!
Now take off your clothes and...
I assure you the statue is not
armed-harmed-in any way
In fact, it's completely
Get them!
His arm!
Thank you, Phileas
That was very heroic
Yes, and needlessly
time-consuming
This is exactly why I should
never have let you come along
Kill them! I want my arm back!
Sir, I've received a telegram
from Inspector Fix
According to him, the bank thief
and Fogg's valet are the same man
That numbskull Fogg doesn't even realize
he's transporting the bank thief
Or does he?
He left town in quite a hurry
wouldn't you say, Lord Rhodes?
Indeed, Lord Salisbury. Evading arrest...
and stealing a police vehicle...
sounds rather incriminating to me
One can almost deduce
this entire bet...
was merely a ruse to
facilitate his escape
Don't you agree, Lord Kelvin?
Yes. Brilliant, Lord Salisbury!
I shall name a beef-related
entrée after you
Kitchner? Sir?
Inform your men in Scotland
Yard that Phileas Fogg...
is without a doubt the man who
robbed the Bank of England!
Done. Where are they now?
They're taking a train across India
from Bombay to Calcutta
Thank God we own India
I want their faces posted in
every police station
army barracks...
post office, railway station
and outhouse in India
We're going to stop Fogg and
get my Jade Buddha back...
by any means necessary!
Agra is where we will
capture them
Intercept them at Agra
Carry on, Colonel!
Alright, fall in
on the double!
(fall in: Army term
for "form a line")
(on the double: Army
term for "immediately")
They were the greatest Kung Fu boxers
the Ten Tigers of Canton
Brothers in arms, they fought to
keep order and justice in China
The most famous of the
Ten Tigers is Wong Fei Hung
One night Wong Fei Hung...
It's salivating on these
Is this your goat?
Did they really fight like tigers?
Each tiger had his own animal
fighting style. The tiger!
Snake!
Where are my steam
pressure calculations?
The goat! Passepartout
I'm being attacked by a
ferocious animal!
Sorry, Mr. Fogg
Please keep that inconsiderate
beast away from me
And refrain from your
ridiculous anecdotes
Why do you not like
his story, Mr. Frog?
It's Fogg. Phileas Fogg
How can man learn...
to defend himself by watching
animals behave like... animals?
It is a famous legend
A ridiculous legend
Most legends are born from truth
Yes, but all truths are born from facts
Solid, tangible facts that can be
calculated and written down on paper
And then eaten by a goat
Mister Feelsillious
when I tell the story of the man who...
circled the entire world in days
would that not be a legend?
Only if the man's name was Feelsillious Frog
What the blazes is it now?
Get back inside! Now!
Find these men!
Time to go. They seem to think
we robbed the Bank of England
That's preposterous
It's merely a desperate attempt by
Lord Kelvin to impede my journey
I am a British citizen
I have nothing to fear
Except bullets
Seen these men?
Any word on the bank thieves, sir?
They were spotted on the train
Keep your rifles ready
They won't get past us, sir!
Ladies, have you
seen these two men?
Look closely
hey're very dangerous
They're everywhere!
This is not going to work
Stay calm. Just act like ladies
Not a problem
I feel faint
Women are not that weak
No, but I am
Hello, darling
What can I do for you?
Wait a minute!
What are you doing?
This is no time to sleep
Stop! Stop!
Go, go!
Get us out of Agra quickly!
We did it!
Wrong way!
Phileas! No!
Run, Passepartout!
Fogg's valet! I have him!
What are you doing?
Now I've got you!
Hand over the Jade Buddha
Help! You're under arrest!
Watch my plums!
See? Now you made him very mad!
Let's go!
Stop or I'll arrest you as well!
Run!
Which way?
Down!
Jump!
Go, go, go!
What's upsetting him?
He also wants the Jade Buddha!
Then give it to him!
Wake up!
Please, you must go
My husband will be home soon
Phileas! Help!
Fear not! I'll protect you!
I'm here, my dear
That stumble was simply
to buy me time
This cane is not
what it appears
If I press this button
it will deploy a weapon
far deadlier than yours
This is... a strange knife
Isn't it a sextant?
Yes
Are you alright, my dear?
Phileas, it was so enlightening
Everybody, come with me!
You'd better put this on
Perhaps I should wear
women's clothing more often
We should run
Now?
Yes, we should run
Break down the door!
Okay
Not on my brains!
Give me that Jade Budd-air!
Okay. What's a Budd-air?
Get ready to jump! Now!
It is him! The Englishman who
robbed the Bank of England!
He's escaping in that
palki-gharrie!
They'll check all
trains heading east
Even if we make it to the coast
we can't sail into Singapore...
or even Hong Kong
They're both British colonies
Does England own everything in Asia?
Not China. Not yet
You look troubled
I cannot keep lying to Mr. Fogg
You did what you had to
The fate of your village
is of far greater...
importance than any bet
Phileas has made
If he loses, all it will cost
him is some money and pride
No. Mr. Fogg will lose
much more than that
What do you mean?
My village!
Your village?
I mean... "My, what a village!"
It's beautiful!