We are closed.
Just a small drink.
The toilets?
A quick drink
and then l'll leave.
Why are you rushing off?
l said, ''Why are you rushing off?''
l don't understand.
The man from Bristol called ya.
- What man?
- The man in the wheelchair.
What were you doing back here?
Lady, l never walk into a place
l don't know how to walk out of.
Then why get into that van?
You know the reason.
Make yourselves at home.
You've come a long way.
- Thanks for comin'.
- What's the job?
There are some people
who have something we require.
- And we want you to get it from them.
- Does it involve shooting?
You must be tired.
We'll tell you more tomorrow.
- Seven fat years and seven lean years.
- That's what it says in the Bible.
You ever kill anybody?
l hurt somebody's feelings once.
Don't l know you?
l don't think so.
l'd remember.
Two hour shifts.
- l'll watch the front, you the back.
- For later.
Merci.
You awake then?
How we doin'?
You labor or management?
lf l was management,
l wouldn't have given you cigarette.
l am the tour guide.
Over there is the Eiffel Tower.
Over here the Louvre.
Over there les toilettes.
- What do l call you?
- My name is Vincent.
Sam.
As per the agreement,
your salary will be $5,000 a week...
with a minimum
of four weeks' work.
On the successful completion
of the mission...
you will each receive
a bonus of $20,000.
And by the way,
my name is Dierdre.
-The broad outlines of the mission are--
-Who are your principals?
For you, no one but myself.
And what can we infer
from your charming lrish lilt?
Anything you like.
Where's the equipment?
Make a list
and give it to Vincent.
- The equipment is quite technical.
- lf it's in Paris, l'll find it.
This is what we're after.
We need to take it intact from several
men who'll be intent on preventing us.
- How many men?
- You American?
The group would be quite small. Between
five and eight. No more than eight.
You don't know for sure?
l don't know now,
but l will before the event.
lf you don't know,
why do you say between five and eight?
There's two to three cars.
The group's travelin'.
- They're not in Paris?
- Where are they?
- You'll find out soon enough.
- What's in the case?
Our plan, in the broad strokes,
is an ambush.
lt's to hit the car,
to take them in transit.
Transit? City, country?
Right now l don't know.
But we've to move very quickly.
We've to improvise.
We'll start with this: ambush
and assault on two to three vehicles...
five to eight men, and our objective is
the safe retrieval of this case.
Tell Vincent what it is you'll need.
What do we know about them?
Are they French?
Where are they from? Who are they?
All you need to know right now
is that they're very unpleasant.
You've done
this kind of thing before?
- How difficult can it be?
- No idea how these men will be armed?
They'll be very well armed, indeed.
Where are we going
and how do we get back?
lt'll be in France, and the group
will disband at the RV point.
- What does she mean?
- After that, we're on our own.
- lt's a military term.
- That's right.
Larry, tell Vincent
what you'll need.
Something very fast.
Audi S-8.
Something that can shove
a little bit.
l'm going to have it
for you by afternoon.
l'm also gonna need a nitrous system.
l've got the specs.
What do you use, weapons-wise?
Weapons. l'm a-- l'm a weapons man.
Weapons man?
- Yeah.
- Great.
They tend to settle the argument.
So what do you favor?
lt's a toolbox. l don't care.
- You put the tools in for the job.
- What?
You know, l actually
favor the old 1911.
Forty-five? Old gun.
lt served my country well.
A long time.
Your country. Not done too well,
though, last few wars?
Perhaps not, but at least
we don't go around whining about it.
- You ex military?
- l got my job through the ''Times.''
Don't let him get you down.
lt don't mean nothin'.
l say what l think.
You ex military?
Hereford?
l'd like to do it backwards.
The line of retreat is?
She just told you.
We meet back at the RV, disband.
l understand. l'm just trying
to get a vague notion of the opposition.
l mean, we're setting out to cause
some animosity over here, and l--
- How many are coming after us?
- You worried about your own skin?
Yeah, l am.
lt covers my body.
All your concerns will be addressed
before we leave.
- Electronics and commo.
- Not more than three cars?
That is our information.
- Can you get me a simulator?
- What's a simulator?
Gunpowder. Sound only, no lead.
Sounds like a pistol, an assault rifle.
Quite diverting.
l'll need bigger injection jets. The
Bosch won't do it. Must be custom made.
We going north or south?
l'd like some new clothes.
- Vincent will sort you out.
- l'll take care of it.
- What brought you here?
- A fellow that doesn't work so well.
The man in the wheelchair?
- How did he get there?
- That was in your neck of the woods...
back in the late unpleasantness.
Good reflexes.
Yeah.
They die hard.
- lnterrogation.
- What?
Methods to withstand interrogation.
You've done that?
We were taught
to hold out indefinitely.
Nobody can.
- ls that so?
- Yeah. Everybody has a limit.
l spent some time
in interrogation once.
- They make it hard?
- They don't make it easy.
Yeah, it was unpleasant.
l held out as long as l could.
All the stuff they tried.
You just can't hold out forever.
- lmpossible.
- How'd they finally get to you?
- They gave me a grasshopper.
- What's a grasshopper?
Let's see. That's two part gin, two part
brandy, one part creme de menthe and--
Fuckin' smart-ass.
- Can you find this place?
- Of course.
l know it.
That's where
they wanna do the exchange.
You're gonna exchange
for cash?
- Aye.
- You know these people?
My people know them.
Your people have done business
with them before...
or they just gave
your people a number?
lf we're gonna do it,
let's do the goddamn thing right.
l'm busy.
Come on. Let's go.
The answers to your questions
l'll know when l get back.
- l'll go with you.
- Go with them.
Who's this girl work for?
She works for our ''betters.''
Seems that's what we're meant to know.
Always a waiting game.
- What?
- lt's a waiting game.
Would you not do that, please?
Bad for the night vision, yeah?
There they are.
- You have the list?
- Yes, l have it.
Give it to me.
Money?
You follow my lead.
Just make sure you watch my back.
Don't make any sudden moves.
Just because we're buying guns
doesn't mean we didn't bring any.
Don't worry.
Everything's fine.
Want to back him up?
What would l profit
from your death?
- You'd have the money.
- l have the money already.
l'll watch the back.
Have you got it all?
- You're sure?
- Of course. Come and see.
There it is.
lt's not all here.
What?
He said the rest is in the other car.
The boss wants to check the money.
lf he agrees, we have no problem.
Here, take the car keys.
Go on. Take them.
There you are. No problem.
Come along. Come on.
Give me some money.
- You aren't going in there?
- Yeah, l'm going in there. So are you.
- Why am l going in there?
- To protect me.
There is no protection there.
lf it's a come-on, we're fish in
a barrel. Why do they want you in there?
- What are you, crazy?
- You think too hard.
Nobody ever told me that before,
but l wouldn't go in there.
- What is it?
- l don't like it. Look at it.
Let's just do it.
Let's just do it and be done, yeah?
Don't go in.
l'm getting paid to go.
lt's that simple.
Let's go.
lf anything goes down,
get next to one of those guys.
lf there's a sniper,
he'll be afraid to shoot his own guy.
- Let's go.
- All right.
Stop!
Stay where you are.
So, everything's fine.
l can't see!
Have some of this!
Fuckin' arsehole!
Fuckin' have some more, bastards!
Come on!
- Let's go!
- You goddamn--
Come on! Let's go!
- Anybody hurt?
- We're fine.
Wow. Almost a bit of raspberry jam
back there, yeah?
A bit of raspberry jam back there.
Got the swag, kept the money.
Job well done.
That's a fact.
That is a fact.
Slow down.
l think l have to stop.
Thank you.
Why did you take this job?
My friend, l need the money.
The money is here.
That's what this is, money.
But who are our employers?
You're right.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, monsieur.
The Russians are trying
to bid for the case.
The case is in Nice. They're trying
to sell it to the Russians.
They're staying
at the Villa Belle Mer in Nice.
- The team isn't ready.
- Whatever the team is, you do it now.
The Russians have decided to bid.
We need to move now.
Excuse me.
l have the information.
We'll be moving very soon.
lt'll definitely be
in the nature of an ambush...
somewhere between here and here.
We'll anticipate a three-car convoy
with backup team.
Obviously we will try and stop
the target before they can get away.
- What's in the case?
- That isn't necessary.
ls it heavy, is it explosive, is it
chained to some unlucky bloke's wrist?
- Are we gonna have to chop it off?
- All right.
But l am not under any obligation
to let you know--
lf not,
the price has gotta go up.
l'll get you the case,
but the price has gotta go up.
lf it's gonna be amateur night,
l want $100,000. l want it up front.
l want it in a bank account. l want
another $100,000 when you get the case.
We've got shooters here,
shooters here.
l'll tell you an old trick.
- What's your problem?
- Draw it again.
Draw it again. You're the ace field man.
Draw it again.
lt's a simple diagram.
Just draw it again. Draw what you saw.
Draw it again!
Two shooters.
Car comes through here.
Shooters across from each other,
kill each other dead.
Oh, my. Where'd you learn that?
- ln the regiment.
- What regiment was that?
The 22nd Special Air Service.
What's the color
of the boathouse at Hereford?
- l don't like your attitude.
- What's the color of the boathouse--
- Fuck off!
- What's-- You got the gun.
l'm unarmed. Do something.
Go ahead. Do something.
Tell me about an ambush.
l ambushed you
with a cup of coffee.
You'll get your money
when we get the case.
The others too.
That is what l understood.
We've gotten the word. We're movin'.
Put this near the front.
Careful.
Careful with that.
So what color
is the boathouse at Hereford?
How should l know?
This'll complete your compensation.
Thanks for your time.
Feel free to leave when we're gone.
Do l need to suggest
you forget us?
Because we will not.
Morning.
l see you're reviewin' our problem.
You're part of the problem, part of
the solution or part of the landscape.
- lndeed.
- What's in the case?
Something we're payin' ya for.
- You and the girl are in front.
- The name's Dierdre.
Wait outside the hotel for the target.
He leaves the hotel for the villa,
the villa for the hotel.
He activates his cell phone. How do
you know he's gonna use his cell phone?
- He'll use a phone.
- How do you know?
l'm gonna call him on it.
- How do you know he'll have it?
- He's waitin' for a call?
The people he's doin' business with
will call him to arrange a meeting.
The villa. The hotel. The car.
The stoplight. Eight to ten guys.
How good is security?
- l can't tell you.
- Let's find out. Where are they?
The last report,
they were at the hotel.
- The case is at the hotel?
- We presume that it is.
- That's interesting.
- Why don't we do it now?
- lt's tempting.
- lt's a good plan.
Let's stick to the plan.
Everybody wants to go to the party.
- Nobody wants to stay and clean up.
- Please.
The only thing is that the map--
the map is not the territory.
Let's look at the ground. Bring some
money. We're gonna do a little shopping.
Loosen up.
You're my wife.
Be who you want to look like.
lt's just a game.
Just a game.
Man and a woman goin' for a walk
and all that entails.
Piece of cake. Relax.
Relax, darling.
You look good cleaned up.
That the hotel?
Put your arm under mine.
So why aren't they at the villa?
Why are they down here?
Fun and games,
pretty girls and beer?
Can l help you, sir?
We're just looking
at the menu.
Excuse me.
Do you speak English?
A little.
Could you take a picture
of me and my wife? lt's very easy.
- You press like that. Very easy.
- Sure.
Like that. That's it.
Focus like that.
We're gonna do it over here.
See.
- Could you get that palm tree in?
- Yeah.
We wanna show
we're on the Riviera.
Bye now.
- How many do you want?
- Just snap away.
Very--
Again.
Get the background.
Take a couple of my wife.
Just take a couple of my wife alone.
Take my luggage up
right away.
Thank you.
Can we take one picture of you
with my wife? One picture with you?
That's it.
So?
They're good.
A guy goes for the case, the other guy's
protectin' the principal.
Nobody panics.
They're good.
So what have we learned?
- Can it be done?
- lt can be done.
We should have two more men.
- We don't have two more men.
- Go to your handler.
- There is no handler.
- Let me go.
There's no handler.
There's only me.
You want this thing, you want the case,
we're gonna need some more men.
There's no more help.
There's no more men. Are you afraid?
'Course l'm afraid. You think
l'm reluctant because l'm happy?
We've made a good plan,
and we're gonna stick with it.
What do we do?
We wait.
So who are they?
Our employers.
lt's me.
They've gone back
to the villa.
- Did they have the case with them?
- They did.
- Did you get the other cars?
- Got 'em.
- And how do they run?
- They'll do fine.
What does that mean?
lt would be nice to do something.
We are doing something.
We're sitting here waiting.
lt's not gonna happen today.
The buyers are out of town.
Tomorrow at the earliest.
The hell with it.
Let's go put 'em to bed.
- We've got the report.
- l take the report if that's all.
l can go and see for myself.
They at the villa?
l'm gonna take one last run over
the route and tuck 'em in.
l'll come with ya.
So how'd you get started
in this business?
A wealthy scoundrel
seduced and betrayed me.
Same with me. How 'bout that?
Take out the map.
lf anybody looks, we're--
So who are those guys inside?
You tell me.
Ex military, Northern,
Sov Block, somebody or other.
They need a job.
That's my excuse.
ls it?
Cops.
System activated.
System check.
Repeat system check.
There he is. He's being good.
He's activated his phone.
l'm in position.
They're passin' me now.
Target is on the way.
Hell of a time to be workin'.
What do you want for Christmas?
My two front teeth.
May your wish be granted.
Target is 400 meters
from the traffic light.
Come on! Come on!
So far, so good.
Target on the right road.
Escort car...
four tenths of a click
in front of you.
Got it.
You should see them in four seconds.
Two cars.
l got 'em.
Target has escaped.
l repeat: Target has gotten away.
Target heading for Vieux Nice.
Through the market,
then straight.
Right at the fork, Marechal fork.
Okay, you're in front of him.
You can cut him off
at the end of the port.
Roger that. l got it.
He's coming from the right.
He's yours.
- l'm hit! Take the case!
- Up the other way!
Get the fuckin' case!
- Get the car. We'll meet you up there.
- Take it.
All right.
Get out of here!
We'll see you at the safe house!
Give me the case!
Where's Gregor?
Gregor fucked us.
- How is it down there?
- A lot of heat. How you feeling?
Okay. Thanks for before.
Don't mention it.
Could you clean
the paint off this?
Got a pack of Camels?
No, you smoke too much.
We must get out of here.
l'm gonna need your people
to help us.
- And l need you to find the case.
- All right, call your guy.
When we bring in the case,
he'll help you.
- How can l bring in the case?
- Gregor has it.
- Why?
- l presume to sell it to the Russians.
Why the Russians?
Why not you?
lf we had money to buy it, we wouldn't
have hired you to steal it, would we?
Go to your people.
Talk to them.
You want the case?
We find Gregor, we find the case.
How do we find Gregor?
How did you find him to hire him?
Through your friend the cripple who
gave me nothing but a bunch of lames!
- You, Spence and the sorry lot of you!
- Hey, hey.
We can find him
through his cell phone.
Can we trace his cell phone?
They can triangulate it,
if we had that equipment.
Who has that equipment?
Tell me.
Who has it?
All right. Give me the number
to his phone.
How does the day find you?
How do they say in French--
en plein forme?
This was supposed to be
a social occasion?
- Life is uncertain.
- lt is indeed.
But, Gregor, we have
so much history together...
l was sure you wouldn't mind.
- Besides, the world these days is so--
- Unsafe?
Exactly.
l'll show you how unsafe it is.
See that little girl down there?
Have you lost your mind?
Why did you do that?
To make a point.
l don't know her, but l was ready
to splatter her brains all over.
But you,
l don't particularly like you.
Just imagine what l'll do to you if you
try anything. Now give me my money.
Put down the gun.
- l never liked you either, Gregor.
- Where did that come from?
l should have made you strip.
- Now where's my package?
- Right behind you.
Clever girl.
- You liked it?
- My little sun.
You make me so happy.
My sweet love.
Excuse me.
ls it done?
lt's done, Mikhi.
Gregor? ls that you, Gregor?
Much to your disappointment.
lt was a mistake.
lt should not have happened.
lf it happens again,
l'll sell it to the lrish.
- Don't do that.
- Then don't make me.
My price just went up 300%.
l want the package.
What do l have to do to get it?
Just wait for my next phone call. l'll
find a place where l have the advantage.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Could you tell me
how to find a post office?
Do l know you?
l'm sorry. Do l know you,
'cause how did you know l speak English?
You got an English newspaper.
Sorry. l'm sorry.
l beg your pardon.
lt's all right.
What do you need a post office for?
- Over here, they use them differently.
- l need your help.
- l thought you left.
- l did leave.
- You did leave? You're out?
- That's right.
Can you help me? l need your help.
What's the number?
The post office is
down to your left.
Up on the left? Thanks.
- A friend of yours?
- We went to high school together.
Everyone's your brother
until the rent's due.
Ain't that the truth?
On the terrace?
Facing me?
l see him.
Yes, l'll get him.
Hang on, please.
Excuse me, sir.
Are you Sam?
A phone call for you.
Good to see you too.
lf his position changes,
l'll let you know.
Gregor's in a town called Arles.
He's at the Arena.
This is the amphithιβtre of Arles...
which was built at the end
of the first century A.D.
lt was built with limestone.
l know those men.
You can see the dominant yellow color
which is caused by a lantern.
We're not sure the walls
were actually yellow.
So now, we will continue and visit
the Roman baths down this way.
Thank you, gentlemen.
That'll do nicely.
lt's Sergei. l remember you.
Yes, Gregor, it's me.
- How have you been?
- Well.
These are trying times. l'm sorry
about the unfortunate incident.
lt was excessive.
And more to the point, it was foolish.
l couldn't agree with you more.
Mikhi did it without consulting me.
He's turned rogue
and can't be controlled?
l don't--
Oh, English. Sorry.
Such a fool.
l was looking
for van Gogh's old house.
What could have been conducted
in a collegial atmosphere...
is now fucked into a cocked hat.
What do you think?
l'll think we'll meet your price.
So let's see it now.
Where do you have it, in your belt?
- Let's see it.
- Show me the case first.
You're great in the locker room, but
you're weak when you put your spikes on.
- Are you all right?
- Gregor's fine.
But l think you're in
a wee spot of trouble.
Where is it? Where is it?
- l don't have it with me.
- Where?
l mailed it to myself.
Post office box in Paris.
Help! He's robbing me!
Stop.
- Where do l know you from?
- Vienna.
Of course.
- Sorry to have to do this.
- Hey!
- Christ.
- Drive.
Stop! Piss off.
l'm gonna have to
take care of this.
What do you want to do?
Get to a doctor
or a veterinarian's office.
l'll just boost what l need.
- Could you do that?
- Of course. l can do better.
- How is it?
- l'm leaking.
l'm sorry.
That girl sold us out.
She sold us out.
- ls everything ready, Jean-Pierre?
- Yes, everything.
Get my legs.
Careful.
Sure you can do this?
Yeah. l once removed a guy's
appendix with a grapefruit spoon.
- Have a drink.
- No booze.
Easy, easy, easy.
Yeah. lt's just below the surface.
All right, let's do it.
Just douse it with alcohol.
Take the gauze and wipe away the blood.
Keep it clean so l can see it.
What we're gonna do is routine.
l've done this many times before.
There are no vital organs or arteries.
lt's okay. You won't kill me.
Just make sure you get the bullet
before you pry it out.
Take that scalpel.
The upper part.
Over here. Just cut up there.
Just a little cut.
Got it.
Now take the clamp.
Take the clamp
and open up the hole.
Just put it in there.
Put it in there.
That's it. Put it in.
Now open it up. Spread it.
Now get the other clamps
and get the bullet.
Don't take it out
unless you really got it.
Do it again. Do it again.
Just try with--
When he pulls it out, put the gauze in.
There's gonna be a lot of blood.
Put the gauze there.
Fucker sprayed his bullet
with Teflon.
He was trying to stamp me.
Paid in full.
ls that why it went
through the vest?
Can you stitch me up
on your own?
lf you don't mind,
l'm gonna pass out.
You gonna kill me?
No.
l'm not gonna kill you.
Why would l want to kill you?
- l gave you a job.
- l did my job.
- So how'd it go wrong?
- l thought you wanted the case.
Oh, we'll get the case. Huh?
We'll get the case, eh, Gregor?
Don't you worry about the case.
l want an explanation.
An explanation? For what?
- You bollixed it up.
- l did?
- You hired him.
- Through your fucking contact!
- You didn't do your homework.
- Why did you have to kill Larry?
Larry, is it?
l was clearing up your mess.
My mess? Well, you take over then.
- Huh?
- But you can't, can you?
lt's you that's hiding, isn't it,
Seamus? You can't show your face.
Who else thinks that?
Who you been talking to?
That's why l'm doing this job.
You're a good girl, Deirdre.
Do your job.
He's tough, your Yank.
You're right about that.
But who is he?
That's not important.
Didn't he work for the ClA?
He used to.
Not anymore?
He's on the run.
You're sure?
l know what he can do.
l've seen him.
Why would he carve himself up
if he were still ClA?
He makes a phone call,
and it's taken care of.
And you?
How have you been?
We need some information.
We need to find
some people in Paris.
Who?
An lrish man and woman...
and a German, ex-KGB.
They're professionals.
And they're in hiding.
This is really important to you?
He saved my life.
l'll find them for you.
Where's the case?
lt'll come tomorrow,
l'm sure.
l'm sure it will too. Let's go.
Let's hope so,
for your sake anyway.
Are you feeling better?
Yeah, enough to move around.
Thanks.
My hobby.
One grows old.
A lot of friends of mine
just wanted to live to open a bar.
Had they lived,
would they have done it?
Then they were spared
their disillusion.
That's right.
Who were they,
friends of yours?
- l wouldn't hurt a friend.
- Was that my question?
That's right.
Well, who are you?
A fella like you,
trying to make it to retirement.
At the end of the day, we're likely to
be punished for our kindnesses.
Don't worry about me.
l won't hurt you.
The 47 ronin, do you know it?
Forty-seven samurai whose master
was betrayed and killed by another lord.
They became ronin,
masterless samurai...
disgraced by
another man's treachery.
For three years they plotted,
pretending to be thieves...
mercenaries, even madmen.
That l didn't have time to do.
Then they snuck into the castle
of their lord's betrayer and killed him.
Nice. l like that.
My kind of job.
There's something more.
All 47 of them
committed seppuku...
ritual suicide in the courtyard
of the castle.
Well, that l don't like so much.
But you understand it?
What do you mean?
The warrior code--
The delight in the battle.
You understand that, yes?
But also something more.
You understand there is something
outside yourself that has to be served.
And when that need is gone...
when belief has died,
what are you?
A man without a master.
Right now l'm a man
without a paycheck.
The ronin could have hired
themselves to new masters.
They could have fought
for themselves.
But they chose honor.
They chose myth.
They chose wrong.
Seppu-- what?
Seppuku.
Disembowelment.
The sword goes in here.
- You sure this address is good?
- Jean-Pierre gave it to me.
Under the bridge by the river...
how did you know
it was an ambush?
When there is any doubt, there is
no doubt. First thing they teach you.
Who taught you?
l don't remember.
That's the second thing they teach you.
All good things come
to those who wait.
- Why is Gregor still alive?
- He's taking them to the package.
How you doing?
What are you?
What are you gonna do to me?
Let's just be calm
for one more moment.
One more moment.
Why? Why?
Oh, you know why.
No. You don't want to do that.
You can't.
Get back!
Get in the fucking car!
Why didn't you shoot her?
- Take the tunnel now!
- Oh, Christ!
Come on!
That fuck.
Where could he be?
The lrish and the Russians are looking
for him. So where does he go?
He goes to the Russians
to make the deal for the case.
Gregor ain't coming in unless
he can figure out a safe exchange.
He knows they'll kill him for the case
rather than pay him.
He's got to work it out soon
before the lrish find him.
Where does he go?
You go to what you know.
He's KGB. He goes to
one of his old safe houses.
No, they're all blown.
Where does he go?
You're on the run.
Where do you go?
Where has he been?
He made the fake case.
He had the fake case made.
Gregor.
He had it made.
He had to have had it made.
ln Paris, before we went to Nice.
He didn't have time
to have it made.
He bought something like it
and painted it.
Where did he get the paint?
He never left.
Where did he get the case?
lt's a case for ice skates.
Why ice skates?
And why would Gregor
know an ice skate case?
He didn't have time
to have it made.
to have the fake case made.
The Russians made it.
We're following the wrong people.
We don't have to find Gregor.
lf we find the Russians,
they will take us to him.
You've lived in Paris a long time.
You know the people.
l get around.
You meet the new Russians.
You know how it is.
Ex-spies. Now it's Mafia.
Under diplomatic cover.
KGB?
Ex-KGB.
Heavy hitters. Gamblers.
Lots of money. Big cars.
They live like Tsars,
throw money away.
Fur hats are expensive.
And bodyguards.
Expensive coats. Dr. Zhivago.
l have a lot of work. No time.
l understand.
All right. Let's go.
lt's going to be fine.
The guy is gonna reach out.
ls he any good?
Jean-Pierre says if it's Russian
and it's in Paris--
lf l wanted to find Russians
in Paris this week...
l would go to the ice show.
l'll trade you a favor
for a cigarette.
The favor is,
steer clear of those guys.
The Russians?
They sure throw money
around here.
The Russian is seeing this Natacha
Kirilova, the star of the ice show.
He spends every evening
in the audience.
- How'd you find that out?
- We went to high school together.
Mikhi, is everything
all right?
Everything is fine.
Sweet girl.
Go. Go on.
Ladies and gentlemen...
we are very proud to present...
two-time Olympic champion...
and three-time world champion...
Natacha Kirilova!
Let's go.
Wait out here.
Yes, he is.
Hello, Mikhi.
The meeting is not
until later tonight.
The meeting's now.
You have the money?
Well, you know, we were going back
to get it before the meet.
l don't think so.
You have the money?
l might have the money.
Where is the case?
No, you have to do it.
l couldn't live with myself.
l have the money.
We conclude this now
and part friends.
Where is the case?
l'd like to be paid now.
No doubt.
Now tell me the other part.
The other part?
l'm leaving.
l'm taking my fee
and l'm leaving.
l have a person with a rifle
in the stadium.
l've worked with her for years.
She never misses.
l will call.
l have to call within
45 seconds...
to say that l'm leaving.
And then in another ten minutes
to say l'm safe.
Should l be unable to call,
your friend will be shot.
Thirty seconds.
We have to see
somebody inside.
You can't pass
without badges.
Twenty seconds.
Ten seconds.
There were two of them.
They were looking for those guys.
Just a minute, sir.
l am a Chilean citizen,
as you can see from my passport.
Maman!
Stay with him.
Get out of here.
Get out of here!
Get out. Walk away. Walk away!
Go.
- l will if you will.
- Just go.
Come with me.
Forget about the case.
l didn't come for the case.
l came for your boss.
l came for Seamus.
l came for him.
Just get out of here.
l never left. Don't you see?
Get out of the way!
Get out of--
You can't pass this way.
lt's blocked.
l can take you in
or leave you here.
That's him with the case.
- Sir, over here, please.
- Wait, wait.
There are more back there!
All right. Stay where you are!
Don't move.
Shut your fuckin' mouth up!
Shut your mouth!
You stupid shite.
You're a dead man.
This is the BBC World Service.
lt was announced today
after almost 30 years...
of bloody and seemingly intractable
civil conflict in Northern lreland...
that a peace agreement
has been reached between...
the predominantly Protestant government
of that British-ruled enclave...
and the lrish resistance--
...have told CNN that it was the
apprehension and slaying in France...
of the lrish terrorist Seamus O'Rourke
by parties still unknown...
that contributed a stability,
largely allowing...
the negotiations to proceed
to their historic conclusion today.
O'Rourke had been denounced...
by the lRA,
the military wing of Sinn Fein...
as a rogue breakaway operative.
Then, good knowin' ya.
- l'm sorry?
- You said something.
l said she would not
be coming back here.
Yeah.
She would not
be coming back here, would she?
l can't even put my hand
in my pocket to pay the bill.
l'll get it.
l'll get the next one.
What was in the case?
l don't remember.
Lesson number two.
Keep in touch.
Let's go.
No questions. No answers.
That's the business we're in.
You accept it and move on.
Maybe that's lesson number three.